How are you doing? Good. Really, really good. I'm glad to hear it. This stream is going to be
bopping in the next minute or two. Tonight we're going to do Connect again, but we're going to be
focused. Laser focused. Horror games. We've got quite a selection. There are two. Blockjam,
blockjam! There are two of them, and one of them has really bad reviews, and the other one
has really good reviews. So we're going to do them both, because that's what we do here. We explore
the entire gaming atmosphere, and I've got an even better hair solution today. I'll show you
in just a second. Oh, and by the way, if you're good, I'm going to show you something remarkable
later. Only if you're good. Only if you're good. I got my coffee. I've got my large water.
I'm never going to be good. Well, you better be good. If that guy that said that is not good today,
it ain't happening. We're going to start with Rise of Nightmares. It's going to be a coin flip to
which one of these sucks, but I'm, I'm going to give it some time. I also lowered the, I lowered
the volume of the lights in the room too. I don't want it to be too loud in here. And yes, there are
some denominations. Sound is, it can be used as volume. That's a scientific term. It's DB.
Let's go. Why did it just spit it out? Get in there. So here comes Rise of Nightmares. We're
going to start off like this. You should see it right now. You should also see me. Uh oh,
they don't see me. Hold on. I gotta like fix this. It looks like I have a warped head. I promise I
don't have a warped head. I had to have some kind of solution. Oh, this is going to be up
a little higher. What the fuck is this doing? All right. No, no, no. The connect is moving.
The connect is moving on its own. Okay. Is that better? Extend your hand forward to start.
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta make sure this is in the right spot.
That looks all right. Is it too loud? Well, it's a horror game. It's supposed to be fucking loud.
You don't turn the volume down on a horror game. You turn it up. Today we're going to play as Dave.
All right. Will you? I'm going to recalibrate this thing. It's been a week. Great new saying.
Yes, please do. Is that one like holding your hand this way?
Wait, position check. You are, you are now in the optimal play area. Extend your arm forward to
begin. This is matched up. Should be. Did you hear it? Brightness. Adjust the brightness of
the triangle edge is visible, but the inner crest is not. I need, I need to be able to see. You know
what I mean? I don't know how people play horror games like this. Why would you ever turn it down
like this? You can't see shit. You can't even play the game. All right. We're going to go right there
because I can, I can see the outline. That's better. Hold on.
And oh, it feels good every time. New game. All right. Play from the very beginning. I'm going
to get ready because this is going to, this is going to scare my socks off. Wait, this is good.
The camera's on a good spot. Wait, I feel like I'm going to like send a fucking like birthday
greeting to grandma. Wait, hold on. Okay. Hey, grandma happy? No, a little lower. No mercy humane
or, or every time streamer says something that has any base in science at all. Anytime streamer
says something that you disagree with. Anytime a streamer says something that you didn't know
before, but now you know now. No mercy. Is no mercy. Okay. This the game of difficulty can be
changed. Yeah, that's fine. Let's go real quick. This one's for moving. This one's for grooving.
You know what I'm saying? That's dope. Don't even need it. Oh, he's going to spill it and
it's going to be hilarious. Oh Christ, he barked. He said something. Turn your shoulders left and
right to rotate the camera. What was this shit? When you extend and hold your arm out towards the
screen, the target pointer will be displayed. Interact with any object that has an interaction
icon. I don't speak French. Thank God it's you. I didn't think anyone else survived.
She's going to get like grab. When you extend and hold your arm out towards the screen,
the target pointer will be displayed. There's a pipe. I didn't even pick that up. By holding
your arms like you're boxing, you will do a fighting stance. You can attack by swinging
the weapon you're holding. Okay. Hit the chain. Hit the chain. It's a cut scene.
Chains holding door shut can be broken with a weapon. First hit. All right, now go on.
Try opening this door just like you would in real life.
How do you move? How do you walk? How do you walk? To move forward, place a foot out in front of you.
Your speed changes based on how
Why am I walking like that?
What the fuck is that? Stop doing that. I'm like the Warner Brothers frog. This is fucking odd.
All right, hold on. Walk? What the fuck? I can't move around. What? When you see an auto movement
icon displayed, hold up your right arm to move automatically. Yeah. Let's go. Automatically,
please. Again, there ain't no way I'm going to be able to do this. Somebody in here? Oh,
there is somebody in here. Open the door. All right, here we go. No. Can you get me back on
track, please? Thank you. Can you do that again? Just get me back on track. I would appreciate it.
Okay, thank you. Oh, you just hold it. You don't have to actually walk. You just slide your foot out.
You can't open that door. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I go this way. Wait, wait, there's a thing. Pull
it down. When the icon is displayed, you will need to perform a situational gesture. It's a pole.
Uh-oh. I'm glad they closed the doors behind them. While in fighting stance,
you don't want to make them focus. All right, that feels all right. Now what? How do I get
over there? I pull the lever. Oh, there's another guy right here. Who's next? Can I run? Or do I
just have to walk like this? Turning? You won't be able to turn while focusing. Remember to drop
both arms when you want to turn. Oh. Like waiting for your children. Got it. Open the door. That's
bullshit. All right. Let me tell you something. If you like are like a building contractor or
you're like an architect, handle is pulled. Plate is push. I don't know. How the fuck do we not
understand this? It's been like 60 years of this. What am I supposed to do in here? And sometimes
some buildings have half of them are push for plate and half of them are like push. They go
half and half. It's fucked up. Why am I in here? Just do it for me. But that went both ways.
That door is on like an axle. Do it for me. Hey, it's me. I got you. Now what? Are you going to
follow me? What are you saying? You're an autopilot. Big bits can't rule. Shit. I can't do it.
Oh, it's one of those monsters. Where did you go? Where did you go? How do you run?
It's blood. I don't like this. I don't like blood. Oh shit. Okay, I can do it.
Well, we both died. Now I'm going to be a reporter coming to investigate the scene, right?
The ice has already melted. It's so hot here. All right, that was a cool game. What's next?
This. For like the next seven to twelve hundred. I'm going to be a reporter. Come on. Notice how I
said seven to twelve hundred. That is seven with no digits after it. Oh shit, the walls. The train.
The world. Who's in your jacket? I take my eyes off of you for
why would you take it out of your pocket? I didn't mean you should start hiding it.
I hate sounding like a nagging wife, but I've been putting up with this for five years.
When do you grow up? Excuse you. But I can't with you at the bottom.
We don't typically listen to private conversations. I can't do this right now.
Kate, I'm sorry. I was just completely eavesdropping in front of you of your
private conversation. All right, let's go. I need to wake up. Head to the bathroom.
Bathroom. You don't want to pause menu, but okay. I am like drunk right now.
Where's that bathroom? Look at this one. It's going to go. Ready? One, two, three. Into the mirror.
What were you drinking? Did you have horns? Find Kate. Looks like your
sotsuwara wrote you a message. What did you do? What did you do? You did something. Help.
Where's the letter? Sorry, I got angry myself lately. Meet me in the dining room. Kate,
you used way too much paper for this. Now, the way to correct this would be to write it gigantically.
Like a second writer. I would not be as angry as I am now. Head to the dining car.
It's very difficult to navigate. All right. Wait, stop. Stop. Don't walk into the wall. I'm not moving.
Look out the window. Looks like it's going to rain. I guess the weather has a sense of humor.
Are you going to achieve it by looking out the fucking window?
God, they really tacked these on back in the 360 day. Remember this shit?
Oh yeah, this game has 120,000 achievements. Five points for shooting your first round.
Can I go? Can I pass this? Can I like go by? Excuse me. I'd like to pass. Can I like,
what do I have to do? Is this going to teach me how to like crouch? I actually have to. Are
you serious? Why wouldn't you just put your down to the leg? What's so funny over here? Hey. Hi,
guys. Yeah. I know this trick. They did this shit weekend at Bernie's. That guy's not real.
That guy's not alive. There's somebody up in the luggage cab. Are you on a phone? I'm just
rude. Oh, sorry. These old Soviet rail cars buck like shop shabonies. So who's this? I'll see you
around. I'm missing something, right? I'm missing something. That was like the oldest trick in the
book. That's the like I bumped into you and like my colleague came and like wrapped like something
that he backed back. What am I doing? What was I supposed to? I was supposed to find like the
dinner car. It's taking a lot more time than I thought it was going to take. Put it in there.
Oh, we got somebody in here. How are you? I'm a friendly bunch. Actually, I'm Canadian.
Fucking assholes. Appreciate. Oh, right this way, sir. Come on, tell me where to go. I must
see your ticket. I just dropped everything. I'm not going in there. You can't pass without your
ticket. Well, you just it's in there. Can you just like, can you go in there?
Can you like knock on the curtain to find your wife? What the fuck? That guy's waiting up there.
He's probably like, what the fuck's going on in here? This will help. Sir, did you get your ticket
yet? Shut up, man. This is cool. Which card should I? This card is your pass. This is very good.
You love your wife very much and she loves you. This is the present. All right, it's going to be
go on. Turn it. Fucking joker. This is your problem. Somewhere you have lost your way.
Next one's gonna be death. Don't worry. We still have future. Oh, my fucking god is the death card.
Did he get it? The alak, the alak is the ala was it the alchemist?
Somebody's giving like 60 fucking something.
If I like to religious give 69 something. Jesus. That's a lot. On top of the two plus hundred,
I think that you were responsible for already. Thank you. That is a shitload of subs. Oh,
yeah, sorry. I'm sorry. I just said there's something going on there. I had to do that real
quick. Always predict doom and gloom, but nothing comes of it. I mean, I just, I thought, I swear.
Dude, I'll give you 100 bucks if you eat that pen. All right, I can't even fucking look at it.
Let's go. How many cars are there? I probably shouldn't be holding like a hot coffee in my hand.
This is like a jump scare game. Right? Okay. This is the worst thing you could possibly do.
Did I ever tell you guys the idea that I wanted to do, but I never did it because I just I'm just
full of empty ideas. I wanted to play a horror game. This is back in the YouTube days. I want
to play a horror game and have various annoying things in my lap. Like I have to think of popcorn
that when I jump scare the popcorn goes up on me, get like a stand up mixer and be like making
fucking good cookies and batter and shit. And I've been another jump scare like, oh, the cookies and
batter went all over me. What am I doing here? Here's my ticket. Excuse me. I'm Canadian. Why
does this keep happening to me? Forward. No, go forward. Kate, Kate, where are you? Help. Help me.
I can't do it on my own. Is there blood? It's a lot on the train. Hold on. This is important.
I gotta get ready for this. Okay. I'm gonna go talk to security because you're just happening
back there. Can I do anything with this stuff? All right, I'll go in. Bartender joke. Anybody
need anything? All right, let's go in. Here we go. Scary horror game. I said I was going to play it
and I'm like, I'm pumped up. I'm hype. Oh shit. It's scorpion in the $12 skin. Get the fuck out
quick. That guy's got money. Get out of here. That's how tacked on these achievements are.
That achievement was just called the train. I didn't fucking do anything. The train. I got 10 points.
God, what about Kate?
Escaping from the train. It's right, I can get out right there.
Bleeding in blood. Where are you? Restricted. Restricted auto. There are some situations
when you won't be able to auto move. Okay. Where is this person? Oh, I found the exit.
Drop the jump. God, I really shouldn't be drunk doing this. I didn't think I was that drunk.
I knew it. Stay balanced? How is that not balanced? I was doing the pencil.
Do I have to put weight down on my right foot? Stay balanced.
Train. Okay, I gotta go left. Why can't I do auto movement? Okay, balance. Stay to the left.
Good. All right, let's go. Okay. Should I go try to get the secrets over here on the left?
There's no secret over here. This shit's gonna make me sick. All right, now where?
I'm good. I'm good. Stay, stay, stay, stay. Okay. Okay. He walked backwards off the train.
He walked backwards. I put my foot forward. You saw it. I walked fucking forward. Why can
you even walk backwards? Oh, no. I got Luigi. How do I run? The whole game that you're supposed
to go like put your foot forward to automatically move. Now I have to all of a sudden run?
All right. This is how you move the whole game. Now fucking sprint, dude. Hurry.
Hurry.
Achievement. Run for it. No. I'm just standing very close to the fire.
No. Why would you throw the phone? People always do that in fucking movies and TV shows.
What if it works? What if you get a signal over here? Like 100 feet that way.
In the middle of nowhere in a fucking cave. You relax.
Somebody's going to come for us. I mean at least I take pictures of shit on your phone.
Like document our trail so they can figure out like what happened.
And then once you document the whole trail throw it as fucking far as you can
and it'll get washed up with somebody going to decipher the photos and find you.
He thinks it's dangerous to go out there at night. I'm studying foreign languages.
Romanian is one of them. Great. Derailed into a cursed forest. This keeps getting better and better.
I thought that was the person in the fire.
I thought it was the person in the fire. I thought that guy was on fire.
Oh shit. I got too close. Let me lead the way. So we've got. We should stay together. The old man.
The train conductor. The badass. The college educated. The journalist. There's one more.
There's one more. What's the last one? I can't. I physically cannot see this. It's so blurry but
from back here. The funny guy. Wait is that me? Are we supposed to go over here?
I just felt something grab my.
Already. And then. Okay now we got some train conductor. We don't care apparently.
Nobody is upset about the fact that the train conductor just literally got sucked underneath.
A giant alligator. What? What? What? Get him off me. What's on me? I'm coming in leeches.
Oh no I can't do that right now.
All right if I just stood there. Would everybody have just gotten all their blood drain.
By the way you cannot slot off leeches. It doesn't work like that.
I sensed a presence behind me. Like I was being watched. But though I spun and looked often.
All that I could see was the perpetual gloom of the forest. But I'm certain of it.
Someone is next to go. I've been doing this long enough to know that I'm not just spooking myself.
I think this guy is next to go.
See he's first. No no no go forward. This bottle. I think there's someone up ahead.
Come on I'm always the last person. What did you guys see? Is there a person right here?
Oh it's the fortune teller. Okay.
I want somebody else to do their fortune. It's just a bunch of gold.
Oh it's the fortune card. It's the gold card. You're gonna make a lot of money.
They're like oh cool. They get on the fucking helicopter at the end and leave.
What the hell is going on? Is it a hub?
All right let's talk. Don't punch guy in head. I saw interact.
Well now that you made it seem like it. Now that you gave me an opportunity.
Like I kind of have to know. Shit traveling through Europe seemed like such a good idea.
You can't. You cannot. I know everybody wanted me to try so I did.
It's a fortune teller went down here. That's what I'm understanding right?
Just do it for me. I don't want to walk down this. Oh god did that one just move? What's in here?
Is a body in here? Who is this?
This is not working. Do I need a weapon or something?
I did it. All right so that doesn't count. That negates each other. Oh god just go.
How many times do I have to punch something in the face? Is there a dodge mechanic that I didn't see?
I'll handle this. This cannot be happening. Nice got it. All right anything else in here?
Health potion? Okay let's go. Here comes a jump scare. Here it comes. Just want to make sure.
Got it. Did you just lock me in here? What's wrong with you? Why would you do that?
Block attacks? How do you block? I'm just gonna go for it.
Even doing anything? Why is it still fighting?
I you get rid of the brain. You get rid of the head and it's gone. What?
Your brain is in their legs. I didn't even get the fucking knife.
No I'm getting out of this. I'm fucking winning this. No we're not next. We're not going to the next one.
I have to kill these three zombies. Okay here we go. Here we go. Let's do it. Get out here.
What armor for? Good. Go. Open the door. Out. Forward. Just go forward. Watch out. Watch out. They're gonna come up with us.
This is fucking ridiculous man. I'm just gonna. No. What? What?
Can I leave? Open the door quick. All right. Out. Out. Out. Out. We're good right?
Something's coming from behind me. What happened? Escape? Oh he's got acid.
How do I get out of here? Iron pipe? Give me that. Get the pipe. Okay good. Out. Just go. You kick your enemies.
What the fuck? No I'm getting out of this fucking cemetery. Not yet. Not yet. I gotta get out of
the cemetery first. Here we go. I'm getting out of here. What are you doing? Go forward. Why am I moving
backwards? I need that pipe. Man why is there so much acid? Go forward. I don't even care.
All right. I'm just gonna kill this thing. I'm not gonna do the tutorial kick.
Now focus on the person over that way. They're this way. Turn. What? Put your hands up. Watch out.
The chest. A bunch of chests. How do I open these? Oh shit. This is not good.
No. I have to get out of here. I have to get out of this. I have to.
Okay give me the pipe. I still am moving backwards for some dumb reason.
Hey shit. Hey shit. Shit. Get the machete. What? Hey shit. Get the machete. What do you mean? Hey shit.
Where's the machete? Hey shit. Get the machete. I don't see a machete. Hey shit.
Lower the difficulty. Just too late. I'm going for it. All right. I can do it. All right. I'm gonna make
it. This is where we go. Fight. Just kill them. Hands up. Why are you backing up?
Go. Hey shit. Hey shit. Where is it? Is it over here? I don't see a machete. What's that?
Iron pipe. I got two pipes now. Can I do both hands? Let's go. All right. This is where I died
last time. Hey shit. What's going on?
There is some fatigue in this.
It just suddenly came back to life.
Where the fuck is it? Man.
I didn't kill this guy. Get rid of the arm.
It's enough to order to make me forget about this job.
Yes. Cut its handle.
Did I win? Oh my god. Oh my god. What the fuck?
Let's go.
Still. Where is he? Where is my weapon? I can't see. Knife arm. Get it.
Can I please be done with this? Oh, thank God. No. Jesus. Okay, that was
That was fucking brutal.
He's doing a lot of good Arnold noises there.
He looks like a fucking jester.
Oh, shia!
Uh-oh, it's the mad doctor.
That guy had pretty weak arms.
That was like, he was doing like a little tap.
What is this for, right?
They always have like the crazy,
fucking butcher doctor psycho in all these things.
What are you doing this for?
That wasn't an experiment.
He just put an ax in that person's head.
That was not like, oh, and I'm doing a test
on the globulation of human skulls.
He was always fucked up using the background.
Why can't it be like, like a top 10 song?
He waves first.
Wait, instead of waving, just get it done.
Like, oh, hey, I'm about to say,
just remember me, right?
I'm the fucking old guy.
Wait, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop,
put it down, put it down.
I wanna go back in there.
Probably like an item.
Watch out.
Is there like a saw or an ax or something?
You gotta have something in here, right?
Nothing?
God damn it.
Take the hand.
What do you mean take the hand?
I can't take the fucking hand.
I'm very indecisive, old man, I'm sorry.
You can't, you can't, guys, you can't.
All right, where to now?
Let's let the game tell us.
Monsters in here?
Does he have a weapon?
I'm all right, I'll be fine.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Let me help you down.
Was this person just saying that?
Put it down.
All right, I just, I activate something.
Ah!
Oops.
He's trying to save me, man.
I'm just trying to save you.
I'm surprised that you can actually do that.
No, no, don't go back in this room.
I don't need to be in there, no.
I want the old man to go in there first.
No weapons, just go.
Okay, what if I don't?
Is it safe to go over there?
I can't, okay.
So what do I do now?
There's a key around his neck.
Key's a key.
Reach for the key.
I got the key.
Key for unlocking a closed door.
No shit.
All right.
All right, I hear another, another person.
Device over here.
What's this do?
Should I go through the hole?
There is a hole right there.
No, can't even go through it.
A lot of walking.
There's gonna be something in here.
There's gonna be another person in here.
Downstairs?
This is a giant hallway.
Could be another survivor.
Jesus.
I didn't even get to you.
I'm dying.
I didn't even get to fucking have it.
One minute with any NPCs.
Every single NPC is gone in less than a minute or two.
I wanna get close enough to feel the fucking wind on my face.
Oh, that's close.
The tip of my nose is gone.
Really?
There's a lot of ways you can die in this game.
All right, survival lab, let's go.
Oh, do I get to fight the doctor?
I probably am.
I get to fight.
This is the worst part about this game.
It's the actual fighting.
Everything else is like kind of cool,
but the fighting is the worst.
Pick the flasher, my quarry.
A scholar hailing from Ingolstadt.
An authority in medicine, science, philosophy,
history, and more besides.
The purportedly brilliant man vanished without warning,
according to my client.
How many screens?
I'm curiously attracted to my neighbor,
who, while not related to me,
feels to her urgent need to have information.
But sympathy serves no purpose to an investigator.
It only clouds judgment.
Besides, she played generously in advance.
Investigate yourself in the middle.
Can I reach?
Turn this way.
What's that?
Schloss, schloes, scalpel.
A surgical scalpel to be hurled at enemies.
It's throwing knives?
All right, easy.
Straight down here.
What's the rhyme or reason to this?
Can I just throw them at their heads or something?
This is, I love these.
You don't even have to fight anything, it's great.
I just gotta get to the first boss.
When I get to the first boss, we'll go to the next one.
But I gotta get to the first boss.
Put your hands up, put your hands up, put your hands up.
Put your hands up.
I don't know why you're not putting them up.
Who the fuck is she?
God damn it.
Okay, download the hatch.
Why, I, yeah, it's them, yeah.
First boss is gonna be the doctor.
I'm gonna kill the doctor.
Spitter on the right.
Who made this game?
What company did this?
You can't ask that question.
One shot, good.
Who's next?
There's somebody behind me.
Somebody's in a fucking stall.
What?
The smell.
Go into the, you flush the toilet?
Ugh.
What, pick up?
Why'd I put my hands in here?
Oh!
I'm glad I tried to look in here
because there's no way I would've ever gone over there.
I would have never in a million years ever opened that.
And I would've freaked out,
I would've been like, this game's fucking stupid.
I mean, the game is, this game is fucking,
this game is stupid.
But I would've been like even worse than that.
It's not bad though.
It really isn't.
It's not the worst game I've ever played.
I mean, it's up there, the top like,
probably top like 50 worst games I've ever played.
But it's not the top 10 worst games I've ever played.
Being in the top like 50 worst game ever
means you're like, probably like a,
I don't know, like a five and a half, six.
No, that's not even fair.
I wouldn't put this in the top 50 worst games ever.
I'd put this in like the top.
I'm gonna be, oh, all right.
I'm gonna be quiet.
There's no way I'm gonna get through this.
Oh my God, just die.
Okay.
So,
three, two, go cross.
Oh my God!
Focus, focus on this, focus!
Focus before he spits you!
Oh my God.
What?
No, go forward.
All right, who's next?
Is that it?
Okay.
Let's go.
Saw, saw, saw, saw.
No, I'm not just gonna get hit by the saw.
All right, I've made it through already.
I can't get killed by every single trap in the whole game.
Okay?
We gotta put our foot down somewhere.
Fuck, not good.
Just punch him in the chest.
All right, go.
Nobody else down here, no?
Good.
Up.
Wait, what is that?
What's that thing?
Is someone trying to get my attention?
Is there somebody standing right here?
Did you throw that all the way from down there?
Holy shit, man, that's pretty impressive.
Get the knife!
Shit.
Wait, hold on.
Are you going over there to fight the guy
that just spit at you?
Kill that one in the middle.
I gotta get rid of that.
Where's the knife?
Oh damn it!
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
No, what are you doing?
Stop!
What am I doing?
I'm not doing this.
I'm not doing this at all.
He just helped me get through.
Thank you, sir.
Open the door, open the door.
Ready to keep?
Okay, no, that was me.
Looks like this door needs power.
I need to turn the power on, of course I do.
There's gotta be something in here I can use.
In this little office area.
Knife or a board or a plank or a something.
A piece of wood.
A two by four.
Or a, what the hell is in here?
Have I been down here?
I'm just checking them.
Volatile test tube.
They're gonna come alive.
I gotta get something in this room right now.
Okay, filled with unstable chemicals.
What's that?
Test tube?
Okay, I've got like a explosion or something.
Not bad.
What are you saying, what are you saying?
Hey, shit.
Tape, tape, you don't need to listen to the tape.
That's not a problem.
I can turn the power on
and then get back up there and open that door
and then throw acid and the doctor's fix it.
Hold on.
More test tubes, gimme them.
21.
Here's the generator.
So this is where this game's gonna become stupid
because I'm gonna turn the generator on
and then 20 enemies are gonna spawn.
Get ready for that.
Okay, power's up and running.
Maybe that door upstairs is open now.
Yeah, of course.
Another electrify.
I can phase it, I just electrified it.
What's that?
Steroid arms.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, gimme that.
I'm gonna wait for them to come down here.
Where is this other one?
No, no, no, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Don't stand in it.
Oh no.
I can't go that way.
No, I want the knife on me.
Stop moving.
Okay, I can't go that way.
Break your bones.
Move bones.
Can I fit in here?
Can I fucking kill this guy?
There are spikes behind me, by the way.
I don't wanna walk forward.
What the fuck?
Did he just spill on me?
God damn it.
I wanna go backwards.
There's something on the ground right here on my right.
Ah!
Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up.
Just scraping my back.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Step forward.
Forward.
I know they're behind me.
I'm trying to go forward.
Thank God.
I have to kill the first boss.
I refuse to go next until the first boss is dead.
Stop.
Back up.
Give me the thing on the ground right here.
Where is it?
Knife.
Oh my God, game.
Whoa.
All right, I want to pick up the thing on the ground.
Oh my God.
The millions of dollars that this took to make.
Pick it up now.
Okay, I'm good.
Let's go.
Enter the hole.
That's a spit guy, spit, spit, spit.
Okay.
Don't bump into that.
Don't bump, I'm fucking standing still.
Get me the fuck out of this place.
Seems to be closed off.
Chainsaw.
All right, I'm going to get the chainsaw.
Wait, what's that?
What is this thing?
This is the thing on the wall.
Can I do that?
No.
Where's the chainsaw?
What is that?
Bloody chainsaw?
Ooh, wow, you're not lying.
I thought that was a gas can.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think I heard something.
How do I turn it on?
This thing sucks.
Get me out of this.
Climb up.
Up.
Climb.
Okay.
Then we, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
What do I do?
I would love it if you would walk forward.
Oh shit.
No.
Okay, I got to be careful.
Okay, there's another one right here, right?
This is a, it's a, I knew it.
That's why I was waiting.
Okay, now this is where we turn it on
and we just drag it across the screen
and hit everybody here.
Okay?
That's what's gonna happen.
All right, are we aware of that?
We are?
Good.
There's so many people in this room.
How am I supposed to do this?
These guys have like electro-zapper things.
This guy ain't doing shit over here,
but he's freaking me out.
What?
Where?
What happened?
I think I have to run for it.
Straight for there, right?
I can't read what you guys are saying.
You're probably giving me some really good advice right now,
but I can't see it.
God damn it.
They're on like this interval.
I'm gonna have to just walk.
Hey!
Ah!
Get it, get it, get it, get it!
All right, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You see?
What's he doing?
Ah!
Why do I have to be so drunk?
All right, he's gonna kill me.
He's gonna kill me.
He's gonna kill me with that thing.
It hurts, it's still, I gotta move.
Oh my God.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Oh, this got in my eye.
I'm lying.
Here comes first boss.
Fish, am I gonna fish Comet?
The movement's fucked up because of,
what are you talking about?
Escape with your life.
What's that?
Vase.
Why would I wanna use this as a weapon?
All right, where's the doctor?
Let me smash this man's head.
Let me just sneak up behind the doctor
and bash him with this thing.
So those can explode.
Sure thing.
I'm just gonna walk by him.
Just get over there.
I'm just walking.
I don't even care.
There's no points, you don't level up.
Thing.
There's no level up system.
There's no way, who cares?
Just try to get around him.
There are points you do level up.
That's horseshit.
No, they aren't.
No, there are not.
What's that?
Somebody gonna eat in one of those things.
What are you doing?
This game kind of reminds me of
if House of the Dead fell down the stairs.
What is he talking about?
There you go.
He's gonna come out in one of these.
Oh no, watch out.
No, all right.
Well, no trope.
Let's go.
Here we go.
This is it.
This is the reason why I've been playing for this long.
Sorry.
It's you.
Thank God.
You're alive.
We've got to get out of here.
Let's get right back in the face.
All right, well, remember,
how long has she been on screen for?
One minute, two minutes?
We are at that threshold
where she's gonna get thrown off the bridge here.
The bad guy's gonna crawl up
and just put both of his hands like this
and just squirt your head.
Here we go.
The piano's gonna fall.
And like a snake.
Yeah.
Right through the chest.
Just like.
Quiet, don't move.
This guy's name isn't Ernest?
His name's fucking Ernest.
That's not scary.
That's not scary at all.
Oh, you're not pretty stupid.
Stupid.
Whoa.
Uh-oh, hold on.
Be careful.
He's gonna turn around.
Quick.
Take the phone.
Put your phone on silent.
Really?
Can I move?
I guess.
Where'd she go?
No, go this way.
I think you're gonna,
you went over here?
There you are, okay.
Fucking easy.
So what do we do now?
Knife?
I told you.
Hand.
I knew it!
Squish!
Not even two minutes.
Not even two minutes on screen.
Count it.
Give me that.
No, let him bite me.
Come on.
Fucking take it.
One more.
All right, all right, all right, I've had enough.
What's in there?
Just a bunch of gross shit.
That corpse is rather suspicious.
It sure is.
I should probably kill it now.
Looks like there's something inside.
Am I going, digging around in here?
I don't wanna do that.
Oh.
Yeah, well.
I guess it turns out you just had gas.
Huh.
Ancient key.
Key for unlocking a clip.
Somebody's next to me.
Somebody's around here, and I go.
Oh shit.
Hands not in the air.
This video game just got fucked up.
It's a top 50 worst game.
Happened on stream.
I'm gonna have a huge red mark on my head right here.
All right, here we go.
Yeah.
That corpse is rather suspicious.
Get in there, dig in there, get the key.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Looks like there's something inside.
I'm gonna take my hand out.
Pick up the key.
I'm sure I can probably spot him.
I'm not leaving until I do.
Ooh, what is that?
A meat hammer.
Nice.
All right, easy.
I don't want that vase.
I don't need it.
I got an ancient key to the ancient door.
No good.
Won't budge.
What is it, the valve?
Ancient door for the ancient key.
There it is.
Okay.
He's not actually gonna beat this whole game, is he?
No, I don't think he will.
I mean, sometimes he does that,
but I mean, this is just, I don't think even him,
I don't think he would even wanna do this.
It is connect carbonite, though,
so I don't be surprised if he does.
Yeah, I guess it's true.
I can't get up.
I gotta throw my back up going down that fast.
Ah, ah, oh, I can't.
I gotta go.
I don't have to start on the way back, do I?
Oh, give me a fucking break.
I don't wanna do this again.
I'm about to turn it off.
I am about to.
I'm fighting it.
I'm fighting the urge to turn it off.
That corpse is really suspicious.
Do it, do it, do it.
Oh, I want it so bad.
I button, like, hold on.
I want it so bad.
I want it.
Okay, no, I'm gonna do it.
I'm not gonna think about it.
I'm just gonna turn it off.
Last try, last attempt, this final attempt.
No matter what happens, if I lose again,
so I'm going on to the other one.
The other one's called punt.
Key, fight the people, walk down the hall,
open the door, here we go.
Turn, check it out.
Got my hands up already.
Go, let's go.
I'm done, I'm good.
I saw.
I want that, no I don't.
Just keep this, who cares?
Go, it's all the same item.
Every item is the same item.
Okay, here we go.
Same deal.
Get the fire poker.
I will take that.
That's an extra, like, zero percent damage.
Go, good, done.
Let's go.
Duck.
How long can I stay down?
Do I have to duck again?
Why am I going this way?
What are you doing?
Why is the auto thing going the other way?
All right, come on.
No more deaths.
I just have to kill the guy.
I just have to get rid of the guy
before the audience turns on me.
Did you go through the wall?
No, come on, come on.
I wanna finish this.
Don't do this.
It's just moving on its own now.
Okay, it's time to turn it off.
It's time to turn it off.
Well, it's not.
It's not time to turn it off yet.
All right, quick.
Go this way and touch the thing.
Did I already do this?
I don't even remember.
Did I turn the valve already?
Did I?
What do we got?
Yes.
Did I turn it already?
Need to run.
Okay, I did.
We're done with this.
Hey, hey, hey, you fucking idiot, got up.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm turning.
Don't ever buy this.
If you go like this,
yeah, you don't have your fucking hands up.
Yeah, sometimes it works,
but sometimes it just doesn't
if you don't stand there.
Go like this instead.
You're like, the other two guys will slash you.
Holy shit.
Shred it?
All right.
Fine.
Give me this fucking thing.
Let's shred it.
Let's shred this fucking thing.
What do you say?
Let's go.
Piece of shit.
Hey, what's this one?
Oh, Kung Fu.
Remember that game?
That was a lot of fun too.
Let me get it in there.
Fucking dumb thing.
Fucking crap.
Oh yeah, remember the Power Rangers game?
That game sure was fun, wasn't it?
Fucking piece of crap.
All these games suck.
Fuck the Kinect.
What's this one?
Stuntman Ignite.
No, that was a good one.
That was a fun game.
It's this one.
Oh yeah, remember the Petsch game?
Fucking dumb ass game.
Oh, my tie.
It got my tie.
Just like in the fucking Gremlins movie.
Oh shit.
Now we're gonna play Haunt.
Should be fun.
At least I hope it is.
And somebody just gave a fucking hundred bucks.
Oh no, no, no, Xbox.
No, Xbox, stop.
Xbox, stop it.
Cancel, cancel.
Okay.
It was AB Joe just gave a hundred bucks.
Thank you so much, AB Joe.
They say, hey, Yerma, good to see you up and about again.
I got your night sky t-shirt a while back
and I've had six strangers compliment the shirt so far.
Feels good, man.
You've always been there to help us all through the hard times.
Know that if you ever run into some rough times of your own,
know that we're all here for you.
Love you, man.
Keep up the good work.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
Sometimes I feel pretty down too.
I'm just like anybody else, right?
You got good days, you got bad days.
But I really appreciate that.
Thank you.
I'm not gonna shred the Kinect.
But seriously though, thank you so much.
We also had five community subs from Local Boomer.
Thank you, Local Boomer.
And then Phylactery gave 50 more fucking dollars.
Use this to buy some new legs.
Also, there's a machete and a tape down
in that tomb you left.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right, so this is called Haunt.
I'm gonna change the name of the game.
Is this even, I don't think this is even on Twitch.
I guess it is.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
Wait.
I'm not ready.
Haunt.
I think this one's a little more lighthearted
than the other one.
Is that right?
I don't know.
I think this one's supposed to be a better game.
Start game leaderboards helping off
with downloadable content.
Let's just go.
New game.
To ensure that Haunt functions correctly,
please ensure that the Xbox 360 Kinect sensor
and microphone are calibrated.
Would you like to?
No, I've already done this one.
I did this like fucking all day.
You can use either hand to control your flashlight.
If one arm gets tired, just change to the other.
So I get a flashlight in one hand.
Shred it.
I can't shred this one.
It's digital download only.
So it cannot be shredded.
As much as I would fucking love to.
I like a German.
Well, that was a copy pasta that I haven't seen in a while.
All right, let's go.
Avatar Award unlocked.
Hey, hey, hello down there.
Buddy, hey, hello.
Gamer picture?
Are you all right?
Can you hear me?
You're not dead, are you?
Pick up that flashlight if you're not dead.
Just reach out your arm and grab it.
What's a pick up flashlight?
I guess I got it.
Oh, wow.
You're not dead.
That's a nice surprise.
And now you can see where you're going, which is good.
To aim the flashlight,
move your arm just like you're holding a real flashlight.
Hey, can you test something for me?
There are some suits of armor around you.
Try turning towards them
and shining your flashlight at them.
Turn to left or right, look up and look down.
Okay, stop shining your light on that dirty thing.
Turn around and light up the suit of armor
on the other side of the corridor, will you?
Test failed.
Luckily, I was testing my maid, not you.
She's fired and you've passed.
Now, look at the painting at the end of the corridor.
Hey, who's that handsome fellow?
Why, it's me, Benjamin.
Surprise!
I mean, if you think Harry Potter is scary,
this could probably be in that same universe.
As you can see, I am stuck in this painting,
but the good news is I can possess any portrait in the house,
so I've got that going for me.
Still, I wish I could walk around freely like you can.
Hey, wait, you can still walk around, right?
He's doing monkey hats.
Turn around to the right, will you?
What is it?
To move in the direction you're facing,
simply walk on the spot.
That's so much more intuitive.
When you get to a corridor junction like this,
you need to choose which way to go.
But you still look a little groggy, so I'll choose for you.
Take the corridor on your left and then head upstairs.
Left.
When you're approaching corridor junction,
arrows like this will appear
to show you the available directions.
To choose which way to go
and your flashlight in the direction you want to take,
the arrows will change to show the selected direction.
Then just keep walking.
There's no need to stop while you decide.
If you'd rather move around freely,
you can turn assisted movement off
at any time in the settings page.
I ain't gonna do that.
Absolutely not.
We're gonna stay on aim assist.
All right?
You made it.
Welcome to my grand hall.
It's pretty grand, right?
I mean, under all the dust and stuff.
Let me take you.
What the fuck are you guys saying?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
I want a little tour.
I'll move to another painting
and you try to find me, okay?
Ooh, this is going to be fun.
Try to find the painting that Benjamin moved to.
This is kids' game?
I didn't look that up.
No, this is supposed to be good.
What painting?
I got you right here.
Great.
And now that I have selflessly gotten you back on your feet,
I ask nothing in return.
Save for one teensy-weensy favor.
Sounds fair, right?
Of course it does.
I'd do it myself if it weren't for this whole
stuck in a painting thing.
Said what?
Why don't you just take your not stuck in a painting
back through this door and we'll get going.
But I can't interact with the chat room.
All right.
Am I on my own yet?
That was a little scary.
I'm gonna go left or right.
I'll say left.
Now, you'll need to rummage through various objects
around the mansion.
See that chest on your left?
Pop it open and let's see what's in it.
I made the right call.
Okay.
Open it.
There's nothing in there.
Aha!
Look at that!
Vitality!
Sweet, delicious vitality.
There's vitality in there?
I bet you've never seen that before, have you?
I've got a bunch of it hidden around the place.
And you're gonna need it.
Not that this job is dangerous or anything, but-
Put my hand down.
If you do lose all your vitality, then well,
let's just say I can't be held responsible.
Let's keep moving.
Benjamin will often have useful interesting viz- viz-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're stuck or, no, I am not, I'm not,
I'm not a kid.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Gosh.
What the fuck are you talking about?
All right, this is where it gets scary, guys.
Turn the lights down on your house.
I don't want to listen to Benjamin.
Fine.
What do you have to say?
This next room has something really great in it.
Oh, was it something really dangerous?
I can't remember.
Either way, open the door,
because I'm dying to find out.
Doors work like any other objects.
Just hold the light on it and-
No!
Vitality.
What was that?
All right.
I'm gonna get full of vitality here.
Man, I am seeing some monkey-essence right now,
and I agree with you.
I completely agree.
Oh!
Don't be something in here.
No, it's vitality.
Good.
Was it a slug?
Extra vitality vial found.
What does that do?
Vitality vial.
Hey, you guys, you guys should come here and comment.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
You right back up again.
Good as new.
Let's get out of here before more ghosts show up.
Go through the door to the left of the painting.
All right, go to the door in the left of the painting.
It's time to start playing The Haunted House.
Brats, now where did I put that key?
Oh, there it is.
Collect the key and unlock the door.
What a specific item you needed to proceed.
An icon showing what's required will appear on the screen.
You need a key.
There it is.
Sure, I'll get it.
Focus.
Door key got.
Okay.
This is where it begins.
Uh-oh.
That could be me in some way.
That's me.
That's just, I feel like I look like that like every day.
Ho-ho, we are getting close, my friend.
I've got a feeling that this next room
has something very exciting in it.
Something I want very much.
I mean, something that we want.
The drawing room.
Uh-oh.
I have the boat.
Ghost, these guys are as mean as they are stupid.
This is what we just made.
This is Luigi's mansion.
Good.
Now's your chance.
Hit him with a counter-attack.
Now what?
I'm gonna punch him?
I'm gonna punch the ghost.
Yes, you got him in a daze.
Now hold your flashlight on him.
Brutes hate that.
Keep it steady.
This is like a horror game.
We only played one horror,
it's only one horror game for the Kinect.
And we played it.
He's dazed again.
Now hold your flashlight on him to finish him off.
Be done.
Good.
All right, I got him.
That was so simple.
Open the chest, get the reward.
And that's, I'm kind of regretting
turning off the other game.
Not yet, though.
Bingo!
Honest to goodness, Fanta Blast.
I've been looking for one of these forever.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Quick, let's get it back to the grand hall.
The fastest way, the longer corridor and up the stairs.
Let's get a move on.
Hut, hut, lift those knees.
Oh, let's get in here and see if the game's any good.
It is fairly intuitive.
Okay, all right, here comes the scary part.
Whoa, what happened there?
Almost there.
Through that door into the grand hall
and then head down to that door.
That was very scary.
This is going to be incredible.
Quick, go back, go back to Rise of Nightmares.
Quick!
Not yet.
What are these doors?
Vaults?
I can't read that.
I can't, I actually cannot read it.
Oh, have you guys been good, by the way?
Have you been good?
How good have you been?
Played in the dark?
Well, it's currently almost 6 p.m. here.
The sun's not down.
Have you been good?
I think you've been good.
This game sucks.
Don't say that yet.
We have to get out of the tutorial.
Hold on though.
If you've been good, I've got something to show you.
So what I'm about to show you guys
is something really exciting.
This is a sneak peek at one of the robots for the carnival
coming up in a few weeks.
So if you do not want to be spoiled,
close your eyes and block your ears.
Or just put me in a fucking tab or something.
So this is the official, official reveal
of one of the robots.
So why don't we take a look?
Pretty interesting stuff.
World premiere.
This is the robot that will be used for the dunk tank.
And if you think that looks cool, just wait.
Let's take a look at the side view.
We've got a good side view.
There will be more than one robot.
There will be more than two.
There will be more.
This ain't the only one.
Oh, and if you want to see a full,
kind of wide of how it all works, take a look at this.
This shit is the real fucking deal, guys.
And yes, the company is Andy Mark.
Awesome group of people.
Some of you probably already know who this company is.
Why don't we see how it works?
You will be in total control of this machine
in just about three weeks.
Up, down, left, right.
Oh yeah.
When is this stream?
It'll be the 21st of September.
And that ain't nothing.
You ain't seen anything yet.
But huge, huge, huge, huge, huge props to Andy Mark
because they're just as excited as I am
as probably a lot of you are now.
We'll talk way more about them at a later date.
But I just wanted to tease that.
Hey, let's not go back to being home like this.
It's gonna be fun.
September 21st, is that correct?
No, like this?
Cause it's mirrored.
No, now this game is like lame in comparison.
I want to do that well.
We're at like peak time.
But I'm so fucking excited.
You have no idea.
It's been a few months
of trying to get this all put together.
Lots of people involved.
It's gonna be fucking awesome.
Save the date.
All right, let's play the kids' game.
What's it doing?
Oh, I gotta find the ectoplasm, right?
Hurry, get the final phytoflask back to where it belongs.
Take it to the statue before...
These guys, anyone but these guys.
I'll stature you little creeps.
It's Beatback Sonic, except he's orange.
It's Garfield, Beanbag Sonic.
This slimy ghost fingers off my phytoflask.
Good day.
I'm so, so close.
Years of work wasted.
Now I'm back to square one.
Still, they haven't beaten me yet.
I have one of the four phytoflasks.
But of course, I still have one, right?
It really isn't.
It is just Luigi's mansion.
Now, first things first.
Let's get that phytoflask back to the statue.
It's all right.
It's fun.
It is.
Don't make me put in another one.
I'll put in Guy Fieri's minute to win it
if you don't fucking calm down.
See that coming?
To protect my last phytoflask.
I've got him.
Nice work.
Where's Dr. Regat?
You should talk that ghost a thing or two.
Oh, there he is.
Now let's get that phytoflask.
Get that phytoflask.
Yeah, thanks.
I appreciate the encouragement.
To the statue where it belongs.
I have to move.
I can't, I'm like turning to stone.
I just slammed that phytoflask down into the slot
and we're good to go.
Do I have to get three more of these to win?
Should I do it?
Well, we've got one phytoflask safe.
Now if we could just get the other three,
we've still got a chance.
Luckily, those stupid ghosts can't leave the boundaries
of my glaring designed mansion.
So tracking them down should be easy.
If we work together.
I think they went through those doors up on the balcony.
They all lead to different parts of my mansion.
We'll need to search them all,
but I'll let you pick which one we go through first.
Collaboration is the key to any successful partnership.
Now, get up those stairs and choose a door.
All right, this is where I get to choose a door.
This is where I'm gonna, this is important.
Check this shit out.
There is some exhilarating fucking gameplay.
All right, one, two, or three.
This one's got the solar system on it.
That's what I'm going to.
If I'm not wowed in 10 seconds,
I'm gonna put in Guy Fiori.
I talked a lot of shit.
Oh, they lit up the hallway.
It's, behold, my beautiful lubinarium.
Well, at least try to imagine my beautiful lubinarium
and what it would look like if.
Okay, usually it's chat that gets bored
and they're like doing Jupiters and talking to each other,
but I'm bored right now.
Like that's pretty rare.
That's pretty rare for the streamer to be bored.
It is.
I don't typically get bored of a game.
Like I'm bored.
I am.
All right, we're gonna go, we're gonna go straight.
All right, what's down this hall?
Anything in particular?
How about in here?
Open.
Okay.
Oh no.
Not another one of these.
Punch.
Why does it go twice?
If you had a son or a daughter,
that this would be fun, right?
What was that?
What's in there?
Something scary.
I hope it's not something scary.
I need slides.
All right, all right.
What's that?
The telephone?
Let's split the switch.
Nothing.
I'm gonna go in that door to the left.
Open it.
I can't open this fucking door.
Why not?
Where are these slides?
Okay.
What was that?
All right, we're gonna go right
because that's where I haven't been.
No, no, no.
Dumb game is dumb.
Dumb game.
Turn.
I wanna go this way.
That was pretty intense.
I'm gonna go right.
What was that?
Try this door.
Okay, easy.
This is the lunch room.
Let's examine some stuff.
I got full health.
Check each one of these.
What about that?
What's that sound?
Projector slide found.
Oh!
It doesn't even come up on camera.
I don't come fucking at it.
Poured water all over my eyes.
Let's try, wait, just try that again.
Ready?
It's fucking terrifying.
I don't recommend playing this game
because it's really fucking scary.
Am I actually about to type in the Guy Fieri?
Then there's no way no one's ever played this.
No one has played Guy Fieri.
Guy?
How do you spell Guy?
Oh, it's right here.
I'm wearing a hat.
This is a baseball hat.
What the fuck are you guys talking about?
No, I gotta wear it like this.
Why is it warped?
All right, there is no Guy Fieri.
I'm gonna have to just make it games and demos.
Guy Fieri doesn't fucking exist.
I don't even know how to play Minute to Win It.
How do you play?
In a minute, you have to win it.
Right.
I guess that makes sense.
This is not even on right.
All right, Guy Fieri, let's see what you got.
This might be the scariest fucking game all night.
I hope he's on camera.
Please be on camera.
Is this him singing?
Could be.
No, no, no, I don't care.
Fuck your error code.
There it is.
Just me.
It's just me.
All right, I don't know how to play Minute to Win It.
I've never seen this show.
Show one.
No, I don't know how to play Minute to Win It.
Let me just try easy.
I wonder the lyrics to this song.
Hold on.
No, I wanna hear the lyrics.
Let's go.
Everybody out on the floor.
Get up, get up.
Now, let's move.
Can you show me what you're gonna do?
Get up, get up.
Because the party don't stop.
I would rather just you have not have a theme song.
The party does stop.
The party does stop at 2 a.m. in most fucking cities.
That's when it's over.
That's when you have to go home.
Don't listen to this bullshit.
No, because the party don't stop.
Yes, it does.
You have to go home and go to bed at like 2.30.
What are we doing?
Guy Fieri, come on.
Fieri, and this is Minute to Win It.
This is these mind blowing games using household items.
Whoa.
It's a million people here.
Now, let's see if our next contestant
has the luck and skill to win a million.
Contestant.
Catch me.
What are they spraying on the audience?
60 seconds each.
Knock them all out and you'll walk away with be so easy.
So, we've given you three lives.
Challenge, you lose a life.
Lose all three and your game's over.
The bigger the money, the harder the challenge.
Remember, three banking levels.
Complete level one, you'll make a thousand bucks.
Baking levels?
Can you guys quiet down back there?
Let's take a look at your level one blueprint.
I don't have play.
We're dialing in.
Nervous Nellie.
The standard pedometer is engineered to count footsteps
while walking or running.
In this challenge, the contestant must strap
four of these counting devices to their arms and legs
and then let loose.
The player must accumulate the required number of clicks
in the time allotted.
Number of clicks?
Trigger your arm pedometers
by moving the correct arm.
Does this happen on the show?
Simply move your legs to activate the correct pedometers.
Failure to complete this task in 60 seconds
may result in elimination.
Okay, so I'm doing the amount of clicks.
The challenge.
You've got a minute to win.
Here we go.
A thousand dollars at stake.
The game begins in three, two, one.
Ha ha.
Maybe three seconds left.
Failed.
You have two lives remaining.
Win the challenge.
That was fucking impossible.
How the fuck can somebody do that?
Total clicks.
How many clicks in my left leg?
Five?
Why does this taste like blood?
I gotta do it again?
Are you ready?
You've got a minute to win it.
Good fuck.
All right, I gotta have a new strategy here.
The game begins in three, two, one.
What the fuck?
30 seconds left.
Ha ha.
Guys, this is, God, this is impossible.
Failed.
You have one life.
I'm sure you can beat this challenge.
It's not easy.
It's do or die on this one.
So now you know what to do.
You've got a minute to win it.
Shake your elbow.
That's what I was doing.
What about the leg?
The game begins in three, two, one.
30 seconds left.
Let's go.
$1,000.
That wasn't easy, but you finished the challenge.
Look at the money.
Oh, I got a long way to go, guy.
I think I'm gonna throw up.
I'm gonna throw up.
No matter what challenge I put in front of you,
you banged $1,000.
That's what it is.
Do you want to stay and play,
or do you wanna take the cash?
Guys, and no.
No, there's not somebody mowing the lawn out here.
There are no lawns. This is Las Vegas. I'm gonna stay
Go the distance
In this challenge a measuring tape will be used as a bridge to roll ping-pong balls into shot glasses
The contestant must deposit balls into the shot glasses at varying distances
Perform a steering wheel like motion with your hands to get the ball into the glass
Steering wheel the speed of the next ball will automatically increase after a successful roll
Failure to complete this task in 60 seconds may result in elimination
Do I get three more lives?
Did I use them all?
You complete the next challenge or you want life so now you got the low down on the showdown
You've got a minute to win it. Okay
How many points nine
That's pretty zoomed out. I can't see
Am I taking a shit ready for the next level is this all right stay stay stay stay
I'm gonna ruin this hat
I like this tattoo. It's gonna get a brown sweat ring in a circle here and I don't like that
I hate having hats like that
I don't know what i'm gonna do about it
extreme hanky panky
What began with a single box of 160 tissues has now evolved into a tissue typhoon in a test of dexterity
The contestant must empty two standard tissue boxes alternating between both the left and the right hand
Raise your corresponding hand to remove a tissue from the box remove tissues from your face by waving your hand in front of it
It
Failed to complete this task in 60 seconds may result in elimination. Let's go
This is your final chance. You have a minute to win it. You can do it. Are you ready? You've got a minute to win it
The game begins in three two one
What oh
With like a face hugger
Go go go
Five grand, all right close into a million no more mistakes
Why don't you have to pee on a show like this
Or stay and have some fun. What if I had to pee right now?
Gotta be like hey guy, I I gotta pee
Can I leave?
Go next door and help them out. I have to go film an ad
All right, I can do that
commercial
Follow the coach's movements
make 15 squats
without lowering the audience gauge
I actually do have to pee that i'm gonna piss my pants from this
I'm gonna pee
Look how strong I am
spectacular
Like me only from m power the m power mpl is made of a revolutionary new material that lets you lift weight without
Getting tired. You can improve your strength without getting stiff the next day. Our friend is raring to go
The strength and endurance has increased only after a few sessions orders the mpl and increase your strength with less effort
Is your level four
They just used me that was that was just free fucking work there
How's it hanging?
In this challenge the contestant must hang a banana from a string attached to their waist
Using the momentum generated by their hips the player must swing a banana to knock several oranges across the floor and into the hoop
They just knew like what were they thinking?
To move walk or run in place feel like this thrust your hips forward to swing the banana and hit the orange
Failure to complete this task in 60 seconds may result in elimination
That's hilarious
This is your last life now you can do it. You've got a minute to win it go get it
So what do I have to do I have to knock the game begins in
I have to get all of them two
one
It's in it's in it's in 30 seconds left
Last one get the fuck over there. I want to say 50 000
Try p no, I can't pick it on the game show
The choice to take the money and run or stay and have some fun
10 000 is not enough
Is your level blueprint
Actually, I can still hear it
I have my bluetooth headphones on I can still hear what the I can hear the explanation
A ping pong ball weighs one tenth of an ounce and has a diameter of approximately 1.5 inches in this challenge
The contestant must bounce the ball from the floor to the wall and catch it in a bucket attached to their head
Hold either hand out to the side to grab a ball
Perform an overhand throwing motion to throw
Move left or right by stepping in that direction
Move left right forward or back to catch a ball
Failure to complete this task in 60 seconds may result in elimination
Um
Fuck the mic was muted. All right. Hey, I heard it
lead left and right it was like
lead right and
Forward with the ball. I think I have an idea
Overhead throw step you gotta catch it, right?
All right. I got it. What's going on here?
You motherfucker, really?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I'm good. I have a pee stain
Well, that would be funny if that was true I can you come over to my house
Nah, I got I got a lot going on
I want to do minutes to win it again
No, that one sucks that one. All these games are so bad
I don't even want to play these ones because I know how shitty they're gonna be
You know when you just know I don't even need to put this in. I know it's gonna suck
I don't even need to play it
Where is my fucking thing that I want?
Zoo is my connect just broken might have to shred my fucking connect
Let's go don't stop now. Let the party fly through the course of the day
Just me i'm ready. Let's make it fucking hard
Check these out
Play
Nervous nelly
Ah, it's this one
The standard pedometer is engineered to count footsteps while walking or running in this challenge
Four of these counting devices to their arms and legs and then I know how to play I know how to play
The required number of clicks in the time allotted
Similarly move your legs to activate the correct
This is it
You got it. You've got a minute to win it. Good luck. How many do I have to do on hard?
I'll make sure my fucking my wig doesn't come off
350 no way
I'm pulling a muscle
Oh
Let's hit the music again
I can't do that. Well, when did this not gonna happen?
That's what I imagine like all these fucking
All these like pop stars that you see dancing around singing at a concert
Yeah, that's what I get sound like that's why the lipstick comes in play
Let's go party on the floor
Get up get up
No way
I'm not leaving
Can you imagine like some of these fucking moves that they do?
Just this move right here. Oh, that's all I have to ask
this one
Imagine singing a song. Let's say the lyrics are
And we're gonna go for it, right?
Imagine doing this fucking smashing your head that way
Like and we're back. No, no, no, it's gonna be like
And we're gonna go for it deposit balls into the shot glasses at varying distances
You're being lied to
Into the glass
The speed of the next ball will automatically increase after a successful roll
Failure to complete this task in 60 seconds may result in elimination. I'm fine
Now the challenge you get a minute to win it the game begins in
18 shit, okay. I got to be actually careful there
I'm going to go down you fucking dumb
Don't worry, I know you can win this challenge grind up all the connect and turn him into fucking shoes
So now you got the load on the showdown. You've got a minute to win it go get it. He's tilted
Well, yeah, like come on
I would be I am
This is like as far as I can fucking do this the dumbass steering wheel
Level complete $500
Great job, you beat the challenge. Let's check out your money
The question is do you want to stay and play or walk away stay
This is on hard mode
See resident sleeper right there
Extreme hanging sleeping anymore
What began with a single box of 160 tissues has now evolved into a tissue typhoon in a test of dexterity
The contestants must empty two standard tissue boxes alternating between both the left and the right hand. I'm awake. I'm awake
I'm awake. Raise your corresponding hand to remove tissue from the box remove. She's got to go like
Are you ready you got a minute to win it go get it
The game begins in three two one
I just sneezed. I actually just sneezed. I held it in like a champ though
I cry at the boobies
That's not an achievement. That's a statement. Do you want to stay and play or dash with the cash?
No
stay
That was the realest no you're ever going to hear me do
Put the studio next door filming to add I don't want to do it skip
No, no, no skip skip skip skip skip skip. I don't want to fucking do this. It's stupid
How's it hanging?
Okay, I remember this one you go
Is the elephant one in this challenge the contestant must hang a banana from a string attached to their waist
Using the momentum generated by their hips the player must swing a banana to knock several oranges across the floor and into a hoop
To move walk or run in place
Are you ready you've got a minute to win it the game begins six I can do this
three two
One great job
What the fuck is happening?
Three seconds left
Get the fuck in there
Good ass game. Oh, you didn't win the challenge a fucking shitty algorithm
This is the final 60 seconds in the competition now you can do it. You've got a minute to win it go get it
the game begins in
three two
one
This is the stupidest fucking thing i've ever seen in my life 30 seconds left
Why?
Yes, i'm actually shredding this game
You have the choice to take the money and run or stay and have some fun
This is your level five blueprint
All right, I haven't done this one yet
bucket head
A ping pong ball weighs one tenth of an ounce and has a diameter of approximately 1.5 inches
In this challenge the contestant must bounce the ball from the floor to the wall and catch it in a bucket attached to their head
Hold either hand out to the side to grab a ball
Perform an overhand throwing motion to throw
Move left or right by stepping in that direction
Let's go
This is your last 60 seconds now you can do it. You've got a minute to win it recorded five lines
The game begins in
three two
one
What are you doing? I can't see shit
This is the most unintuitive piece of shit i'm shredding it right now
It actually what it's it's like wants to come out. I didn't even do anything. It wanted to do this
It was like i'm coming out. You saw clearly I was over here. The xbox is over here
All right, i'm gonna do this safely
Shred it how many how many of these exist?
How many of these exist like is guyfury's minute to win it on xbox connect like a commodity?
I need like a surface to put this on let's get my fucking table over here. There are too many
It's five bucks on ebay. All right, well i'm just gonna fucking recycle these these things anyway
All right, don't try this at home unless you have a shredder that's capable
Don't even do that. Anyways, this could take up to fucking five like 5 000 credit cards
Seriously, though, don't fucking don't try this at home. I'm a professional. This is a professional shredder
What do I get the biggest shredder to shred the little shredder that didn't shred the fucking thing that you're supposed to be able to shred
In the shredder you can shred credit cards. You can shred plastic you shred it. It's it's I want I want my money back on that one
I think
Fix it there. All right, so you want us to play it you want me to play that game?
There's nothing to clean. What are you talking about? What do you mean play that game? Oh, we'll play in a different one
We're gonna play a classic game
And I ain't shredding it. Don't try that at home. That's a real disclaimer that then don't you get hurt
Don't fucking do that. Not with the midlife professional shredders. Don't fuck around
Here we go. Did you unplug it? Yeah, it's fine. It's don't worry
It's unplugged. It's safe
safety only
Get a polenta
This is connect sports show the dip. I will I will later. We've got to move on rare. We've rare made these games
No, that's right rare did make like all the connect games. That's right
They put rare on like connect only
Pick the player. What are you talking about? Oh
Let's go
I control everything
How do I how do I get the game to go? Oh, I have to okay
main event soccer bowling
What's the best one?
Boxing. Okay, is the boxing good on this?
It's pretty damn fun
Uh against computer you can do a good setup
How would you do?
You face each other and like fight each other in a room
I feel like that'd be dangerous
Okay, let's go
Let's hear your supporters cheer
tornado gardens
Am I gonna fight an old man i'm gonna fight like a fucking seven-year-old man
That doesn't seem right. Let's give these people a good show. All right, wait, what?
We can expect something quite special from this pair
All right, I guess we're gonna go punch to strike your opponent right? I mean obviously punch high
Or punch low
Pull your shoulder back before you punch to add power and knock your opponent back
Pull your shoulder back
That
Okay, that's that's a power punch
And this is a block
You got it
Or block no
Wait, you go like this?
Okay, let's go
I'm sorry. I don't want to fight the old man, but I have to apparently
Oh, he got me
Oh, he's out
He's out
Do I know does it automatically move forward?
Oh, I knocked him up. He's been knocked out
I like to move it move it
How could I do that
It's all right. Wait, it's recording
He's crying
Continue
Do you go through other players that are better than you are?
You look tough. What a tough guy
Play boxing, right?
Let's get this show on the road
No, that okay, that's my okay. So let's so who do I fight now the same person
Kevin again, I don't want to beat up kevin again
Strike your opponent. All right. I guess we're going to beat up kevin one more time before I go play soccer
This feels bad
So, how would you do this with two people in the room I've no I don't understand that
I think gaining health
Scream somebody just screamed
It was kevin's mom
It's gonna be this again hide my video I don't want you recording me
All right, let's try soccer
You owe kevin an apology
I'm sorry kevin
I did not mean to punch you in the face enough times where you were unconscious
Right, let's change this. Okay skill level. Let's go with professional. I like it action
Okay, now how do you do soccer on this of someone who really knows their soccer?
We are seconds away from kickoff now. So let's get down to some superb
No, I can move my hands
attacking kick in the direction you want to pass the ball
So go back turn this way kick
Okay
When you reach the goal kick to shoot
Kick
That's a very high quality animation. That looks great
All right
I'm gonna go for it
That's a throw in but slide or
The line shows you where the ball will go
All right, get in the path
And then what put the foot up?
Heal the ball
Get any part of your body to the target to save the shot
Okay
This is gonna be I think it's gonna be fun
This would be pretty interesting actually
Here we go
The keeper now kicks the ball to a fellow player
Kick it up here
score
Over that one
shit
Look at that replay
That replay was fucking so stupid
Clears the ball upfield
What
Come on what did I pass it backwards? All right
That's a penalty
Get it again
This is fun, I like this one clear of the goal mount what oh shit
I don't even know how to do that style shot. What is a style shot?
Ah, here we go. I was wondering if you could do that
What does that
Fuck gotta do it again
He's cheering i'm cheering him on go for it. You can do it
good kick
No
I was paying attention
That was a workout
Why does it look like my pants my pants don't
Why my lower body looks like it's not part of my upper body
All right. Why do I have like humpy dumpy pants?
Doesn't look like somebody like just screwed me on
It's weird. It's a two per yeah, it's two person
All right change for it
All right, I got uh beach volleyball. I'm gonna do
What do I want to do?
Table tennis sounds like fun
Bowling i'll do bowling after we'll do one
Stay with that professional skill level, too
That makes the most sense
So it's right in I think so we've got a professional gamer here
I'm gonna take a shower after this
I'm like 5 000 degrees right now
I'm gonna i'm gonna take a bath. I'm just gonna lie in the bath. I'm gonna lie in the bathroom
Just go under just move my hair around
I'm not doing those movements
Oops for this match
Reach to the right or left would you call yourself a table tennis star?
Reach with your arm straight out
I'd call myself a only play table tennis when it's part of a video game like this
And never any other surface
Same thing with tennis
Tennis to me whenever I played tennis was always just to end up being
Okay, here we go. It's really really a finesse based game
But you just yeah, I just hit it so hard every time it just soars over the whole thing
I can't do it
It'll be like i'll get one volley like don't don't
And the thing will just it's like I I can't do it. It's gone
It always goes like way out of control
Move backwards that shit. Sorry. All right, let's go
With the paddle right hand to the action we go
Stop celebrating you idiot
We're off screen
I'm just staying way back
That's it I got it right on the side
That works
All right, i'm gonna go as hard as I can
You stink
Fuck I was trying to give him a thing to serve up
You know how much it costs
to license that song
for it to play
for one or two seconds
That has that has to be hundreds of thousands of dollars to license that song
You're gonna have a whole montage with that song or it's not worth it
Okay, okay
That's so stupid I crossed the plane of the connect that was a smash
And turn the fucking song off
Yeah, that's at six five I got my eye on you buddy, this is an even game such an evenly matched game this
Shit
I'm gonna lose. I'm out of gas. I've breathed a gas already. It's only been like four and a half hours. I'm out of gas already
Yeah
A great match joke. Oh well intense
That didn't even been four hours it's been four
I know it's got the d to my property. Is that what we were playing for? I wasn't aware
All right time for bowling
Everybody wants to see bowling
Throw your hands overhead. All right, let's go
It's kind of getting dark in here. I think I need to turn the lights up just a little
While we have some lighting
Neon lanes enjoy welcome and thanks for joining for what looks like
Spin on the ball maybe possibly reach to the right or left to pick up a ball
Reach with your arms straight out
Okay, and then back
forward
Swing your arms straight back and then forwards to bowl the ball
Yeah, what about spin?
Spin is very important. What how do I do it? If you want to add spin bring your arm across your body
Let's go
Not bad. Not bad
Interesting approach there
All right, sarge your turn
Oh, you got a strike, okay
I would have loved to seen it
No, i'm trying to do like a cool thing
That means you got to okay i'll believe it sure
Bullshit spare
Oh, come on
That sucks
It's a product placement ball
How so this guy just only gets strikes?
Give one to me, too. Uh
spare
finally
Geez
I have to earn these
Well, it's all right. He'll choke like four or five times three pins two pins three pins three pins four pins three pins three pins I win
I'm getting destroyed
I would have been cool, but I actually spun
Yes, this game tried to one up we sports you can smell the desperation
I have to get some strikes where this is it
Come on
We sports is way better
We remember like we sports you could like go all the way back here and be like
Bang and it would spin all the way down
You could go like what?
Wasn't average uh bowling
score
Like 150 120
It's not the other how did it spin the other way?
How did it spin the other way?
You know fuck it. We're going on here
I didn't think you could do I didn't think you could do that
You can actually break it
That's this is better than we sports because of that alone
Might be
Oh, no, you got eight pins for the first time. Oh, no, who knows? Oh god. Oh god
That's not I was trying to do the diaper technique
It went wet that went way too fast what i'm trying to do
Anytime somebody makes fun of you when you go bowling
Let's take and you do that and you get like four or five strikes
Don't ever feel ashamed of that
Well people listen echo like
No, cool cool
I went like this
Straight down going really slow enough to every single fucking pin over
It's not how cool you look doing it. It's how many pins you knock down
That'd be not true
It's how many pins you knock down
You could turn around backwards and go like this through your legs
That doesn't matter. Did you knock down all the pins?
94 not even 100
Bullshit absolute dog shit
I leveled up some real highlights in that game
He's still level one. I well, how do you level up in this game?
I don't get it. I don't understand
You lost to 10 pinwheels
Clever
That was that was cute. That was cute. You're right
All right tracking field. I feel like i'm gonna do really good at it. Just moving your body violently around in the circle
We're gonna go champion. I'm gonna get here we go
This is all about just moving violently like shaking violently
I should nail it
You're gonna break a bone
That's not you can't break your bone here unless I like slipped
Okay
If I was going like freaking out like wildly moving around and then I went like that my leg flew up underneath and I
Went back and landed like on my neck or something
But that's impossible
What happened to my hair?
I just have a hat on so it's easy to keep it away from like because I you saw how it looked the other time
We played this
It was all over the place. It looked crazy
I looked crazy and I didn't want to look crazed anymore
Comes the falling gag 100 meter finals. Now you can feel the tension
Okay, let's go shake
Run in place lift your knees
See here what's here's what i'm gonna try here because i'm not taking my knees i'm not taking my feet off the ground
See if I can just go with my back here
i'm just
Hey, what you doing mind and body in perfect harmony. That's what breaks world records
All right, here we go
Keeping your own way. Oh, that's like pretending to be an airplane
All right javelin I will
I'll just go again
Grab a javelin reach with your arms straight out
Okay
Run in place to get to the throw zone
Hold the javelin when the ground turns green throw the javelin throw
Throw high. All right. That was pretty. All right, let's go
And this throw needs to be good
What the fuck come on, man?
Now the results from that event have been processed. We can see where we're at 32 is so bad
Failure is not an option
Make what you will of that
Third throw now, how do these athletes cope with such tension?
Oh my fucking god
Let's see how that event's results affect where we stand
At this point in time, that's how it's looking
Then what's the spring javelin high jump discuss what are we discussing?
Is that like a debate platform run in place to get to the jump zone
Lift your knees
I will I will destroy the discuss
I could sit there and talk about anything for hours. I will people will leave because i'll bore them
Okay, so run room jump
I have to like explode out of this a firm footing and is what's needed here. It's got to be a record
The previous event's results make
Second jump and an improvement is vital now. Stop moving
Fucking dumb game
I don't know how to like make it go faster
Just take a look at the results from the previous event
No, stop
I figured it out. I figured it out
The result now from the previous event and look at that
A lead is starting to open up. This competition is really close
Thank you for dropping into the discus event
Okay, disgust throwing
I think when you stand
At a certain length of way and you throw it the most power comes from when you're spinning around the momentum
Lol
That's it don't you just spin face to build from with their first attempt
If I went like this
I'm just a fucking clown. I'm like the comedy routine that's here at the olympics
The pressure is on straight into the sky
Like that person's not even trying that person's not trying
As we thought third throw and if ever there had to be success
Results from the last event and my my take a look
Take a look at these scores who would have believed it
It's daunting for the athletes, but the hurdles are next. I can't do it
I need some fucking help
Lift your knees
As soon as the hurdle turns green jump in place
Jump with both feet off the ground
Do any of these athletes have what it takes to beat the current world record?
Oh, why is it in my way?
You know what fuck all this I ain't crossing
Athlete it was the taking part that mattered you that's like i'm trying not to fall over
That's like i'm shimmying on the edge of the cliff
Volleyball is the last one time for some beach volleyball
How many connect games came out for the xbox one?
I want to say three
There was so many but 360
All right, so volleyball is just table tennis for the bigger ball larger people
Well podrick paddles
You gotta be tall to play volleyball
All volleyball players ever known for like six two
You gotta like get over the net and like stuff
People paddle toss the ball upwards then hit it with your hand as it falls
Move to the target and hit the ball with your hand and then
Jump as soon as the jump indicator appears jump and jump and then you have to stop it jump jump
All right, I got it
What just fucking happened
I have no idea what's going on. Okay service passes to the other side now synchronization for this guy
Oh big dive
Oh nice
Shit my my my body is so sweaty. I can't keep my earphones in
Two hands
Is that legal
Serve it up, let's go
Jump higher than that. Why are you waiting so long? You're killing me
Change it. He's killing me
The team are playing like clockwork today
Come on pretty good
I'm blaming it all on my teammate. See how far i've jumped i've jumped really high
I am too
I just threw the game i'm tired
i'm tired
Nothing in the air. How can you not take a picture in the air?
Like why give me up here jumping in the come on, you don't want to be in there
I want to get some water
water time
All right
I'm back. So what can I do now?
I need to slam something
My oxygen tank
I can't do it anymore. I just can't do it
What what's more game?
mini games
one bowl roll
What is that?
I guess you just roll it once
Don't worry xbox. I'm gonna
i'm gonna
in like another 15 to 20 minutes, i'm gonna probably call it
I don't know what it is, but you know what it is. It's probably because I was like sick over the last like yesterday the day before
My like physical energy levels are like zero
All right, here we go. Oh, I said, okay, I get it
Get it finicky is too it's not like the levo. You know what I mean? It's like
I shred the connect
Give me one
zero
Just roll it straight
I'm sorry. Hold on. Let me play. Let me roll a ball on the connect
Okay, then uh translates to
team mobile
All right new video game that one is
stupid
I want to do
Super saver and no. Yeah, I want to do super saver
Do han solo
No, I already a five-star expert at that game
I'm not doing that again
And then I shred it down. So i'm sorry. I can't it was one of the games I shredded earlier
All right, so just block balls
You can do better than that come on
My face what okay, why green why doesn't it just why do you have to have the green background?
Why can't it just be a an image?
Now let's see what else is here javelin sprint
distance
Let's get your running shoes on
I gotta perfect this
What do I mean? My screen is always green
This could be a tough one. What does that mean?
Streams does is playing haunt
Ah, fuck does it really? No, it doesn't it should say games and demos you gotta refresh
Yeah, I switched that a while ago. It'll be today's champion
All right, let's go
I'm gonna try to get this over at least like 80
Gearing up for that all important first attempt
So i'm just gonna throw it out to the side like just frisbee it like that like this
That was terrible
That was awful, but I don't
Let's try it again. Oh, is that it?
Cannot afford to make one mistake here. The pressure is on
Come on 50 something 40 something
All right, this one's gonna go over 50
third attempt
And it really really has to count
What happens if you drop it at the olympics count, you know, what if you picked it up and you turn zero shit drops it
You can do it again, right? Like clearly that was not your throw
I'm not gonna play hot solo again
Has it not happened?
Can you actually spin? No, I don't think you can I think you just put your arm back
All right. I think that's it
bump bash
body ball
We need hans
I'm not shredding it. I'll fucking do that at home. You get one star wars
Han solo connect dance
And that's it. Just play the rancor game for like five minutes. Yeah. All right, we'll do that, too
So so so so so so so so
Do be careful master
I honestly couldn't care less if you oh, hello
I am c3po human cyborg relations at your service master. Luke said we would meet you here
We're most excited to have you supervise our mission
You've been recognized as tended d. Rangoon 74
just
Like that
Just like that
Oh, how you do it?
Oh, yes, r2. We're all eager to get going. Did you guys know that I could moonwalk? I've never shown this before
Pretty cool. Oh do be careful with your selections. I'm told some of these files are highly restricted
I knew r2. It's a touch operated interface. They clearly hadn't invented neural sequencing
We can view the data in detail from the briefing room
Ah, there you are commander r2 and I have prepared the details of your next assignment
Yeah, i'm feeling good tonight finally feeling free and it feels all right, oh
Time to do the things I like gonna see your princess. Everything's all right
Oh, no job, but I answered to ain't a fixture in the palace
No, and since the carbonite's off me i'm living life now that i'm free
Yeah, told me get myself together now. I got myself together
Now I made it through the weather better days are gonna get better. I'm so happy the carbonite is gone
Can I can I pass it with the baby can I pass it with the baby
Holy shit little timmy get the camera
What the fuck is he doing
Loving myself makes me want to sing though. Why am I doing this again?
Now my days are gonna get i'm so happy that it's gone
I'm so happy that it's over now
The pain is gone
I'm
That was fun
Proof proof proof proof what the
All right, I gotta stop. Hey yourself. I gotta go fucking take a bath
He needs his heart medicine. All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow
I actually don't know what we're doing tomorrow because uh, I talked to star and star
I don't think in due to raria tomorrow and we're not sure if we're gonna do it on monday or not
So we're probably gonna happen is
Hey, hey, hold on. Hold on. Hold on
If you can read my lips, you can figure out what we're doing tomorrow. You got it. Super mario rpg. We'll start tomorrow
Overwatch, why would I do that? Let's take a look at this
fucking egore, um
Anyways, uh, that's been connect. Just stay safe with um
Playing with discs don't fuck around with them. They made it a plastic and metal and shit
And uh, that's gonna be it. You look disheveled. It's because I am
Yeah, like this is the thing. I think a lot of people don't understand when like when you go like this
For four and a half hours straight
Like something's gonna something's gonna cry
Like when you go like this
for like five hours straight
Like there's gonna be like a
You did not do that. What are you talking about?
Half the time i'm going like this
Why does it look like my fucking pants are like
This looks weird, right?
Something about this is weird
What's weird about this?
Am I i'm gonna onesie
All right. Good night
I'll see you guys tomorrow for super
mario
rpg legend of the seven stars
between three and four pm
Pacific time because I live on the west coast
I'm gonna go fill the bathtub with lukewarm water
Oh shit, that is the wrong card. You're right
Now I got the right one
All right
Let me uh, let me just go grab a quick thing of water and I will come back and we'll do the bits
We'll hang up for like another 20 30 minutes
I'll be right back
Okay
I am back
But i'll see you tomorrow if you're gonna come out tomorrow
Maybe i'll see you
Oh, okay
God, I don't know what it is about moving around. I'm too old
I really might be too old
Move this up
Fieri how's my burkey water filter? It's pretty good
But yeah, let's go back at two earlier. Let me move this
So i'm gonna mute so didn't they let's go back to earlier today
There we are. We had five dollars from turkey 90. Thanks for the five dollars turkey
You got rid of the whole crux
No, but like honestly honest to god
Like yeah, like you can shred CDs if you have a paper shredder that can do them
Don't fuck around with that like
If your shredder is not actually capable, don't do that
You'll fuck up your shredder
Let's make that triple clear
We're doing shredder safety
Uh, but thank you turkey for the five dollars. No message. Thank you
Thank you to uh
Nikolai does gaming. Thanks for the 10 bucks
Thousand bits. Hey german want to say thank you for the amazing content you produced
Discovered your youtube channel a couple days ago and you helped me get through the stress of getting wisdom teeth removed in the pain afterwards
Thanks for the laughs
wisdom teeth sucks
It really is
I remember when I had
I had all four of my wisdom teeth taken out. It was not fun
Your face ends up like getting
all swollen
I don't even know how it gets that swollen either. How does your face actually get to that point?
But after like a week or two you're back to normal. Hopefully you're doing all right
Hopefully you're not too sore from all the uh
All the procedures or anything
But thank you for the 10 bucks. I wish you a swift swift recovery
Thank you the 10 dollars
Thank you trident jacks for the five dollars
Much love to the stream of my best friend steven
Thank you trident. Thanks the five dollars and
Uh, shout out to steven
Hey steve, how you doing sly 161? Thanks for the 250. Is this the return of scare saturdays?
Uh, no, just I was sick yesterday. So it happened to
Just kind of go on to this today
Were we supposed to do this yesterday?
But I was not feeling well yesterday. I wasn't feeling that great this morning either, but i'm all right
I'm good
Thank you tingy for the 250. Were you we are were you playing a horror game or a skeleton?
luge simulator
What what does that mean?
Sir canine thanks for the 250 old man streamer got roasted by hip young ravers live on stream xd omega lull
omega lull kappa hd
Phylactery lich gave the 69 community subs earlier
Thank you for the 69 subs on top of the other hundreds you've given already
We did touch upon it, but thanks again. That's a fucking lot. Thank you
Elizabeth thanks for the 250. Oh, hey jeremy. Here's your order of the monthly door cube
I already opened it for you. Oh, I see you playing a horror game
I'll just leave it on your lap next to the cake batter coffee cup and popcorn on the floor
That would have been a pretty good bit. I think I think that would have been really funny
Thank you. Jamie for the four dollars
No messages. Thank you for the full box
We also had a mitchell
Gave 15 dollars
Thank you mitchell
I said, I can't wait to play with uh
feasto at the carnival stream
Also, I caught you playing music in the first game tonight
What do you mean caught you playing?
music in the first game
Fiestos no, it's like I don't know what that means. I'm not gonna say it again
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I I kind of need to see this. Oh shit. Hold on. I gotta go grab my thing
So I can actually hear this now my headphones were not plugged in
I can't even right now. I can't even do this right now. What the fuck
This is the fit. This is like the audio video clip thing
how
summer
Yeah, I have to kill the first boss. I refuse to go next until the first boss is dead
I don't even know how you guys picked this shit up
But thank you mitchell for the 15 dollars. Thank you. Aeroless for the 250. Will you have a behind the scenes stream after the robot stream?
I love the stream with jbuffet after the live rumble. Yes
There will be a whole other stream after the carnival the week after the carnival
where
There'll probably be a lot of behind the scenes footage
There'd be a lot of things to talk about
I think andy mark is actually going to
um, give me some stuff maybe potentially to show
so there will be a
kind of ask
am a anything behind the scenes thing
like last time
It should be really really really cool
Yes
Sir k9. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey, jimmy. What's up, man? It's jeff from psychology
Hey jeff good to see you again
Thanks for the five dollars
Uh, thank you gnarly for the 250 that hat makes you look like 2014 germa where you wear it for it
Sir k9. Thanks for the 12 dollars and 50 cents here
100 bits for every second of the terrible menu music
And if you lose all your lives guy fury takes you
And turns you into a beef brisket for the audience
Thank you, sir. Can I uh, thank you leftist garfield for the 250. Good evening. Jeremiah wonderful stream as always keeping the vibes positively blissful tonight
Always wanted to see my favorite streamer dressed like a 90s
new wave rapper
I just had a hat. I just had a backwards hat on
I have an ant man shirt on and a backwards hat
That's
like seven out of ten people on the subway
What are you proving his point? What are we talking about?
Thank you to
buh buh buh buh buh buh bird for the five dollars
Thank you
Uh, sir k9 says for five dollars. Oh my god germa. You fucking killed him monkey s
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 250. Happy saturday. Happy saturday to you as well
Thank you the 250
sir k9
Thanks for the 250. Where's sarge 985 stream? Can I watch that?
No, you can't it's just me
Thank you to razzle for the 250 I put the peanut butter jelly
on
It says something about putting peanut butter jelly somewhere
Something about a bum sandwich or something. I don't know. I don't know. I'm not gonna say it
I just want you to know that that's kind of just what they were saying
Okay
Hey mitchell, thanks for the five dollars
Somebody said he says what's going like here. This is this video is called what's wrong my legs with my my legs
It's just a clip from of my legs from today. I don't understand
I don't fucking understand
Thanks
for the clip
Play it again. No, I am playing it again. Thanks for the five dollars though. Appreciate it
Hey, sir k9. Thanks for another 250. I'm feeling like a star. You can't stop my shine
I'm loving cloud city my hits in the sky. I'm solo
I'm han solo. I'm han solo
I'm han solo
solo
It's a great song
Thank you, sir k9 again for five dollars still in anorlondo. I'm fucking dying
lol
What?
I don't know. I can't even fucking use my brain power to know what this means
Hey great canadian fk club. Thanks for the 15 dollars stream your bath
I I feel like that would not be again. It would probably be against the rules
But thank you for the 15 dollars. Appreciate it
That was great canadian fk club
Thank you gnarly for the 250 seen a good movies lately. Uh last movie. I saw was far from home and I thought it was fantastic
That's pretty much it
Hey thundersquid. Thanks for the five dollars germa today's my birthday. Thank you for being a great streamer and love you chat
The chat doesn't get enough credit sometimes i'm glad that you
Shouting out your fellow chat members. It's good stuff
Uh, happy birthday thundersquid. Hope it was a good one. Hope it continues to be a good one
Thank you for five dollars. Happy birthday
Thank you clueless sniper for the 250
Thank you gunther for the 250. It's payday germa
for me
For you or for the both of us. I'm not sure
Why do we get the credits rolling?
There's still some bits to do but let's get it rolling
I will see you guys tomorrow for super mario rpg legend of the seven stars
It's going to be a nostalgia stream tomorrow
If I were you
I would
Show up if you think that's interesting and you'd like to watch that stream
But thank you everybody all the subs
The huge amount of community subs that came in earlier as well
Much love to you all
Super mario RPG is the best snas game. I would
I would agree
Chrono triggers up there, too
There are a few and most of honestly like at least the top five
Super nintendo games for me are rpgs
At least three of the top five I think are
That was just kind of the golden era for rpgs
turn-based at least
But thank you to
Uh tingy for the 250. I was talking about the first game where it makes you put your hands
to your side
Still as a board and turning your shoulders you kind of look like this
So many of these games required so much like random t posing
Yeah, like like a like a luge
I did do this a lot. You're right
You are right
That is a terrifying sport by the way
What a scary sport. This is
Don't you go?
More than 50 60 70 miles per hour on this thing
Can you imagine the speeds?
you just on like
What abouts to a potato wedge?
That takes some skill to be able to maneuver that thing around
But thank you tingy. Thank you bone jackal for the five dollars
Jeremy you may not believe me, but you were my substitute teacher back when I was in middle school
Is the rest of this comment is is just is just just horseshit. Um, i'm not gonna read the rest of this
I like that's this is not real and i'm not i'm not gonna even read it
Thank you for the five dollars, uh bone jackal. I really I appreciate it. Thank you
I
No, okay. Thank you for the five dollars
Bone jackal the bullshitter. Yeah, that's that's the new nickname there
Being rude to your old students
Hey, why don't you scroll back and see what they wrote and then tell me if you want me to say that on stream
Hey lieutenant campbell. Thanks for the 250
Hey, jeremy longtime viewer first time tipper. Just want to say don't let the balders and olders get you down
You have hair that rivals matt mercer's and he's an actual god made flesh
I'm gonna be hunkered down for the hurricane
Reaming into florida. I hope
Uh, that's true. Everybody stay safe. Uh, is that is it here now?
I know that was that was happening in the next day or so
Take care of yourselves guys. Your safety is way more important than anything else
I wonder when it's at when it's gonna be over. Is it miami?
Something like that, right?
Just be careful guys. That shit is scary
Do what you need to do stock up on things you need to stock up on make sure your friends and family are safe
hurricanes are no joke, especially when they're
As powerful as they you know, possibly could be with this one. So
But I wish you the best of luck
Uh, thank you. That was lieutenant campbell
Stay safe
Thank you so much for the 250
Thank you pretend dear for the 250 feel like I gotta throw some bits to you for the amazing stream today
That's not necessary
But I will accept them. Thank you
For the 250 much love dear
Wink death. Thanks for the 250 on my birthday. I had a dream my parents got you to come to my party and we talked for
three hours
But then I woke up and was really sad
What are you talking about? I was there
I was there
That was real
I had a really that was a great we had a great conversation
That was a that was an unbelievable fucking party
He sees you in your dreams
Didn't our real monsters used to do that
That was the whole premise of that show, right? They would you'd be sleeping and they would like crawl into your ears
And give you nightmares and stuff
That's a scary show
No, that's true. Yeah
Our real monsters that was their job. Wasn't it? That was part of their career
as a monster like an ah real monster you had to go and like scare people and
Give them nightmares
That's not monsters ink. That's our real monsters
Thank you. Peaceful. Haley for the 250
German it's been a while, but I want to tell you in chat that I got a role in dragon ball gt abridged
It's going to be on youtube in a little while
But i'm so happy
Well, hell, yeah
I'm gonna be videl in the show. So yeah, I just want to tell you can't wait for my future. Have a nice night
That's pretty fucking awesome
I've never seen a dragon ball
But that's fucking cool. That's really cool
Because dragon ball every time it's ever explained to me
There's like four or five different
Dragon ball series, right?
There's dragon ball dragon ball. There's dragon ball
Kai there's dragon ball gt. There's dragon ball super
And they follow a different timeline or something
He knows yeah, I know
I've never seen it though, but good luck to you. That's
Sounds like a ton of fun
That's really really cool
Fuck. Yeah
Have fun with it
Thank you. Peaceful. Haley for 250
Hey nefarious bear. Thanks for the three dollars
Thanks for being one of the only streamers to make me bust my gut laughing on a regular basis
If you're still taking videos, here's an extremely late green screen video
Uh, we're gonna hold on to it add it to the list of things. We're going to have a submission room probably this weekend
For community stuff because I want that well, maybe yeah either tomorrow or
Monday or so I want it to be up there fairly quickly
art showcase video showcase
Content showcase we're gonna do it once a month or so
When we feel like we have
enough stuff
There is no deadline on these things
It's not oh, well, you have to get it in there by uh, september 6th
Otherwise, there's no way it's ever going to be shown
No, it's just going to be an open submission platform on that discord channel
And we're just going to take stuff. I'm going to pull stuff into some slides and we're just going to make it
there'll be
Obviously rules for submitting
But there's no deadline
Tomorrow is in like 30 minutes. Well, it'll be there within the next few days
In the discord channel. Also, there is discord channels for
the activity book stream
Which I keep like pushing forward and forward and forward and forward but it will happen that stream is going to happen once there's enough
Uh interesting stuff that comes in
activity wise
I mean backwards and i'll put pushing backwards and backwards back not forward
But thank you to fairies bear. I look forward to seeing it. Is the activity book stream even real it will be
It will be
Sir canine. Thanks for the five dollars
Uh, i'm feeling like a star you can't stop my shine i'm loving cloud city
I'm so long. You just did it's just the w thing with every other letter is a w
Thanks for the five dollars. Appreciate
C4g, thanks for the 250
Today is hatsune miku's birthday. Did you remember to tell her happy birthday? Happy birthday
Happy birthday
Is it?
What?
I can't believe it
That's the the the sega pop star, right?
I just I just told you that you were in all caps. Do you even know who that is? I do know
I know exactly who that is
That's the pop star made by sega
I couldn't tell you one of the songs
I don't know any of them
I just
Know that they keep making games
I don't know what they are. I know they're like singing and dancing games
Song games does hatsune miku have albums or is it just games rhythm games?
There no there are songs. It's just a music program. I don't know. All right. Well, i'll make sure to play the entire
uh ost of
hatsune miku's
artificial existence
After I take a bath
But thank you. Happy birthday to I don't know why i'm saying happy birthday to
This this this entity
I guess all right, let's have it. I guess i'm gonna say it again
She created minecraft
Wow
That's quite an achievement
Superintendent chalmers. Thanks for the 250. Hey germa. I heard you were going to do a gta stream
Will it be before or after the carnival?
Yeah, I really did want to do a gta casino stream
but
I don't know maybe
Maybe i'll just who cares and just join a public lobby
You gotta be careful though
Isn't gta the the easiest game on earth
To have your like ip just get grabbed
That's why I haven't done it yet
Yes, it is. Yeah
Yeah
That's roblox
You can literally hack into single player gta 5 games
How would you even?
I do I do use a vpn
But to me, I don't know. I haven't used a vpn for that long
I really feel like a vpn is a guy that like is standing outside
My door and like you know, what if you punch the guy in the face that's standing there guarding the door?
He just falls over is it possible
If yes, it is a paid vpn
Oh, okay
cool
nice
All right, maybe I will do it then
All right, that sounds like fun
Add to the list
But thank you superintendent chalmers. Yeah. Yes. The answer is yes. I do still want to do that. Thank you gunther for the 250
Thank you for being you. Thank you for
Being you as well. Thank you for giving me two dollars and fifty cents
To tell me to thank me for being me from me then to respond by i'm glad that you are you
Do you thank you?
And finally we have choco 80
for the 250
Hey germa, i'm the one whose mom thought I was shouting when you were shouting before in another stream
Anyways today she came in when I had you on the tv and asked frantically. Is he cussing?
You weren't
Good. All right
But remember this is if this is an r-rated pg-13 stream
Right. This is a pg-13
With like i'm i'm dip i'm dipping my toes into r-rated
Pg-13 can only say the f word once
one per stream
No, it's an r-rated pg-13
stream
Yes
So it's r-rated
No
It is an r-rated
pg-13
stream
How is that so hard to understand
Explain that one because I can't no there's no rating on this stream
Tomorrow, we're gonna play super mario rpg and i'm not gonna say one swear word
earlier today
Uh guy got cut in half by a guillotine
It's an r-rated pg-13 stream
And that's the end. I will see you guys tomorrow
Thanks for watching
Thanks for hanging out
Super mario rpg begins tomorrow and we'll see what happens on monday
Because we have about two days in a row good night guys
See you soon
Take care