I fixed it. I fixed it. Okay. Hi.
Hey, how are you?
Actually muted. Not anymore.
How do I sound?
What do you guys think?
Do you like the new audio? Do you think it sounds alright?
How does it sound?
Welcome back. How are you?
It sounds like shit.
It does not sound like shit, okay?
By the way, I only stream every three or four days.
So, I already know the joke.
I already know the funny joke.
To put the mute thing up.
You sound like you're in my head. Please get out of here.
You sound like old Jerma.
It sounds too clean.
It does sound worse.
No, it doesn't.
You know what the funniest part about this?
In like three days, you guys will get used to this.
And it'll just be normal.
You sound like a 16-year-old.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Hold on. Let me listen to it. Let me see how it sounds.
You sound like 2010 Andy.
This is what I hear.
Okay?
I am a quarter of a second delayed in my head.
So, I'm listening to myself talking
and I'm a quarter of a second delayed in my head.
Okay, I have to mute that.
I was hearing myself in my ears a quarter of a second after I talked.
Okay. You sound like a librarian.
I don't sound like a librarian.
Look, it's going to take a little bit of tweaking.
I just got it set up.
It's going to take some tweaking.
It's going to take some finagling.
It's fine.
You sound like a podcast host.
Well, okay, what's worse podcast host
or Jerma, please go back to the setup you had.
You sound like you were in my bathroom.
I don't think there's any compression even on.
All right. Let's do a test. Ready?
You guys can help me.
All right. This is going to be a quick test.
We're going to see how you guys feel about this.
How do you guys feel about this?
I turned off some setting
and now it sounds probably really awful.
That sounds better.
That's perfect.
It sounds like an Xbox 360.
Your voice is too crackly.
It sounds exactly the same.
Worse.
It sounds the same.
Okay.
How about now?
How does that sound?
Do you guys like this better?
Are you happier with this setup?
Does this sound better?
If I were to turn it up?
It's very quiet.
Well, okay.
So how about this?
You tell me. You tell me.
We'll figure this out.
How do you sound now?
How you doing?
Now you're too loud.
Sound like a podcaster.
That sounds really good.
That was better before.
I can't tell the difference.
How do you sound?
It's really too quiet.
You sound like SpongeBob.
What?
It sounds like SpongeBob?
Somebody said that's good,
but you have the mute thing on.
So you're full of shit.
And look, there's no compressor on now.
So if I get loud, it's going to hurt your ears.
Hold on.
I have to...
We're going back to this one.
Oh my God.
Okay.
All right. I don't fucking care.
My audio setup has sucked asshole
since I started fucking YouTube back in like 2010.
Okay.
Are you really here for the audio?
Are you here for the audio?
Is that what you're here for?
Huh?
You're here for the audio?
I look like my fucking dad.
Hold on.
Are you even here for the audio?
Okay. There we go.
How do you...
I think that sounds fine.
Let me listen to it.
Let me see how it sounds.
Let me get it.
I haven't changed my audio setup in like fucking four and a half years.
Okay.
I think this sounds fine.
This really does.
Holy shit.
Complainer Andes.
This sounds fucking fine.
This sounds flawless.
If I get a little closer to the microphone,
by the way, it's up here now.
This sounds fucking flawless.
This sounds...
Let me get loud.
It's too...
It's too loud.
Oh, it's too loud.
Oh, it's too soft.
I need the band that's just right.
Hold on.
A bunch of fucking Goldilocks Andes.
I have to stop monitoring because I can't even talk.
How many times am I going to say Andy in the same day?
Okay.
I think it sounds great.
I'm ready.
That last bit sounded weird when you went high-pitched.
Microphones are fucking stupid.
Microphones suck.
And like you're in a different place too.
I moved my...
Look, this is here.
It's in the way.
Look at this.
I don't even want to move it because I got it on the right spot.
This thing is aiming at me.
I have this thing that's like aiming directly at me.
It's literally aiming at me.
It's freaking me out.
It actually is kind of freaking me out.
This thing is literally aiming at me like a cannon.
Dude, you got a duck.
All right, we're good.
You sound like you have auto-tune on.
No, I do not.
I do not.
I sat there for fucking an hour holding my hands like this
and talking and going like ABCDE, ABCDE, ABCDE.
And I was like, that sounds fine.
So we're going to keep it the way it is.
Check the gain.
I think it's fine.
It's fine.
Look, I have to turn my gain up because...
Look, listen.
Why can't I talk?
This is like froze up.
Listen to me.
Where? There you are.
You're in a different spot now.
Like the chat's like over here now.
Like you're over there.
I don't like this new thing.
I'm going back to what it was in 2012
when I used to hold the mic like this
because I didn't have a mic stand.
The laugh had a distortion on it.
Well, we'll figure it out some other day.
My audio has been too low.
People have complained about how I'm not loud enough.
It seems that the laugh had a tinny sound.
Hold on.
I know. Look, trust me.
We'll get on with it.
Just hold on.
Let me see.
So when I laughed, it was a tinny sound.
Oh my God.
That is weird.
What the fuck?
Why is it doing that?
You're the loudest person on Twitch?
No, I'm not.
Why is it doing that?
Shit.
I'm sorry, guys.
I didn't sit there.
I didn't sit there and put my headphones in
and sit there and go...
Like what am I doing in here?
You need to refund it.
Am I too loud?
But everybody says I'm too soft.
The gain is too high.
All right, I'm going to turn the gain down
and then we're going to get this right.
We'll get it right.
Okay, you ready?
Boom.
How's that?
How are we feeling about this one?
How do we feel about this?
Do we feel pretty good about this?
Are we feeling better about this?
This is literally perfect right now.
Okay, we have to do a test.
Oh, I fucking hate that.
Get off camera.
The laugh is still weird.
I think that was a weird laugh, man.
Does that sound weird?
You have a distortion filter on.
I actually, I really don't.
I promise, I really don't.
It's phasing.
Yeah, why is it phasing?
Whatever.
Look, the game we're playing
is wicked fucked up today anyways.
So look, just pretend it's part of the VHS filter.
Yeah, who gives a shit?
Let's go.
I'll get it right.
It's trying to cut off your weird voices.
Why?
That's weird.
All right, I just came in here to do some settings.
Should I turn the filter off?
Should I turn the VHS filter off?
Or what?
I mean, everyone hates this, don't they?
Turn it off and lights off too.
All the lights are off in my whole house.
Just don't laugh or don't make any weird sounds.
I'll figure out the weird sound filter
that I have for no reason.
Your mic thinks your noises are inhuman
and is filtering them out.
That's so stupid.
Whatever, I'm getting caught by a weird noise filter?
I don't have a noise gate on.
I don't have a compressor on right now either.
I think this just hates me.
The VHS filter kind of hurts my head.
I'll keep the CRT filter on.
If anyone has to complain about that,
then get in line,
because I have a lot of announcements to make today.
Hold on, what?
I'm not even fucking ready to stream yet.
I got a lot of things to talk about.
Yeah, I'm not even ready yet.
Hold on, give me a second.
I have some announcements.
Announcement number one.
Are you ready?
Over the next day or so, next couple of days,
we are going to be officially...
Officially...
Did that sound weird?
I just coughed normally.
Green screen part three, the finale.
The final green screen stream
is coming in the next week or two.
I'm going back in front of the screen one last time.
One final time ever.
So what's going to happen is,
just like in previous years,
in the Discord, you are going to go to the Discord.
The channel has to be created and has to be...
The rules need to be pinned up and everything.
But I need actions.
I need things that you want me to do.
Just like in previous years,
we're going to have people curate a ton of actions.
I, myself, am going to go do some things as well.
I'm going to make my own actions up.
Please do all the Fortnite dances.
Well, let me just be very clear.
This is the last time this is ever happening.
Three times in front of the green screen.
There you go.
That's it.
We'll have the whole trilogy.
And I'm going to do a green screen movie night
at some point in June.
I will tell you the hard date
that I'm going to go in front of the screen,
but for now, let's just make this really, really...
My microphone socks, dude.
We'll make this really easy.
And just, if you have actions,
I would like to see you do this.
We're going to have a discussion channel to open up
in some ways you guys can figure out what you want me to do.
I'll give you more info soon.
What's the status on baseball?
July 14th?
The baseball stream is happening.
That's all you need to know.
I'm not telling you anything else.
Please use multiple outfits.
Do this, IRL.
I just did!
Yeah, a lot of Discord users probably covered it right now.
I don't think it's there yet.
I just want to talk about it now.
The second thing I want to talk about is Otto.
Otto was doing way better.
If you don't, if you missed the past weekend,
Otto had a UTI
and it was actually really, really awful.
Really sad.
He was throwing up.
He was peeing 10, 20 times in a couple of hours.
He was constantly every 5, 10 minutes.
I got to go out. I got to go out.
I got to go out.
It's like, all right, well, let's see what's going on.
So I kind of canceled the whole weekend worth of streams
and we're picking up this horror stuff I was supposed to do two days ago.
But he's been put on an antibiotic and he is way better.
I would say he's pretty much back to normal.
He is almost 100% normal now.
So that's really good too.
Really happy about that.
The other thing I want to talk about,
let's talk about this.
The archive channel, the VOD channel,
you know, the German archive channel on YouTube
that you've come to know and love over the years,
is now officially an official channel
that has been absorbed into the German network.
So that's really, really cool too.
If you don't know what I'm talking about,
the archive channel has been uploading every stream I've ever done.
And I mean, they're dating back to like 2014, 2015.
Every single one.
You need to upload the...
Guys, I don't even have access.
Okay, people are like, hey dude, back in like 2013,
you did like a stream.
You have like access to that stream.
Like we kind of want to see it.
It's like, bro, I don't even know what computer I uploaded that on.
You know, I have no fucking idea.
I have no idea.
Hey dude, you played like Diablo back in like 2012 on stream on YouTube.
You have any like idea where I can find that?
I know.
I don't know where that would be.
I have no fucking idea.
Only three German channels.
Hey, back in 2013, you did a stream.
You have backup of that stream because a lot of us would like to see it.
I have no fucking idea.
Because I don't even know.
I don't remember what even happened at breakfast yesterday.
You think I remember what like hard drive from 10 years ago
that I had some stream on it maybe?
I don't fucking know.
Can we see the baseball stream in person?
No.
Sag.
What about baseball merch?
They will be baseball merch.
A lot of it.
And I'm really excited for it because it's going to be.
Oh man.
What do the kids say?
It's going to be.
Give me some things that the kids say so I can sound fucking cool right now.
What?
I'm serious.
They're going to be some of the best merch you've ever seen in your whole life.
It's going to be awesome.
Now, let's add a style right now.
Bustin'.
There you go.
Oh man, you're going to be wanting to take like fucking pictures of this.
This is going to be so sick.
Trust me.
All right.
I got another thing to talk about because this is something that I wanted to address.
You probably noticed a few days ago or a week ago now that I VIP'd some new people
and revoked VIP for all those people.
Well, some of them.
And it's a very important reason for that.
As you know, over the last three years or so, where's mine?
Precisely what I'm about to talk about.
So VIP has been in this weird place in the channel for the last three or four years or so
because I haven't really given it to really anybody.
I mean, maybe a few times during random streams and whatever,
but besides the community leader stuff in the Discord,
I haven't really given it to anybody.
And what I realized and what I'm going to kind of change my rules here,
I'm not giving VIP to anybody ever again.
And there's very few specific reasons why I cannot pick and choose people in this community.
It seems like if I give VIP to somebody, there might be 10 other people that are disappointed.
There might be a hundred people that deserve it.
But how can I possibly do that?
Since this, I mean, there are 16,000 people here right now.
Ever since this channel grew two or three times in the last two or three years,
I cannot reliably pick out even probably a hundred of you that I would be like,
okay, should I? You've done this.
You've been around. You've said this.
You've been like an active member of the...
There's just too many people I could give it to.
So no one's going to get it.
Just no one's going to get VIP anymore.
Unless you are somebody that I really need to see you,
but like another streamer or a game dev comes in or whatever, right?
And I want to see them like in the chat.
This is communism.
This is what do you mean communism?
I'm literally removing it from everybody.
I'm not giving it to everybody.
That's not, what are you talking about?
Durama, communist move.
Mad, communist.
Actually, that's not communism.
I'm about to disturb my microphone.
Don't get me loud.
Don't make me distort my microphone.
No, but in all seriousness, no, it's too hard to pick.
And I don't want people will get pissed off at each other.
And I already see the issues of,
hey, this person got VIP.
Why didn't I get it?
Or this person doesn't deserve it for XYZ.
And it's like, I just don't even want to do it.
There's too many people to give it to.
Too many people I could give it to.
So I'm just not going to give it to anybody.
You understand?
No cap, your mic is ass.
VIP that person for an hour.
The nuclear option.
But sometimes you have to do the nuclear option.
You really do.
I don't want to have, I don't want to give VIP to five people
and have five other people then like get mad at those five people
and cause ripples through the community of people
that are just pissed off that they don't have it
or that they don't think somebody deserves it.
For real.
I don't want to cause this big pick,
Jerma's picking favorites and he gave it to this person,
but not to this person.
It's a huge problem.
It really could be.
And so I don't even want to have it be a problem.
And this is a horror game night.
So you should be fucking scared.
You have a webcam mic on.
I don't, there's no webcam mic on right now.
You know how angry,
you know how angry that just made me what you just said?
You guys are going to get used to it.
New things are evil and awful, right?
Remember when I had the new audio setup
and everyone told me that like I'm the worst streamer
on the website.
I remember looking over at chat
and people on my other audio setup
that you've gotten used to over the last two to three years.
Right?
Somebody brought like this paragraph.
I might be making this up.
I don't know, I could be,
but like I swear to God,
I looked over and someone was like, dude,
like you're like probably the worst fucking Twitch streamer
like quality wise and professional wise or something.
And I'm just like, what the, what the hell?
Let's go.
Why is this here?
I don't know, this is a mystery that we need to solve.
Can you guys help me with this mystery?
Why is there a chili cheese Frito here on my desk?
But what, why is this here?
I'm not gonna eat it, what if it hit the ground?
Why is it in here?
The mic censored, fuck, or did you not say it?
I don't know.
He saves all his production value for the big streams.
Thank you, thank you.
I appreciate that.
All right, this is blood wash.
It's a scary game about, I don't know.
People told me to play this.
People said, hey dude, play this game and it's scary.
And I've been sitting here for 30 minutes.
So what production value?
So I'll have to say about that.
How do you not know what I'm doing?
What a day.
There's people talking.
Professor Watt was his usual miserable self
and that test was a killer.
Like I can just rocks and.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Liam didn't do the laundry or clean.
I'll have to do a load of laundry.
What are you?
I have an interview for a job tomorrow
and have nothing to wear.
Those, no, I'm doing the thing.
I'm doing the thing, that fucking meme.
Okay, I actually just did it.
I, whatever, I don't care.
Let's go.
I'll gather these clothes up
and head to the laundry room in the basement.
I'm going to have to be too upset and tired
to go through it again.
Let me pay attention to this
because this is important.
I need to pay attention.
This is a scary game and you're fucking with me.
Do I turn the volume down on this?
Do I turn it up or down?
This is one of those games
that's going to blow my eardrums out, right?
I'm scared.
That's why I'm not scared of the jump scares.
I'm scared of my ears hurting.
Okay, haven't had time to unpack yet.
Not sure when I will.
He did that on purpose.
Not really, actually.
I mean, I got like halfway through it
and then I realized that I was doing it.
So I was like, fucking whatever.
And then I started laughing about it.
Hold on, I need to see it.
Well, people were like,
what do you mean?
What am I talking about?
It's so clear what I was pointing at.
Soy Andy.
Let me see if I did it on purpose.
Laundry.
What are you?
Those.
Yeah, okay.
No, I'm doing the thing.
I'm doing.
Okay, at about, so of this clip right here.
Those.
At exactly eight seconds when my mouth opens
and I say those is when I realized
that this is what I was doing.
So I just held it.
I freeze.
I froze.
No, I'm doing.
And that's when it was, you know,
it could have been on purpose at that point.
It was not on purpose until about seven
and a half seconds in that clip.
I can't play the game before people scream
at me for being the worst streamer on Twitch again.
Okay.
Why do you hate Europeans?
I live in the fucking America.
I live in the United States of America
on the western most coast of the country.
You and I, when you're eating breakfast, dude,
I'm just going to bed.
I'm like getting under the covers
and like going to sleep when you wake up
and you eat breakfast.
When you go to bed, I'm like, oh, waking up.
It's like fucking 11 o'clock in the morning.
I live across the world from you.
I live in the United States of America.
He hates Europeans.
All right.
I need to leave.
It's 3 a.m. right now.
Dude, it's four o'clock in the afternoon here
and I'm at peak happiness.
So I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's go.
I can't leave.
I need to gather my dirty clothes.
All right.
Let's get the dirty clothes.
Pizza, chair, small black and white TV, okay.
All right.
How much dirty clothes do I have?
Dirty clothes and Coke 24 packs.
Did I get it all?
Okay.
I think I got it all.
What do you mean all my dirty clothes?
Is that it?
There we go.
I think that's all the dirty laundry.
Time to go to the basement.
You didn't deny that you hate EU.
What do you mean I hate EU?
No, I'm saying I don't hate EU.
I just said it.
I said I don't hate EU.
Why are you making that up?
What are you trying to make me look bad?
I'm sorry that our clocks are different right now.
Where's the basement?
Oh, okay.
Wait, what?
Jerma, keep me entertained
while my bowels are being cleansed.
That's from the Dusk Dev.
I'm gonna try.
A nice man lives here.
It's good to know you have
at least one good neighbor.
Newspaper.
Headline reads,
womb ripper strikes again.
In the early hours of the 30th,
authorities were called when a passerby
found a terribly mangled corpse,
haphazardly tossed on the nearby grounds.
Sources indicate that the woman was indeed pregnant.
And just like previous victims,
the fetus was cut out and assumed
to be taken by the assailant.
This is now the fourth victim in as many weeks,
and authorities are struggling to come up with leads
and one of the most gruesome crime sprees
the city has ever endured.
The woman and her son live here.
Now that I think about it,
I haven't seen either one in about a week.
Okay.
Oh, also, you know what's different about this audio setup
that a bunch of people are gonna be really pissed off about?
But I'll try to fix it eventually.
I make a ton of mouth sounds.
And now, now you can hear them all.
See, before you couldn't hear any of those.
See?
I hate that.
Okay.
I don't need to go to that floor
besides one of the people in that floor has a mean dog.
All right, we'll make sure we get over this really quick.
Let's get over this really quick
because I know that we're gonna see a lot of these.
So let's just get over this for the next minute or so.
Let's just get over this.
Hold on.
Let me just get over this real quick.
Let me just get over this.
Okay.
This is, we're gonna get over this.
Just bear with me while we go through these.
Very nice.
Yes.
Absolutely.
I think that's BB-8 or whatever that character's name is.
Okay.
Let's keep them coming.
We're gonna blow through these.
Uh-huh.
Very nice.
It's a pretty good website.
If you're looking for news or...
How did you, what?
That one's kind of big.
Uh-huh.
But why are these so, like, who cares?
This is like...
Yeah, I'm sorry, but Las Vegas is fucking cool.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Me pointing at the Las Vegas sign
is not me pointing at the Reddit sign
because Vegas is fucking cool.
I love this place.
So, excuse me?
Somebody made the template, but it's not even...
Here's the template.
Should I leave this on the stream?
So stupid.
Oh, this is so annoying.
Wait, I've already done this?
What do you mean?
Hold on.
A classic.
I did already do this?
This is from years ago.
This is the hot air balloon.
I didn't actually do this, did I?
I fucking did.
This is before anybody even gave a shit about this.
This actually was from, like, four years ago
before that meme, anyone even cared.
Oh my God, I look like shit.
I look tired.
What's wrong with my eyes?
Why do I look so fucking disheveled?
Okay.
This one, we'll just put this one up
and then I'm gonna move on.
I'm gonna play the horror game
that I'm supposed to be playing.
You know, why not show this one too?
This is gonna be a favorite, I think.
You look like a newly discovered fish.
All right, dude.
That was fun.
Let's play the video game.
Do I have audio?
All right.
You look like a taxidermy fish.
What do you look like at eight o'clock in the morning?
Oh, that's loud.
That's very loud.
It hurts.
I get a...
All right, this is the last one I'm gonna show.
I promise.
Nice zit.
An old tire.
Actually, I don't like the CRT filter.
It kind of makes me wanna throw up.
Out of order?
Turn it off.
Yeah, it kind of makes me wanna puke.
It's worse.
It smells like it hasn't been taken out in months.
Out of order?
What am I gonna do now?
I should probably go back upstairs and figure something out.
Turn the headbomb off.
I think I heard something coming from the closet.
I think I need to keep it on.
I think it's designed to have it on.
It looks weird now.
Yeah, it somehow looks worse the other way.
What do you mean from the closet?
Oh, that hurts.
I don't need to go through there.
Loud, by the way.
It's probably gonna be loud.
Somebody's probably gonna jump in front of the screen.
Go back.
You ignored this jump scare.
What?
What are you talking about?
Let's see what's inside.
This one's empty.
Filled with porno.
What are you talking about?
The closet?
What closet?
This is a filing cabinet.
That's a tuba reaction.
I kinda feel like a cartoon.
It was a tuba reaction.
I did not expect, whatever.
Damn girl, you scared the big Jesus out of me.
God damn girl, you scared the big Jesus out of me.
I scared you?
You scared me.
Goku.
I'm sorry for scaring you.
I'll tell you, but can you keep this to yourself?
I love this acting.
I love this actor.
This is great.
This is actually, I love this.
Jesus Christ, Joe, you're insane.
Yeah, I can.
What's up?
The missus kicked me out and it's too cold outside,
so I'm trying to wait her out down here.
I really didn't mean to creep argue.
Honest.
This is never gonna end, is it?
This is never gonna end.
This is what happens.
I just can't stop.
I cannot stop this.
But I need to show them, right?
It's my obligation to.
I believe you.
Just next time, maybe don't go around
slinging doors open and hiding in the dark.
I will.
Thanks, kid.
Say, if you're wanting to use the washing machine,
it's broken.
Yeah, thanks.
I figured that out.
Okay, thanks a lot.
I thought you guys were full of shit
that I missed the jump scare.
I thought, like, go check the closet.
I thought it was this.
I did not know the door was gonna rip open.
That was very scary.
It was probably loud.
Just, it's gonna be loud.
Just, please be aware of that.
They're gonna hear it.
Oh, fuck, I don't have a noise gate anymore.
You definitely heard that, without a doubt.
Oh, well.
Fuck.
This is why I can't, wait, forget what I just did.
What's up, sir?
Oh, you know, trying to balance life, school, and job hunting.
It's a tough world these days.
Liam been treating you well.
When he isn't drunk, yeah.
You'll tell me if it gets bad, yeah?
This is my neighbor.
I know it ain't easy to talk about.
And you don't have to tell me nothing.
Just promise me you'll tell me if you need help.
My sister used to be in a bad situation, too.
And there's places you can go.
I appreciate that, Stan.
I really do.
Yeah, sure.
You doing some laundry at this time of night?
I'm trying to.
Of course, when I really need it,
the washer downstairs is broken.
Ain't that some shit?
Yeah.
And speaking of shit, I have an interview tomorrow,
so I guess I'll show up smelling like crap.
Jesus.
Well, if it's an emergency,
I heard of this laundromat that's open 24-7,
just outside of town.
Still early enough to catch the last bus.
24-7, outside of town.
I'll have to say, though,
it's a hell of a time to be out so late,
especially with that maniac roaming around.
I mean, if I needed to do laundry and I couldn't,
I'd probably just turn the sink on
and just put a bunch of soap in the sink
and plug the hole so the sink will fill up
and just like...
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
And then just kind of hang it over the shower curtain
and just let it dry.
I'm a big girl, Stan.
Do you know the address?
Sure, sure.
Let me write it down for you.
1800s laundry?
Promise me you'll take care, all right?
I mean, if you just need one, you know,
a shirt, a pair of pants,
maybe another shirt or something.
Yeah, I would just do it in the,
I would just turn the shower on and just,
I would just put the clothes on
and just get in the shower
and take a shower with the clothes on
and then just take them off and just air dry them.
That's how, why is that weird?
Is that really that weird to like wash your clothes
if you're in like an emergency situation
where your laundry machine doesn't work
or to just wash your fucking clothes in the sink?
Why is that such a weird take?
It's warm water and soap.
What do you think happens in the washing machine?
Do you think there's like a magical elf
that when you turn the washing machine on
that takes your clothes to someplace to clean them,
it's just soap and water and it just goes.
doesn't do anything else while wearing them?
Well, you could like probably save water.
You take a shower and clean the clothes at the same time.
So now I just gotta get ready
to go to the laundromat, I think, right?
I thought it was a clock, thought it was a health pack.
All right, I'm ready to go.
I got my clothes, I'm ready to move out.
Hurry, you might be able to catch the next bus.
Thanks again, Stan.
Do I have to go all the way down
or just out this front door?
I'm on the second floor right now, okay.
Second floor.
I need to get my purse first.
What?
Dan's the murderer.
Don't you dare.
It just, okay, if that's a spoiler, you're in deep shit.
You're in deep shit.
That person's in deep shit.
All right, where's my purse?
Where's my purse?
Oh, there it is.
You can backseat me.
You can call me an idiot.
You can call me stupid.
But the second that you put what happens
at the end of end game in the chat here,
I don't think so.
All right, let's do it.
Goodbye.
I gotta, this image is just on my other monitor.
I'm gonna add this as Jerma Chest to BTTV.
Whatever, that's fine.
That's fine.
Ugh.
All right, can I turn the audio down?
Is it really gonna be that loud?
Like, I don't like that.
I don't like this.
I don't like how loud the sounds are.
There's a person right here.
Hi there.
Are you okay?
Can I get you anything?
It's gone.
They took it.
Did someone steal something from you?
The people in the walls, they took it from me.
Oh God, she's here now.
I should probably leave him alone.
Poor guy.
Jesus.
Bus stop.
What?
What are you doing?
Run?
Is that the bus?
That's not the bus?
That'd be a really weird bus.
Got any change?
Sure, I have a couple dollars.
Better than nothing.
Thanks, kid.
Haven't seen you around here before.
I moved in not too long ago.
I'm usually studying or at my classes.
It's your Uber.
So that's probably why.
What was that?
Oh, a college girl, huh?
What are you studying?
I'm pursuing a career in education at the moment.
Nice, that's what I got my bachelor's in.
Oh, that's great.
I hope I can find a gig soon afterwards.
If not, my sleeping bag has room for two.
Anything in the dumpster?
Oh, there's the bus.
How do I get on?
Where are you heading at this hour?
If you don't mind me asking.
The laundromat on the outside of town.
Not sure I believe that.
Pretty late to be doing laundry.
Hey, if you're looking to score,
I have a good deal just for a pretty little thing like you.
Oh, fucking leave me alone.
You won't even have to pay cash if you know what I mean.
How about you just drive the bus
and I'll pretend you're not a desperate loser.
Whatever, bitch.
Sit the fuck down so I can get this piece
of junk rolling again.
What the fuck?
Dirty seat, dirty seat, dirty seat,
dirty seat, dirty seat.
Well, I guess I'm gonna sit here.
It's gonna be fucking loud.
Should I turn it down?
Turn it down.
Turn it up.
I was gonna say, excuse me,
when does the bus leave?
There was a, I looked online
and said the schedule was at 12.15 and it's 12.18.
Turn the FOV down.
What are you doing?
Sit down in a seat.
Why are you still, okay, that's fucking.
All right, dude, like seriously, sit down.
This is, no fucking way.
This is no way.
This guy right now would be going like this,
flanning his right foot and stuffing it on the ground
desperately trying to not fall down.
You don't have to do that, by the way.
I know that when some of you guys get on the train
or on the bus or whatever,
or whatever, you just grab onto it.
Dude, I fucking hate this guy.
He's just weird and he's right next to me.
How many of you guys have done that shuffle
where you just plant your foot
and you don't want to grab onto anything
because it's like, well, I know,
I can't grab onto the pole.
I can handle it.
Then you go, ooh.
And then everybody looks at you
and they're like, fucking idiot.
Should have just held onto the pole.
All right, I don't want.
This person's freaking me out.
I did that as a kid.
Look out the window.
It's so dark, I can't even see the street.
I knew he was going to do that.
I was ready for it.
I was like, oh dude, look out the window, okay.
I fucking knew that was going to happen.
I knew it.
I was waiting for it for the whole time he was on the bus.
May I sit beside you?
There's plenty of other seats,
so I don't see why you would need to do that.
May I, may I sit beside you?
Are you deaf?
Do I need to get the driver to throw you off?
You're going to die tonight.
What?
I've seen it.
Tonight is your last night on earth.
You are walking straight into your doom.
Can't you see that?
You and that child inside you.
How did you?
You will be found just like all the others.
Ripped open, your insides displayed
for all the angels above to look down and see.
Oh yes, of that I am certain.
Please just stop talking.
May I sit beside you?
All right miss, this is your stop.
I mean, so where you put the fucking,
just fucking grab him by the neck.
Just grab him.
Just fucking go bang into the back of the over here
and be like, what are you threatening me?
What's how we tell what's happening here?
Get his ass.
Yeah, you mean it's something like, I don't know, man.
I'm just like, you kind of be like, oh, what's,
let's go.
You know what I mean?
Like go.
Like, what's that?
There's lights or something, grab.
No noise gate, so loud.
I told you.
It's not that bad.
That guy was fucking scary.
I'm scared, please turn it off.
This is what we're here for.
Good job, you completed the tutorial in one hour.
No, don't be a liar.
Don't be a liar.
That's what you're doing, you're lying.
The first 30 minutes of the stream
was me talking about announcements,
talking about some changes that I'm gonna be making.
We sat there for about 30 minutes.
Then I did the soy face thing.
That was about 15 minutes.
So no, that's you being a liar
and I don't appreciate that very much.
It's been about 15 to 16 minutes
of actual in-game video game time.
Laundromat.
Yes, what is it?
Oh, are you all really open all night?
We're open all night, but I take my naps at midnight.
So you better not need anything after that.
Oh, okay.
I'll be sure not to need anything.
Yeah, we'll see.
Need a game toy here?
Press tab to equip and un-equip your inventory.
I'll bring it back before I leave.
It'll be a long night, so I might need it.
Game toy, can I play it?
Whoa, okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Fork sees revenge.
Left mouse button to start the game.
What do I do?
How do I, what do I do?
How do I control the game?
What the fuck, did I just kill somebody?
Am I doing this right?
Should I not be doing that?
All right, what if I avoid?
I can't, I have to.
Score one.
Okay, I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it.
How do I win?
All right, I gotta pay attention to the screen.
What do I need to win?
The song is really good.
Yeah, it's a pretty good song.
Oh, I'm done.
That's stupid.
All right, do I actually have to do this?
You have to get to 100.
Okay, get that out of here.
All right, so I'm just gonna do my laundry.
Which one should I use?
Those are dryers.
Soap dispenser.
Brought my own soap.
Laundry cot.
Coffee.
A patron.
Laundry down the road.
This place is the only one open when I get off work.
Was a real pain when the first one burnt down.
First one?
You knew around here?
Yeah, this place used to be next door years ago.
But there was a big fire.
I don't think they ever found out exactly what caused it.
That sounds awful.
Girl died in that fire too.
An employee.
I don't like to spread rumors, but.
Pretty mysterious.
The way she died, I mean.
It wasn't a fire that started quickly.
She should have had plenty of time to get out.
But she was found in the office.
It was me that died in the fire.
This is like a whole weird Silent Hill type thing
where it's me that died in the fire.
I heard they were close to opening up
a murder investigation.
Right.
That a detective thought the girl was locked in.
Could be.
She decided to drop it when nobody came up.
You know, cops.
Lazy sons of bitches.
As a fellow writer, you know, you can,
as a fellow writer, when you start to see
the pieces come together in the intro
or what could be the outro,
I can kind of see it from a pretty long way away.
As a fellow writer, of course.
Well, if that's true, it does sound pretty suspect.
Sure does.
Feels like it got swept under the rug pretty quick.
What with the womb ripper coming around
and butchering those women.
That has all the headlines these days.
Okay.
So, all right.
So let me just do my laundry.
Pick up urban legends one.
All right.
That was pretty good.
What happened though?
I couldn't really tell.
Yes, what is it?
Oh, um.
We're up on.
Oh yeah.
So how do I do laundry?
Dryers, washers.
Okay.
Where do I, how do I use one?
Washers, washers, washers.
Oh, okay.
This one's up.
I need to get some change first.
Where's the change?
Change machine?
What do I make change?
Yes, what is.
Oh, um.
We're up.
Oh yeah.
Where do I make change?
The vending machine?
Isn't there usually a thing to do it with?
Where is it?
Magazines.
Where's the change machine?
You put the dollar in and you get the arcade tokens.
You need to look in your purse.
Explore, you stooge.
I still fucking so pissed off
that they're not in Fortnite.
Yeah.
The other day they added to Fortnite in the last two weeks.
And you tell me that the three stooges
could not have been a possibility.
Please.
In fact, it's gonna, it's going to fucking happen.
It will happen.
It's just not gonna happen on our timetable.
Aren't they adding, aren't they adding like obi-wan Kenobi?
Three stooges is too,
Pac-Man?
Pac-Man, how is Pac-Man not Boomer?
All right.
Where do I make change?
That's fucking weird.
Oh my God.
Why is it all the way over here?
What a terribly designed place.
Pac-Man's coming next week.
They're gonna add all the Wizard of Oz characters.
Dorothy, Tin Man, the Tiger, the Scarecrow.
They're gonna add,
there was gonna be a Wizard of Oz update.
They're gonna add, okay.
They're gonna be,
I feel so pissed off about this.
I'm gonna have like FOMO on this.
Because if I don't make a bet here
and they add the Wizard of Oz characters like in a year,
I'm gonna be pissed
because I could have told you I was right.
You know what I mean?
Like I didn't say that.
I was, I may have started to say it, but I didn't say it.
Take a look at the other stores and the plaza.
How much are you gonna put up?
There's no way they're gonna add the Wizard of Oz.
What about like Willy Wonka, right?
Also, I don't know why I'm attributing,
fuck, this is what's happening.
I am attributing all the slot machines in the casino
with what is popular with the Fortnite kids,
which is completely inaccurate.
Willy Wonka slot machines are literally fucking everywhere.
Wizard of Oz slot machines everywhere.
The three stooges have a bunch of slot machines.
I'm doing this wrong.
I still think, sounds like a child crying,
but I don't think it's a kid.
Shoes.
That's cause boomers play slot machines
and zoomers bet on Fortnite skins.
Just wait, I am, are you ready?
Listen to me.
You can, in a hundred years,
you can go back and watch this clip.
They are going to have to pivot soon
in these Vegas casinos
because all the Wizard of Oz slot machines
are not gonna do very well when the zoomers are like,
no, no, no, no, I want, where's my Fortnite machine?
There's gonna be Fortnite machines.
There's gonna be video game, like zoomer type machines.
There's not, I don't think,
I think slot machines might be replaced, but like skins.
You sit down and you like pull the machine.
It's like the skin, like a box opening.
I think, I don't know in like the next 50 years or so,
if people are gonna care that much about spinning a slot,
just in making, oh, like I hit money.
I don't think so.
I don't think the younger generation cares that much.
I think like Fortnite skins might be more,
or some type of video game thing.
A Morbius slot machine.
I'd play it.
I'd never even seen the movie.
I would just sit there and like laugh.
Morbius slots.
Customer, looking for a TV, toaster?
Sorry, I'm just browsing.
What kind of person just browses the appliance stores
at this time of night?
I don't know if I, I mean, anytime I go to like a Best Buy,
I always just end up walking around the washer
and dryers and stoves and just go, oh, that's nice.
I'm never gonna buy one of those,
but you kind of just walk around and just open up the lid,
turn the dial.
That's it.
I'm just waiting on my laundry.
Well, then why don't you just buy a washer and dry here?
We have the newest models at the lowest prices.
That's such a stoner thing to do.
I've never heard of a stoner that's like,
yo, bro, let's go look at the washing machines
at Best Buy, dude.
No, it's like, I've been abducted by aliens
and like, I think aliens exist.
And like, I think the aliens are all,
are putting the TV shows on the TV stations.
That's like a, I'm high conversation.
I'm a fan, but I feel like you're the newest thing
in the store.
That's meth.
Well, thank you.
You take pride in my appearance.
Oh, wait, question marks.
What are you talking about?
You talk about like weird existential shit when you're high.
Not, I want to go look at Best Buy washing machines.
Now, when you get high, you think about,
are all my friends actors?
You know what I mean?
Not, oh, I want to go look at the washing machine.
Customer, looking for a TV, toaster.
What are you talking about?
I'm not saying you really think that.
You sit there in the couch and you go,
holy shit, what if like, we're all actors?
You guys don't have those gone, what?
I don't, I've never gotten high and gone,
everybody's an actor.
No, I've got, I'm go, man, wouldn't it be crazy
if everybody was an actor?
Sorry, I'm just browsing.
You're delusional.
I keep talking to this person.
Get away from me.
Okay, what do you got here?
TV?
Oh, look, drying machine.
Oh, wow, that could fit probably like two, three loads.
Cool.
No, you know, I'm not a big fan of the front loaders.
I'm not a front loader guy, no, not really, no.
Oven, stereo, radio, can I,
what am I supposed to do here?
A lock box.
I need a code to go in it.
Okay, I need a code for the lock box.
Okay, well, goodbye.
I need a code for the lock box.
Pizza.
Sorry, didn't see you there.
What time is it?
Can I get you anything?
No, thanks.
I'm just killing time until my laundry next door is done.
Well, you're out. How about it was supposed to be late?
Just a heads up, we're closing soon.
Feel free to hang out until then, though.
Ask for pizza?
What do you got here?
They're about to close, so the pizza is pretty stale now.
That's not what I asked.
I'm fine, that's all right.
Soda fountain, trash can.
Any codes in here?
This is, what is this?
Sin eater.
I knew the whole thing.
I did not realize that was gonna be that flashing.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was gonna be,
I thought it was gonna be colors.
I didn't know it was gonna be black and white.
I'm really sorry.
I thought it was gonna be like this one.
Like, look, that's not a problem doing it like this.
I didn't know it was gonna be black and white.
I'm really sorry.
That actually, I didn't know it was gonna be that painful.
I'm actually really sorry.
I was trying to inhale the magazine.
I just got flash-banked.
What the fuck is this?
Okay, guys, that's a dick.
Okay, well, sorry.
That's back-to-back, kind of.
I didn't mean to do that.
I thought that was not gonna be as flashing,
and then you got flashed anyways a few moments later.
So I'm really sorry about that, back-to-back.
Nobody else is gonna, okay, very sorry.
Can I do anything else in here?
I get nothing.
Well, you're out.
No pizza, vending machine, no.
You flash-banked your audience
and then showed him a dick, great start.
Shit, I wanna be more careful with that.
I didn't know.
I actually am annoyed that I just did that.
All right, so where are we going now?
Peapaws?
No refunds or exchanges, all sales final.
Peapaw.
Can I help you?
Looking for anything specific?
Looking for something specific?
You have a great day now.
A movie?
A video game?
Fish?
No, just browsing, thanks.
Let me know if you need any help.
And don't you even think about stealing anything?
I have eyes everywhere.
Wouldn't dream of it.
You have quite an assortment of-
It's Peapaws.
I'm Peapaw.
It's my store.
PeaPants.
Right.
Am I allowed to tell the story of PeaPants?
I mean, I tell it like once every two years,
but I feel like we have a lot more viewers here now.
Can I just do your TLDR?
What is that?
Read Reapers, what?
No, I'm not doing this.
I mean, this is cool.
This is, I mean, this is cool.
They got like these comics in here.
This is cool.
They got comic books you can read.
Okay, well, we're gonna have,
we're gonna just go like this for now.
We're gonna go like this.
We're just gonna get rid of those.
Okay, cool.
There's probably an item in here.
Or no, tapes.
Okay, get it.
I'm putting my hand up over this screen.
What am I doing?
What?
I can't put my hand up on,
I just put my hand up to block it
like you were behind me.
Hold on.
What the fuck?
Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
Does that, do I need to be in here for anything?
I swear to God, there's probably something in here
that I need to get.
Okay, okay.
I was looking.
That's not what you wanna have happen
coming out of this room.
This is like, you put the hat down,
and you go like this, and you're like.
No, hey, how are ya?
You're not stealing anything?
No.
My apologies.
My friend was making a joke about,
let's go into the porn section,
and it was funny, it was like,
you have one of these?
That's crazy.
I was just saying,
I couldn't believe you actually had one of these.
This is crazy.
Like, what the fuck?
I was going into it, like, that's funny.
Should I buy a gumball?
Ooh, games.
The Master system is out now.
This is still my favorite.
Okay, I don't think I,
my laundry has probably been done for an hour.
What am I doing still here?
Oh, the story of pee pants, right.
Okay.
So, Burger Boy and I used to play Smite all the time,
and we would just, you know,
you'd make the,
I think it was like a party or something.
You had to like join with a password or something,
whatever it was.
So, we would be playing games,
and we'd be making the,
yeah, Smite, okay, whatever, fine.
You batch-ass me all you want.
So, we were in the,
essentially, I was being told,
hey, here's the password to get into the lobby,
so then we can queue up together or whatever it was.
So, he gives me the password.
He's like, hey, this is it,
the password is pee pants.
And I was like, okay, fine.
So, I'm like, pee pants.
It doesn't work.
So, the password is incorrect.
I say, hey, dude, the password is incorrect.
This doesn't, there's no,
it's not pee pants.
And Burger Boy looks at me and he just goes,
yeah, it is.
By the way, Burger Boy was high.
He was like as high as a kite.
And he's sitting there going, it's pee pants, dude.
I was like, Burger Boy, it's not.
Is there a space?
Is it like pee space pants?
No, it's just no spaces, no capitals, pee pants.
I'm just like, I keep typing that, it's not it.
And me and him get into an argument
about how he thinks I'm fucking with him
because it's pee pants and you're not doing it
and this is annoying and I wanna play.
So, eventually, finally, after probably
at least three to five straight minutes
of being annoyed with each other,
I go, how are you spelling this?
And I walk over and I show him what I'm typing
and he's like, what?
This not, he's like, this, pee pants.
That's how we thought it was spelled.
He thought it was P-A-N-C-E in his like high weed brain.
So, we were actually in a pretty,
it was, I was not, we were both pretty annoyed
and he was spelling it P-A-N-C-E
and that's how we thought pants was spelled in that moment.
And then, finally, he sat there
and he was just like laughing his ass off
and then pee pants just became a verb
that we just started using.
We would call each other that
if we had like a stupid moment.
It'd be like, oh, hey, yeah, hey, pee pants.
Oh, come on, pee pants.
Like, we just started calling each other that.
We started using it as a verb and stuff.
Oh, dude, that's, you're a wicked pee pants right now.
Oh, yeah, okay, yeah.
It was fun.
Using it as a noun, verb.
We pretty much used it as,
we used to use random words, kind of like smurfs.
We'd replace them as nouns and verbs
and it was just a smurf language.
It was weird.
We used to do it all the time with tons of stuff.
Who the fuck is Burger Boy?
Oh, that's a new viewers.
Okay, so I think I'm ready.
Okay, I thought someone was coming to get me.
Why is he called Burger Boy though?
I don't know.
Maybe it has something to do with the fact
that he used to bring double cheeseburgers
into the movie theater.
Like they were popcorn.
Like a bag of at least four to six of them
and eat them for the movie.
That might have had something to do with it.
Did I get the laundry?
You haven't said that.
How do I use the dryers?
Are these washers?
Bathroom key?
That's old lore.
Oh yeah, that's, I mean,
I know I've told that story before.
Okay, so go to the bathroom.
You've told the pee pants stream a bunch of times too.
Oh yeah.
Do you guys still talk?
Yeah, from time to time.
I think he's doing all right.
Just living on the West Coast.
A lot of people that I would talk to on a regular basis.
Obviously I live in Vegas, right?
But yeah, I think he's doing pretty good.
Last time I talked to him.
Don't I have the key?
God damn it.
Now I'm gonna read that.
Six, seven, five, eight.
This might be fun to call if I get bored.
There's a phone in the lobby.
Really?
Wait, why did I go in here?
There's something I need?
Police report.
Police report that details a suspect named Lewis Kennedy.
This is just for public intoxication,
but that name keeps popping up.
Wonder if I can find out more about him.
Bring this to the people and see if they have anything
to say about it.
Do something funny.
Your dog is crying.
Why does your dog care if I make a joke or not?
Oh my God, there's somebody in here.
Oh my God.
Is there an item I need over here or anything?
Dude, okay.
This is probably something I need right here.
Nothing?
Okay, goodbye.
What is, who's that?
What happened?
I feel like I was supposed to be scared.
I was like, why is there a naked guy?
What happened?
I just turned the quarter
and I thought there was a naked person
so I just went like this
and then I was supposed to get jump scared, I think.
Who put this here?
I don't know.
Did you do that?
Doing the late night wash too.
Yeah, I work night shift at the factory down the road.
This place is the only one open.
Yeah, we know, we know, we know, we know, we know,
we know, we know, we know, we know, we know.
Mysterious.
Doing the late night wash.
The first one, that's good, but what?
Okay, don't click again.
Do you know anything about this?
No, not these comic books.
This.
Don't know how you got that, but yeah, I knew Louis.
He owned the old laundromat that burnt down.
We were buds, but he disappeared one day.
It's the aliens, I tell ya.
Louis is looking down on us poor schmucks right now
from the cosmos.
Do you know anything about this?
Shows him a porno mag.
So I just gotta show this to people in the town
that sounds like you.
Call that number.
Don't tell me what to do.
Okay, where's the phone?
Oh, what?
The phone is ringing.
You will be connected to the girl
of your wildest fantasies for 63 seconds.
Well, hey there, stud.
All right, for one second,
one second I thought she said 63 seconds
in English accent.
Not 63 seconds, 63.
You'll be connected for 63 seconds.
I was like, what?
Oh, okay, that's a weird number.
And then I read it.
Cool, no?
I mean, hey there.
I'm so glad you called.
It's been so lonely over here.
Been thinking about your big cut.
Wait.
Damn it, I'm sorry.
This is my first night on the job.
I don't think it's for me.
That's okay.
I didn't even know what this number was for.
I just called for cakes.
The phone rang.
Oh, it's been one night,
but I've had my fair share of creeps.
Didn't the phone ring?
I didn't call.
I answered the phone.
A person just dials a random phone number
at this time of night.
A burnt out college student
who's waiting for on-
I didn't make any phone calls.
Go home and get some sleep.
Those places are still open at this time of night?
Not just this one a little out of town.
Wait, in that plaza with the pizza palace?
Oh, that one.
Hey, you really shouldn't be out over there
this late at night,
not with the womb ripper at large.
I remember,
do you guys remember the commercials late at night on TV
for these lines that were 1-900 numbers?
It's like, call now
and talk to the hardest of all of us, right?
Now, do you remember those?
And it was always like two or three dollars a minute.
I remember just sitting there going,
I wonder,
do they like try to keep people on the phone?
And the more that I thought about it is like,
oh, I'm trying to think of ways
if you would keep somebody on the phone
for two dollars a minute.
And one of the things I was thinking of was,
oh yeah, it would be so sexy
if we played a full game of Monopoly over the phone.
Oh, I would think that was so hot.
Yeah, you do?
Yeah, yeah.
That'd be like,
oh, you know,
if we could play Risk, that would be fantastic.
Just gave them there.
They were always so weird, though.
I remember just being,
because I was an infomercial aficionado, right?
We all know that.
But in between those,
or on random channels at the past 12, 1 a.m.,
you'd get those ads all the time.
You called them.
Do you guys really think,
so I'm gonna call and have sent to my parents' house?
Huh?
I wasn't even fucking old enough
to make these phone calls, I don't think.
Why would I, what are you talking about?
I am in no way going to have my mother or father back then
be like, why is there,
why is there all this shit here?
Why would there, I never thought they were worth it.
I was like, I'm not gonna call these.
I'm like, I don't know, I don't wanna do that.
That's weird.
He's offended.
What an obvious lie.
The 30 second call the 1-900 number
that we're just talking, taking the piss on right now.
You think I was calling it every day?
You're weirdly defensive about this.
I have not called one of these numbers.
I was with one eye open like this.
What's that on TV?
I don't fucking care.
Where's Kathy Mitchell?
Right, no.
No.
Why do I do this to myself?
Why do I do this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Listen to me.
I mean, infomercials, infomercials, infomercials,
infomercials, I wanted to watch infomercials,
call fucking, okay.
All right, that's enough.
Why are you doing this to me?
That's enough, that's enough.
There's some things that the newspapers don't talk about.
There's things to get out of.
Look at how red I am.
I'm like embarrassed.
I don't want anybody to think this.
There's more to it than just talking and killing.
Fuck.
It's a real psychopath
and you are right in the middle of its hunting grounds.
Do you understand? Shit, shit.
You need to take your laundry right now
and get out of there as fast as you can.
That's like embarrassing.
What is going on in this dialogue?
It's the same reason why hotels,
when they had all the porn in the hotel rooms.
I didn't want to check out of a hotel
and walk up to the person at the checkout counter
and, sir, would you like a receipt?
No, no, no.
Don't look at the receipt.
Just, you know what?
Here's $200 cash.
I don't want you to print the receipt.
I don't want you to look at the receipt.
Can you drag the receipt into the recycling bin right now?
I'll give you $200 right now.
Sir, it says you only have about $42 in charges.
No, just don't open it.
And here's $200 cash.
Don't look at the receipt.
Don't look at it.
I don't know.
I don't want to talk to somebody and be like,
oh, hey, by the way,
oh, what do we have with these charges?
Some incidental charges to the room.
No.
So you bought it.
No, I didn't.
I'm just saying.
I didn't want to have anybody.
You're making it worse.
This is a self-report.
No, it's not.
I'm watching porn in a hotel room.
No, I just want to sleep in the hotel room.
You know what I mean?
I don't want to do it.
No.
I don't want to sit there and just sit there and be like,
all right, here we go.
No.
Jerma, stop.
You need to act cool.
Act cool.
You got to act cool.
All right, all right.
I'll act cool.
All right, I'll act cool.
Okay.
Just be cool.
Be cool.
It's not a big deal.
Whatever.
Be cool.
This is actually so bad.
No, it's not.
We made a couple of comments
about late night telephone sex lines
and all of a sudden I buy porn every time I go to the hotel.
That's you doing that.
That's you putting that on me.
We never talked about that.
We literally never talked about that.
I made a quick comment about this
and it became literally what I do every day.
Lewis Kennedy.
Jerma watches porn and gets naked.
Yeah.
No, no.
I get naked because I have to go take a shower and get naked.
I'm done with this conversation.
Put it in emote only mode right now.
Put it in emote only mode.
I demand emote only mode right now.
Emotes only for an hour.
Lewis Kennedy.
All right.
You never heard of Lewis Kennedy.
That's fine.
Anybody else here?
Can I play this?
You look just like her.
Who?
Same eyes.
I'm telling you it's me.
Same hair.
It's me.
She used to be so beautiful,
but I've lost her.
It's been so long now.
Oh, did you know one of the girls
who went missing around here, ma'am?
Oh, and by the way, let me just make this really clear.
It's 2022.
If you've consumed pornographic material,
this isn't like 1902 where it's like,
oh no, nobody's consumed, how dare you, the devil.
Now, who really gives a shit?
Who really gives a shit?
If you watch porn movies in the hotel room,
I don't care.
Who cares?
I don't give a shit if you're watching porn
in your hotel room, but what the fuck do I care?
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm glad that got sniped, and I'm glad it did.
My fingers are so, ugh.
I'm going to take it off of emote-only mode in 10 seconds.
I want strict behavior.
Doing a late night walk.
First one.
That's girl, but what?
I don't know if-
Okay, we want behavior.
I want you on your best behavior.
There could be a sponsor watching.
You never know.
How would you, there could be somebody from, I don't know.
You never know, I gotta be careful.
We'll talk about that anymore.
All right, so is my clothes done?
I just keep getting derailed.
I think this game is like a 40 minute experience,
and I just keep getting so derailed.
What about the, maybe P-Paw?
Yeah, I'll go talk to P-Paw.
Old Louis was a real son of a bitch.
Had a real eye for the younger girls he did.
Don't mean to gossip, but I have it on good authority.
He was the one who knocked up that poor girl
who worked for him.
Can't remember her name,
but between that scandal, the fire,
and then the disappearances,
I would say all the details will never be known.
Okay, I don't know why.
I just thought it would be like kind of funny.
Remember Supermarket Sweep?
Imagine they did like a supermarket sweep type thing
with like a video store.
And it was the person, the contestant got to the end.
It was like, okay, you gotta go through each aisle
and you gotta get as many DVDs as you want.
Any shelf, anything that you care about, right?
And the music starts and it's like,
all right, let's go.
They fucking sprint into this room
and just start sliding their hand into the cart.
Just filling it with all these porns.
And they don't even touch anything else.
And after five straight minutes, they come out of here
with like a cart full of just porn DVDs.
And everyone just sitting there like,
what the fuck?
Don't go in there.
I, whatever.
He looks like a shrimp.
Me?
Like, wait, the animal, the shrimp.
What does the shrimp's face look like?
There's blood on this?
Gross, okay.
Can I just read you a portion of my modding chat?
This is from VR Josh.
This is very important.
Thumbs up.
Emote only mode enabled.
I'm not gonna read that one, next one.
I'm ready, LOL.
Okay, emote only coming off.
I'm gonna block the word porn.
Nevermind.
They're trying.
They're trying, guys.
Did I already show this?
Did I already show you this?
That is, but he sounds like a real asshole to me.
Okay.
I think that's pretty much it.
There's nobody else to talk to, right?
Is there another store over here?
What is the car that was in front of the bus stop?
Yeah, that's the bus stop car.
Do I look like a shrimp?
Let me see.
What does a shrimp look like?
I know what they look like, but do I look a little bit?
What animal do I look like?
All right, mods, run a poll.
I want you to run a poll
and I want you to put 10 of sort of the most iconic animals.
I don't want people to vote
on what animal they think I look like.
I need a code for that lock box.
Can I break this?
What do I do with this doll head?
Polls only have five options.
Oh, nevermind.
So what do I do?
Is my clothes not done drying yet?
Maybe they are.
No, they're not done.
Oh, there it is.
What the hell?
These clothes are still wet.
This machine must be broken,
but those were my last quarters.
Where's that employee?
Excuse me.
Where are you?
Hello?
Get up.
There's blood.
What are you doing in here?
Doing a late night wash.
Yeah.
First one.
That's girl.
But what?
I heard.
Well.
What do you have to say about this?
Not my kind of doll, if you know what I mean.
You read these?
I don't need to ask him about this.
Okay.
So what's going on?
What?
Oh, it's the employee.
He's been ripped to shreds.
I need to call the police.
Shit.
You watched porn at the Holiday Inn and got caught.
That's very specific.
Why are you still on that?
Hello?
Somebody just fell from the ceiling.
You need to send someone now.
I'm at the...
Somebody fell from the ceiling covered in blood
and they were like ripped up.
And you're still on the dude you got caught
at the Holiday Inn back a year or two ago or something.
We're trying to play a game.
Shit.
20 minutes later.
Dispatch said they got a call coming from out here,
but it's strange.
Don't give them specific timeframes.
I'm just, I'm getting in their mindset.
I can't seem to be able to find anyone.
Where is this person talking?
There's no body in here?
What?
They don't know.
What do you mean?
I'd be a rodent.
I don't know if I'd be a rodent.
I think I'm more of a lion.
Is that someone crying?
It sounds like it's coming from that office
by the pizza place.
Well, you're a police officer.
Go look.
I hate this.
Go look in there.
All I have is I have a key for a weapon.
I'm the police officer.
What are you?
Oh, I'm the officer.
Oh.
The office by the pizza place?
Oh, it's just somebody that has to do the taxes.
Yeah, I get upset every fucking April 10th as well.
Is anyone there?
That was a boomer joke.
That's fine.
This is the police.
If anyone is there, then come out now.
There's something wrong here.
Investigate thoroughly.
Oh, God.
Business plan, computer, doesn't look suspicious.
Binders, copy machine, water cooler.
The TV got worse.
It's hard to see.
Fuck off.
If you, I found if you sniff in,
when you think a jump scare is gonna happen,
it scares you less.
Yeah.
How many bolts do I have?
An infinite amount.
Good.
Office key.
That's so bad.
I wanna press G and throw a grenade down the hall.
Get the key.
Get the key out, man.
Where's my key?
I got an office key.
Officer.
Oh, that's an office, Burton.
Burton's office.
Locked.
I can find a key.
What is this?
Is that where I can't, how do I get it?
The door is stuck.
Why do I get my key out?
Turn on a flashlight?
What do you mean turn?
I don't, I need, where's my key?
I just picked one up.
Door is stuck.
But I got a key to the office, didn't I?
Locked.
It's tab, isn't it?
There's no scroll.
Where do I get it?
Press I.
I picked it up, didn't I?
I don't get it.
Yeah, I have it.
What is it?
Look at the fire extinguisher.
Where, I don't get it.
Press one, two, three, four.
Press the key button.
Usually I just hit tab and I have an inventory.
I don't understand what's happening here.
It's one.
It's not one.
It even says I need a key.
Is it bugged?
Right click.
Locked.
What the fuck?
Scroll with the gun out.
Oh, come on, Gwyn.
What?
Oh my God.
You gotta help me.
Slow down.
It's okay.
Just follow me.
Fire!
What happened?
What?
Okay, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I didn't mean to do that.
I'm too jumpy today.
I wanna say at this point, I don't give a shit.
I'm gonna turn the corner and...
Yeah.
I don't care.
I'm gonna turn the corner.
Someone's gonna go, wait!
And I'm gonna...
You know what I mean?
In those old like shooter games.
What are you talking about?
I didn't get them.
I was shooting every two steps.
And the one step that I don't shoot, I get killed.
No one's coming.
Maybe I can make a run for it.
Fucking smashing.
In that receipt.
It's a receipt for a building repair company.
Looks like they had to repair one of the walls in the...
Oh.
Okay.
I can smash the wall with a hammer.
Without a doubt.
God damn it.
My clothes done.
What the fuck are you doing?
What?
Cradle at baby is drowsing.
Who is doing that?
Are they in the washing machine?
Discord Mike?
I don't know.
We're just gonna get out of here quick.
There's a door behind here.
Get out, get out, get out, get out.
Grenade.
No.
Do I hide?
Do I, where do I go?
Do I hide in here?
An event?
Leave.
No!
Fuck you.
Newspaper.
Main suspect in police investigation disappears.
45 year old Lewis Kennedy has gone missing.
The top suspect in the grisly crime
of an arson alleged kidnapping.
What the fuck?
Sources say that Kennedy had been under surveillance
for a few weeks and at some point of the course
of last night had broken contact with officers.
That was a centipede scream?
The audio did something really weird to your voice.
Can I hear, let me hear it.
Take less cocaine next time.
Let me hear this.
Let me see, I need to know what this sounds like.
How bad does it sound?
That's so weird.
Fuck, it sounds like it's in a different room.
So what doesn't sound like that right now?
It's only when I get loud?
It sounds like I have like,
it sounds like I'm yelling into my hands.
It doesn't sound like that right now, right?
It sounds like a Diablo II death sound.
It really does.
It sounds like a fucking Diablo II death.
But what's missing is me slamming the desk
and going, what the fuck, dude?
It's trying to filter out anything
that it's a noise that humans don't normally make.
I don't know, I try to fix it,
but I don't know what the fuck is going on there, man.
That's so fucking dumb.
Sounds like an old Mortal Kombat attack.
It does, it really does.
Like Mortal Kombat on the Sega Genesis.
Okay, okay, I'm gonna fucking freak out.
AC unit, it won't open.
Flashlight, how do I turn it on?
F for flashlight?
Oh, hey, fuck, hey, I don't wanna look this way.
I wanna run away.
It won't budge, what do you mean it won't budge?
Hide somewhere, hide in the filing cabinet or something.
Hide in the filing cabinet.
Hide over here.
Go this way, turn on the flashlight.
Yikes.
Oh, like, oh, no.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, a scalpel.
I thought that was my face.
I thought that was an emote of my face.
I know I won't be getting out of here alive.
That psychopath, it kills women like me.
I've heard at least three of those brought here and killed.
Peeking through the cracks I saw
that it creates these masks out of skin.
Whoa, I don't know what kind of game it's wanting to play.
I think my time is up.
It made me swallow a key,
a key that I think would get me out of here,
but I have a feeling it won't let me live long enough
to use it.
I'll be struggling butchered like the rest.
Ah, where are you?
I know that this is this person over here.
This is gonna burn me.
Yeah, you, I got a scalpel and I got, there's a key.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I got a key to get out of here.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Give me that key.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Just, I'm gonna hold this out and run.
Oh, he's gonna be in this door.
He's gonna break through this door.
I know it.
He's gonna break through the door.
He's gonna, he's gonna break out the door.
Wrong key.
Is that, who's that?
Corpse.
Corpse, been here for years.
There's a wallet sticking out of his pocket.
Who is it?
What?
The driver's license belongs to Lewis Kennedy.
This doesn't make any sense.
I need to get out of here and call the police.
There's a, what?
No, I don't wanna get out of here.
How do I get out of here?
Oh, oh, person, Scoob.
Rocky, we need to get out of here.
Like, I agree, Scoob.
Let's skedaddle.
Rocky, we need to get out of here.
Find the child.
Oh, by the way, speaking of those two,
I have access to the Multiversus Early Alpha.
I was thinking about playing it on stream at some point.
Just letting you know.
I have access to it and that could be pretty fun
if we were to do it eventually.
Can I go through here?
I need to get this lock off.
What was that?
I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
What was that?
Ammo.
I have ammo?
Okay, I've got ammo.
I don't know.
You're gonna be right here, aren't you?
Wait!
Gun.
How many bullets does this have?
I'm afraid to shoot it.
How do I turn the flashlight on?
It's so hard to see.
Oh, there's so many warships.
Gosh, there's so many washing machines down here, Mickey.
Of course there is, Goofy.
That's where they do their laundry.
That was a bad bit.
I'm not doing a bit.
Come out, you asshole.
I'm ready for you.
Why would you do that?
Don't say that.
You need to...
Actually, you know what?
This is what I'd do.
I'd say, like, come get me, motherfucker.
Like, I'm here, I'm waiting for you.
And then I would throw something over there
and be like, ow, my knee, ow!
I'd be like, ow, my knee!
And then they'd think, holy shit,
he must have fallen down and gotten hit.
And then he'd go on over there.
There's a person right there.
Oh!
Where's my flashlight?
Oh my God, I can't see anything.
Oh my God, I can't see.
Whoa!
That was like, that sounds like my mic.
Why can't I move?
All right, I'm just gonna...
What the...
Oh!
What the fuck, dude?
What's wrong with my mic?
What are you guys talking about?
Something wrong with my mic?
It's fucked up?
What's wrong?
What the fuck?
This game's not even fucking scary.
It's fucking easy.
That'll make sense now.
Lewis Kennedy wasn't killing all those women.
You sound all muffled.
I don't know why.
I think the microphone is freaking out
when I hit a certain level,
because I sound completely normal right now.
But when I get to a certain audio level,
it just muffles me and puts a wall in front of my face.
The mic keeps freaking out.
Is it the noise gate?
I don't think it's on.
Your mic is trying to smother you
when you get really loud.
Scream loud right now.
Actually, let's find the level, right?
So like...
Were those all fine?
Were those fine?
Yeah.
Okay, so...
What happened?
What happened to the end there?
That was fine too.
Weird.
I don't know.
I have to mess with some of the settings.
She must have lost her baby though.
With almost being killed, losing her child,
and being terribly burned.
Completely snapped.
Maybe loud, quick loud sounds freak it out.
I think she has sudden loud sounds.
That's like half my fucking content.
She killed Louis,
and then set her sights on killing others
who had something she didn't.
God.
That was intense.
That was blood wash.
Isn't the barf drinker?
It does kind of look like the barf drinker.
It turns into a McDonald's mic.
Eventually, yeah.
It does.
That was pretty good.
That was good.
That was scary, interesting, creepy.
I thought that was cool.
Are you gonna play multiverses?
I mean, yeah.
Eventually.
Wait for the end.
I'm not gonna skip the after credits.
Don't act like you were paying attention.
I was, what do you mean?
Of course I was.
What's next after this?
Hold on a minute, that's really cool.
So those were custom-made comic books for this game.
Is that what I'm understanding?
That's pretty cool.
Hold on.
Well, I was pretty upset to be woken up
so late for an impromptu autopsy,
but when they told me that it was the actual womb ripper,
well, I got down here as soon as I could.
I can't believe that it turned out to be Samantha Rhodes,
who'd gone missing and was presumed dead years ago.
So what I did is I do what I do
with all of these potential serial killer maniacs.
I stand across the room first,
even though they're supposed to be dead,
and I throw a fucking brick
as fast and as hard as I can at their head
to make sure that they're not gonna get up and scare me
and grab me and stab me with a knife.
The fuse box is down the hall.
Yeah, great.
I wonder what happens here.
You should have threw the brick.
I mean, like, honestly, it's like, do we need to,
just, mm-mm.
Always keep a brick with your, no.
God damn it, I thought it was over.
Shut the fuck up.
No, don't.
What the, she's gone.
I have to get out of here.
Cause of death, multiple gunshot wounds.
That's the official cause of death,
but Jesus Christ, I don't even understand
how she was still alive in the first place.
I took so many shots to bring her down.
Most of these look fatal on first glimpse to me.
Guess we'll dig in to find out more.
I, okay, well, let's go.
Oh, how does that, done.
I'm sorry, but I'm just gonna go right here, right there.
Just bang.
You wanna see a fucking, that's fun.
You should play chess.
Why would I ever play chess?
I'm never gonna play chess.
I, it's too, the game is too high brain for me.
It's too slow, I need it to be.
All right, if there was chess,
where after every move, we got to watch a family guy clip.
That's just, it just happened.
Then okay, I'd play it.
Make the, make a family guy chess.
And every time I move Peter Griffin,
he says just a random audio clip from the show.
It's very clear that they didn't record any new dialogue.
You move Peter.
Oh, holy crap, Lois.
So you didn't record any new audio for this.
Stewie gets moved, and Stewie just says,
you can tell he's talking to somebody
during one of the episodes,
but it has nothing to do with chess.
He's on to something.
No, they know that, that wouldn't happen.
It wouldn't be, oh, look at me, I'm the king, Lois.
No, no, no, no, no.
It would be like a specific, oh, wow.
I can't believe I became mayor.
Like, what does that have to do with chess?
All right, we're gonna go on, we're gonna move on.
Play checkers, I'm not gonna play checkers.
All right, I'm gonna take a quick break.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna pee, I'm gonna refill this drink,
and we're gonna play Murder House.
That's what's on tap next.
See you guys in about, I wanna say two minutes,
maybe a little less.
We'll find out.
See you in just a moment.
Oops, hold on, let me fix it.