My gun is jammed again. Good. Get out and fix it. I don't know how to do that. Get out on the plane.
Wait climb out of the plane? Yes. Climb out of the plane and like get a broom.
Get a broom is going to fix the gun jam? Well I assume it's getting jammed so much because you have to state your plane.
Alright, you just like went robot. I have no idea what you said.
Gun is jammed again. Fuck. Can my friend, Star, please play with me?
I have one minute remaining on this patch. It is 47.7 megabyte training. And then I can get into the war. Thunder.
Can my like friend not go robot like all the fucking time? Can that like be a thing?
I'm downloading a patch for you.
Hey, I just got somebody. Somebody's on my tail. Hold on. I'm whipping around.
Which one? Oh, there he is. Oh, there he is. Hey, what's up, buddy?
Oh, there he is. Oh, look at that. Going upside down. Oh, he's right there.
This guy, get off me. I need to do like, I don't know. How do you do like a super roll like to spin around like Star Fox?
How do you do the Star Fox roll and kill Leon the fucking lizard?
This guy's so done.
Good bye. I don't think I had anything to do with that, by the way.
What? I have to make an account. Don't put that in.
No, I've got to put it in. I know.
Why is my name is the joke man because you made that joke
Oh, yeah
You really made it the joke man. Yeah, my name is the joke man and the more thunder
What will you make your name something equally as stupid? I already made it
Make your name like dog shit burrito or something something like dumb. Oh, it's stir underscore
While in battle press f1 to view help on the controls
Your main objective destroy the enemy planes and ground vehicles and bomb the place
Well, we can fly together let's like fly together
Are you fucking shooting me right now?
You fucking asshole
You fucking dick
Take that
Did my plane come crash on you?
Look at this guy
What the fuck this guy's pissed
Are you back in no, I'm at the main menu I fell off the face of the earth
I just just slow down a little bit cuz I need to like come get on your you have to find you on my friends list
I need to like I'm fine
No, I'm still in the air. I'm still here. I have one way me too. Oh
All right, for the love of God, can we please stop this and actually play the game?
You started it. I
Started it. I started this says the guy that was shooting me from behind when we first started the game
I want to fly the same speed and like do like a top gun moment. Can we please do that reduce your speed?
No, no, no, no, no, no
That's all my planes I think you might have to get better at this game
I have to get at least one kill for this video
Otherwise, I'm just gonna look like I'm gonna look like a baddie. I don't want to look like I killed you plenty of times
Yeah, because you're using one of my clips. You're a tking asshole. That's why
Star I don't want to look like look like a baddie. Okay, and please
Help me kill someone. I don't want to look like a baddie. Come on one use the force
No, no
Yes. Oh
No, Jesus
Does that count as two kills? It should are you are you driving really slowly? Why am I catching up so much speed on you?
Oh, no, okay. I get it. I get it. Sure
Biggest fuckface ever I
Was wondering I was like, why am I cat? Why is my co he's coming? Okay, I gotta stop talking
There's a guy like right here. Well, you're already a little bit damaged. It's okay
You should just go back to that hangar and make me a sandwich
No, I think I should get this star. I drive straight at you and shoot you. No, look who it is
Oh, look everybody. Oh, I wonder what just happened. Oh, no, I can't not again
I can't believe you go back to the hangar. Bye
Are you quitting right now? Well, no, I don't have any more planes left. I can't play war thunder. Welcome to war thunder
Don't play it with star