Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Excel for Microsoft Windows.
It's a gameplay commentary. As you can see, the background is going to be me using Microsoft Excel,
which is probably one of the best releases gaming-wise this year.
And yes, I gotta get this out of the way. Yes, this is a paid upload.
I was paid $27,000 to make this video from Microsoft from actually the CEO Bill Gates.
He handed me actually two briefcases full of $100 bills,
and they all were kissed individually by Bill Gates, so I take it as you want it.
But anyways, we're going to talk about Microsoft Excel again. This is the best game to come out this year.
And now we're going to drop this little facade and talk about why I'm bringing this up.
First of all, let's transition to some actual gameplay here. We're going to transition to...
I don't know what it is. It's going to be some random game. It could be TF2. It could be SMITE.
I don't know what the gameplay is, but I do need to bring this up,
because it seems like every time I upload a video that's not TF2 or that's not like a big AAA title,
there's always at least a few people that ask me,
did you get paid to upload this video?
And some people get quite upset over this notion that there could be a video on this channel that somebody paid me for,
or any YouTuber, that you got paid to play a game or to talk about a certain game or to upload a certain game.
And to firstly bring this up to start off talking about this, I have never been paid to play a game.
That's never happened. All the videos on this channel are games that I really enjoy playing,
that I've spent a lot of time with, that I actually enjoy the experiences of.
You're never going to see an upload on this channel of a game that I didn't generally enjoy.
A game that I didn't... Or let's rephrase that a little bit.
But games that just came out can fit in this category too.
Like if a game just released, I'm doing a review or a breakdown or first impressions.
That's the same thing. So I would say those are the two categories of video content on this channel.
If it's not a skit, if it's not me doing a vlog or just kind of like a general podcast type video where I bring up a topic.
The gameplay on this channel will always fit into one of those categories.
I'm never going to just accept from Satan.
He comes up to me with a contract and he says,
Jeremy, I want you to sign on the dotted line. I'm going to pay you $5,000 for you to upload my shitty game.
That's not going to happen. The only time I've declined, guys, this is what a lot of people don't realize,
and a lot of YouTubers can vouch for this as well.
I've declined a lot of offers from people that I just didn't see as making sense to put on my channel.
The notion of paid videos irks me. It really does.
It really kind of gets under my skin unless it's something that I'm already a big fan of or something that I'm really excited for.
But the flip side of the coin here, an argument for something like a paid video or a paid playtime or a stream or something like that,
is a lot of YouTubers do this for a living.
A lot of guys wake up in the morning, myself included.
We get up in the morning, we come up with these ideas, we try to make new content.
We're always trying to innovate on things, make better videos, try to make the highest quality videos we possibly can.
And maybe it is okay for somebody to take a couple of paid videos because it's just more money in their pocket,
more money they can use to spend on improving the channel, buying more games, buying more stuff.
Now, I'm not saying that all these deals should be done because there are some of these deals that are just, let's just face it, downright stupid.
Like really, really stupid, and they are completely meaningless videos, completely meaningless things.
But there are some things that are worthwhile.
And the reason why I started this video out as the Microsoft Excel type thing is because that's the type of thing that I see as stupid, I see as dumb.
But if it's an actual gaming video and it's something that the person, the YouTuber happens to be involved in,
then I find that to be okay, especially because of the state of YouTube right now, how, you know, monetizing views is so difficult at the moment.
And it really just comes down to, I guess, channel integrity.
Do you want to be known as the guy that has a paid video every two weeks?
Or do you want to be known as somebody that is supporting good companies or that's supporting their own channel
and not taking every single handout from companies that they ever receive?
But I guess this is the part of the video where I open it up to you guys.
I want to get a discussion going in the comments.
Let me know how you feel about this because, like I said in the beginning, it is a very touchy subject to a lot of people.
The notion of even ad revenue on YouTube just by people running ads, it's, you get into a really weird set of waters here
because once you bring money really into anything, you can cause a lot of problems and a lot of conflict can arise.
And in reality, that happens everywhere, not just on YouTube.
You're talking about every business, every friendship.
There's so many cases where money can really destroy things.
And I want to get your opinions on that, so please let me hear them.
Anyways, that's going to wrap up the video, guys, so thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it, and I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.