Hi guys, welcome back. It's me, Jeremy. It's hair in my mouth. I just took a big almost sip of my,
I took an almost big sip of my coffee with just three or four hairs on the top of my tongue.
Good afternoon. Starting about an hour or two early today again. For the sake of Sekiro. I'm
going to continue. If you just got a notification and you just came over here and oh my, wait,
Jeremy streaming right now. I sure am. I sure am. It's Sekiro though. So you might, oh fuck,
get me out of here. You don't want to be spoiled. We are about eight hours into the game. Just want
to make sure you're aware of that. So I don't press the button here and switch over and you go,
I just saw a huge spoiler. We are also going to go into sub only again for today.
We did it with Dark Souls three and I think it just, it's just warranted for a game like this.
It keeps the spoilers and the potential spam of said spoilers at bay. I don't do it that often,
but like I said, for games like this, it's something that I do. Sub only greedy streamer.
The greed is taking him over. He's going to force us to pay money to speak. What's next?
I want to watch you so bad, but I want to start playing. Well, the beauty of
where you are right now is this is recorded. So if you really don't want to watch me play,
you're really torn. You could play and then you could just see how I do, you know, or vice versa.
You know, there's no obligation to watch, but remember this is forever on the internet.
Everything that I'm doing right now, no matter what, everything I'm saying
is recorded forever. That's why I got to be careful. You know, I got to make sure I stay
completely sane. I don't do anything weird. Don't say anything weird.
Cause that was permanently the sentence I'm saying right now, permanently recorded.
There's no going back into leading this. It's already here. Every single sec and
forever recorded everything here. So I got to be ready. No pressure.
I actually am still sick too. Just it's been annoying. I'll be all right though.
I went to eight hours yesterday. We'll see how we do today. With that being said, I think we can
get off of the starting soon screen. I'm just sitting here in the inventory and let's get that
audio on too. I really want to watch the stream, but I don't want the game to be spoiled. No,
I can, I completely understand that. Well, hey, what you could do is here. I have a solution.
You ready? Here's the solution. Go down to the quality settings that are on the bottom of your
window here. Click on the little cog wheel, make it like three 60 P or like one 60 P
cell phone quality, turn the screen brightness down on your monitor to about 10%. Once that's done,
have a system, make a script on your computer that auto mutes the audio coming from the stream
every 10 seconds and it stays muted for 15 seconds. So you'll get snippets of me talking.
You won't spoil anything. Cause like, what the hell could I be talking about? Have the audio just
randomly cut off every 10 seconds for like, like 30 seconds. And at the same time, uh, be working
on something, have like your other monitor or have like another device in your hand, like playing a
game monitor or something. So you're not really paying that much attention. That's how you can do
it. Or just play it on your own time and enjoy it because it's meant to be enjoyed.
And speaking of things that are meant to be done, also write a script to donate big bits.
You have a script like on your computer, it's an exe file. You double click it
and every like 20 minutes, like a thousand dollars is given. Don't do that. That's,
that is absolutely the complete reverse. I know. And I had to say a thousand too, right?
I couldn't have said one. Speaking of one dollar, uh, those of you that weren't here yesterday,
this is actually pretty funny. Somebody, um, I think it was Tingy. They brought this up to
Tingy if you're here. They were saying that every time I die in Sekiro, cause I made like a, I don't
know, late last night, I kind of went out of my fucking mind. I went insane that one of the bosses
had lost control of all of my bodily functions, including my motor speech, uh, vehicle. So what
we decided to be funny is every time I die in Sekiro, tally it up. And at the end of the whole
thing, whenever I stopped playing it, I got to buy scratch ticket for every death or every five
deaths is one is like, you know, like $5 scratch ticket and just scratch them on stream. And then
whatever happens, whatever money comes from those scratch tickets goes back into the channel for
community subs. So if I hit like 500 bucks on scratch ticket, $500 worth of community subs,
watch you win $20,000. Now that would be fucking hilarious because what is $20,000?
I would, there'd be almost every single person, every single person on the channel would have a
sub, right? That would be too many. I would, could I legally even do that though? I might get in
trouble. If I do like 20 grand worth of community subs, some, someone's going to take a look at that
and be like, uh, what's going on here? Anyways, I'm going to consume this memory to get some more
attack power. This is the butterfly. This is the last, the boss that I just beat before moving on.
What are you in for? Too many community subs. All right. So the battle memory of an extraordinary
foe, although distant recollection of such a memory provided sustenance for the wolf.
The Phantom Lady Butterfly was appointed by the wolf's foster father as one of his mentors in
Shinobi techniques. These mentors employed strict methods. The cultivation of Shinobi techniques can
only be achieved in the midst of battle. Attack power has been enhanced. So I have attack power
three. I'm almost have another skill point, which I'm looking forward to because that means I get
more, hold on a second. Let me see. I was going down this path, but I don't, I, I want this.
This makes the heal better. Cough cough slash last sounds like a league of legends pro username.
Well, somebody get it. Somebody get it. Then win a tournament and give me 2%.
That's all I ask. Not even, no, 1%. That's all I ask. All right. So Emma taught this technique
to the sculptor long ago. So it just increased the healing effects of recovery items. I just like,
I need that. I want it. I'm going to get it. So we were, the last thing we did, we cleared the
chamber and that brought us out. I think this is where I was before the castle gate, right?
Friday and you can't stick around for tonight's stream, but I wanted to drop in and show some
support anyhow. Have a great night, Frodi and thank you for dropping in and you also get 10
bucks too. Have an awesome night. Thanks for sticking around. Well, thanks for hanging out
for the few minutes that you were here. You just made me sub. God damn it. I'm sorry. I don't do
sub only. It's only sometimes. It's for Sekiro shadows die twice. Seems a little loud to me.
Is it a little loud to anybody else? It's because of the spoilers. So where were we? Uh, this way.
Uh, let me, I want to look at something first though, because who are these people? The man
who coughs has witnessed endless battling. Get my mouse off the screen. The sculptor is coughing.
The maid is coughing. The fine son, the coughing the reason he sounds of a man thinking only of
his sick mother. The man who coughs has witnessed endless battles, making offerings to the dead in
the battlefield outside Ashina castle gate. So there's that guy and his mother and the son,
right? That's going to remember where these people are because I don't think I can kill them.
Well, that's too low. I'm going to turn it back up. Sub mode is emote only mode with words.
Well, that's just chatting.
What? All right. Let's see here. Anybody else? Oh God. I don't know how I pulled that off.
Oh shit. Give it back up here. This is not a place I want to be right now.
Okay. Um, let's see. Where are those dogs? I gotta get the dogs first. Dog. Shit. No, I want the dog.
Oh no, this is the mushroom people are here too. I'm not gonna aggro the whole city.
Oh fuck. I gotta get out of here. Run away. One at a time. Please. I think I'm gonna die.
Everyone's fighting me here. Something I learned from playing last night and yesterday,
not every fight can be won. Sometimes you just got to run the hell away. You don't have to fight
five people at the same time. See if I can pick off the guy that was here. It's two dogs, right?
Was it three dogs? That's a coward's motto. That's not a coward's motto. That is a strategist's motto.
There he is. Okay. There's another dog. Let's just kill this guy. All right. How are you?
That's a very cowardly strategist. Well, isn't the goal to live? If the goal is living, isn't
that correct? If you were that skilled, would you really want to just be able to die that easily?
No one's Superman. Superman isn't real. In real life, you can't fight more than one person at
the same time. Somebody's gonna come from behind you with a chair and hit you in the back of the
head. It's not gonna happen. This guy's real. Oh great. All right. Fuck the guy with the gun.
Come here. Oh, perfect parries. Oh, absolutely perfect parries. Spoilers for real life. Yeah,
you can say that. Wait, there's something over here. Let me see. Oh, a ledge. Is this the guy
that got good at Sekiro? I told you I had to just fucking save my game. I didn't get to the guys.
I didn't get to the level up screen. I dumped a bunch of experience points into my talent pool
and I didn't put the points in. I put them in. I fell asleep. I woke up with those skills.
Is this the guy who beat Sekiro? Shadows die twice on stream? Well, only once.
Wait, I'm gonna die if I do that. The best part about being sick is you get to do the wicked
old man laugh whenever you want. I hope somebody clips that. I guess I can drop down from this way
rather than... Well, let's just kill this guy in one hit. Who else is down here? This is important.
I think I can get him and get out. Let's get in, get out. That's how you get in and get out.
Any questions? What? Why did I just do that? Oh, I can take him. I can take him. It's just two.
What are we gonna do? I've never fought a big guy like this before.
Dodging. Wow, you have fucking lots of... I forget there's no stamina. Oh, fuck.
Yeah, they can just keep swinging. All right, where are we at? Let me go down here.
Well, let me just go down here. Can you deflect blunt objects? I think you can deflect anything,
but dodging... When I have a chance to just dodge, I'm gonna take the chance. Just because I'm so
much more used to that. Let's go this way. Anything else in here? Around the corner?
I could have hit over here. No? All right, well, let's go. Only seems to be one way to go.
Wait, what about down here? That's death. What about behind the building?
Aha! Clay. A Boston baked beans a thing. Yeah, I think I can actually upgrade one of my tools
now, but I don't know if I want to. Yeah, parrying is so much better now. You have to.
You can't not parry. It's impossible. That the whole game is based around you doing that.
Dodging. If those of you that didn't, weren't here yesterday, that had no idea how the game
plays. Well, first of all, that's five community subs from Kaiser, from Durnure... Thank you,
Kaiser. Okay, my name is... Not my name, your name. It doesn't discriminate between friend or foe.
Wait, say that one more time. All right, so wait, I'm assuming this is a boss or a mini-boss that
I can have fight a person, right? But, thank you for the community subs, and to keep that kind of
question going. Yes, this game... I'm one of those people that wasn't very good at parrying
in any of the Dark Souls games. I relied on dodging and iframes, and it's all I did.
Sometimes I would parry regular enemies or Black Knights. You cannot do that anymore. There is no
dodge every attack. You have to learn how to play this game, and it can be immensely fra... I think
that's one of the reasons why everybody's saying this is the hardest one they've ever made.
It's not the hardest game they've ever made, it's the fact that you have to use all the tools they
give you, when before you didn't have to. That's the problem. No one's used to doing this. You
gotta like learn how to play this game, not just rely on iframes. And it can be immensely frustrating.
But, it's... Oh yeah! What? Wait, wait, where the fuck is this coming from? What the fuck is that
thing? Did somebody's dog just get out? What the fuck? Okay, um, let's take it...
It's just talking to... Speaking of dodging and parrying, let's see if we can do it.
No, I ain't gonna. There's no verticality here either. No, are we really gonna use that thing?
You mean this? Yeah. All right, hold on. How do you parry a gigantic pig? I feel like I had health.
I'm running around. There's no stamina. Oh boy, I'm dead. Okay, um, let's just die.
Use the... I used it all, I don't have any left. Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. I haven't even used this. Should I get the, let's see, dowsing powder? Burn resistance and
resistance to burn damage. I'll put that on. How does this work? It costs two to use. Okay,
explosive flash that briefly blinds foes and inflicts partial damage on beast-type enemies.
It's got a wide, frontward field of effect. Scaring beasts. Oh, sick. Do something funny?
You got it. Hello, my baby. Hello, my darling. Hello, my ragtime gal. Send me a kiss by mile.
Baby, my heart's on fire. If you refuse me, baby, you lose me and you'll be left alone. And tell me,
tell me that I'm the one and all. Happy? Can we move on? That sounds good. So, what's the point
of fighting these guys? Just go over to the giant animal. Oh, you asshole. Now I have to reset it.
Do something funny. You see, for you keen viewers, that wasn't funny. You know,
he looks like an idiot. It's not me that looks like the idiot. He looks like the idiot, right?
I gotta utilize this laugh while I have it. I have skill. Oh, you show me that face. Here we go.
Let's get it. My heal is better. It can be even better. I'm not gonna save up for that, though.
Don't show me that face. I don't want to see that face. Let's see how this works. Let's see the
range on this. Okay, it's pretty much right in front of you. It's not that far. Can I put it,
like, on his ass? Or do I have to just have to be right in the face? That... Not this time.
So yeah, it doesn't understand friend or foe. So then let's just aggro the whole camp
and have him kill everybody. What's the harm? This is gonna be a mess. This could turn into
a real mess. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop. Okay, so here we go.
Let's bring the whole... Bring everybody. Oh, god damn it. Oh my god.
Well, that worked out. Scare him. Okay, that's pretty effective. Oh, he's immune to it now.
I can only do that once, it seems. No, you can... Okay, it's only kind of a weird cooldown.
Oh, this area is not that big to be diving around in. Just whittle him down. Ow! Would that hit me?
Come on. Jesus! Oh! That was... That camera was fucking stupid. Did you see that camera?
Who's cam... What? Forget it. Fuck the camera. Fuck the camera? Why would I have it on? Shit.
I gotta move. He's almost down to half. Um, not bad. Uh, let's just try and give it an attempt here.
Fuck. He's got a... He's got a little, like, half delay on his, uh, dash. I like that. I'm fucked.
That was decent. This run back is kind of a pain, though. Uh, I wonder. Now we'll keep this the way
it is. Hello. Goodbye. How's the game so far? I think it's great. I love it. I have, like, one or
two very slight minor issues with the game, but I don't even know if I would class by them as a
real issue. All right, let me go... The problem was last time I just got fucking screwed. All right,
stay back. This guy's gonna die. All right. Oh my god! The start of it every time. Can I jump him?
Oh, this motherfucker can't get jumped. I just have to, like, oh, lay him. All right, now I'm
just getting overzealous. All right, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Everything's fine. You can jump over him. Come on in. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Nothing
too crazy. Wait for him to come in. Boys and girls, that's what we call, um, D-O-G-S-H-I-T.
That was dog shit. I, like, didn't. You can, like, clip on his head and not jump over him when he
charges. Of course you can. That just threw me off. I should have jumped over him that time. Not the
time you just saw, but of course. They always gotta put that guy. They gotta put this one guy
with the gun that will accidentally, he's gonna shoot me once and I'm gonna have to redo the whole
thing and run back. I beat this boss on first try, so haha. I hope you did. I bet you didn't though.
No, you didn't. No, you didn't. No, you didn't. No, you didn't. All right, watch out. Oh no. I wonder
what dog is gonna win this. How did a dog get in here? Oh, I have a bigger dog. No, that's not a
good idea. I'm just gonna dodge. That's not reliable at all. It really isn't. I really should be trying
just to run around him. Don't let him get in front of you. Do the chase. I didn't get the frame there.
Oh, don't do that to me, man. That little spin. All right, come here. Nooo.
Shit, wrong button. You can only do this one more time. That was just bad timing. Let's use it now.
Mm-hmm. Come on. Oh, come on. I really enjoy your Katamari cosplay, but come on, dude. Let me up.
He's like wicked aggressive right now. Oh yeah. Where am I going? He's got new move. He's got a
new move. I don't even. What a fantastic camera. I got him. I got him. I got him. I'm dead. Oh my
fucking god. I just love having a camera just be like somebody was filming something else.
The only way that would have been. You would have made that worse. It happened. It happened,
by the way. Look, it happened. It happens. Now I have to start over. Yeah, the only way that
Nakata would have been worse right there with the camera was if it was a vertical fucking video.
Come on. Boom. Almost got him. Don't worry. I'll try again in like five minutes. Dude, okay. From
software. I've got an idea for you. I have a really good. Here's an idea for a next video game that
you make. All right. Let me coat my weapon in like, let me eat. Okay. You have candy in this game.
Let me take a bite of a candy. It lasts five seconds. No, not even the next enemy you kill is
permanently dead. I would use it right there and kill that guy. You haven't figured the game.
They haven't come on. They haven't thought of that. The next enemy that you kill with your
blade is permanently dead. That doesn't respond. No, that would sell millions. I want to try
something. This is, this is like the, the, the idiot run. Ready? That's not going to happen.
How much is this? What does this do for my posture? I didn't even try it yet.
It actually hurts me a lot. Yeah, that's not a good idea. That's a horrible idea.
That's not going to work. Got him in the head. The head is where he, I need to hit him. Yeah, yeah. I
know. I know. This was the idiot run for a reason. I want to see how much damage it takes to hit him
in the head before he staggers. It makes it even worse because the thing on his head just is such
a distraction for where he's moving. What is it? How many hits does it take? I can't even tell.
Upgrade your vitality. I already did. Tried deflecting. Why the fuck does this have to be
here? Like it's only purpose is to be annoying. This could be empty. Put a tree here. Just put
a fucking bush here and it's the same purpose. The same thing. Just put a fucking statue right here.
It worked. My potion works. I had it that time too. I'm just, you know, this happens when you
fucking shake. This is why you're not allowed to shake pinball machines because now the fucking
machine doesn't work. The pinwheel machine. All right, here we go. I'm going to try a couple of
things here. That's, yes, game. That's the guy I wanted to lock onto. The one dickhead that's still
here. Yes, that's the person I wanted to lock onto. Prioritize the fucking bald guy game. Yeah,
do that. Give me a break. I don't have the thing. I was going to try it. Why do I have the flame
thing on? I was going to throw a hit. I was going to hit with the axe. This fucking camera. Come on,
man. Like what the fuck? You got to like, I have to just untarget him. The thing just spins around
in a fucking circle. What is it? How did this guy get in here? I don't think I have any more
hit now. I'm dead. Not yet. No, I got nothing. Well, I'm going to try it. It's possible.
No, no, it's not. This guy's arguably harder than the last person. Last person at least had
even remote. Don't you dare. The butterfly lady. I mean, at least you had a second. This is just a
bull screaming and running in circles. You're the one that gets things down around here. No,
I'm not going to use that right now. This is very beatable. It's just, did that dog drop on my back?
All right, lock it quick before anybody gets in. Shit, somebody got in.
What? Oh, I didn't even have, just restarted. Geez, you die in fucking one hit too. You die
in like one or two hits in this game. You can't take any hits. You can't get hit in Sekiro. You
can't take damage. Fuck. Fuck. This is the one. I don't know. Yeah, I got, like the perfect world
has to really happen here. Don't aggro in three bald guys that accidentally hit you with a sword
that throws off the whole attempt. And perfect dodging. There's a lot of things that have to go
right here. Yeah, see? And that's what I'm talking about. It happened. If I didn't turn around, that
would have been, I would have screamed. Kill these guys, please. You actually hit me with a, oh my
fucking god. Why? Why can those guys even come in that fucking room? Kill them before they come in.
Just kill everybody before attempting a boss. I don't know if I want to do that. All right,
put it up. Fuck. I thought he was going to do a move. The thing about trying to deflect
all of his moves is you still have to hit him. And by the time that you are done deflecting,
it's time that he's going to, you're dead. He's going to swing at you again. It's like hard to
get a word in edgewise. I think I'm still taking damage too. Anybody catch that? I didn't. I'm
already dead. Well, I'm going to try it a couple times by parrying. It's like, you know what it's
going to have to be? It's going to be parry, parry, parry, parry, parry, and then get the attacks by
using the skill that I have. That's a bad idea. I should have parried. What? What? That made the,
I made the blocking parry sound. Chip damage? Yeah. I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm just going
to try to play as hyper safe as I can because trying to dodge around him too is just, he moves
around so much that even the camera, the camera just can't keep up with it. So we're going to
attempt a, oh this is a free kill. All right. I also have that move too. Let me try this.
This one. I wonder if it's worth stunning him and doing that behind him. Maybe. How did that not
block? I'm sitting there holding it. I don't know. That's not worth doing. That's probably not worth
doing. It's so hard. It's going to make me fucking scream. Oh, that was a mistake. Chip damage. I'm
dead. Is this the only spot I can, I think I have, this is the wall. I have to beat this.
Or I, I don't think there's anywhere else I can go. I just have to beat it. I have to win.
I don't have any pellets left either. No, what? No, I just did it right in his face. What the
fuck? Come on. What? That was, that wasn't part of the cool down. That was like,
hold on. Let me reset because the statue that shoots the gun just shot me. Hold on guys.
I had it that time too, unfortunately. Just fucking man. I'm just going to run at him.
I'm just going at him. Aggressive. I'm going to be more aggressive than he is.
Fuck. Wrong button. Yeah. Fuck the defense dog shit. Go at him. Let's go. Stop talking. No!
Get the camera. Come here. Oh my God. I didn't jump it. How? I don't believe it.
I refuse to believe it. I'll get him right here. Here we go. Yeah.
I'm getting stupid. Fucking getting stupid. I don't like it. I don't like this fucking game.
It's too hard. It's too hard. It's too hard. It's too hard. It's too hard. Hey, I beat it.
All right. So that healing effective. Okay. Cool. Huh? That was fucking intense though.
If here's the thing, I know this isn't Dark Souls and I know it's like you got to play
it completely differently, but sometimes you don't. Sometimes you have to just play like you play in
a Bloodborne boss. That's what I did differently that one time right here is just fuck it up.
Forget about like just go after him. Dodge. Go after him. Go, go, go, go, go.
Where is the bull though? For real. The more you stand there and like,
oh wait, what's moves you going to do next? Oh, watch out. Nothing in here.
I hope there's a place for me to hide. He got disenchanted.
All right. Let me just wait. I have, I wish there was a forward. This was an up, right bumper,
kick down into the boo. I'll take it. Let me get that item. Well, let's take a look down here.
Cool. More people that way. Let's check. I want to make it the item first.
It's going to hurt. All right. Where's the item? Isn't there an item down here?
Where's the other side? What? Item? All right. That was weird. Oh, it's right here.
Is it, it's just, oh, oh, it's just extra spirit emblems. Well, I'm down here. Might as well be
down here. What? What? Okay. Well, I need to get back up here. Yeah. No secret walls. How do I get,
is there a spot I can jump to? Or do I have to just live out the rest of my days down here?
There we go. There's a fucking wallpaper for you right there. No, no, no. Right, right, right. I'll
tell you when. I'll tell you when. Ready? Now. No. Now. Now. Hope you got a good screenshot there.
And then just like smear out the shit on the bottom left and right.
Gate is firmly sealed shut. Well, that's not good. Oh, look, a memory. No, I will. Why'd you link
the slap? Why, of all things. All right. Let's go this way. That's by far the most embarrassing
thing I've done on Twitch. There's a lot of layers as to why that is. I could go straight
up the stairs, but there's a lot of people there. Does this open? Oh, this also opens.
Worse than dinosaur on green screen? Yeah, way worse. Because the dinosaur on green screen was
intentional. Ooh, iron. I need to go take a look at what I can do with these. Fuck, man. So much
cool shit in this game. What is down here? Pellets. I need those. And a cellar? The cellar?
It's worse if you meant to do the raptor. Yeah, but that's my own doing. I really did not mean to
hit myself in the face hard. That's another form of embarrassment. Intentional, whoops, that was not
like I shouldn't have done that. I thought that was going to be different. It's a lot different
than I just hit myself in the face as hard as I could. But I didn't, though. Wow, that was
really hard. Intentional embarrassment is not worse. No, because I knew what I was getting into.
When I put on the dinosaur ski mask, I knew what I was getting into. I had a moment off screen.
I was stage right. I had the gloves on, and I had the mask on, and I'm like, I'm about to do this.
Here I go. Go this way. Ashina Reservoir? Did we find the branch that goes this way?
We're just going to go this way. Wow, that was almost death. Would I ever put the raptor on
again? No, I don't think so. Wait, no, this is the beginning of the game. We went all the way
around a circle here. This is the very beginning of the game because I didn't have the grapple
hook before. Oh, okay. Interesting. So does that mean that can I now go somewhere in the beginning
that I couldn't go before because of the grapple hook? Oh, would you look at that? Oh, that's cool.
I don't have the axe on. It doesn't really help me here. I got to get some parries
because no way I'm going to take that hat off without them. Come on, take it off. Get your
fucking hat off. Take that. Finally. Okay, look at that R1 spam. Heavy coin purse and scrap iron.
Cool. So it was really worth coming up here, wasn't it? Yeah. Oh boy. And I'm poisoned. Poison's a lot
worse than this fucking game than any of the other ones. Whoa, that takes fast. How long does
it last for? Come on, man. Really? I think that's all I can do down here. It was worth coming to get
the iron. Yeah, I don't think there's much else I can do here. Let's maybe up this way. Stinky Sekiro.
Nope, I can go over here. So this leads back up to the second area. This leads to here. So then
let's go this way. Might as well just rest here. Speedrunners are beating this game in 20 minutes.
It takes 20 minutes to run from that first zone probably to where I'm standing right now.
I don't believe that yet. I don't think anyone's beaten the game yet. I looked on the
steamachievements.org and zero percent completion at the moment. So I mean, nice jibate attempt.
You almost jibated me there. Speaking of trying to not die, I'm just gonna have to get it done.
You know what I mean? Like just get it done. Dogs first. Get her dead. This one time I went
out of the store and not tell you. You guys know that that guy's not really... That's just a character
you get that right. I thought about this for a long time. You know like grandpa? I had this
conversation with myself. Is it worth like 50 million dollars for me to have to become grandpa?
This is what I do. I'm just an old fucking guy every day and that's me.
I have to change everything. I have to just be grandpa in my conversations with people
in my everyday life, in my you know just shows. I just have to be grandpa for life. That's what
Larry the Cable Guy is doing right now. He's doing grandpa for life. I think I can jump up.
I can get up there. Probably not in private. I'm not so sure about that though guys.
For one very important reason. If you do a voice for long enough over and over again you kind of
just like start to... How would you... It would just become your everyday life. If eight out of
24 hours in a day you're talking like grandpa you're gonna have a conversation with your
mother like that. That's just gonna happen. And maybe it'd be like a little different like this
or something but I talk like this all day every single second of every day. You would permanently
change your vocal cords. And by the way I'm kind of being stupid here. Can anybody see me?
I cleared out the arches. That's good. All right. Can he see? Are these not stealth bushes? Yeah
they are. Oh shit he's coming. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Go for this one. This one. This one.
This one. Oh you have a punch. You punch too do you? Oh shit. Okay. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Cut it out. Nah. It's always the slow ones that cause me so many problems. Every time.
No. Watch out. This is gonna jump on somebody's head here. Assholes. Don't even think about it.
Fire? Fire doesn't really do much do you? Wow. What about you? Are you guys beasts? Kind of.
Kind of. Oh my god. This is come on. Jesus. How do I separate you two? If one's not swinging the
other one's getting ready to swing. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Where's the fuck? Why?
Where was his bottom bar? Oh my god. His bottom bar was like blank. I'm just angry now and it's
causing a problem. I'm dead. No I'm not. Fuck it. I'm not losing that shit.
By the way you just came from a boss that attacks 50 times a second and I'm here to show you.
I'm so mad right now. He's gonna kill me. I'm just gonna run. Just open a fucking door.
It's locked. What do we got over here? I get the last laugh. No I don't. I thought I was gonna get
it up. Uh. Hey. Hey there. I didn't even tell him. Uh. Is that it?
He's coughing. Coughing my face. I need to go back and bring it to the lady. He's a huge sword. Yeah
that's right. Shamisen. Okay so the shamisen is down here. What's up here? Uh well I think I just
figured out a way to take a full bar off that guy. Okay. Not right now obviously because I have no
health. Hey I'll be back. You stay there. All right. I can go into here. Wait. This doesn't open.
That I could go. This is the tutorial zone. Remember I went in here. Where's the big guy?
I will have my revenge. Is somebody else here? I will have my revenge. Wait till he turns around
then I'm gonna go right behind him. He didn't hear a thing. I just Kool-Aid man. Threw this
guy's apartment window. All right. Did it. I need. What the hell do I need? What? No no no no. I need
a. I need a save point. Not a boss. Oh. How do I? He's just guarding me. This. I just smash brothers
all over again. Come on Diddy Kong. Give me a break. What do you got in here? What are you guarding
in here? Why are you doing this? What's in here? Rule number one. Never leave your house.
I didn't think he'd really come back in that quick. You scared the shit out of me. He's scared. No
somebody else is dying. Uh well I know where two people are. Let's see if I can get there without
causing any problems. The one dude's over there. Let's see if I can. Let's just go this way. Okay
so up there. No not the guy with the frying pan. There wasn't anybody to alert anyway. So let's go
this way. Okay why can't I just stand up here? I can't like break this and open that door from
the other side. I probably can right? All right. I should be able to. I wonder if I can avoid the
big guys and just fight the dude up on the stairs. Oh yeah definitely. So this is the route to go.
Somebody saw me. Although can I? Who saw me? Big guy. Question. Maybe I can I get behind him
and take off one of his bars? Maybe. Now that would be cool. I wonder. Let's go all the way around.
Absolutely. Watch this shit. I'm gonna go sneak through the house. The door. The tutorial door.
And I'm gonna backstab him. He can have no fucking idea. Okay I don't know how that happened. Oh
this is gonna be perfect. But there's a cutscene. Let's okay. Let's watch the cutscene. Rule number
two. Leave your house so you don't get backstabbed. Hello. I'll take a free bar please. If you could.
So he's gonna thrust. Thrust. What else you got? That's a sweep. Okay. Oh fuck. Fuck. I'm dead.
Oh I should. I might be able to still kill him though. You gotta be kidding me. One hit kill.
Why did everybody have one of these? You. I gotta get that back. I just have no idea what the fuck
he even does. It's got full baseball insta-kill. Unseen aid. Okay well I. That doesn't. Who cares.
Prediction master. I got juggled. I'm like playing Street Fighter right now. God. Oh come on.
It's fantastic. Well so he has a thrust. He has a sweep and he also has a giant baseball swing and
now the guy with the dinner plate now ruined the whole thing. I can beat this guy. I mean it's
very clearly I got one tick on him already. Just gonna hang on the ledge. Just run and get another
backstab on him. I mean I don't know if that's possible. If it is, this game doesn't know what
kind of game it wants to be. If that's possible. Like are you a stealth game or are you an action
game? Right? Because if I can backstab him, run away and then backstab him. Like what the hell is
going on here? If you run away he gets two bars again. Okay. That's. I'm glad that happens. You
shouldn't be able to do that. Otherwise you could just do that to everybody. Let's go. That's a
sweep. Oh he digs it into the ground. He doesn't go straight forward. What? Just. Did he explode?
Oh my god. So slow.
Unlike any game I've ever played, the absolutely just tremendous amount of focus you have to have
in each one of these fights. It doesn't matter who it is. I forgot about the guy with the
fucking pan again. Oh god. You always have to worry about the one guy. The one guy that makes
every route annoying. They're always there. Don't forget about me. Ding ding ding. Remember me? I'm
the one that causes all the fucking problems here. It's me. I'm one person that causes every issue.
I'm the noise statue. You ran into the gun statue. Well sorry. I don't use weapons. I just smash my
plates together and make everybody come after you. Oh everybody else on the whole map. Fuck them.
You don't. You worry about me and only me. Who saw that? Oh he saw me. All right. Here we go again.
Hi. I'm here for you to baseball one hits kill me again. Just kidding. I saw him. I'm coming to help
you. It's a sweep not a fucking. Again. Oh it just takes up the whole fucking screen. I keep on
trying to get it. He's got such quick. Not enough. Oh I didn't get it. He just varies up his timing
so much. It's either going to be a big baseball swing or a little. No don't go. I'm going the
wrong way. Just rest. Bear it. It's like the rock paper scissors between sweep stab. It's you got
that tenth of a second to figure it out. Fuck. This game is brutal. I'll get him. Oh what?
I made a fucking joke. I made a joke and he still hit it. Now I might just go reset. This game looks
amazing. It is. Oh it is. It's fucking unbelievable. It's just brutal. I fucked this whole thing up.
It's like punishing is the way. It really is like a fucking fighting game.
The punishment for mistakes in Sekiro is way way more aggressive than it is in any
of the other games they've ever made. You make a mistake in Sekiro. Oh fuck you. You fuck you.
You made a mistake in like Dark Souls. You could take a few hits and you could fuck it up a couple
times. You got like 10 Estes. Sometimes 15 Estes flasks to drink. That big guy's gonna see me
isn't he? All right here we go. Oh I couldn't really block that. Careful. Got it. He's not gonna
go off the... We're in such a stupid place right now. Come on. Why did we get over here? He's like
just stuck over on the... I don't even know what the fuck that was. Got it. What? Come on. I didn't
jump over it. What? Oh what? I thought I clearly jumped over it. That was a big sweep right? What
are tools? I don't like don't know which one to use here. I'm just trying to get his moves down
to fight him. I mean it's one thing to use the tools. It's another thing to like... I don't even...
I gotta get down like how to even fight and parry him. That's not a sweep. Are you sure? It looks
very sweep-ish. He comes like up with it. Let me see what else I got here. I have dirt, oil. I wanna go
for equipment. Fire, axe. I don't want to use that here. I'll try throwing dirt at him. Firecracker.
I don't know if it's gonna work very well but I'll try. All right. If somebody was saying don't fight him
on the stairs. Well if I don't fight him on the stairs, if I bring him down, I have to clear the
whole area right? Because if I bring him down there, there's like two big guys, like two archers,
three... it's... I'm gonna fight him up here. I'll aggro the whole fucking town if I go down there.
Let's see here. Eat some dirt. Okay well it's parryable but it hurts... it gives me a lot of
bullshit. Yeah. Jesus Christ. Yeah just... eeeek. I didn't catch... no I didn't want to do that.
I didn't want to do that. No! No! I got the wrong thing equipped! It's hard to get around
him too because I need to take his health down. I gotta dodge around him. I need to hurt him.
I have no fucking idea what he was doing there. Fuck. It's hard to tell with that what he's gonna
even do. My goodness gracious. He does so much posture damage even if you deflect him. No I forgot
again about the one guy with the fucking pan. I'm resetting it. I'm just so focused on fighting this
guy that happened to fucking... it's my one gripe with all these games. Like you're so focused on
fighting the guy that you want to fight that you just... I want to go fight that guy not like run
through pan guy 30 times. What? Oh okay. Somebody can still see me. Use firecrackers. I'll give it a
try. Hello? That guy went all the way around. Yeah imagine not backstabbing this guy. God it would be
hell. I don't want to... that shit takes too much posture. I was gonna get away from it.
Nope there it is. He doesn't do it that often. Do you see how much recovery that like... okay so I did
I did the the fucking... I stepped on it for the stat slash and then he immediately does another
move that I'm still stuck on animation. Like I'm in the animation right now still. See? When you
step on it you have to parry. Yeah but he like pulls it out. To the right instead. Let me see.
A class... whatever just bring back to the fucking idol. Classic case of get good. Yeah you know
that's absolutely certain because you literally cannot play this game. Go look up like threads
about people talking about this game. People are like giving up on the game because they can't do
it. If you don't get good at Sekiro you don't get to play. That's pretty much how it goes. So where
am I? What am I doing? No how can I reach it from there but not reach it from here? So what you're
saying like from this direction you mean? Let me just take a look. Let me just look at it. I've got
to deal with these guys but I'm gonna just see what you mean. Like up on the roof? Like over this way?
So if I go from roof to here. Well and then to here. Oh all right. Yeah but don't he sees you
here though? Does he not see you? I guess he just doesn't see you if you do that. That's weird
considering how good he is at everything else. I got I pulled everybody though. How did you not
know this guy's coming over here to fight me? Does he know? He still doesn't know. He's just
pretending. He's gonna turn and baseball swing me and I'm gonna die. And then I'm gonna go on like
the Reddit and be like guys I don't know if I can do this. It's fucking insane. I'm so much in trouble.
I'm in trouble. Good I distracted him. I'm just gonna back away when he does it. I haven't figured
out the reliable way. Fuck why? I didn't I didn't have enough. Oh it's so he strings it together so
fast. No that's the longer one. Oh my god. This guy's worse than the other bosses in the game.
Oh worse than the ball? Maybe. The ball only had like one or two. The ball really only had one
thing. Speed and psycho. Didn't really have much else. Fucking pan guy. Yes from software. I'm aware
I gotta kill the guy with the pan every time. Why am I coming over here? Oh my god. I just wanna
fucking play the game. Fuck it. I'm going this way. I'm about to go on Reddit. Yeah guys I'm
having like a lot of trouble with the game. There's this pan guy. Is there a way to spike
the pan into his skull as hard as I can and make it so that enemy never comes back?
I actually read an article. I looked up like an article. There's an article that says is
Sekiro the hardest game ever made? It might be. It might be. Maybe ET. ET was impossible.
Battletoads 2 was up there. You got so you guys okay so you got ET, Battletoads, and then Sekiro.
Sekiro. Lock on to him. Is there somebody? Where is that? Where are you coming from?
Good I like a challenge. Bring it on. I gotta get off this fucking staircase.
We're the fucking guy here. Have to fight him one on one otherwise like don't even fucking try.
Use the dodge to step on his spear. I've done it like 30 times. I've done it. I don't know why
left bumper wasn't working there. What the fuck man. You can listen for the clicks when I did this
last time. And I'm going the wrong way again. What are you doing? What the fuck are you doing
game? God why are you like this? Am I playing Assassin's Creed? Is there a reason why I was
getting like fucking stuck on the ledge? What the fuck is happening right now? Come on. What? Oh my
God. Just fucking kill me. I don't even care. Just reset it please. Why did the lights turn
off in my house? Like come here. All right let's try this again. Okay I have to kill this motherfucker.
Why? I don't know if I like coming this way. Unless can I get there from up here or something?
Who is even looking over here? What? You came all the way from the courtyard. He's just waiting for
him. This way is... I don't know if I want to go this way because they keep... Come on. Come
get me. Let's go. I don't even know where that guy came from. Do that again but this way. No what?
Come on. Fall with me. At least make it worth it for me. Enemies don't fall off platforms in this
game. I'm gonna go the route that I know. I feel when I go that way I just pull everybody
and then they they walk this way. I just have to worry about stupid fucking pan guy. All right
let's go. So I can go that way but will he see me? I wonder. I wonder. Let me just try this.
I don't think he saw me do that. I'm so worried about this guy turning around. This guy's so
oblivious to everything but then again big guy's still here. Hydrate? I will. I'll be fine. I will.
That guy in the other hand is not leaving. Okay turn around. Get out of here. All right if I don't
beat him right here I'm gonna go get some water and fucking just pee and no I'm beating him right
now. That was so delayed. It's so fucking delayed. It's so hard to time it. I've seen if I had frames
on it. No I'm done. Jesus Christ. I'll be right back. Going offline? What? This game is so brutal man.
It's so fucking brutal. It hates you. Everybody makes that joke like oh Dark Souls. From Software
dang you're gonna die. You're gonna lose. You're gonna lose. Not only are you gonna lose in this game
but man From Software is gonna make sure nobody goes to your funeral. You know what I mean?
Easy game. Oh my stream deck is fucked up. It's definitely because you're sick. No.
Am I going to Pax East? I am not going to Pax East. Unfortunately. I live on the west coast now.
It's just something that wasn't really in the cards anymore. Hey beat the game now. Stop trying.
I'm trying. I missed the old Sekiro streams. There's only been two. One of them is yesterday.
I missed the old Sekiro streams. You know the one from yesterday
when he got so mad that he pretended to fall down a well in his fucking room.
Ah again. A good old days like yesterday.
Okay.
All right. Wait for that. Can I go up the stairs? There's nothing else up here. All right. Come on.
Just beat him. Beat this guy. This guy's giving me more trouble than anybody and he's not even a
real boss. He's a fake boss. Wow that was weird. Hi. I just want to say I want to thank everybody
for supporting this this whole time.
I want to thank my mom for giving me the constant support that she has given me my entire life.
Where's the emote? How do I do the emote? How do I? How do I like physics roll this guy off the cliff
and then do a full P stream down on his body? Oh that was so.
Hardest game ever made I'm telling you. Now how does it feel that you are
like the second hardest thing I've done in this game?
First hardest thing was even turning it on. You know. Who the hell are you?
I got overconfidence now. Let's go. I got my confidence back. What's that line?
All right. Stop fucking around. Get out of here. Get out out out out out. Going up top.
I got four beads now. Oh but what? Restore a node of resurrected power
to enslave a Jizo statue in his to express. Okay so I can. I'm so happy to beat that guy.
But do you guys think this is the hardest game ever made? What do you guys think is the hardest
game ever made? And I don't know. Okay let me rephrase that. I know that there are. Okay look.
I know that there is like modded Super Mario levels that are unbeatable. I'm talking about
like a game that was like published by like a major publisher. What do you think it is?
The Jeweled. Ghosts and Goblins. Because I know people are going to tell me that.
Well hold on a second Jeremy. What about like Boshi? Right? Boshi is considered one of the
hardest video games ever. But there's no ad for Boshi. There's no TV ads for Boshi. That's a
bullshit requirement. Now I'm saying like a major AAA published game. And what do you think it is?
Because there are a ton of indie titles that are insanely difficult. I'm talking about ones that
are on the shelf at Walmart. I'm talking about games that you could just go and buy right now
at GameStop. I asked that question 30 minutes ago Jeremy. Thanks for stealing my icebreaker
conversation pieces. So Sekiro is the hardest Walmart game. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Sekiro is the
you. Sekiro is the hardest game you can buy at Walmart. Where am I supposed to go from here?
Oh yeah there was that oh yeah wait no no no there's that other guy. Am I enjoying the game?
I love this game. It's fucking awesome. It's making me it's making me like question everything I've
ever known in my life. It's testing me. You know it's testing me like like a true god should.
What about the Surge? Are we talking about worst games you can buy at Walmart or hardest games
you can buy at Walmart? The hardest Walmart game. That should be a tagline. Sekiro. Yeah. Sekiro.
Be careful not to accidentally buy this. You will hate it. Sekiro. It's too hard for you grandma.
Right? That would have been like if this was on Super Nintendo that's what it would be.
All right I need to get back up to where was that guy that was standing above the thing? He's like
don't go down there unless you want to hear this music. I don't think that was back the other way
wasn't it? Have I even been over here? What's the point of me coming up here? What about this way?
No this is to come back out. Wait is this that? No. Your grandma definitely won't beat this game but
maybe she will. I don't know. It's possible. This is uh hold on. This is okay right yeah here we are.
I didn't go up. I didn't go straight up there. How much money do I have?
Well I have enough to do this. Loose beads. More health and more vitality. More posture.
All right well then let's let's open up the new dialogue then. What is the hardest fucking game
ever? That is like a game and not an unbeatable joke troll game. Ninja Gate. Dragon's Lair.
Wait cough in my face. Take coughed up blood. I'm taking a blood sample. Please if you could
do it directly into my mouth. Get as much of you can in there. Okay.
What's the hardest movie to watch to get through? You think? Because if we're gonna have a video game
definition it has to be a movie and tv show definition. I got something for you.
What's the hardest human activity? Without something that's not just like lifting weights.
Something that's oh uh deadlift a thousand pounds. No.
The gate to the castle however is shut. Let's see.
It's driving? It might be driving. Driving is a really difficult thing to do. It kind of just is.
It's too easy sometimes guys. Come on. All right what do I have here?
All right I need to do one of these. What do I got? There's only a certain amount of these tools
though. Spring loaded firecracker. Spring loaded axe. We can go down axe tree. I kind of like the
firecrackers though. It's hard to mess up firecrackers. They're big radius. They sit
around for a few frames. Cooldown's not great though. I'm not really good with the slow weapons.
Would you recommend this game to someone who just wants to have a good time or like come to hate
myself? It really depends on how you approach it because I mean you've seen right. Anytime you
play a game like this you're gonna hit that point. It happens to everybody. It does. And saying that
it doesn't happen to you is just horseshit and I don't believe you and I would love to hook you up
to a lie detector and have you say these words with a straight face that you don't do these things.
But you're going to get upset at the game. It's gonna happen. You're going to be irritated by
something. You're gonna lose over and over again like you just watched me do in real time. You're
gonna lose like five times in a row to something and go why am I can I even do this? Am I capable
of doing this? And you probably are yeah. But if you're okay with getting through that sort of
pushing a rock up a mountain the experience is unforgettable. All these games. It happened to me
like 10 minutes ago yeah. It's very natural to get upset at this game. Now not to a point where you
know obviously there's different levels of being upset because you can be like what the fuck like
fuck this this is stupid like god I blocked that I blocked that and then like you know you obviously
don't want to get to a level where you're like smashing shit and screaming as loud as you can
and like if it's you don't want like actual like real negative energy coming into your life
because you can't beat a sakura boss. But as long as you you know you you give yourself that limit
you can take a break. I went downstairs and I drank some orange juice. Just smash the tv. No.
But if you can put up with your own mind getting in the way that's what happens every time I play
these games it happens and I know it's gonna happen that's why I always like push through it
and just continue to go because no matter what I say no matter how many things I say about you know
what I'm uh I think this is too hard I'm not sure about this this boss is I think it's impossible
no I know I can't do it I can't I know I'm gonna try again as long as you just like fight through
that your devil on your shoulder telling you that you can't do it you'll get better and you you will
also applies to life in general there's a lot of symbolism while you play these games for
you know getting in your own way getting out of the way trying failing succeeding that's why they
made these games they knew what they were doing yeah but how though I really just keep dying
uh but that's a whole nother conversation entirely though maybe the maybe the game's
just not for you like some people love that kind of intense punishing punishing experience
that forces you to do well otherwise you won't do it at all but you know you don't have to have it
you know you don't have to do it that's look I'm that's what I'm here for right just watch me
scream at stuff and get upset about how bad I am at parrying something but eventually I
I will beat it I don't know when but okay I'm trying to figure out what the hell I want to do
here uh I wonder what you unlock down let's not do firecrackers let's do it enemies in all directions
and then this when you gave up on celeste I beat celeste I just didn't do the extra celeste
just got here when does he play the game I I just was talking about like the difficulty and somebody
asked like how hard it is to get into these games oh I can't have like I've been playing for like
two and a half hours I can't have like what two three minutes of just talking for a second
over over the course of like what is going to be tonight like a 10 hour broadcast no no I don't
how dare you spend three minutes talking about like somebody asked a question
what the fuck now I'm gonna go down this path I want to know what that is well I don't have that
tool but I want it spring-loaded firecracker I'm doing it long spark oh long barrel I wonder what
this is yeah I mean this game is like really intense too so if I I just spent like almost
an hour trying to beat that fucking samurai out in front of the uh the steps there I'm gonna take
a second I gotta collect myself a little you know but now here's the sample obtained one
let me see the narration is very similar to the sculptors the color is just slightly tainted but
what's this do you have enough blood I believe so I know what BWL is I beat that game like last week
when we speak again it's likely I'll have made a breakthrough in fact okay do I have any seeds
BWL he doesn't know BWL he doesn't know yes I do I looked up I got a confession to make
uh I really hate to say this but like I wanted to make sure I was prepared for the stream and
that I'm like a streamer you know I read the Wikipedia page and I read every boss and every
strategy and every reference and I know what whatever item is come on guys I'm streaming it
like I have to like make sure I'm presenting it and I can like keep going I don't get lost or stuck
I know everything I know they did this weird thing like I know the last boss is it's a giant
it's a snake with five heads and then it transforms into a giant goat and with horns and shit I know
what it is I'm sorry I'll try better next time I'm sorry all right oh what's this stuff breath of
nature light get that off the fucking screen a latent scale increases the damage of
increases the damage inflicted to posture upon performing a successful deflection
so it's just more of this no that's not right recovers posture upon executing a successful
death blow yeah um this reduces the amount of damage I want this one I'm gonna save up for this
one isn't this too much of a normie game for me to be playing this what a normie game isn't this
like the anti normie game this is not a game that from your definition of like a what a normie
what is it what does that even mean a normal person what does that even mean
how dare you say that here walmart gaming unbelievable isn't this too much of a normie
I love fucking dark souls in these games come on you've seen me play them all on stream too much
of a normie game what would you rather I play I actually don't know where to go it was was
the reservoir was the castle hold on a second where was it it's the reservoir no it's not
let me just go back here shrek racing they never made shrek racing hey play some underground games
this is okay I'm gonna really I'm gonna hold up the shield here I'm gonna defend I'm gonna defend
myself here can you guys name me the last triple a release that I played on this on this stream
it's probably resident evil 2 where was that guy down here no where the fuck was he shit no where
is it that guy with I was looking over the well it's over here I think played minecraft I was
forced to play minecraft because I lost a bet what are you doing anybody else find it funny
at the time that I I'm not trying to get there as fast as I can and kill pan guy
that pan guy doesn't make a sound but when I when I get there really really quickly pan guy
forgets I don't know what happened here he this is a fucking actor and he didn't expect me to come
back he was waiting for me those other times so now he was surprised to see me oh fuck wait he's
back here no there it is hey I have not heard it but I'm gonna go here we go it's dropped down
there please check this out hey look another free orb hi there how are you okay whoof
did I just hit him oh ow ow ow ow ow what is that where and what does that classify as
as what is that is that a thrust technically it is okay that's I mean that's a weird thrust
not that time buddy where the fuck am I fuck it's okay no god damn it oh my hand slipped
shit I just like uh fuck I had that too my hands are like just covered in sweat
but you know what the problem was switching to this for no reason in fact just get it off the
bar you dumbass what is it even there for you know I'm saying like oh let me switch that and do so
I already have it why would I need to do that fuck I have the uh I bet that one was
when it gets orange never mind I wish the indicator was bigger what the fuck come on
why was that not a thing again that wasn't over him this is kind of just what the hell I'm
even doing this for at this point the camera in here is so bad because of just how small the
corridor is see that's a sweep I haven't seen it yet sweep whoa that didn't work all right come here
here whoa double kick what the hell was that oh goodbye just spam all the buttons
well somebody else is dying now beautiful melody oh that guy's sick too the guy out here oh sorry
I had to do that coughing my face I don't need any more blood all right this time let me get a
solid attempt here by actually like getting the jumping stab oh I'm in the corner bad I can't
fucking move my god why is that even possible welcome to dark souls games if your back's in a
corner you may as well go microwave a fucking burrito that's my motto too
thankfully this is way easier to get back to than the other one fuck man oh man
oh these just movements are so erratic
it's pain oh am I live oh I can parry the kicks I know but when he fake pumps two of them it's
hard to do fucking believable man unfucking believable I just want to get over there
ah I didn't even see it he's breaking my posture so much even when I parry he's doing a dick load
a posture damage even when I'm blocking and parrying shit I gotta back up posture's broken
no man no my god I just I gotta just go in I'm not I'm just going in I'm just gonna I'm just
doing the fuck I'm gonna play the way of the game in a way that I know how and that's fucking
burger boy technique just going it's not gonna work oh the kick is just it's when you think of
countering a thrust a foot is not what you think of you think of a sword or a weapon and I keep
thinking I have to dodge it or jump over it let me thrust you with my foot I didn't stop him what
I'm stuck in the fucking wall what the hell what the hell is this
it's all right come on come on get up
oh my stomach it cut me open fucking hell and I I didn't even I didn't even have the
fuck I didn't even get the this drop down orb removal what the fucking I'm so mad that let
you fucking get this motherfucker you know I'm saying my teeth are clenched he ain't fucking
doing this shit again man get in there bearable unbearable unbearable pain they just get right up
on you so quickly I still have a chance no I don't that's a sweep my posture back please
no no no no this time let me actually get the dive down and then it'll be fine it'll be over
is the second phase harder than the first I don't think it is I mean maybe he adds like a
move or two but I should be able just to get this like this I thought the fucking goddamn ceiling
bump I seriously man come on what the fuck just kill me jump down you saw it up when I jumped
down last time I jumped way over him where the fuck is he oh my god I did it like three times
in a fucking row and I can't do it just kill me again I'm like overthinking it just kill me my
god no hurry off go yeah death I know I can't believe it wait what do you mean jump down here
are you fucking kidding me really hey you lied to me you lied to me you lied to me
I'm gonna die I'm sorry I can't mute right now where am I going I'm going the wrong way I'm so
fucking beyond oh these mini bosses they have hell they're actual hell they weren't fucking
around they really weren't these aren't even bosses these are just guys that are strong
and I'm like I'm getting hyper tilted by even dropping down on the guy and doing a back a stab
on him okay here we go somebody says jump I jumped okay it's time to die all right all right here we
go quiet on the set please he just kicked me he kicked me mom he kicked me in the face from across
the fucking game I'm so mad I'm so angry at the world don't I'm the best I'm the best
you're not the best I'm the best god damn it magnetic ore base material for prosthetic tool
upgrades of intermediate and higher rank and another bead this game is something else
hardest goddamn fucking game of walmart seriously okay how many guys total 30 yeah like I said
that's what we're doing that's a one dollar scratch ticket every death is a one dollar scratch ticket
and maybe but we'll see if you guys want to compile them oh by the way if you don't know
I just want to make sure everyone's aware of this because I mean I talked about it last night late
and this morning so every time I die and I have to I do have to confirm that this is like okay
for twitch terms of service but every time I die I was gonna buy a one dollar scratch ticket
or maybe upgrade them into like a bunch of five dollar scratch tickets and then scratch them at
the end after I beat the game if I do hopefully I do this game's fucking brutal but scratch them all
and whatever I get money wise will just be paid community subs whatever it is I need to make sure
that that's like okay though I need to make sure that that's actually like not against like terms
of service somehow so I'm gonna confirm that I'm going into like a new area here what is that
there's like a snake over there or something or like a toad or a crab this is sorcerer down there
this is okay do I get any means of oh it's just lizards they're really really really easy
okay no shrine or anything of course it is of course I have to fight this thing I see a shrine
down there can I get there from here don't alert the boss can I make this jump
bulging coin my god safety let's rest here I only have 97 dollars I mean do I dare just see what
this is she's shichimen warrior I just like ran into a stop sign can I deflect these I wonder
I don't know what that purple bar is I don't think he does anything besides throw this shit out here
terror oh I just want to avoid this dodging it oh boy well that's what that guy does
maybe illusions yeah I don't think how many I think I only have like one
what can I buy snap seeds I don't have like one well I have one let's just see what it does
just get up there real quick and start smashing them watch out for the terror terror terror terror
terror all right illusions it looks like it's real ghosts are real guys can I bring it back down but
the surety well I'm gonna go for I don't just see what's up here and I unlock this zone might
as well see what it is no it's like a lady
stop screaming
I don't know what's going on out there fuck maybe like a fucking birthday party
I wonder if they got a clown so I get this is just blood-borne yeah this is blood-borne
all right I'm not I don't want to do this I feel like that's I'm gonna be stopped there
let me go back you are the clown uh so this was those two mini bosses I could go back to the
reservoir this is the hmm see if there's anything new here do you have any more info for me I have
one of these tiers but I don't know if I can use it yet oh here we go okay progress yes is the
stagnation in your blood what causes the stagnation the blood has only a limited amount of power
available to it let's say you've used all of this power and then you attempt to resurrect again
the resurrection still occurs but it must draw on power equivalent exchange from those that have
the dragon rod for those who have the dragon rod the natural life force that everyone has
that allows them and function as human beings been taken from them their blood has stagnated
gonna be cured yes by giving back what has been taken here you are dragon's blood droplet
so an item that is really uh by the way I'm gonna mute this for a second because I'm gonna bring up
something I'm gonna just we're gonna listen here for a second let me tell you something ready
I want to make a game show and title the game show birds or small children and see who can
tell the difference if you listen to this could you actually tell because kids like next time
in a grocery store there's a kid being like they sound like birds that could be like a bird habitat
hold on the birthday party must have gone inside yeah I would have different birds making bird
noises and then children outside or children at grocery store and see if anybody could really
actually tell the difference sometimes you can't tell all right recovery charm so now I actually
have this so you can offer a dragon's blood droplet to a sculptor's item to restore all
afflicted with the dragon rod all right so I have two of these now right I thought I had two of them
didn't I buy one of these oh there's one in storage okay the recovery general's dragon rod
suffers to be healed from sculptors idol a dragon blood droplet can be consumed to heal dragon root
from all those afflicted doing so will cause all rot essence to disappear returning the chances of
receiving unseed a to the default value which what does it know seven percent now the question that
I have for this though is should I use these now or should I say I have two I wonder if I should
save them or will people just start dying I feel like this is the weird from software catch that's
in all these games what do I do with these should I hold on to them I mean maybe I could
just do it I have two dragon rod healed so now I have I have another one so it heals everybody
not just one person okay that's cool what do I got skills right I wanted to this is five
put down here Ichimonji double as a follow-up overhead sword strike to Ichimonji deals high
posture damage and also recovers one's own posture the follow-up attack is especially useful for
preventing enemy counterattacks yeah it's just a much better version of this hmm I want this one
though I'm gonna get this one first all right now the real question of the evening here
is where the fuck do I go now that's a great question yes bottle of sake by given by Emma
sake is a drink meant for sharing doesn't contain water from the fountain that is made from the
purest of waters and as a drink beloved by the people now I want some fucking drink what is it
it's his favorite tea I thought it would be a fitting way to celebrate his return to hell
get drunk give drink wait you just oh he just gave okay maybe I'll make my own like
brewed up fucking sake
don't drink alcohol you're sick no I'm not I'm not sick I just have this lingering I feel better
justify I feel great
that's maybe it'll leave me play better here you know wait we're done here wait so I have
the Ashina sake I have this unrefined shit so this is a case of let me take the product from
over there give this guy the unrefined dog shit one and then keep one for myself and sell it
which one I wonder what if this open maybe this opens up something else take the good one
I brought some tea he smells pretty good the boys I'll have some mix them together
I like one of those now Emma's father about lady Emma's father what go again he was an
extraordinary doctor he drank Emma's father used to pee in a cup and devices better put he was
obsessed with mechanisms tastes just like Emma's father's pee that's my favorite pee seriously but
I owed him I would say that you owe him your life as well what do you mean when I lost my left arm
Dogen created that thing which has now become your left arm the first version was a complete
failure didn't work at all so he then he remade it again and again I tell you it's too easy
sometimes he told me I needed to practice with the prosthetic in order to use it properly
so Emma would pester me into carving her spinning tops and other toys after much
training of that sort it came to be called a shinobi fang in other words that prosthetic arm
is Dogen's legacy his legacy so much time has passed by shinobi ways that alone I could not
bear to abandon so any booth us is the face of those who owe a deep karmic debt understand
when you try carving one for yourself so okay ask about your arm all right but I can use various
purifying agents to further hone that purifying agents so if you find something of that simple
purifying agents what about the unrefined one something should I just give this to him
or do I can I use this for a different I wonder if you just take this yeah just take it I brought
some sake don't mind if I do oh Spencer Spencer I got a question for you is it not tear-licking
no it's damn good oh you have no idea okay but it does make my old wounds
ache you're left on yes and this sake was a favorite of the man who is she
is she he did it for my sake did it for my sake oh I was on the verge of being consumed
consumed by what sure well they're talking about sake come on I thought he like cut his arm off to
get his secret crabby patty sake recipe I don't know okay I hope you enjoyed that sake all right
I don't have any seeds so what do I need to do now look at that bad bad game design bad game design
look at that blurry like bug patch right there bad game development game dev no nevermind all right
I've wasted enough time bottoms hole I don't think there's anywhere else I can go let me go
back here let's take a look so this is the reservoir no the heat that that boss was up there
he's dead um I feel like there was another place to go wasn't there this is the castle
yeah let me go back out there was that spot up the stairs yeah right here up this way
I'm no lawyer man but I just read the terms of service and I feel like scratch cards are okay
but here's another thing though not just scratch cards but whatever money is one off the scratch
cards I buy a bunch of community subs subs with that I'm gonna I'll add that's like a that's a
weird like roundabout thing I gotta like ask maybe or it could just be to charity too charity yeah
no that's a good idea as well now let's rest here and then I'm gonna take a look upstairs
so there's that let me just see what's up this way there's a
I could go this way let's check over here no I mean I've been uh I've just I hate this game
I've been pretending this whole time I'll probably see you guys tomorrow no no the dog the dog the
dog the dog the dog in the stairs that was perfectly executed oh what hit me oh you're
homing boomerang devices what the hell are those he's actually curving bullets at me
is that it clear the area and then I'm gonna take a little exploration what's in there oh boy this
goes up high hold on oh um and this stuff down here I don't really want to just miss everything
right just wait hold on I need to yeah I'm gonna slow this down I don't want to just jump across
let me just and yeah see this is what I want to do come over here what did that incense pot do to
me you ever have an incense pot in your house it's just it's overpowering sometimes this looks like
the only way to go it's a fire hazard same anymore I feel like this probably items are missing yeah
like over there cam security cameras look at this it's like four security cameras right there right
with my head is right now see that they'll get alerted all right I gotta get across
okay whatever all right let me try can I jump from here and grab that balloon of wealth I
gotta use these two I have so many whoa whoa who's looking who sees who sees me uh backstab this
guy no there's like five people here that's a mistake vendor or something down there who are you
but aren't you on the enemy team maybe maybe I should say yeah yeah that's right
unfortunate things happened and now they're after me day and night
I'm at the end of my rope here he's not gonna get a quest so far up there you'd think they'd
have bigger things to worry about than chasing after me anyway so of course I'll make I make
my living selling information selling info the samurai around here I'll let you in on something
sure of course how many do I have to kill do you have a number in mind or all of them just one
see you later all right I did it where's my info maybe I should get rid of all of them
anymore down here nope all right I'll take that info please take care of the shinobi and I'll give
you some info here as promised it's all yours beacon memo a note on smoke signals used by
Ashina shinobi the gray night jars pale pink smoke signals are placed along the rooftops of
Ashina castle these signals guide the night jar the ashen feathered flock are surely the only ones
able to follow such a trail see you pal maybe we'll cross paths again someday so the stuff
the burning incense stuff oh sorry but I don't do business in dangerous places like this
he who fights and runs away you know maybe we'll cross paths again okay so any more dialogue look
friend you're not going to convince me maybe we'll cross okay well that means yes I'll see you soon
all right so the the smoke things on the top I think requires some investigating there's one
of those weird bird bird boomerangs up there item yeah what a smoke this fire you know what I mean
this one oh there's an item right here I I bet I have like 500 of those okay I just don't even
use them hey sup okay here we are anything else no no no no no no no no just fell down
no come on stop being so sloppy with this there really is cameras oh no it's not
these guys are pained I'm not supposed to use it up there no this way what the fuck
oh that's gonzo the great just shot out of a cannon at me oh my god ah kermit
you got gnomed in the game well there's an item this way um um uh oh uh oh this was not a good
idea oh my god the whole baseball team is here what the fuck oh there's a bad guy okay let's
approach this differently I gotta get back up here can I reach this from here no that was
insane I gotta go back the other way I just I actually just jumped off the building just jumped
off of the building and didn't care I'm gonna wrap back around geez they're all just standing here
they were waiting for me they're all waiting for me oh fuck oh shit oh
bye come on you you you now no fuck there's too many there's too many it's just too many
it's five people turn the corner and they're just all waiting for me four of them just waiting for
me at least I know where I'm going although I have to deal with all those people again and this I
probably was so close to some form of god damn it sorry whatever where are you going man baseball
teams thrive on rooftops what I'm saying did you just see that why don't my character freeze
now I'm just rushing all right this time I gotta watch out for gonzo gonzo's up here
oh no there's another oh my god this I didn't make the oh my god this guy had to die he was
just down here okay not this time all right come on gonzo okay so I have one heal left
and a resurrect so let me see how the fuck I approach this I got two pellets all right
one there see I went this way maybe if I just hug this wall can I go down maybe I can go down
to level no let me put on some shit throw the cans derma lied about minecraft vr thanks to
the five community subs oh welcome subs thank you derma lied about minecraft for you five subs
thank you thank you thank you I wonder if there's the only one there is it one down here I don't
think there's one over here maybe I don't lizard I guess I'm gonna try down here I hear something
walking oh poison watch it watch it watch it is anything down here no just lizards that's where
I fought spear guy a body of water over here nothing to jump to guess I'm guess I'm gonna go
for it what is that doesn't open from this side shit this um oh there's people there
hold tight hold on I am lost oh this spear wizards there is a bonfire right there
I'm first made it nice oh where I don't even know where I ended up so where is this
so this is old grave hmm what about this way well that's another uh dragon root heal
cool item up there grave robber another sugar so this is the stealth sugar let's just take a look
I gotta pee but I'm curious about this area you didn't see a little scoundrel come running
through here did you we're after one and I'm fairly sure he came this way what was he wearing
get a black hat on short little guy black hat I don't have one thing is nobody's passed this way
at all the only thing that did look like some kind of animal a raccoon maybe a badger couldn't say
for sure you sure you didn't mistake that animal for your criminal oh come on forget it
mistake this oh fuck it let's just go come on
anything else nope a lot of items here though oh bald guy bald guy
cannon guy whoa who who saw me guy the cannon saw me I guess well let's just pull this guy down
oh it's a pan guy of course the guy with the fucking pan sees me well I got everything there
is that not I can't grab up there should be able to right I gotta just oh I just got denied so
and I got shot on the ground wow I didn't just got so denied you gotta go first
all right now let's not try to get disrespected again you fuck you not fair come on why can't you
hurt yourself with that shit I can't get him I can't get him reloading all right that guy
was a pain in the ass he shot so many times and he had to reload his gun brings us to here and
nothing else I'm missing though but yes because I want to get that come on I can't reach from here
yeah I can there's a hole in this roof Jeremy Jeremy okay more sugar NPC uh told those morons
to give it a rest but they don't they just keep sending more such a pain in my
are you one of them nightjar cronies no no of course not there's something different about
but I'd say you're in the same line of work this is my favorite character
what's yours I don't know real sociable one first this stubborn lot now we're down in the dumb
and then those boys racing hell outside could this day get any better you're a fugitive
something like that sure by the by I'm a little out of got the goods but in the cellar too vendor
waiting for someone like you to show up oh bite down on your controller secrets shinobi drug
when times call for death by one's own hand samurai turn their swords on themselves
as a matter of pride while shinobi demand a swifter means simply crush in the back teeth to die
nothing more is required resurrection is not limited after use why would I want these
resurrections not limited after use so what I said the attack can't but these iron fortress
can be fit into the shinobi prosthetic become a working prosthetic tool experienced iron ribbed
fan users can deflect arrows and even bullets using this tool oh it won't it wouldn't be
surprising if the next owner decided to wait was impractical so it's just a giant metal shield
to block from arrows and bullets okay what about this anti-air it's a shinobi martial art anti-air
death blow a technique technique which serves the shinobi who is not bound by the earth in battle
leap towards an opponent who has exposed himself in mid-air and strike killing him before he hits
the ground huh okay well I got money I got coin bags how many do I have how much is this is this
a thousand I would assume this is at least 750 I could get them both thousand okay so that's how
much is it total for everything so this is the anti-air death blow try it and then it's another
1600 yep and then so I need I need 1350 I get 250 so I need 1100 so long no how many no the light
ones are not that much never mind so long I mean I thought for some reason I don't know why I
thought that was gonna be 500 so that's 13 that's 16 okay something should I get all the three should
I get these three of them yeah fuck it let's just buy them so long yeah I'm gonna spend the money
somewhere okay so that leaves me with I have to go learn the skill right and that's a prosthetic
thanks guy anything else to say hear about this one rats have been swarming into ash in the castle
these days you know the one that means but there's this hell bent old timer oh I know who that is
I know was he wearing a Tengu mask see I killed for him it was a quest we spoke you're just full
of surprises I'm impressed he let you keep your head right so you know that I hadn't heard
at the big castle gates where there's a watchtower yeah I saw it I knew it I knew what I knew what I
know I know so long so long okay so I gotta be getting close to some kind of the door or
something a door or a new area or something right yes there's a there we go here's the door
let's go fit this shit wait let me just make sure I didn't there's nothing else down there right
just that guy and then over this way so go down to the right next time can I go this way let me
just see what's over here um let me fit the prosthetic and I gotta pee too I have not peed
in four hours it's kind of remarkable we must go to the new area I still fit new prosthetic tool
loaded umbrella uh-huh iron-ribbed umbrella to the arm costs spirit emblems to use when spread open
it will protect against all attacks from all directions hold it out while moving to protect
from light attacks but this is an umbrella after all it won't protect you from low attacks such as
sweeps shit really okay just want to see if it was on the uh let's test it out yeah light attack
light attacks not all of them yeah what do I replace in here probably this loaded umbrella and
uh I like them I like this let's see loaded umbrella cool now I also have let's go to skills
let me see what that looks like I'm gonna pee my pants fuck I have enough to do what I wanted to do
for this but what was that skill anti-air death blow it's a shinobi martial art so is it just
in here somewhere that I what do I just have it now is it one of these you just have it okay
okay all right I gotta pee I'll be right back see you in two seconds well two minutes I'm back
good to go what are you linking me here Mickey Mouse hat that's fucking funny just sad just a
sad boy trying to get through Sekiro no we're good Oswald hat yeah that's true that's not
Mickey Mouse that is Oswald you're right please correct me because I was speaking
complete not truths all righty from here so I already have the skill which is how do I do it
though do I is there a way can I is it just happen maybe I should train yeah let's go visit the guy
we haven't seen this guy in a while oh speaking of people we haven't seen there's
a castle I'm gonna be hanging around here for a while I need time to sort through all the info
I've got speaking of which I'm happy to do business with you well all right this is I
finally have somebody in the town to sell to a high king 10 community subs thank you milk
for your 10 community subs the king of all milk oh finally yes pellets a seed a gourd seed do I
have enough to buy this I might buy I do no I don't that's a thousand shit I don't have enough
what about selling anything here that I don't care about there you go I only have the two coin
purses will only get me to a thousand and I need two thousand what does this do I don't know who
knows pellet well at least I have a place to actually buy and sell things so that puts us
in a position to uh right I want to go talk to this guy we haven't been up here in a while
I thought he was on fire for a second you may use me to hone your training uh we already did these
anything new tracks I certainly fit that description and I suppose that's interesting
things make their way yeah we already come up with bucks if you have nothing in the box let's take
a look at this one more time anti-air death blow so looking for anti-air death blow in the skills
menu there it is okay so it's it's just here right trigger near an enemy high up in the air
so it's a death blow if they're in the air only okay I think it's time for me to go so where was
I going the old grave is where I was in the bottomless hole I'm gonna go just back to the
old end of the stream no I'm fine stopping for a while okay so let's see I already did everything
down there which leads us back this way maybe there's that general out here I did kind of just
speed through that area over here did I already look through here yeah so the grave was maybe
like just take a peek out here I don't think so remember I I could not even fucking I couldn't
kill these guys it's so weird just how you see how you progress progress through these games
I couldn't even attempt to fight those guys yesterday all right so we go let's go this way
across the bridge eavesdrop I do I'm streaming Shakira salt who's the bigger threat
uh I don't know that guy that guy's this guy his sword is like I know I'm gonna regret not ever
using one of these all right well there is tall grass here to hide in something just fell from a
tree what are they I don't know what they are is it people is it bugs wizards what is it gonna
dash what is it it's a monkey that was funny they're not that dangerous so let's see if there's
anything else over here can I get on top of the trees makes sense right that sounded like me
screaming I'm a monster why I'm being attacked I'm being swarmed that didn't feel good I felt
bad that's unnecessary anything else besides just like chimpanzees I think I'm good but I'm
gonna be cautious still uh all right uh just a house anything inside of the house that's a
real question those balloons of spirit well here we go always triple check
uh-huh that leads us to here can I make this jump I don't know maybe I guess so yeah oh shit um
what is down this way have I already gotten this no there's an item sunken valley uh I
I was on my way and this is like looks like another area this is a new area
so sunken valley is down that way I gotta remember that uh I was gonna teleport back up to
there wait what about over here god damn it I mean I kind of have to let me just see what's
over here shit he's that's quick he's got a gun on top of that wow that's a pretty cool weapon
blood-borne weapon this way um so many paths to choose from I don't know which one to go through
I could go over here I guess through the mist snowy the outskirts this looks like an area
where you fight a guy like that I don't know if this is a boss though prey slaughtered what just
a free prayer bead and a pacifying agent okay so reduces terror buildup it's just like a that's
cool it's like a little pond all right drink from pond that's another one right here they
tried to be sneaky and hide it behind the ice another pacifying agent okay cool that's a cool
little spot I'll just take I'll take the prayer bead it's very useful nice what was that guy
doing down here he just like sharpening his wooden stick I killed him for literally no reason well I
did kill him for a reason because if I didn't kill him he was gonna try to kill me I preemptively
killed that guy to protect myself which leads to this way back to the all right now I can go down
that's case sunken valley down here or I'm gonna go back to that other teleporter that I just
unlocked and which one was it this one right here can you play minecraft now thanks in advance
um no I'm not gonna play minecraft sorry in advance eel liver greatly reduces the amount
of damage received from lightning attacks as well as shock status abnormality okay is there
nothing else I can do over here yeah this brings us back down to like sunken valley
was there somewhere in this behind maybe I feel like I didn't get to the end of that last
exploration over here no uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh I'm gonna just turn around because when the
gods of the great was flying down I didn't keep going that way I went down so if that's the case
then I should come back out here and go back up right not this one which one was it is this the
closest one if I come out and go back around I think it is we'll find out in a second won't we
hi now this way and then is this the way this is the monkeys right monkeys move that way
is there another way I could go from the monkey path because I went down from here I wonder if
I can go up or over here yeah okay so I went down this way can I do anything up here does
this just take me back down to where I was hi yeah this is just that shrine now I gotta go back to
the way raid a raid just came in massive raid a huge raid hold on I've got chimpanzees fighting
me the Dan's gaming raid oh shit all right hold on wait wait wait wait I can't embarrass myself
right now is it no it's real Dan's gaming 2100 thank you so much for the raid that's uh welcome
guys hope you had a good stream I'm not sure if uh I'm not sure if Dan is also doing you know
secure hopefully you're doing well I'm struggling a bit but it's fantastic so far welcome to the
stream as I try to climb uh walls you can't actually climb now I'm like nervous oh shit
all right wait wait wait wait wait I got look I'll show you how much of a gamer I am I promise
so where was I over here look at this idiot can I do that just wait I promise I'm good I'm pretty
good at parrying I can uh I could dodge I can block but hi regardless I think I've made it did
I make it to the right spot I gotta get back up can't open that door because this is uh how
did I get over here it was over here right I'm lost hey welcome to the stream I'm also sick too
what about through here yeah I have a cough too so if you're wondering I'm fairly sick at the
moment I'm gonna go back to where I know where I was going it's probably better I did just the
castle because this is where the stairs leading up to that guy with the and if I keep going up
this way yeah right okay so here we are I didn't deal with this yet but this is the way to go up
and this is where gonzo the great comes in and then from gonzo the great all right I gotta fight
though just wait wait wait what's that item worth I'm glad I saw that I wouldn't have got that at
all is that item oh shit I can't open this uh thank you for Frilly thanks for the 10 community
subs coming in with big subs thank you so much all right let's do this again that's probably
a better place for me to jump up right here thank you for the 10 subs let me slow it down now here
we go yeah I gotta go up there we're gonna beat the did I just aggro them all right so up around
back to where gonzo is all right I'm on the right path it's got to clean it out I'm gonna take it
slow because I have full health no reason for me to go crazy gonzo is gonna show up where are the
other people that are on top here see you come here make a jump quick yeah I was supposed to
put on the Japanese uh I was gonna say Japanese dub for a second I'm like that's not how that
fucking works gonzo I forgot about gonzo shit okay that could have been real bad
hold r1 to thrust what oh no no no don't fuck this up this is where I got collapsed on before
so I went down from here I gotta go up from here and watch out for the huge
watch it I want I need to pull somebody here just like well that didn't do it this guy
I have so many just follow me over here come on one by one just pull look at me I'm here
I'm just barely not close enough to irritate you enough to okay bring it in come on let me
get rid of you before this guy comes over here please oh yeah all right we're fine just pull
them back and I want to you got any more cards in your deck asshole come on all right there's two
there's only two more up top and then let's just go I'll aggro this guy maybe not I can get behind
oh this guy is stupid oops I'm stupid idiot I didn't mean to do that all right this is as far
as I got last time coming up here but there's an item this way let's get it can I trade these in
can I seriously just sell these wait a minute will he see me do this it was another gonzo but I don't
I don't think he didn't get me where was he that guy just flew away uh why why did that happen
was he the one making the sound I don't understand okay well it's a chest here yes
oh my goodness thank god there's a gourd seed here I can buy a gourd seed how many how much money do I
have 550 do I have any more two heavy coin purses that'll be 1500 it's not quite enough but I'm gonna
go because if I bring this at least I'll get one gourd seed here all right there you go that makes
me five right I don't have enough money so I'm just gonna store it let's just buy one so I'm gonna
buy a heavy coin purse because I'm just gonna lose I'm gonna die like 30 times here probably
this is probably a boss that'll put me at yeah because that'll be 1500 next time I could also
just grind for money but I don't know if I really want to do that upper tower antechamber hey
spoilers this game has bosses oh change the language right right right I'm sorry I keep
forgetting to do that can you from here I don't think you can change it from here oh sorry guys
I did attempt I made an attempt yeah don't I know this guy I swear to god I know this guy
oh that's a thrust okay he's got a lot of fake outs oh that gets like a full second after that
almost this is the cat the casting call for if you can fight this boss or not apparently
through this door all right um nothing else in this house let's do it again
discovery spawn that's much easier that's the real that's canon right there oh shit okay there's a
whole new area okay left right these are new enemies there's a guy like a window shop over
there okay let's try does this work yes I'm surprised that actually did that now come on
what does this impasse here why don't you turn around which way you're gonna go go left no shit
back it up back it up I'm dead oh you know that guy don't you there we go it's always a thrust
there's a lady oh please no oh I'm just a maid for fuck's sake should I not have done that
uh quickly get it this guy's not wearing pants they both swing at the same time I didn't block
that one oh I'm out of stamina or something hey all right fighting you and your dad in the same
room is not gonna work just get me the hell out of here where's my dad how come I don't get a dad
oh my god I hate you I hate you I'm just give me all the stuff in case I die that's pretty good
scrap iron oh sugar come on I'll take a lock on please no dad holy shit he really is like pissed
off about this oh my fucking god he's gonna get he's gonna get vengeance for dad isn't it okay
that was way sloppier than it really needed to be I have seven skill points I think I should
probably take care of this I'm gonna go down oh man okay uh I gotta put some points in I collected
pretty much everything I needed to collect right this is important so down here I was doing this
path this one reduces the amount of damage to posture when attacked by an enemy with a sword
cool I really want this Ashina cross requires the combat art Ashina cross
from a sheathed stance draw the blade at high speed it costs spirit emblems to use hold the
stance to intercept at will interesting okay wasn't there this I'm gonna wait for this one
I want the extra heal unless this is not bad either excuse me just extra spirit emblems
is just useful I think I'll get it what's this recovers vitality upon performing a successful
death blow that's also really good now I'll get this one yeah it doesn't go up by hold on a minute
did that only go up by one emblem that doesn't seem worth it um okay interesting all right uh
let's try to sneakily get through this area
up or down let's see down I guess but does this not open I feel like I should be able to open this
how did the guy with the no pants get in here that's what I wonder all right so now I'm gonna
I could fall down and try to kill one of them go for just a jump here I think that's what I'm
gonna try imagine that happened in front of you it just did it did just happen more eel
liver that's the electricity one all right roomful items posture damage all right the next box the
next boss we're already opening this one I'm gonna try to eat those candies uh is it an ancient
kodachi short sword this is a new tool is it a second weapon I don't think so I think you
only get the katana right this is the door I couldn't get in before cool okay so then if I
wanted to this is okay there's this one there yeah cool nice shortcut that's a sweep
well cool good thing I just lost half my fucking money unbelievable what's the point why did I
I don't even care about this shortcut why do I care about this this just made this worse for me
this made it hard to get through right because this is just oh my god I forgot about these guys
were spawning uh I'm going back to town I'm going back to town I'm gonna buy the the pouches because
I have like 300 I need to just store it I'll be so close I can only afford two of these sell just
something stupid how many vases do I have yeah just sell like fucking two of these
that's all I need yeah you're right I haven't even opened the umbrella that's true
so this puts us down here wait no what's this this one oh the new prosthetic too
ah I'll do it in a minute damn it there's a lot going on in my brain with this
stop I haven't even used I haven't even used the one I just got I don't know what it looks like
all right so it's the sabi maru let's take a look at it the blue poisonous rust on the blade
applies poison status prosthetic tool with the blade allowing for a quick series of attacks
together with the sword I'll give it a try and it does poison that's cool I already did the gourd
seed no okay I have I have almost enough money to buy that seed let's keep progress moving here
take your time sweet boy show umbrella oh it's just okay now what about this that's not bad
it's really not you can probably supplement it for a little all right
come on you think you're gonna get it off you're not so I'm at the bottom of this tower
backstab the guy take out his buddies and then I'm not sure if there's anywhere I can go from here
hello the bonfire at the top as well yeah that's true I just want to see if there's
anything else down here because it's easier to go from here than it is to go from the top
there is a way over here another shortcut oh this is the don't go steal their
fucking lucky charms and get out of here this is the general here
that's one way to stand up okay I had to listen to the whole thing first
what's in here divine grass this is the full complete all heal that I'm not going to use
at all I may have you know what I'm think I'm going to sell that because realistically think
about it in games like these when they're so hard and you die all the time you never know when to
use them I know a good opportunity sell it so you get money for it because if you use that and die
at a boss it's gone you didn't kill the boss I can use that money for other shit this is probably
a bad idea somebody behind me now who's behind me somebody throwing rocks who's throwing rocks
at me that's a slash all right what's this idiot up here it's okay I gotta memorize this shit
you fucking asshole hit shut up over here god does he have two he's got him both back
I gotta fight him over here fuck whatever oh my god I'm just boning back to the bonfire
oh god's sake there is a strategy that's possible and that's just kill the guy next to him no
okay kill the guy next to him kill everybody then once everyone's reset go from there right
so I can just keep picking them off one by one and then he'll eventually reset with two and I
just go behind him and kill him I hope they don't come in here they're not that's not this stupid
they're too dumb to come in here right you ever played this game before Jeremy come on
they did come in here I knew it all right so let's see if that strategy works goodbye
bye goodbye you'll all forget I was here and then you'll go back to doing whatever you were doing
people linking the slap that's great we have a bunch of new people that came over from Dan's
gaming defer you're gonna show them the slap that's the first thing you show them what about
beat beating flame lurker first try someone's got a clip of that one right I don't think they're
gonna I might just have to go kill them they all have guns though so this one might not be as big
of a deal yeah that's what we're doing get out again did I just what am I locked onto still he
died to pinwheel yeah you can you can you can spelt that bullshit all you want we all know the
truth all right come on come on come on come on come on come on come on come on didn't die to
pinwheel don't let anybody let any of these fucking I was gonna say prankers but that doesn't make any
sense all right give up give up so I can do this without a problem fine just go down and do it
what am I waiting for now I get the hell out of here so hopefully this easy let's see is
he gonna reset here don't come in this room oh fuck he came in this room no he's not he doesn't
know what huh wait wait wait wait wait what did he just fucking bait me to do this oh my god
now where is he come on uh is he gonna come to square one come on back out here so I can
let me beat this guy first try come on reset reset reset I'll just hang off the ledge I'm so
hidden right now I am twice over him drop down yeah is he go where is he still in there
where is he uh there he is I don't know what the hell he's doing I don't think he's gonna reset
I hate it I love it that's fast he just sweeps and he just thrusts fuck that tracking though
oh goodbye I'm dead hey thanks for the aid when he's gonna hit you move
ah nah I'm just gonna be a dumb ass already watch this he's blocking the door
want to say how you do this like an asshole I'll show you how many pizzas is it gonna take before
you guys eat the whole pie come on there we go yep yep somebody else fighting down there
okay okay fine time to lose these ones now so what really you're that far away and you still
are doing this what the fuck uh now can you leave me the fuck alone can you see him oh yeah
he's across the whole game oh don't worry I'm homing I'm homing fucking boomerangs that I can
throw as long as I have line of sight from across the game I'll hit him this whole thing was just an
this whole thing was a mistake I need to reset just reset the damn thing my god I went in there
like an asshole and then had aim hacks pointed at my head fucking bald Gandalf over here
I'm at that's I'm at the stage again where like I just get shaken up somebody just bursted
through the door grabbed me by the back shoulders and just rocked me back and forth as hard as they
could come on man let's go he's got a backwards hat on he's just like fucking funneling alcohol
let's go buddy come on then he leaves the room I don't want to go down there I don't want to
fucking do that what have I done all right can I please stop being so stupid did I do that I've
started coughing I had to mute how did I do that on purpose I didn't I'm just going to the front
door this is gonna be another one of those situations took me so long to kill it took me
so fun to kill the last mini boss I'm seeing I'm looking up I'm at the bottom of a giant skyscraper
and I just know it's gonna be a very long climb to get up there and I got two plungers
they're guaranteed to work they're not some weird like little fucking gremlin guy
yeah hey I guarantee you these will work 100 the plunger is perfectly fine they work
but I have to climb up like that side of the empire state building plungers
and now what if I'm already fucking it up
isn't there one of those things up here why did it not grab the wall
why can I not grab that what why I'm so flustered right now
I need to go eat like a Snickers I'm gonna shove the Snickers up my fucking nose
okay what was my plan here though what's the plan I don't have a plan it was to kill guys
don't even think about it I don't have I don't have a plan there's no plan I have to come from
this way where did they come from I don't have a goddamn plan the plan is to you gotta backstab
the big guy and then just deal with all the other people that's just how it works I mean it's how
I'm gonna do it I might be wrong I'm definitely wrong but every time I play the way I think is
wrong I end up winning you all know it look at every boss fight everything every encounter
what do you got fight him in this stupid room
slash dash what what would you do that for he felt bad for me he just gave me a free hit
yeah I mean you're doing really terribly people that just make it fun of you so I'm gonna make
it easy I'm getting trolled right now by a guy in pvp he knows he's gonna kick my ass I think
actually you know it's funny I think this has actually happened before when I played in Dark
Souls pvp and then they one hit kill me what are you doing are you not gonna fight me inside why
you want to fight me over here which fuck okay at least he's in the room that was a sweep I
thought it was the thrust fuck me look at his health though like come on he's so close to this
there's one oh my frames are dying dropped frames everywhere I think we're good dash
holy fuck how did he not hit me with that I have no idea I wish you would stay in this room
you're such an asshole fuck oh why come on
don't you think about this don't you think about this he doesn't like fireworks
did you actually just do that all right cool so now what do I do first try more like I want you
to take a moment everybody to understand the first time I did it the stupid fucking way that I wanted
to do it and it works I have to just trust my instincts here do what if I like sneak up
you don't know that's Waldo from uh what's his name Waldo from the simpsons I don't know his
name the guy that drives the bus oh fuck I have guns all right wait wait wait wait
now just that's how this game works I one shot at the drunk boss by killing his guys running
and rinse and repeat then I okay can I please no wait no oh excuse you didn't forget about me
I don't want to throw us utensils down I don't I think I can get out of here now
hey don't you forget about looking at me I think that's it there's nothing else I can do I have
to go now go all the way up the tower maybe don't be a fool what oh right up the stairs oh I don't
think upstairs maybe maybe um I actually have no idea what do we have what are half the places
here there's up here where the that first top of the tower is there's I could go back I could go
down to that sunken valley let me see there's that way down towards the monkeys but that goes
down to the sunken village place let me go back up like the top of the building just go all the
way up see yeah the Japanese audio is in the options I don't see anywhere they have to do
it at the menu that's what I thought I'm so bad at stealth so what about back up front let me just
see because I came in here is there more up this is the explode guy this guy I thought he was
already dead I thought it was that guy right there that does the hoop um I heard him I just
for some reason didn't think I thought he came from like down there I didn't think he came from
over here so he was up there all right um I don't think I can go higher from here I'm just gonna
rest again he did this time imagine being that strong that if you walk into a display it just
explodes in front of you imagine just the absolute balls you must have and you just don't give a shit
it just explodes all right oh that doesn't that's that lady so this door I can't open
I can go in that room yeah I am sorry for all the coffin guys oh shit oh my god oh my god
what do I do oh my god how do I stop this lady from doing anything what do I do I thought I had
like a shuriken or something I didn't fuck it's just one just one one-on-one one-on-one's fine
poisoned him fuck he broke my posture I have a lot of trouble with these guys
I don't know why they're just they're just better than me in every way dude you have no health will
you just like fuck off that dude was already dead that dude was dead three times oh shit that was
just lag man I killed that guy like four times and it's a computer and his internet connection
caught up with him touch bullshit I have people like you know rip out their ethernet code and plug
it back in you really want to win that bad okay well here's that room I couldn't go in so we got
old lady with a cupcake and uh this guy well I can definitely get you I didn't want her to start
screaming and then all of a sudden we have a big problem we already we have a big problem all right
bye they're not gonna follow me in here right they don't know where I am it's just two people
it's three it's the guy with no pants yeah see two guys always two guys it's actually four guys
three guys just go after him it's only two guys it's three of them there's no way I could have
like pulled him oh my god how many times do you have to block and attack before you fucking do
something oh just open this no I can just sneak in here why would I want to do that though
wait what is an item over here he's gross gross mouth streamer is what somebody just called me
gross mouth hey I'm sick I get an excuse you kill my posture man just destroy it
back to back in a room I hate you
hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry oh did it work did I get it I don't know if I did
you got to be kidding me
don't do the magic he's so angry at you if you beat me here okay this guy kills me
I'm gonna give 600 000 community subs I'll give this up to everybody on twitch everyone that has
a twitch account I will contact twitch directly to do this so what is here while I have a second
here how much money do I have all right it's time I need another gourd doubling nothing no I
ain't doing that again so now I have the pouches so I got six seven eight nine well yeah okay I
got plenty so let me let me do the math right here so I have six seventy three seven eight nine ten
so four so let uh that'll bring me to I need two thousand right and then I can sell some little
piece of shit hey hey tell me it's probably worth it all right so I can just get rid of
vases I don't use them I hate these things so I need 73 83 93 nope not enough math wrong
wouldn't it what a dummy what an idiot gourd seed so let's bring me to six right yes
yes maximum gourds increased while I'm still here let's take a look at what I can do with the
upgrade path here any new tools no okay this is what I've already purchased don't know what this
is though I have the improved firecracker which takes me down to spring load flame vent
this is currently unavailable because I don't have this I'm missing some new tool that I should
probably have by now play the game where you spill the buckets talking about um you're talking about
this for cleanup detail why this is for cleanup detail cam on what the fuck that'd be bad because
I don't have any clothes on some of these people say I should buy the memo how much is it
so tomorrow memo five hundred dollars until next I don't have it what's the memo
does it unlock an ability forward or something am I sweaty yeah probably upper tower here we go
I'm sick don't want to be bothered with the face cam yeah yeah I've been kind of under the web
so uh this is a thing I can listen to right here and I can go down but hold on where does this
bring me that brings me here yay all right let's listen to the memo yeah I know the door just want
to hear this okay uh Larry lizard says streamer please stop what you're doing can you play my
favorite game yeah what's up which one I'll load it up right now which one what's your very good
securo all right let me load it up for a second though from software
that's game of thrones but here we are is this it yeah I aimed to please yeah I wasn't planning
on playing securo but I'm gonna I guess I'll try it uh-oh
I'm gonna give you three seconds to come out with your hands up one two three should have
fucking listened should have listened oh wow that was overpowering that was uh I got him
hanging scroll of an old battle ghosts once lurked the lands of Ashina the ghosts lightning was of
the fountainhead gods unstoppable by normal means avoid ground reverse the lightning
lightning reversal if one is standing on the ground lightning surges through them making
movement impossible but if one is struck while in the air the lightning can be dispelled from
the body and sent at an enemy instead don't stand on the ground get lightninged in the air
uh okay can I go up here palette well we are getting items here gonna get introduced probably
to a boss real soon I think I can see him he's just waiting there look at him he's gonna fly
in right who's whistling to me oh no this here it is okay let's go
it's a wonder he's still with us is that so rematch from the beginning
divine air I'll ask you once more accept me to your mortal into fire fuse that die
I cannot do that Lord Kenichiro your victory that day means nothing
he will risk his life to take me home is this the final boss I don't think so
is my shinobi and he's also here that's what I would say he did the thing he did the land
and he did the look-up too come for you this will only take a moment now watch as I die 30 to 50
times your highness I hope you have about an hour and 45 minutes this is how long it's gonna take
slash that looks like a thrust don't let him break you that's just let me get that poison come on
wow oh that's also a thrust he's got a lot of moves he's got them to have back it up
come on my cool shit doesn't work on you I got out of that one pretty uh unscathed
whoa that's a grab that would that look like a slash to me looked like he was queuing up for a
big swing fuck I'm gonna save my pellets it's not worth it all right I'm gonna one maybe I should
fuck it let's do it fuck he's a lot more that's not a it is he I don't think he even does a sweep
oh no every time dude get first fucking try let's go let's go
now just cut his pinky toe off and then say he can go it did only take a moment you're right
oh fuck no no I did it uh lightning jump and do lightning here comes the lightning it was just
too easy they're not gonna let me have that are they they're not gonna let me have that are you
I'm still gonna do it let's go holy shit oh my god fuck I have no healing oh man you gotta jump
every time every time you see the lightning you gotta jump damn it oh all my confidence there
goes all my confidence it built up and I just like shit it out all over the ground I don't even
remember where the hell that was it was like an open window right where the fuck was that oh right
there oh it's all right I just gotta be that wasn't that bad for your first try dude all right
I did make it clean that wasn't clean that was very that was very unclean
I'm gonna give this motherfucker a chance let's go got a cornered fuck fucking goddamn vroomer
outside can we god can we arrest this guy already on seriously lock that fucking guy up
can you please pull give that guy like a fifteen hundred dollar speeding ticket
he's fucking obnoxious oh my god I was doing so good too and they know it ain't not over yet
oh like seriously
imagine the type of fucking doofus you have to be like just imagine just just the fucking
like what's wrong with you like what a strange motherfucker you really are every day
no no I've queued it up because I have you guys I can't even explain it damn it
oh easy got it all right three healing potions let's go electricity man bring it on
oh I thought he was doing this
did it not work I think I got it mom mom just wait mom mom I gotta revive mom calm down
I almost lost that
Genichiro battle memory nice nice oh what's this
race car noises that was a cool fight that was really fun but turns the spraying blood of a
victim to smoke activated after a backstab death blow the smoke screen allows for one to retake
the element of surprise damn only be used after performing a backstab death blow they must be
equipped in the equipment menu interesting so all the issues I was having with the the group at
the top of the stairs you were victorious interesting you can just go back into hiding
are you shinobi of the divine yeah there is xp and levels in the game I don't have to do
this again do I do I have to find the third time phase three no this lamp is everything to me
for her sake no I even got the like unlock thing so your final boss you're going to turn into a
demon or something okay he's self uh I have seven points what about my son where's my little like
son um nope this is it right here here we go I wanted to buy this so this makes the heal even
better what is the final move here living force allows him to perform a follow-up attack with
certain tools that imbues the sword with the tools effect huh after using certain prosthetic tools
right trigger is living force the sword is imbued with the tools effect the only one that I have
right now is flame fence I turn to a flame sword okay cool still have two points I don't want to
spend it on anything though uh I'll probably just get this either that or maybe this too
I'm not sure I want to go all the way down this tree that doesn't seem that interesting to me
or no this is cool too no I'm gonna I'm saving it that's the moment you get health back uh I'm
actually gonna pee again so I'm gonna go use the bathroom I'll see you guys in just a minute we'll
keep going see you soon sorry we're back oh I can upgrade twice this is more health and more posture
right very very cool this out of the way sorry all right so rampaging beast and nothing more
max health and posture then I can also do more attack power right yeah from the genichiro
although distant recollection of such a memory provided substance to the wolf
born a peasant genichiro ishino was taken in by the ishina after his mother's death
with his country on the brink of defeat genichiro took to a heretical axe and
mastered the lightning of tamo such heresy may be the key to saving her damn all right awesome
did the skills rested up a little I guess we can talk to the lady seems the next course of
progression here let's see I've managed to fill my mask to give you my thanks who exactly do you
serve ishina I'm a doctor in the service no desire to use the power of the dragon heritage
he tried to help lord kuro escape ashina correct the message I found in the well that was
the hell are you guys also correct you guys there's someone I think you'd like to see
lord kuro is downstairs waiting for you there's another one already was this one here is one
upstairs anyone downstairs all right I guess what can I do for you I have come yes you did well to
come here let us go we must leave ashina wolf my blood blood of the dragon causes men to become
undying one something goes for you yes my lord I wish to save you I'm sure that I would
know already happened thing given another chance however undying begets stagnation the immortal
oath the rejuvenating waters the dragon rot they all corrupt men to the point that they no longer
live as men I wish to sever the chains of stagnation bred by the dragon's heritage
wolf will you help me achieve this aim this sounds like the text to speech voice
I was trying to figure out in my head what that was it is um how are these not the same thing
help kuro obey the iron code help kuro this is telltale level of choice here yeah this is yes
or hell yes I have hell he wants to die but what about my code yes or yes in a bad way
I think I have to obey the code if I was in this position I would say dude you know how many bosses
I've had to fight and kill to protect you to come find you and for me just to kill you you're not
even a boss uh-uh obey the iron code to protect you the divine air that was the duty my father
entrusted to me how many times have you died and come back to life for my sake two three times
you severely underestimate how bad I am at the game how many times have you died two three
uh yeah yeah only only three times yep yep that's me I'm really good
thank you what does he know we are seeking to sever the immortal ties I know a good place to
start where tell me the next place to go the sunken temple book from kuro on the art of
severing ties with the dragon's heritage it looks old the binding is torn and several pages are
missing herein describes the means to perform the rite of immortal severance beyond the fountain
head palace locate the sanctuary and imbibe the tears of the holy dragon of the divine realm
okay it's an ancient record that was kept in I can read I can read
good dragon it is my belief cuts him up puts his hand up close excuse me
the divine that incense burner over there it belonged to a person of interest
take a look now he's trying to slash is it this cactus over here is there something special about
it oh no it's a dimple long ago there was another divine heir living here in ashina castle his name
was lord takeru this incense burner belonged to him where is he now he died a long time ago
apparently wrapped in the aroma of the fountain head I returned to the divine realm those are
supposedly the words he left behind text is sent of the fountain head is the key to reaching the
divine realm that is my belief let us discover the truth together I might have to change the
voice because of that text to speech fucking donation messages all right well cool sounds
good where where do we go where to now as to how I am certain some of lord takeru's books remain
in this castle books that he collected in order to find the divine find the books I will search
for them in addition to finding a way to reach the divine realm might we also look into how we might
sever the immortal ties a fine suggestion talk to ishii if anyone knows the answer it is him
well come with me I want to what's what is the name of that thing I want to clip I want to put
into the text of speech the last two or three sentences and then play it back play the clips
back and just see if it's exact I'm into this right now hold on what is the name of that
justin text to speech is there a is there a website where I can get that or do I have does
it have to be through streamlabs how would you how do you know that let's see this looks like
the right place let's see you know I can get uh I think you can I think you guys might be crashing
this server yeah I can't no no it's like it's here hold on let me I know it's in streamlabs
let me see if I can get it to like test it I'm pretty sure it is in streamlabs right let's see
I'm this is gonna take a minute but it's worth it okay let's go to my dashboard and then let's
go to like maybe I can just test the message okay I wonder just donate to yourself with messages
I don't even have to link maybe I can do it with like bits all right can I okay here we go
I'm not sure I can get this to work I don't think so unfortunately dude how did they change where
all this stuff is in streamlabs where is all my shit the spin wheel wheel spin oh you got it is
that it okay here we go let's see is this it I don't think it worked no it's not good it's not
working can you guys hear that because when I pick uh like for instance I just text it and play it's
not working I'm trying to like all right not working for me let it load it's yeah it's loaded
yeah hit and play let me see let me refresh this page maybe because I have this on hey yeah okay
there it is I think it's because my I had like a thing on Mozilla hey this is what's the what's
the kid's name no it's not working all right stop using the website I think we're overloading the
website with uh with attempts like Justin doesn't work no nobody works hates me hates me hates me
there it is okay all right how loud is this hates me let's get some dialogue here let me make sure
this works blah blah blah blah okay nobody use this website you ready I'm going to try to do
this as best as I can oh fuck hold on I need to turn I need to put this like in a window
I'm going to type everything he says on screen you guys are not going to tell the difference
it's loud enough right test to see if it's loud enough okay let's go Lord Isshin is not within
this castle citadel I'm told he's recuperating in one of these watch towers however the path
to his watch tower is closed his health is a little how do I get in I'm a ninja it's intended
Lord Isshin is not within this castle citadel it's so fast I've heard the nightjar use smoke signals
as landmarks yes so if you follow their smoke signals you should be able to reach Lord Isshin
Lord Isshin is not within this castle citadel however the path his watch tower is closed
I can only do five seconds at a time find him
Finn's at Batfuck
I can't get him to do it come on play stop look stop loading that website
dear Iscariot head towards the citadel and recover all the energy immediately
walk Megaman well okay one more
find Lord Isshin and ask if he knows how we might sever the ties of immortality
all right that's I'm done
Lord Isshin and ask if he knows how we might sever the ties of immortality
come on
recuperating in one of the watch towers reach the roof from that open window then follow the
nightjar smoke signals I entrust this task to you get better at parrying I was watching the last
six times you died try strafing left and shit it's embarrassing go get the q you dumb fuck
okay sure let me put this back in full screen
just the typical donation it's just a donation
typical donation oh that's so funny whoa easy oh we had our fun can you turn on donation
text to speech just for this stream because of that voice I don't even have that room I
don't have a link I don't have that setup I don't have like a PayPal donation link
I don't have like text to speech for bits or anything I don't have it I don't even know how
to set it up that would take me like a while to figure that out all right well that was fun
let's go ahead and keep going wait one last thing I gotta move it does take a bit to set up yeah
if only only with that easy all right here we go back to it no I don't do text to speech
I'm too easily distracted I could never do it and plus I feel like something I feel like
when you have text to speech sometimes if I'm let's say I was talking right now and somebody
did the get the key you dumb fuck it would be talking over me and I would have I'd be fighting
with that voice okay so I was supposed to follow him and then go let me just listen to this for
real and actually comprehend it because I was find Lord Isshin he's in one of the watch towers
outside this castle
all right follow the smoke signals go out the roof did I already find that guy
I'm ready smoke signals there they are Jeremy if you die can I have your channel
no it's going right to burger boy and he'll just get like TOS banned in like three days it
won't even like matter right so going this way just want to make sure I'll walk around
they usually hide items back here in these random places okay stealth kill now now
every time I never mind somebody else is throwing shit at me I gotta move
these people are making noises that I make follow the rooftops to find Isshin hey streamer you think
that was actually a little kid that did those voices that recorded every one of those lines
okay great fun funny yeah really funny like 50 out of 50 humor there come on man okay if you
don't have to fight then just don't forehead and just just don't fight for it oh okay yeah let's
don't do it see you later didn't get money though unfortunately hey it's me Mr Satan yep that's me
Goku what are you doing down here all right okay I'm gonna fall off the
fucking building if I keep doing this so might as well just keep it going you don't see
it's the only way I can get strength how do I get up there I've already I even told myself to
stop doing it and now I have to bone out of here wait do I oh what a dumb asshole I really am
now we got copypasta coming in taking over my channel look at me god I wish like when I said
don't do copypasta people just listen to me when people come in here and they spam copypasta it
ruins my experience as a streamer because when I look over and I see spam it distracts me
and I need total chat concentration don't copy and paste this come on I didn't get the indicator
yeah like you know hanging out in jurama stream you know like sometimes he just does like Mr Satan
and stuff it's like so fun and funny he's like just so lighthearted about everything
last night he did Mr Satan and he fell off the roof and oh boy the popcorn dropped out of the
lap on that one can you do Vegeta no nobody can do nobody can nobody nobody nobody nobody can do
nobody can do Vegeta not even me Mr Satan can't even do it and I'll try I'll try a lot forgot
that we got raided by Dan sometimes I forget that there's like people here sorry they all left no
they didn't they're all still here look but seriously though like seriously that thing thanks
for sticking around if you have I think I have to go that way I gotta follow the smoke signals
there they are and then why does this have two you botched that blueprint did you just buy an
extra one accidentally and you were like ah whatever well I think I made it did I make
it go I don't I what is it he's in one of these towers
whoops I tripped he's inside of one is it the one with two is that him I think I found him
he said follow the towers follow the the smoke signals and he's in one of these do I just have
to check the buildings I think I might just have to check them this one there's another one here
follow the smoke signals till you find him he's inside of one of the buildings
make sure that you don't fall off cliff not even close really except oh no Gonto
where is this guy hiding he said he was dying inside of a building somewhere
smoke signals dying in a building upstairs was it the guy wasn't there somebody I swear there was
somebody oh my god okay where where are you that's where the last one is in this one all
right can I get inside of this tower this looks pretty big my tongue is out right now it's just
sticking out there's almost three smoke signals noise joke that's my favorite comment am I going
crazy or what am I doing here go back to the kid dudes I'm trying dude I don't know where to go
and he said follow the smoke signals and he's been in a tower and I'm just trying I don't know
I don't have a Wikipedia page open to tell me say it again kid find him okay he's in one of
the watchtowers outside this castle reach the roof from that open window then follow the smoke
signals that's what I did kid look right there there's a smoke signal there's a smoke signal
here we go you gotta be kidding me really what how did I fuck that up where was the
I that wasn't there before how did I screw this up because there were other smoke signals all
over the place no god damn it I'm sure who cares what who cares how I got here like who gives a
shit I got there I don't know how I got how would you put a smoke signal outside the front of your
house I can't and by the way that's not even on the roof that smoke signal is clearly on his balcony
this guy's a grade a dickhead tell him it's on the roof get to the roof
oh if I could slash in my wood about the divine air's life yes there is something I wish to ask
before that sake what you earned thank you are we gonna go back and give this to the guy
bewitched by the rejuvenating mortars you did well to put a stop to that for me you have my
thanks I merely followed the code my father taught me the iron code of the shinobi I see
so you're the son of all that boy he found during the rebellion talk is pretty good
don't you think
wait it's the guy's mask the divine air's desire is to sever the ties of immortality
is the guy that had to kill the rats can be done the mortal blade if you had such a weapon
may be the key to what you're after blade with it you could kill one who cannot die through normal
means if I gave that back to him that'd be really disrespectful the infested I believe I've not
seen one before but it said you could stab them through the heart or remove their head
and they wouldn't die if the stories are true they'd surely be quite fearsome
to kill a monster such as that you'd need the mortal blade where can I get that
where is this mortal blade right here it's held in simple temple however they say the mortal
blade right behind me take it I am not certain of the meaning it's just here sir
hmm the gates to that temple are closed now though who knows what those degenerates are
doing shut away up there in the mountains there aren't any sunk in the temple how do I get there
the abandoned dungeon just outside of Ashina castle if you can pass through its waterways
you should find your way all right you're leaving Sekiro severing immortality Sekiro
or Sekiro it's Sekiro the plans and desires of those involved churn endlessly
if you hesitate you'll be swept away and lose the battle that's right best you keep it in Sekiro
Sekiro Sekiro hesitate and you lose Sekiro what hello what's going on
okay uh are they supposed to be in here uh maybe I don't think I want to fight them up with grandpa
just three of them in here something's not right here damn it Sekiro hesitate for a second and
you'll die I have a training mission for you downstairs go fight fucking snap crackle pop
prove to me that you can take my Buddha idol thing on the ground over here this is
it's not supposed to be in here mine excellent excellent it truly is the worst cereal isn't it
Sekiro yeah it is absolutely no redeeming qualities at all gets soggy in 10 seconds Sekiro
tastes like cardboard pieces that went through a wood chipper yeah so I'm just going here
haha all right running out of energy dude dude just will you cease a nice hat uh a note here
I wonder what it's like I don't even have the website anymore I don't it's not even a hat
this shit okay so this is if twitch chat uh gave this uh message let's see what it says
wolf found something I've opened a library meet me there clear out
couldn't be
thanks thanks uh appreciate it thanks to the uh thanks to the five dollars all right let's uh
where are you are you here yes for defeating Kenichiro there's a lady oh to think that Lord
Kenichiro would go as far as to drink the rejuvenating rejuvenating sediment that's
what we call a particularly concentrated part of the rejuvenating waters I'm sure you saw it
for yourself the rejuvenating sediment grants great resilience in one's flesh one becomes able
to withstand blows that would be fatal to anyone else nice my mentor Dogen devoted much research
to its uses but all of his work documents medicines everything were burned and destroyed
I'm not sure who but I heard one of the senior apprentices was able to salvage some of it
probably dojun did you ask lord crowe's thoughts on the matter I did and we've decided to sever the
ties of immortality I see I thank you for all of the help you've given me almost sounds like
you're bidding me farewell I've carried out my lord's orders so I will stay here in the castle
come and speak to me whenever you please I will provide my assistance to you as a doctor
oh okay it's said to be a power those who have been given the power of resurrection
so we have a new fire keeper is what I would classify it but
goodbye gun for shrine key the gate behind the shrine's idol is made to be
opened the sunken valley clan will shoot any stranger who approaches and the snake eyes guns
are particularly feared this elite group of women are descendants of the ancient okami clan
their especially sharp eyes allow them to snipe victims a great range got the key
you're back did you meet with lord ishin I did he said the mortal blade it could be the key to
severing immortality the keys of it it's a sword why smart clicks on it shouldn't be
it can be found at senpo temple I see yes that seems promising as you say for my part I hunted
for any books that may contain clues about the aroma of the fountainhead it seems lord takeru
indeed sought a way to reach the divine realm so far I found one piece of relevant information
what is it a flower show the droplet my lord could this be it's a sakura droplet
that's when the undying pledge of the dragon's heritage is broken it said that this remains in
place of the oath do you think this one was left behind by lord takeru that seems likely why are
you streaming if you so desire I don't use this that's kind of a loaded question it's got a lot
of answers to it give the droplet or keep the droplet what are you gonna do with it
I only have one more I only have one of these I already used one I wonder what this does if
you give it to him if you should be so kind of course close your eyes my lord what lord takeru's
dragon blood lives on with you wait he's wait I humbly accept yes what you may open your eyes
now my lord was a boon granted by lord takeru you can turn your monitor back on yes better
resurrected power the flower first it is said that relatives of tomo once gathered the fountainhead
fragrance and arrived at the palace you may find a key where the waters of rejuvenation
converge in a deep pool and why do you deeply fragrant flower lord takeru left it behind
I was looking for information on the fountainhead aroma and how it relates to the divine realm
there is water that flows from the fountainhead through ashina and the book speaks of a white
lotus flower that grows where the water pools deeply it appears that's the most expensive
magic card it's worth like seventy five thousand dollars
fountainhead waters pooled deeply white lotus cards in a deep valley yes indeed the sunken valley
may be the place the fountainhead water should flow into there where is this sunken valley it's
beyond the woods to the rear of the castle there's a shrine dedicated to the white serpent deep in
the woods as the name implies the sunken valley is just below that place there's no proper path
down there but a man of your talent do you prefer water with or without pulp
I really hate to tell you this but if you're drinking water with pulp that's like lead you're
drinking fucking all kinds of messed up like copper and minerals and shit I don't know if
you should drink like metal I'm gonna say without they did the smell was reminiscent of sawdust
but also it smelled faintly of sakura flowers oh so you smelled it too I felt the scent was much
crunchy water but slightly different what is it wolf that scent it reminds me of something you
smelled it before are you gonna turn on the japanese voices are you gonna make us suffer
this shit it's fine what's wrong with it it's just like it's voice acting what's wrong with it
my goodness so little do you know kid and everybody that I've talked to in the game
over the last 15 to 20 minutes I I have another rez really holy shit okay that's pretty cool
shadows die three times now uh what was I saying right um I already have the sunken temple ready
to go it's like I'm ready to do it right now I don't have to traverse anything I've already
explored down there already take a look at that oh what's that made it how did he get down
here so quickly all right now pop there was I went this which was the right way this way takes me to
no that's not the right way it said something about snipers so I have good thing I have that
hat to protect from snipers hey can I just keep this on forever hmm very interesting stuff
I could keep going or I could go this way looks like certain death is it though yeah what's this
here for no wait can I make that jump there's a guy down here they're the most elite snipers
in in the entire world oh a sniper looks like a can of tuna on top of a broomstick I think I'm
gonna be fine I always get the hardest items to get in this game that are in the weirdest place
are always the vases they're just the ceramic shards anymore I think I have to get down eventually
I'm going this way this is where I was I was spoke okay hey I mean I could probably use a
like a slice of pizza right now all right somebody name food name like a food and I'll eat it tonight
not on stream but you know a little bit when I go eat burger sushi a burrito uh ass cool
I'm talking about something I can consume for sustenance a panini that's actually sounds pretty
good it's a good call uh a gyro I love gyros gyro gyro gyro however you pronounce it I think it's
gyro right I've heard people say gyro it's it's sekiro it's sakiro sakairo sakiro
I just saw somebody walk over here just keep going I think I can get a kill here
if I didn't teleport inside nice fucking slide that dude's playing apex
oh my eyes are watering that was the that was really that's the worst one all night
I'm so glad nobody heard that that was purely just disgusting it was absolutely fucking
oh what up nice reload going when he's reloading Dr. Oakley's pizza I had one of those on stream
it's the only time I've really ever eaten on stream was for that all right let's take a look
looking for stuff materials or trinkets oh it's that guy would you have a cook on stream
no no not really probably not maybe as a joke or something
was even more formidable than we'd heard
they cook meth on the screen last set I need the gold um no I don't why would I do that
uh-huh well there's here here's this it's gonna do a dive that's what I brought this for
nice shot so you probably save at least three or four streamers play this part
and they would probably get just what happened there I don't why I didn't why couldn't I jump to
that for real you guys I mean it's not like I didn't try oh no and they're shooting sniper
rifles at me a gun what god damn it give me a second fuck I don't touch I gotta deflect there
well okay where's my gun oh you're alive this guy gonna die every time isn't it all right no
at least it's right here oh my fucking god why Jeremy just do it the right way first
I'm gonna get shot right now I can just block it
fucking hell boy what is that classified as a grab the guy's a grab and uh this is just a wacky
move set that's not what I wanted to do don't fucking bombs back it up back it up oh god damn
oh that posture damage is bad I almost have one down parrying it's just everybody it's so hard
because everybody is so different everybody's move sets are so completely different than you
guys learn it's really learning the whole video it's like really what is that like spin 360 degrees
around in a goddamn circle really I'm going for it fuck it fuck
I'm out of posture out of posture that oh fuck I can't oh my goodness that's not good
no I wasted one of my resurrects too all right come on now let's just
do it like the trolley all right come on back up like that I'm just gonna go for it
hey getting the distance on this person is difficult oh my god again come on oh I'm so
actually fun that's that's come on dodging and it just still stays there and just
magnetizes to your head and now I lost all like the fucking frog that didn't happen that time
I'm gonna wait till the last second dodge through you gotta fucking get away from me you push me
off this cliff I swear to god guys where am I jumping to come on fuck that grab
fuck that like dark souls to magnetize to somebody I nobody likes that nobody wanted that
nobody wants that no that wasn't even supposed to happen wrong button shoot what oh I didn't
look through what the fuck's happening right now um what it's lost control there for a second
nobody wants that somebody likes that one beat oh put the hat back on one down only
300 more to go nobody wants that nobody likes that nobody wants that but I want that
that's fine I can make it fuck you snipers wait I get this happen on forever let me like this let
me see it's over nothing just checking this rain is bad magic if that is a piece of glass if that's
a glass vase I'm going to throw my controller into the sixth dimension okay it's not how do I
get the fuck out of here though how do I get out of this uh can I jump back up I can hurry hurry
hurry hurry okay we're good scrap good don't just rush it's like dog shit it's bullshit grabs
fucking dumb dumb my fingers slipped off yeah is that what happened uh which one of those
which one of the planks does that did I okay now that I've seen it it's not gonna happen again I
gotta wait ready click click ready one two three jump what are you thinking one up top
huh whoa that just scared the fucking shit out of me oh my whole body is in pain oh my god hold on
oh god and the people love this shit listen to this shit that's fucking beetle juice
uh new voice unlocked uh that's like four voices happening at the same time run that back listen
to that that's like five voices happening at the same time wait I think wait wait just don't move
I think I can do the voice now I think I can do it now hey hey hey I think I have an opportunity
here let me see who has a voice like this somebody of a celebrity somebody come on I need to think
of somebody quick um I don't know I can't think of anybody Mark Simpson home homer no that's gonna
fix it homer it's it's Joan Rivers oh Joan absolutely it's unbelievable oh darling you look
so beautiful right now on the runway let me tell you something about just how I forgot about the
fuck I forgot fuck let's go I can't fix it I think I have this voice forever I have this voice
forever it's it I fucked it up I coughed too much and now it's over I actually have this voice
forever this is it my career is over oh my god my career is over I have to turn it to Larry the
cable guy oh no hold on I'll be back I'll be back um I think I'm forever changed forever I coughed
too loud and I actually like exploded a vocal cord I think it's gone it's not happening what
can I do now no I'm good I'm good I'm good okay I think I'm fine watch it watch it watch it are
we good yeah maybe not I'm also fucked up no it's back but not really though it's still a little
different oh my god you know I actually it uh go for seven and a half hours one more go what happened
to old germa that's who that's who's here is the old one the old person oh my god I'm losing it
I jumped oh boy okay I gotta I have to think about how I'm gonna approach this I think I
might just say who cares and just run up you know what I mean just climb up it just gets to talk
forget it it's gonna be too hard to kill everybody and deflect everything there's a way to jump up
here can I reach it from this place though I don't think I can just with a shot I'm just
going for it oh boy no no I did it I think I'm up here am I yep okay I'm here gunpowder oh shit
who cares get in here who the hell are you that just kills like an old prospector
that's not good this one's free shit over here
I'm quick all right I did it yes yes I finally made it all right yeah and speaking of making it
I think I'm gonna have to call it here I gotta rest the voice now because uh by the way I love
what you've done with your necklace it looks beautiful here and who is that who are you
wearing right now who is that no wow back to you in the e-hollywood studio gucci I love gucci
oh my god and I'm gonna tell you something what we're gonna do we're simply just gonna break up
the banks you know what I mean it's gonna be real easy taxes we're gonna we're gonna have more taxes
and we're gonna have the other banks broken up power back to the people if you don't say
oh who else we got who else somebody else quick fire about five quick while we have it here this
is why we got it somebody else anybody doesn't matter who it is donald trump uh oh well oh my
goodness I'll tell you every time I'm able to say it let me take no collusion absolutely not no
collusion there never was collusion it was just which hunt that's what it was who wants somebody
else quick joe pesci joe pesci yeah I mean it's funny like how funny like uh funny like a clown
like I'm a clown to you that what you think I am a clown yeah you're fucking idiot clown
who has someone one more one more somebody richard nixon I will tell you I I'm a crook
no that's gonna make it better um marlon brando good one let me tell you something real important
if you ever come over to my house again and you disrespect me I'm gonna fucking slap you upside
ahead one more and I'm out larry david I can't I can't believe it no I got foisted
got somebody else quick come on Seth rogan well I mean uh
uh
somebody else quick one more george god hey jerry I can't believe it how am I supposed to do with
this every day somebody else quick I'm going I'm fucking hot right now steve-o steve-o from
jackass man haha man I just ate elephant shit or something I fell into it quick one heck hill
oh puppy let me tell you this is this is larry king and I'm still here okay
I'm gonna call it here now the plan the plan was to go tomorrow too um I may have to take a day
because uh if this is gonna be a problem I I'm gonna get like laryngitis so we're gonna pick
up exactly where we left off here hold on let me try to like caught no that's probably gonna
make it worse um right where we left off here is where we're gonna start not tomorrow I'm gonna
take tomorrow because it really is probably the better idea this is a lot of fun thanks for
joining uh we got a huge raid today happy to have you why is larry david here quick let me rifle
through like the only impressions I can do I have the the outro on here who uh dan's gaming came
in with a raid really really cool really cool of you thank you uh so I am going to just take
this out we had a bunch of bits but I'm not sure I can read them all no yeah I can yeah I can
there's not very many your boston accent is stronger hey look guys up here read them in the
voice this is gonna end up just getting better randomly and like I'll be fine but I feel like
I'm using uh use the justin tts no no no no we'll go through uh I'm unfortunately I can't read
every single paragraph and message right now but well then I have to like okay here we go
that's actually a really good idea here we go I'm gonna mute this I'm gonna come out of here
let's do let's have justin read these bits turn it up a little and move this
um turn sekiro down all right so I'm just gonna copy and paste here this is from
this is from some guy let's see what it is thank you some guy appreciate it this next one is from
freudian weapon thank you freudian for the 10 bucks freudian oh hope you and chad have a good
night sorry about that sorry sorry sorry cheer 1000 hey yerma can stick around for tonight's
stream but wanted to drop and then show some support anyhow hope you and chad have a good
night yerma heart thank you you as well freudian really appreciate it this next one's from sad
vega for 250 frank or 250 this game is great I have a cough IRL and I blamed you for my dragon
rot fix it already you jerk seriously though my only complaint is AI and this game resets way too
easy from watching you kill his friends to being perfectly fine
really the only gripes that I have about sekiro are the the fact that it's a stealth game but
then it's also like a dark souls game too and it can be confusing sometimes because there's certain
sections of the game that are stealth only that essentially that you can hide in bushes and stuff
but thank you for the 250 just take some getting used to that's all this next one is 15 dollars
from you thank you cheer 1500 chat has been painful these past two days thanks for always
being a positive energy you always brighten my day hope you feel better less than three thank you
appreciate it thanks for the 15 dollars this feels really weird i'm fucking alive this is
fucking freaking me out it's i'm talking to somebody but i'm not talking to them
uh thank you something i wrote up for the 250 cheer 250 hey germs fell asleep yesterday but
wanted to give a shout out to the mods and all the work they do the work they do can be really
tough sometimes and wanted to let them know they're appreciated hope you've been having
fun with the game cheers yeah moderating the channel is hard it's they do their best they're
trying uh but sometimes there are a lot of people here and it's hard it's hard to manage that many
people it just is but they do try they are trying thank you something order for the 250 appreciate
next we have internet Jorge for 25 dollars thank you internet Jorge 25 bucks thank you streamer
blames boomer coffin cold cheer 1000 cheer 1000 cheer 100 cheer 100 cheer 100 cheer 100
cheer 100 probably shouldn't copy and paste those parts but thank you for the 25 bucks it's a lot
of money rad bruise thanks for the 250 cheer 250 doing straight shots of lemon juice is actually
way better than cough syrup i don't know if i could do that unfortunately because i have um
i have digestive problems and i think doing straight lemon juice would probably be a really
bad thing for me to do but vitamin c that's what you're looking for right okay sorry this next one
is for soul harry thanks for the three wow thanks for the three dollars soul harry i'm getting even
it's getting it's getting even worse it's turning into who is this i don't know what this is a
different voice now wow i'm turning into old morty old morty um we're gonna have to dial back
oh it's four people talking undo this and find the four people talking larry larry you came over my
house and my wife is here and you're gonna talk about the swan i don't want to talk about the
swan larry i just don't want to hear it anymore we're trying to have a nice meal here with our
families and you keep bringing it up like an asshole that's super day got it uh anyways thank
you uh soul harry for the three bucks soul of 100 soul of 100 soul of 100 here question i appreciate
you wanting to upload highlights to second year me rather than your main channel but is there some
reason that you feel you can upload videos like meet the albert since two year main they are
basically the bigger projects you talk oh okay cut ran out of words
all right but basically let me uh i'll just finish the rest of this uh it's basically the
bigger projects i talked about just seems like over half a million subs are going to waste so
i have this question you're tired of answering whatever you do you'd be the giant rat always
the thing about the youtube channel right is it's almost like it's on ice and it's a great
archive of the shit that i used to do and i've sort of transitioned and adapted over to twitch
and over to live content but remember i i did the youtube thing for five six years it was a long
time and i made a lot of videos and the reason why something like the you know meet the albertsons
is not on the main channel is because in my mind the original thought was i will put video gaming
and stream highlight stuff on the second channel and then spend a bunch of time on videos that i
spend like two weeks on for a week on or whatever three weeks on for the main channel and what
happened was i'm just one person and i ran out of i couldn't do it all it was impossible to stream
three or four days a week and make a video that's been two or three weeks on i wouldn't
streaming wouldn't happen i would have to take way more days off i'd only be able to stream like
once or twice a week and i wanted to really give twitch a real shot so and that also was in the
same realm of in the same time frame of youtube really kind of shitting the bed for everybody
ad revenue was down content id was out of control and i just figured you know what fuck it it's i'm
gonna move on and the second channel really exists to have a place for people that don't want to or
can't watch entire streams they're still able to stick around and and watch videos and of the
the jokes and the streams that happen still you know that's the that's kind of the point of that
second channel is to have a means for other people that can maybe not i mean this stream has been
going on for almost eight hours and a video that's 10 to 20 minutes is much easier for a lot of people
to consume and still get the gist of kind of a lot of things that may have happened right but i never
wanted to abandon the youtube channel there was never the point it was always just and i mean you
saw starve tweeted about this a week ago or so it's for the type of content that i want to make on
youtube it's not it's just not viable to do anymore the the amount of time it takes versus
what you get out of it is it's just hard to do now and hold on and unfortunately unless you have
like a big sponsorship or you have like a patreon which is another thing that floated but then i
thought about it again it's like there are thousands of subs on this channel and like
there's already a patreon it already kind of exists and it's people paying a month on here
you know it's hey i'm gonna pay you a patreon once a month and oh by the way i'm also gonna
be subscribed on twitch too it feels like double dipping people and you know i don't wanna i don't
want to have like three different income revenues to try and bleed everybody dry because i want to
make a youtube video tomorrow you know this people are you guys already pay me to make content which
is the streams right and i guess it is possible to do another patreon but i feel like you guys
already pay you guys already pay the fee in quotes why would i want to make you guys like
pay again oh yeah people pay five dollars a month give me five dollars a month too and i don't even
want to look at it like a fee to you know watch the content i want the content to always be free
always accessible always people that you don't have to pay them any money to hang out here and
watch right and that's i never want that but streams started to take that the time that i was
going to put into stuff on youtube turned into stuff that i put a bunch of time on and twitch
and i've done it a few times already this year and even last year and once the summertime rolls
around you're gonna see a lot more of that oh in studio we're gonna be in the studio this week and
we're doing something interesting you know the weather's starting to get nicer there's more
opportunities to do stuff and you'll be seeing a lot of that in the summer so the time and energy
and resources and money that was going to go into the main youtube channel is just here now hopefully
that makes sense but really appreciate it thank you and the main channel at this point i'm only
rather even probably call it like the the archive channel because it would have to take some there
would have to be some reason why i would go back and make another video that i spend like a two like
a week or two on voices sounding a little better now yeah it's starting to even out but it still
still sounds like shit and it's like barely at that point where it's it might fall back into
joan rivers but we're good uh all right fuck this text of speech i'm fine thank you sly 161 for the
250 hey germ i'm not sure if this is asked already but do you know if we're gonna get a three year
subscriber badge i just hit three years this month keep up the great streams that's insane
yeah i just i gotta get in touch with lordel i gotta talk to him i gotta like send the message
i just haven't been around but yes there's gonna be three or four years there's gonna be cheer
emotes there's gonna be new emotes there's gonna be new channel artwork channel animations and
the whole thing is gonna get done i just have to and probably do that i'll probably reach out to
him tomorrow but yeah that's there you go that's what we're doing hey cad b tv thanks to the 250
the hardest thing to do in life is fart without shit in your pants uh i don't think that's that's
really not that hard that's not that hard thank you door cube for the 250 i know this game has
made you mad but holy hell some of these noises you made while fighting the long swordsman made
me bust a gut so bad that's just the nature of the game though i love this game don't take my
frustration and anger and shit talking as i don't like what i'm doing i love this game it's great
it's fantastic it's so fucking hard it's so different so yeah it's refreshing to lose over
and over again and not be able to fall back on the shit that used to do in their other games
because i would just dodge dodge dodge dodge dodge i frame i frame i frame i frame here comes he's
gonna swing seven times in a row i frame i frame i frame i frame i frame i frame i frame swing swing
swing but i will keep my final assessment of the game until i get further or i beat it right that's
how everybody played yeah now you can't do that anymore you have to block you have to parry you
have to dodge certain attacks and it changes everything it throws your brain into it snowballs
it down until the snowball is huge and then you die three times music commuted oh shit right
thanks for that uh callee brady thanks for the 25 dollars callee brady 25 bucks hey germa glad to
see you enjoying sekiro sekiro uh i've never had the patience for soulsborne games so i have to
enjoy you through it keep the fun coming for sure i'm going to try my hardest to complete the game
on stream that's exactly what we're going to be doing when i come back the day after tomorrow
thank you smelly boy thanks for the 250 it's probably hard for you to register when you're
focused on playing it but the combat in this game is genuinely entertaining to watch a lot of dark
souls combat is pretty basic with the repetitive dodge roll and attack literally what we were just
talking about but watching you play this genuinely is genuinely beautiful at times yeah i'm trying to
because for me i'm just trying to time parries and not get hit by moves and dodge but i imagine
from a viewer's standpoint it actually looks pretty cool when you land two or three good
parries and a dodge and then a reversal probably looks cool it feels really good to play too it's
not sloppy the camera is really but that's a complaint for every from software game but a
game that's this fast and is visceral that's i remember i told you about like my two gripes
with the game and one is the camera because sometimes it really is just spins in circles
and gets locked somewhere but that's pretty much it it's a pretty minor complaint like i was telling
you i think it's great you the thing is you can get over that really quickly it's not something
that's a game breaker but thank you smelly boy uh thank you mango's evo wins for the ten dollars
thank you mango they say long time fans since 2010 have seen most of your youtube videos on
your main and second channel just thought i'd hop over to twitch and give you some cash well thank
you thank you thank you thank you 2010 what am i gonna do for my 10 year anniversary for being
online what am i gonna do i have to do something for 10 years of youtube and twitch that's a big
deal for me that's a big deal for me being able to stick to something like that for this long
i i can't i can't believe and can't imagine that i would be doing the same thing doing this still
for 10 years i could barely do anything for six months straight let alone 10 fucking years
rent a pony but thank you mango for the 10 dollars really appreciate it sad vega thanks
to the 250 heads up there are secret rooms and walls in the game you access them by pressing up
against a wall and it spins you around like scooby-doo well i've been trying to swing at
them randomly sorry that was a big one that was a big one but yeah i'll check uh more often it seems
like some of them could i could have seen maybe a few of them scooby-doo walls but thank you for the
tip and thanks for the 250 ben elinor thanks for the 25 dollars ben 25 bucks they say you zap please
i kind of did i threw the zap right back in his face but thank you so much ben for the 25 dollars
good old zap hugs not drugs thanks for the five dollars close my man close i think that was the
the gen the gen each your real fight right that did come kind of close i kind of did
uh hey kamira thanks for the 250 lord ishin is not within this castle you could say that i don't
know where the hell i was going i was so lost hey snoozing copter thanks for the 250 every time you
play one of the new from software games i actually play ahead so i can watch the stream you take the
route i didn't take same in dark souls 3 so now i gotta watch the vod i love all your dark souls
and demon soul streams by the way they always have a certain charm to it looking forward to
watching the rest of the stream once i progress far enough sekiro is a blast enjoy yourself i'll see
you when you reached the temple the monk temple i've been forward to it i'm looking forward to
fucking scraping that off the bottom of my shoe after i stomp it i'm gonna destroy that place
hey thank you compact viewer for the 25 dollars a lot of 25 25 25 you guys give me a lot of
fucking money hey germ i have two extra tickets to star wars celebration because my only two
friends bailed on me serious offer no joke also great stream as usual star wars celebration
what is star wars celebration like star war like a movie or oh wait there's like the wait the star
war is in the opening of the star wars park the opening i'm sorry i didn't eat that i didn't come
back uh sorry about that star wars park in disney well just tell them to go what why would they not
go to that but thank you for the 25 i hope you have fun seems cool because star wars sucks come
on get that out of here i don't want to see that hey tingy thanks for the 250 you might actually
have to do one or fives five dollars per death for scratch tickets i went back through yesterday's
stream and counted the deaths it was 34 jess you got it and i kept count today it was 44
if a mod is around and wants to make a death counter you're at 78 deaths total so one doll
scratch tickets let's go why not it's gonna take so long to scratch no it has to be it's gotta i
don't even know what to do about that am i gonna scratch like 150 scratch tickets on stream
i don't think that's gonna that'll take like four hours we're gonna have to we're gonna have to
condense these a little i'm still gonna do it but instead of one dollar per death it's gonna be
you know a five dollar ticket so i don't have to sit there for like six hours scratching one dollar
tickets but thank you thank you flying sombrero for the 250 the first video in years and the last
video to your main channel should be one last autos big adventure that's only 20 to 30 seconds
long one final send off from auto final auto send off i don't know about that here comes the
credits these are tonight subs and resubs thanks a lot everybody thank you for your continued
support of the channel you guys are fucking amazing thank you cad btv thanks for the 250
bullshit name one thing harder than farting without shitting your pants what didn't somebody say this
like an hour two hours ago uh but thank you hey uh clueless sniper thanks for the 250 at the end
here hi jerma what's your favorite boss so far uh genichiro that one felt that one felt the most
involved i felt like i was actually winning and beating that boss the ball was cool but a little
all over the place the butterfly lady was cool was interesting too that's me that'd be hard to
think about what the horseman was really cool they were all just generally interesting fights
with a something different going on but the genichiro fight i just felt i felt like the more
like i was having a real sword fight with somebody with the genichiro fight but that's going to wrap
it up uh special thanks to dan's gaming for the raid thank you good luck to you if you're playing
uh sekiro you come across this wish you the best of luck and that's my time i'll see you guys yeah
i'm gonna take tomorrow just because i i feel like if i stream tomorrow and do some more screaming
that i might have to go on a commission for like four or five days or something i would
fuck up my voice so i see you guys on on monday i'll update the sus and everything so
we'll go from there you're allowed to take tomorrow off only if you talk to blow it out
get well thank you oh i'm gonna take you know i was supposed to take a bath last night i'm gonna
take a bath tonight tonight's the bath night good stream no i had a blast it was great i loved it
oh you mean stream the bathtub stream myself in the bathtub i don't think i'm not gonna do that i'm
not gonna break the uh terms of service have a wonderful rest of your weekend everybody see you
real soon take care ta ta farewell for now oh and by the way i didn't even mention go follow dan's
gaming he's one of the fucking grandfathers of all live streaming if you aren't already take care