I made it. Hey, I made it. Okay, 530 pacific. It's we're here. I made it. Okay
We're waiting for the presentation to start. Oh my god. I can't hear it. Am I gonna be able to hear this? Yeah, right?
What if I just can't hear it? Let's hope so. I'm gonna make a tweet
Uh, I could I could put this on I guess you guys know what's coming up. Why is that?
Let's talk about this real quick. Let me go this
All right, i'll be right back
Okay
So let's take this time. I know why there's no intro necessary. This is gonna start here in like two minutes
No, I have to kill the bro. I gotta kill the notifications too. All right, let's do that
Uh, no notifications tonight. They are going off
For the game awards 2018. I'm gonna wait for people to get here because there's another thing there's something else we're doing
Something else we're doing
Facecam. Oh wait, are you telling me you didn't think there was gonna be a facecam? You didn't think that?
Hold on. I gotta fix it. It's in the wrong spot
Hey
How are you?
This is the game awards. We're waiting for it to start
And before it does why don't we peruse something else too? I mean
bang
This is the bingo board
Ladies and gentlemen, we're playing bingo. Take your seats. Everybody is about to begin
This is the this hey, this is the bingo board. We're gonna be using everybody. Take your seats
Is we're playing super bingo as you can tell
This can't be on the screen look at how like you can't read any of that
So I need to like have this open. Oh fuck. I need to have this open like over here
But first of all, uh, what's very important is fortnight is the middle spaces because it's gonna be game of the year guaranteed
That's the guaranteed space
And uh, let me move this so we can let hey, here we go. It's starting i'm right on time
Link link the board
I didn't upload it to anything. It's like on my computer
I don't I don't have any access to it. Hold on. Wait, wait, just wait. Wait, wait
There it is. There it is
This is like too much space
It's all right. We got one. We got one
All right. I need to see
Because I have my bingo home. I could eat this back up here. Thank god. They have a weird long intro
Good thing I didn't put this on
There you got it. You got your bingo board ready because here
I'm every time there's something happens. I got an opportunity here. Make sure we let's see here
No one saw this coming that says mispronunciation by the way at the top here
celebrity presenter
Is there anyone about long run time in the beginning?
Loud no, no, no, that's not the loud i'm talking about
I'm talking about unbearable. Like you
I it's not me mispronouncing. It's them mispronouncing. It's all right. We we'll go back to that
Here we go the game awards
oh
Really important by the way, there's a couple of things on there that say wine
I don't have a wine opener. I couldn't fucking open the bottle and I almost broke it
So I bought a bottle of wine specifically for this
And I couldn't do use it
I don't know how to open a bottle of wine without a like a opener. So this is um, this is this is rum
So replace wine with rum, but I ain't drinking I ain't drinking more than five of these tonight
This presentation is like fucking 45 minutes. It'll be fine
All right. So a couple of really important things here
We might as well do it right now. So uh, well while we wait
If you could please get over to your game board and put a order of over fortnight game of the year
Because that's absolutely
uh going to win
covered no
That's the free space guys. You know what I mean? So i already got four spaces
Fortnite isn't even nominated. Oh, that doesn't fucking matter. That's it's the game I
Well, we're gonna get a fortnight dance I could fucking guarantee that
Whatever who gives a shit here it comes
This is it
It's on the way
Fortnight came out last year. Yeah, but fortnight br didn't come out till 2018, right?
Uh, it's 5 34. Let's go buddy
Tooth fortnight came out last year like the actual battle royale boat came out last year. Is that for real?
It doesn't match fucking game of the year. It's guaranteed
Doi, you know doi
What's this?
game announcement
spider-man
Sekiro
We already know these ones. These are these all fortnight
Oh, we gotta I gotta pay attention to these because there's a lot of them. This is super bingo by the way
I think the first thing we're gonna get is car on stage
I really think so. I think this can be a big fucking car everyone the game awards pre-show
I am just the pre-show the main show is on the way at the top of the hour
And I can't wait to share it with you
But right now we're gonna recap some of this year's nominees highlight fortnight on the way
Present some game awards and unveil some of our many never before seen world premier
That wasn't that loud the fifth year of the game awards
I simply can't believe it and each year we tried to build on the moments
What if like none of these fucking things happen clear from the community and actually it's a little
Intimidating because we've got such a great response to make it louder show, you know this year
We're bringing back the game awards orchestra
We're making that bigger and better part of the show if I didn't put the orchestra on here
We're expanding the reach of the show to many more platforms
So you'll be able to watch it around the world in many different languages
Which I think is really important that we can have people around the world kind of share nobody booed
We're allowing people to vote in new ways
You know gamers get to choose the winners alongside our judge board
And this year you can vote on discord server you can vote on twitter facebook
Gamers, he didn't say it though alexa and google assistant
We have I think more new games being announced this year at the show than ever before
I can't wait to get all the multiple game announcements around the world been working in secret to kind of prepare for the game awards
one of the things we found last year that fans really liked were these
Giveaways and special incentives to kind of watch the show and well two bald guys. No
Uh steam we did something called a game giveaway, which was amazing
Exciting because if you're watching the show steam santa would just sort of drop games into your account if you were lucky enough
So we're doing that again and we're expanding that
Um in a lot of really interesting ways free stuff right game awards sale
And this is a chance for gamers around the world to get special offers on nominated games on their favorite gaming system
And this year we're working again with but no no no
Did it happen it didn't happen box with nintendo e-shop with steam
To create special offers on the nominees and every platform will do this differently
There'll be some games that are across all some only on certain ones. It's happening right now. Is it happening right?
All right. Well, there you go. Oh, that's amazing
This just one I want to go. Where is it something for free, but I get a special offer on it tonight
Let me go grab it and free something is free. The most here we go
We have the show or sometimes when these game developers will call me up on the monday after a small indie team
And say, you know what jeff like it was cool
We were in the show, but we actually sold like a lot of games this weekend
That makes all the hard work worthwhile for everyone on the team. This is a confusing bingo board platform
And we can drive an audience to check out a game that they're really gonna love free show
This is 2018 was an incredible year in gaming and we say it every year
But this industry continues to get bigger and better did he say cutting edge using this tagline worlds will change
in our promo campaign
And I think started with some people thinking like this is the you know announcement of this game
but really the tagline to be honest with you what it means five community subs is that a lot of existing games have
This year why dna?
Five community subs in game storytelling the fortnight's done
With the rocket launch and the cube and all these other moments and how other games have evolved, you know
No man's sky. It's like nominated this year and it's like it's a wait
Why is no man's sky nominated for a game updating it?
So the worlds will change really reflects the idea that the games that we initially play evolve over time
Used to be you would know get your cartridge. All right, so that's bullshit
So then fortnight gets to be game of the year then now you keep those games in your systems
And what you're going to see this year at the game awards is a lot of these sort of ongoing games
Are going to evolve at our show too in interesting ways
So that's kind of a tease of that theme fortnight season seven worlds, you know
I should have put that on there you may not know anymore after the game awards
We often get asked how we pick the winners for the game awards the nominees are selected by a jury of
Around the world. There are over 65. That's supposed to be the press. Is that like what they're saying?
Staffs that have yeah, it's a bunch of fat journalists
So we think that's the best way to survey everything out there in a very neutral agnostic way
What was that? Here are the the games that we think are the best of the best
Those lead to the nominees which have been announced
And then the winners are selected by a blended vote between the jury and also the public
That gets to vote and help influence it
Why don't you be 100 fan voting and a lot can be socially engineered and I don't want awards to go to
Games that just happen to you know be able to have more twitter followers or you know
Buy a bunch of ads to somehow convince people to vote for them
So I really think it's important that the right listen to him win
And we have an authentic credible process and that's how we're going to continue with um voting for the game awards
Okay, fortnight is such a competitive category in 2018
Will it be marvel spider-man or red dead redemption this whole thing or will it be fortnight?
Or will it be god of war close your heart to the desperation celeste
Celeste pizza assassins creed odyssey. I love those things we will become their monster hunter world
You're on the a-list right
We're about to find out at the end of the night. Mm-hmm cannot wait to see how this ends
It's gonna be right now. Here's a look at our first world premiere
Okay, here we go
Nintendo what do we get for nintendo video game pop figure pop figure
Oh
It is really fucking loud it is really loud very very loud
It's on the switch. All right, so that that's that's not banjo kazooie. That's uh, that's a loud switch game
What the audience have to say, okay
Look for a guy sleeping. That's really important
Hello keely and come to the microsoft theater for the game awards 2018 everyone ready for a big show
This is so exciting. What's the countdown for ever coming up at the top of the hour?
There is so much news so many surprises the game awards orchestra and we are streaming live around the world
It's your over 45 platforms. I want to say to hide everyone watching in
China and india and all across the world
I know it's late in europe but stick around because we have an amazing show ahead for you
17 minutes it actually starts some new game announcements. I know everyone's anticipating do the frozen throws behind him and a lot of special guests
We're gonna kick off the show tonight or the pre-show before we get to the main show at the top of the hour
With a guy who made some headlines last year. There's a fair as here it comes at the game awards
Here's the fuck the ost forced fuck the oscar's meme early in the night joseph wait for it. Hold on
It's actually nice to be the first guest to be honest with you actually you should have the award
Look what you put together man
Thank you this this guy said it's it's crazy. It's five years imagine in 10 years what you will do
I hope i'm really i'm really proud to be what about jeff can't get the mic back
And i'm really excited to be here again. Well, you're a nominee tonight as well. Congratulations for best game direction for a way out
Okay, i'm expecting to win so hopefully I get up on stage
I was gonna say I can only imagine your speech. Well joseph, uh, we're excited to have you here tonight
Uh, don't get me started jeff the internet wants to hear from you, right?
How do you think we're doing this year compared to that counts?
It just started but I feel like it's becoming bigger and bigger and I i'm telling you in five years
This is going to be the craziest thing ever in the whole world cameras back. Definitely sure
Oh, yeah, the cameras here, but I like to have wrong direction connection with the audience
You know, that's the thing the last year when I was here people thought I was crazy
I mean I am a bit crazy
But it's the audience and like the way they were like sharing around the world. Yeah
Everyone around the world. We all love games. Yeah, but I can't see the people in the world. I love games, of course
Thank you very much. It's great to be here. Great. All right. Well joseph, uh, you are here for
Another purpose right now. What's he here for first award of the evening?
Here's the first award best action game and let's take a look right now at the nominees for best action game
This year as voted on by the jury and fans the action game nominees are all duty. Why is that up there?
dead cells
Why the fuck is color duty up here?
far cry five mega man and mega man 11
Best action game this year. The best action games is dead cells dead cells. Congratulations guys for motion twin
And they got me they can hold it
Nice to meet you guys looking very dapper and this is for you group presentation. It's heavy
Thank you so much. The stage is yours. Don't drop it drop it. Congratulations. How's it feel? Uh,
This is so unexpected that we even prepared a speech for this award actually
Just a special thought for the whole team back in france
Hopefully watching us at 3 a.m. In the morning
I hope you guys are awake because yeah, you just made it. So congratulations. You should be proud of yourself
Incredible game. I know a long time
I don't think so. Yeah, I'm just a special thanks for our incredible community of fans
It may sound a bit cliche, but we couldn't have done it without them. So thank you so much for your support
Yeah, sorry
I like your hat man. It's cool. Oh, thank you
Should have put a guy in a fucking hat amazing
Yeah, really unexpected and we're really proud for our fans and all
Everyone will love the game. The game is incredible. You guys did a great job
Thank you for coming all this way to the game awards. Congratulations on your first of many game awards, we hope
That's awesome guys. All right. Thank you. Congratulations joseph. Thank you as well. Good luck tonight
They didn't thank their mothers maybe with your name on it. Take care. Thank you very much
Uh fill them in guys
We've got some more work to get to you before we get to the main show at the top of the hour
Uh right now we're gonna take a look at the first game from a new studio up in montreal canada
Typhoon it's published by 505 games with support from epic games and makers fund check out the announcement of this title
It's a world premiere
That's a bald guy that's a bald guy does that guy come
No, it doesn't count. That's not a real person. No, no, no
It's got to be a guy presenting on stage the kid's got to be a real person
Not just a bald guy in a video
I can't believe they didn't think they're mom
Provide a future home for humanity forward to a victory
No man's sky, too
journey to the savage planet
I've no idea join the pioneer program savage. I don't know what that is
I don't know what we just watched it was just like space stuff and a guy lying on the ground
That was the announcement of journey of the savage planet
I'm now here with alex hutchinson one of the founders of the new indie
Studios. So first of all alex welcome to the show
Why did you guys start this new studio up on my trail?
I think it's that moment in life, you know, we've been doing this about 15 years for myself making games for other people
So it's incredibly
Amazing to see a game we build on our own from nothing with friends of ours in the business
And to see it on at your show on the big bill it is super fulfilling
So in a weird way, that's the that's the start of the reason why I just screamed that so loud
We love supporting new teams. Tell us a bit about journey the savage planet kind of a teaser trailer
So what kind of game is it?
Yeah, so everyone they watch the teaser and they always say is it a is it a you know a battle royale?
I'm so happy. I'm so happy. No, it is not
Uh, it's an adventure game you get dropped on a strange alien world by a company called kindred aerospace who are very proud
Interstellar space exploration company so they drop you there with absolutely no gear high hopes and no ability
And they hope that you can uh, solve the uh, the mystery of what's on a savage planet
We find out more about this game when we get updates, uh, so we're not gonna show much gameplay until next year
But we're very uh, no gameplay trailer
I didn't put no gameplay trailer. All right, so get ready for 2019 alex
Thank you so much for coming down and showing your game for the first time here at the game awards
We really appreciate it
All right. Uh, now we're gonna move on to present another award now
After the best role playing game and the nominees in this genre the witcher three
The witcher three the witcher three
Monster hunter world. It's gonna be monster hunter world better be nino kuni two
Octopath traveler
And pillars of eternity two
It's got a monster hunter world and this is the word I get to give out
Uh for best role playing game. Let me open this one up
What is this trophy and the winner for best role playing game goes to monster hunter world. Congratulations
I can't scream now like they're all on stage. Hold on a second. What is this?
It's for you guys at least two people accepting an award. How does it feel?
Photo off selfie take a selfie. How's it feel?
Yeah
It's very great that we actually were able to come to come from japan
welcome
That's a good game. It was a good game
Somebody on here is going to fry. I know it this game we were talking with amongst the team members that
It's kind of our goal to actually be able to hear be here and receive the award more than five
So we made the
We made it full circle. That's that means a lot to all of us. Thank you so much
More bald guys
We will have great news for our fans soon at least 10 people accepting the award that's way too
Okay, all right scratch that off your bingo card, all right
Congratulations guys on winning the best rpg. He's watching. He's watching this screen as well
So maybe we'll see you guys again on stage. Thank you very much guys. Congratulations. Awesome
All right, thank you very much
I know there's been a lot of gaming conversation happening on twitter this year
Using the hashtag the game awards and to celebrate twitter decided to create their first twitter gaming award you the fans voted
For the best conversation and the winner out of all the big things that happened this year was spider-man's ps4
photo mode
Here we go to twitter gaming now to see the announcement video of that winner
And of course tweet up a storm all night about the game awards
There's some big news breaking that you definitely will want to be talking about now
We're also back on twitch this year. We've got an interactive extension that lets you predict the winners throughout the show
What what is that post streaming?
But there's also this interactive extension so you can go online to the game awards channel
Pick your winners throughout the night and at the end of the show
We'll share the final leaderboard and see who predicted I didn't have that I didn't do that. Where is that?
All right. Well, we've got some other awards to get to now
It's been an absolutely huge year for esports and coming up at the top of the hour in the main show
The best esports player award will be presented by omen by hp
But right now it's my honor to announce some of the other winners in many of the esports categories that we added this year
To the show. Uh, so for the best esports team here are the nominees
Cloud9 has won this I think the past two or three years
Cloud9 every time fanatic london spitfire and og
And the winner this year again is cloud9
Oh, I can't believe it cloud9 wins again
Now for the best esports game the nominees this year were cs go dota 2
Fortnite everybody's to laugh their ass off if fortnite wins it fortnite's gonna win. It's gonna be fucking hilarious
All right, it's gonna be my favorite
I guess and the game award goes to fortnite overwatch for the best esports game like that one last year as well
All right, next up the best esports event the nominees is a new category this year the e-league major boston
2018 back in january evo 2018 the summer in vegas
the league of legends world championship
The overwatch league grand finals where's rocket league and the international 2018 up in vancouver
And the league of legends world championship los vegas congratulations to lol
All right best esports host those nominees were alex golden boy mendez
Alex machine richardson
anders bloom
I apologize fj shocks depotere. I know she's in las vegas tonight
Was that a mispronunciation all red eye shallender and the game award goes to
shocks congratulations
That's a mispronunciation
Next up the best esports coach. They're just running through these are repert
Paracel
zonik
Dillon falco he corrected it doesn't count. No, that's still a mispronunciation
Now that counts and y nk and the best esports coach as voted by the fans
Reaper congratulations to him put it up get it up there
Now best esports moment
This is the top moment as voted on by the jury and fans first up with c9
Winning triple overtime versus phase that's probably gonna be two beating rng
Kt versus ig base race and og's massive upset of lgd
And sonic fox is this award show 15 minutes side switch against go one in dbc
15 minute award show he's going so fast come back winning triple ot versus c9 of course the c9
All right, well, we've got more esports coming up in the main show
But right now we've got another world premiere
This is a favorite game of mine a couple of years ago
And they reached out to me a couple ways go and say hey
We've got something more we're doing we want to share with you at the game awards
So check that check this out. I think you'll like it
world premiere, all right
Let's see. This is a story of a video game called the stanley parable
You know the stanley parable, of course after all it was the video game sensation of 2013
Don't you remember all those awards we were nominated for and this year's winner for best narrative is
Are they gonna do another game the last of us the last of us papers, please the last of us papers, please the last of us
Yes, it was thrilling to be so unanimously recognized by our peers
Which is why we've locked the game's source code away where it can never be touched by the greedy hand of capitalism
a pristine time capsule of perfect artistic integrity to be preserved for
Wait
What do you mean we never put the game on consoles, of course, we put it on consoles. This is a remake or remaster
We didn't here it is. Excuse me a moment
Remake or remaster stanley parable on a console
Stanley i've had a great idea. I want to add new endings and new content new adventures for you. Won't it be fun?
Oh shush, of course it will
We'll package it up with the original game and we'll put it on consoles and everyone will buy it again because they're suckers
Come this might be a joke daddy needs a third swimming pool
What do you mean the last of us two is also coming out next year
All right, uh, stanley parable back again
Now is my honor to present the award for the best student game judged by an incredible panel including megan ellison
From anapurna tawd howard janova chen and my good friend hideo kojima
The nominees are combat 2018 from norway dash quasar from uc santa cruz jara from japan in spain
Life from icar digital in france and recharge. They are powering through this as fast as possible student gaming
All the students who are here with us in the audience why student game goes to combat 2018
This one of the presentation come on up guys, how are you?
This is yours the first of many game awards. I know
Yeah, absolutely. How does it feel? Congratulations feels amazing to be a knowledge for the student game. Thank you so much for having this award
That's really great. Congratulations to you guys and hopefully your game will come out soon. We'll get to play it
Yeah in august hopefully i don't think we're gonna get the mic thing new name mics for everybody
Okay, new name be sure to check that out. Yes
All right, we'd also like to thank the jury and all the people who voted for us and of course our team
We're at mark in your stage with me and aurora and thomas been back in norway
And of course our school in line norway university of applied sciences and of course, uh our mentor
Special thank to you
And your mother congratulations your mother of your game the student game award winner
We love doing that award
All right
We got another world premiere for you
This is from a small indie team of three guys who have been working on this game for the past five years
It's called among trees and when I saw some footage of this I said we've got to share it with you
So check this out
This trailer uses pre alpha footage and represents a work in progress. It's not real
That no, that's not is an animal that's not a trained animal on stage
Some of these are not gonna fucking happen. But if they do that's pretty
It's pretty cool
Myself, what was it called? What was it fire watch? Yeah fire watch two among trees
I don't okay. All right, whatever
All right, well now it's the top of the hour that means I think it's time for the game awards
Are you guys ready? Well, this is now it starts
You know, this show is all about bringing everyone together to celebrate video games
When I started this show five years ago my dream was the people that were just awarded awards come together to celebrate
You guys just the pre-show shit. This is the real game awards coming up right now
Five years in the making for me. I can't believe it's about to happen
But to kick off the show, I couldn't think of anything better than this. Uh, please join me in welcoming
from nintendo reggie fesimae
From playstation sean laden and from xbox phil spencer
Fill it in
All three types of gaming. I can't wait till they announce tonight at the game awards
We come together as a community to celebrate video games the most compelling and immersive form of entertainment in the world
as an industry
We are most powerful when we come together. He's just gonna rip that fucking blood. So when it's gonna be like g
No confirmed for smash of games
We join with the viewers and gamers around the globe to celebrate creativity
Innovation and the role that video games play in popular culture
together
We will continue to invite new voices
creators and players
into our worlds
Because when everybody plays
We all win cross-platform because when we video games see the strength of a united gaming community, we remember
that we've never
Seen the challenge that you can't defeat
This isn't the only moment like a united superhero in our commitment
To leading and pushing this industry for video game justice games
new experiences
And new ways for everyone to play
Good luck to all the nominees
And congratulations to all the things they're doing the thing with you and enjoy prompter here awards. We just take it away
Thank you so much guys. It's my favorite thing ever. I love it red g sean and phil together on stage
What the show is all about
We have an amazing show ahead
They just put them on stage and read a prompter with an incredible performance by the game awards orchestra
Conducted by our amazing musical director lauren balfe featuring the legendary
Han zimmer and harry gregson williams and they will be joined by a nominee tonight lana rain and sarah shackner
They are premiering our brand new theme for the game awards. I can't believe it. Enjoy the show
but
I was going to do this, too
I was going to put on full orchestra on stage, but instead I put fucking
car
Car on stage. This was going to be full orchestra on stage and I fucked it up
There's not going to be a car on the stage. It's not going to happen
Cover it anyways. No, I can't I can't just cover it because it exists. You understand?
I
It was supposed to be orchestra, okay fill it in let's cheers the creator of the game awards jeff keely
We're sleeping amazing. How about that the game awards orchestra hon zimmer harry gregson williams
Lauren belp with sarah and lana what an amazing start to the show. Welcome to the game awards everybody
Wow, this is so cool
And we are live around the world on over 45 platforms and tonight including german on 85
The world are coming together to do one thing which is celebrate the video games that we love
So thank you all for joining me and thank you. We've got an amazing show for you
We've got a show filled with of course awards some new game announcements many things that you've been rumored online may happen tonight
We've had an amazing year for games. So let's get right to the show with our first big award of the night
To present our first award
He's a mega popular youtuber and she's a twitch streamer nominated tonight for content creator of the year
Please welcome jacksepticeye and pokeymaid. I didn't put him on there. That's that's a celebrity, right?
Is that a celebrity parents that accounts, right?
I was gonna put you too
No, no that didn't count
We're pretty lucky in that we're able to play games for a living and so to all the developers here and watching around the world
Thank you for doing what you do and making the games that we love green hair
She's got green hair. I know. Yes, thank you. We're here to present the award for best narrative
These are the games whose stories captivated us with complex characters surprising twists and profound philosophical ideas
Coming up here are the nominees
Best this isn't like a family get-together. This is like an award show. I didn't choose to be different
To be true to start the war
You I can't wait until the bald guys get on that stage
My most favorite villain of the night I can guarantee
This is a nightmare. I know who you like the strange two episode one
What you and your brother have is the most important thing
Spider-man is just but it's spider-man. I don't know if I agree with that
Spider-man is just hey look, we're doesn't want me. Yeah, the narrative was great when it was written, you know
10 years 15 years ago
Shots fired what? No, i'm just saying like spider-man like as a series like dock octopus rp exists
It wasn't like an original game award character. All right, it's gonna be red dead red dead redemption, too
Yeah
Thank you from the entire team at rockstar to all our fans everyone who voted
For us, um, we love telling stories just as much as we love crazing worlds and it's been incredible
Seeing people connect to the game and go on arthur's journey for themselves
Um, i'd like to thank our amazing cast
They brought this to life in ways we didn't even imagine get it off and you can see tonight and across this category
It's been an outstanding year for games and storytelling and there's still so far we can take it
So, uh onto the next one. Thank you very much. Yeah, it's very fun. That's like a fantastic video
German has moved to visibly drunk
Throughout the night, we're gonna take a look at the future of games with world premieres now some of them
You've probably heard of and some of them you definitely haven't we've got some good surprises tonight
And this is one of those that no one is going to see coming. Enjoy
Uh
Idiots your stupidity may have doomed the universe wouldn't be the first time sweetheart guardians of the galaxy video game presentation
Oh, who's our master shall fall?
At its chance to rule avengers
He's just marvel heroes
Like to see it try scrappy
When the black order
Death always prevails
If we want to survive here
We do it as a team on ipad iphone and switch
Marvel ultimate alliance. Oh wait, that's actually kind of cool, but that didn't look good
I shall be waiting here for you
That was Thanos you missed it
Please welcome an actor and the writer director of the film mid 90s
Here's Jonah hill
There he is shout out to woody jackson the best composer in the world we might get bingo much earlier than I thought
I am honored to be here tonight to introduce someone who has truly changed gaming forever
Someone who in his own words just wanted to make killer games with his friends
And ended up making some of the world's most memorable titles
30 years ago, he and his friends started with nothing. They worked in a small basement under a nurse's call center
Over the years greg thomas and his team at visual concepts created iconic games by following a simple recipe
Hard work strong ideas in a passionate team
And that rep is uh recipe gave us nba 2k
Greg, yeah, I give it up
It doesn't
Greg is a humble giant, but his forward-thinking passion and dedication to excellence
Has made his name known throughout the industry. Let's take a look back at his highlight reel
industry icon
Oh boy, I talk a lot of shit about this company a lot about visual concepts
The speakers baby 2k sports major league baseball
The nba right here on 2k sports the greatest basketball game in the world this game bigger than the court
This king is far from finished
Very cool why that i'm honored to introduce the 2018 industry icon the legend the myth the goat
Mr. Greg thomas
He did a lot he did a lot for the industry
Thank you jona
It's such an honor to be introduced by you
What the hell was that seeing a compilation of the games that we've created over the last 30 years is also very humbling
Do we have something like that on anyone who knows me?
You know i've shied away from the spotlight
I'm not very comfortable being the center of attention
This has never been
about
Making a name for myself
It's always been about making great games
But this is an incredible honor
First I need to thank my beautiful wife and family
For allowing me to do
They're sleeping everything i've always loved to do there have been many sacrifices
And they have been patient mom loyal and understanding through it all. I love you all very much. Thank you
So you did a lot you did a lot and none of this would be possible
without my business partner
And co-founder scott patterson and my brother and the leader of the nba 2k team
Jeff thomas i'd love for you guys
We've been together
Since the very beginning and we've always shared the same values and passions when it comes to making games
No
We never imagined that over the years visual concepts would grow to where we are today with six worldwide studios
And more than 350 employees the philosophy has never changed
It's all family to me. I also want to thank david ismailer
carl sladoff and strouse elnick from 2k and take two
For believing in me and giving us the freedom to make games our way
And I and I owe everything i'm not even there i like my management team this team has been together for a long time
The culture of the company has always been about believing in our people
It's because we love working together and we all believe in the same things
And I need to thank all of their families as well for supporting us and putting up with us
That can't be easy. Thank you so much
Wow all three of them start without these people there is no greg thomas receiving an award
There is no visual concepts. They are the real icons and I share this award with them. Thank you very much
All right now he got it we got the name congratulations greg now tonight
The game awards and facebook gaming are recognizing global gaming citizens people who are enriching the lives of others around the world
Through video games we're going to tell some stories tonight of three people that I think you should meet and hear their stories
And i'm so proud to have these in the game awards first up
Steven spawn from able gamers, please take a look at his story
I don't know how I got where I am or what i'm doing
All I wanted to do was figure out how to play video games
And along the way I figured out that I can help other people play video games, too
When I was coming out of high school
I went to my guidance counselor to figure out what's next in life for me
They sat across the table for me and they told me that I should go home and have fun with my remaining years
Because i'm going to die soon anyway, they told me to just go home and die at the time it kicked me down
But now it's a memory that I look back on and I realized that you can be disabled
You can be productive. You can be a valuable contributing member of society and you can change the world
By doing a few things along the way that no one else is willing to do
I'm proud to be one of the leaders of able gamers in helping people with disabilities be able to conquer the challenges of getting back
Into playing video games
My mission is to enable people to use technology to reach out to connect with a world that
Was otherwise inaccessible they're able to have a greater quality of life
By having people in their lives. Cheers for that
Amazing steven, you rock
Three years ago psionics burst onto the scene and rocker powered soccer has never been the same with more than 52 million players worldwide
It's a two-time winner at the game awards and now rocket league is revealing their latest dlc right here. Check it out dlc
Is that actually a game announcement though? Come on announcing the downloadable content
On the game awards, but it's rocket league. So it'll be like an ice cream truck, right?
All right, it's already filled in car on stage car reveal just change it to car reveal
Who cares that thing already would have been off you took you you took the fucking fondant off already
I don't focus on in the game school. I guess but I don't whatever parents in the game though
I don't play rocket league. I've heard it was fun to people who played rocket league
I think it's a fun game to enjoy themselves in rocket league. That's fun coming up
Christophe waltz and rosa salazar hand out the award for best performance and later
More surprise game announcements and musical performances
2018 oh are they gonna get like actors on stage to act out stuff in the game
That's what I would fucking pay for wake up wake up. No now. Yeah. Yeah
ads now for paths to be beat and treasures one
And impossible tales to be sung
As we take on our foes
together as one
We send our fears back to where they came from
I don't show whoops. That's my camera. I don't show fucking ads on this stream
I don't show ads on the stream, but i'll show it, but it's just like smash brother. So I gotta put it back on
Who's that character
Who's that character who's that the guy the bear
Right now we've got an exclusive action-packed clip from the new film elita battle angel directed by robert
Rodriguez and produced by james cameron and coming to theaters february 14th. Check this out. I don't show ads on my stream
Sorry
I don't put advertising on my stream
Whoa, it's baraka. All right, it's back on fine. Watch your time
Okay
Oh cool from the upcoming film elita battle angel, please welcome rosa salazar and two-time academy award winner christoph waltz
Neither are the celebrity presenters, but we gotta we gotta let's see
To deliver a powerful game performance. You must humanize a digital puppet made of polygons and textures
In a sense the actor plays the surrogate for their audience their entry point
into the game's world
and
personalities
Then unlike any medium
The connection continues and strengthens that was fucking sneezed controls that very that was like a cough or a sneeze analog stick
I'm, sorry that counts. I prefer mouse and keyboard. I'm not gonna do this with you
Look, I mean
aim assist is just
Okay
These are the nominees for best performance
Best performance
For me it was strong female characters that I happen to know
Join us in battle. All right, do you see all those dots fight with you?
I
Didn't choose to be better with like you better win
Connor come on. It's conor and conor has to win this. Come on. Do you have anything to say in your defense?
Effective in combat a warrior must not feel for his enemy. So i'm a man like you
We are more than that
Spider-man look next time need the fighting to the pros. It was a good spider-man. It was really good spider-man
But if there aren't any around fuck
He's good, too
If we get paid or you get shot i'm happy
I would say conor or carter and the game award goes to
roger clark
Can I add a category
I guess this is the part where words that make sense are supposed to come out of my mouth
Thank you, I humbly accept this honor, especially in light of the amazing performances of my fellow nominees
Wow
To share this moment in time with all of you a moment in time
Which is clearly becoming the advent of a golden age of this medium
I gotta thank my wife molly. I love you molly and mom
She watched me
Come home from long days of performance capture and kindly reminded me to check arthur at the door put the kids to bed
You didn't want arthur that reminds me
I would also like to thank rockstar games for the amazing opportunity
The faith that they put in me
Thank you. Thank you all
This is an amazing moment
It was very good. It was great
I feel back to conor though because conor
It's very it was that performance was very real director for one of the biggest games in ubisoft history far cry five
And he's here right now to unveil the next chapter. Please welcome far cry six
Far cry number six guys
At some point, okay, like honestly like if it's far cry six. Hello everyone
You at some point like you may remember
Indeed
Ah, we didn't put confetti dropping on montana and this marked the very beginning of a brand new world
Because yes, we're finally bringing the post apocalypse to far cry
and
As the creative director of this new project. It is my absolute pleasure to reveal to you far cry new dawn
No, you just didn't number it. Whatever
Do we have to like make a make like a fucking monster movie or something? You know what I mean?
Make like a return of the monsters
Far cry like seven. I just make like a movie where you have a video game you play as a character and you're a monster in
monster universe
You were just kids when the bombs dropped and the world went to shit
They said it was supposed to be the end
Just like put I want like jason freddy krueger the mummy
It was just the beginning all the same game and like he plays plays a monster
This new world took it all. That's how we came out on top
That's how we got here
That's how we found you
Listen here rabbits
You need to understand something the only currency left in this world is power
We're gonna take everything from you
Starting with your home. I want to play as a chef if we can't take these studios have millions of dollars
Don't make like another far cry make like a fucking chef game
You just be a chef in an open world. Why the fuck hasn't somebody done that?
There's a that's a monster they finally listen to me I wanted a monster in the game
I'm sorry. I played for like about three hours into the new world
I thought that it would be glorious
I was wrong
That's so close
February 15th is when it comes out
Far cry new dawn now tonight you can also find special offers on all our nominated games across xbox
Live in nintendo eshop steam and the playstation store
So make sure to check your favorite place to get games for some special offers on nominees and more right now
We've got another world premiere check this out. I'm looking forward to this. I love the world premieres. It makes you feel like just so
Bubbly inside, you know what I mean?
from the creators
Bastion and transistor
Comes a new game. Where do you think you are?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Nobody gets out of my domain whether alive or you wish to learn. It's not gonna be a card game fine
Get out. Don't let me stop you. It's not gonna be a card game
Wasn't planning on it father
Mobile it's a mobile game
Zeus who do you play?
What's his name plato i'm home well time to go get killed again
Dude, it's like a dark souls, but it's like bastion and transistor in the same game
Death is your only family
death hades
I would play it for a little bit
Sorry
It's oh it's now available on early access in the epic games store
Fortnite game store giant that is an early access title
They're going to be updating over time and it's available tonight right now on the epic games store
So congratulations greg amir and the entire team there at super giant
I am here now with my friend patrice daisley the designer behind assassins creed famously and uh, you're working on a new project called
ancestors a humankind odyssey. Thank you. Tell us about god you're not making an
Assassin's creed. Thank you for having me of course quite an honor for me to be here
Thank you. This is the game is gonna have monsters the humankind odyssey
It is a single player open world exploration survival game
It is set in africa starting 10 million years ago
Where basically players will play from the last coming and ancestors of all the big apes up to lucy
The famous australopithecus
Okay, that's that's a lot of game there
uh
Tell us a bit about uh where you're at in this game and what we're gonna see tonight because you're gonna show us some
Gameplay here comes some game totally okay
So this game is that is done by panache digital games my new studio back in montreal 30 people. Hi everyone
And tonight i'm gonna show that was four clips of
Actual gameplay that was really close. How long is an awkward silence. This is real
This is real on the sticks exactly. All right
And yes people like what they see they can go on game spot and see another 20 minutes of me playing
The very beginning of the game after the show. All right, you're showing it all here
It is ancestors a humankind odyssey. Thank you patrice. Well, the fuck is awkward silence. There it is
Inspired by true events
This is 10 million years ago
Giant snake the fuck is happening
Fuck ancestors
Okay, now there's a few ways that mean
That's kind of like spore, but it happened in real life. You know what I mean?
The question i've asked is is do do I get to like fly in spaceships eventually?
You know what I mean? I'll be right back. I gotta pee
I need another one of these two
Games play best on xbox one
So
Girls make games is a program that inspires girls to make games
It teaches them the tools that they need to get from start where they know nothing to get to a full
Develop prototype in three weeks my favorite part about camp doing the designing for how the platform is
my experience with gmg
Has given me the confidence to pursue author writing
and
video game projects
The whole mission is just amazing to really inspire young girls to learn to make games and really get
The female perspective and voice in games
We're good you didn't even see why you didn't even comment on my glass
Why did you not even comment on that?
All right, so I did anything happen while I was gone
I don't think I missed anything
We have so much more game awards to come right now. Here's another world premiere
This might be more than five, right? Is this more than five premieres?
Because they I gotta fill that in
This would be five
Okay, fill it in only possible with spatial os
Is this a vr presentation? Well now somebody needs to get on stage and they put the headset on
I don't think that's gonna happen though. I don't think anyone's gonna get on stage with a fucking headset on
Garfield of what?
Is it starfield? I don't think it's oh starfield
This is not starfield
borderlands 3
But didn't gearbox shut down didn't they permanently?
No, no, no. No. Yeah, they did
They may as well
I'm just kidding. It's a joke
I'm kidding
I was just making a joke about video gaming
Uh scavengers, that's your first look at scavengers and i'm now here with josh holmes from midwinter josh
Tell us a bit about your studio
Yeah, well, so midwinter is a new studio up in seattle washington. We're a relatively small team
We're just over 20 people
Uh, many of us come from triple a background working on titles like halo and battlefield. This is our newest game
I want sequels. Why do you want sequels? We got a tease of sort of the world there
Some of the characters what kind of game is it? So scavengers is a survival shooter
Co-opitition it's uh, it's a game where teams need to cooperate to survive but compete to win
So what we're doing is we're taking all of the aspects of a survival game and sort of condensing that into a replayable
Session based multiplayer experience awesome. All right, and if people want to learn more it's a little tag there to sign up, right?
Yeah, yeah for us. It's so important to have players have a voice in shaping the game
And and so starting in 2019
We're going to be having play tests and people can go right now go to scavengers game.com sign up
And you'll be among the first to play scavengers in 2019. Awesome. All right. Well, thank you so much for putting that together
It's an amazing world premiere first look at scavengers. Josh, uh sign up for that now
All right, it's now time to present our next award
It was just please welcome the front man from panic at the disco to do it brendan yuri
Why
I don't know. I I just want to say what an honor to be here first off and secondly
I have to apologize because I was supposed to write something last night
But I stayed up till 5 a.m playing season 7 of fortnight. So I apologize fortnight reference
Oh, wait, never thought they wrote it for me. Okay
Personally, I'm constantly amazed by the skills of the composers in this industry
They make tracks that elevate all the action intention and set the perfect mood. Here are the nominees
What's this for best score music presented by spotify
Has any disgruntled nominee tweeted after they lost somebody needs to find that out
They didn't play either one of these two games
That was pretty good. Spider-man is pretty it's gonna be red dead
I don't know what this game is
Apparently, it's it's got a good musical track score
Octopath traveler
I can already tell like there comes red dead. This would be three for red dead, right?
We only need two more to get the extra bonus space
Okay, only two more for the extra bonus space red dead redemption two
One two three four get them up there. Come on get ten up there
Right, this is gonna be just like when return of the king came up
They've won every single fucking award of the academy awards
It's gonna win like 12 different categories
Thanks
Wasn't expecting it, but thanks a lot. Um, thanks to my wife
Sharon Jackson
my two daughters
georgia washington jackson
And theodora roosevelt jackson to make sure I get that
Um, I they've been all the games their heart beats since the past 10 years
So I really appreciate my family and use them appropriately
um
Not a comedian, but I try to play one sometimes
Rock star. I thought everyone was a surrogate family. I severely underestimated that
and this guy
Came in and did the most beautiful
sad
Music thank you so much. Yeah. Yeah
All right, my brother
Is that right?
Not quite. I don't think so
No, that wasn't that wasn't it to daniel and woody and speaking of score and soundtrack. I uh,
Want to let you know i've got a new podcast series with spotify six episodes called score points
We're actually went behind the scenes and interviewed a lot of the composers nominated there including uh, woody about no
It's not a candy company. It's not a soda or candy uh, fuck me
Whatever and about fifa so lots of great stuff. Uh, make sure to check that out tonight on spotify
It's called score points. Uh right now
I'd like to recognize some other winners tonight in other major categories the best audio design presented by
Dolby and these are the nominees in that category car on there for the horizon horizon for god of war
Marvel's spider-man and red dead redemption 2
And the game award for best audio design goes to red dead redemption 2. It's having a pretty good night
Uh, all right for best art direction get the bonus square the nominees in this craft category are assassins creed odyssey
god of war
octopath traveler
red dead redemption 2
and return of the obra den
and the winner is
return of the obra den
Congratulations to lucas poco. I know it's here tonight
Next up the category of best mobile game and those nominees are donut county
florence
fortnight fortnight had better not mobile and reigns game of thrones
They'll be booze at fortnight wins best mobile game goes to well here it comes lorence. Oh, he said
He said the
All right. He said the f ar game. Those nominees are florence rescue mission
Beat saber firewall zero hour. That's gonna be beat saber
Beat saber right astrobot rescue mission is the winner for best vr ar game congratulations
Now on twitch everyone is voting right now to select who they think is gonna win in major categories content creator of the year
Is coming up and let's see what the twitch poll is predicting
It looks like people are predicting that ninja is going to win that one with 49 percent
He ain't gonna win the vote. We'll find out ninjas in the house among with many other content creators
All right. Well next up warframe. It's had its biggest year yet
It just launched fortuna the newest open world expansion on pc and it's coming to xbox and ps4 on december 10th
That's some breaking news and for the first time ever you can play warframe anywhere on the switch warframe did come out
On the switch for nintendo switch, but it is a remake or a remaster essentially right or a re-release
I'm gonna get some more votes first
I hit the wrong button. I gotta I gotta get more votes for fucking best streamer on the platform
Two people voted right there
Somebody took it away and put it back on on ninja
I see 10. I see 10 just jumped up
Thank you guys
Thank you so much everybody
Thank you
Wow warframe is good on view yeah, but it's warframe but it's on switch
Where do you vote?
It doesn't matter
Yes, it does. I thought I knew why I came here
I saw what is this for
You set the apocalypse in motion
I want let's take a look at how we stand here though
All we really need listen, here we go guys bingo is upon us. You had the power somebody has to save revolutionary
Somebody has to get played off
Because they're on there too long and somebody has to heckle somebody somebody does a heckle from the audience
That's bingo coming up
Oh, we need somebody fall down 10 people to accept an award and then there's gonna be a pop figurine in the shot somewhere
That's a fortnight dance, right?
What what was that was that saw
What video game is this this is freddy krueger jason in the mummy in a video game
What was that? No, no, what was that one? What was that one that I wanted to see?
Freddy krueger
It's got them all
It's got everybody. What game is this?
this jason
dough
dead by daylight
What is that describing whatever here with matt cote? He is the game director for dead by daylight
We just saw that matt welcome to the game awards. Thank you very much
It's such an honor to be here. Dead by daylight. Lots of canadian montreal teams up here
Which i'd love to see my home country canada. I hear you've got some big plans for the game, right?
We plan to keep this game alive. Where's the fucking captain america video game our dedication essentially tonight
We're announcing the dedicated servers are coming to dead by daylight this summer. Okay summer 2019. Yep
And I also want to show the trailer for the very first time for our new chapter coming to dead by daylight
Darkness among us. Okay, let's take a look at that another world premiere. Thanks so much
That's more than that's more than five
Who's the new character?
in dead by daylight brothers
Who's the new confirmed character?
What what is what what what what that's not even a fucking horror movie character. Who is that?
Is that like a from from some one-off
one-off fucking movie
What one-off fucking horror movie is that from sure to put the mummy in
I'm back here now with casey hudson the general manager at bioware another canadian company. It's the canada section
All right. Well, you're almost done with anthem casey. Tell us where are you at? It's coming early next year, right?
Yeah, it's coming out in february and so we've got uh, you know mark dara and the team are doing an incredible job
Finishing it up. It's almost done
And uh, yeah, we're super happy to be here and be able to show a little bit more of the game tonight
Yeah, so what are we gonna start crying? Well, so a lot of what we've shown so far is the gameplay
It's super fun
You're basically
You know an armored super hero in a fantasy setting and we've shown a lot of that
We haven't really let people in on what the story is and the characters and things like that
But you know like a great bioware game
We're building out a whole world of story is what I want to know
So we're gonna start letting you in on a little bit more of that
Well, I know the the entire team is working very hard on this, right?
Yeah, I mean we've got a big team working on it, but we've got a few projects at bioware
So it's not the only thing that we're working on
And uh, so we do have a few surprises left
Okay, but anthem right now anthem right now and uh always thinking about our next thing
All right. I tried. All right. Uh, here's a look at anthem. Check it out
That was kind of awkward, but we already filled it in
All right world premiere of anthem. It's not that's not a world premiere. Is it?
I have seen the power of the anthem. Why is anthem just destiny?
Is this just destiny with peter dinklage in it? Wait destiny was peter dinklage
Did they make destiny?
I feel they made destiny, right?
Did they it's cool. They did
The generations our people struggled just to survive
So they did halo destiny which is kind of
Put the fucking mummy in a gate guys
It's like halo. Look, it's the flood the walls at destiny our families. Where's the mummy loved ones?
Remember we're a team i'm right there with you. It's a freelancer job always has been
Nobody ever thinks they're mummy by the way
Which is bullshit
You understand
Oops can only do so much. Oh fuck i've ruined it. I didn't i'm fine
Yeah anthem play it out your funeral that game's doa
I think it's probably gonna be fun
You're not mic'd up nobody can hear you guys
Nothing
There's nothing here though
Trained animal used fire alarm fortnight dance. I already got fortnight dance
Somebody in a costume guys sleeping in the audience. We might get a chance here
Why do I even have some new banjo kazooie game on here is it more than two bald guys on stage
Oh, fuck me. Hold on a second here. Hold on
There are at least four guys that have balled on stage
One two three four fill it in
So close to a bingo. What do you mean that doesn't count?
Two or more bald guys. That's a that's it
That doesn't matter about the book. They're on the stage that counts the game awards continues. Everybody is here tonight including
crash bandicoot
Cb in the house. What are you doing here? Not much man. Just thought uh, you deserved a trophy of your own
The standard issue crash crate should I how do I open this thing? I think uh, maybe give it a good somebody
I got a long show to host. I'm just gonna open it very professionally here on games biggest thing. That's good. That's good
This might happen. What's this? This this kind of looks familiar
Doesn't now booyah booyah kingdom hearts. Let's check out the world premiere kingdom hearts
Two three
What?
Check out the trigger for crash team racing
Crash is back
That's not banjo kazooie shit. I mean it could be
Hold on a second here guys. They're the same color scheme
Crash bandicoot is like a bear with orange fur
Right does that count?
They're both bears. They're both orange
If crash bandicoot has like a pinocchio nose, that's the only difference. That is the only difference. They have same color shorts on
They have the same color shorts on the only difference is the pinocchio nose crash
Yeah, it's the same character that it just shorts on he's a bear. He's fucking orange. I'm gonna count that one
I count that there are two of the voices from god of war. Please welcome sunny soljic and christopher judge
Oh, okay, it's the voices games have always had a strong sense of community
I remember when I was a kid booming voice younger
Uh gathering around someone at the arcade who was close to breaking a high score
But i'm blown away by how much bigger that community is in today's connected age
Millions of people around the world aren't just playing games. They love they're watching their favorite online personality stream for hours at a time
These are the nominees
For the content creator of the year
Come on creator of the year
That's not me
Something that I enjoy and being able to bring joy to others doing something that you enjoy is a miracle
Me whoa and the game award goes to heckler that's a heckler rian boy
What who is that what's that twitch name the award goes to ninja
I'm not gonna lie. This is a an incredible honor
I would first off just like to thank my lovely wife. Jessica who's joining me today
And my family who's supported me my entire life. They've always let me play video games
As long as I was just a little bit more active outside. So
But you know, this has just been an incredible year for gaming and video games
And i'm just honestly blessed to be in the position that i'm in to have won this award and to bring joy to all
The people who who love watching video games, so I mean, I think it's crazy that
every single person in this room
And every single person watching
It's all because of video games. So
Uh, I mean here's to another incredible year 2019. Thank you guys so much. I appreciate it
And yes, I respect my fellow nominees
Please welcome the creator and game designer of fallout here are tim kane and lennard boyarski
It's hard to believe it's been 20 years since we made fallout and 13 years since we last worked together at troika
Yeah, and it's great to be reunited on a new single player rpg
We're very excited to reveal our brand new brand new universe the outer worlds. We hope you enjoy it
Oh, wait, uh, hold on a second. You were supposed to say that you remember. Yeah. Um
What we're supposed to say is by watching this trailer you are legally obligated to enjoy it
Thank you. Thank you
I just broke my neck. I just broke my neck. I think I just broke my neck
I just did that dog tilted so much. I think I just broke my neck
What's going on question first? Are you feeling anything that can be construed as explosive cell death? No wonderful
Let's get started
Destiny three
What is this? I wasn't paying any attention
Being the edge of the galaxy the frontier of space
Well, at least it was until the corporations bought it branded it and started selling it at ludicrously
Prices biochalk lands three the rest of your fellow settlers
Abandoned on the edge of the colony. I'd save them myself, but the boards got a bounty on my head
Survival wasteland game. That's why I thought you out you appear capable
Look I get it
Taking on the corporation has left us taking on the corporation bad and worse
That's fucking corporations
And you have to choose now
Let me tell you something about this fucking corporation
You know, you didn't have to shoot either one, right?
But it's fine. I guess you just keep being you
Okay, okay i'm stuck like this
Oh
I can't move
Spacers choice is not responsible for any feeling of vertigo wonder or hunger you may have experienced while watching this advertisement
They thought that was funny they were laughing at me
So is that like gonna be like good fallout from obsidian? Thanks for that and check out
That's that's probably gonna be fucking really good because that's like fallout, but it's supposed to be actually fallout
That's that's like a fallout game by the guys that made the good fallout, right?
I'm excited. You see my I I got fucking pog stuck. You know what I mean?
It happens sometimes gotta be careful
How's the league of legends riot games developed in the monster hunter world? That's an alpha, right?
Yeah, this that this that riot games presents
monster hunter
Now it's not a mobile. This is an actual like an action game
And then they take the loop from his teeth, right? I told you where's the term of predicts?
I fucking think that that was great
now here from dotless is
mike mike
Now here at judgy cowston the ceo of phoenix labs a couple years ago
You were with us announcing this game jesse and now you're back
We sure are and it's been quite a couple of years. It was a heckler
You know, we're super excited to not only talk about
The last couple years but also the future and you know, it's really awesome coming into the future and being able to see
In april rather and launch the game
On xbox and ps4 and the epic platform
Um, you know from the get-go dotless has always been about bringing players together
Friends and killing big behemoths and uh, you know
Those platforms are going to be kind of the next big journey for us
And tonight you got something launching too, right? We sure do so
It's our biggest content expansion pack frostfall drops today, uh on pc at play dotless.com. All right
Well, check it out play down. I thought you couldn't even play this jesse. Well, you can actually all right
We'll be right back after this
Sorry
When I was growing up
I didn't see any women doing a lot of bigger things in my life
But so you can now you can play that game right now expectation from girls
So even the girls education is not like the like the top priority
I'm, I thought you had to background. It was be like invited to the alpha
Pursue this to make money to be able to afford the private school so that I can go and study computer science
Getting education. It's not about just getting degree. It's actually getting exposure
to the world
You can't be if you can't see
That's what we are trying to do is give them an inspiration
pixel art games academy is a training academy pixel art games academy
In focus is actually empowering game developers and creative artists to be able to make their own game ideas
This is my biggest dream. I want people to see what kind of ideas what kind of creative five community subs from kazi
Thank you
Welcome to the guy that lost top streamer on screen
Thank you. Oh, I shouldn't put him on here
I was gonna put it on later Joel McHale shows up from fortnight
This is the game awards. I mean like honestly like I don't know what but was I shit faced when I made this
No one's gonna fucking fight on stage. Hold on. Wait a minute. We got smash brothers brawl
Ultimate I hope you have the stamina because the game's about to be in stock and it's almost time
Welcome to my store. It's one not bound by walls
No, this is everybody has seen this fucking commercial, you know what i'm saying
Everybody's seen that commercial
I don't put ads on my stream
Never you'll never see an ad on my I mean I can't control pre-rolls because I can't turn them off
I don't think but I you'll never see an ad be play. I don't play ads on the stream
You haven't seen good. Oh, yeah, see that commercial you haven't seen that commercial
That commercial was on tv like seven years ago
Seven months ago, whatever and this is an artifact
No, it's not
Tonight, we've got some of the biggest franchises in the world unveiling their new games
We've also got some smaller studios sharing their projects. This is another one boomer watches tv
Is there any an ember drifts from the flame?
Life is strange
Why are you telling me to skip this? I don't have control over this
Skip the game
I can't and you don't know which way
Through the shadow
I made a puzzle game
Okay
I wonder if after this trailer they're gonna say this is the greatest video game to ever be made
Mean streamer. No, i'm just kidding. It's a joke
It's a joke
And then
That looks kind of good
Let me like backtrack a little
Oh, no, my sky was terrible. Those developers were fucking what the hell are they thinking? Oh this game looks kind of good
When I was asked to present the award for best esports player I
Did not hesitate
Video games have brought me and my sons closer together every morning. They fire up shocker
fortnight and
uh
Their eyes light up with the promise of a new day and they demand my credit card information
And you give it to them joe and you give it to them joe
You forgot that part of the presentation. They were forcing me to buy a rainbow rider an astro backwing
They grow up so fast. Anyway, he cried, okay
Esports continue to grow exponentially every year with sold out arena tournaments all over the world and millions of dollars on the line
This award recognizes the most dominant athlete in esports
Whomever wins this is basically the lebron james of sitting
It's amazing. Here are the nominees
Best esports player presented by omen by hp
Because a maddie game is playing this kid can do it can take it all sonic box the champ
Fighting game fighting game is your champion
We won more championship for the best player in the world
Break was too far back. I don't know. That is stunning from simple
Oh
Okay, there's a rubik's cube guy award goes to who is the rubik's cube guy fox everybody the guy that can like
What do you mean? Who the fuck is that guy? That's a guy in a costume. We already have that selected
I'm in full
buried costume
uh
Wow, I really want this shit. Oh my god
Guys
Big honor, uh, I kind of just really really enjoy playing video games competitively
um
I've never really really done it for the fame. I kind of just
Enjoy the rush of like beating people up, you know, like
I don't know like even like, uh, i'm sure you guys heard the story of
uh
When I won the ips finale the other thing I don't do this for is for the money
Because when uh, my best friend my best friend one of my closest friends. Oh my god. I'm nervous
uh
His dad had cancer and
After I won before I even like uh did the match I told him whether I win or lose
I'm gonna be donating at least like 10k of the prize winning to his father for his stage three cancer
Pretty fucking awesome works out for him. Um
And he really really
That's pretty nice fucking thing
But
I mean I guess
I never really I had always just done it just to make new friends and bonds in the community
So, um, I guess for now I want to give a shout out
So obviously the team that's helped me with all the way ankle fox. I want to give a shout out to uh,
um
All my friends back out of home my best friend to kill sage. Uh, he's helped me out so much through life
Um mckinnon black the game the goons back at home gang gang
Um, uh as you guys also may know or may not know i'm also super gay. So I mean
I want to give a shout
So I want to give a super shout out to all my lgbtq plus friends that have always
Taught me through life. Um
Obviously i'm a furry so shout out to the furries
Furry
Guess all I gotta really say is that i'm gay
black a furry pretty much everything about public and hates and
The best sports players don't go here. I guess
Thank you so much. I'll tell you one thing, right? That's pretty smart. They have that too
If you would be nervous to give a speech or talk on stage
Is one thing that you need to remember is if you like can cover your face or like be cover your eyes
It's actually easier to do like in a costume or in character. So that makes sense
It actually makes sense easier to talk publicly don't eat those pills. Don't eat the pills. Don't eat the pills bird. Don't eat the pills bird
Don't eat the pills bird
Nobody's fallen down yet. How has nobody said the word revolutionary is that impossible?
Dead bird. Okay winter has arrived the wind the winds of winter
Oh, it's pubg. That's not a world premiere
That's a pubg video game
No revolutionary
No fist bump
No cutting edge
Nobody's visibly drunk. All right. I have here with dave kurd the world art director at pubg corporation
Uh dave why don't you tell us about the uh, the new map besides the new terrain people can get to play tonight
What else? All right, except for me. It's our first six by six map
Which is the sweet spot between the chaos of sanic and the tactics of eringal
It's also a snow map, which means you leave footprints players can track you you can track them
Hunter becomes the hunted
Uh, what about new gear this time around?
Absolutely, we're gonna have the g-36c assault rifle and a very fast very new badass snowmobile to explore the map in
Okay snowmobile and we're gonna get to like
Yeah, it's the best news it's ready tonight pc test servers and it's gonna be on xbox one and playstation 4 in january
All right, so jump on steam tonight for that. Uh, and also the ps4 version hits tomorrow, right?
Yeah tomorrow, december 7 food references. We're super excited to join the playstation community
All of our new ps4 players are going to receive an exclusive parachute
And finally, it's your last chance to pre-order which will grant the nathan drake desert outfit from the uncharted series
And ellie's backpack from the last of us get it
All right. Fantastic dave really appreciate it pubg great to have you back with us again
All right
Now i'd like to introduce our next presenters they're members of a grammy award-winning band that I love personally from weezer
Please welcome brian bale and rivers cuomo
Just a warning
Things are about to get heavy. Why do they look like created character versions of themselves right now?
I'd like you to throw them away
Am I like out of my mind toss them anywhere?
Also, if you have any religious artifacts put those away
Just tuck them under your seats because we're about to summon some dark spirits
Here's the composer of devil may cry 5 casey edwards with vocals by alley edwards
We're gonna get a full song didn't put full performed song on here
maybe
Maybe somebody will drop the microphone
Oh
Drop the microphone might get us a mic drop or in the middle of this is a madden announcement
Stop, I how am I you want to stop? How about even stop?
Okay, everybody action game awards are cancelled
German on eight five seven do something else
What are you supposed to like snap my fingers and all of a sudden there's another thing on the screen
I should have put tongue on there
Fire could have been on here
Comb your hair until it's over. I love that like going all the way up and all the way down
All right, there was devil trigger and that's you wanted it over the last three years nearly 20 million players
Boogered
You didn't did you see hold on?
Did boogers just come out of my nose?
I think they did fuck whatever it was trans you didn't see anything
This is not in the right fucking headphones
sea of thieves
It was a wellhound
Could have put that on there
What does he put on there?
We need revolutionary somebody to get the music and we need somebody to heckle the the winner
We get big bill or somebody to fall down
10 people accepting an award and a pop figure
We're also pretty close to
Miyamoto live via satellite and somebody dropping the microphone
We would make some ground if elijah would showed up
Uh, there's definitely not going to be a trained animal used in any presentation
I'm here with jeremy and jesse from wildcard studios guys. Congratulations on the announcement tonight coming next week
What exactly is atlas? She knows not going to smash massive open world survival
Mmo for 40,000 concurrent players in the same environment. It's a game about building an armada
Claiming territory forming an empire say it and ultimately dominating the entire globe. It's a same
How big is the map?
It's really big
The alice world is 1200 times the size of a single arc server and our team has spent countless hours
Handcrafting a beautiful place to play in with biomes from tropics to tundra desert polar regions
And we've filled it with amazing creatures
Everything from things you would expect like livestock to crazy mythological creatures that are guarding the secrets of an ancient civilization
There's so much fun stuff to see and do in atlas and it's just going to be awesome to reach in amazing
Well, uh coming to pc any word coming to console yet amazing
Alice will be coming to console next year to xbox game preview program
We got great feedback from the fans on arc for a game preview and we're excited to bring it first to xbox next year
Awesome. All right. Well, thanks guys. I know lots of work ahead in the week week ahead to launch it
We really appreciate it. Uh, we've also got our twitch poll continuing
Um, so the award for best independent game people have been voting on that that's coming up in the show
And right now twitch is saying that they think dead cells is going to take that with uh, 39 percent of the vote
So we'll find out if they're right when we come back on the way a world premiere. You won't want to miss
Then ninja and pepe the king prong present the award for best independent game
And later we celebrate the music of red dead redemption 2
Don't stop streaming. This is the game awards. They're talking like they're talking about the muppet
They're talking about they're talking about the muppet. Is that actually gonna happen?
Uh, that's the only thing I care about for the rest of the time. We're streaming
Is
Does pepe the king prong count as a trained animal?
I think about that counts that counts as a trained animal
That's a trained animal
Yeah, get rid of the philodend
He's he's technically a pro
Uh, oh my eyelids stuck in my eye
All right. I'm good
He's crying. No, i'm not crying
Oh, hello neighbor remember that came that came out back like point zero point eight alpha
I never released it on every platform
Is that i'm not mean
Oh, I actually i'm actually the end of this game. I actually want to play this one
This one is actually on my top to-do list of 2020
This is ashen, right? Yeah
That's top to-do list
What it's available now what's what's available right now where when when what?
That game's out. It's not out
Oh, we're gonna get a crackdown
Actually coming out today is there a reason for me to blow the dust off my fucking xbox
Everyone gets behind each other. It's very touching. Should I take that out of my like storage unit?
That's down the fucking road
So in the television series that i'm currently working on the outpost I play a knight captain and in elder scrolls online
I play a magic award. I'm rob boudica ufc middleweight champion. I play an imperial tank and elder scrolls online
I'm chris keely and I play a redguard stamina dragon knight and elder scrolls online
Even though my brother has been far too busy to play with me recently
Okay, good we're back boy that was his actual brother welcome back to the game awards
We have so much more show coming doing that was jeff's brother lots of awards and right now
I'd like to announce some of the other award winners across some other categories
The nominees for our best debut indie game. This is recognizing a small studio making its first project
The nominees were donut county florence moss the messenger
Yoku's island express and the game award goes to the messenger. Congratulations
Also a canadian studio. There's something going on here
Uh, all right next up best fighting game and those nominees this year are blaze blue dragon ball fighters dragon ball fighters z man
It's gonna be that
Street fighter 5 arcade edition and the winner for best fighting game dragon ball fighters
What's ticking?
For best family game the nominees this year are mario tennis aces nintendo labo overcome two
Starlink battle for atlas better win and super mario or i'm gonna smash this into my mouth the game award goes to
Overcooked two. Oh, no, I have to do it now
Another genre category for best strategy game those nominees the banner saga three
Oh tech frostpunk into the breach and valkyria chronicles 4
And the winner for best strategy game into the breach. Congratulations subset games
All right. Well, we've got a lot more show ahead for you tonight and uh, we've got the big awards
We've got best game direction game of the year and so much more
But right now it's time to look at another game announcement world premiere for a second. I thought I was gonna say
frog
Oh, here's ninja and pepe the frog doing an announcement
pepe the king prawn
Let me do it. Let me do it
Let me do it
Just let me put the thing on diablo 4
Just let me do it
So you found me at last
I suspect you have questions
The dread wolf rises
I don't know what that is
Diablo 4 he's a mega popular streamer and he's a mega popular steamer
Here are ninja and from the muffins pepe the king prawn
That's a selfie that's a selfie friend on the big win, thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Let me get a selfie come on
Fill it in that's a good
Did you just say shelfie shelfie? See see it's a crustacean thing
That's a selfie and it's a trained animal. We didn't get a good one. My eyes were closed. Say manchego
manchego
That's a good one. That's a good one trained animal and selfie bucks for this. Okay
That's a
That's a fork knife reference
Uh, did you say fork knife? It's uh, it's it's actually pronounced for tonight
No, I don't think so. No, no, but believe me definitely. I know it's get out of here
Please
Well, I hate to disagree with everyone's but you're wrong
Fortnite makes no sense
Fortnite is only two weeks and I know I've spent a lot more time than two weeks playing this game
Say sangria
sangria
All right. Yeah, that's a good one. Look look we're supposed to be presenting
Uh the award for best independent game. Can we can we do that, please?
Sure, do what you gotta do. I'm gonna take some shelfies. Okay. All right
This award is for the best game made outside of the triple a system
Oh, there's a good one
Oh, did you say triple a? Yeah. Oh, it's amazing what they do without batteries these days
And here are the nominees. Oh nominees
Best independent game
The best indie game to see what it is dead settle it's gonna be dead cells
That's not just gonna win as many awards
Really party chat actors music, too. I'm surprised it hasn't happened yet. They've been like on the ball this year
Drop it. All right, and the award goes to
Hold on my friend. Let's get one more big shelfie with the big crowd in the background. Okay, everybody get crazy scream shelfie
Shelfie
Okay, my friend continue please. All right, and now the best independent game goes to
Drop the award how to do this alone. It's hard
The award goes to celeste
Tonight celeste also wins the games for impact award
I just I was just hoping he's gonna drop it because i'm gonna that's a mic drop, right?
So one two one two three four five six is it ten people up there
Uh, there's a few team members who I don't I don't know if that's ten and I know they're watching one two three
Four five six seven eight spin and uh the power of god. We love you and we wish you were here
eight
And
We're nothing without our support networks. So thanks to like our our partners and our family and our friends
For amazing six seven eight pressure my parents one two, three, four five. I can't count them for
I can't count these so
People on the stage
Hi, mom and dad. I love you. Is it nine?
so thank thank you for thanking we got completely lost in the work of making this game and uh,
We kind of forgot that people would eventually play it. So the reception has just been like
Well, what about really overwhelming ninjas on stage?
And jeff, right? That's ten
I'm like at a loss for things to fade
all year above the reception
uh
So there is one thing I want to say though. Um, if celeste has helped you come to terms with
uh mental illness
I just want to say that uh
You deserve credit for that
Uh, that change came from inside of you and uh, you're capable of a lot more. Thank you
I don't think that the prong doesn't count as a person so that they can't that would that it's got to be
That's nine. So didn't happen. Sorry guys
Yeah, that that's there was eight people on stage plus ninja is nine
But the king prawn that's I mean maybe the guy actually the guy that's that's uh got the hand up the prawn's ass, right?
The guy the puppeteer, right?
Is that that's ten, but that's not ten people that accepted the award
Now that doesn't count
Eight people accepted that award not ten
What platform would
The pathless on ipad ios
and iphone
Now epic store. They are really
Things are gonna get real interesting in the next couple of years
We got a muffin on the show finally, so i'm very personally happy pepe. Thank you for joining us
All right
She's gonna get really interesting special offers on all the nominated games across xbox
Nintendo e-shop steam and playstation store. So make sure to check out those offers tonight
Uh, and over the next few days, of course, uh, we are trending number one worldwide
People are like gonna be releasing their games exclusively on you see some of these amazing tweets at twitter
Many more surprises having so much fun. Why did I lose? Where's where's like the I lost?
Right launching tonight. It's human heads new game survived by it's launching right now on steam
You can play now in early access and it's published that's not a disgruntled vomiting developers of warframe. Here's a first look at survive
If I interesting you mean annoying
I mean people are using it though. That's the crazy part
It's like it's getting exclusivity dark has emerged from the depth. It's gonna get really weird here in the next couple years
Even the cute and cuddly
Into the damned and deadly
It is up to you to build your arsenal
And set forth on an epic journey this is like a this is like the maple story remake what is this
It's now up to you and probably many more of your descendants to set forth on an epic journey
To defeat this spreading plague that sours our land
I want to play this game team up with friends and tackle menacing foes
Or go it alone
Well, you can try it's totally up to you
Join a massive online adventure to help rid the lands of this mysterious and nearly unstoppable force
Nearly this realm of the mad god hd
there it is
Play for free and be among the first to help build the heartlands into something your ancestors would be proud of
Survived by find it on steam early access. It's early access
What's up, everybody? It's me melody mac here and on most days you can catch me streaming some games
But today I wanted to hop in at the game awards to talk about vaping and the simple fact
That if you vape you are four times more likely to smoke cigarettes
Now everybody knows that smoking cigarettes is extremely bad for you
But how vaping can lead to smoking cigarettes may not be as obvious
The amount of nicotine in just one jewel pod is the same as this is an anti-vaping
To learn more go to the truth.com to join the cause to finish smoking that many people
Is vaping like a fucking epidemic right now?
Oh, we gotta talk about vaping
People are just going like this, you know what I mean? They're just like
Why why everybody why you gotta go like that, you know, I mean go like that
What what's with the side like weird mouth thing? I don't get it
Your mom will tell other moms
Your little sister will know there's my aunt. There's my anti-vaping ad dog will know
Fake vapor store owner will know and so will these guys and so will she and the actual creator of magic
Will also know because when you're the world's number one magic player
the world
Will number one magic player
I just wanted to just do like a fat cloud at the end of that commercial, you know what I mean?
All right. I'm here with elaine chase the vice president of esports for magic the gathering elaine
Uh some fun cameos in that piece. Uh, what will the world know tell us so jeff
I am so excited to be here tonight to announce magic the gathering's new esports and competitive gaming program in 2019
We have 10 million dollars in prize money on the line across digital and tabletop magic
Wow, all right. That's that's a lot of money a big big prize
When is it going to start? I wasn't paying attention. It all kicks off in march at pax east in boston
Where we're hosting a one million dollar mythic invitational on mtg arena. Okay, that's that's a lot of money
How do people get on board if they want to?
Download and start playing mtg arena. Um, i've got something special for the audience tonight
We like special things. What are you she's gonna unpack a magic lotus card words
You'll receive an esports starter kit with some awesome cards to play
Awesome. Get that quick. Well elaine. Thank you so much. It's great to have that part of the game awards
Have a great evening. Thank you
We have a lot more show to come up tonight a winner tonight for a bunch of awards red dead redemption 2
Created a new standard among the beautiful landscapes and meticulous detail to its world
There is also a brilliant score that transported us straight to america in 1899 here tonight
It's a little surprised to perform a revolutionary red dead redemption 2
Did somebody say it grammy award winners did somebody say it with his band and fellow grammy award-winning vocalist ryan and guinans
Did he say red dead revolutionary?
a new standard
A new standard that's it
Your day is done
With a musical act
Nobody's made a food reference no peripherals no mobile game yet, which is really surprising
Yeah, what the fuck i'm i'm remembering from a couple hours ago
What the hell was that like let's get all the heads of all the companies on stage thing
That was really weird
It was like you got three villains on stage and they all supposed to appear together and like the good guys are all backstage
You know what I mean? Just like get out there and like make a presentation. It's like what the hell was that?
They like didn't belong on stage
Crew crew world i'm gone this big old world sure got me running around
I heard a voice
It told me settle down
With the moonlight as my guide and this feeling deep inside
I know now that i'm homeward bound
I feel so like weird sitting here
i'm just like
What's wrong?
I'm a guy in the audience. Yeah, but i'm drinking you get drink here
It's a great game
I've got to turn my back to the camera so i'm watching it
I fucking wall over here
I don't know what you're talking about
Oh
And he's got lice will you pay attention to the game awards, please it's only happens once a year
Now go win another five awards guys
Wow
Rihanna daniel. Thank you. That was absolutely beautiful
Uh, and we want to thank the band for that amazing performance
It's always a thrill for me to bring the music from games to life on our stage
And I think we did it better than we've ever done it before so, uh, thank you so much guys for doing that
Right now
Let's take a trip back
To hawkins indiana
We gotta do this
Let's engage
This is a tv show
Uh, it doesn't count as the actors because they're not pretending to be in a game with each other
You should go. It's almost here
Avoid, please welcome the creators of the netflix streaming phenomenon stranger things
madden ross duffer
Oh, I thought it was elijah wood
I thought we got elijah wood. Thank you guys. No, that's not elijah would be here
Uh, we were what six years old when we received this brand new system called nintendo for christmas
And we've been gaming ever since they both could be elijah. This has been a particularly all right
Is that close enough? Which is kind of unfortunate for netflix because playing your games is probably delayed or released by at least
So what a month at least for sure, but I mean red dead got a war astrobot. I mean, come on. It's incredible
Anyway, we're we're glad we could be here tonight
He's gonna show up new stranger things video game from netflix and bonus xp
He's gonna show off the events of season three with a few surprises of its own
And you can play co-op on xbox switch and pc
And we've also made a big graphical leap this year. We're up to 16 bits. So watch out rock star
All right, let's take a look 16 bits
What does that mean?
It's a stranger things super nintendo d make i've never seen this show
So I don't understand any of this
I've never even i've never i've never consumed one
Solitary second of this television show. I know that they play dungeons and dragons in the first 10 minutes
And the show is about dungeons and dragons
And like the dnd campaign like turns real, right?
They like it's like the that remember that old horror movie where the guy wrote on the typewriter
And everything he wrote on the typewriter became real
It's like a home horror movie. It's like that but their dnd campaign becomes real
Like I don't know whatever what? Oh, this is they're doing like a meta thing
Do I have that on here?
I'm not talking about murder sheep, bro
He's the creative director at nether realm studios and the co-creator of mortal combat and injustice
Oh, yeah, here's ed boone. There he is
What he got first ed
Thank you
It's great to be back here at the game awards
It's my honor tonight to present the award for best sports or racing game. Let's check out the nominees
best sports racing game
It's not elijah wood. Stop it. That's ed
I said ed wood, but that was an old shitty movie director
Why is this one so elaborate? Why?
What's with the electricity? This is like what? Yeah, the game indie game couldn't have gotten this
Oh, this is it's joke because this is mortal combat 12
Okay, that's pretty good. It's too bad. It wasn't madden
You a shit talker. We got
Trying to fix fight where you can fill it in your lung for that. I thought okay. I thought I was playing
Fnn on me in the mood sign block 19 in the blue flank. I was scrapped when I stood inside your booth
21 immortal we'll never stop lawyers
The last
Yeah
That sounded really unenthusiastic, but I actually think it's cool. It's hard. I'm
Holy shit mortal combat battle royale victory royale for raiders
Who is it here we go
God
Mortal combat 11 straight up april 23rd community reveal event january 17th
Okay, there's children in the audience
Sorry
Actually, sorry about that. I think they played the wrong video
um
Actually, here are the real nominees. Wait, that's wait. They're really doing one
They're actually doing this sports racing game
Games
How do you have a best sports racing game category when they all come out every year anyway
Really like fifa 19
Like nba 2k 19 this same game came out last year
Wait, this is another soccer game
with two soccer games on there
and the game award goes to
Forza horizon 4 I voted for mario tennis. No, I didn't
I got fifa best sports game of the year
Just like the last 30 years in a row. We've made one of these ad what a bit what a visionary in legend
So there has been so many people working on the force of franchise
It's a huge honor to accept this on their behalf using tilt control for surprise and four
Is now our best selling we already have that horizon game millions of people have played it
Uh both by buying the game and playing it in game pass
and uh
It's just been an incredible honor to watch the team is working really hard as you saw
We have a whole new update. No fortune island coming on december 13th, and we're just getting started. So, thank you
No, that guy wasn't drunk
That guy wasn't drunk. I want to tell you about a boy. Oh, is it me?
Please save your questions to the end rass builtin. Okay
He was like oh not two times at acrobat
But also a gifted psychic don't forget my canoeing badge
It was a big pain in the neck
Didn't they kick start this game for like 400 million dollars led him into the psycho knots
Uh, that was you pageant crow this ten-year-old circus runaway was somehow allowed to join an international group of psychic
Super spies and now he's headed to our main headquarters
right into
the mother lobe
Is this a remake or a sequence? You guys really like puns, but he better wise up
This is no summer camp. The mother lobe has its own way of doing things
Its own way of protecting itself from outsiders
Its fair share of dangerous hidden secrets if they ever got out
Things would never be the same again for the psycho knots
For your friends
For your family
For you listen rass butin there are folks that should never be opened
Not all minds are safe to censor that guy smoking. I can't some brains I better off
Broken don't worry. I won't do anything crazy
Was the original game any good?
Well, whatever you didn't just leave me out of it
Is that honey pepper ball bacon
I always thought psycho knots was like a brain training game
You know where you look at the stylus and you'd like you do like math problems every day
certainly not
Psychonauts to first announcer a couple years ago tim schafer thinking of you great to uh, we'll see you next year
I hope tim schafer. Oh, no, that's not tim schafer xbox
We saw you at the uh, the top of the show with your new buddies reggie and your longtime buddies reggie and phil
Yeah, no, really. Uh, you deserve credit for putting that moment together with reggie
Sean and I you pushed to make that happen. I think it's great to show them
Yeah, we all stood in a row for 30 seconds. Yeah, it was really ridiculous
I've never been in the same room before it's reggie in my life. It's been a big year for xbox
How you got allowed to be in same room city? Uh, how's 18 been going for you guys?
Yeah, we had a pretty good year. We can do better. We had a pretty good year
Okay added some studios shipped some good games sea of thieves shipped state of decay
Forts horizon was great to see forts horizon 4 win an award
Ship the adaptive controller this last year something i'm very proud of. Yep
No, it's it's been a good year and news coming about xbox
We saw the guys from studio wildcard up here atlas coming next year to game preview, right?
Yeah, I mean we have a long relationship with studio wildcard. They were one of our earlier game preview
Teams game preview really helps developers always trying to build programs to help developers our id at xbox program game pass
I mean all these things just to help developers reach as many gamers as possible
Well, uh speaking of game pass, uh, let's talk about that
Tell us about uh game pass seems like everything is coming to game pass now, right? Yeah, we had
Mutant years ago to play that game this week launched launched any game pass. We have action launching
You're not gonna get that one. It's very obvious. It's incredible. Yeah people gonna go play that
Next week next week kingdom's two crowns next week all of those in game pass all part of winter of arcade
We mentioned we're bringing winter of arcade back
It's great to have all those games coming and launching both for sale and any game pass get as many players as we can
I love you guys supporting the smaller studios same thing with me here at the awards
You want the big games and the small games and that's what makes this industry so vibrant
Dead cells up dead cells such a good game. I know congratulations those guys win their award
2019 obviously lots of big stuff coming from you guys. Uh, what can you tell us about 2019?
Yeah, we got crackdown three. We're gonna be launching that. Uh, we've got gears five
Which would just be incredible
One of my favorite franchises come out this generation for anything else bill see the next ori come out
You know, it's uh gonna be back here camera is drunk, but it'll be incredible right here in this theater
I mean, it's gonna be uh 29 this year was an awesome year for gamers and I look at next year
I think those things are so slippery. Have you ever held a mic before in your life?
It's like and also we can't fucking hold on to them. They're like covered in oil
Performance of devil trigger you announced that here in this theater at e3, right?
We did I mean the support we've had from captain's awesome and just seeing the game and people don't know devil may cry
It's gonna be launching their beta tomorrow on xbox so people can go out and play a demo of devil may cry
Yeah, demo of devil may cry on xbox tomorrow
So people can go give that a try and just see that crazy engine with that game. It's gonna be great
All right, and that's coming first xbox, right the demo first on xbox. That's all right
We'll check it out devil may cry 5 phil great to have you here at the game
Hope to have you here every year along with everybody and right now. Let's take a look at some brand new stuff from devil may cry
No, nobody's cried
You guys have seen this trailer already haven't you?
You need to stay to the board
You've never seen this
When evil works we must destroy
All right time to kick some ass
Yes
Why don't you tell me everything about this job a powerful demon is about to resurrect and we need your help dante
Stay to the board
What do you say?
Unless something else happens here games play best on xbox one. All right, we need we need uh miyamoto appearance
We need somebody to fall down. We need a winner to get played off
But we need party
It's not easy, you know, what is neck? What are you going to leave tomorrow? Are you not going to leave tomorrow?
I missed cell phone one day. I asked my mom
To buy for me a computer. She saved that money for almost three years
It was like that moment. I just turned everything like
For at least 10 seconds 73 percent of the population in south sudan
Is under the age of 30 they are born in war they were raised up in war
So their mindset and attitude is all about war
I decided to teach myself programming so that I can make game for peace
I made a game called salam salam is an arabic word and mean peace
So what you do as a player you have to stop the bomb from destroying the communities
And you know people start playing the game and a refugee come and bringing the people together
And I have the passion and the capability to change the world and make a difference
Coming up worlds will change in fortnight
And we present the award for best game direction. We're getting close and later directing duo the russo brothers
Assemble on stage and more music from the game. Well, the russo brothers. That's the it's the matrix guys awards
We'll be right back
right
To make the matrix is that like the matrix version of
I'm, so sorry. That was loud. Hey, we played that last night. It was a game
I will give them this though
Because this used to be on tv, right? The game always was on spike tv, right?
They have they've snuck in a lot of ads here
Oh, I thought that was for a movie
Loud to louder not actual gameplay
Oh, it's a playstation. Oh this thing sucks, right?
I've heard nothing but negative responses
And a member of the game awards orchestra tonight, can't you just press escape for the keyboard plugged in it gets like the debug menu
as demonstrated tonight
Games require hundreds of elements from music
And art to acting writing programming and design
Great direction is evident when the work of hundreds somehow combines into a unified creative vision
Here are the nominees for best game direction
It's gonna be miyamoto with mario odyssey and he's gonna show up live via satellite
I'm just trying to come here that is long and unforgiving
place for a boy
Spider-man, I don't know
Look next time spider-man was really good
What was it? I didn't play god of war. I didn't play god of war yet. We don't want to kill any of you
and the game award goes to
god of war
God of war, all right. All right. I'm ready. Uh, I
I'm ready. I'm not gonna cry tonight
All right
Um, first I want to thank sony for the support and faith you foolishly placed in me and our great team over at santa monica
To my amazing wife
Uh foolishly placed it that what a fucking fantastic video game director what are you talking about inspirations
throughout all of this, uh
To the unbelievable team that I have been blessed with that santa monica every human being who put so much of themselves
Please wrap it up
Uh into this game
I am forever thankful for all of you and all the work for the cast that we were blessed with you guys
Are amazing you brought it every single day and elevated
The work that we wrote on the page beyond what we could have ever imagined is so thank you
To david jaffee who created all this I wouldn't even be here if he hadn't done that
2018 has been an absolutely bananas year for games
We are all lucky that every creator out there every creator in this audience every creator out there in the world
Is absolutely crushing it motivating me and everybody else to work even harder, but it wouldn't even be worth it or even
He said we wouldn't be driven without all the fans out there without all the people who love games all games
All throughout the industry. We have an amazing community and there is so much more that unites us than divides us
So, thank you everybody. It's a great. That's a great game
Christmas time. Hey, merry christmas
Is this a christmas game or a thing is this dreams is this is this dreams
Oh, it's fucking fortnite. I thought it was gonna be dreams
They love the christmas update fortnite
Season seven and I was gonna put it on there and I didn't
fortnite season seven launched this morning. He's had a busy day, but here he is on the game ward stage yet again donald mustard donald
Welcome to the show and congratulations on such an insane year. Oh, thank you. It's been a insane and crazy year and uh, we're just
Humble and grateful for all the players everywhere for playing fortnite and for helping us build the game with them
Well you guys I know it's an ongoing game as you guys are a nominee tonight
So season seven, uh started this morning wiki i forgot to mention season seven
So season seven nobody gives a shit about this on this channel. I can guarantee it
uh
if
If we get bingo i'm going to gift community sub
a hundred subs
Right. Yes, uh fortnite creative
Is launching on december 13th. So next week
Uh fortnite creative is a mode a brand new mode where everyone will be given their own private island
Where you can design your own games and build
Whatever you want. You're gonna give myself i'm just gonna delete money for us
We are all passionate
Game designers and we think everyone is a game designer and our goal
Is to let you build your own holy shit. He's given money to himself now
Except he's just deleting some of it. It's early early
Um early access is actually available right now
So if you want to get into it right this second go pick up a battle pass and you can how do you give it?
Completely so it's early access week. Okay
But I hear there's there's maybe something a little more there is so I don't know how in the few hours that it's been out
We've seen just already millions of people building crazy crazy stuff and we suspected that might happen
Yes, and the map is kind of crowded and on the island and we figured we needed to clear out a little space
Where is it? Uh to make room for some stuff. So let's let's watch this head over to the game now
See what's happening in the fortnite world. That's right. Check this out
Should I just like should I turn this off?
I can't just turn it off
Here just watch this awesome fortnite season 7, uh gameplay
Hey, maybe they'll do like a big purple cube again that elected you
All right, I can't I can't talk shit about fortnite because like the game right donald fuck you just half of earth
Loves this game. I would just be solidifying my own new space where we will be featuring
The best and the coolest content created by you
And we will be bringing it into the battle royale map right on the island everyone place it there for everyone to see
Okay, how you gonna pick?
We're gonna all pick it together
Okay
And so there's gonna be new stuff coming there all the time
And we think this is gonna be an incredible way for us to all continue to build this game together
All right. So the block if I if I load a fortnite right now i'd see the block
Yeah, the risky risky reels is gone. Goodbye risky reels block is there but you know, don't I i'm a big movie fan
We will find a way to get movies back in there. Well, we'll work on it. All right
Well the block creative mode, uh, thanks so much for stopping by the game awards
Uh, we can't wait to see where you take fortnite in the future
All right, so we've got much more game awards ahead right now
We've got a brand new look at rage 2. Check out this. Oh rage 2. All right. I'm on rage 2 looked uh, kind of interesting
Bingo I just did it now. Oh shit
Oh bingo bingo
I completed I thought I could like
I thought I could like schedule a time or something or like give them out
It just gives them out. It just does it immediately
I thought you had to like buy them and then you could
I've never done that before
500-dollar joke up next the russo brothers present best ongoing game
And then the game awards orchestra celebrates the nominees for game of the year who will win
Will it be red dead redemption? I'm not gonna get fucking bingo guys. No one's gonna fight on stage
It's all coming up
All right. All right. Let me be completely honest here
um
I it's it was the you check out and it's like complete the purchase of the subs
I did I
Whatever vape guys civics agree that final fantasy 14 online rises above expectations
Imaginations
A world that grows beyond imagination
With awe-inspiring lands to see I can't skip this shit
No, I call this shit. That's not I shouldn't say revisit
Hey, well, congratulations to those. I got the community subs. I just deleted money
Because I just paid myself money
And like twitch takes a cut of like, you know, so I just I just took money
Gave you guys subs and then just gave it to myself your way
fantasy 14 on play for free now
money laundering money laundering, uh
Implies that you make it money from the transaction
under the smash brothers
That launches in like 40 minutes
Less than an hour
Thanks for the sub
Who's gonna win game of the year?
That's what I want to know the gun. I don't know how close we are
It's it's gonna be red dead. I would assume right?
No one has said the word revolutionary
Stay alive and be the one pubg mobile play free now
There's a lot of ads in pubg mobile
There can only be one winner that's kind of mobile when you're facing over a million people every day
If you think you have what it takes download the game right now. It's free. The only thing you have to lose is bragging rights
Uh the game where you fought bots and lost game where I fought bots in one
But they weren't bots. I was already level like 15
So the bots were they delete bots from the game after you get to like level 10 on on the internet there
So i'm sorry, but what you're saying is inaccurate
Play free now, they're really pushing pubg, huh?
Please welcome the directing ad number 12 infinity war
joe and anthony russo
My brother and I are thrilled to be here tonight to hand out the award
For the best ongoing game somebody was sleeping
This award is for those games that continue to get better and better after their how do I rewind?
With new adventures and experiences for their fans. I didn't say to be sleeping
Originally there were 10 nominees in this category, but then
They asked us to present the award and now
That's a huge spoiler. I didn't make
Sorry, okay. He just did that I didn't
Everybody it's gonna be fortnight
It's not destiny too. It's gonna be fortnight watch. Yeah
so
Check out the middle here. That's fine
that counts
Why the fuck is this on here?
Did they have to fill out slots or something? I understand. Why is no man's sky over here?
The rest of these make sense
best ongoing game
and the game award goes to
Why wouldn't you put like warframe there instead of fortnight no man's sky
Also wins for best multiplayer game
Best multiplayer game fortnight best
ongoing game fortnight
The russo brothers
Like we we love you so much all of us, right? Thank you so much
For everything you guys have done for for us
um
I represent just
the teeniest portion of
The team that just works so hard
Every day to make the game that is fortnight
uh
There's just so many people pouring
Their souls their talent their time
Into trying every day to bring why I guess doing mustard playing that game
uh
Joy and delight. What's what's the mustard for? That's all that's our mission
How can we just bring joy and delight
to people and
And we're just so grateful. We're so grateful for all the people who have uh
That guy's not sleeping with us who've played fortnight who continue to play it every day and with us help make the game better
uh, we're this is a
extremely humbling
Year for us at epic
as we
Really learned and tried to just uh
Do something that felt why are you guys doing mustard wonderful to us and we're just let the guy give his speech about
There's so many of you that uh that agree with us and that are playing the game with us
So I imagine that
Almost everyone here the reason why you it's his name history
or why you make games or love games is because
It feels like a new medium and it really is games aren't that old
For tonight mustard, I think that's what's so exciting for me every day
Is that feeling that donald mustard? There's something over the horizon. That's this guy, right?
And it feels like we're there again that we're on the cusp as an industry
of of new
amazing experiences
And i'm just so grateful for all of you. We're all kind of one big team
All of us in this industry really pushing this medium
And i'm so grateful for it. Thank you guys so much
Fist bump go for a fist bump
There are still lots of amazing moments coming up in the show
We've got more performances and of course the game of the year announcement. Uh, oh, whoa. What's going on technical difficulties?
Uh-oh, we've got a secret announcement to make through our snow tv
This is joker is this gonna be uh actors in the game?
Wait, seriously, he went alone to the game awards
But it's so far away. Why is he there?
There's only one thing the phantom thieves apart specialize in
He's there to steal a treasure
Have you already sent a calling card?
We're not the ones sending a card this time. In fact, we've been invited
Invited to steal the greatest treasure of all
Is this a smash brothers persona?
character
We'll be going up against the best of the best
Can't wait to see our fearless leader show his stuff
Is this smash brothers dlc character announcement? It's one of these it's one of these it's
Show the strength of thy will and rage against all challengers
What oh reggie reggie reg
Reggie
We meet again
Quite the surprising
So, uh, all right, so super smash brothers coming out tonight, but it looks like uh, I know great choice of shirt here reggie
Uh the internet, uh is going crazy
Uh, the announcement of uh joker persona five coming to smash brothers. Everyone's in this game. Everyone's in this game, right?
So we've said that
Super smash brothers ultimate it is the biggest crossover in video game history. Dare. I say joker
from persona five is the first DLC character and so and so yes you know the
the the game's about to launch we're super excited that's pretty cool though
I get the fans the opportunity to summon a persona into the game amazing
all right so the DLC fighters that will come out so this gives you a flavor of
how we're approaching the DLC so the DLC there's going to be five characters
each character will come with a stage it'll come with a collection of music
these are going to be characters that are new to the series just like Joker
from persona five characters that you would not anticipate to be in Super
Smash Brothers Ultimate we're super excited about this the fans can go and
they could get the fighters pass to get all of the five fighters that will be
coming to the series we're tremendously excited well I would think
you'd be even more excited because tonight is about to launch and you know
you need to have a really good show for me sure everything's going great for
the launch so yeah we're super excited smash is just minutes away yes and
it's gonna be fantastic all right well Reggie you've been here every
year for us for the Game Awards we really appreciate it and before we go
maybe we should head to the stage for the Game Awards Orchestra a little
something for Super Smash Brothers Reggie great to see you enjoy that
but if you're pretty if you're persona fan that's fucking
they haven't fought on that stage the band is drunk where we at we need no
Miyamoto no Jeff can't get the mic back from
presenter is it cutting edge everybody's sleeping in the audience who
drops the mic no banjo-kazooie game
was a heck of a sleeping has happened when somebody somebody asked what does
the music mean the music is when somebody is on the stage too long
accepting an award they get played off by the music you know what I mean
and they like if they keep talking and they get played off big score we
got enough money to leave what do you say nothing means more to me than
DLC for red dead no PC PC announcement would be fucking huge PC right PC and
not coming out like in a year and a half that'd be a big deal
redemption to an announcement it was just an ad we're all getting we're all
getting so hyped up for a fucking ad nine out of ten amazing or the
Nintendo nine and ten for Nintendo switch presents Diablo 3 for a second
that's it's like 33% on Metacritic I was like oh fuck really that's
terrible how would you advertise that building a sound like a 33% it's a shitty
game evolved personality so we kind of started from scratch for this one and
really thought about what is Lara's mindset and how we can bring that
forward with the sound yeah Diablo 3 has been re-released as much as
Skyrim this point when I heard the first time the jungle in Dolby Atmos I
was that's that's incredible we're all conditioned to look at it so to the
image and honestly though believe that it's it's more than a 2d image what's
the most likely to happen here goes this way but what this bumps in this
huge soundscape it makes it feel revolutionary and it's taking a piss I
mean but that leads us to Miyamoto it has not made an appearance story
Elijah Wood hasn't showed up and that's what you know it's not a
really brings to the media where you're feeling this is the moneymaker right
here guys from like here this is the only way it's possible just like I
forgot I was on webcam sleeping habit there's been a ton of hecklers no but
for a real heckle the person presenting has to respond and be like
yeah right all right all right we already saw this though so is dead by
daily trying to do a thing with a they're trying to get people to dot by
and download this new character so then they can move on from games and make a
movie about that character in like a couple of years or is that an actual
horror movie character all right it's finally that time here to present our
final award as a member of the team that won game of the year in 2016
revolutionary get the music and somebody yell I'm going game from
overwatch here's the vice president of Blizzard entertainment Jeff Kaplan
revolutionary two years ago we were honored to be up here to accept the
game of the year for overwatch it was so awesome and it meant so much to our
team it's so special right now to be able to share that with another studio
red dead here to celebrate all of the nominees for game of the year and
game awards orchestra what oh okay I thought they were presenting oh they're
gonna do a piece from every every game the orchestra has been it's been
they've been on screen more than bill spencer has
came out like God of War there's a God of War has a very large chance to my
understanding it's a very very fun game
Arthur's gonna bring it and then we're gonna get 10 people on screen we're
gonna get a pop figure in the shot someone's gonna say cutting edge we're
gonna get bingo on this last department they're gonna bring up a pop pick you're
up Arthur for something right this sounds like it's pre-record I don't
think it is I don't know how you went fucking Return of the King like I
said but there's also spider-man there was some really good games this
year actually sitting here thinking about
there are at least two or three that yeah I would absolutely say like at
least four
we didn't get any booze from the audience no soda or candy sponsorships no
new banjo-kazooie game all right let's see it game of the year all right
who gets the gaudy here it goes god damn it Arthur and the game award for
game of the year goes to red
fucked it fuck the ceremony fuck this award ceremony thing I've ever been
a part of in my whole life I think it's seriously
oh boy right boy one two three four five six seven eight nine that's like
15 people and they're all drunk at least one of them is drunk where is it where
is it where is it somebody fist bump somebody did a fist bump over there
thank you and thanks so much the team back in Santa Monica it's just an
amazing amazing group of talent that really pulled together to realize
this beautiful vision that Cory Cory brought to the franchise reboot God of
War and I'm so grateful that Cory returned back to the studio and joined
our family once again and somebody trip you are an amazing visionary love
your partnership Yumi Yang it's really hard to see the behind-the-scenes work
that goes into producing a game what he got up there he fucking fell down
and the triumph that it is all right pull up a God of War pop figure
fast ability come on to thread that very tricky production needle in the balance with
Cory's and the team's creative vision we would not be where we are on this
stage today so thank you to you me and the entire production team come on
somebody hold the pop figure and you guys the fans around the world together
we all dream big dreams and that's an amazing feeling every day when we
walk into the studio to create something like God of War I want to thank my
children for being the very best and all of the families throughout the God
of War team for the support that we were given over the course of many many
months many hours many years this is no a guy sleeps a tremendous support to
Santa Monica studio Shuhei Yoshida and Shawn Layden really stood behind us
for a studio reboot somebody pull up a visioning of this franchise which
takes a lot of goods at that level easy and the entire PlayStation family
who stood behind us as in that partnership over many years to really
realize what this franchise was capable of thank you everyone Cory just pulled
it out of your pocket and just go like this guy right here I'll be quick
because they're flashing to please wrap it up but I just want to say
every single game that was nominated up here is an hour masterpiece so
please give it up for all of them say it revolutionary and please give
it up for every say it revolutionary creators of games creators of movies
creators of comic say it creators of every single thing that enriches our
lives that makes us believe magic it's real no revolutionary it's
revolutionary shit that's the music playing them off something he's gonna
have yeah it's your last opportunity you gotta say the God of War team
for winning game of the year let's check the twitch leaderboard and see
who was the most successful predicting all the winners tonight amazing well
it's been a great year for games as everyone has said thank you so much
for watching the game awards we'll see you next year for the game awards 2019
no no no no no you need to say revolutionary
no you didn't say revolutionary
has given up 20 community subs I gave a hundred earlier 20 here thank you so
much RVM 20 fucking subs thank you they said it in the beginning with
Reggie are you sure you're gonna link are you sure wait I gotta rewind hold on
I get it we gotta watch that hold on give me a second we need to see if they
said it holy shit so be winner given up five
community subs just fight claim claim claim claim claim claim what are you
guys claiming what are you doing claim what is claim uh Bebram given up 10
community subs thank you so much oh it's a meme oh well okay thank you Bebram
for 10 community subs let me I let me see if we got bingo because I'm gonna
want well when they were on stage we'll see I need to get into here
where is it there all right we need to go open up the video lightning ride
of five community subs get rough whatever the dot all right I need to
for those of you that didn't know here's like the what we were doing there just
people were saying I can't see behind the the dot so we need to find out if
we actually had bingo though let me get that going real quick I even can I
can't like interact with this anymore my like feed died okay hold on let's
go over here so you guys saying that they said revolutionary or
revolutionized I would take that if you were on jeopardy that counts too
didn't remember where that was videos okay hold on it was like in the
beginning right here we go okay all right here they are here they are
players please join me in welcoming from Nintendo Reggie Fils-Aime from
PlayStation Shawn Layden and from Xbox Phil Spencer okay here we go
tonight at the Game Awards we come together as a community to celebrate
video games in the world as an industry we are most powerful when we come
together united by our common love for the art form of games right but where
do you say that when do you say it we join with the viewers and gamers
around the globe to celebrate creativity innovation just saying every
word besides revolutionary together we will continue to invite new voices
creators and players into our worlds because when everybody plays we all
win because when we see the strength of a united gaming community we
remember that we've never seen the challenge that you can't defeat they
didn't say I knew they didn't say it we're united in our commitment to
leading and leading united with new games new experiences and new ways for
everyone to play good luck to all the nominees and congratulations to all the
winners and enjoy the Game Awards Jeff take it away thank you so much
Liars we didn't get bingo sorry even if let's let's fill in even the ones that
that may not have even happened right so we didn't get cutting-edge no pop
figurine give me a break that was so easy to take the hundred subs back
audience booze nobody no they did we didn't get like a real good boo group
presentation that that barely happened oh you guys are booing now you got to
use the free red dead one on the left but where does it okay but what that
was like up here I can't just put it over disgruntled nominee tweets within
ten minutes of their loss well we got bingo then quick search Twitter he
doesn't know Jonah Hill does not count as Elijah we got five four
different bingos mobile game but we didn't get a new Call of Duty
announcement or Diablo 4 teaser oh my fucking god rvm is another 20 community
subs from rvm dude you're like matching nearly euro you what 40 holy shit dude
thank you so much I mean I was just I just gave money to myself but you
gave money to me so thank you so fucking much dude Jesus Christ very
generous of you for real I'm looking right in the eye too look at you
right in the fucking eye well it wasn't by accident like I bought it I was
going to do it I was gonna do it regardless even if we didn't get bingo
I was gonna do it I was gonna be like who cares like boom right but I didn't
know that like completing like actually purchasing them is like then they go
out I thought like I had maybe if I could give them out so and like
what the fuck guy buys a hundred subs and like accidentally what the
just cancel your credit card no I'm glad get off of me fucking red dead
didn't win I'm glad whatever it's good needs Vaseline 10 community subs
thank you thank you so much for your 10 community subs and that that's it
that's it man that's the end of the game awards big night for a holy fuck
that's 10 more from pin man I need to play God of War I think that's
that's I gotta play God of War now I have to just play it I'll probably
stream it oh my fucking God what is happening in this chat room that's 10
subs from Kyra Toby 10 from pin man 10 from Kyra Toby holy shit you guys
fucking awesome play fortnight no but that's good that's gonna be my time
that's all I really wanted to do tonight I will see you guys but first
of all holy shit there's so many fucking subs on this list are you
kidding me this is an insane amount of subscriptions my god well let's go
back in time here Jesus Christ that's a lot of fucking subs
commander pepper with five community subs I didn't have notifications on
tonight but I do want to at least touch on a few that came in
there was 50 dollars that came in let me go back here
thanks for the sub hey thanks for being here man I did see 50 bucks came
in I want to make sure I figure this out
because I kind of lost it somehow I only read 50 dollar bit messages
that's not true I want to make sure I can at least go back far enough
there we go okay don't read this well I just did
is there any reason why this is only pulling from like 40 minutes ago
don't ask me why but uh yeah I'm gonna end the stream here
let's be right back let's get the outro on just so you know
I'll see you guys again on Saturday probably for Dreamcast
I'm looking to try to get some of that going should be a lot of fun
thank you for watching the game awards it was pretty interesting
too bad we didn't get a bingo kind of annoying
but have a great rest of your night and I'll see you guys on Saturday
so you're gonna see Smash Brothers or Dreamcast on Saturday and Sunday
depends on how much I want to play it and unlock stuff and do things you
know but for the purposes of um
I don't know why Streamlabs does this for some reason
if there's too many notifications it just deletes all them that were at the
bottom why I don't understand isn't the whole
purpose of this thing to keep track of bits and subs
I don't understand but if you've taken off have a good rest of your night
uh what's what's the German mustard site that very useful website
all right so this is from yeah that's a good time frame
so we had there we go excellent okay so thank you too
we're gonna go back to front here thank you extra cheesy for the one dollar
haha first bits I win it's not a contest man
bake me home thanks for two dollars here I heard somebody equally as
compact as you is hosting the oscars this year
I don't know who's hosting the oscars but I don't know what that
means but thanks uh divas thank you divas
three dollars no message just three bucks pretty much
every single damn stream man thank you uh mr cloud mr cloud thanks for the
ten dollars no message thank you for ten bucks mr cloud
a dollar from I am monk you're my game of the year hey
thanks thank you really appreciate that extra cheesy again thanks for one
dollar dude I can't believe they're announcing no man's sky this year is
going to be epic no man's sky really that just felt
really out of place I can't I can't give a reason why
that was there it's weird but thank you mostly lost for the
one dollar there were two bald guys on stage in the
orchestra we got them they've done a lot to make that game
better but is it better than warframe you know what I mean a lot a lot but
not enough I see but thank you uh mostly lost
for the one dollar thank you wild fox for the one dollar hey germ it's
3 a.m. while I'm writing this and I decided to stay and watch because I
had way too much caffeine today I've touched on this subject before but
I found that keeping myself busy with something
whether it be games or crafting helps a lot to keep my mental health
up what are some of the things you do to deal with bad times
um mostly I would say is kind of just when you're lying down in
bed anytime I lie down in bed decompressing
I think your thoughts whether in the shower or
honest to god I'm gonna be real with you here and when you're taking a
shit is just like I get a lot of
I improve my mental health by taking a shit
taking a shower a line in bed and compressing thoughts
that might be you might mean you might give me some disgusted faces
here but a lot of a lot of my growth has
come from when I was sitting on the toilet
all at the same time weird flex but okay but yeah that's
really when you can I don't know alone time for me
especially when you kind of just you and only you you can really do a lot of
good for yourself shower and on the toilet for real but
uh thank you wild fox I'm sorry that you stayed up this late
but thank you uh Paza Jan thanks for the one dollar I genuinely clicked off
my porn to watch your stream uh thanks all right I guess I guess
that's a welcome thank you okay uh ass burns
assa burns thanks for the two dollars here or three dollars actually thank you
assa burns flug boy thanks for the one dollar destiny was made by bungee
fuck extra cheesy thanks for the two bucks maybe if you dye your hair
green you'll become number one like ninja if I dye my hair green it's
all fallen out you understand guys uh look sir
luxuriant hat thanks for the 20 dollars they say cutting edge are you at the game
awards and did you present because then we get to put the blue
circle over the marker there thank you for the 20 dollars
20 bucks hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar fallout new vegas just
got a massive story oval hall mod called fallout new california is
basically a brand new game with a brand new story
and the quality is breathtaking and it'd be awesome if you took a look at
it and gave the creators a well-deserved plug
new california interesting i've never heard of it till now but
modders are a dedicated bunch takes a lot of time and a lot of
effort to put something like that together so applaud
applause to that nice try todd uh thank you
ooweegee for the 10 dollars here ring your mom and thank her right now
i'm not on the stage doing awards but thank you hey golden cricket
thanks for this the 50 dollars here from golden cricket
50 bucks i'm glad you made a decision to cast this germa i sincerely hope you
make this on on this stage or another one of these
days i don't know what the hell i would
even do man i'm i'm i'm gonna i'm not gonna get invited to the game
awards i don't think that'll ever happen
come out dressed as a clown they wouldn't ever invite me back
i already was there i was the muppet best joke
they don't they don't tend to invite small streamers
see that's a dub that's a double joke right there i'll give that to you
but thank you for the 50 dollars golden cricket it's a lot of money
thank you thank you the swiss giant for the 15
dollars no message just kappa's thank you
timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar when you play world of light go
left that's a spoiler i don't i don't want to read a spoiler
captain jake 1998 thanks for the one dollar hey it's my favorite compact
streamer how does it dangle dangles well it's going well thank
you dubsky dude for the one dollar i feel like such a boomer because i i
think you were literally the only redeeming thing out of this whole
thing that furry on stage was what just having a good time
you know what i mean just just trying to have a good time
just trying to relax a little you know what i mean like it's up don't
worry about it thank you dubsky dude uh acid
burns again thanks for one dollar no message just four or five dollars
here in a row uh flying muffin bunnies thanks for the
one dollar they say the dot the dot with a pug there's garfield the
monday killer for the one dollar thanks garfield
uh breaking news read all about it spider-man got snubbed for best game
award they just couldn't handle all those
merry and mild stealth missions i suppose that's a real shame
spotty has been getting a real raw deal this year
especially sad since andrew garfield played spider-man so gar feels a
connection to spider-verse even if oh my fucking god that's
true that like that is so painfully true
andrew garfield played spider-man so i feel a connection to him
also where's earthworm jim and smash i know i know
thank you garfield thank you blue comet for the one dollar
uh thank you tetra reggaeton for the 12 dollars and 22 cents they say
do not do something under any circumstances here that i'm not going
to do it and then deado deado at the end gave
ten dollars play fortnight or lose best streamer i already lost
okay i didn't win guys come on wasn't even close
uh a few more at the end carrot thanks for the one dollar carrot hey
germa i'm turning 18 in about a minute
so i thought i'd celebrate by helping you pay back those 100 community subs
these past four months of being subscribed you've been a blast crazy
think i've been watching since the tf2 days
thank you carrot happy birthday and no i was just i was planning on doing it
anyways it was i was like oh if we get bingo
i like i actually was talking about that last night
to uh italics i was like oh i'm gonna get like 100 community subs if we get
bingo and then i forgot about it until like
two and a half hours into the stream and then i bought them
and then i i i was under the assumption that i could but you know
you saw what happened i just completed the purchase
and 100 community subs went through that's what happened i've never done it
before do a hundred more somebody was like
even if you fucked it up it doesn't mean it's not illegal
i don't think it's illegal i just gave twitch
money and 100 people can now use emotes
in the channel pyramid scheme i'm pyramid scheming myself
but thank you to uh 420 squid for the five dollars
clueless sniper for one dollar zazz is all for the one dollar remember back
when you were a top 1000 streamer never expected you'd make it all the
way to number one can't wait to read about you getting
arrested in five years after waiting wasting all your money on slots and
cocaine thanks kairatobi for the one dollar
hey germa the uh tough wrench asks if you're going to
play medical but i'm going to play metal gear solid five
i don't think i'm going to play metal gear solid five on stream i did it a
long time ago i already played it i already got
enjoyment out of it i'm not sure i would scream it
but thank you though and thank you to sticks renegade for the one dollar
knowing you have uh colitis and ibd ever have an abscess i just
had my second one i almost forgot how painful it was
hopefully i can reach him remission again soon at least the pain is gone
um i've don't know i've never had an abscess before
i've had something called a fissure before which sucks
but not that thankfully i've been pretty much okay
recently like completely but i really uh i'm really sorry to hear that
two that's not good that sucks hopefully you do get into remission soon
fissures suck also oh yeah they do it's not good
but thank you sticks hopefully you uh get better real soon
uh extra cheesy for the one dollar thank you they say johnny bravo will
be the next character in smash i'm from the future uh modus ponus
thanks for the one dollar and then raving happy thanks for two bucks
no messages on those last two thank you everybody for watching
i'll see you on saturday we'll do something fun
oops what a fucking mess let's roll the credits it's gonna be so many subs
there's gonna be a lot just fair warning here
here they come oh my god
yeah sleep tight guys i'll see you on saturday thanks for sticking around
read them i can't read these no i will never be able to read these
oh tonight was rigged i don't think so i think auto war probably deserves it
i was just kidding around fucking around when uh
i was doing the whole um fallout 76 can't win 2018 game of the year yeah
because no yeah you're right it can't i
wanted to be mad thought fortnight was gonna win i
really am just stupid and i just put fortnight in a giant circle in the
middle it didn't even help either conor got
robbed it would have been nice to see conor win
but there was some really good competition up there
there was some very very good competition why was conor not in the
rumble uh i actually was gonna make him and
hank as a tag team but i ran out of time do it
yeah i just i ran out of time there wasn't enough
and i've crunched it to the very last minute on that uh stream so
you didn't make conor but you put in the quiet man yeah but the quiet man was
so relevant at that particular second you know
he was very very relevant so again i'll see you guys on saturday
we will hopefully be doing i don't know i really don't know it really it
really depends on how much fun smash really is
if smash is all right whatever it's i'm just playing it spongebob movie
2004 ashen's is up but is that did that just come out today
how have i not heard about that yet i was looking forward to that game but how
long has that been out for interesting okay well get to check
that out too but yeah that's it guys have a great
rest of your night thank you for watching the game
awards with me see you soon take care guys