Hey, what's happening guys? It's Jerma again. I got a one life gameplay for you.
This is the series I'm continuing from before where I show you one life from one class and with a particular loadout that I choose.
This is a soldier gameplay with one life. I kill 22 people in one life.
It's an absolute massacre of a gameplay and you'll see right off the back at Kritzkrieg and I just destroyed two or three people.
I know that you can't kill sentries with the Kritzkrieg.
I know there's no bonus to the Kritzkrieg if you are killing a sentry.
I know that so don't worry. This pyro goes down and I'll tell you the loadout for the match.
The loadout is the Liberty Launcher, the whip, and the buff banner. As you can see here
I have the buff banner ready to go, but we are just really really crushing them right now.
So I don't really see a need for it, but right here there's a lot of people coming up.
So I switch it out, blow the horn, and here we go. Time for some complete domination.
I love the sound it makes when other people get Kritz. It's awesome.
So all these people, my screen starts lagging because I just couldn't handle it. Kill one person here, get this demo man.
Sorry, I think I get the pyro. I get the pyro. Sorry. Now we're spawn camping now and this is bad news.
Get that engineer with a nice shot. This is bad news. In the middle here
I kind of tell people I say, you know what, let them come out of the spawn,
but we have our fun for a good five or six minutes. So Smart Soldier comes out with the battalion's backup.
He blows it. They make a great push, but it's just not enough.
I actually have like two pocket medics in this particular gameplay. Not right now,
but this guy right here, he's a good, this guy, Swift,
he's my pocket medic for a while here. Kill a couple more people and then he pops the uber and
there's nothing I can really do here. I kill this heavy.
There's no one really around. Get the heavy with one shot. He tries to run away and I get him. This pyro,
I believe he gets killed by the heavy right next to me, and then I get Kritzkrieg'd.
I was like, oh no, because I blew the horn and I would have definitely waited,
but I killed two or three people with this too, this Kritzkrieg. So I get ubered and Kritzkrieg'd.
So everybody else on the server, I'm sorry that you didn't get to use these two medics to your advantage.
Heavy medic appear on the way out. I'm not gonna get myself killed. Me and Larry, the combat spy,
just hanging out back here behind this rock, taking a little detour,
charging the buff banner on all those people that come out, and then there's a spy that turns around the corner.
There he is. Definitely a dead ringer, but it's not a problem at all because he charged my buff banner.
Blow the horn and guys, watch this, like eight people die because of me and a pyro.
Check this out. Look at him. There he is on the left. Just like absolutely smoking people because of the Kritz.
Unbelievable. We kill like eight people collectively together, and I guess I also had the uber from the quick fix on me,
which I was not aware of until watching this gameplay.
I guess I was just so in the moment right there that I just wasn't even paying attention to that,
but that was definitely a reason why we pushed so well right there.
Uber heavy on the cart, but it doesn't matter. My team is very, very good right now.
We're very confident in what we have for our position.
So we make our way back up here, and they're in their spawn again.
They haven't been able to come past this rocky area right here for the entire match.
So it's really not a good thing to spawn camp and to keep people here,
which is why you'll see eventually I make people go back. I say, guys, guys, guys, don't do this anymore. This is stupid.
I'd rather have a challenge. I'd rather have them be able to get out because when you're getting spawn camped,
it's very, very difficult to even get out of the spawn, and it's just not fair.
Let's get a crit screak here now. Bang, get this one guy, and then I get Ubered again from the quick fix.
You'll see I was just pocketed the whole time by like two or three different people, like I said before.
So I apologize again, blow the horn for the banner, and we're at their spawn again.
That's all there is to it. We're just at their spawn again, and they can't even get out, and this is just bad news.
Look at this. Just shooting randomly into the spawn getting kills. Lucky crit on that heavy,
and then he just dies by, I think he got headshot actually. This is the point right now where I'm saying over the mic,
everybody back up, everyone get to the point. Let's forget this. Don't spawn camp, and everyone listens to me.
We all come back here. See how we're all just running this way. We're all in this little cubby area.
You'll see it's kind of funny. Look at like everybody just sitting there.
We wanted to give them at least 10 to 15 seconds to get out of the spawn. There they are.
They're all out now, and it really just didn't matter at all. I get Ubered again,
and we come back, and look at where we end up after this push that they have. We end up right back in their spawn.
Lucky crit on that heavy goes down, and this soldier watch is funny. He just turns around. He's like, you know what? Screw this.
I'm just gonna run the other way with the equalizer. Probably a good idea, and now look at where we are.
We're all back at their spawn again, and at this point, there's only a minute and a half left.
I just said, you know what? Screw it. Whatever. I tried.
I tried to let people come out of the spawn, but it just didn't matter.
Only reason why I came back here was to make sure there was no scouts or no spies that would potentially be able to cap the point, or even get on the cart.
I just wanted to make sure that we could just end this without a problem. Blow the banner, and here comes the cavalry. That's a spy.
I know it. He tries to face Stabby, but I do a self-destruct kill on him. Once again, when we get down here,
I get critscrieged again, and I don't know. You'll see. Where the hell did this guy's teleporter go? Look at this.
Where did that thing go? Get a few kills. I actually kill him. See,
I kill him right before he gets on the teleporter.
Where did that thing go? If you were in this server, and you were on Blue Team when this happened,
tell me where that teleporter went, because I'm really curious to know. At this point in the match now,
somebody was screaming over the mic. They're saying, oh my god, get to the cart.
There's like a bunch of people here, so I was like, oh jeez. So I blow the banner.
Of course, I had one again, and there's a heavy medic on the cart. It doesn't matter. They go down, and look at this.
I am screwed here. I'm like, no, no, I'm having such a good round. Please don't kill me.
I whip you to death, and that's the end.
22 kills in one life, and that's the one life as the soldier in this gameplay.
Thank you all for watching so much, guys. I'd really appreciate it.
I'll leave the rest of the gameplay up so you guys can see that I scoot Dugan's like a goose.
Scoot Dugan's like a goose, and I'll see you guys later. Take care, everybody.