Hello again. How are you? I'm back. Those of you that were here last night,
sorry for the abrupt ending. Don't know what happened, but they were either doing
maintenance or there was some kind of accident or something. Maybe
potentially we don't really know. But internet abruptly just turned off
to the whole house and didn't come back. Came back for like 30 minutes and then
came went down again. So sorry about that, but we're back now.
Everything seems to be back in working order.
I hope you're having a good day so far. I'm having a good day. I'm gonna do
something today that I said I was gonna do a year and a
half ago. Just over a full year ago I said I was
gonna do this. We played Stuntman Ignition on a PS2
night. Remember that? Remember when I did all those
PS2 games in a row? Well Stuntman Ignition was one of them.
And it turns out the game looks like shit and is almost unbearable to
to play and look at on PS2. So I said wait there's a PS3 version. Everyone was
saying there's a PS3. It's way better. It's so much better graphics, better
handling of the cars. So I said all right I'll get the PS3
version. I said I was gonna do that like probably in a few weeks.
It's been more than a year. So Stuntman Ignition PS3 version tonight.
Been sitting on it for a while. Here we go.
Don't know how long we're gonna play this for but I figured I would do it
because it's here and I'm gonna do it. If this takes less than a couple hours
because DOS got disconnected. We had disconnected DOS last night.
I will just go back and we will do more of that. I might get addicted to this and
I might want to play this all night. I don't know.
I can't tell you. So if we go more than four, five, six, seven hours on Stuntman
Ignition which is possible. I can't predict the future. We'll see.
But we're here and I gotta do some. You guys, I have to do some tests
with you guys because it's been a long time since I've
connected the original Elgato HD to this computer.
So we're gonna see how out of sync this is.
You ready? There it is. So if you could do me a huge favor and let me know when
you hear the sounds. Well I mean you're gonna hear the music
but ready? So like for instance let me like turn the music off. Okay
so you guys hear that right? That like let me ask you a question.
Ready? How bad is that? Are we in sync?
It's fine. Is it? No way. I know I'm louder but I mean I can change that.
Okay so for instance. Ready? It's in sync. That's I can't even
believe it. Okay it's a little off but it's a little
late. This sound is a little late. Tell me to check this out. Let me know
about it. One, two, three, four. One, two, three,
four. Yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What was that?
Perfect. Worse. Hey that's perfect. It's way worse.
The duality. Now it's worse. What about hold on.
Let me try one more thing. Just doing a little bit of experimentation here.
One, two, three, four. Ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding. One, two, three, four. Now it's worse. It was better the first
time. Okay, hold on. Hey, welcome to German at
85. I need to let me see. Can I hear this?
One, two, three, four. All right. Now my voice is late.
It's good. All right, can I mod tell me if this is good?
Okay, I'm just gonna play. Now that's way too loud.
A mod has spoken. All right, we're good. Welcome to Stuntman Ignition. Last time
we started the first little bit of the career. We're just
gonna do it. Remember this part? I did this for like an hour.
Remember we talked about how this was Vegeta? It's very blurry.
It's really low volume for me. Why is it so low for me and not for you guys?
Get out of the car. Get out of the car. You only got five seconds.
It is low. Oh, fuck. Welcome to British Columbia. We're shooting a disaster movie
up here, so you'll have plenty of work.
Pyrotechnics, burning buildings, lava raining down from the sky. Hold on.
I remember this. We did the first mission and then I gave up.
Yeah, I'll change it. I'm gonna get water.
I'm told this is your first time on a big set, so I'll walk you through how it
works. We'll have you wired up in your vehicle
and your coordinator will call out all the major director stunts.
Yeah, you gotta do what they say. You gotta land it, stick it.
Yellow stunt icons. These include drifts, gaps, jumps,
closes, and other maneuvers. I remember this shit. We'll be using a point system to
judge your runs. It's deja vu. It's gonna be deja vu for the first like 20 to 30
minutes. More precisely you perform, more points
you'll land. Fail a director stunt and you'll get a
strike. Five strikes and Richard will have to call a reshoot, which won't make
him happy. Once you finish a run successfully, he'll
look at the court and be happy. Get motion sickness.
Yeah, why is the cameraman doing this? If you really nail it.
Richard's been doing this a long time and he's well respected. You could get all
this from just having a wide. You don't have to zoom in on
everything. I'm still on with this studio. Look, it was nice to meet you. I'll see
you on the set. All right kid, let's get you prepped for
your work on this. Oh shit, I gotta zoom in and
go out of focus. That's what they pay me for. You'll drive four different vehicles
in Aftershock, an RC-1000 sports coupe, an older SUV, a dirt bike, and a fire
chief's patrol car. Each handles differently. He's too
close. You pull it back, man. So just relax. These sets are big and chaotic
with live explosions, projectiles. This cameraman went to the school of 20
year old YouTubers. Or the whole production will have to
stop while the crew pulls you out. We've got some great stunts planned. There's
a high risk sequence racing over burning rooftops
and a huge finale where the town gets ripped apart.
Before each scene, I'll give you shots of your key stunts with tips on how to
pull them off. So just listen to me and you'll get through this in one piece.
All right, I'm good. And now it's fucking loud.
Now it's loud again. That's just how it works. Remember, every cut scene is its
own full motion video rendered video that they put at a certain level.
Okay, all I can do is the Reign of Terror.
It's gonna be right for your scene. You'll double for the town's
troublemaking drifter in his R-3000 as he flees the volcanic eruption.
The center of the ramp will be this huge jump over a burning semi.
The key is to hit the ramp straight. That'll set you up for the stunt that
follows. As soon as you land, you'll have a pair
of precision drivers coming at you fast and you'll need to gap between them.
It's dangerous, so be careful. And don't be afraid of retakes. Mr. Langston's a
picky director and it can take a while to make him happy.
Driving directly into the guy. Roll tape. This is our first big setup, everyone.
Let's focus and start the film right. Over the jump.
Through the middle. Here we go.
Three, two, one. Action!
Gap the cars. God, I just, I murdered that person.
What's the, what's handbrake?
How do you drift? Oh, shit! Hold on, hold on. I need to see the
controls. Handbrake is O. Gas, brake, steering, right.
Action is triangle. Okay. Got it. It's circle. Uh, Jerma sucks thanks to the five
community selves. Circle is handbrake. I'm ready.
Three, two, one. Action!
Drift turn right. Turn right. What?
Can you seriously imagine him having a fucking
stunt man? You're telling him what to do as he's doing it.
Let's move on to the next shot. Oh, hey, you're gonna have to go, let me, come over
here, man. Let me talk to you for a minute. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm new.
I'm the new stunt driver. Yeah, come here. Uh, we need to go through the gap and the
car is here. Go through that and it's gonna be the take.
And then when he gets in the car, you fucking like strap him in,
lock him in the front seat. Drift turn right. Guy's like fucking screaming.
You have him like locked in like straight jacket style.
Screaming the commands and it's, you never told me any of this shit before.
Oh, you guys can't hear me. You can't hear what I'm saying.
Fuck.
Let's watch the replay. Ooh, almost got by that guy.
Nice. A guy in a mustard dress shirt. No, I kind of just said fuck that one.
I'm not doing that one. All right, let's keep going. New scene.
This next scene is a lava flow. Lava flow.
This is just GTA V with a cinematic camera.
And stunt stringing is how you rack up the big numbers.
That's just a regular day in GTA V. And goes into your stunt string.
If you perform a stunt within two seconds of another stunt,
that will continue your stunt string and add another number to your multiplier.
Now your stunt stringing. Be sure to watch your stunt indicator on the upper
left. It tells you what stunt you just performed
and how long you have until your string breaks.
That one's hard to do.
String them.
Fifth star.
I'm never going to get five stars, guarantee.
Zero. Wait, what? Wait, hold on.
My total score should be zero. Is he just telling, is he making fun of me?
I feel like he was just talking shit. Okay, string the scene.
Let's go. Three, two, one, go.
I gotta, I gotta hold on a minute here. Is there a way that I can make this so
the audio, the, the, it's gotta, gotta keep it all the same level.
Menu volume is gonna be the, let's just do like this.
Everything at 60. Car volume six, right?
Like then everything would be the same and I can adjust it perfectly.
You know what I'm saying? It's the menu volume that's fucking it all up.
I think that's gonna be good. Let's go.
We all right? I think so.
String it. Pretty good. What's next?
Too early. Got it. That's not bad. That's not bad.
It's gonna be four step, five stars. That's good.
Does anyone remember when I did this the first time?
It took, I couldn't do this.
I specifically have this memory of being, of being angry at the game
because I could not do this. What happened?
I don't understand. What changed?
All right. Today's role will be the drifter's last scene when he tries to escape the town
and gets torched by a lava boulder at the end.
The feature stunt is the pyro charge.
I was not pretending. I was probably like fucking tired.
Which will mark on your HUD. Trigger the charge and set your car on fire.
It'll get hot, but you'll be wearing a cool suit.
Once you're lit, drift hard to the right and gap through the car wash.
That'll extinguish the fire. Then race on to the big finale.
And remember kid, watch out for that lava.
Yeah, but the PS2 version was like unplayable.
It was like 12 frames a second at like 360p.
String it. Here we go.
Three, two, one, action.
You have to stay out of the lava.
Three, one, action.
God, that drifter is not going to be alive.
Car wash. Oh my God.
I had an instant fucking headache again.
I knew it was going to take less than five minutes.
God damn it.
Motherfucker's dead.
It's a burning building.
It's horrible.
Why am I alive?
I want to see.
Ignite your vehicle for the first time.
Hot wash and hot wax.
Okay, cool.
I got a color customizer.
Very nice.
You unlock the R3000.
It's too loud.
The camera angle's bad because I killed the director.
Yeah, that's true.
Oh God, my fucking stomach hurts.
I did a pretty good job, but I contained myself pretty well here.
What?
What happened to that car?
That car just flew forward.
And then they just detonate me.
That person's not alive.
There's no way.
Okay, let's keep going.
I'm really, really...
I'm so glad I actually a year later decided to play this game.
So this is a volcano climb.
How can a game be so loud and so quiet at the same time?
Thank you Klosski for the five community subs.
Thank you.
Five subs coming up.
Let's talk motorcycles, kid.
Directors love them because they're fast and loud and add punch to any scene.
But they're also harder to control and a lot more dangerous,
so watch out or they'll be mopping your skull off the pavement.
There are two major stunts unique to the bike.
What are the unique ones?
It's a great way to start any motor run and keep your strings alive.
How do you do a wheelie?
Just pull back?
Yeah, all right, you just pull back.
Then there's the slide.
To pull it off.
Oh, nice.
Perform the action as you pass through the designated stunt box.
That'll make you lay the bike down on one side while you're still barreling forward.
That's a lot of info on the screen for just holding left.
Simple as that.
Let's see what you...
All right, let's go.
What are all the diagrams for?
Yeah, I just...
Somebody just had...
I mean, it is like a Hollywood movie studio,
so there's somebody just making slides for everything.
They make slides and like storyboards and shit for like what they eat for lunch every day.
Doesn't surprise me.
Oh, it's hard to do on the bike.
I don't know if it's going to be U-turn.
This is like when you're driving in the car with like your mother or something.
I go, can you take me to the bank?
Yeah, sure, ma.
Oh, what bank do you want to go to?
I know how to get there.
Just listen to me.
I'll tell you.
What's the...
Put it in GPS.
No, no, no, I don't need the GPS.
I don't need that fucking stupid technology.
And you get to like the turn that you need to go to,
and they're just like, oh, yeah, like when I...
When your grandfather and I used to...
We used to smoke every day and...
No, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Just tell me the address, grandma.
I can do that better.
Slide under.
Nice.
Spring, spring, spring.
What?
That was a U-turn.
I just did it.
Huh?
All right, we're good.
I got it.
No, don't play again.
Next scene.
Looks so goofy.
U-turn.
No, you.
I see what you guys are doing.
There we go.
Oh, I did it.
All right, just get me out of this.
In this scene, you'll be doubling for a desperate team
racing through the carnage to rescue his grandmother
and her mountain cabin.
The key stunt begins with a jump off a downed semi
over some collapsing trees.
Keep it high speed when you land.
Then a blast will hurl a couple of cars right at you
with some serious force.
Dodge under the flying cars by sliding the bike
like we rehearsed.
After the slide, you'll move real quick
into a hard drift left, so be ready for it.
Continue up the mountain.
After that, Grandma will tell you where to go after that.
She'll tell you how to get back to Grandma's house.
Let's see that desperation in your driving.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Guys, I can push him over there.
Just wait a second.
This is important.
Three, two, one, action.
I gotta be quick about it, though.
Let's go get Grandma.
Close left.
Through the gap.
All right, come on.
I can hit this.
Use action.
Why?
Why would I use action there?
Come on.
All right, we got it.
We got it.
New color.
Nice.
Okay, here we go.
Let's watch that movie.
What?
No.
Bad editor.
That's unfortunate.
Cameraman missed it.
Well, to be fair, why would the cameraman
be filming at the crew?
There's no reason for that.
That was like a Tony Hawk rhyme.
That was way cooler than what they wanted me to do.
All right, let's keep going.
Career meant new scene.
Three, two, one, Earthshake.
What?
Can I have a suit of armor?
I have a t-shirt on.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, the budget doesn't call for anything besides a red t-shirt.
Good luck on the 180-foot fall.
Where do I go?
Action.
Get up.
Close to the explosion.
What?
Was that a jump?
All right, I got it.
I thought I had to drift here.
No, he's going to go through.
Close call.
These people, who are these other people?
I would hate to be one of these other stuntmen.
Right through the sign, right there.
Boom.
Why am I still on my...
Hard left turn.
I don't even know.
What?
You...
Come on.
U-turn.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Three, two, one, action.
No.
God damn it.
Through the sign, right here.
And then there's another...
Where's that other jump?
Right there?
Left turn.
Damn, that's hard.
Doesn't have to be real lava.
You don't have to have real lava.
Three, one.
Doesn't need to be actual magma.
Wait, wait, how would you even get that here?
I gotta be going faster than this shit.
Right there, got it.
All right, land.
Land in the box.
In the box.
Got it.
It's that frame rate, man.
Come on.
Break through.
Use action.
Action, and then I have to drift.
U-turn.
Fuck.
That was such a shitty jump.
Why?
Get out of my fucking way.
Why would they break in front of me?
Jump the shack?
I did it, okay.
It's one star, I'm gonna laugh.
Thank God.
It's two.
Dude, that's two stars, it's all right.
We don't even need to see the replay on this one.
But we're gonna, we have to watch the replay on all of them.
Not bad.
All right, that person, that person's on fire too.
They don't even have like a head protector, mask, or anything.
Just burning.
Ooh, that was pretty dirty.
That was weird too.
Why did that speed up?
Is this going like three times speed?
What's going on here?
It's playing this EDF music.
Could've, yeah, I could use a little work.
What did I do wrong here?
This game is fucking ridiculous, I love it.
We're almost done with the first set of scenes here.
This is first tremor in the movie Aftershock.
In this scene, you're stunting for a vulcanologist
racing down the mountain to warn the authorities
that this eruption is gonna cause even more damage than everyone thinks.
With a big stunt, you'll off-road to a ramp on a hill,
take a long jump over a chasm, crash through the support beams,
and land on the bridge.
Chunks of lava have torn the bridge to hell.
So after you land, watch for a quick series of pitfalls
and make your way to the other side.
You've held your own so far on this film.
Keep it up.
Gonna have to do this a few times, I think.
I'll do my best.
Keep up the speed.
You didn't tell me that was, what the fuck?
Got it.
Not bad.
What?
Through the gap.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what else to do.
I don't know what...
This counts like a fucking backwards...
Go backwards over it.
String it.
Through it.
I did it.
Land in the box.
No, please.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm sorry.
Take him out.
He's taking me out.
I got a minute.
I'm good.
No more mistakes.
The X is X, X, X, X, X, X.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it.
Forgot.
I forgot that happened in the beginning.
No X.
How is that not through the burning house?
I don't...
What happened?
Why is that not through the burning house?
Restart it.
This car sucks.
Give me my motorcycle.
Turn left.
Downhill.
Through the burning building.
Hard right.
Through the gap.
He's doing it.
Through the trees.
In the box.
Come on, something.
I love keep up the speed,
but it's like possible.
There's so many turns.
All right, crush through.
Ah.
We're good.
Next time, what is it?
Tell me.
Oh no.
Am I gonna make it?
I got it.
What?
There's more?
What does he want me to do?
He was still...
He was sitting right here.
Why would you be 10 feet in front of where the guy lands from a huge jump?
You set the camera up and get out of the way, man.
Let's take a look.
Finished product.
I'm always in the same clothes, too.
Nailed it.
GTA V.
It's funny because this is playing GTA V online in cinematic mode.
There'll be helicopters flying around, dropping missiles, and you're driving around.
This actually is what this is like online.
Cars that have just recently exploded on every single street.
Not even a helmet on me, either.
This is a long scene.
I messed that up.
I don't know.
All the doors are open.
No, all the doors on the right side are just open.
Did they edit?
Did they edit that?
I feel like I was there for much longer.
They did.
They fixed it in post.
That's cool.
All right, that's Aftershock.
Stunt City.
Fire unlocked.
Now there's more Aftershock.
Here comes the escape.
This is the end, for sure.
This next run calls for a special stunt maneuver called the Reverse 180.
And it's a bit tricky.
Oh, no.
Let's make sure you've got it down so you're not wasting time and money on the set.
I'm gonna blow this so bad.
First, come to a complete stop.
Then hold your brake to take off in reverse.
Once you've gathered some speed, move the wheel hard all the way to one side.
That'll start your spin.
Is that talking in the background?
When it turned about 90 degrees, move the left stick in the opposite direction.
Release the brake.
Never gonna do it.
Throttle it hard to bring you through the 180.
With the right timing, you should come out straight and fast.
And ready to hit your next mark.
All right, let's give it a go.
Okay, I'll try.
It's gonna take a few attempts.
I do this in the parking lot all the time.
Don't do that.
Absolutely don't do that.
What are you?
Don't do that shit.
All right, complete the stunt.
Let's go.
Reverse 180.
That was perfect.
How was that not correct?
I got it.
I got this.
That's not bad.
This is the final scene we'll be shooting for Aftershock.
We've saved the toughest for last.
You'll be doubling for the town's fire chief,
escorting some fire engines across town.
The mark he's done here is a reverse 180 on the second floor of a parking garage.
After you've whipped your car all the way around like we practiced,
you'll need to keep enough speed to crash through the barrier,
fly out of the garage, and land on the other side of the lava.
I have to actually break through this concrete barrier.
So you better give it your all.
You can't just paint a piece of cardboard gray.
I have to have enough speed to drive through the concrete.
Stay with them.
Break through the fence.
Gap the cars.
What?
He just threw a car at me.
Where's the reverse 180?
Through the building.
No, fine.
That's so dangerous.
What the fuck are you thinking?
That's insane.
Just sitting in the middle of the road with all these explosions.
I can still make it.
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
Reverse 180.
Here it comes.
What?
Second floor.
Here we go.
I got to remember how to do this.
Reverse 180.
Stop and reverse.
Got it.
What?
Bullshit.
I had that.
I did that perfectly fine.
How are you supposed to go that fast through the barricade?
I want to see this.
Imagine setting all this up for another shot.
Yeah.
This scene alone was like $175 million.
You're not just going to take it as the guy.
There he is.
He's here.
That's the moment in the Disney movie when everyone's like,
no, is he?
Where is he?
He's okay.
And he's okay.
And he comes out and like sinks with three.
All right, I don't understand what went so wrong.
Why am I in a firefighter outfit?
Wait, am I a fireman or am I a policeman?
Oh, I'm okay.
I am a firefighter.
Here it is.
Fine.
I'm fine with that.
Come on.
Really?
Three, two, one.
Action.
Break through the fence.
Do it again.
A little too fast.
I'm on two wheels right now.
Cut.
Downward.
It's not.
Shit.
Three, two, one.
Action.
I'm going too fast.
Is there a reason why I can't do this now?
I did it first try last time.
Coming up.
Frame rate.
No, I'm a liar.
No shit.
Monica, no.
See, I landed in there that time.
Did you see that?
I hit my back tires with lava and I didn't fail.
We called that bullshit.
There goes another one.
In the same spot.
Doing it again.
You think they would have learned from the last shoot.
Just be the same guy.
I'm in there.
I'm gonna get this right.
I just have to go fast enough to get over the gap.
Here we go.
Here it comes.
Is it?
What?
What is it?
What does it want me to do there?
What the fuck?
What do you mean 180?
I can't fuck anything else up.
Come on.
Through the gap.
Don't touch anything.
Got it.
Just barely.
No.
We can't.
Still two stars.
I'm okay with it.
All right.
Let's watch the actual finished product.
I know I can't skip.
People are gonna be like, oh, you don't have to do it.
Just skip it.
It's gonna be like, no skipping.
We're in 300 or more air time points.
The world's done the world.
Fire down below.
Color customizer unlocked.
Okay.
Not allowed to skip, right?
Let's see it.
Pretty good start.
You can hear the guy in there going.
God damn shit.
You see that dodge and it hit that car that was behind me and exploded.
We don't have to.
Do we watch the whole movie?
Is there any dialogue in this movie?
Or is it just these six scenes back to back?
I got this pretty well.
For the first time I've ever seen that, it was all right.
Oh, it's because I fell down.
No, I didn't.
They followed a camera guy just ran up the ramp.
That was awesome, but I didn't even get points for it.
We just need a gorilla reading a book at the end of this.
Yeah.
Here we go.
That hesitation.
That was like, what am I supposed to do?
This that hard break into no, no, I have to go forward.
I'm concentrating so intently right now because I had four strikes.
It wasn't crispy enough.
It's all right.
I was escorting the fire truck and the fire truck at the end didn't make it.
All right.
Movie.
Wait, movie trailer unlocked.
No, really?
Come on, little buddy.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
So you go into that softball tournament next Sunday.
Did you guys feel that?
That was it.
Staying here is suicide.
Try to be a hero.
Just try to stay alive.
If you'd listen to me in the first place, we'd all be safe by now.
This is not the time.
There is no more time.
Uh, is that implying that the earth is destroyed?
The best part about all that is they make you really feel like you were a part of that.
But they really only took two or three clips of me driving the straight line
because I must have been so bad that they didn't get anything cool.
They got me driving down the road.
Director intro stunt coordinator.
All right.
So, uh, we're good, right?
So I can just go.
No, no, no, no, no.
What the hell are you doing?
Aren't shot in orders.
I hope you know this next scene comes just before those weren't even my scene.
He's still trying to get out of town and up to his grandmother.
The big moment here comes early in the run.
When you take the ramp over a major drop and smashed through a burning bill.
Time to reshoot.
Do I have to go back to the menu?
Career menu.
Yeah.
Career menu director intro.
We already did this, didn't we?
Career.
Hold on.
Is that it?
Oh, all right.
I was going to say no way.
Okay.
So this is a whooping and a hollering too.
Can't speak here for a while.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
This is this is whooping and a hollering too.
Sup, dude.
I'm the director.
Andy faction.
Andy in the house.
Whoop.
Hey, guys, this is the stunt driver.
No, you're the stunt driver, dude.
The stunt driver.
I thought you were a beard.
Guys, take these fireworks to my butt.
Jim boy's playing the lead, so you'll be doubling for him.
What's for a reality show?
We had Jim flab a bridge in his shopping cart with handcuffs on him.
Seth Rogan.
He's like chained to a goat.
That was sweet.
That goat ain't coming, man.
That's our version of stunt driving, man.
Anyway, dude, this flick's called whooping and hollering too.
Back road and cracker fest with some trouble making brothers
getting in car chases with the cops and all that kind of stuff.
You just like your trailer park family, or you just want to fight me?
I can do that one.
So you got to make a killer, you know?
We've planned out some huge crazy ass stunts for you.
So any chance you get to flare it up, just do it, OK?
You just take it.
I'm not afraid to go to jail to make a poor cop.
Jim boy, put your hands on my booty.
Awesome.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
I'm trying to make a movie here, dude.
That's the coolest thing ever.
Just hit your marks, and we'll be cool.
It's good to meet you, man.
Have fun out there, and I'll see you on the set.
I don't even know where the set is.
Look, kid, this director's a clown, so we
may have to work double time to give the producers what they want.
Get up.
Of course, they signed me, Jim.
The bait, you're like a four wheeler.
We'll mostly double for the Creek boys and their signature muscle car,
the General Stewart, as they try to stop the corrupt sheriff from
foreclosing on their family's land.
You'll also have a scene on a dirt bike as your crazy brother Otis.
A fun scene is Uncle Cletus in his monster truck full of moonshine,
and a great run as a bank robber in a hijacked armored truck.
This will be your first time to shoot chase scenes, so be sure not to fall too far behind
the lead car, or we'll have to stop and reset.
Most of the action happens in the town square, but we've also got some exciting
stunts planned in the junkyard and in the lumberyard.
Baxter and his crew are all about backwoods mayhem, so I hope you're ready to
tear things up, literally.
I'm ready.
In this first scene, the Creek boys' Uncle Cletus has loaded a ton of moonshine into
his monster truck, and he's trying to escape the cops.
Big thing here are the crushing stunts.
When you see a crush icon, drive your truck over the marked car to smash it.
This is a tightly choreographed run, and if the icon turns red,
that means the car's left the shot and you've blown your chance.
It's about it.
Let's start this movie right.
All right.
Okay, let's get this freaking movie started.
Crush.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, action.
Hit the police car.
I missed.
I missed all the police cars.
Hit the police car.
No.
I got a double?
I'm gonna make it.
I actually did.
I just got nominated for an award.
I can do that better.
This movie stinks.
Movie stinks.
No, I can do that better.
One, action.
Hit the police car.
What the fuck are you doing?
Okay.
One.
Let's go get it.
Do it again, do it again, do it again.
I can do it again.
Three, one, action.
Hit the police car.
Okay.
Straight through.
Hard right.
Smash the sign.
Got it.
Hit the police car.
Hit it.
Yeah, I got it.
If you can't do it, you'll be consumed.
What?
Perfect.
Get off.
Ten.
Quick precision.
Precise.
Four stars.
I did it.
Five stars.
Threader is stringing the entire movie scene.
It's got bonus, like a five-star replay.
What does that mean?
At least it's a better cut.
I don't know.
That was pretty clean though, until we got over here.
I still snuck it in.
Ready?
Whoops.
Yeah, I still got it.
On the bike, right?
Car commercial unlocked.
Wait a minute.
Is it a car commercial that I can do in this game?
I'm looking forward to that one.
In this scene, you'll double for some bank robbers as they try to escape the Creek boys and the cops in a hijacked armored vehicle.
The challenging stunt is this double overtake near the end.
You've got to pass the police car, then thread the needle to pass the semi.
If you haven't built up enough speed, you'll smash into the semi head-on, so make sure to lay heavy on the throttle.
And remember, the more collateral damage, the better.
This game is an assault on the senses.
It really is.
It's gonna be really cool, so break it loose!
110,000 points.
One.
Action.
Ah, sorry.
Scrape the police car.
Scrape the truck.
The gap.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's better.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One.
Action.
Scrape the police car.
On.
I gotta be right to the left.
Two.
One.
Action.
Hard right.
Ripped.
I still gotta-
No!
Through the gap.
Don't touch anybody.
It's okay.
I can still finish it.
Ow.
I didn't even tell you that was gonna happen.
They just killed me.
That was driver's side.
Driver's side.
That's the scenario, I think.
It just- everything turned off.
The game freezes at a- when you are down to the level.
But that is what would happen.
I'm driving down that road and then it's off.
Everything's off.
Oh, shit.
Good job, boys.
I can't.
I'm gonna say it again.
One more time.
Yeah, that was really as if somebody spawned that truck in.
And that- I like- I might like that more than I might like the last one.
It's like a perfect cut, too.
This game is awesome.
Mail run.
Next, you'll stunt for Otis Creek, the brother with a couple screws loose.
He's taking revenge on the corrupt sheriff by disrupting his beloved
Catfish County Chicken Day Parade.
Your big stunt is an extended wheelie.
Gap between these cop cars, then one-wheel it all the way across the porch.
Then come down hot so you'll have enough speed to take this final jump.
And don't let the giant chickens distract you.
Andy, how come you always get to call out the director, dude?
Shut up!
There's a giant chicken.
Did I- heck, did I make it?
I'm just still concerned about the guy that just got crushed through the gap.
What?
No!
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Land on the semi.
No!
I thought it was gonna be on the ground.
Well, I wanna see.
Let me see what happens.
Because somehow I went- I jumped the car.
It's POV camera.
This is sped up.
Double jump.
It's gonna be like a laugh at this game.
Like, I don't even know what else to say right now.
All right, I can do it here.
Play again, let's go.
Three, two, one, action.
Don't hit the car.
I'm gonna take the left.
I hit by that fucking truck.
We both got hit.
Oh, I need to calm down.
Through the gap.
Jump the lake.
I- I can still do it.
I just don't- don't fucking- I gotta get up here.
Up on the ledge.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, then it's up here, over here.
Come on!
It's all right.
Jesus!
Really?
Okay, I'm gonna take that one.
We were filming that, right?
I want to see-
No, we both get hit by the semi at the same time.
That was brutal.
Everything was going real well up until that point.
Who was the third dead person?
There was somebody lying under the tire.
Who was the other guy?
Off the bike.
It's somebody else.
Come and get on the bike.
Another stuck man came and got on the bike and drove it away.
Okay, so two people got murdered right there and then behind the truck another stunt man was like,
oh shit, get on there and drive away with the same jacket.
Well, I need- we gotta- I want to see that again.
I need to- I wish I could slow it down.
Is that what actually happened?
So, there's two people involved here.
Here we go.
Dead!
So, where's the third person?
I can't even fucking think about that right now.
There you go.
That was a hard jump cut.
Strike Force Omega Unlocked.
All right, we're not done with this one yet.
Why wouldn't they make another one of these games?
Where's Stuntman 4?
Because I know there's one more, right?
This next run calls for a special stunt, so let me break down how it works.
It's called two-wheeling or skiing.
It's one of the trickiest maneuvers in stunt driving, but master it,
and you'll really start turning heads in the industry.
You'll begin by hitting the ramp with one side of your car.
That'll kick you up so you're riding on two wheels.
Once you're up, hold steady on the throttle and use the left stick to keep your balance.
Watch where you're going because you must two-wheel in the indicated zone to pass the stunt.
To successfully maintain your two-wheel, it's all about control.
Small adjustments will turn the vehicle.
Big adjustments will raise or lower your vehicle.
Once you're ready to come out of it, turn towards the low side or tap the E-brake to come down.
Ready to give it a try, kid?
Yeah.
I guess.
I can't believe All Might is talking to Jerma.
Yeah.
Drive on two wheels?
Oh, are you sure you didn't want me to get on the right side and slide?
No, what the fuck?
Why is it so hard to do this?
Hold on.
It just ripped over.
Three, two, one, go.
Drive on two wheels.
Dude, it's really hard to do this.
I have to be going slower.
Three, two, one, go.
Drive on two wheels.
Get down.
Get the wheel down.
This is actually really hard to do.
It's really kind of...
Three, two, one, go.
Drive on two wheels.
I mean, I just...
Let's see how...
I can't turn.
If I turn, the car starts to fall down.
And I just technically did it.
Let me do it again.
Okay.
Now you'll double for the Creek Boys, racing to City Hall to save the family farm.
Other than some two-wheeling at the top, once the wheels are in the air,
if I hit left or right stick, it like goes up or down.
And I can't turn the car.
After a left turn, come in straight and clean with a good amount of heat
so you can pull the 180 right as you pass the semi.
It'll take some practice to learn exactly where to start the drift.
So don't sweat a few retakes.
Dude, if you can nail these stunts, I will totally give you my sister's number.
Oh, go for that, dude.
Yes.
Seriously.
Nice.
I think she's Asian.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, action.
One.
Excuse me.
What's wrong here?
Three, two, one, action.
No, it's okay.
I got it.
I broke it anyways.
Two wheels.
No, not bad.
I did it first pretty much first real try.
Oh, I got in the nomination.
Let's take a look.
Two people in the car now.
I did do that pretty well.
That was, and I didn't hit a single person.
Didn't even hit that guy.
I was focused, except for that part.
I had the break for the last.
Can't wait to see the trailer for this one.
Only probably one or two more scenes, right?
I've improved.
Look at three, three, two, two, two, two.
This is five, four, three, three.
Getting better.
This next scene's a race between the Creek Boys and another redneck in his souped up hot rod.
The key is to follow the lead car.
We'll have it clearly marked.
You can't bump it too hard, can't get ahead, and can't fall too far behind.
There'll be some jumps, 180s, and other stunts where you'll lose sight of the lead, but relax.
Long as you stay the course and keep roasting your tires, you'll meet back up with it soon.
Don't get too close.
Stay close enough where you're still in the game and don't overtake them.
Pretend like you're playing your little brother in Mario Kart.
Quiet on the set, everybody.
Shut the hell egg in this movie, not suck.
All right, let's go.
Three, two, one, action.
Follow the lead vehicle.
Just need to see.
I didn't even scrape it.
That was a much better stunt than what they wanted me to do.
You can't turn.
No, you can't.
You gotta, it's gonna be the worst one.
Jump the logs.
Okay, sure.
Just do it again.
Three, two, one, action.
Follow the lead vehicle.
Scrape the vehicle.
I'll just add my own stunts.
Big drift.
I'm doing my own stunts.
No, the tree just ruined everything.
Why did you do that?
I had like a four or five star going too.
Jump the logs.
There he is, I'm fine.
Oh shit, I got it.
Oh my god, how was I supposed to know?
Oh no.
It's fine.
He's totally going to work.
I can't even watch the game replay.
It doesn't even matter.
Whatever.
I'm Jack Lee, General Steward.
You are average.
Well, two and a half would be average.
A little bit above average.
Let's see if we, in full motion video.
Added my own stunt here.
I jumped this entire semi.
That's some people doing their shit right there.
The chicken sound was perfect.
Here we go.
Leads a good view.
See the temptation there to just run that guy over.
I didn't do it though.
I wanted to finish this.
Here we go.
That was actually way, way better.
The music stops and the music picks back up.
By design, as intended.
This will be a bad action, but we'll do a good comedy.
All right.
Stunt City Team Unlocked.
Here we go.
We are at the final scene of movement and hollering.
This is the other side of the bank robber chase you shot in Grab and Go.
Not the side.
And the last scene for this movie.
This time you'll play the Creek Boys.
Trying to stop the hijacked armored vehicle to get some reward.
Do I get a Mario Kart ghost that is on the screen too?
Another chase scene.
So remember, don't fall too far behind the lead.
The key stunt is a jump onto the upper deck of a storefront.
Hit the jump and break through the balusters.
Once on top, keep that speed going to hit the jump and clear the semi.
All right.
Let's get out there and break some stuff.
That would be awesome if it actually is the other cars.
That was all over one radio.
They're all leaning in.
That's me, right?
That's other me.
It's definitely other me because it's dropping like a fucking idiot.
Scrape.
Oh, I just barely scraped.
Again.
Okay, good.
I am.
That was tricky, but I did it.
I think I just, I think I just accidentally killed that car.
Did I get it?
I got it.
Over the tanker.
Now what?
That's a real hard left.
Damn it.
That's not, that's going to be the end.
That's going to be the end of me.
No, got into the tires.
Um, do I have to keep going?
Apparently not.
We're in a one-star ranking for all seasons in an all-around guy.
Taurus World Stunt Ward.
More color customization.
Don't skip.
You don't skip it.
Why is it stuck there?
That was pretty tight.
I do something up here that I'm really proud of, actually.
I weave in and out of like four or five trees, like right here.
Ready?
One, two, three trees, four trees, five trees.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen trees.
You see that?
Fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty, twenty-two, twenty-three.
Most of those were lamps.
I'm excited for the trailer.
I'm going to do the commercial.
Nice.
Three stars.
All right, time to be quiet and watch the trailer.
You look mean, Sheriff.
You look mean.
Well, maybe this will be enough to remind them boys whose town it is.
Definitely.
There we go.
Uh, it was whooping in a hall room, too.
Where's the commercial?
Oddjobs.
Ooh.
Stunt City Club.
Hold on.
Rehearsals.
Here we go.
Stunt City Fire.
Car commercial.
I'm doing a car commercial.
In this commercial, you'll play a citizen of darkdom driving the new Venus Vexation
sports car.
The gags that you out-drive Night Avenger because your car is so fast.
You'll be using Nitro and the key run happens during your second boost.
Speed past the exploding cars and under the torch semi.
Then overtake Night Avenger on the left and end with a huge drift right.
Turning will be hard at high speed.
So you'll have to anticipate the stunts early.
You're faster than Batman in product placement.
Okay.
I'm ready.
There's Batman.
All right, I gotta be cleaner than that.
No failures are allowed.
What?
Oh, I didn't even know it was over there.
Shit, this is one of those addicting goddamn games where it's going to make me just sit
here for like an hour, isn't it?
I tried to pass close, but he flew backward.
What's going on here?
Three, two, one, action.
This car is too fast.
Show them this.
What?
I couldn't get what the fuck are you talking about?
Get close to the explosion.
You blew it up on top of me.
I'm faster than Batman already.
I'm faster than Batman.
Tell him to speed up.
Can we switch cars?
Just paint this one black.
Just give him this one.
What happened?
What happened there?
I didn't do anything.
All right, I overtook him.
I drove in front of him.
How else do you overtake somebody besides like driving around?
Am I going too slow?
Two, one, action.
I did overtake this thing.
He didn't say overtake.
Watch, ready?
So I overtake this guy.
I did it.
I literally drive right next to the cop car and overtake him.
Ready?
Did that not count?
I don't understand.
Why did it take so long to fail again?
One.
Why is it waiting to the end of the level to fail it?
I got you.
I can get five on this one.
Let's do five.
One, action.
That was close.
That's all the shit.
I can do five on this one.
Three, two, one, action.
Drip left.
Last try, that's it.
Christ, I'm spamming triangle.
Why?
Oh, I'm so angry right now.
I'm fucking furious.
I'm literally sitting there hitting triangle.
Three, two, one, action.
That doesn't make any sense.
Drip left.
That is impossible that I didn't get that.
It's actually impossible.
One, action.
I'm gonna look at a chat, hold on.
Three, two, one, action.
This is it.
This is the last one I'm gonna do
and then I'm gonna fucking pee and come back.
Hey, let's go.
Five.
In this show, you'll drive a bike that's on fire,
causing explosions as you drive close to propane tanks
and other vehicles.
The big moment in the show starts with a slide
beneath this semi, igniting it.
Then throw a 180 between the propane tanks,
making them blow up too.
As soon as you've spun around,
line up for the big ramp and gun it hard.
He beat up his pillow into the bedroom,
just like.
Hey guys, I'm back.
What's going on?
Love mech this train.
Jesus, this looks damn good.
Three, two, one, action.
He starts off the jump.
Oh, I almost missed it.
Let's reset, try that again.
Look at how big that jump is over there.
There are traps everywhere for me.
That's not nice.
Two, one, action.
He starts off the jump.
180.
Oh, you gotta start that way earlier
and go too fast.
Yeah, you're going way, way, way, way too fast.
Three, two, one, action.
He starts off.
I technically still did it, so it's okay.
Jesus, that was like going down a roller coaster.
Four, I'll take four.
Check it out.
I landed on the front tire and stuck it.
That was pretty insane.
There's one more here.
Stunt City team.
Might as well do them.
The emphasis of this show is team precision driving.
You'll be out there with a bunch of other stunt drivers
weaving back and forth between them
in a tightly choreographed run with lots of overtakes.
180.
Back to Batman.
I'll show the Batman.
Make your maneuvers as quickly as you can
and be sure never to hit the other cars
or you'll knock them off their marks
and the whole show will turn into a collision derby.
Fun as that sounds, it's not the goal.
So behave yourself.
This one sucks.
This one's horrible.
You've seen them on TV.
It's okay.
Now see the rip roaring.
I got this.
Only 60,000 points.
Close to the first car.
You got to be perfect there.
All right.
What?
I have to keep going all the way back?
I got to go start the turn in the box.
Okay.
I figured I could just go through the box.
You're going to restart because somebody else crashed.
That's not me.
The camera's not even on them.
The camera's on me.
Damn it.
Shit.
Come on.
What the hell?
What's happening?
What the fuck is happening?
What the hell do you want me to do after that?
It didn't say anything.
What?
What happens after the reverse 180?
Do I have to drive by the drivers again?
Okay.
I get it.
So I have to drive near that guy.
Did I do it?
I did it.
Give me a break.
I was right there.
I caught running out of gas at the finish line.
I'll get it.
I'm holding right on the pad.
I was holding right that whole time.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe I didn't fucking stop with that.
I touched him.
Game over.
I was holding right trick.
I was.
Dude, I could see like a 17, 18-year-old losing his fucking mind.
I'm 34 losing my mind too.
It doesn't matter.
That age doesn't matter.
When I hovered over this, somebody in all caps wrote,
this one is horrible.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
Get in there.
I did it.
Everything's fine.
Don't worry about it.
It's good.
I'm good to go.
Everything's perfect.
I'll take four.
I don't want to see the replay in this one.
I don't want to see it.
It's angering me even just like smelling this in my vicinity.
It actually gave me the boost I needed.
There you go.
All right.
Back to the career menu.
Where's the Batman at?
Overdrive unlocked.
I can't show you the replay of the Batman.
I have to...
In this commercial, you'll play a citizen of darkdom
driving the new Venus vexation sports car.
The gags that you out-drive Night Avenger
because your car is so fast.
You'll be using nature
and the key run happens during your second boost.
Speed past the exploding cars and under the torch semi.
Then overtake Night Avenger on the left
and end with a huge drift right.
Turning will be hard at high speed
so you'll have to anticipate the stunts.
Take on...
Nice gag.
What gag?
Everyone was saying show the replay
because I skipped it because I freaked out.
Load.
I didn't save a replay.
All right.
Here we go.
I swear to God.
You have to understand something.
There's no way I fucked that up.
I'm hitting triangle.
Like this.
Do you understand?
Like that happened twice now.
Like in the same spot.
In the same spot.
I'm hitting triangle.
Like what?
I've never...
What?
That doesn't make any sense.
Triangle is the button.
I swear to God.
That happened.
Like clip this and clip one to the floor.
That happened in the same spot.
I swear.
I promise.
Why would I not look?
Oh, it's triangle.
Okay.
I just forget how to play the game.
Ready?
All right.
It's over.
I did it.
That's not five stars.
All right.
I'm going to skip this.
I got the five star replay.
Here.
Just pretend this is like 25.
That was really, really bad at rehearsals.
All right.
Aftershock.
Here we go.
Strike Force Omega.
Is that a thistle on the truck?
Army style truck with 50 caliber auto turret.
It's a badass with a capital B.
Anyway, lots of my fans still think I do my own stunts.
So you better be good.
I got a reputation to protect.
Now I need to go bulk up for my next fight scene.
I'll see you on the set.
What?
You looking for an autograph?
Hey Marcus, get him one of those commemorative iPads.
I'll tell you, nothing beats working with a director
who thinks he should be driving for you.
I've worked with Steel before and trust me,
he's not easy to please.
But the good news is the man knows how to make an exciting action film.
So we've got some killer stunts lined up.
All right.
Some of the vehicles in this movie are heavily armed
and include a modified dune buggy, a motorcycle,
an unwieldy semi towing a giant Scud missile
and Commander Black's heavily armed assault vehicle, the Scorpion.
The missile is mostly open desert terrain
where you'll be driving on loosely packed dirt,
but you'll also need to weave your way through the strike force base
where there isn't much room to maneuver.
You'll also have your first chance to use nitrous,
giving you an extra punch of speed to make that fast escape.
Listen to me and hit your marks and you should walk away
with some impressive addition.
You'll start as a strike force Omega operative
trying to get a stolen Scud missile back to base.
The focus stunt is a side swipe of a combat bus.
Don't aim straight for the bus or you'll get drawn out too far.
Instead, aim for the gap in the bridge ahead.
And the gap in the bridge.
So you can veer slightly to side swipe the bus before taking the gap.
This is not like an active missile, right?
That moves with it.
Okay, that's a tricky turn with this thing.
Oh, just start over.
Just start over.
I was trying to swipe him with the tail.
Around we go.
Scrape, scrape, get up.
Come on, get the other one.
Nope, didn't get it.
Is this thing gonna blow?
Oh, I just rolled across the bridge.
They blew the bridge that I was crossing.
Once it became clear that I wasn't gonna go over the jump,
I would just still blow the bridge.
That seems like a bad idea.
Double, nice.
Okay, I gotta go over the jump here.
Left, right, left, right.
That was panic turning.
Sorry, three stars, I'll take it.
Nomination.
Let's take a look.
So what, I got caught on something over here.
I didn't kill the other, I didn't hit the other guy.
I just scraped his friend.
That was it right there.
That was the issue.
Actually, it was not even that bad.
It was pretty good, actually.
That was fine.
There's the gap, though.
Motorcycle mission, let's go.
Now, you'll double for a strike force scout returning to base with vital intelligence.
A challenging stunt is an aerial gap through a passing semi and into its trailer.
Come over a hill, then straighten up fast so you can aim for the jump.
Don't make last second adjustments once you're on the ramp.
That'll mess you up.
I have to go through a gap.
You'll need to slide beneath a second trailer, so be ready.
Oh, God.
If you're any good on a bike.
Okay, I guess we're gonna go, I'm just gonna go for it.
Action.
Overtake left.
What a movie scene.
Our hero overtakes the criminal on the...
Bye.
Not even wearing a fucking helmet.
No, I know.
This guy seriously get...
Now what?
What?
I just...
Did I do that?
Did I really do that?
There's no way I was gonna do that.
Not a chance in hell.
Absolute zero chance.
Ah!
Gap!
I can't believe I just made it.
I can do that one better.
That's three, it's fine.
The majority of the stream has been him saying a thing that I'm not ready for
and then me shockingly yelling the word he just said out loud.
This is one of those comedy movies.
And by the way, you gotta be careful for that gap.
What gap?
Gap?
There it is.
That was a pretty cool first person cam.
What?
That was a little messed up, but it's okay.
That first person cam doesn't work there.
It sounds like I hit something else too.
Pretty good.
It's all right, I'll take three.
Armor all, commercial unlocked.
Nice.
Dogs of war.
In this scene you'll double for an enemy merc rampaging through the SFO base.
The key stunt is a weaving...
It's a real brain, yeah.
Once you're in the base,
drift left as quickly and sharply as possible so you can set up your line.
Then thread between the three semis as they come straight at you.
You'll pass right, then left, then right.
This is another high-risk stunt, so keep it safe.
You're playing an enemy merc in this scene.
I want him driving wild and crazy.
Don't let me down.
270,000 points, that's a lot.
Three, two, one, action.
Oh my god, I'm not gonna do that.
The thing exploded.
I can't pass it when it's gone.
What an explosion.
This one.
I love this game.
This game is so bonkers.
Three, two, one, action.
To the explosion.
This pole.
Fuck this pole.
You know what I mean?
No, fuck that pole.
I'm not gonna let that win.
Three, two, one, action.
Too much drifting.
Drifting all over the place.
Way too much of it.
Pass this guy.
Got it.
Oh shit.
Which one?
Sloppy.
Very sloppy.
Too sloppy.
But it's alright.
This is really bad.
This is really, really bad.
Man.
There was a live animal in that car with me.
That's the only way that I can describe
the way I was moving around.
There was a fucking bear in that car.
This guy right here.
That guy fucks it up every time.
No.
I gotta get around that.
It's just, that pole sucks.
The pole and there's an exploded car.
Right there.
You gotta go around it.
Here it is.
No, pass around here.
He just turned into me.
You're too close.
Fuck you.
No.
That's such a small area to do that in.
Oh.
Damn it.
Too early.
It's okay.
No.
That's gonna.
No, no.
I got it.
No, I didn't.
Oh, come on.
Trying to line it up.
That's not a direct thing left.
Great.
There's too many things going on.
No, I gotta be in the fucking circle to do it.
Oh, yay, yay.
Too many instructions.
Yeah, it really is.
I'll get it.
I'm gonna get an X here.
No, I got it.
All right.
Smooth it out.
I got it.
Got it.
Come on.
Okay, I'm fine.
Shit.
That's the whole reason for the stunt to be here in the first place.
Dude, I went too fast.
Slow down.
I can't believe it.
I'll get it.
Come here.
Please.
Okay, here we go.
Close to the explosion.
I thought I was going too fast.
It's all right.
I can do it between now.
Every now and then, I went too fast.
I fucking hate that part.
Oh, damn it.
I gotta...
I'm playing Simon Says with cars.
Come on.
I can't touch it.
I can't touch the fucking thing.
Even touch the tire.
I...
That's dumb.
I'm being so careful.
Trying to get it right.
I just want to hit the helicopter.
I don't care about anything else.
Just let me hit the helicopter.
I don't care.
Hit the helicopter.
Get it.
No.
I'm all right.
No, you motherfucker.
Don't come here.
No.
I just want to hit the fucking helicopter.
I don't care.
Just give me the fucking helicopter.
Thank God.
I'm finally out.
It's worse than before.
It's fine.
I'll be...
I don't want to see the...
Yes, I'll find it.
I think you get to play as Batman.
That's a good question.
Probably never.
But when it's cut up like that,
it looks way cooler than my panic screams.
What is this car made out of to be able to handle that?
This is going to be a fun one.
I can already tell.
Now you'll double for Commander Black,
protecting a strike force convoy when they're ambushed by the mercs.
A challenging line starts with you hitting two motorcycles at the exact same time,
which will make them both explode.
Then immediately throw a 180,
and quickly line up so you can avoid the semi that's speeding straight for you.
Once you've passed the semi,
you're left to take out the next bike.
Okay, it's Commander Black time.
If you've been holding any mojo back,
you better show it now.
I'm going to get hit by the truck.
200,000.
Let's see if I can get it.
Three, two, one, action.
Take out the motorcycle.
I missed one.
I was so focused on...
Take out the motorcycle.
Get it together.
One, action.
Right straight ahead.
Take out the motorcycle.
Damn it!
Can I still get him?
Take out the vehicle.
Pass under it.
What?
What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to do here?
Redo, redo, redo it.
Restart, restart, restart, restart, restart.
I thought that was the end.
Three, two, one.
Take out the motorcycle.
Perfect.
All right, let's make it happen.
Take out the vehicle.
Pretty good.
Take out the motorcycle.
Come here.
No!
Fuck!
I got it!
That was times 42.
Unfortunately, that sucks.
It's all right.
I'll take it.
Scorpion and watch.
And a five-star replay.
Let's check it out.
That's so bad.
That's not even a stunt.
I'm just actually fucking murdering those guys.
This is so lukewarm at the end here, though, really.
I don't...
You can't edit this to make this look any better.
They kept that wide shot.
That's like...
That's the awkward shot.
It's on there for a little too long.
That's funny.
A couple more scenes.
Behind enemy lines.
In this scene, you'll play as Commander Black, escaping another ambush.
The highlight is the use of nitrous to aid your getaway.
There's a tricky line after your second burst of speed.
You'll smash into the back of a merc buggy, knocking it into the air.
Then pass beneath the collapsing silo before it falls
and immediately let off the gas so you can drift hard left and stay on the road.
All right, let's go.
240,000.
Three...
Two...
One...
Action!
Good.
That was good.
Overtake the dune buggy.
I didn't...
What the hell?
Not fast enough.
It's a dune buggy.
I did it.
I technically still did it.
Through the siloooooooooooooo!
You gotta be quick on this one.
Am I fast enough?
I gotta go all the way to the left, all the way to the left. Explosion. Good. Gate. Got him. Kill. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Too fast. Too fast. Too fast. Too fast. In between dune buggies.
Ah, didn't count. Didn't count. That was pretty good so far. That was pretty good.
Okay. Explosion. Hurry. Ooh. Tight. Scrape. I'm gonna miss it. No! Not again! I don't know where to press the button.
Ah, shit. It's so easy just to get thrown off the rails in this game. I get that start pretty good. Oh fuck, I forgot!
Alright, scrape. Why is that stupid thing there? The bus is just in the fucking way. Why is the bus there? What the hell do they have a bus there for? It's just in the way.
I think it's not good enough. No. No, no, no, no. No more twos. I'm not doing it. Not good enough. It's gotta be this thing.
Is that part of the bus? Do I have to go around the bus? Cause I can't go through it. Same deal. Go. Nitrous.
He's going just too damn fast. It's too fast. You go out of control. Use nitrous. Stop using nitrous. Oh, you're going 180? Ah, it's alright. You'll figure it out.
I'm so mad right now. That one guy on the bike. He goes so far to the left. Okay, let's go. Whatever.
Three! Yes, I'll take it. He killed him in the air. That was horrible. Let's see it. You go too fast, too slow, too fast, too slow. When you go too fast, something like that happens.
I missed this guy, I think. I don't think I hit him. No, yes I do. The motorcycle. Was the motorcycle on top of my car? Yeah, that's the guy I missed. I missed him twice.
I tried to swipe him, tried to swipe him, and then I just took it all out on his friend, apparently. Final scene. Here we go. Final conflict.
I'm going to flip four times.
I do this in parking lot all the time. No, I see what you guys are doing here. You just say that for every single stunt. Alright, so just do a roll. Sounds easy enough. Yeah, that's pretty self-explanatory. Yeah, I got it.
After you're airborne, you'll smash through a watchtower mid-spin. When you land, veer to the left and get back on the main road and continue the run.
That's it? That's all you have to explain? It's great that they do all this, but then there's 20 or 30 other stunts in the middle of this whole thing that he doesn't even talk about. It's a secret.
325,000. That's a pretty big score. It'll never get old. It really won't, really. I actually did that by a hair. Hurry up. U-turn again. Oh, uh-oh, not fast enough. No, it wasn't.
Dude, oh! Did I get it? Smash the pipe! Not bad. That was as good as you could do. That it? Perfect. Is that not five stars? That's three stars. Alright, that's like a times 20 or times 30, didn't it?
Why don't we take a look? First try. That's the first time I've done a first try. Felt pretty good. Felt pretty good. That was way more impressive than just going through it. Landing on it and then driving off of it. I went flying. That guy wasn't even looking.
The guy forgot to say, and go! Start firing! Be part of the scene, man! They didn't even know I was coming. That was really good. I'll take it. Alright, here comes the turn.
And the fate of the world hangs in the balance. Who answer the call? We come in peace. Blazing the trail of justice in a land of corruption and terrorists at the foreign corners of the globe.
Bring me the weapons or I kill the hostages. This nation has nowhere else to turn. If those newts reach American soil, we'll all be glowing. They are their only hope. See you in hell.
The guy that narrates the movies in the movies?
That was the second time somebody went through the glass.
There you go. What up next is? Here are some odd jobs. Armor All. Let's do the Armor All commercial.
Wait, why?
No, after your car is nice and clean, drive into other cars. Armor All. That doesn't sound like something I should be doing.
It's a metaphor, I get it.
It's just a metaphor.
I remember getting very distraught over this mission as a kid.
There's a lot of hard turns.
It's a lot of left, left, left, left. Scrape. No. More drifting. Ok, I got it.
Let's all go to drift.
That was alright. Ooh, I still got it.
That was a pretty cool stunt.
This one's tough.
Yeah, you do kind of have to nail it.
Turn left. Scrape the vehicle.
One. Action.
It's that scrape that's hard to get.
Turn left. Scrape the vehicle.
Hit the boxes.
Watch out. Big drift here.
All the way around from the car.
What? That was not a drift through there?
And cut.
I really felt like it did that.
I was drifting into it.
Three. Two. One. Action.
Too slow.
If anything that was like too fast.
It's okay. In. In. In. In.
I don't care.
I want to see what's in front of me.
What are you talking about?
So it's one, two, three.
Save the slow mo for the replay.
You don't have to show me from the cameraman's perspective.
I want to see it from my perspective.
Hit the jump.
That one's going to get me every time.
Damn it.
This one's got me.
It does. It's got me.
It's better.
Shit. One more.
That's it. What?
Strike the truck?
I thought I had to jump.
Oh no. No.
No. No.
Three. Two. One.
Action. Strike the truck.
Damn it.
I was so focused on doing all this I forgot that it's part two.
It's alright.
Oh no. No. No.
No. No. No.
I'm losing it.
Jump through the gap.
Blasphemy is so much of a pain in the ass.
I agree.
One. Two.
One. Action.
Strike the truck.
Hit the jump.
Don't strike it. Armor off.
Be gentle. Strike the side of the truck.
I want that guy
fired on the sim.
That guy will never work another day again in Hollywood.
Neither will that person.
Again.
That's...
I have to slide
into that fucking guy.
And I don't even know when he comes out.
Hit the jump.
One. Action.
Pain in the ass.
Strike the truck.
Strike the truck. Strike the truck. Strike the truck.
That's bullshit.
Unbelievable.
You've got to be kidding me.
There's no...
I can't even believe that happened.
I have no...
It's fine.
I can't let it bother me.
One. Action.
I'm not going to let it bother me.
I'm good.
One. Action.
Very.
Strike.
Which one?
Okay, I did it.
There were a lot of trucks to pick from there.
Three hundred and forty.
These commercial ones are much harder than the base game.
It's a nice game.
Replay.
Sometimes it just seems like the elements are out to get your car.
That's why there's armor.
Tireshines for the wheels.
Washing wax for the exterior.
And protecting wipes for the inside.
They'll give your car that
armor-all protection to make sure it
looks its best and stays that way.
Armor-all.
Stare.
Go ahead.
That was definitely one of the employees of this game company.
So if you have like
a twenty-nine to thirty-one second spot,
definitely make sure that you have
a twenty-nine to thirty second
voiceover line.
That was eleven seconds of dialogue.
Or just
make it a fifteen second commercial.
You can't
get some marketing guy to write
an extra few lines.
You waited way too long.
Alright, there's one more here. I feel like this is going to be very hard.
Navigate through the course.
Crashing through each crate and passing under the semis.
The trick is knowing how to
control your drifts on the ice.
And keep your eye out for those under the
semi-stunts. They'll be tough marks
to hit.
Jump right off the bat.
Only a hundred thousand. This is not that long.
Only a hundred thousand points.
Boy oh boy.
This is gonna be
one that I
probably don't do.
I can't go slow though.
You don't have to go that fast. I can drive with it.
This one's not long. I can do it.
To recite this word more
in this video later.
Yeah, I may play the same thing
like a thousand times. I can't talk.
I can't talk.
Nope. Nope. That's it.
No, it's not. Oh my god.
I'm gonna be stuck here.
Just slow it down. Don't have to go fast.
My tongue was out of my mouth that whole time.
No. I have to beat it. I have to.
I can't not do this.
I'm gonna turn the voice off.
I think I have to disable voice for this.
Don't go out of bounds. It's the ice.
Holy god.
Oh, that sucks.
That really sucks.
Going through that second semi, you gotta go fast
enough and then there's the ice right there. You gotta...
I give up.
What the fuck?
You gotta go really fast through that
last screen. You have to
lead that target too.
I have to drive in a straight
line like 200 feet in front of that semi.
I can do it.
Excuse me?
It didn't go fast
enough. I can't even get
through the first one anymore.
That's
insane.
That's insanity.
You just gotta get lucky to do this one.
I'll do it after like another
200 attempts.
There we go.
I can see it in chat and it's fucking
messing me up.
Stop spamming. It hurts my eyes.
That's bullshit. I fucking drifted.
I can't...
I'm gonna have a fucking meltdown from this one.
You wanted
a meltdown? You might get one soon.
I don't know how much longer I can
handle this as a human.
Oh, please.
He's
under the semi. He's gotta control
this drift. I had
it too. That was the end. That's the turnaround.
What a good break from playing
the regular game to do like this
hard bullshit levels.
This ain't even a commercial.
I'm drifting in there. I am.
How do you expect somebody
to do that?
I'm drifting. And if I drift too much, I just
fly out of the goddamn playing area.
What are you on about,
game? How do you expect me to do
that? Oh my god!
Oh my god!
You see what I'm saying?
You see what I'm talking about, right? You understand.
You get it. You guys get
me. You do. You get me.
I know you guys always got my back.
I love just looking over here and just seeing everybody's
got my back here.
This music playing over and over again
too is not helping.
Hey! What?
I turned it off.
Uhhhh!
Why?
It's so hard.
I gotta get it. I will. Eventually
it'll happen. Didn't even give me
them. It's actually
impossible. It's impossible to do that. It's
not possible to do that last semi.
I don't think it is. I think this is a developer joke.
That's a developer joke.
Because you have to drift
out of that. And then
you can't straighten up yet. There's no
way. It's not possible.
It's a fucking developer joke. I'm gonna try
this one more.
I get further the quieter
this frame.
He's very
Two. One. Action.
He jumps on the trailer, then
down to the ice below.
Can he hit everyone?
Two. One.
Action. He jumps on the trailer,
then down to the ice below.
Can he hit everyone?
One. Action.
He jumps on the trailer,
then down to the ice below.
Can he hit everyone?
He's gotta
control this drift. Can he make it
under the semi?
Can he hit every
One.
One. Action.
He jumps on the trailer, then
down to the ice below.
Can he make it under the
semi? Can he hit
everyone?
The one. Action.
He jumps on the trailer, then down to the ice below.
Can he hit everyone?
The one. Action.
ice below I can't I can't change the language change one action he jumps on
the trailer then down to the ice below can he hit everyone and under the semi
he's gotta control this drift can he make it under the semi can he hit
everyone under another semi watch this 180
I can't believe it okay hey welcome to Stuntman ignition conceivable unbelievable irreplaceable
irredeemable Spencer thanks for the five community subs thanks for the five subs
I'm cool I'm normal I'm fine I'm just a normal streamer hey welcome to the stream
thank you but no it's just a thanks with five subs Spencer welcome only four
stars I ain't doing that shit again no way I did get a five-star replay so let
me actually I can't even wait there's no sound I can't change it cream corn
thanks for the five subs enjoy this the soundless replay I can feel it I
imagine missing that turn the 180 at the end I was just barely almost out of the
range there that would have been terrible I would have been so mad all
right well that's all we can do now let's go back to the other game there is
one more odd job and looks like this two or three other I think I'm just gonna
beat this game well I'm just gonna beat the game tonight I think that's what's
gonna happen all right I need to turn the voice back on no no no not the voice
the what was it 60 everything at 60 put the music at like 40 60 60 60 50 music
at 40 that's fine music something else the music's kind of annoying music and
replay only voice a hundred no I heard the overdrive this looks like an
ambulance one or a firefighter one
okay overdrive is a street crime movie set in today's San Francisco okay it's
one of those throwback movies to the 70 exploitation films bombs car chases
afros hot chicks windsurfing space shuttle okay you kind of get where I'm
going with this we're gonna go big with this one we might as well even just call
the movie super big and awesome but it's not gonna fit on a poster okay all right
you're gonna be doubling for our hero stone okay all right now I want you got
to be tough but not leather tough like steel chainmail tough okay you get where
I'm going with this hey do you want to you what do you want to mint a sandwich
something like that can we get this guy a sandwich okay now this thing is gonna
be real lo-fi okay we're not gonna do any space-age crap okay we're not doing
that no lasers on the car no kangaroos that no Spanish okay that sounds like
the smash mouth leads there really unsafe with insane stunts as many as you can squeeze
together into one run okay so you get behind the wheel I'll get behind the
camera and hey guys let's have some freaking fun out there okay where is
that freaking sandwich I'm never gonna hire family again I'll tell you what
don't ever do it kid all right okay let's talk about what you'll be facing
an overdrive kid character wise you'll mostly split your time between the loose
cannon cop stone and the ruthless drug lord Varga we'll have you in one scene
with a bulky fire engine that can cause serious damage two scenes with stones
custom-made muscle car the claw cool two scenes on a high-powered street bike
and one with the MVX Spartan a European sports I like that one the films said in
San Francisco with lots of steep hills and tight alleyways
Rodina was known for pushing the envelope in his action scenes so you'll
have your hands full with some complicated lines including a great
scene on a cargo ship and a massive jump from a parking garage roof that ends
with you smashing into a helicopter excited yet come on let's get to work
Rodina wants to start with the movies final chase you'll double for Vargas in
a hijacked firetruck there's a tricky line that starts with a drift left why
do I know what you mean the drift smooth you said this guy's sounds like
he's speaking from SUV as you exit the alleys other end then turn left plow
through the gas station and hit the semi I know what you mean by this crash to
stop the back end of the trailer not the middle it's that way you'll turn the
trailer and keep barreling forward
I smashed into that that was a smash
I told you I was not having this thought
this is like going from toad to Bowser I play all I play with toad and Kuba
turbo I don't play with Donkey Kong Bowser and this is why I like that's
like 2,000 hours in Mario Kart and now you make me play fucking
good
another drift fucker don't get angry don't say the upward again it's too far
away what how am I getting X's I want to see that again I need to see this is
all this is just GTA it really is it's just oh I took I took a fire ambulance
look at me I'm just gonna hold down R2 what you do excuse me do you think I'm
funny I've got it I'm gonna spray you I'm gonna spray you with the thing so
what I don't know I drove close to it why did I get too close you missed the
dumpster you're as big as the hallway you're as big as that you're I'm as big
as that thing is tall I just know why you know I'm saying how is that even
possibly good scrape it I didn't oh I thought killer that's a scrape how is
that not counted as great like this that's the end of the oh shit that's the
end of the mission I'm dumb I thought I screwed something up this is makes me
want to play GTA 5 and just drive around in the fire truck whenever I do the
casino stream my car of choice will be the fire truck notorious all right is
the muscle car in this scene you'll double for stone in the Claudine chasing
a gang member through the city a key stunt is the trolley overtake you'll
drift hard left next to the stadium then take a jump onto the main street that'll
get you to the trolley tracks really guess it so you can pass the first
trolley then turn quickly to the right to avoid crashing into the second trolley
head-on I just I smell like heat I don't smell bad I don't I'm not like don't
smell bad I smell like warm like heat my body is just emanating just fire
425 thousand
you're going the wrong you stopped me
little alley turns and not gonna be gonna be like I just like knocked it out
of his hands move where's the horn oh no change it back through the gap
hard right overtake the trolley got it why did you crash Diana that guy did not
need to crash I he just drove into the fucking pole there was no chaos there
was no problem there was no I didn't I wasn't creeping up on him he just did
that I was on I'm still making up time what a bad angle of that is for a bad
camera angle you got I got there before you did oh I'm gonna I got there before
like where's your cue I got there before you just it's alright there's so many
points for what yes I know I'm arguing with a video my mother used to go into
my fuck that my mother used to come into my bedroom and just ask me who I was
talking to because I'd be like this is ridiculous I can't even understand it
like I would be having a full conversation you did it again mother
fucker honey who are you talking to huh no no full conversation you've done
fucking fuck you ruined it you ruined it I didn't do anything I just was trying
to get through told me to jump off the ship sorry I didn't say Simon Says you
lose Jeremy I got it still okay now you want me to turn this way yeah that was
the car that was there for a tenth of a second and then exploded
three I'll take it don't skip great car chase I don't think we've seen the other
car there it is it's me it's happened so frequently that I just assumed that
that was me past that guy by the way past that guy to on the on the right go
around him just go around him why can't you do that why don't you have an 11
millisecond response time long two stars is unacceptable three to four is
the bike one yeah I love the bike there's so much fun now you'll double for Varga
on his bike escaping a sting operation this scene happens right before he
hijacks the fire truck in Big Red the challenge here gap between two cars move
quickly to the ramp and jump the trolley aim your landing to overtake the cop
after you hit the ground then top it off by sliding under the low-flying
helicopter this all happens very quickly so it's gonna be about that's a really
hard left bad what that was good I couldn't control
okay I don't want to hold on I think you see what happens
ready that doesn't it doesn't matter it doesn't just kill you
action through the gap cleaner than action through the gap trolley red the
needle well still got it in here I go geez into the trolley wheelie sorry why
am I apologizing I'm sorry guys cut me off I'm sorry I got it I can do it
oh shit where where's the next part
where did it all go so wrong I didn't get hit by that which I
almost did and then what happens that's this is fine that was done fine where
does this go so wrong
oh sorry screaming there's too much but really though how are you supposed to go
up there go through the window in the jump leads you right into the wall okay
oh hold on okay I'm gonna try this again
over the trolley over the trolley come on that can't take on the left it's
all right I still get three stars good really I get it I didn't know I had to
do that did it what window I have to move on I have to get out of here before I die
that's slumping back into the seat because I got you getting an accident
and the accident doesn't make you fall off the bike just delayed reaction a
few seconds later you fall backwards you just pass out from the extreme
stress of the situation but you can't believe you're still alive and you faint
I didn't get it I've made that on the back tire though where's the panic try
to do the objective is coming up here go through the trolleys oh shit I'm gonna
just hurt myself to do this here it comes what was that I made it through
though I may have like skinned my whole body but I made it through I hope that
makes it into the trailer please have one of those make it into the trailer
you know this AI in the algorithm here is gonna pull a random scene with
something like that happens it's gonna be so funny in this scene you'll play
stone again as he's ambushed by SUV driving hit squads the feature stunt
will be a reverse 180 getaway you'll turn into a narrow alley then two SUVs
will block your path slam on the brakes and reverse back the way you came as you
enter the main street spin the car all the way around so you can drive forward
into the next alley and escape your pursuers you know what Rodino said
about making stone tough this is your last shot to give him some balls
pre-rendered a million points this is the real deal
oh I thought I had to turn right apparently not for the glass what I got
it yep the gap yeah I did it nope don't happen not happening
then I go too high no he knocked me over action was do that's not bad I got
did you see what happened that guy watch this replay the first car and that was
explosion they can't be a human in there watch how fast this gets ripped off the
screen beginning wasn't that bad that was bad placement their RNG placement
where that was gonna land physics-based what oh that was good
tell I wanted to go right there but yeah there that yeah I'll take that over the
original should get some style points there three three three this is called
snitch this scene happens at the start of the movie when stone chases down a
bike pump who's hopped up on Vargas new drug you'll double for the pump the key
to this run is another well-timed slide after a hard drift right you'll
accelerate up a steep street and pass close to a police car then you'll slide
to dodge beneath another cop car as it comes over the hill and flies straight
toward you the vehicle could take your head off so be careful and make sure you
trying to do that though
this one sounds hard
oh shit
hey oh well I didn't even like see it all right
I don't
it's okay you gotta go you gotta hug the left side
good physics made no sense there
the person's still in there what what
tells me that should not have been like that
I fell down like four times like that view
I'll fix it
nothing about that seemed correct thank you gnarly for the five minute subs
came in right there a minute ago thank you gnarly five subs bring to the final
mission of overdrive how do I get four on this and not four on this one or this
one all right this is the super fast car in this scene you'll play a stone whose
commandeered Vargas is prized European sports car the MVX Spartan the major
stunt comes at the end you'll shoot across two rooftops then take a huge jump
and smash into a helicopter in mid-flight you'll need to gun it going
into your first jump or you won't have enough speed make sure you're lined up
and throttle it hard the rest of the way trust me kid pull this off and you'll
have some serious bragging rights
let's go whoa what now what now what
holy shit
I get it shit that ain't gonna happen
what happened in the beginning so it's go back and then do a 180 but then what
and then turn back around that's holy shit this car's fast hence I'm ready
let's do it I thought I was gonna keep going
whatever
I'm missing this whole thing here go back go glue it up all right let's go
reverse through under the semi guys through again
I'm not flipping that SUV I'm just touching my god use action I got it
okay in the helicopter or is it me I don't know if that was me or not did I
fall out I can't I'm sorry it's not enough it's not good enough it's not good
I can't live without one action one action I'm sorry god damn it one action
semi's right here good technically that was a drip move please
don't lose it here I missed it it's gonna land on me it's better all right
that should be three stars
my back is so itchy there's like bugs all over me
come on they didn't show up on a map it doesn't show up on the goddamn screen
it's not gonna this is not gonna be three stars on a thousand years all right
string it now start now please that's it yes that has to be it
times 38 that's it how was that less than the last time I don't how was that
less than last time 325 what what I can't that was going so well that was
going so well I'm so fucking mad right now what happened I need to see look at
what a great start I strung together everything and then the game just
decided to flip me what happened that's great though that's great TV but it's
not good enough I'm gonna try this one more time I'll live with action that's
the bane of my existence this one's the bane of my entire existence that little
tiny hallway I want to flip that guy come on you idiot I can still do it no
I can't fucking taxi you piece of shit you ruined everything you ruin
everything every time dumb taxi why are you here you don't have a purpose I'm
just in the way why is he I don't can I call the director and say can you move
that fucking taxi
it's again okay we're good the string didn't stay how I did it so good
oh shit okay it's not enough it's not enough to do this but it's more less
poison than before all right that's it I'm done after this I don't care this
one's too hard times 28 come on don't do it don't do it no I hate that part it's
so fucking finicky you're going you're going off of like 500 miles per hour and
I have to drift into like a toilet bowl no way you can do that perfectly
okay what happened to the string just go just don't drift do something
coming crazy come on keep the strength come on 50 60 60 70 oh no I hate it
I wasn't going fast oh okay I have to get out of here I'm gonna have a real
meltdown it's gonna happen I didn't think it was gonna happen tonight but
it might I just I have it so close it's so close guys it's so close to me like
more than three don't worry it's everything's fine just remember every
time you're about to have a meltdown about like a ten-year-old video man
remember you're 33 you know it's like not properly so I'm fine everything's
fine you know I'm like I'm in my 30s you know you don't do that well I didn't get
the right piece of candy at the candy store everything's fine I'm a grown man
grown men don't get angry at things like this they get they get they did they
worry about like taxes and there's a gap where it's not really feasible to keep
the string going there drive me I know you have to drive near cars but when I
had okay so this taxi right here right there's an explosion and then I I'm
driving close to this car driving close to this car and then check this out got
it doesn't matter just keep going you get points for running people over
nothing out there was nothing for me to string together to fucking 95 let's
watch I'm gonna go like scream and he's stone and he's a tough cop with an
attitude
and he's after this man Varga a vicious drug lord with a sick taste of violence
pretty kitty when the new designer drug gristle hits the streets the death toll
rises daily one man's rage can only boil for so long
till he explodes
bloody fists and a few marble short stuff will stop at nothing to get barged
off the streets forever it's loose cannon versus loose
cannon instead one man fall that didn't happen don't do drugs
overdrive rated R pretty rendered pretty rendered all right that was fun that
was cool this next one is called never kill me again and then we have night
Avenger we also have this final job here which is delivery commercial this is a
commercial for tick-tock delivery service you'll be driving through the
set of aftershock and taking out the competitor delivery trucks along the
way the concept is that even in the midst of a volcanic eruption tick-tock
delivers on time your big stunt is the pipe ramp keep in mind this is a heavy
vehicle so it'll take longer for the truck to rotate in the air land
straight then continue your run through the ravaged town tick-tock master
freight hundred and ten thousand two one action
straight the truck
great this one too oh too much first
cut no mistakes next time oh there's a huge huge turn but I have to be careful
three two one action
scrape the truck drift turn right I get the first three two one action
great the truck oh come on I'm over it come on great the truck
yeah I'm here and scrape it easy this one great
yes this thing's sloppy fucking are the trucks great the truck great great the
truck come on which one I didn't even know I thought it was one in front of
me I thought it was the one that was in front of me
two one action
scrape the truck
oh fuck did it that wasn't that bad actually and that's a wrap boys and
girls we've got ourselves a commercial that has been okay right three let's
watch it commercial when you need to ship a
package in today's chaotic world you have a lot of options but there's only
one delivery service that knocks its competitors right off the map only one
service with a worldwide network of experienced drivers giving you unmatched
customer service speed and reliability so whether it's raining cats dogs or
giant chunks of lava
anytime warranty ship around the clock with tick-tock
you know you had a couple of you too many lines you could have deleted a few
of them and tighten it up so you don't have to overlap okay we have two more
movies to do never kill me again and Night Avenger what do you say we get
stuck
world-renowned director of never kill me again this is the 14th spy movie in this
series and you are thinking oh how easy we will slop together some explosions
and boobies and fancy gadget cars and not have to think but you are wrong we
will have these things we put such a naughty point we will revolutionize the
series with a post post-modern mise-en-scne we will delve into the inner
psyche of our hero outside he is shooting wristwatch missiles avoiding
crotch table saws making big-breasted women moan with animal pleasure but
inside he is spitting at the gods despairing over the absurdity of
existence this bar I know I know you are thinking oh this is a spy blockbuster I
do not see how you can make it out that is because you are a simple man who
lives by his calloused gorilla hands and not his mind no offense okay out of my
office you bore me bring in my art director tell her I want to finger
paint I need to be inspired I don't know if you got this from mr. pretentious
this is a spy movie with a giant fan base in this first scene you'll double
for Simon crown he was gonna do the same thing twice Chinese base to confront a
rival spy the feature stunt happens on a bridge take out a couple cars then take
the ramp onto the bridge railing the trick is to keep yourself mostly
parallel to the railing when you jump don't go too fast or turn too sharp on
the railing overshoot and crash into the ravine
okay people welcome to my set if you did not come to make out go back home to
your miserable little lives yeah you do all right three two one snow James Bond
close to the explosion over there if the shoots over it's up one action play
James Bond in the background like that like I felt all the way oh shit oh dear
I've made a couple of mistakes like I'm gonna be a little bit over here
goodbye close to the semi not under the semi you got it
jump so two 180s in a row
everywhere it's all right
okay that seems like it was a cross up there
all right part of me thinks I'm playing an action game
turn the fucking motorcycle left gotta go so much more action
and I didn't even get it I didn't even get it unbelievable why I have to go
faster
stupid-ass no I the snow just killed it's like times 10
action you land on the snow and you may as well just drift into the fucking wall
I'm holding that one part right there to delete it from him action delete that
part from the game like fucking shave that off
Wow he hit me directly with that 180 in the snow 180 in the snow through the gap
180 in the snow don't go too fast oh shit the box
that wouldn't even that bad that wouldn't even that bad that wouldn't
even that bad three with two X's that hit someone that's weird see right it I
barely that director commentary here while I was on this bike I had almost no
control of this the director actually told me just close your eyes when you do
this part because you may as well it's gonna be the same thing whether or not
you open or close your eyes so I was like yeah you know that makes sense he's
such a great director though oh I love him he's so smart he's one of those real
smart directors
chasing the enemy spy through the base we've got a great stunt plan near the
missile silo when the explosion blocks the path between you and the lead you
turn and go back the way you came the platform above you will collapse
creating a ramp dead here the falling platform throw another with a 180 drive
up the ramp to the second level try not to lose speed in your turn so you can
avoid the falling road keep up with the lead you're gonna rush this guy spy if
you manage to give them I assure you just Mario jump he just super Mario one
jumped in the air do you want me to do scrape my gun huh holy I did it I did
that I buried that was so I did it perfectly I did that I'm so that's of
anything I did that shit you saw my wheels go up my wheels went down going
faster than the other actor I was looking at you now you'll get over here
get over here my god land guardrail good good start good start under what here
oh that's very hard you should have said very hard oh no it's gonna collapse on
me I didn't know when they're gonna come up it's you gotta like trial and error
play the match fucking ten times before you know what to do yeah right yeah
right miss not happening I'm so much of a better actor I can drive so much faster
than both of you land good all right I'm good this next part sucks good I hit
the 180s why you here why here comes up on you too quickly and all these sounds
I'm gonna lose my fucking mind in here guys you know what no he's coming right
out of three no I don't want to have a load again
sorry give me three attempts and that's it I promise three attempts and we're
done no bullshit either every attempt is an attempt even if like oh I fucked up
right here no every attempt is an attempt three
attempts to get to three stars every attempt is an attempt my god I that's
one that's one that's it that's one no I'm done after the two more of these
inside that little area it's so hard to get like a drift you have what amounts
to like a studio apartment to fucking turn around I just forgot that was even
here oh fuck object to smash drift I'm trying to keep the string going oh I
fucking my mouse just fell down that's so hard to get in the right spot man
that's too hard to do that you need to be so precise shit this is the last one
on a dime like that shit right you dumb motherfucker just ruined everything this
was decent it was a decent run you blew everything you'll never work in
Hollywood again it's alright this is possible still there's no fucking way I
don't think anyone can do that no one how do you drift turn into that and go
up on two wheels and do this fuck that level next you'll double for crown as
he chases his rival over a frozen lake there's a tricky line as you exit the
base jump onto the roof then keep gunning it as you make the second jump
over the base wall soon as you land hit your nitrous switch and speed through
the narrow pass ending with a big jump over ravine you'll be going too fast for
big turns so pick your line early and only make small adjustments not
complete it didn't finish right through here Jesus around again in a circle
through here in ice fucking ice I'm not even controlling the car
dude oh boy all right all right slow down don't go that fast I'm gonna be
drifting all over the place now what what it's nice it's slippery it's
slippery I technically did it it's all right I I did it I technically drifted
in the right spot I wouldn't be that bad I can't talk now where down here I got a
bolt of this turn I'm still in a turn dude it's so slippery oh thank you for
saving me guy just like going sledding nobody I don't have any control of this
car I could take like one or two ice levels you can't have a whole zone based
around ice levels I'm sorry I just want to finish the damn thing trying oh you've
got to be fucking kidding me you've got to be kidding me that's just that's
angering no matter how you say it I top that's it's infuriating no matter how
you look at it I went faster on the rebound there than I did in holding down
acceleration and snow this is a Mario maker loving this is I played this one
already and I'm not gonna lie I really think I could control a car better than
this in real life on a full ice lake it's like they dialed up the slipperiness
by like six hundred percent just paved the fucking road can I get a road paver
who drives around on snow like this no one does this not even in the movies
they drive on roads we're driving down a mountain this no one drives on this I
want to bring up the something that somebody said earlier they said this
level made them quit the game forever I can see why that happened 14 year old
fucking version of that guy whoever you were it's a bug on my fucking eye it
really is I wish face game is on a fly just like landed in my eyeball it's in
my mouth that's it I did it I had to have done it
god I did action you were too far away launches me further then I can launch
myself
done truck come on keep going I can feel it in my body when it happens this just
like I'm not turning the car all right here we go
you can't turn I gotta go slower over that you can't turn the car I wish you
could play this I wish you got give this to you right now so you'd be like oh
shit okay I get it I see what you mean by that just you play it just take it for
a second you'll see and you're gonna be like oh fuck man yeah this sucks asshole
and then I'll be like I know right man we go like yeah like high five let us
click that was bullshit this just wasn't fair I went too fast this time let it go
off the fucking rails here how do you do that how is it I do I should have
failed that that's why this game don't make no sense I should have failed
right there but I didn't okay here we go okay I have to be like on the right
side I did all the actions I did every action I did I could be here I can sit
here and just be like I believe but what the fuck my stupid hard games fucking
dip no let's do it let's just hang out you know trying to get together you
know 33 now so I can't fly off the fucking handle anymore
I killed the camera I just want to get out of this part I just want to be out
of this level in particular don't bump me I'm the stuntman enough speed please
okay here we go was that enough speed I'm trying not to go so fast yeah no it's
insane you have to you could you can't turn so even if I try to turn the car
even a little it doesn't I have to go in the same the car can't be the car can't
be turned so you have to be but you need speed it's harder than secure how many
attempts is this how many times did I do the final boss in secure 57 this is like
attempt number like 30 or 40 at least right and why did I didn't land in the
box I guess cleaning in now you got I got gamer neck right now I'm leaning in
deep with like a tilted crushed like Brockas Sora's neck punch it please I
don't care okay all right all right all right all right all right
stegosaurus neck I don't want to see it I don't want to see it again anything
else with that I want to see that again we need a face cam I'm sure it wasn't
sweating
next level is worse next to where I had I hated this one next one is worse next
one's worse
as a chopper smashes into it fire missiles at the clips and knock some
glaciers into grounds okay 180 on ice too much too I can't imagine making
these levels even playing them and being like yeah people will like this this is
good anybody in the studio have any fucking hair left oh no it's all patchy
everyone's like ripped it all out that's fine this damn movie hey your
movie sucks this thing's gonna flop day one no no no no no no no way not
possible I don't know I'm gonna try to do it anymore
that's just not possible no one can do that I don't think anybody could what
were they thinking that's not fair man that's not fair it really isn't I just
want to get to the end of this visit level I'm gonna do whatever it takes to
just get like 10 points who cares no what a spy would not drive on ice he
would get a fucking ice pick goggles and a ski mask and he would climb the damn
mountain and bring a tent and shit and that's how we would infiltrate that's
how we would get away because he'd be smart he wouldn't be stupid and drive
like 80 on fucking ice James Bond didn't do this it was smarter than that and why
is your entire base made out of ice where is this supposed to be where it
why is this here there's a base here nobody can try fun yeah even they can't
drive on the setting of Goldeneye gold he's the keys the ski jumper whatever
the fuck the things are called he used a snowmobile he didn't use a streetcar I'm
you have to go faster than this ship no fucking way you go that fast you ain't
gonna make it and a million years throw 180 yeah okay this is a developer joke
whole thing have to be ice the whole course Sonic racers didn't even have this
shit Mario Kart doesn't even have a level like this across the entire like 16
Mario Kart games cartoons don't even have this shit no I don't want to watch
it instant replay I want to like be out of this terrible terrible very awful bad
place I'm waiting for like the guy to come out of the closet with a camera hey
we just want to let you know we got you our streamers get bad that whole ice
level the whole thing was made from the ground up just to fuck with you really
no way yeah I mean it's such a dogshit level the whole thing so it's not real
look over there there's a camera over there too oh in the corner no way how
long has it been there for you know a few months oh okay we don't keep any
other footage that we've recorded don't worry please just get me to the end I
just please get me to the end of this level this not a chance and help that
you can do that what 180 and then reverse just want to get to the end I
just want to get to the end I don't care about anything I just want to get to the
end I just want to get to the end this doesn't look fun oh I can tell you with
a hundred percent certainty it isn't so don't worry about that it doesn't look
like that because it isn't touch play operation with the cars too what's up
with that oh worse manure you gotta play operation with the cars on ice put on
easy there are no difficulties of this game this only ice there's just ice
there's nothing on you got ice and then you got a car there's no other there's
only one difficulty it's ice has anybody completed this fucking game can I look
at like the global trophies have more people beat orphan that have done this
level I can't imagine fucking just playing this casually and then going
like well I'll never do this again like that guy like that one guy earlier all
right let this be like a game design 101 lesson for you guys this is how you get
people to break their discs you make a whole entire area based on slippery ice
in a driving game what is I want to know what the last mission is here does the
game uninstall itself after this part slowing down doesn't help because you
need to get there in a certain amount of time no operation oh my god no no
no no I'm gonna skip this level I would rather no nevermind I can't even I can't
even give you a reason to have this what's the last area what it has to be
like did they just go back to like formula this is out fucking rages
you can't imagine doing this on ps2 oh my god no way this there was a lot of sad
kids when this came out people were probably crying I imagine myself tears
screaming down my eyes crying as like at like 17 and whatever so the handbrake
just slides you across the whole entire map this is it for this month I'm
skipping this level I'll come back to it god just get up there how much how far
you have to reverse hey can I tell you this I'm bad at the game joke is and I
got four stars oh get out of here this bad at the game joking needs to stop
stop leave me alone I hope the next area is you run don't have a car I clearly
had no idea what I was doing here and that holy shit there's more oh no oh no
okay fresh start
no I'm gonna relax we're just gonna relax and I'm gonna get it done just
calm down and play right just play it that's all right nothing there's no
problem just relax that's all right it's okay I wasn't supposed to do that I'm
supposed to do it like that this one is just a mess okay no I'm fine scrape this
guy does he that he already got scraped actually did that all right I can do
this he was a ghost he was a ghost he was a ghost I had that too I actually
had that I didn't miss replay that all right let's go melt downstream melt
downstream melt downstream melt downstream that was two wheels wasn't
very long but it was two wheels oh that's fine I don't care what it is that
like the wise words of vault boy says good enough wise words I don't want to
see the replay either it's like across the room oh no no no no easy easy if I
accidentally click a few buttons I might stop screaming what was I trying to do
with this I don't remember all right this next one's a hovercraft this is the
final one wait did I just give myself a debuff a hundred percent more
slipperiness that's okay I got it we're gonna it's it's too light to cause
screams you know I mean I got it all out of me I'm not upset at anything and that
is a fun level I'm just gonna do it why the arrows are pointing in almost every
direction that's a jump on the wreckage up here oh hard very hard that one get
in that box and then inside the box unbelievable that's in the box whatever
just get in the box just get in the box just go into the box we still have one
more area after this and I'm I accepted with open arms the only way they would
make this worse was it was like anti-gravity like with the spaceship for
the next stunt so anti-climactic going over this every time okay almost there
all right into the box here we go line it up there we go that's it it's in that
was not even remotely as bad as that third level just watch the movie night
Avenger unlocked so the last area coming up I'm almost done with the game if this
movie has more than 12% on rotten tomatoes I'll eat a pair of shoes the
whole thing I'm gonna check it I'm not even in this movie yeah all right guys
enter the Avenger am I prepared for this hey kid Howard
right man look you know who I am that's my wall of fame work with everyone tell
him Mr. Wright has been directing since 67 he's incredible they call him mr.
Hollywood thanks Sarah you're a dog enough Sarah Jack coffee and ring Murphy
at pyramid Sarah go with it what is she anyway you've heard of night avenger
right huge comic book well we're making that fan screamed for it for years but
it was trapped in development hell when I told pyramid I wanted it they've shown
up with me I've got Murphy on the line sir great tell him I'll call him back in
40 seconds you've got a decent resume after shock overdrive whooping to ride
that Baxter screw up and his friends what a mess can't believe it grows 200
mil mr. Wrightman's last film gross 600 that's true sir she's great with numbers
wardrobe's got a problem latex suits sir too much well I just lost in snakes
versus my guy next to me my friend the jokes are fucking empty at moment I'm
sorry I'll make sure you're known as the best in the world let me down and well
Jack here he was directing summer blockbusters before he got on my bad
side but now we get along splendidly right Jack you're incredible mr.
Wrightman see you on set it's like we'll not rewind that like make it funnier
snake you've come in this first scene you'll double for night Avenger when he
spots Big Top's gang on a crime spree the focus stunt is an aerial gap through
the open doors of a helicopter jump across the rooftops fire your weapon then
get up to maximum speed to take the ramp oh after you've gapped through the
helicopter and land yeah you'll need to react quickly to avoid traffic and cross
to the other side of the street I get to wear the suit too nice I don't think I
could get angry here cuz I get to win I thought that was gonna happen much
earlier I thought I was gonna be this one here this other cop did it nominated
for an Emmy really that's so stupid you can't you try action
Avengers no I just barely made it I can't not a time what do I do that was
pretty cool I'm okay with two stars at the end tonight here let's watch that one
so I failed that one collectively come together and find out what
because you're bald oh all right yeah that makes sense
yeah like a college film what's next scene I was more like I love the bike
it is all right you'll double as Night Avenger again trying to stop Big Top
from killing the mayor the toughest stunt is early in the run take a sharp
left turn then line up to go beneath the semi trailer with enough speed to jump
over the cop cars right after then cross to the next stunt box and fire at Big
Top's henchmen and wipe them out did I tell you that I know Frank Jones the
leader of the camera he got most of his ideas from me did I tell you that I knew
okay I'm doing fine um what we talking about I'm right behind him I'm right
behind him I was going the right way and then you drop the cop car on me and it
didn't knock me off the bike and put me on the other side of the road honestly he
might just say at this point try not to die don't die careful don't die this
will kill you trying to kill you first attempt looked fantastic yeah
unfortunately see if they edited it up in post edited it edited it edited it
that is right that's correct somewhere is this Night Avenger or tactical
intervention they seem to share the same similarities here clown car now
you'll shoot the other side of the chase where Big Top is going after the mayor
this time you'll play Big Top the focus is a two-wheeling stunt you'll hit the
ramp with your driver's side as the tunnel bends to the left make sure
you're in control when you hit the ramp you're sliding all over the place you'll
mess up the stunt to wheel it through the zone and a pair of vehicles will fly
right over your head my character didn't lose all of his hair
one car fuck wait did he say you hit the mayor watch out you hit the mayor
what is he doing here it's a dangerous set man fucking usable but it's not my
stomach god damn it you keep that if you have the two or three days left of
principal photography we got like four hours left to close principal into the
city's water supply we take the fuck out of here come to the pier drift hard left
to fishtail and knock the police car into the water then speed along the
jump over the water and while you're airborne drop the bounce bomb drift
right when you land and continue your run watch out for the toys great the
police car but there was no turn
throwing overtake here you're supposed to be the best oh no you hit the mayor
again boomer reflexes it is exploding I did I did every I drove long ways
against the railing just restarted I went through it I've been in constant
fucking like laughter this constant stress this whole stream it's been just
if it's not like stomach stress from laughing it's just like I stress
constant comment oh there's not a okay I thought those water what oh into the
building into the building do we really do a wheelie
both the explosion I did all the ice cream truck where three last two levels
last for the campaign I think so the two back wheels there sloppy you could
probably five star on the first speed like I would destroy the first few
we'll see how much I've improved I'll go back and just do the first few let's go
only two remain this is with Batmobile and this is the both last two with the
Batmobile now you'll double as night Avenger chasing big top in the climax
this focus done is a jump onto elevated train tracks while you're on the roof
accelerate to crash into a big top helicopter and land on the L hit the
copter at an angle so you'll be prepared to turn right when you land
overtake the first train on the left side then veer to the right to avoid the
second oncoming train this is gonna this is gonna take a few tries I think
there's almost a million points you told me to kill that guy I what do you mean
I'm good let me see let me see it I can do it let me see if I can do it
let me see if I get enough speed going down I don't have to do it like I don't
have to do it like this why am I doing it the same way I did before here we go
fuck come on that had to be close that had to be close going through backwards
would be so awesome I can do it no it would do that that would be before
it's five minutes by this game is insane what I pressed it it has to happen
man oh god
Simpson's hit and run
I'm fucking getting trash bags
with the green shit all over the ground
3,2,1 action
good action
alright I'm good
perfect
five stars let's see it
oh fuck
I can make it I can make it I can make it
I'm still on I'm still on
I got it twice
oh no
I got it
seriously
look at how good this was
I was still on the track too I could have made it
or something
I cleaned this up good too look at this turn
that looks so nice
I got something to say
for all the stuff that Batman does
and all the crazy shit you see
and like oh in this
car racing movie
or this game or Batman
or Superman when he drives the super car
I don't even know if Superman has a car
he might
that would happen
probably
you're talking about like a 1% chance
or like a 0.5% chance
to do any of these things
even driving by this person in front of me
is like a 0.2% chance
that you'll actually do that
I'm surprised Batman's not been hit by more trains
it doesn't matter how good you are
at driving
going this 200 feet right here
not possible like no way
you will lose
Superman can fly
so what doesn't mean he doesn't have a car
what about Clark Kent
you think Clark Kent flies around
three, one, action
no he's got a car
he doesn't take the bus
how much money does Clark Kent have
he's not like a billionaire but he's probably doing alright
can't hit the lead vehicle
Clark Kent as network
is probably
what does he work he has like the glasses on
he has the tie and everything
somebody look that up
what does Clark Kent do
maybe he doesn't work on a hotdog stand
he's a journalist
journalist journalist okay
he's a newspaper journalist
this is where it fucks me up every time
got it this time
actor you actor
you actor you actor
did I get him
one action
five stars
guaranteed
I guarantee it
I still got it
it was a five star up until that point
where am I going
Simpsons hit the run man it's the same place
alright
that guy's just fucked
that was a five star fucking run
and the stupid
turn ruined everything
I guarantee it
my fucking ass that was bullshit
I was in there
you saw it like I'm in there
I don't even give you that shit
got it
boot cap
that was a big
final level
here we go
okay this is your final scene as
Night Avenger tears through Big Top's hideout
a tricky stunt is driving on the
roller coaster track shoot Big Top's
henchmen and get on the track
then drift right around the horseshoe curve
as you're nearing the end
take an abrupt left to break through the railing
then maintain your speed so you'll be set
I'm the roller coaster
this is your last chance to impress Mr. Reitman
give it your all
okay boys and girls time for the finale
let's hurry it up so I can start shopping
for my red carpet tux
alright
what do you want me to do
wow
that's a lot going on
you're at it
go let's go
oh this is gonna be hard
gotta go all the way
NITRO!
that's gotta be close
400,000 what was that 5 stars
that's how you go out strong
5 star
I'm gonna get a 5 star replay
see the guarantee was for this level not the last one
my guarantee meter was off a little bit
that could have been cleaner but
just fly right off
alright
so now we get to see the movie right
let's check out the Batman trailer
what's possessed you
fear
and rage
it's a wrench
by the pricking of my thumbs
something wicked
this way comes
you should try
living for the moment
moment's gone
that's how I feel right now
you did it kid
there are no more movies
ever that was the last one
nice work
I did
unlock a couple of things I didn't I
I didn't do it yet
what did I fail here
let's talk motorcycles kid
directors love them cause they're fast
there are a lot of extras
in the options
I'll take a look before I do
get out of here
is there anything else cool to see
louder
I'm sorry
alright here we go
extras
movies
cheats
slow mo cool
thrill cam vision switcher
untouchable
freaky fast
vision switcher
thrill cam slow mo cool
so L1R1
and then square
please
multi cash quick fix
what's quick fix
freestyle
directed oh there is a lot
of shit huh
freestyle traffic cam
so I have freaky fast
I have a lot of weird PC
mods on
so what's the deal just do whatever I want
spring it
thrill cam
what
that's ugly
this is just like DS mode
hey look guys it's the PlayStation 2
version
remember this
this is really what it looked like
that's so dumb
is there a photo booth
no there isn't
I missed a jump
I'm untouchable by lava
how long can I hold it for
I'm gonna hold this wheelie all night
yeah
two hours go by
that was
sick
I let go
press action press action press action
what else is there besides
freaky fast
alright I'm gonna do this for real
here we go 35,000 string together
action
I'm not doing that
I just wanna see if down
cause I know up started I wanna see if down did anything
but what does freaky fast mean
am I just going much faster than normal
I don't understand
maybe I am
am I going that much faster
what oh come on
you hit square
three two one action
alright
that's nitrous right
yeah I disappeared off that bike
it's on forever
oh
land on the car
no I have to get over this
I gotta be on the left side
this jump there it is
now go to the left
okay slow it down don't look crazy
and then cut across here
holy he turned right into me
hand held camera
mode
cheats the chat link
there was an error
on the screen
cheat
alright
let's get out of there
go to extras or go to passwords
cheats
enter cheat code
alright what's the cheat code
I gotta go
I'm gonna pee my pants
I'll be right back I'm literally gonna pee my pants
okay so what's the password
it was like L U
something whatever it was
unlock all cars
die to pinwheel
what was it actually
it was like L something
I'm not doing ice age
let me look at these for a second
it looks like we can do
stuntman ignition cheats
in game spot alright
cool prop
steal justin
alright randar
randar loves unlock all cars
we are frozen is unlocks everything
including all career stages
okay so we are frozen is literally everything
capitals or what
cheat activated okay
so we got everything
use the editor use the editor use the editor level editor level level
level alright alright right right
let me get this like hold on
uh frill cam we can leave this stuff on
vision switcher this is
I don't it's dumb
freaky fast off
okay so let's go to the editor
constructor freestyle
construction challenge
freestyle constructor challenge
easy tough we'll just try it out
easy
welcome to the constructor challenge
this is where you really get to test your constructor
and driving skills
each challenge has director stunts placed
in the arena you can't alter those
but you can use the props you're given
to make each stunt work
place a couple of props together and activate
that gap stunt or drop a building
under an elevated stunt so you can reach it
there's no time limit when it comes
to editing your arena so plan it out
once you've got everything perfect it's time
to test your arena you've only got
30 seconds to play through the challenge
hit every stunt alright
whatever take the challenge editor
arena so I need to
start here I need to go
over this
okay
go through here alright
done let's go
oh shit no
get back here okay
let's go
I win
done that's it
I did it
try just drift in a circle
for like infinite points
scene rejected why
I only need 15,000 points okay
I got it
I didn't even know that was here
alright so I gotta be close
prop picker is this all I have
to work with this is all I
have to work with what's up with that
4 of 26
I just need
15,000 points
I need to unlock the rest but didn't I do the cheat?
I said cheat activated
to unlock everything
I'm trying to string together
I'm in the wrong mode
going to freestyle
well okay that makes sense
then what can I even do
in this it's really chugging here
can you just
hear that alright editor
arena props okay
well this changes
everything a little bit here alright let's do
alright here we go
camera
smackables alright
I need how do I put this up
is there a way I can bring this
up R2
R1 L1 how do I get elevation
here it's not middle mouse button it's not
up and down do I have
to put boxes up here
smackables
oh no no no
wait wait wait I can't
they can't go that high
look at the right though doesn't the right
is that total that I'm allowed I can't bring
this up I got a better idea
let's see if I can make it through the hoop
alright we got
other cars
this is what gas canister
stacked crates
special
I don't know
if this is going to work
I'm at my maximum for things I can
place really
let's try it alright
nothing else
checking
here ready one two
three damn it
burning construction barrel
what is this clown cars
a scaffolding
it's like a mario maker level
it's like a mario maker level with
just odd pieces
well I know I'm going to do this
really sonic level
it really is going to be
a sonic level not doing this right
nitro here no go this
way alright and then
you have to give a little bit of room
and then I need nitrous over here
that's good
let's spice it up a little that's it
big head top
camera ramp
kick ramp no
I need like a special
I need a where's the nitrous thing
firework crate
remote car
exploding propane tank
train fire hoop
where is it
should be in special right
change cars
here it is nitro box
alright let's do it here
right there
let's get it everywhere
in front of each one
I don't know I guess I don't put it there
can I even do this
this is kind of menacing
that did not work at all
alright how do I change the car that I
spawn with
let's try this one
got it
of course this is my first choice yes of course it is
here we go
the door is open
the doors wouldn't open the doors are closed
I need a muscle car
uh oh
I need a muscle I need a fast car
a very very very fast car
velocity
that might do it
let's go with black dragon
I want a better
nice bright blue
alright let's go
can I do it
can I actually do it
blind yourself
well I did one full revolution
so that's good
fix me fix me
one more let's go
yes
it feels really good
this car has nitro
wait
that means I can use the big one right
ah
I want the give me this one
okay good
of course he's driving around
he's going into the stands
oh
invisible wall
stunt city that's a cool name
let's try the explode
cool
alright I think that's it
let me go back and make sure I don't miss anything
constructor
what is multi clash
this is multi player
we'll do one more on the bike
did you miss the main story yeah
I went through the whole game
I didn't 5 star every level but I certainly
completed it
now this is with the missile
oh yeah he's gonna give up the
yep he's gonna say do this do that
oh that's cheating
no I'm not gonna cheat
didn't even get it wait
I went too fast
no square
how am I supposed to land
on top of this
I'll have to jump over it
sideways
a few times
that counts right
alright not bad
through there
alright come on
that one did it
that one was actually really cool
do I have to watch the 5 star replay
I mean you kind of have to every time right
so LTXT error that's
what's happening
does anyone actually know the difference
between a 5 star replay and a regular
replay you know what I'm trying to say
is there a different
thing did they do it better
bad ending
I know I can like getting any
what's the final one here
I already see frost
I don't want to do it I do see boat
jump though I would love
another one of these games though this game
is a lot of fun
just that one level in the ice place
was nearly almost a meltdown
I mean it kind of was that's the one thing
that I didn't like about the whole game
and as like a 7 to 8
hour experience
I would love another one of these
with updated graphics and better engine
it would be so much fun
I want to place the cameras
imagine you have control of where you can place the cameras
during the actual scene
it would be awesome
shit did I make it I don't think I did
just barely
that was close enough
alright that's the first
one star in a while
so here's what we're going to do
because it's already been about 7 and a half hours
I think I want to go
relax for a little bit
play full
rounds of mario young
I think that's what I'm thinking of
I'm kind of feeling it right now
just relax and just chill
and that's actually probably how we'll do the bits
because I wanted to do the bits from
last night as well because they got cut off
so I think just playing some yasi
going over the bits sounds like an
interesting way to chill out and
end the stream you know
because we do have a lot of bits to go over
but that was stunt made ignition it was a lot of fun
that was equal parts hilarious
challenging interesting
that was
awesome
I'm really glad I played it
there is one more thing to look at
behind the scenes
cars world stunt awards movie
I unlocked this what is it
did Arnold did all that
oh is he alright
I can't handle this anymore
look at how high up he is
that's like
5,000 feet in the air
it would have taken
like a minute
for him to fall
alright I'm out of here
let's go play some mario yasi
my stomach is fucking
killing me give me a second
well I switch over
if you take it off we'll see you later
you will see me again
on probably
probably Thursday
I have a lot of stuff to do over the next two or three
days so you'll see me again on Thursday
I have a
very very very
interesting stream on
probably Saturday we'll go Thursday
Friday Saturday this week
Saturday will be the movies the
you kind of star in the movies stream
not it's not the same game as it was
before this is completely
different I had to buy a 360
for this this is a full
on obscure ass game
I didn't even know this existed
it's called you're in the movies
it is a bootleg version
essentially of you star
we'll see how that goes
apparently there's like 60 mini games to play
and you make a movie while you play the mini games
I don't know but that's what we're gonna do on Saturday
I have that
well we'll see how good it is
but if you take it off
see you later we'll see you Thursday and if not
then we'll play some yasi
and go over the bits
stay tuned I'll be right back