Why, hello there. Welcome to another episode of Germacraft.
And as you can see, I'm doing a little bit of renovating.
Doing some renovations on the house, if you could tell, because this thing is a mess.
Just trying to clean it up a little bit.
And oh my god, no, this has happened before.
Don't worry, got it under control.
So I changed the brightness to be a little brighter.
And I also made the black bars on the sides of the video.
That's probably gone now, at least I'm hoping they are.
Because they were kind of annoying on the top and bottom.
So let's do some adventuring.
I already did a little bit of, I did some stuff before we started.
I got some torches, I got a couple of tools, got a little bit of iron.
And it's time to go on an adventure.
Iron sword, already got a shovel, got a pick, I got some rotten flesh.
I don't even know what this thing is.
What the hell is a slime ball?
What does that do?
I have no idea.
Let's get another pick.
Just because I know I'll probably need it.
Two shovels, a sword, a bunch of sticks.
I need to make, do I have enough?
I do not have enough.
Shoot, I think that'll be all right.
I got to get, I want to put this iron away.
All right, that's next on the agenda.
You know what, screw this.
I'm just taking it off the house.
I'm cutting down my preliminary wall so I can make a case.
So I don't lose all my items if I die.
Because that is a real big pain in the ass.
KKK, let's make, there it is.
A chest, a golden chest.
Put it right here.
Put half the coal in there, put the iron in there.
The slime ball and the sticks.
I got a bunch of sand.
What the hell am I going to do with that?
Okay, so now if I die, it's not a complete and total waste of time.
Let's go.
Try to find some kind of cave system here.
Because I had some iron from before.
I found a little bit of iron before.
Keep going.
We'll go this way now.
We'll dig, we'll dig straight this way.
You never know what you're going to run into in Germacraft.
Or Minecraft for that matter.
By the way, the music in this game is really, really good.
I, the composer's name is what?
Like C3, something like that.
It's some kind of crazy stage name he has.
He's a talented guy.
Because this stuff is really, really soothing.
He nailed it.
He absolutely nailed it.
Mine coal.
We got to keep going forward and keep going below with the coal.
Mine steel.
We got to mine that steel and mine that cobblestone.
Where the hell am I even going?
All right, let's go.
I will find something before this pick breaks.
Or it was, it'll kill me.
Oh yeah.
Aimlessly digging around.
Best part about Minecraft.
Torch.
Ooh, we found a little bit of coal.
That's good.
Ooh, I will definitely take you.
And you.
I'm going to give you all names too.
Your name's going to be Coley.
Your name's going to be Steamy.
And your name's going to be Diarrhea.
Because that's what you kind of look like.
Diarrhea.
Well, there's a lot of coal here.
Uh oh, I think I'm going to get lost.
I think I already am lost.
Ladies and gentlemen, we found gravel.
Which means...
All right, I want...
I don't know why I'm doing this.
Why?
All right, enough gravel.
We got a lava pit.
What else is in here?
Okay.
Ooh, that goes down.
I'm going to block this off.
This is really risky and I hope I don't die.
Ooh, okay.
Nice.
And there goes the lava.
It is now disappearing.
Let's see if I can...
Ooh, I see iron.
I see iron.
I'm going to accidentally fall in this.
I know it.
I'm going to accidentally spill it.
Just like a hot cup of coffee on my new pair of pants.
All right, I think that should be good.
Give me that iron.
Only one?
There was only one thing of iron there.
You got to be kidding me.
I do not approve of that.
Yeah, right.
One iron.
How unlucky is that?
Yeah, well.
Ooh, there's even more.
I got a sword this time.
So you're...
Ooh, more iron.
Let me get this first.
All right, so this is a big intricate little cave system.
Big intricate little cave.
I like the sound of that.
Oh, hi there, guys.
You didn't think I had a sword this time, did you?
Goodbye.
And thanks for coming.
Oh, I don't think you understand.
I got a sword this time.
I'm not messing around anymore.
I'm hungry too, apparently.
You're dead.
What does he...
Is there lava?
He had his lava over there.
All right, I need to eat this rotten, disgusting flesh.
Hold on.
Can you puke in this game?
Because I would definitely puke from eating this.
Oh, like...
What?
What's going on?
Am I, like, toxic?
Am I going to die?
Oh, God.
This is great.
Now I have, like, toxic green blood.
Are you serious?
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Dude, you are, like, levitating right now.
Do you need some help with something?
Ha ha ha.
Yeah, you need some help.
Oh, okay.
I don't have any more picks, do I?
Nope.
Time to make the trek back.
Hopefully I can find my way.
Or else I am...
Look at this sneaky...
Whoa!
Okay, that...
Okay, really?
No!
Oh.
My.
God.
You have...
You've got to be kidding me.
That was...
How was that even possible?
There were two creepers sitting in, like, the same...
Exact spot together in the same pixel?
Oh, my God.
Look at this sneaky...
Whoa!
Okay, that...
Okay, really?
No!