Say it now. What's say it now?
Say what now?
The Drew Crew, what do they want me to do?
Say it. What do you want me to say?
Drew Crew, coming in.
Is that what you want?
Want me to call you the Drew Crew?
Say no.
Alright, we're not playing this game right now.
Hello everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to another live stream.
This live stream is going to be on a video game
that's been shafted quite a few times.
Over the course of the last, I wouldn't say maybe three or four months.
This keeps getting on to chat choice polls
and either wins and then isn't played
or loses and isn't played.
So it's been stuck kind of in a limbo.
We're going to be playing Signal Simulator.
Pre-stream chat decided that's what was going to happen.
They finally got it after
after eliminating everything else and playing other stuff.
It's Signal Simulator was still here.
Signal Simulator has always been here.
We're going to do it tonight.
This game could be very, very interesting
or I might get frustrated in the first 30 minutes.
I'm going to try to give it at least an hour before I freak out.
If I love this game, we're going to keep playing it.
If I like this game, we're going to keep playing it.
If I don't like this game,
we are going to do a hard pivot
to something else.
I'm not going to tell you what it is,
because then all of a sudden I'll look over and I'll see
the waiting room, the waiting room.
Oh my God, Resident Sleeper.
Where is...
I'm not doing that right now.
It's got 20 community subs.
Holy shit.
40 actually from John Cena is killed.
40 community subs.
John Cena, you're a madman.
Thanks for the 40 fucking subs.
And who could forget Hold Up On Zombie for the five subs?
All right, whatever.
I'm not going to play...
I'm not going to tell you what the next game could be.
We are playing Signal Simulator,
not...
Get that through your mind.
What is that in Morse code?
I don't know.
Slow it down.
Figure it out.
Thank you, Ratchley, for the five subs.
Catboy waiting room.
You're going to be waiting here a little while.
You're not going to...
That's not going to happen in the next week or two.
I promise you.
All right, is my cam on?
I hope it's not.
Let's find out.
Let's hope it's not.
If it is, I'm just covering the lens just in case.
Okay, it's not on.
Good.
What's up?
I'm getting a lot of subs right now.
Thank you for the subs, everybody.
Robotic Rogue, thanks for five subs.
And you're going to see this over here.
This says continue.
I didn't play.
I just want to make sure the game ran.
It has the costume on.
I don't have the costume on.
No cam because cat costume.
No, no cam because I have no cam
for 85% of every livestream I've ever done.
All right, so I don't know how this game works.
I'm going to have to pay attention.
I'm going to try.
You guys can't hear anything, now you can.
I'm going to...
I have to pay attention.
This is a pay attention game.
We have to find aliens with our satellite dishes.
If we can find them, we...
I don't know.
I don't know what happens.
I haven't played.
Here we go.
Signal simulator.
You guys have been waiting for this.
Thanks, Jim Beas with five subs.
Appreciate it.
I'm zooming.
Oh, good.
That's very loud.
Let's fix that.
Better be a solid sound.
Oh, all right.
Yeah, we're going to bring that down.
We're going to bring that down just a little.
Now it's too soft.
What?
This is full blast and this is zero.
This is still zero.
But the last third of the bar is what actually matters.
That's all right.
I like that.
All right.
Press F to sit.
Is this my office or something, I would assume?
System efficiency, 100%.
Is that my microphone?
Is there a tutorial?
Press F11.
Use the antenna control panel
to start rotating the antennas.
Azimuth will rotate the antennas horizontally.
Elevation will rotate the antennas vertically.
I can rotate the antenna up and down.
While the antennas are rotating,
the energy consumption will increase.
Antennas can be upgraded to rotate faster.
We're looking for this guy.
So let's do that.
Press F to press.
All right, so this is...
I can't even read that.
Is my FOV too high or something?
I can't even read this.
This coffee is really hot.
I don't think that's the same reaction.
I think you would have a different reaction
with coffee that hot.
Drink it all.
No, are you serious?
Wait, do we seriously have to drink coffee
in less than 10 minutes of weirdos in this chat?
No.
If you get a hot coffee,
you sip it over the course of like three hours
until it is warm and then cold.
And then you get the gross part of the bottom
that you just end up dumping into like the sink
because it's so disgusting you refuse to drink it.
The last like one to 2% of the coffee.
All right, how do I rotate this thing?
Oh, okay.
I can't...
Is there like a magnifying glass?
Okay, there we go.
All right, so Azimuth, Q to decrease,
press E to increase.
Wait, don't rotate yet.
Which one am I rotating?
Press E to Q, okay.
Start rotation, E, Q.
Turn it on.
I'm pressing, okay, E, Q.
How do I turn the fucking thing on?
Is it not on?
You're never gonna figure this out.
Info, hold on, let me read this.
Info monitor will provide you with information
of your main systems, okay.
It's the efficiencies, performance of the systems
and percent.
This is like why I have like five employees.
This is like one of them does this.
I just want, guys, is there somebody that does the monitor,
somebody that does the signaling,
somebody that does like the repairs
and then I walk around with an expensive suit on
with my hands in my suit pocket jacket, both hands,
walking around looking over at everybody's monitors.
Oh, nice, nice, nice, nice, dude, nice.
And I shake my hands a little bit
and my hands come out and I point.
Nice, dude, nice, nice, nice, cool, cool, cool, good job,
good job.
Hands go back in the pockets, walk to the next station.
Use the laptop button just to access the sky scanner.
Sky scanner will detect anomalies in the sky
and once analyzed, you'll be able to start
detecting a signal, okay.
Laptops for the sky scanner.
Gotta figure out how to turn the fucking computer on first.
Performance of the systems in percentages, okay.
Charge efficiency, reach, stop resident sleepering me.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to learn the game.
Recharge performance of the solar panels,
cleaning them, I'm just reading and not comprehending.
Stop, here we go.
Recharge performance of the solar panels,
cleaning them will increase the charge efficiency, okay.
How fast the antenna is rotating.
Detection error for the signal.
If the signal elevation is 50 and the coordination is,
oh man, I need to hire somebody for this.
I need to hire somebody for this.
Range of the antenna or how close you are to position.
I need to hire somebody for this one.
I'll figure it out.
Okay, so status is ready.
Azimuth is ready.
Azimuth is the name of the satellite.
How do I turn the fucking machine on?
Start rotation, do I do it?
On, wait, what?
Wait, wait, wait, why is it like an old dryer
to turn the fucking computer on
that's like 100 billion dollars?
Really?
Okay, 80, 80 and 82, what should we do?
70, 60, 80, 65, all right, 75, 82.
Start, do I do it?
Where is the thing?
Turn the volume up?
This is getting really loud.
Okay, did I do it?
Oh fuck, something's going on over here.
What's going on over here?
All right, I'm just like the new employee that's like,
oh, do I turn this on?
What's this button do?
Oh, deactivate government firewall?
Shucks, what's all these numbers?
Access granted, whoopsie daisy.
You need to scan for the signal.
All right, well let's open up the laptop.
Oh boy, okay, shooter, scanner.
Oh shit, all right, here we go.
Look for a signal.
Are these every, is this every planet
and every star in the universe?
Left mouse button, scan here.
Scan failed, oh shit.
Scan failed, you must check them all.
Scan failed, I have to hold it?
Anomaly detected, anomaly detected.
Detected, help, boss, I detected an anomaly.
What do I do?
Just close the computer?
What are these coordinates?
Seven, one, one, point, three, zero.
All the arrows, what arrows?
What the fucking arrows?
What arrows are, where are the arrows?
Now what?
I mean, bottom right.
Oh shit, what the fuck is that?
I found, I found a planet.
Polarization of the electromagnetic waves.
What, no, oh, all right, I'm gonna fall back.
I'm gonna go to my boss with all this info.
Turns out I was like in the middle
of like fucking Miami somewhere
and like this guy brushes teeth.
Like look what I found, I found aliens.
Look where it's pointed, it's pointed.
It's like dude, that was pointing at Miami, dude.
And that's like a dude brushing his teeth
like you're a fucking idiot.
Tune the anomaly.
Something's talking.
Like, can you hear it?
Visual proceeding.
I can hear someone speaking.
Whoa, signal detected.
Is my phone ringing?
Yeah, what am I supposed to do?
Where?
Escape, escape, escape.
The phone's ringing.
How do I answer the phone?
Shoot it down, whatever it is.
Leave the PC, leave the PC.
How do I answer the phone?
How do I answer that?
Leave the building.
Why would I leave the building right now?
Signal available, tracking available.
How do I track it?
Next to the laptop.
Download audio data.
The fuck was that?
Hold on, hold on, let's help here.
Frequency detection.
Once a signal is detected with the sky scanner,
you have to find the right frequency signal.
When you've found the coordinate detection system,
we activate the search for somebody.
All right, what do I do here?
How do I do this?
Off the secret, next to the laptop?
I can't pick this up.
How do I pick that up?
Look behind you.
Wrong panel.
Audio signal control.
Download audio control.
Should I scan this here?
Manual mode, frequency lock, volume.
Right, middle.
Antenna detection control.
Detection, energy.
I don't even know what it wants me to do.
What does it want me to even just hit auto scan?
Auto scan.
Too many fucking buttons.
Where is it?
Auto scan.
It's not doing anything.
Just turn on the coordinate machine.
Left, Jerma.
All right, look, there's like a five second delay on stream.
If you say, look to the left, and I go left,
and you go, no, that's too far left, go to the right.
I'm already over here.
By the time I get to here, you say left,
and by the time I get to here,
you tell me to go back right.
Phone.
I can't even go this far.
Auto scan.
Once signals detected, you have to find
the right frequency for the signal.
Didn't I already do that?
I just do it on manual mode?
Look up.
It's negative 16 degrees Celsius in this room.
I don't know, I can die here.
I do manual mode?
Thank God.
Well, that's not your movie.
What am I doing?
I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
The game's tutorial is like a syllabus you get
in the first day of school.
I don't even know what I'm supposed to be doing.
You didn't read the syllabus.
No, I did read the syllabus.
Very much so.
Just hit the auto scan.
I pressed this button, I think, 30 times.
The shit.
Oh, fuck.
My mic is desynced because of last stream.
Oh my God.
It was by like almost two full seconds.
Thank God you caught that.
Wait, so that's another problem.
Hold on a second.
So you were telling me to go left,
and I was saying I'm going left,
but a full two seconds was going by before you heard it.
So therefore, I was going right
by the time you were telling me to go right,
and I was saying left.
All right, so where the fuck do I actually go?
Wait, what the fuck?
Okay, hold on.
Hold on, right here.
And just, this is it, right?
So track the coordinates.
No, that's so funny.
Turn the manual knob until you click green.
Wait, I got something.
I got something.
We got one.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right, track it.
Oh shit, what's going on?
That's some Ghostbusters.
If you don't know what that is, then oh my God.
Get out of here.
All right, so I have 55, 51.
Okay, hold on.
That's too many things.
28, 76.2.
Look at the averages.
31.5 and 67.9.
46.9, all right.
44....
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I did not...
43.1 and 75.2.
This keeps changing.
Eleva...
All right, so let's go elevation.
We need 77.
Let's just, I'm doing 47 and 77.
I don't even care.
So we need 47 and 77.
And then 77.
Okay, here we go.
It's time to go.
I've found the coordinate.
I've found the alien.
FTP is running.
I have unlimited services.
FTP connections.
How many, why are there like 2,000 people connected to me?
Okay, is it there?
Did I go into this completely blind?
One, yes, 100%.
I have no idea what's going on.
Absolutely no clue.
I downloaded it and then I turned it on
and turned the stream on.
Okay, so tracking available.
Is that, are we good?
Coordinates.
The system will activate when a signal
is detected in the sky, yeah.
Once the system is activated,
it will give you coordinates within the range
based on the coordinate detection system.
You can switch between different visual layers
using the coordinate detection control panel.
Okay, but now what?
We're at 47, 77.
48 to seven, maybe a little, okay, 48 point.
No, this is accurate.
Now I have to go to the coordination detection panel.
So it's on, okay.
Oh, shit, there it is.
All right, so we gotta go up a little more.
We need to go to,
up and right.
What is up and right though?
42, 42 and then 80.
All right, 42, 80.
42, 80.
Oh, we good?
We're spinning, okay, and then we're gonna go up.
It's not instant.
Oh, I watch as it moves in elevation bars to the right.
Okay, go for a walk in the meantime.
What do you mean go for a walk in the meantime?
I just get up from my desk, you sure?
I feel like I'm almost there.
I'm over the bullseye.
Look at the center console.
Well, as it moves, it's at 41.
We need as it moves to be at 51.
Oh, crap.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm gonna get you and when I get you, I'm gonna get you.
50 and 75, what are we at?
70, 51, we need elevation to be at 75.
51, 75, we almost there?
That's like, we're right there, 51, 75.
All right, come on, what the fuck?
Where is this thing?
53, it's like right here.
Is it, can I track?
Track coordinates.
Do I do attention detail?
48, 78, it's not a fucking scope.
All right, I can finally watch my favorite streamer.
Start at the minimum and then go to the maximum.
Wait, what?
29 and 64, that's not what I do.
Why would I do that?
No, that's not how this works.
I can't, what is making that sound?
Because I'm gonna turn it down.
Oh, fuck, what happened?
I thought that was volume.
Shit, did I mess that up?
All right, but what am I, all right.
How do I turn this fucking sound off?
Oh, thank God, okay.
What am I trying to do?
Am I trying to get this blue circle in the middle?
Can't track coordinates or anything.
No, it's time for a hard pivot Andy.
We'll see, maybe.
Do I go back on the laptop?
Put the elevation up a little more.
Okay, 79, go for it.
Elevation, 60, I can't even read this circle.
Don't get discouraged.
No, I'm just, I feel like this is one of those games
where you have to sit here for like an hour or two
before you understand how the game even works.
Oh, up, not down, wait, I didn't go up?
What is detection control?
Do I have any more tutorials?
I can switch between different visual layers
using the, yeah, I thought I did that, hold on.
One or two hour resident sleeper.
I can't track these coordinates because it's not in there.
Board is right there.
I mean, look, you can't sit me down
in front of your school project
that I've never been to one class of yours.
Like you're in a fucking geology class
and you sit me down in all this shit that I don't know
and you go, hey, can you do my homework for me?
It's right there, it's right there.
You don't know that?
No, I don't know, you have like 10 monitors, dude,
and I have not sat in one of your college classes.
I have no fucking idea what's happening.
In fact, you're gonna get an F.
Do your work, don't tell me to do this, do your own work.
All right, I'm missing something here.
I feel like I need to do this.
Wallace and Gromit waiting room.
You can scroll down on that tutorial page, I can.
There's nothing here.
So what, okay, what is the goal
of me trying to hit this average here?
It's 48.75.
Wait, what do you mean actually pretending?
Scroll on the right, fucking God.
I have a criticism here.
This is a criticism for the game.
What's all this space for?
What's the point of this space?
What is the point of this space?
Why do I need to scroll down
past like a paragraph of empty space?
What's the point of that?
It can just be right here?
Oh, he's a real critic.
Okay, azimuth min plus coordinate detection
equals possible signal.
From that point, start lowering the current position
or wait until a new lower azimuth is detected.
Okay, so we go to the minimum, like that person said,
and we start lowering.
I heard like a fucking animal.
Okay, what's the minimum?
27.3.
Okay, 27.3.
All right, here we go.
What do we got, anything?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, it's not,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Check the bathroom.
Why would I go to the bathroom?
Not, not, not, not, that's wrong.
No, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Oh, 29 minimum 62.
I'm just gonna go up from here.
Remember, the bars on the left try to fill them.
Azimuth elevation signal strength.
Well, what the fuck is this thing?
Okay, that, I got up.
What do you mean I had it?
Check the azimuth didalis.
It was green.
What was it, how many minutes green?
Launch the nuke.
Uh, okay, so I'm gonna go 27.86.
Did I go by 27.86?
Somebody said it was green before.
Was it?
When both these are fully green, you have the signal.
Why wouldn't they even be a little green?
The thing is right here.
We'll go back to 50.
All right, let's go 32.
I'm just trying to get the azimuth.
I don't care about the elevation right now.
33.
All right, 33, 33, go back, I gotta go up, up, up, up, up, up.
I'm gonna go 35.
Where's the alien?
No, this is like learn how to fly a plane
in the first day of class.
No green at all, how?
27, all right, um, I'm gonna go back up to like 48.
Still red, why is it red?
Check the bathroom.
I'll go to the bathroom in a minute.
I need to get to like the first alien.
Let me get to the first alien first
and then I'll go to the bathroom.
What happened?
What the fuck happened?
Why is it broken?
What happened?
I mean, I lost the signal.
It took too much time.
You think they would wanna ease you into this shit?
No, just sit down at the battle station.
I'm going to the fucking bathroom.
No, I know this is one of those games
where this game over there doesn't mean anything.
This is a fake game.
This is a horror game.
I'm gonna like have to sleep
in this guy.
I'm gonna be like, I'm gonna hear noises
in the kitchen and shit.
I know what this is.
This is a fake game.
And then I'm gonna have to,
there's a scary alien monster that I have to avoid.
Okay, yeah, right, okay, fake game.
Game's not even real.
This is like a runaway from the monster
and it's just for show.
Get a coffee.
That's an audio, what the fuck is going on here?
Let me mow in the lawn.
Did I leave the computer on all night?
That's the alien.
Oh shit, avoid the alien.
Open the server rack.
Next one with the main server established.
I don't know about this one.
All right, where's the bathroom?
This is the fire exit.
Wait, why can I go outside?
Where is the bathroom?
What is this doing?
Is this dropping like a package?
No, this is fantastic, dude.
Everybody playing on this server's gonna fucking
just be swarming this area right now.
Once this drops.
Great.
Had a good spot here too.
What's this doing?
Wait, what?
That was an Amazon delivery.
Is that a helicopter right there?
Could I fly that?
Okay.
I still don't even understand
what the hell I'm supposed to do.
Where's the bathroom?
Is everyone saying check the bathroom?
All right, I checked the bathroom.
There's nothing in the bathroom.
There you go.
Bathroom has been checked.
Okay, cool.
What do you mean plus one letter grade for a bathroom?
What are you talking about?
All right, well I checked it.
I need to find at least one alien.
I still don't get it.
I don't fucking get it.
I'm trying to get it.
I don't get it.
We gotta start from the beginning again.
All right, so what, how, how, what's the,
what do you, do you start?
Um, I don't get it.
I don't get it.
You gotta go on the laptop.
Okay, there it is.
All right, got first part done.
Found.
Oh, that's, that's fucking Jerva Jupiter.
Okay, tune the frequency.
Let's get a frequency here.
I understand this part.
What the fuck?
That's not it?
I got it.
Okay, that part's done.
Okay, detected the signal.
Now, disconnect.
Here we go.
I got a whole day to figure this out.
We got, I, I, I, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
I don't know, I forget.
What's the next part?
What's the, I don't know what the next,
what's the next part?
I forget.
Frequency.
Oh, I, I, I, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Tracking available?
How?
Tracking available.
Track that, track it, track it.
Track that, track that coordination.
Track it.
Auto scan.
Auto scan, stop.
Track the coordinates.
Manual mode.
Turn off auto scan.
14.7, .8, .2.
Okay, here we go.
This is the part that I have trouble with.
We need to go, I've got plenty of time.
Let's go.
30, what is it?
32 and 53, 72.
53, 72, let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on?
Track the coordinates, I can do that?
Oh, fuck, what happened?
Did I have it?
Why are these not green?
I thought you guys said I could only track the coordinates
and these are fully green.
Is that a lie?
I've got, I'm just pretending to drink coffee now.
This is not moved at all.
He's never gonna make it to 6 a.m.
All right, this is the part that I don't understand.
So, I'm at 55, 74.
Shouldn't there be at least some strength at all
on either one of these two things?
You need help.
Call Joel, you need help.
What do you mean, call Joel?
Like, I don't have just Joel on speed dial.
It'll be like, Joel, hey, hey, answer the phone
every time I, hey, listen to me.
Wait, he might be like eating dinner.
He might be busy.
He might be like streaming.
I'm not gonna interrupt somebody's dinner
with my annoying, hey, I don't understand
how to like do geology.
Hey, hey, Joel, help me with my geology homework.
Can I copy yours?
And here's the best part.
I'm pretty sure Joel played this
like five months ago.
So, I need to copy Joel's geometry homework
from five months ago.
I think I got an F in the class already.
Okay, so, let me get back to this.
Is something to do with this?
I feel like it's something to do with this
and I'm not doing it.
It's still rotating.
Well, hurry the fuck up.
This thing's like worth a trillion dollars.
It can't turn faster than that.
Okay, we're at 53, 76.
Oh, fuck, oh, fuck, oh my god, oh my god,
oh my god, oh my god, okay.
As it's, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, 53.
53, we're gonna go 52.
51, go.
What?
Wait, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
What happened?
54, go.
I gotta start updating.
Wait, that's what was screwing me up.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, 54.
55, here we go.
Wrong one.
56, go.
Because it wasn't updating in real time.
That was the problem.
56, we're gonna go 57.
58, what happened?
Wait, what the fuck happened?
What happened, what happened, what happened, what happened,
what happened, what happened, what happened, what happened?
It was just almost all the way up here.
What the fuck happened?
What's going on?
56, go back.
What happened?
5.2, what is going on?
Wasn't this just like right here?
55.2, I have to go back to 54?
54.2, all right, wait a minute.
54.2, three.
54.3, wrong.
54 point, 54.1.
Holy shit, okay.
54.12, 54.10, 54.0.
Oh shit, 53.95, 53.98.
53.97, I can't tell if that's going up or down.
53 point, 53.79, I can't tell if that's going,
was that moving?
I almost just puked.
Okay, 50, why am I gonna puke?
53.6, 53.5, come on dude, really?
53.7, this is, I, oh my god damn it, man.
53.7, 53.76, 53.8, here we go, 53.81.
Here we go, here we go, one more, 53.86.
Bingo, 87, bingo, 88, there, oh, 887.
All right, elevation time, 74, okay.
Let's go to 74 elevation.
I didn't know it was like this precise.
I'm gonna find that alien.
I'm just gonna put two hands around his neck
and then shake him back and forth and say,
give me the fucking secrets, give me the magic secrets.
70, oh, 72, go back, just back and forth.
I know you've solved time travel.
I know you have holograms, just give it to us.
Little do we know that all these aliens
don't have any of this technology at all.
They just figured out how to plant corn in the ground, guys.
Aliens probably have like space ships
and crazy weapons and lasers.
No, no, they just figured out farming,
like basic one-on-one agriculture.
We're the ones with the technology, got news for you.
70, 74, fuck, nothing at all, nothing at all.
We're going up higher, 76, hurry, hurry.
74, come on, I don't wanna lose the signal.
Oh, all right, we're going all the way down.
I'm going like 64, my favorite console.
Hey, VYKing, thanks for the 10 community subs.
StormyChew5, Jimbius5, RoboticRogue, we already got you.
Thanks for the 10, though, we're fine.
All right, I get the game now.
Look, it took me like 40 minutes to figure,
it's like how it's an interesting game
and I have to figure it out.
I can't just know everything,
I can't just do your homework in five seconds.
Low, lower, 62, no, go up to 60, I don't know.
Shit, all right, we're going up.
Minimum, minimum, minimum.
I think it's between, yeah, I'm gonna go up.
Come on, have me be high.
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Well, I, okay, hold on, down.
Average 63, I'm going down to 63.
What do you mean down?
It's not, I don't know, it's hard to, 63, 62?
Well, I was just going up, it's not, okay, it's not high,
it's low, go.
62, you have three seconds to comply.
You have three seconds to, minimum, minimum.
Oh, fuck, I could die, hold on.
You have three seconds to, minimum, minimum, minimum.
That's an old video, no one's fucking saying it,
who cares?
All right, 60, come on, pay attention.
What am I gonna pay attention to?
There's nothing to pay attention to yet,
I have to wait like 15 seconds.
Hey, how's your, how's your new year going so far?
Wait, it's loud, too loud, I don't like it.
He's scared, not really, what's there to be afraid of?
I know there's gonna be a jump scare when I beat the game.
It has to be, right, why wouldn't there be?
Hurry up, 62.1, nothing.
How could I still have absolutely nothing?
59, how the fuck are 12K people watching this?
I don't know, that's a good question.
You should ask them one by one.
Ask them one by one what they're doing here.
56, no, it's higher, it has to be higher.
It has to be, right?
It's forcing us.
Start with, wait, hold on.
You guys are trying to give me help here.
Start with azimuth, start at the minimum value.
Wait for it to actually go to that position.
You can check the current position, yeah.
It's at the maximum value.
Start rotating through that and watch for the green bar.
Start the rotation when, I already, um, excuse me.
What, this is full, I did that, I did it.
Why give me, I did that already.
All right, so it's, I gotta go up.
Let's go 60, 64.
I already did 64, but we'll do it again.
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you guys doing a bread recipe?
Really?
Get out of here.
Just change the difficulty.
I could do that, but I'm already doing this.
Not even a single part of that bar, come on.
69, no?
70, it has to be in the 70s then.
It's not, 70, 71.
What the fuck is happening here?
72, um, 74, 75.
Oh, you piece of shit, is that higher?
Max is 83, the max is 80, but one decimal at a time.
That sounds like a painful experience.
Elevation, right, that's what we're doing.
We already did azimuth, this is elevation.
Max is, well, it just was 80, it just updated.
Come on, it's almost night time.
Really, then it has to be like between 80 and 85, nothing.
Oh my fucking God, really?
Use the minimum, minimum 64.
I was already down there.
I did like 63, 64, 65, 66, 67.
There's a golf cart outside, you can drive.
Yeah, well I need to be able to find the signal first.
All right, I have no idea, I have no idea
why I can't find this.
60, I already did like, I did, it's 72.
Oh, you don't know that.
Do not skip numbers.
Signal loss incoming, fuck, I know, but I get it.
This is only my second day on the job.
Imagine about your third day, you understand all this.
I would give that person an immediate raise.
They would get an immediate raise.
Jesus, I can't even come close, man.
I mean, Jerma sucks.
I'm doing what you're supposed to be doing.
I'm just, I'm checking, I'm just checking decimal point.
I'm just checking numbers.
That's what I'm supposed to be doing.
You did 71, you didn't do 73 and 74.
Dammit, I'm gonna lose the signal now.
Not even one blip on the fucking radar.
Not even a single blip.
I feel like I've done every single number in between
without tiny little decibels.
I'm about to lose signal.
Like, you what, you have to find the signal
between 65 and 88 to the hundredth decimal point, okay?
All the way up to 86, it's gone.
Fucking, the signal's gone.
Great, fun.
Just turn the knob very gently until you find the signal.
No, I'm not done.
No, I'm gonna find one of these signals
and we're gonna go do it.
I'm not gonna give up on it,
even though I am very, very upset about it.
Put it on easy instead.
You guys care if I put it on easy?
I don't think I can.
Lock the door, is it?
Why am I still asleep?
Take the bathroom?
Mm-hmm.
You left the doors open?
So what?
Guys, this is like the game Firewatch.
I'm the only person here.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's go find the signal.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm not wasting a single fucking second, I swear to God.
Laptop, let's go.
I'm going to try as hard as I can right now to find this.
I know exactly what to do.
It's his third day, third time's the charm.
Let's find this planet.
Come on.
Was it higher?
Why do I hear the German Raptor?
Watch a YouTube tutorial?
Well, I think I already know now.
The time for the YouTube tutorial was 40 minutes ago.
My favorite part about the stream so far
was being on a two second delay
and you guys hearing me turn and say where I was going.
Accidentally on like a two and a half second delay.
All right, got it.
Cool, done?
All right, here we go.
It's time.
Find that frequency.
Scan it.
Scan that.
Almost there.
Come on, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
Why can't it just auto scan?
Do I not have enough power to auto scan?
Ow, my fucking ears.
My footsteps?
That was weird.
I got it, got it, got it.
All right, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Here we go.
Let's move.
What do we got for an average?
Now I will find this stupid frequency.
We have, what the fuck?
300.
333.
What?
That's so, that's too high.
325.
That's going to take so long.
That's going to take all night.
300?
Don't go to the average.
All right, we're going to go, the average is 320.
What was it?
312.
Turn around.
I'm not turning around yet.
312.
All right, 306.
But people say go to the minimum,
but the minimum changes every time.
All right, I'm going to go to 306.
I can't.
Well, we just have to wait for that to get to,
it's going to take all night.
Optimize the power box.
All right, you got it.
Let's put it on antenna, right?
It coins at $37,000.
But I was an idiot three or four years ago.
I was stupid.
I was a dumb guy.
You are now too.
Well, sure.
Bitcoin almost $40,000.
Hey, remember when it was like 3400 or 3500,
like two or three years ago?
I was the idiot.
What's your net worth in Vodkilling?
Oh man, I'll tell you my net worth in Bitcoin.
Sick.
Hey, when it dropped down to like 3800.
Oh yeah, I told you, here comes the crash.
Oh no, it was a scam.
I held onto it for like, I don't know, six months
and I got rid of it at like $4,500 of ECC.
But that doesn't mean I was wrong.
That does not mean I was wrong.
That means I was right in the longterm.
I always knew.
And guess what?
I held onto one, okay?
I held onto one.
I still got one.
I still have one.
And I'm not gonna sell it
until it's worth a million dollars, all right?
You're asking what this is going down, what?
Send power to the coordinates.
Oh shit.
Why would I do that?
320, all right, hold on, I made it better.
This is, I'm not gonna be able to do this.
If what's your BTC, well, give me that coin.
Use the website.
What do you mean use the website?
Let me check and see how my BTC's doing.
Wait, hold on, I have zero dollars.
Upgrades, what?
There's upgrades?
Hold on, I have to look at this.
Azimuth, rotational speed increase.
I don't have any money.
Do I get money for this?
Terminal, database, all signals.
Story signals, random signals.
Play, where is this?
Executed?
I haven't found anything.
Well, I'm just gonna go drive the car then.
It's gonna take like three days to get there
and I'm gonna lose the signal by the time it gets there.
How do I leave out here?
I'm fine, what's that?
Yeah, this does get a full letter grade,
but what's the point of this?
You can hand crank the radar to have it go faster.
What, am I on Earth?
I'm realizing this is, this is a strange planet.
Do you hear that?
It was snow, it was like snow sounds, wasn't it?
By the way, I don't have a left ear button.
If those of you that, you guys know that.
I do not have a left ear button.
Why is it snowing out here?
You missed it.
What was it?
It was exclusively left ear.
It was an alien sound, was it actually?
One ear butt Andy.
Why is it all of a sudden accumulation on the ground?
It just started snowing.
What the hell is this for?
I found my test.
Can I climb this?
Oh, you know, I may have found somebody else's test
that they got scared, they heard Jigsaw,
they threw it out in their golf cart
and just didn't do the test.
That would just kinda fuck up Jigsaw's whole routine,
wouldn't it?
I'm in my golf cart, I'm starting my job.
There's a recorder under here.
I pick it up and I press play.
Hello again, David.
This is Jigsaw, fuck, just throw it out the window.
I don't know what it is, but I don't wanna know.
And I would get away from this.
I would go to the doctor immediately.
I would get every scan.
Yeah, David, everything looks clean.
Everything?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, there was a small little thing
behind the back of your right side of your neck.
Was it a key?
No, no, no, no, just a little fatty nodule.
Not a big deal or anything, it's just pretty normal.
Okay, but then I would be fine.
What is that in the distance?
I have to, it's a UFO.
It's a UFO.
I'm gonna go find it.
This is the shittiest version of Independence Day
I've ever seen.
How do we stop them?
Oh, we have no power.
Our weapons are useless.
Who's that down on the golf cart?
I'll take care of this.
Aw, I need to look at that, I need to see what that is.
It gets close enough.
You alien bastards!
And just a small little,
ray just comes out of the front of the UFO
and liquidates this.
There's no explosion or anything.
There's no, oh my God, what a big death.
Nope, it just, vaporized, gone.
That person's gone.
I don't even know where my base is.
All right, I gotta use this telescope and look.
Oh, come on, really?
I can't, okay.
Wait, there's a car too.
Wait, why would I get in that when there's a car?
It's a Tesla truck, it's a cyber truck.
And there's window breakings.
This is a joke, right?
They did this on purpose.
That's pretty funny.
What are they loading in here?
All right, telescope.
Okay, where was that?
It was like over there somewhere, right?
Is it up?
I don't see it, what?
I don't see anything.
It was just the helicopter.
It was actually the helicopter,
which is really far away.
Oh, okay.
All right, let's take a look.
Let's check on my frequency.
How's it doing?
All right, we are, 323.
We'll go 30, 307.
Hurry up, what am I doing?
I'll bring this down to the minimum
so we can go from minimum to maximum.
Use the website.
I don't know what you mean, website.
Terminal?
What website are you talking about?
Use the website.
Dude, that thing is scrolling.
Radio, use the radio.
ABC lounge.
Why is this buffering?
Can't even fucking hear it.
Extreme DMCA, actual DMCA.
Wait, is this for real?
All right, we're at 316.
This is a real radio station?
Wait, can you get DMCA'd for a radio station?
You can.
Well, Santa Claus is fucked.
Every mall Santa just went.
Worst noise.
What?
What do you mean worst sound?
Oh, I just went gulp with a cat puke sound.
That's not a big deal.
Do you hear yourself?
No.
No one understood that joke.
I'm saying every mall Santa has just
the Christmas radio station playing right next to them.
Was that a bad joke?
That wasn't very funny?
No, oh well.
But they're not streaming.
Oh, yeah, right.
It's not illegal to listen to music.
Or will it be eventually?
There's the deep part of that joke you guys missed.
It went right over your head.
You have to have a fucking Blizzard authenticator stick
to stick into your radio to prove
that you can actually listen to that song.
Just wait, just wait.
And then at that point BTC will be $100,000
and who gives a shit, I'll be a millionaire.
Well, I'll have one.
Then I'll probably sell it when it crashes in like a week.
I don't know, I'm not a financial advisor.
Don't take any advice from me.
I have no idea what's going on.
It's fucking, it's insanity.
I have no signal.
I have no signal again.
Well, can I get one that's not over 300?
Is it, wait, did I go, is it time to sleep?
You idiot.
Coordinates, signal simulator on GitHub.
You guys are linking me a GitHub.
I need to go to a GitHub website to play this game.
Really, you want me to cheat?
Nope, I'm gonna find one before the stream turns off.
I swear to God.
I need to find one.
And the second that I find one and it goes,
doot doot, wait, I have money.
I have 20 bucks.
Okay, how about recharge?
Recharge rate upgrade.
That doesn't seem like very much.
But on the solar panels, 20 big ones, that's right.
I'll probably do this, how much is it?
30 bucks, I don't have, it's all these are 30.
So let me get this straight.
I'm not getting paid to work right now.
Is that what I'm understanding?
How come I'm not getting paid?
You only get paid if you do your job.
How have I not been doing my job?
I've been desperately trying to find these
needle in a haystack pinpoint coordinates
and I almost got one.
You get paid when you find the aliens.
Where's the alien?
I don't, I'm looking, what, I,
just because I haven't found the alien yet
doesn't mean I don't get paid for the work I'm doing
to try to find the alien?
All right, let's get a signal.
I've slept.
Where are the results?
I don't know.
I want photos, Jerma, photos of aliens.
What is this, Jade, Spider-Man guy?
This is what he goes into when he realizes
that Spider-Man's just a fucking teenager
and it's not this big of a conspiracy or anything.
Get those pictures of those aliens.
Parker, I didn't invest $200 billion in this university
to not see results.
And they better be big and they better be green.
I want coordinates, Spider-Man.
Wait, why does he call Peter, wait,
at this point he knows, right?
Why is he talking to Spider-Man?
Peter Parker just goes in without the mask on
and he goes into the daily bugle.
I spent two decades following you around,
God damn it, Parker.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, this.
What do we got?
Why are they all in the hundreds?
100 and a, come on, all right, 148.
Let's just get the process going right now, 148, go.
We're at 300 fucking hundred, dude.
I have to go down to like 180?
This is gonna take all night.
Brack is available.
All right, so if I press this button, what happens?
Just do both at the same time.
Wait, why is it doing that?
It's tracking the coordinate right now.
Turn up detection.
Your antenna's not at max efficiency.
Efficiency is at five.
Aliens don't omega low exist, dumbass.
All right, but why is my system efficiency so low?
Do I have to like recharge the battery or something?
How do I recharge a university research facility's battery?
Go to the solar panels and clean them?
Oh, come on.
You actually aren't, that's actually for real.
You really mean that?
That's really what I have to do.
I have to go clean the solar panels.
Where are the solar panels?
They're covered in snow.
Oh, please.
But where are they?
Are they on the, how do I get up?
Where are these solar panels?
They're on the left?
Like down there?
How do I get up?
Oh, for the love of God.
Where's my car?
No, my other car.
What was that?
That was me, okay.
Okay, let's go.
Cybertruck, oh my God, Cybertruck Pog.
Are you serious?
Get in your Cybertruck and drink your Heul.
I like Heul, I don't care if you hate me.
How do I clean this?
This is not solar panels, this is like a grain mill.
That's not a solar panel.
Oh, I forgot, all right, solar panels, let's go.
Clean them off.
The splash light makes things worse.
Open and close the door.
Start the cleaning system.
The cleaning?
System efficiency, 0.9%.
What happens if that goes to zero?
Don't press it, what?
What do you mean, it's nighttime?
I can't clean at night?
Solar panels do not work at night.
But they still take in the electricity.
They take in electricity?
I have 0.1% battery?
Oh shit, a huge raid just came in.
Who just raided?
This Connor Eats Pants.
With like 5 fucking thousand people.
Welcome everybody, what's up?
How's everybody doing?
Welcome to the stream.
My name's German985.
What's your name?
Don't write, just write like your handle in the chat.
Don't write your name.
Make one up.
I have to sing the raid song.
No, we don't do raid songs anymore.
That's how you delete a thousand people in one second.
Can I just stand here until morning?
Oh, thanks for the raid, welcome guys.
Hope you had a good stream, whatever you were doing.
I'm trying to figure out how to contact aliens.
But wait, wait, wait, wait, here we go.
Would this work?
You know that in an M. Night Shyamalan movie,
this would work at some point.
This would be a huge thing.
All right, let me check.
Oh, God damn it, I have to go to sleep.
What the fuck?
I don't want...
3,000 people left because you didn't sing the raid song.
I'm not singing any raid songs, not anymore.
Nonsense, it got nominated.
There's a UFO right there.
That's not a helicopter.
I saw the circular angle on it.
That's not a, that is a UFO.
All right, remember where that is.
Where's my house?
Where's my base?
It's back this way, over there.
I see it, I see it, I see it, I see it, I see it.
What's this?
Turn on, I don't know what I just did.
Turn that off?
Should I turn this off?
All right, where was the, where was the UFO?
It was right there somewhere.
It's gone, what the fuck?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, I'm gonna see, I'm gonna see.
There it is, there it is.
Where'd it go?
Hold on, whatever.
All right, am I coordinates ready?
I just need, I need to sleep so I can,
to go clean the stupid solar panels.
You have a dirty monitor.
I kinda do, you don't need to rest right now.
What am I supposed to do?
Okay, we are at two, why is it still spinning?
Oh, I had track coordinates on.
So this thing's just been, I've just been using energy.
No wonder I can't even turn the TV on in my house.
I used it all up just spinning this thing in a circle.
You need at least 50% efficiency to do anything.
Oh God.
I can't sleep either.
Lock the doors.
Change difficulty to the azimuth
and elevation trackers update in real time.
Yeah.
It didn't even give me,
I think I'm starting detection mode to update
only when the internet finishes rotating.
Oh, fuck that.
That's not even how it works in the real world.
This is not even how this works in real life.
If you tune something or, what,
you have to wait till you get to the end?
When you're sitting at your car radio
and you use the tuner,
you don't have a silent fucking radio
until you reach like 91.2.
That's not how it works.
You hear it.
You hear the frequency, you hear the noise.
You get to hear them in real time.
That's how it works.
These things are worth like $500 billion.
You're right.
Aliens will be found tomorrow.
All right, here we go.
Let's do it.
I'm ready.
Everything's at max efficiency.
Configuring the ISAPNP file system up.
Did that just say imminent shutdown?
All right, here we go.
Scanner.
I'm ready.
I want this shit in real time the way that it is.
Analyze that planet, please.
Name this planet.
Balthazar.
Balthazar dash one, two.
Planets are so far away
and you want to see them instantly.
It's a, this is not,
I'm not actually in a research facility.
This is a, this is pretend.
Okay, now I got that.
It's time to, let's find that frequency.
Auto scan, please.
Can't, it's all right.
What is the exact speed of light?
Is it like 10,000 miles per hour?
It's an easy number to say.
I'm just gonna say that.
Add it, add it.
No, give it back.
Got it, got it, got it.
Give it back.
Use auto?
I can't.
Doesn't do anything.
What's the speed of light?
I would walk 10,000 miles
and I would walk 10,000 more.
Just to be the man who would walk 1,000 miles
to fall down at,
you've already, we talked about this, right?
You would walk like five miles, get tired,
and then just be like, you know what?
I'm just gonna drive there.
This is too much.
Here we go, got it.
I would walk 1,000 miles.
No, I would not.
I would not.
I would walk a few and then I would,
here's what I would do.
I would walk for like 10 minutes
and realize what I was doing was really stupid.
To put forth the illusion that I did so,
I would just get the clothes I was wearing.
I would like roll them into the dirt a little bit.
I would take a little bit of like dirt
and like rub it in my hands,
like rub it on my face.
I look like cartoon character style.
Like I got attacked by a shot with like a cartoon shotgun.
You know what I mean?
Mess up my hair, shit load.
This is a family guy joke.
What the fuck?
Are you kidding me?
I can't even tell a joke anymore
and it's like already a family guy routine.
They, whatever.
What do we got for a signal?
I'm really, come on.
All right, 149, 10, go.
On, E, E, turn it on.
Turn this thing on.
All right, 149, 10.
I'm gonna go 140, 10, go.
Let's go, spin.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
and I'm gonna put a ton of power into this.
There we go, better.
Oh Jesus, it can take all day.
I'm gonna lose the signal by the time it gets there.
Why would they,
how are you even supposed to do this?
I have to go clean, this is a new game.
The solar panels are nice and they're fine.
I'm at 99% efficiency.
It's gonna take like all day.
Go explore in the snow.
No, I'm gonna get this, I'm gonna get this.
Worst, this is not the worst stream of 2021.
Just wait till fucking like a month from now.
You'll be begging for this to come back
when I play like golf simulator 2.
You'll be begging for this to come back.
All right, no real time data yet.
We're getting closer.
All right, so we're gonna go from 140,
we're gonna go to 188 and then 42.
188 to 42.
Looking at that elevation right now.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
It was 19, 19.
19, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
19 and then this one was that's not we got that one ready one. We're gonna go up to
One like 60 and he said I can't read this you can't why did I can't wait for during the catboy stream from like
I'm gonna put up like a fake cat foot and like
Behind my right ear on camera you guys are gonna fucking freak out. I missed it. What was it?
Spoilers oh, I got a lot of spoilers for you if you want to hear. Oh, just wait for that you guys
Guys I think that you're not gonna like that straight. Just wait alright now. We gotta go to 180 so it was 19
We're gonna go to 20. We'll do
2020 I don't know
Where are we 165 165 21? Oh fuck 165 17 165 17 come on. Oh you idiot
165 17 oh my god pay attention shit. It was 18. I fucking hate these dials
18 160 I
Can hate these dials with passion why can't it be a knob one knob we are adding one 60
165.3. Oh, please
164.9. I read it there it is elevation 18 point 18 point 2. I hear some new noise
18 point 4. Oh boy. I got quiet 18 point 5 18 point 4. We got it 18 point 4 5 18 point 4 7
18 point 4 5 18 point 4 4 18 point 4 3 was that
Waiting for data to be downloaded download it a video. What happened waiting for wait? Oh my goodness
What is this shit coordinates and then upgrades modules energy solar panels energy distribution calibration?
How do I download the data? Oh, it's downloading. It's right now. It's downloading. This is a one gigabyte of alien Zorn
Go to the power. Oh, yeah, let's let's don't quick. I gotta download quick. I need more
Server server put more download power. There we go. I increased my fucking speeds a little bit
I need to shut this off. This is annoying 50% incoming. This is dedicated Wham planet type
This is called Trojan planet and it's called fast radio burst
If 60% drink some of that coffee right now
66% fast radio burst. It's a bursting Trojan
Alien Zorn, I guess this is pretty fast
What internet provider is this five megs a second downloading from?
500 billion light years away. That's really good. The ping on this download is probably like
600 million. In fact, I probably had I probably already downloaded this like 30 years in the future
Right or like 20 years ago by now, right? How that has time works weirdly when you do it going through
Like light speed and stuff what would happen, right?
I downloaded this now and I started the download like 10 million years in the future, right?
How does that work because I activate the download now
It goes to do that to pull it but 50 million light years away
But it would take like oh no, it took a million years to me to get it, right radio is light dumbass
Okay, professor. Wait, wait, wait
That's not even right. That's not even accurate ready. Okay decoding complete. I got the message decoded data is oh
Great all this bullshit to have picked up like the end of a barcode on a single banana
Fantastic. How much does this facility cost? How do I bring this up to my supervisor? Right? I bring it
Look at this call. We got a secret code. Oh, we're gonna put it through all of our machines
Let's see what that is and think it put it in the machine and it's like one Chiquita banana 40 cents
Okay, do I get fired immediately? What do I do with this now? Just get this shit out of me. What do I do with this?
I have this decoded data. What do I do with the decoded data? Oh shit
Oh, I play it you can get this exact same audio holding a microphone up to the wall
If you have a neighbor that shares a wall while they're currently watching Monday night football
I don't think we found anything very spectacular. Wait, that's not that's just the sounds that's going on in the room. Wait, what?
Hold on. The alien is watching Monday night football. Oh shit. All right, cool. So what did I get any money?
$240
$240 for that upgrade the rotation please and oh what I was gonna do a cooling no more more charging
What else should I do efficiency lower the energy consumption? Yep twice fracking reduce the consumption of electronics. Yep. All right
We're good. I did it. I got my first alien. I got my first alien. I thought that was a gas can
How do I not need to sleep? I haven't slept in like three days like the bathroom
Why does everybody keep saying this is an alien climb out of the bathtub eventually? I'm sure it does
That's a weird place for toilet paper. I did that one time. I don't know what happened
I got stuck in a fucking light. I got like jumped it
I got jump into a light speed wormhole there didn't wash hands. I didn't do anything
No, I didn't know I didn't wash my hands cuz I sat on the top of the ceramic part of the toilet and then flushed it
I didn't touch it. I didn't like touch if I didn't touch anything. I didn't do anything. What planet was that?
Okay, it's time for another frequency I can't wait scanner
You know, I'm thinking I'm thinking up here. There'll be some aliens up this way. I'm really feeling top-right
veto this
I'm about to cross like the steam refund threshold. So therefore I'm not no that's not happening
It's too late one hour and 59 minutes and 58 seconds of its
Happy new year. It's been exactly two hours. I can no longer refund the game. Happy new year. Happy refund new year
Well, you should have why did you not bring that up to me an hour ago? You made no progress
I just I just solved the case of a secret alien planet. Yes
I did. I just got $200
I just cracked the case of an alien planet in two hours. It takes scientists like 30 years to do this shit
Imagine being upset that the scientists that you just hired in two hours found an alien planet. I
Really wanted you to do that in like 20 minutes
Come on, where is it? This is a super high frequency
Scientists haven't found aliens yet. Okay, you believe that then I don't know what to tell you
They've been in communication with aliens for like the last fucking 400 years 500 years
You get you guys didn't say like, you know
John alien signed the Declaration of Independence, but they fucking whited it out
They didn't want people to know get a big powdered wig on they photoshopped him out of all the photos by this point
Yeah, John Quincy alien
They just what do you want me to tell you wrong way? What come on? Yes. All right, what we got
56 let's give it a try
Go are you still playing this huh? There it is the two-hour mark somebody in pre-streams chat said
We're gonna pick this in pre-stream and in two hours exactly. We're gonna start seeing why is he still playing this right on the dot
They were right in two hours. Exactly. Here it comes. Oh
I gotta hold on power. Oh, no, it's already there
Still playing this
We're looking for 44
Alright, let's just keep an eye on it. Stop being mean to this game. I love it. I'm not being I'm I'm having fun
When did I say I didn't like this game? I just said that I was I needed a better tutorial and what's with the paragraph?
That's the only good wait. The only complaint I've had so far guys is the extreme paragraph space. That's it
Oh, and I hate the knobs or something, right? Whatever. That's not a big deal in the panels. What are we at 61%?
I'll do that today after I find this I'm gonna scan it and we're gonna watch the video
Oh shit, look at this. It's got from back from pooping for an hour
Is he still playing the science homework video game?
I would probably make an appointment with like a you you go into that for an hour
Wait, hold on this important was your computer in there because of that then that's fine drink some water
Yeah, but if you what it was a switch that counts too. That's fine. The video is of the poop slowly
Look at it can't look at it you fucking weirdo. Are we getting there?
70 what was it 75 stop stop stop stop stop stop stop it stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
or
D3
Free stop stop every three
Almost there nice job, dude up stuff stuff stuff up stuff stuff stuff alright now. We're just gonna do elevation
We're at now 53 elevation is 58 to 89 okay, so let's go
Let's go for it. You can find something stop diluting yourself this game sucks
Everyone knows that it's a meme game where all you do is I know that person's upset about this and that guy no
If I ban him for having an opinion he's just he doesn't like this game
Oh, what am I gonna say how dare you not I like something that I don't like wait
I mean I do I like this, but you know I'm saying I agree with this person
I think I like agree with that guy
But still relax we already banned him. No. I'm kidding. I'm just kidding. I'm having it. I like this game
It's fun. It's fun. Just sit and look at a number go up not a game with the simulator. It's a video game
It's a video game refund. I'm not why would I refund it? I'm I've been joining myself
I can we please pay attention to this
I'm so glad I turned on the easy mode. This would have been hell
Really really really really weird okay even more than 80. Hold on a second
I'm at 83 right now. I miss it. Did I miss it was it back down like 60 on really
No, it was not go to 90, but no max is 89
I like the part when the number was 60.1. Oh cool. I mean it was pretty cool
Let's call when it was that number for like a second or so. I don't know. Oh, yeah
87 got it. I can't believe people didn't like that. We got one thing thought that was gonna be a huge hit 88 89
There it is. We got it waiting for binary data. Let's go play the video. There's no video. Oh shit. Okay, hold on
While this downloads I gotta go clean the stuff downloading
Clean the solar panels. I'll be right back stop beating around the bush this game sucks. Give us catboy
You'll get catboy when you get it you'll get catboy when you get catboy not a second sooner, okay
How we doing 60% efficiency clean press F to start the cleaning system. Did I charge efficiency 100% F F F F?
Why is everything F did that work? It's going back up. All right. We're good. That's cuz I said F
Oh, well, I'm forever messed up just because of all the internet problems. I had over the last three or four years
It's being on fiber now every time I see the word F
I just go wait my internet my internet must be done internet sound cool looking like dog F is for fiber dip shit
Stop it. I would do another download 39. That's it. Come on
This like brings me back to when I used to go back on a 56k modem
I would download like stone-cold stunning people from like wrestling websites and a pixelated
160p video of a four-second clip of stone-cold stunning Ken Shamrock. I had a whole folder of
Stuns and rock bottoms and people's elbows and shit. It's like four hours to download them at a time watch a stunner compilation
You just told me how old you are. There was no such thing as a stunner compilation. You guys have it
So good, you had to individually download
Stone cold stuns undertaker. It was eight seconds long and it took four hours to download
You didn't get to watch it. You didn't get to preview it
It was a file you had to download onto your computer and then open it in Windows and no open it in Quicktime
Your kids and your compilation videos. Yeah, I meant do it now. What like you mean on stream? Okay. Well, sorry
I got a little upset that you just attacked me. Oh, that's just like we said of what we had
We asked grandpa how he was doing grandpa. How are you?
We used to have to download four hours to get a stone cold stunner and it sucked and there was no such thing as Amazon
If you wanted a package you had to send it with your own bare hands
You're just shot put it as far as you could into the fucking ocean and hope one of the dolphins picked it up and brought it
To your destination. Sorry. Yeah, that did happen. I just got like charcoal all over my hands
What I just touched the bottom of my chair. What the hell happened is this like tar on my hands because I touched the bottom of my seat
I underneath with like the metal part is I just grabbed it and was like
Touching it and gripping it. I don't know why I just was leave me alone. I'd wash my hands every break
Hi there. Yeah, I had some water. I went to the bathroom. Let's keep going
Rollback German with Chad Wario wear hair
Let me throwback. It was like two and a half years ago. Oh, that's what I look like now
Have I aged that much in three years? Maybe it is a throwback
Okay, let's go
Download is that 87%?
career over
Hey still here had really I got more credits added not enough data. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Why did it move?
71 wait, what? Hey, what happened? What happened 87? I don't understand what's going on
88 what happened you shit your pants. There we go. 88 89. Why did this move?
All right, download that shit. Hey Jim Beas. Thanks for the 10 community subs shit your pants
We doing shit your fucking pants now shit your pants. What are you doing?
Why are you guys doing this you fuck you shit your pants shit your pants
I'm not gonna do that. You guys got on this somehow clear the debt for shitting your pants
Clear the chat and clear the account because that's what would happen permanently. So no, this is the worst chat
I've ever seen. I don't know. I don't believe that we go
Translating to binary zero. Let's see zero one zero one one zero one zero one zero one zero zero one zero
zero one zero one zero one zero one zero zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero
Zero one zero zero zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero one zero
who cares? Yes that happened like five years ago. He told that story. That's a real story. He shit his pants. I think he was streaming too. That was on his stream. What do you mean what? Yeah, Star shit his pants on stream and he just didn't get up. He told this story like three or four times. You guys don't remember? Oh, a lot of you guys knew, right? Yeah, he didn't want to lose the match. If you think about that out of context. Well, in context too, that's not good either, is it? It's not good in any context. All right,
I got that. Wait, module schematics downloaded. Oh shit. Let's listen. Amazing link. Oh, yeah. Hey, ping, ping. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Shit your pants. Fuck you. I'm going to make their day better on purpose. Yeah, I'm going to shit my pants on purpose to make their day better. I'm going to make their day better on purpose. Like I'm going to shit my pants on purpose to make their day better. I've seen this. He doesn't get it. I do get it. Yes, I do. Okay, somebody explain to me why I can't get this out of my head. Smash Brothers
Witch theme song with the lyrics on it. Just that first like sacred hearts are having so much. I can't get it out of my head. Just the woman singing part. I can't stop. It won't leave me alone. Just that first. What are the actual lyrics? First sentence. Colors weave into a spiral of flame. What's the next part? What does that even mean? Nothing about past. Distant past called to a past still unnamed. Colors weave into a spiral of flame. Distant hearts called to a past
still unnamed. Colors weave into a spiral of flame. Distant sparks called to a past still unnamed. Bear this torch against the cold of the night. Search your soul and reawaken the undying light. I don't know what any of that means. You've sung this song like eight times. Do you think I don't? I'm aware of that. That doesn't mean I have to keep having it in my head. Scanner, please. That's your. Every event has led up to this point in your life. Are you happy? Yeah.
I'm doing pretty good. I'm good. I'm alright. I have schematics. Check the module. I will after I scan. Sacred flame to a past still unnamed. Distant voice through the song of the. I don't know. I've already lost it. You just gave it to me and I don't even know what the lyrics are again. It could be anything. It could be just a jumble of words sung to that tune. Oh, I got it. Alright, modules. Modules can be upgrading by downloading module schematics from a signal or analyzing, right? When a module schematic is downloaded, it will be up.
It will upgrade a random module. OK. Well, what did I get? I how did I slow mode Andy? Oh, stop. Oh, no, no. You're talking about. OK, you're talking about me. Yeah, that's 13000 people here. You don't think there's going to be a slow mode on for like a few minutes or a second or two.
All right, let's get that frequency. Got it locked in. It's your birthday today. Baldi, Baldi, happy birthday to you. I hope you have a good birthday today. That's Baldi in the chat.
263 18 to far away 1263 18 and I'll lose this signal, guarantee it. Guarantee I lose this one. That's power doing 65 percent efficiency.
My birthday. Put the music slider up. I can't. So you can hear the decoded message. Oh, happy. Thanks for the birthday present. I don't hear anything.
Oh, I'm going to sing happy birthday to you, but I'm going to replace a word in there with binary. Happy one zero one one zero one zero to you. Happy one zero zero one zero one one zero zero to you. Happy one zero one one zero zero one zero.
Dear Baldi, happy one zero zero one zero one zero to you.
Rude. I was calling somebody Baldi. That'd be so fucking evil. That'd be so mean. But that's their username.
Is that even their username? Did I get it wrong? It's not their username? Yes, it is. It's Baldi.
Not. Shit. It was Bradley. It was Bold Bradley. What did I say? Yeah, but I said the Bald Baldi. I'm sorry. That's not your name, but happy birthday to you. Nonetheless, it's
their name. It's Bold Bradley, not Bald Bald Baldi. Bold Bradley. Bold. What's their name? What's this person's name? Boldy Bradley. Boldy Badly. Boldy Badly. Not Bald Bradley. Not Bold Bradley. Not Bald Badly. Boldly Badly. Happy birthday. Not Bald Baldi. Bold.
Shit, whatever. The chat is going so fast. I can't fucking read it sometimes, man. All right, where are we going? I got pretty good efficiency right now. 65. And that's the reason why we have slow mode. Can you imagine without slow mode, I would never read anything. Go outside. Oh, fine. Read this, I'll shit my pants. I hope you don't do that. Don't do that shit. It's not like who is going to. That's not funny for anyone. That's not like we're just going to. That's a bad idea. Why would you do something like that?
That's not a smart idea. Don't do that. Like, don't take anything I ever say literally. And don't you say something literally that you're going to do if I say a certain phrase. Don't give yourself secret slime actions to do terrible things if I say them. If he says the word gazuntite, I'm going to shit my pants. Don't. Don't. Don't do that. Why are you doing that? I don't know. Just don't do that. Just watch. Just watch the stream and hang on. Here it is again. That doesn't remember the secret slime action stream. Yeah, you don't. Oh, I mean like 80% of you weren't
here probably. That's like circa 2015, 2016 or something. Wasn't that long ago? Oh, yeah, it was. That was at least three, four years ago. It was 2019. What are you talking about? Oh, oh, okay. You're talking about. Okay. I thought you meant the original one with me and Star from like 2015. Right. Okay. You're talking about the one with the slime, the actual slime. Okay. 260. We're at 295. Pull it back. Let's go. So we're looking for 260 to 320. We should be able to get a little bit of a view here. Keep an eye on that as you
move. I've missed it. 291. Stop. 290. Stop. 290. 290. 290. 289. Hmm. Interesting. 289.7. 289.5. 289.288. 288.2. That's not moving. 283. What's happening? Let's do the stupid other one. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Okay. 289. Oh, come on. 289.
Come on. 291. Close. 292. Pogchamp. Where's Pogchamp? Pogchamp. Pogchamp. What are you talking about? Pogchamp is gone. Pogchamp is deleted. Enable Pogchamp. I didn't turn it off.
Come on. Really? 291. The decimals. Oh, stop it. Stop trying to do elevation. I don't care about elevation right now. They removed Pogchamp. How am I missing this shit? Where is it?
290. All right. There it is. 290.80. 290.75. Okay. Now we just need elevation. Germovenus. Well, now you have to use Germovenus. Pogchamp gone. Where did it go? It was right there.
Well, now you're just going to have to use Germovenus. Don't refresh. Hey, just don't refresh and it won't be gone. Thinking face. There you go.
All right. We're looking for 31. We're going to go down. Way down. But you have to pay for Germovenus. Enable Pogchamp. I didn't turn it off. I don't know what happened. Twitch turned off Pogchamp. He did it. It was him.
All right. Elevation. 38. 37. I'm ready to pause. 36. 35. 34. 33. 32. 31. Got it. Download that shit right now. Quickly before I lose signal. Put it all to the server. Download.
What are they going to replace it with? Are they going to replace it with another Pogchamp? Who replaces the Pogchamp? What do you do? 1.6 megabit second. Yeah, that sucks. 8% download. That's so bad. It's going to be you. It's not going to be me.
Pogchamp is undergoing maintenance where it comes back as another guy. Is it just going to be another guy? So are we going to get Pogchamp when it's like not Pog? It's going to be like a different guy. Or will they even bring it back? Is it time to shine? Is it time to stand up and be like, hey, is everybody going to come out here and start saying, hey, I got a Pogchamp on my channel? Every single fucking Twitch streamer has their own version of Pogchamp. We're all vying for this space now. All of us.
It is now every man for himself, every woman for himself to become the new Pogchamp. There is not a single person on this whole website that does not have a Pogchamp version of themself. I'm open for nominations here. It's not going to be me. I'm not going to win. It could be slug Pog.
It's going to be so many. Oh my God, I can already see it. Who's going to be the new Pogchamp? I mean, if there's like a tournament of Pogchamps before that. Let me see.
Holy shit, what the fuck is going on? Well, I mean, I know about the stuff that's going on in the Capitol right now. But I know all of us know that that shit's going on. And it's been pretty stressful and pretty horrible to see. But I figured I would just want to try to pivot away from it and kind of at least escape for a little while. So I haven't really spoken on it at all.
Let's just have fun. It's obviously fucking awful what's going on. We're going to continue to look for aliens, right? Yeah, this is wild. They're going to be a new Pogchamp or something. But I mean, I don't know what it's going to be. I have no idea what they're going to do. What are they even going to do?
Yeah, I spent the whole morning pretty much going like, what the fuck is going on right now? What the fuck are you doing? What is going on? Remember, for president. No, no, that's not going to. No, no, no, no, no, no. Remember, you're old enough to run.
I wouldn't even make it past the I wouldn't even make it past the first like little primary where they weed out the people that are just doing it as a joke like me become president. I wouldn't do it. I would be a terrible president.
No, the jester does not get the crown. That's not it would be bad. I would like drop the crown thunder. It would be a whole episode of this show where I dropped the crown and it shattered on the ground and I tried to glue it back together and pretend like I never dropped it with with a like a British TV show laugh track. What happened?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
I'm not I'm not a fucking idiot. I'm gonna vote for like this person
No, this is like there was a joke for like a week
My immediate family would vote for me and actually I'm not even sure that would be the case either
I'm not sure that would even be the case. I don't even I don't think I'd even vote for myself
Cuz that's what you do
You vote for yourself all these presidents and all these they're voting for themselves. They're voting for themselves. They're not voting for the other guy
I don't even understand why they even ask or why it's like, oh, who did you vote for?
The guy trying to beat me in the election
I mean, you know, it'd be funny to actually just do that just to say that if you're the president like all the president voted today
With uh, then they went out they came in and let's get a let's get a little interview. Oh, mr. President
Yeah, I did you voted. I sure did. Oh, did you vote for a wink the other guy?
I voted for the other party other candidate. I like their ideas. I think they got a lot of things going for them
What happened but they just immediately would you just lose or would you just be like I've right wrote in Mickey Mouse
They're all you vote for yourself all of them
Okay, come out of the booth hold up the paper with the other person's name
Checkmarked the other candidate and say I'm voting for Dean dingus. I like his ideas and
By the way, I am resigning the presidency. What would happen would ever what would happen to the news stations?
All right, I gotta find that signal again. It was right here, right and then later on the next day
I say I was just kidding like guys that was a joke
That was a fucking joke you think I would what are you talking about?
And then the other guy goes no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, I don't think so
He's gonna do that shit. He just got all the cameras on him. Everyone's like talking about it
He's got he's got like a he's fucking trending. I
resigned my
Resign the nomination. Is that how you get like a Mickey Mouse president?
But then if Mickey Mouse got like 11 like a 5 to 10,000 votes like 11,000 10,000 votes, right?
Would Mickey Mouse become the president with that? Is that how that would work on election night?
they both say they they're resigning and they have to figure out who the
1.0 percent like 1.2 percent other votes were
Like Aquaman has like a hundred votes and he's on that CNN screen of potential fucking presidents
You got Mickey Mouse Aquaman Benjamin Franklin and Kanye. Oh boy
That's that's that's like a like a germ of rumble match
Confirmed for next year. All right. Where is this shit 1 and 12? That's easy. No, it's not it's gonna take forever
All right, 1 and 22. Oh, let's just start it. I would do I miss my power. Okay, how am I doing on power? Oh
Fuck, it's just me. How do I make efficiency better? I charge efficiency is 93% power consumption
How do I get more power? Oh, I do burn off antennas when they aren't moving
Make the Sun brighter
Start the generator. Oh shit. Okay
Next game up runs satellites aren't calibrated. They aren't previously on the next game of runs
Elevation is doing fine 31. Let's get that to
It needs to be like
30 it's getting there. It's 300. It's gonna take a long time. Actually. No, it's not shouldn't take that long
27 is that going up?
Komodo crew activated
360 to zero. Yeah, that's not that far. I mean it is but it isn't what is it?
I'm being spammed and thanks among themselves. Is that Jerma?
What the fuck is that that we can disagree with one and wait, wait, wait, wait. What are you fucking kidding? Oh
Jesus fucking Christ
I'm doing a new kill the meme stream. I'm gonna I'm gonna shoot a bow and arrow right through Jerma susses forehead
He's gotta go Jerma susses gotta go. I should have done it in a rumble. It's a fake image. Oh, you're gonna be on say it
Streisand effect. I know I don't
Talk about it. Have you he's going insane. Oh calibrate the antenna. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
I need to wait till I get this. How do I wait? How do you calibrate the antenna?
River temperature forty five point eight degrees at Celsius
You're a diagnostics on the server. Oh
But how do I change your fucking router password, you know, like nobody does what I do diagnostics. Okay, mom
There's no reason to
So why even have a password on it then?
Do you really think that you're like kid or something is gonna get onto the router? What are they gonna do?
Why is there a password on the router if that's the case?
What are you preventing somebody from doing?
You know how much of pain in the ass it is to type in like one nine eight dot one dot zero dot zero what it is
And hit enter it's because you have no roblox turned on after 9 p.m. So they could go on there and they could take the
The roblox server off the band list. I mean you can turn the password off
Can't you also just reset the router?
With like a pen to that one little spot that you just hold the button down and it just goes to factory
Why even have a password? It sets it to the default password, right? So
It doesn't go to factory. You sure it returned it return an error antenna server timeout
So people in your house can't get in the neighbors stealing the Wi-Fi. Well, no, no, that's that's the Wi-Fi
That's the password to get onto your Wi-Fi not the password of your
Your router
You have to be on the network to get on to the router, right?
Why are we talking about this? Does this really matter who brought this up who brought this up?
Well, why are we even talking about this is the dumbest conversation. I think we've ever had
It's all right, I'll see you previously on the next game of thrones I
Did it was always you know, it wasn't always me. All right, so we need to go to
Almost there to go to antenna 19 and reboot it. I will after we find the alien
Okay, I'm too. I'm close. I'm too close. How old is that coffee? It probably five or six days old. All right
All right, hold on. I'm getting ready to hit the stop button so I can hold on 20-point. We're getting close
I'm ready to hit stop 30.9. Stop 30.9. It's moving around
All right, it's 30.90 30.90. We need this to go to oh, just keep it going
Whatever and I Academy died for this. No Jedi Academy is gonna be played tomorrow
That's what we're doing tomorrow. Jedi Academy is tomorrow. I just leaked it. Hey, I'm sorry
I leaked it. All right, I'm gonna already stop this. Are you lying? No, 30.9 is what I need
All right, let's see that we got if 3 to 15. So we're getting there. Here we go. We're at 3
I'm gonna have 3090 is the what we need 3090 right there is good boot it up five
Keep an eye on that Ozzie booth. They're gonna have ray tracing. I don't have the 2080
I have a 1080 after all these years really five seven to 72. Are you kidding me? This one sucks
It works just fine. I have not had any problems with 1080. They can't run watchdogs legions
But why would you want to run that game in the first place? I'm perfectly fine with the 1080 right now. It's sturdy
It's hardy some would call it the Super Nintendo of the Nvidia GPUs. It was it's the perfect card
65 is the max. All right. Well 760 is the Super Nintendo
No, I don't know but I don't think I agree with that. Here's the Christmas deluxe bundle event
The 1080 will get you at least three more years of high. You need a better CPU for streaming though
Yeah, I know now once
GPUs come back and stock really and people don't have to make like discord bots to figure out when they can buy one
I'll get one. That's my CPU I
768 50k 6 core stop. Okay, we need where we got 31
We need to go back to 30 30th. Is this gonna be like a mirror here? Okay, we need 30
Well, like yeah 30 and 39. Let's do that. You missed it 30
32 what I missed it. What was it 30.5? Oh shit. I mean 9. Hey, what was it then 31? Oh dummy
Don't change that. Come on. Hurry up. Come on 31. Come on 30.5 and
We this is moving around too much pretty point. This is looking this moving around. Oh, how do I it's the calibration bullshit now?
Auto track it is downloading a point four megabytes a second. What is that bullshit? What? Oh my god
I have to reboot the server. I don't even know what to do next with server. Is there a server tutorial? Where's my mouse?
Calibration you can check the calibration test for all antennas in the terminal. He's just calibrate. Okay
Calibration reach this panel. You said it's not so I see her. Okay
Calibration looking for an Italian cattle. Okay
So how do I these are all wrong? I have to make these all zero Jesus diagnostics. I'll start
hell start
antenna controls and detection disabled
Fuck I'm still downloading this
So, um, I gotta pee again. I'll be right back pee time. Hey, happy new year. It's you
Why is it always a break but never a poop break? Oh, well, it's really easy to
Explain because I typically don't like need to poop during his stream. I give you a streamer tidbit of knowledge
It's insider information
let's say
70% of every single reason why a streamer is late is because they are currently
Taking a shit and they want to make sure they don't have to shit during the stream
So that's why I would say at least 75% of the time
That's what's going on because and here's the worst part when you start to feel it coming on
Let's say I'm gonna start streaming at 3 o'clock Pacific at like
245 if I start to feel it coming on it's oh
Okay, I know if I start streaming at 3 that's gonna be ready to I'm gonna have to do something
I have to take care of that at like 4 like 330 and I don't fucking have to just go take off like 30 minutes
So you just delay you say hey, I'm having some technical difficulties
What one of my wires is plugged in weird my USB stick?
I just I can't get it right to fit the right way. You can never get it the first try
See you in 45 minutes and you wait till it's ready you take care of it
So then you can stream for like four or five six hours without having to worry about it that image by the way
That you're looking at right now was on Travis touchdowns t-shirt and that's in full HD
That was the one that was it right there
You got to see it up close
Casino ain't got robbed a lot of people think that
Alright, let's go. It's a good dick-dash of Lee Richard. What was I doing? Wait, it's calibrating the antenna
Do I have to do this? Is it doing it on its own? Oh shit. It's doing it on its own
It's doing it still downloading on seven point eight percent said you would stream Doki Doki Literature Club
I already know like you can't if I play Doki Doki Literature Club
I first of all, I don't play those games. Anyways, I don't play those that kind of game. So there's strike one strike two is
So many of you guys told me to watch the movie and hey watch this movie, dude
You're gonna love it, especially after the first hour. Mm-hmm. Oh wait. Hey, hey this movie
It's such a good movie. Just wait till you watch it for an hour and then let me know what you think
Okay, cool. So I know something fucking happens in like an hour. It's gonna be like a big twist or something. Great
Thanks for telling me now at like 59 minutes when one hour crosses. I now know here it comes
Listen calibrate or what? Oh, it's doing all of them doesn't matter do it
Anyways, but you want to pretend to be excited and pretend to be shocked when the thing that everybody wrote Pepe laugh
He doesn't know you know how many times I've seen Pepe laugh. He doesn't know he doesn't know about Doki Doki Literature Club
But you want to pretend to be shocked when I see the thing that happens calibration takes a while. Okay getting more power
By the way, that's good. This is still downloading and this sound needs to turn down not the right one
I don't know which one of these is making that sound what I need. What is making that sound?
Okay, it was the stupid-ass TV. My room is covered in posters with one of the Doki Doki characters
What does this um, how do you want me to say about that?
Alright rare TV spam
That's right rare TV spam and remember when I was gonna remove bald coin
I held I held on to removing bald coin long enough for it to be relevant again
I should have held the real thing long enough, right? But no, I kept the emote
I held the emote but not the asset. What a fucking dope
He sold omega well, not all of it. Not all of it. I have enough to open up an account. Look at it and go
And then close it because of I got out like two years ago
I have enough I have just enough and I had more previously for me to be in the shower
randomly like once every like two or three months now to just go like
Get the shampoo in there. There it is. It feels pretty good
Fucking should have held I had I should have held them
Feels good should turn the water off, you know, you have aetherium. No, why is it quiet?
I turned all the volume down on everything. I kind of miss the the like frog sounds. Don't you?
Yeah, I miss the summertime frog sounds. This is an alternate universe. What shampoo do you use? I use the lush
Everybody asked that all the time. What?
Calibrate this already. I lost all my data. Please be joking. Why is it a joke? I use lush I use big and vegan East
I'm not vegan. I just happen to like this the conditioner. It makes my hair feel nice omega. Lul. He's vegan omega
Yeah, here you go. Fine. Is it weird that I feel like if the word vegan just it's not even it's just activates
A bunch of bots that write the word omega lul vegan. Like I don't think people are writing that
I think they have that you put you have like a notepad that has a bunch of like random insults on it that are
Copy and pasted like a bot that's set up that just says omega lul vegan every time the word vegan is heard because it's immediate
Holy shit antenna number four is fucked. We have to we have to get a new one go to sleep now
Oh, yeah, it's not a bad idea. He said the he said the vegan word check bathroom. I love baths though
I'll tell you I'm a big fan of baths drinks heal and uses vegan shampoo. This streamer is fucked to you
I like you. Yeah, I will die on that hill you could all right fine
You can fight me on the lush thing if you want really you'll lose like I mean you're gonna lose cuz I mean
It's just I like the products. Yeah, you're not gonna win the heal argument with me
He wears a healing bracelet. No, I had I told didn't in that video. I even said I don't believe in this
It just looked cool. I'm not wearing a healing bracelet right now. And if I was whatever, you know, it doesn't matter
It's my life. If I want to wear a vegan healing bracelet, I'm going to it's my life
So you don't have to worry about it. Did I sleep? What's your skincare routine? I use a micro exfoliant
Let me say that again, I use a micro exfoliant every three days and then I use a gel cleanser each night
This is I do I use an eye serum
all real
Every maybe three or four nights. I use this eye serum underneath my eyes at night
You tap it in because I'm starting to get a little crow's feet and stuff
It's not that's not vegan and I try to drink at least at least six to eight glasses of water a day
Is water vegan think about it don't like I'm like squirrels and stuff like die in the water and everything
I don't like fish like die and stuff in the water that you it gets like processed, right? But is water vegan?
Why is it at zero? It's fucking nighttime. No, they filter out the squirrels
Somebody said there's a literally a fossil fuel tier level argument. I don't know what that means, but it made me laugh
It's built
What is what I'm trying to piece together what that means a fossil fuel tier level argument
Fossil heal also fuels equal animals. It's not vegan
But you don't drink fossil fuels. You don't drink gasoline. Okay, not enough data
Let's recalibrate. I still have a signal right going not have a signal anymore. Oh
Oh
Set oh
Set you're a bunch of liars. Yeah, they are this is what they do. Look I've had plenty
I I've had vegan food. That was good. I've had vegetarian food. That was good. I've had meat
That was delicious. Come on, but you can't enjoy something that just is just plant-based or whatever. Why why not?
I don't have to like pray to like a vegan God
Like enjoy a vegan based meal. I don't have to have like a shrine to a head of lettuce or something
It'd be like a vegetarian. You know, I just it sometimes it's nice. It's so this is like good
I know it's not gonna be I'm gonna feel like light. It's gonna be not gonna be heavy
Come on, your skin is gonna turn green
Breaking news people don't need to go to extremes
Like I've had beyond burgers before with like vegan cheese on it. I was like, this is good
This this this taste this is guy. This is I don't hate this. This is dad. This is good. This is fine
Sometimes you just want like a butternut squash soup and a little piece of toast
That's something wrong with that
No, I don't want to drop a meat patty in there today. Not today. It's okay. That's fine
Yeah, you guys are taking the the BK stacker commercial way too literally and I knew when they aired that that was a bad idea
At the second it aired I was like this is a bad idea what they're doing here
Welcome to the stackers Union, buddy meat and cheese no veggies and that was that was cool
It was like, okay
This is probably not a good idea that they're doing this they like they they're working like leaned into
Don't put vegetables on your burgers because they're gross meat and cheese only. It's like, okay, it's not a good idea
184 14 god damn it. Well, I calibrated right and take all day
200 fuck go
His vegetables would be extra expensive if I wanted lettuce and tomatoes, I'd order a fucking salad, but I want a salad
I want a burger
well, I agree with you with the tomato part, but there's other vegetables that are not tomatoes and
Sometimes you want that sometimes I just want like a one steak sauce, but excuse me back up
meat cheese grilled onions grilled mushrooms a one steak sauce
Excuse me
I find that to be very very good now if somebody wants to be mad at me for that
You've not eaten yet and you will just be swearing into your hands with a full burger with everything
I just told you to put on it and you'd be like fucking idiot stupid fucking dumb. I fucking hate that guy
So stupid he's just dumb you couldn't get the signal right in the fucking game single system
I did the game's fucking easy. He did took up two hours. This is all this sandwich stinks. It smells
I hate this guy sucks. I have
Hate this fucking guys. It this is really good. This is really good. See he fucking couldn't figure it's a signal
So I mean, this is working good. I don't have no power. I have to reboot the whole base
You know, I've reboot the entire base. Is that how this works? Okay set password
Okay, new password set new password set pass what no set pass set pass it doesn't even work
What's the security hole here? How do you not feel heavier after vegan meals? Half of them are entirely carbs
I thought I just all I said was I what do you mean?
lettuce tomato
Mushrooms look, okay. I know I keep saying lettuce tomato mushrooms and onions, but that's not vegan meals
That's just that's like the condiment level of vegan food, right like lettuce tomato onions mushrooms
That's not a vegan meal. That's vegan condiment. That's just that's if you add this stuff. I love grilled onions though
Hey, guess what? That's a vegetable
No, it's not as meat the whole base is off. I need to go to bed turn the generator back on. All right, there we go
Seafood onions, I don't know what you mean by seafood onions, but I love seafood and I love onions
But I don't know if I I'm not sure we put them together. You know, I'm a big fan of crab cakes. Anybody else crab cakes
I like California rolls, but not with the fake crab. I like it with
like actual crap
What and I didn't just tell you that that's the only roll I ever eat. I like spicy tuna
I like salmon rolls raw so
Relax, I didn't just say
California roll is the only sushi I've ever eaten and I will fight you if you disagree with me
I did not say that. I just said I like them. We get a new download speed here. Come on
Charge this shit. I'll phone your rules of boring. So fake California roll. What do you think about Korean barbecue? I love it
It's awesome. The generator. Yeah, I just turned it on. It's boring but good. Yeah, you know what else is boring a cheeseburger
It's meat cheese and bread
That but they're delicious what a pounder for the win
I agree what a pounder better than whopper or the whopper bigger than quarter pounder
So like the rock outside, I feel like I haven't I've not done anything in the game in probably 25 straight minutes
We've just been talking, you know, sometimes it's that's what you do. We're just hanging out
We're gonna see the alien before the stream turns off. I've probably not like the rock 500 million dollars in research
Like ten years of
developing this place
Telescopes
equipment radars
Light speed we can see into the distance and I picked a shoe up on the ground and that's how I found them
I just came and picked up a shoe and found the alien
I don't have a kid and here we have right now. I'm sitting here
Surrounded look around in a circle
cameras audio equipment
detectors
Circling me but I don't have any way to capture what I just looked at
That in the middle of the research facility. No way and nothing captured that
Just my eyes and now I have how disappointed is this walk back
This must be the worst thing that this has ever fucking happened. Just like oh no
Look at all this stuff
But it was my entire life was dedicated and nobody's gonna believe me. Oh
Well, I guess we're gonna try to listen to
Like deep-sea noises 10 million years away for another 20 years. No one's gonna believe me
Sit on the bench
And I at least get like a disposable camera from Walmart
Wait, maybe okay. We have all this expensive equipment, but what if it was just something very simple, you know
We're trying too hard good link. All right fine
We'd judge of that. This isn't the right link. I mean that was all right
Okay, do we have power?
we do
at point two nine percent efficiency I
Stopped downloading
actual link
Okay, not that one
Wait a minute. What do you got here? You got McDonald's in the basket down there?
I like it a nice berry heal. All right, cool a healing bracelet and
A lush shampoo this looks pretty good to me. I don't have a problem with any of these things
This seems like a really good like Friday night to me shoes in the tub. No purple alien
Purple alien has become an influencer
I think I just have to turn everything off and just let the word let the facility charge for like an hour
And why is it that I cannot use the facility while it's plugged in if it's dead?
I
Can't stand that when I'm sitting there with if you have a dead phone and you plug it in
Sometimes you have to wait like 10 straight minutes for the thing to turn on because it runs on battery
It doesn't you can't there's no such thing as a running on AC with a phone
Like why can't I run my phone off the wall that pisses me off all the time is what you're doing
Is you're not running off the wall. You're charging the battery and running off the battery
You're not running off the wall and I don't know if they're concerned that
That although if you unplug it you would but you're running on the battery does who cares circuits can't run off AC
The Android can do it. Can it phones don't run on AC. Yeah, but I mean it annoys me
I will say I'll be in the middle of doing something my phone will die and it's like, oh fuck
I'll just plug it in and I'm just sitting there with my hands on my face
Staring at this thing like five to ten straight minutes like check it. No, I can't turn it on check turn the fuck on
I'll leave I'll have to go do so but I come back. It's still not on hold the button down
Finally. Oh, there it is. There's the Apple symbol and it's at like 12% charge
Well, why didn't you turn on when you were at like five? What's that bullshit?
It's very very annoying Android phones can turn out at 1% then I have to relearn an operating system
I don't want to do that. I already know everything is on iPhone. I don't know what to do
I don't know where I already know where thing is
I don't want to like to have to get I've been using Apple
Mobile devices since I was like fucking I don't know like 20 25 or something
I use Apple for all my mobile devices
But have I refused to use Apple for a desktop and I'm getting to the point where I might start
I think I might switch Android thinking about it. They really pissed me off with that iPhone 12 mini bullshit
I'm serious that made me irrationally upset those who that don't understand what I'm talking about
There's a lot of people that might not have been here like six months ago when I talked about this
The iPhone SE comes out and it's a little phone. It's the iPhone 4 case. It's a little guy. It's just a compact phone
That's what I want. That's what I wanted. I don't I hate this big-ass phone bullshit
I hate the huge bricks in your pocket
What do you I need to carry around like a fanny pack or like a backpack to carry around an iPhone now or an Android?
All of them. They're huge. It's stupid. I don't like how big they are. It's annoying to me. So they are teasing
They're teasing there might be an iPhone SE 2. Oh my god
I can't buy iPhone SE 2 you kidding me iPhone SE 2
It's gonna be small right cuz that everybody loved it people have been begging them to make that right the iPhone SE 2 is
Not small. It's just a standard iPhone size and it looked like they were never going to make a small one again
You think that the SE SE 2 would be the same thing you made a little phone
It was the SE the SE 2 is not a little phone and they there's no they don't tell anybody anything
Oh, well, no, just wait. We're making a small one. Nope
They just fucking announced one day randomly that like iPhone 12
Mini is now a thing after everybody that was an SE fan bought the SE 2 thinking
This is the smallest phone we were gonna get these these you know
These I they came up with iPhone 12 mini like six months later, and it's the exact thing that I wanted
So now I have to go buy a new iPhone go trade in the SE that's horse shit. That's absolute dog shit
They just want to put a 12 on it. They wanted to put a 12 on it
So people go one two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve. I got that one. I want twelve
SE what's that? What? S
super I
extreme I don't
Twelve means better twelve small. Oh
angry angry
It makes me so angry
Like you you're
You've been hot this whole time
Can you get back to work we can hit we've heard everything I don't know what you're talking to but
We've heard reports that there's some new sounds at sector 21
Yeah, I'll get right on that. Thanks Mike
See I'll talk to you after work or something. No. All right. I'll talk to you after work. No, you're not
You know, okay. I'll see you later. Bye. All right after work gonna have a fun time
We're gonna go out and go to Chuck E. Cheese
All right, I'm just gonna I'm gonna hang up my line so I'm gonna unplug my line
I always tell it 3.3 percent. This is fucking bullshit. Happy hour at Chuck E. Cheese
What happy hour at Chuck E. Cheese would be they put two or three extra ski balls in the ski ball machine
That's what that would be. Can I download this yet? All right, it's at 16%
All right. All right all power to download. I lost the signal
No turn power off. I need to recharge
I'm a small hands. I just like a small phone. They're just too big. I just I don't you guys I use my phone to
make phone calls and
Check like Twitter. I don't I don't need a big movie screen
I don't need three super high pixel like HD cameras
I don't care. I just want to telephone they actually played the game or yet or you just yeah
I have we found like three or four different signals
But I just I'm waiting for the house to recharge at a landline then no
I'm not gonna get a landline turn on the generator. Yeah, I'll turn it on
No, no landlines. You can't carry a landline around
The whole point of having a little cell phone is to have a little phone that people can like contact you in your pocket
what used to be a thing that was it had an ability to be contactable when you left your house has turned into a
movie screen a
Movie camera, so they're too big. When are you gonna be satisfied?
How many iPhones do they have to go through before before the wheel? That's it
Like that's all we're gonna do how many G's do we have to add we're gonna go to like 10g
I don't even use 4g you do no
I but like do you though one of how fast do you need to load your Twitter feed?
3g Andy you're coming actual boomer moment
Yeah, but like what at what point is it do we need faster internet for our phones?
Streaming we need it now. How many do we need? I don't know
I can call somebody and talk to them just fine
I can like tweet out a photo of me giving like the thumbs up at my favorite restaurant
And that just goes up like in one second, but the quality sucks
You're using like 5 gigahertz internet in your phone right now now in your home right now
But I'm not what I'm not walking around with my desktop and my monitor like attached to my back and in front of me
I'm not downloading like GTA 5 on my iPhone point is it's getting too fast
And when eventually it's gonna get too fast with they're gonna start thinking they're gonna start making problems
They're gonna realize that like our spleens don't need to exist
iPhone iPhone like
50 with like
25g is it gonna be able to understand I can I can make that spleen better. They don't need that spleen
What's it in there for I'm so fucking fast
Okay, all right. All right. All right. I'm done. I was gonna keep going, but I don't I don't want to keep going
I need to stop that now
You know
That was an Ellen tweet
Yeah, it was it was it was like how are we gonna get we're gonna get to
iPhone like 55 and I don't know how long it's gonna take before we get the iPhone 60
It was something like that, wasn't it?
Okay, I have to stop but this is just the shit. I'm wait. I'm trying to get to fucking 7% phone battery
Okay, this is the shit that we have to do. I have to fill time
Joker Ellen, what are you talking about?
Ellen the Joker are the same person
Start turning things off. You aren't using
What what do you mean turn things off that I'm not what that's how this works
Oh my god
Turn the lights off. Turn the lights off. Turn everything off in the turn all the lights off
Turn the stove off turn that's on
Turn all the lights off. I need to conserve energy so I can turn my iPhone on
Unplug everything
Fucking iPhones. I swear to God there are these lights up wherever they go. How are we doing?
Okay, I'm set 8% battery turn the generator off. Yep, turn off the monitors. What I can't turn the computer off
I can't turn off the solar panels. I have one thing at a time
Turn everything off
Turn off the stream
Where's the generator however, I would I go I can't drive this car turn it off turn it up
I'm turning off the generator right now. I can't it's off. No, it's not what turn it off turn fucking generator off
Alright, that's it. Where's the door? Please use iPhones. They're infinitely more secure and private. Alright, everything's off. Nice
10% battery literally every computer can guy can hack an iPhone
I don't I don't know any of it shit about that. It rings and I answer it enough a light in this room
Is there one in this room the Ellen show? Hold on the Ellen show she says
200 years in the future honey. Have you seen my iPhone 378? I needed to pre-order my ps6 my ps6
Why would it be iPhone 307? Why would that what is that implying that only one more playstations coming out in 200 years?
That's the joke fucking hilarious
New deal. No, we're gonna already
Do a cooking stream for 1 billion off the debt. Yeah, I think about it. It's all gonna be cloud-based
That's the theory right?
Well, that's the theory about the stadia is that Google knows it's terrible and knows it's an awful fucking system
But they're playing like the 10 to 20 year long game. So we'll see turn off the antennas
You can already thread cloud infrastructure. I don't know what that means, but it sounds important turn everything up. It's going faster actually
Yeah, cool. New deal. New deal. New deal
Keeping the battery at zero. Hold on. Let me see what this person's saying
Keeping the battery at zero is bad. So your phone charges a little bit
They can they can endure on of AC and bypass the battery. I've never seen it before careful now
Don't put the cat puke into the soup. What's the next big leap in technology?
Do you guys think it's self-driving cars or do you think it's quantum computing or do you think it's something else that we don't know?
What do you guys think AI?
Batteries. Hmm. VR sex. Hmm. Okay, the perfect Poggy mode
AI it's probably it's gonna be either well, it doesn't AI include self-driving cars in a way. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know
I don't know what it's gonna be. It might be something just that comes out of nowhere
Battery an upgrade in battery technology would be good because right lithium is not good, right?
then the whole thing about lithium batteries is what we run everything on lithium and
That's not a good thing. How do we make better batteries? Hmm. Interesting. There are batteries. I think reusable paper plates
Hmm. There are batteries. I think play the video game. I am
For the people that are just like
What it why is he sitting with the lights off I'm playing the game
Solid-state batteries. What was this game about? It was about finding aliens, but we found the alien the alien flew overhead
Spoiler. I saw the alien at least his vehicle. It's gonna right here. All right, we can boot it up
Scanner go in the chat Joel in the chat. What's up, Joel?
How far did you get in this game? Did you beat it? Did you find the alien?
I couldn't I found the alien spaceship, but I didn't find anything else you found the alien. Oh shit
What are you doing this game? Well, you're about to see right now. You have to scan for planets. You have to find sounds
analyze frequencies
upload the frequencies to the governmental database decipher where the alien is and then cause an immediate conflict and
Start an interplanetary war as fast as possible and my record so far is about is 11 minutes. So
Okay, we need here. We are
300 is the minimum and then we got 20 324. Oh
It really is she knows I'm sorry
Let's go drop that power poke noise. We still go. I'm sorry. I just I just scratched you in the eye
We're still going up in power, right? I'm still we're still good. This is not gonna start draining. Is it?
Perfectly balanced at fifteen point six. Okay, we're good lock the doors
Oh cares the only person here a helicopter comes every day and drops off like red
Spam and eggs or something. I don't know aliens are gonna get in well
They're doing a really bad job of it so far. Those doors have been open for four hours
All right, three, what's it on 24 and 300 still counting up charge is doing good at the bathroom
I keep going in the bathroom. Everybody keep Joel people keep saying check the bathroom
They're trying to be funny with me. This is something that's funny in the bathroom. They're trying to be funny with me spoilers
You know everyone was telling me to call you like two or three hours ago because I couldn't figure out how to play the game
And it was I had a little bit of a problem and I was like, I don't I he's like probably he's like
It probably could be eating dinner. He's probably I don't he could be busy. I was gonna call him dinner at 1 a.m
It took him two hours to do the tutorial no
It took me two hours to figure out how to play the game and then it took me about 40 minutes to do the tutorial
Alright, I gotta pay attention. Oh, wait, wait, wait. This has got to get to
306 it's gonna be coming up here soon very soon omega. Lull fleas. What did wait? What do you say? I missed it
You think I know dude
I played this game forever and I forget all the time
All I know is there's a funny alien with a green booger for a dong and he's out of his spaceship
I guess that's all there is to know, right?
Well, maybe I'll find him probably not though. I'm gonna be honest green booger. Are we doing again?
A ton of errors, please. Don't ever play this game again. Um, why not? What other color boogers are there? It depends
It could be green like yellow bloody brown. Why am I who cares? Why are we talking about this?
There's no reason to talk about this. Of course. There's other colors for boogers
You should know you just picked one out and ate it losing power losing power losing power losing power
I'm draining power right now for something. It's nighttime shit. I'm not even gonna get this frequency
Why do I have to be so far away about?
300 fuck was that was that was that what was that?
Well, stop stop stop stop everything stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop everything. What was that? What was that?
Was that the video feed for the coordinates I was passing or is he like in the house he's in the house
But where in the bedroom find him laugh my ass off. He's just running in the snow. I don't see him anywhere
He's not here. Wait, there's like green ectoplasm on this. Hold on a second. Did he like raid my fridge?
What does he do to my fridge? It's in the fridge. He peed on the fridge
Where is this little guy? I would love to use in the computer chair. All right, let's see. Let's find him
That video feedback on zero percent. How did I sleep from night to night? It's just nighttime again
You were abducted you lost 12 hours. Oh
Well, I'm just gonna go look around outside
Remember the clip the clip. Yeah, let me see. Where was he? Was he next to the refrigerator?
Where was he? Yeah, I'm seeing him right here. Wait, he's peeking at me in the hallway behind me
He was right here. No, he was right here. He's right here peeking in here show the clip
All right. Yeah, look, it's just pretty fucked up
60 seconds late actually late what?
60 seconds late
Why late actually late whole late but not surprised late
What are you what's going on here when I scrolled up? Why is it going back to the very beginning of the stream?
I scrolled up like three scrolls. Hey, give me the clip one more time. I'm gonna show it
Those of you that missed it. We can examine it. Hey
Those of you that missed it. What was that? What was that? What was that? What was that? Stop stop stop stop everything stop stop stop stop stop
It get up get up. Look at that. He's peeking in. That's crazy, right? Oh
Dude, it's fucking crazy
Dude, that's fucking crazy, man
Nice. All right, cool
All right, I was gonna I'm gonna go outside and I'm gonna just drive around I'm gonna try to run him over the car
That's what I want to do. I'm gonna find him and I'm gonna run him over
I wish you could drive the truck. It's unfortunate that you can't they glow in the dark
Okay, I'll find him. It's not him right there. Is it this is a little guy right there
Oh, it looked like a little guy with the green eyes
Like I got lucky, huh? Check the rock again bring a camera this time. Nothing on the rock. I don't see anything
I'm it's okay
Is this if I just stand still is a scenario where I'm just gonna get sniped if I stand here for long enough
I feel like somebody all the way up there has just got me just in the crosshair and they're just waiting for the perfect opportunity
And it's just gonna be oh, but I'm gonna just fall down. I'm gonna die go to the train tracks
We're the train tracks Tom. He's there where all the tracks follow the tracks
I don't know rain tracks, right? Stop. Okay train tracks follow the tracks. Oh, what am I gonna eat? I'm hungry
Let's try order. We think
There's nothing on the tracks. Is it a McDonald's kind of night? Hmm. No, I had Burger King two days ago Taco Bell
Oh, just follow the tracks go between antennas 10 and 12. Okay order from a good restaurant
That's not a bad idea. Lots of those in Las Vegas you live in Las Vegas. Oh, yeah
I love the food in Vegas the best some of the best restaurants in the world so much variety so much to eat
I'll figure out something. I'm not gonna order like a Big Mac. Okay tracks train tracks fast going too fast too fast
So slow down left faster faster faster faster. What is it? What am I looking for? Exactly? I missed it
Go go back go. Oh my god. What is that thing? What is that planet? Oh, but I missed it go back
I don't see anything turn around turn around turn around. There's nothing on the train tracks. What was that? Wait, what was that?
What was that? Stop stop stop stop stop. There's like a weird thing on the ground over here. What's this? What's this?
What is this? Why is this here? This doesn't make any sense. Why is this like this? I'm telling you we ain't on earth
Look at land it over there planet over there planet back here. You can't then then that thing whatever that is
I'm sorry, but you cannot see Venus like that from the naked eye standing in your backyard
You can't you can't do that you cannot see that that whatever planet that is you cannot you literally can't know you cannot
No, you can't you literally can no you can't what the fuck is that thing? It's moving. It's coming over here
It's coming this way. Whatever that is. It's moving closer. That's not a helicopter
No, it's not is that just where the UFO thing spawns just waits there until you do an activation for it
Every time I do the telescope it's gone. I'm gonna keep it in frame in my eyes if I look at it
Has to stay hey guys German at a five here fuck I didn't I see a rock I see a rock I see a rock
What should I do with this rock? What about over here dude train tracks? I'm not driving down the train tracks again. I'm sorry nice
It's back. It's right there telescope telescope telescope telescope right there. All right telescope. Where's my base?
Oh go go go go go go quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick right there go go go go go go go
Wrong way hurry hurry. It's right there. I have to
That's not a helicopter. It's right there. Come on. The person is a person's face. Okay, so now that's an Easter egg. Oh
Is it Tom Cruise? It's not I don't think this Tom Cruise. Why is it flying vertically like that? Shouldn't be flying horizontal
That's the alien good deal. All right
I I think I might have had enough
Jeremy you stream three times per week for six hours and there are 168 hours in a week with this much time in your hands
You could be literally a serial killer for a hundred million off the debt prove that you aren't a killer by telling us what you
Generally do while off stream
but I genuinely do when I'm not streaming so I tend to I
Take a lot of baths usually I'm bait. I take a bath for a little while usually what's my what's my routine?
I get up in the morning so between
Depends maybe at 8 o'clock in the morning between 8 and like 12 really just it depends usually between like 8 and 11
8 and like 1030 try to get up. I
Have breakfast. I use the bathroom. I take a shower bathe of some kind morning routine. It takes a while
I usually take me about one to two hours to be ready for the day. So after somewhere around 12 to 1 p.m
I'm ready for the day. I just take you that that's your psycho. Why that's what a killer does
They take two hours to get ready for the day, but I get up. I use the bathroom. Okay, let's break up
Let's break down the exact time that this would take you roll over your alarm goes off. It's it's 9 a.m. Okay 9 a.m. I
Get out of bed stumble into the bathroom immediate full 50 to 60 second piss. That's a minute now. We're at 901
Yeah, I walk into them. I live in kitchen. I get a something to eat. Okay, bring me some
Okay, this takes about me 25 minutes till I get them prepared and eat 930 now at 930
It's time to okay turn the shower on
Get in the shower 10 to 15 minutes go by maybe 10, but maybe like 10 minutes now
You're at 9 at 940 945 get out of the shower pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat my face do a little skin routine
Now we're talking 10 a.m. Or 98. Well, yeah 10 a.m
At this time, maybe maybe 10 to 15 minutes later a little I acclimate a little bit
I sit around I I've got to take I've got to go to the bathroom. I've got it
Take dump. Okay, whatever. I don't care if you hear it 10 20 30 40 minutes depending on the day now
We're at like 10 30 10 15 10 30 I get up. It's now like 11
Like I don't go back to bed and then get up in 30 minutes. So I
Name is Jeremy. What are you doing? Oh stop around 11 a.m. I like rather than to the 12
I'm ready for the day. I think how long that takes I if I have errands to do I have stuff to do
I have to take care of the take care of my place
Do I have to clean something do I have to do like dishes or do laundry or I mean it stuff takes a few hours
You know, I can't I've got to like take care of things. I've got to clean stuff up and by this point
I'm hot. I'm ready for lunch. That takes like an hour. So errands daily errands somewhere around like four three or four o'clock
I will um, yeah
I
At 4 p.m
After doing kind of the day and they've taken care some errands and whatever I'm not streaming or something
I am sometimes I come back and sit here. Oh, yeah, take care of auto too. Of course, I feed auto auto goes out
We I take I mean auto spend time together for at least an hour once I get to 5 p.m. What I do
I don't know what like what does anybody do sit on like the computer go to reddit go to
checks the my like
Accounts and stuff and check on things and change the laundry over
I do a whole I do kind of a lot of sitting around
That's also now though right in like a pre-covid world it was you know, I would go out, you know
Yeah
I mean I think you kind of the the day is just sort of uh
After like four or five or six p.m. The days kind of just become alright
I did things that I was doing today now
I guess I'm gonna what am I gonna do now watch a movie watch some TV play a couple of games off stream
I did that go out and kill
Look I'm not there you go 168 hours a week
Yeah
How much of that is sleeping you stream three times a week for six hours and there are 168 hours in a week
So remove like seven to nine hours a day of sleeping
It's actually more like 40 to 60 hours a week that I have if that yeah
I do a lot of cleaning a hundred hours of cleaning. I
Don't know. I don't keep track of like my daily routine. I just kind of live
I just exist and like eat food and like go on the computer and like take care of Otto and like run errands
What are they like normal humans do unlike your victims?
All right easy easy easy take a hundred million off take a hundred
Take a hundred million off. I'm a normal guy. I'm a normal guy that is normal things and that I don't I what am I?
Live in Las Vegas guys. I don't want to have basements in Las Vegas. Okay, I've seen that a few times
Oh, you probably bring them down to your basement. There are no basements in Vegas. Sorry. I'm a normal guy
It's in the attic. No, I don't have any
Out in the shed in the floor and what's why did you use this photo? By the way? I don't understand
Why why this photo what's wrong with this photo? You chose this photo is the one that's the time the serial killer photo
I mean, no, no, I think it looked fine
You're out in the forest. You're displaying. This is the murder forest
Alright, okay. I'm out of here. I'll see you guys tomorrow
He's on his tiptoes
No, I was like walking
Did I was walking?
Somebody put the camera up while I was walking and I stopped in the middle of walking and I went hey
Mmm, I was middle of I was walking towards this camera. They said hey, hey, here's a photo and I went up
I stopped. Mmm. Look at that tiny feet. No, I don't I have a size 10 as normal. I'm a normal person
I'll see you tomorrow. I'm done. I'm this this game was fucking fun. I you know, listen to the tone of my voice read through the lines
It was good
I'll see you tomorrow. We're gonna play Jedi Academy tomorrow. Thanks for watching. It was fun
It was at least we got to see the alien. Thanks for watching everybody. Good night. Take care
Let's see who is uh, let's see who subscribed today. Yeah, take care of yourselves. Good night
That's uh, I I give to take 500 million off of that. I told you what I put my daily routine was that counts
I just kind of exist. It's gonna hang out. No deal. No deal. No deal. No deal. No deal
I didn't prove it. How am I supposed to prove it? You want my like receipt from Walmart?
I don't know what you're talking about. I'm gonna show you that like the part of the house that I cleaned
How am I supposed to prove that I just like live a normal life I
We're gonna we're gonna raid donkey tonight. See the donkey is streaming right now. What's he doing? I think shoot gun
Shoot gun. What game is this? Don don
Pachi never heard of this
Vertical shooter though, you know how we love those
Go say you go say hello to donkey. We'll see you guys tomorrow. It's a gamer game. I wouldn't know right
Thanks for the subs though, there's a there's a always a shitload of community subs
Always a ton of people still subbing to this channel years later
I don't even know what to say that it's an insane amount of support and I don't even know what to say about it
I'm shocked every fucking day. So
Thanks a lot guys
We'll see you tomorrow for Jedi Academy
Maybe we'll see you there. I have not have a wonderful next tomorrow. See you guys soon. Go say hello to donkey and good night