Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. My name is Hector Arafieri. I'm here to teach you the secret strategies of Team Fortress 2, some of the unspoken things that most people don't talk about.
But let's not dilly-dally anymore. We're going to get started right now. Are you ready?
First of all, you want to make sure your settings are all in order before you start the game. So make sure you go to your settings, pull up the audio and video files, and make the proper adjustments.
Now once that is done, you want to change your FOV to no more than 90 at a 1920x1080 resolution because there is so much evidence and so much mathematics and state as to why you should never have it past 90 FOV, but I will not go into those details just to make sure that it's no more than 90.
But Victor, what if I don't know what my best resolution is?
Timmy the Boy, ladies and gentlemen. Timmy the Boy. There he is. Joining my video and fucking it all up. Thanks, Timmy.
And now I shall teach you how to activate the hit sounds in Team Fortress 2. It's actually very simple. You go to that click it. Here you will find a beautiful arrangement of all kinds of different things to activate or potentially deactivate.
There they are. How beautiful. And the default ding noise is actually pretty annoying. So what we're going to do is change it to something a little more excellent.
Perfect.
But Victor, how do I install the TF2 sound in the TF2 folder?
I really have no idea how to do that. It could be pretty difficult. It could be quite easy. I just, I don't know, maybe somebody help. Help!
And the final Team Fortress 2 super sequence strategy is none other than how to use the developer console.
You can change your weapon model FOV. You can change your FOV. You can change your FOV. You can disable your FOV. You can do so many things with this. I just spit in my own face.
I hope you enjoyed this beautiful arrangement of clips of how to become a Team...
Hey!
Yeah?
You're being really loud.
So, I'm sorry?
It's alright. Just be a little more quiet next time.
Okay.
Well, shit.