My friends are kind of shy, press button 1 to talk to them. Stick around, they may have a lot to say.
Well that's good. Button 11 is jump. Button 2, what are those? Oh. Why am I taking advice from rats?
Why, and why are they, why can they talk? It's all about the speed, dude. See, look at that. Just don't, just gotta move.
Same exact thing I would say about Super Meat Boy. These like super crazy, like hard, like unforgiving platformers.
You just gotta go. You just gotta move, man. Take a look at that. That's how we do it. 22 seconds, almost flat.
Best time in the world, 22 seconds, look. So I'm gonna push this rock over to the right side of the rocks.
Rock's gonna get hit by the dart coming out of the statue's mouth. Statue's gonna bounce over, off the McDonald's, off Grimace's head, nothing but net.
You got it? Let's do it. You're supposed to wait, huh? Go on. Come on. Come on out.
Oh, I have to get this, I gotta get this crystal skull. Come on, I'm Indiana Jones. The worst movie he made.
Fuck! I've gotta get that skull. It's very important. I need to get like the super points. I have to.
If I don't get the extra points, then what's the point? That was a pretty good pun, wasn't it? If I can't get, I gotta write that down.
Hold on. If I can't get the points, then what's the point? Give me an Emmy. Give me a fucking Emmy!
So this is where the actual game starts, huh? Things have fallen already. Unforgiving. We're not gonna get our hands holed anymore.
There's no mice. None of our mice friends are here to tell us super secret strategies. So we're on our own.
No. No. I guess we gotta go this way then. I guess so.
Oh, I can push this. Just need to use a little bit of science. Once you've deduced the problem with the scientific method, that's when you win the game.
Good old science! She planted me with science!
I'm not gonna last. If you guys think you're gonna get a series out of this, I ain't gonna last, dude.
I'm gonna last like 20 minutes and I'm gonna go get like a fucking sandwich. That sounds like a better idea.
You know what? What kind of sandwich do I want? Now that I'm thinking about it.
Because that's like more important to me right now than this like game that's really hard.
I think maybe I'd get a large like steak and cheese with some onions. Mmm. That sounds pretty good.
Maybe a buffalo chicken sub with extra blue cheese on it. That sounds pretty damn good.
Yeah, stop talking about sandwiches and play the game. Like focus. Focus on the game, not buffalo subs.
Not messing around. I need to be level one. Level one needs to be completed.
Fucking god damn. We're gonna cut that out. We're gonna edit. See, we just edited.
Hey, what's going on? Jerma here. We're just gonna play some Thousand and One Spikes level one. It's fucking easy.
This is my first try. You know what I mean? So is it weird to lose like almost like 50 lives before the first level?
Is that considered? Am I good? Am I good at this game?
Okay, assess the situation here. When I jump up, I'm gonna get shot. So I don't want to go that way. I want to go across.
I knew it. Yeah, you can't trick me. Spikes. You always have to look out for spikes. There's spikes everywhere in this game.
I know the game's called Thousand and One Spikes, but there's spikes just everywhere. There's spikes everywhere and there's scorpions.
Isn't that like a Pokemon? That looks like a Pokemon. Is that like Scorpezoid? Isn't that a Pokemon?
When is my Scorpezoid gonna evolve into like a fucking Scorpezio?
Whoa! I don't know what to do. I don't know where to go. I'm freaking out.
Alright, just stay right there. Okay, we just got a bunch of Scorpezoids just dropped. Good to know.
Drop down here. No, not yet. Not yet. We're gonna wait. We have to wait till he goes the other way.
Get out of the way. Here we go.
Spike? Yep. I know your game now. I know your stupid game, Spike. Spike? No.
Shit. What do I do here? What do I do here? I can't do anything here. I can't make that jump either, can I? Can I?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't think I can. I can.
Button. Press. Jump. Long jump. Long jump.
So what happens if I die 946 more times and the game's over? Is that how this works? That's definitely gonna happen.
I'll burn through like 700 of these by World 3. Well, I should probably be careful then.
Excuse me. I said excuse me. You're supposed to get out of the way. This is like World 1.
Jump. Drop down here. Jump. Shoot. Jump. Shoot. Jump. Shoot. Got it.
Scorpezoid. Get out of my face. Do I risk it? This is a bad idea. This is a really bad idea.
I knew it was a bad idea. That's exactly what I needed. Okay. We're gonna drop this one down too.
Go. Go for it. Beautiful. Absolutely beautiful. Just don't screw it up now.
Don't you dare. I don't even know. I think. I swear. I'm good. Yay.
So what do I do here? Do I drop down here? I don't know. I'm confused.
So I must have to break that? I don't know. Don't do that. You're gonna get burnt. Now do it.
Okay. It's broken now. One more time. Go. Spikes. Yeah. See? You didn't think I knew that was gonna happen?
You think what? You think I'm an idiot right now? Dude, I'm so scared right now.
Where do I even go? When I get over here, there's gonna be like spikes and shit.
And there's gonna be like a face shooting at me. Darts. And you know it's gonna happen.
And I'm probably not gonna survive this because I have not been down here yet. Oh, God.
Make it. Make it. No. I turned and I shot. I turned and I shot. I did.
And you all saw it. I turned with total precision. That's it. That's it. No.
We're done here. We're done with this. I'm just gonna go for it and I'm gonna get it right now.
No stopping. No bullshit. This is the Super Meat Boy strategy. I've said this before. Just go.
Just go. Don't even stop for anything except for the things that you have to stop for.
Go. Like, for instance, just go. Right now. Turn. I'm shooting. Just go.
After this, we're just gonna go. We're gonna go the whole way. Whole way. Yeah.
Yeah. Come on. Shoot it again. Go. Shoot it again.
I'm beating this right now. Wait for the stupid piss fire to come out.
No. No. Just wait. Hold on. Not yet.
Now do it. I'm just so concerned about the leftover here.
And even though it's coming out so slowly. God. Seriously. Go.
Grab this. Watch the spike. Watch the spike. Nothing's right here. But I can go.
Time to go. It's time just to go. Just go. After this, you're going. You're gone.
You're already gone. And... Holy shit! Oh my god!
Yes! Oh. Ooh. Ooh.
Is that the end? Is that the end of stage two? I hope so.