You didn't order any food.
Oh, I gotta order the food first. Hold-
Okay, ladies, hold on.
All right, so you want a chicken sandwich.
You want-
Okay, ma. I get it. I understand.
I'm really sorry. They don't have any more chicken sandwiches.
Sorry, mom. I know you're mad about it.
I'm back. I got- What did you want?
My mother needs a chicken sandwich.
Okay, let's just- I gotta back up and go get it.
It's in the back.
Hold on. It's in the back.
Hold on. I think I got it. I got it.
I got it. Coming back.
Here's a chicken sandwich.
How the fuck are you riding this motorcycle?
Where did- Wait, there are employees in here now.
There's employees in here.
What the fuck?
Where did the employees come from?
There's people sitting in here too.
There's all these dead bodies that they're just sitting on.
You have the door locked. They're just skiing around.
How do we get out of here?
What did we do?
Do you see me?
Yes, dude. It's on a motorcycle.
I'm in the ghost world. I can't see anything in here.
This is the most ghost world I've ever seen, Jerma.
All right, so you're in the ghost world.
You are bumping into these ladies.
This entire room is empty.
Just start throwing punches.
You punched a lady.
Guide me. I'm in the ghost world.
Okay. Closing all this.
I have no idea.
Dude, that was ridiculous. Just two random workers.
I got to get out of here.
I got to get out of the ghost world.
I can't take this anymore.
Oh my God. I don't want to go back to the real world.
Jerma.
I'm playing The Sims.
None of this is making any sense.
I'm playing The Sims right now.
This is my house in The Sims.
Oh, there's one of my players.
There he is.
No, Jerma. No.
What if I get out?
I'm stuck in the ghost world.
I think we're both stuck in the ghost world.
Do you see what I'm seeing?
Nope. It's gone.
Jerma, the burger shot.
Currently. Okay. Here I come, captain.
Hey, Jerma.
It's too bad you did the pillow jump into bedfall.
Get up. Get up.
What are you, a punk?
You're probably going to want to stand outside the burger shot for this one.
And just look in.
I have no control of my character.
Again.
Why am I going into burger shot?
I'm just going to let this play out.
Oh, okay.
Let's pump the gas.
Where's your car?
All right.
No. Okay.
We're going to play house.
Okay.
We're not house.
We're going to play like work.
What about the gas?
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
You get in a car and you pull up.
See this person.
We have to like give gas.
God damn it.
Nice driving, idiot.
This guy's trying to get gas.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
You're going to pull up further.
Pull up further.
Let me help you.
He won't.
I would like some gas, please.
No.
There's cop cars everywhere.
So you're just getting gas.
It's not like you're doing anything bad.
What?
Where did that come from?
Why did that?
Hold on.
Get over here.
This person just drove off the bridge.
What was the point of that?
They're still trying to accelerate.
He's still in there.
This guy drove off the bridge.
He really wanted to play house with us.
I know.
He wanted to come get gas.
Well, that made him get out.
Oh, now he's coming after you.
He's going to kick your ass.
I'll lure him to the gas station.
All right.
Yeah.
Lure him to the gas station.
He's wicked fast.
Oh, my God.
He is.
This guy is on so many drugs right now.
All right.
So what are we going to...
Where is he going?
I think he...
I got my bro with me.
I'm pretty sure he forgets where you are.
This guy.
You leave this guy alone.
Dude, it bounced.
Hold on.
Come here.
No, shit.
No.
I didn't mean to...
It's cute.
So yeah, you're dead.
No, I'm fine.
It fell off.
Fuck you.
God, that's a huge crash.
You, shag.
So loud.
Fuck you.
Screw you, bitch.
It's like a crack in that window.
I need to help you on this one.
Somebody got wrecked.
Do you see this guy?
All right.
Let's go wreck somebody's car.