Silence. Silence. The end. Okay. Explore the world. Let me get this on for you guys. We're just
gonna chill. I gotta change this to... what do I change this to? Winding down for a little bit
and we'll... is GeoGuessy even on here? It is. GeoGuessy. Okay, that should be updated, I think.
Uh, no, I need to... no, I need to capture the window. Not the browser. Add window. There we go.
Not that one. Which one is it? Why does somebody process this for this? What the hell? This is
a weird... um, it's gonna have to open some other window. For some strange reason it doesn't want to
work. Okay, uh, let's try it again. Colon cam. Incoming colon cam. There it is. All right,
that took a long enough. All right, I see things. I see things. Let's try not to get
the ads in there though. There. We could do without the ever-changing ad. Okay. And then
let me get my camera on. That camera's way too big. Is this delayed? Shouldn't be. Hey guys,
how are you? Move this... I gotta move the camera to over here. Hold on. Sorry, I'm moving
you around a lot. Let me see how that looks. How does that look? Well, that changed quickly.
Over here, right? Like this? Crazy eyes. Not in frame. I am now. And then we're gonna flip me.
Watch this. Ready? Take a look. Greasy hair. It's not greasy. It's just slippery. Okay. Geo
guesser. Are you ready to play? Look, I played Mr. Mosquito for like fucking two hours. Of
course I'm gonna be sweating. All right, we can go. Thank you for your patience. Uh,
let's find out where we are in the world. All right, so we got, uh, walking... walking
person. Car? What's a car say? Let's just walk down the road. Somebody said Minecraft birch tree.
Look out for the car. I'm in a car. This is a... What is the kind of road is this? This is
small road. This is not in America. Is this two lanes or is this... You tell me a car comes
down here? No, we're on the right side of the road. Well, we'll find out. If a car
comes the other way, then we're not in America, but we're definitely not in America
anyways. What does the sign say? Don't walk or crosswalk? No, this is definitely not
America. The road's too narrow, but hold on a second here. Maybe it is. This is... this is...
I think this might actually be somewhere in North America. That's not a Euro truck.
That's not... that's not a Euro truck. This is America. This is America or somewhere in North
America. We're on the right side of the road. Nobody else does that. We're one of the
places... only places on earth that does this. Keep going. Uh, what is this person doing?
This is in... this is Russia. Passing? Who are they passing? Who are you passing? They were
passing the Google truck? I was gonna laugh if there was like a finger out the window.
This couldn't handle it. You had to get around the Google truck. All right, so we're
somewhere in Russia, Ukraine. The aspect ratio is too stretched. Why? Because it's like
squished. All right, hold on. Let me fix this. Why is this still on? Is that better?
I don't want to... okay, the reason why I don't have the whole thing out here is
because I don't want you to see this. I don't want you to see like the... all the ads that
I have to get. That's good. That's fine. Yeah, that's fine. That's fine. Look, ready?
Now you don't even know. You can't even tell. This looks like we're watching a movie.
All right, so somewhere in Russia. Definitely not a cold part of Russia. Everybody's bad.
People in Russia, man, you don't want to be behind the Google truck or in front of
whatever. Let me see here. Uh, let's just say... because, uh, I'm gonna say
a lot of green down here. It's definitely not up here. Let me see if I can get a sign,
although I can't read. So how am I gonna do that? It seems like outside of some... a very major
city somehow. There's a lot of, uh, development over there. I'm gonna just say here. Challenge
your friends. How the... how the economic machine works. I don't remember getting ads.
That wasn't that bad. I don't remember getting these ads. 3,000 kilometers. That's pretty...
that's not bad. Considering how big Russia is. All right, next round. Why are the outsides of
the windows blurred but not the part of the window that matters? The window part. I don't
know what you're trying to blur here. All right, let's take a look. Let's go down here. Uh,
dirt road. Green, white house with a shed. Okay, let's get off the dirt road so I can see.
This looks like a little European town. Oh, another... look, a Euro truck, right?
Is it prison? What does that say? I can't read that. I could get onto a highway or something this
way. All right, where we go? Okay, hold on. Kapampin. No, this is also... this is Russia.
This is also Russia. Is it? Is this Russia? Russia's always so hard because Russia's so
huge. Russia is like 30% of the whole earth. Let's go down here, right? What is that? Oh,
I thought that was an animal. What are you... what are they doing to this house?
Is it... is it brick? Bricklaying. Interesting. Ireland? No, this is not Ireland. This is Russia.
I can't read that. There's nothing... I don't think there's anything there. I can't...
there's no words there. I don't think this is like a major city. Maybe this...
I'm like stuck on the dirt roads. This is... I don't know. Let's take a guess. White
intersection. Uh, no major city. It's gotta be like a town name or like a town center.
Okay, hold on. What's this? Bank. That's a bank? Bank of... Ben? Bank of Russia. I don't
think it's Bank of Russia. What about down here? Hold on. The thing... the thing about Russian,
maybe it's just because of the alphabet, right? We use the... we use the same alphabet,
but I feel like I'm looking at words in a dream. You know what I mean? Like,
I feel like I'm just... it's so upside down and backwards in my brain.
Like, I feel... when I'm in a dream, I feel like this is what the letters look like in my
brain. Next time you have a dream, wake up. Next time you have a dream, look at... open up a book.
You'll see. All right, I'm going for it. It's the same place I guessed last time.
That's like the same exact spot. It was the same... it was the same spot. It was just over
here. No, I didn't... what am I clicking on? Why did it just load up an ad? It just like
forced me into an ad. All right, here we go. Turn on your ad block. Does this site open
with an ad block? Is it Russia again? I don't know about that. This isn't... this might
not be Russia. This looks American. Yeah. This is... this is definitely American.
Somewhere in the Midwest. Give me a street sign. Give me a name. Give me a name. Anything.
Stop ahead. We're in America. Only in America will it warn you to make sure you understand
that you need to stop at a stop sign. Only in America is that possible. There's a stop sign
before the stop sign. Divided highway, okay. That's a warning stop sign. American town in
Russia. Oh, we've got Westby. That could be anything, though. Westby. But no, wait. Population
2,200 people. This is the middle of nowhere somewhere in the Midwest. Can we get a state,
though? Come on, let's go. Old town, motel, restaurant. There you go. You've got
Kansas's finest. Come on, right? Can't see. No. Galaxy? What about this side? Oh, hold on.
Madison? Wisconsin. Is this Wisconsin? Madison, Wisconsin. So if Madison's 104 miles that way,
where's Madison? Where is Madison, Wisconsin? Madison. It's 100 miles off of Madison. Which
way are we facing right now? This is important. That's my compass. So this is south. So we're
going red means it's pointing, right? So this is south. This is like southeast. Wait, what do
you mean? The red is the indicator, right? Or is white the indicator? Red is north. Why would
north, north up here? North is up. So this is north. This is northwest. So this is 104
miles northwest of Madison. I don't use fucking compasses. Okay. Let's find Westby. So we have
104 miles northwest. Westby. How much 104 miles? It's fucking up here, isn't it? Westby. Westby.
Up here somewhere further. Westby. What road is this? If it's 104 miles on this road.
What road? 14, 12. This might be 12. 18, 14. I'm gonna say like right up here. Warrens,
Thomas, Sparta, Whitehall, Melrose. It's like up here. Did I miss it? Wilton, Jefferson,
Caston, Ontario. 5,000 points. Didn't get it by the street. I'm not looking to get it perfect.
Did you enjoy this location? I've never been there. All right. That was good. That was a good
run. Hoots. Health Mart Pharmacy. Hoots. Still in America, I think. Let's find a city or town
center or something. Wilenskis. Wisconsin. No. Wilenskis Brothers. Saba. What is it? Head Start?
Saba. San Saba. What's? Wait. No, no, no, no. Hold on. What's down here? Bella?
Oh, apparently not. Why would they like blur that out but then not blur it out?
Okay. So this is obviously somewhere in America. Let's go up here. I'm not ready to take a
guess. Decker. Decker Street. Recreation Club. The Busy Bee. Smart. This is all boarded up.
Recreation Club. Where? Okay. We're in Menard. Where is Menard? Looks like this is a school
down here. Maybe they'll get a town name. Is it a pool? It's out here. Hold on. Wait, wait,
wait. Menard Manor. Hotel in Menard Manor. Let me go down here. Right. School. We love
our children. Drive slow. Is it a church or a temple or? Let's go over here. Can I
can't go down there? All right. What about the school? Wait. Hold on. The Menard News.
A lot of these places love to have the name of where you are in the title of their.
What's this? Okay. Weirdly enough. All right. The Menard Church of Christ. That's four
churches. That was one, two, three, four. The elementary school. I think we've gone off
there. Whoa. That's what made me puke. I got to get back to the businesses.
It's definitely somewhere in down south. Has to be. I went way too far away.
I got to go back. Bowie is okay. Back over here. I'm gonna go all the way back. Menard
News. I feel like I can get this one. Jacket's Rule. These places don't even have a
thing on them. Wait. First United Methodist Church. School of. What about back on the
main road? Ah. What we got? John. Eden. Eden. The land of Eden. Yeah. It's Texas.
Okay. Menard, Texas. Is that on the map where it is? Look at right there. Hold on.
Look at the little blip that's right there on the map. You see that? So like right here.
So that's here. Not very many towns here. Menard. Menard. Anybody see it? It's like
right here. Fucking told you the blip was going to help us here. All right. So hold
on a minute here. Let's get this 100% accurate. Menard Manor. Right here. I'm
gonna go stand at Menard Manor. And I'm gonna get 5,000 points. This is 100%. I'm
literally standing out the front door of Menard Manor. We're here. We made it. Wait. It's
where you started. It's based on where you spawned. I don't remember even where I spawned.
Starting location? That was up here and to the left, right? So if we're looking at
Menard Manor, we go to the left. Now we're on 2092. Press the flag. Okay. All right.
All right. Okay. And now I had it right. There's Menard Manor. We're like right here.
First State Bank. It's like right here. Ranch House Meat Company. Hoots. First State Bank.
Chamber of Commerce. It's right there. It was like 10 feet. 5,000 points. That was a good
one. That was two good ones back to back. Harry Potter and the Chamber of Commerce.
That would be a real boring fucking movie. All right. Another sign. It said Menard. That would
be if it was... I hate being out in the middle of nowhere because you almost just have
to go in a straight line till you get to a junction of civilization. There are no houses
out here. There's nothing even out here. Look. One guy lives out here. One guy lives out here.
You know what I think is really weird about something like GeoGuessr is the amount of
probably the hundreds of thousands if not millions of people that have played this game.
Millions of clicks and the millions of refreshing and new locations.
How many times has somebody walked by your house? How many people have looked in your
window? That's weird. You were in my hometown last time you played. See that's
that's crazy. Wait what what's going on? What happened in chat?
I was in your house the last time I played. What is it? Creepy pasta? I don't understand.
Somebody trying to put in creepy pastas? People are posting creepy
ASCII art. It's a meme thing. Do that in your own house. Hey do that in your own house.
I am in my house. All right what we got here? TWP road San Do San Dio. Oh my god. What is over
here? What is stored in there? What is over there? It's it's corn. Just like hurts my eyes.
I don't like the resolution in this city. Whatever it is. I got the bad graphics settings
in this city. What's that? Something up here. I can't even go this far. Why does it end
here? Was the google truck afraid to go down here? All right I that was weird. End of the world.
We're gonna get we're gonna get to the end. We're gonna get to go look over and see the
space. That's the end of the earth. You're gonna go you're gonna go like whoa whoa. I have
no idea what the hell I am. The earth is shaped like a velociraptor. I just the thing
I don't understand is if the earth is 70% water why doesn't it just fall out and go
into space? When you pour a glass of water it goes straight down and you spills all over
the place. So if we're 70% water and we're you know like why is the water not just out in space?
Earth's mass holds the water here with gravity. I don't know about that. Gravity is something
I put on my potatoes and you're telling me that's yeah you also put that delicious tastiest
thing on that's what's keeping us together. Okay. Got some scientists here. Are you
fucking weirdo still doing ASCII art here? Don't make me bring out the mallet. I'll
bring out the hammer. I don't know who the fuck I am. Sub mode? Uh oh. He's about to put it in
sub mode. Maybe if you're good I won't have to do it. Subs are doing it too. I am okay with
if you're a sub that doesn't mean that you get to break rules and spam and
just because you're a subscriber you still got to follow the rules. They're down there
in the description. Just because somebody gave them a lot of money. What? Yeah they did.
Holy shit. Frodeon Weapon thanks for the 50 bucks. 50 dollars from Frodeon Weapon. 5,000 bits.
Gravy is what keeps us together. I love the chill parts of these streams. Yeah. Thank you for the
50 fucking dollars man. 5,000 bits. It's a lot. Um we've had a couple of just kind of chill
hangout streams recently. Sometimes you do you got to just slow it down right?
All right it might be time to turn on sub only mode. You know. Now you've done it.
Sorry I mean we got to control it somehow. I mean all right everyone slow down ever calm down.
All right I need to find out where I am. What have they got in there?
Wrestling? Chief Wrestling? Chief Wrestling? Chief Westins? Westins? Juno Upsetto just gave
five community subs. Thank you Juno Upsetto for the five community subs. That's a lot of subs.
Thank you. All right we just. Russia is like impossible. Russia is hard mode. It is.
It seriously is. Look at these. Bang. Bang. Bang. Where are you in Russia? Who has any idea?
Uh let's do it again. New map. New zone. Now where is this? I don't think this is Russia.
Why is there just a car here? Is this car just abandoned? Why is there a car just pulled over?
Are there people? Five more community subs from Lorag. Lorag98 thanks for the five subs.
Where's the person whose car this belongs to? I don't know. How would you? Oh my god. Jesus.
Not so crippling depression. Thanks for the 10 community subs on top of the other ones
that have already come in. 10 from not so crippling depression. Thank you. If everybody
gets a sub, sub mode doesn't matter. Uh Danishin thanks for the five community subs. Lorag
thanks for 10 community subs. More. Slowly releasing the people that cannot talk. Thank
you for the 10 community subs Lorag and Danishin for five. But what if you give it
to a spammer? Oh my god Adventure MF Dan. Five. Jesus. Five community subs from Adventure MF Dan.
10 community subs from Bebraham. You guys are too much. Thank you. Thank you for the
massive amount of community subs. Even more. More of them are coming in. Time for slime.
It's time for slime. Five community subs. Thank you. They're flying out all over the place.
Five more. Oh and look what happened. One got in. One got in. You let one in.
You let one in. Uh the bala koala thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you for the 10 subs
bala koala. Turn on no chat mode. Oh my god that's fucking so funny. All right I need to
find a sign. Sign. What does that say? You are now in Delaware. Prejalan. All right this is
uh German lot about Minecraft VR thanks for the five community subs. Five. Five more from
Mostly Lost. Another five. Five from Mostly Lost. Five from German light about Minecraft VR.
All right there's an ad down here that it's trying to tell me how much money I have.
It's it's giving me like a bank account number. What is the I don't understand this.
It's in it's since 4th to 7th April it's it's gone. No it reloaded it. What is this?
Why is this tax included? Oh no that's how much the plane costs.
Should I book it? 770 to Argentina. Tax included. That sounds pretty good.
37 Destininos. Destinos. What is that? What money is that? What uh what currency is that?
37 Destinos. What does what is that in US dollars? Pretty good deal. Uh Jeff five
community subs. Thank you Jeff. Five community subs from bingo sunshine. You have to geoguess.
Bingo sunshine five. Here comes like the 50 to 100 subs. You guys are fucking too much.
Thank you. I need to find out where the hell I am. Got it. Watch this one. EFM Losiers off road.
Uh four by four doesn't give us a name though. I kind of want to get back out to that main road.
You baiting subs with geoguess or mind tricks. Um no I put it in sub only mode because people
were like ASCII art spamming. That's what happened. Is this France? I don't think this
is no. I don't think this is France. This is by the um Latin America. No you guys gonna behave.
Behave. Just behave. You need to be on good behavior. I I'm I what at the end of the year
the twitch.tv award ceremony that that happens. I'm people are gonna reference this. I'm not
gonna get nominated like I did last year for most well-behaved chat of 2019. I really really
hope we were gonna get that award but the academy will look back and they'll say oh
everyone knew they were spamming Momo in the chat that time. I can't even go this way. This place
is off limits. Why is that off limits? A private road. How do you even fit a car down here?
Sorry Jeremiah I can't let this go. Destinos means destinations is not a currency.
What are you guys doing? ASCII gets you 30 minutes. Oh I would oh be careful then.
ASCII is now 30 minutes. That's a monka s. Unless you want to be timed up for 30 minutes and there
you go. Fire hydrant. This chat is a mess. Jeremy Albertson contain it. I'm trying to tell
you. I'm containing it now. 30 minutes for ASCII. 30 minutes for asking me about ASCII.
30 minutes for the escape key. Somebody said it's called GeoGuessr.
Not walk around in a circle till you see a sign. Pretend that I'm currently. All right look.
Did you see how perfect my last few scores were? I'm currently dealing with an unruly chat
and I'm trying to like dodge and quell an uprising here. Where are we?
Lacan in Sade Salis. There's like a Gnome and Momo ASCII uprising in my chat right now.
What do you mean don't put this on chat? I didn't do it. I'm like pasting ASCII. I didn't either.
Here we go. Point tourism. So tour agency sports restoration defibrillator. There's
a defibrillator inside the building. Torrisme. Okay we got it. 30% off. My whole fucking head
hurts now. This is a game as of a headache. I got it though. Like it's like cold back
here down into my spine. I just I just pogged myself to death. Okay that was pretty good though.
That was close. You got concussed. I just gave myself a concussion. He's turning into a twitch
streamer. Yeah I'm morphing. 33 years old. I know. I know. Trust me. I ask and answer
that same question every day. I know. But here's the thing. Sooner or later I'm gonna
have to start dressing. I can't wear like a Captain America t-shirt in like five years. Can I?
If I'm 40 do I have to like wear like vests and jeans? I have to wear like slacks with a button
up shirt. I don't want to do that. What am I? What am I? My dad or something? What am I? Dad?
There's a lake there. There's a very long. There's a very long lake that water runs
forward in. Long forward running lake. You guys are way too easy. It's too easy sometimes.
It really is. How do I do it? You gotta like lift your head up and go. When do I plan on ending my
streaming career? I haven't thought about that. When I'm no longer having fun. That's real. When
I'm no longer enjoying what I'm doing. When I'm not having fun anymore. When I'm not enjoying
it anymore. I'm not gonna do it. You know. I'm not gonna give you. There's no time for it
there. That could be in 10 years. That could be in two years, six months. It could be
tomorrow. I could wake up tomorrow and be like, well, not tomorrow. Don't do it tomorrow. Tomorrow
is my birthday. No, I would. Okay, look, we would do. Here's what's gonna happen. I know it's not
called GeoGuessr. It's called GeoGuessr. Don't fucking stand there and talk about your life
story. I know. Listen, when I'm done, I will make it very clear. I'll make it incredibly
clear. I'm gonna be like, guys, we've had a really, really great time. I've been doing
this for like 25 years. I like to spend some time with my seven children. You know,
Dave, Danielle, Dave, Danielle, Donnie, Danielle too, Davey, Rick, and Dick. But you'll know.
I will have a retirement party. We're gonna have a retirement party for me. Not tomorrow.
I just went through the world. Dude, I teleported to the map. Barberville. Stop
doing that. Stop. What the hell? Let me see this. Oh my God. They bug in the fucking game's code.
The collision detection in this part of the world is just not very good. It was Barberville,
but no, no fucking around. No joking around. When I'm done, whenever that is,
I'll give everybody plenty of notice because what I don't want to have happen is to be like,
oh, hey, guys, I'm done. I'll see you later. I mean, there are people that, you know,
maybe just to subscribe to something like, I want to give you like a long time to know that's
coming. But I don't just, whenever that happens, it happens. I don't foresee it happening for a
while. Don't say anything and just disappear for five years. Burning out. I spend a very
large amount of my energy making sure I don't burn out. Injured. Is this Vegas? Those are
everywhere. Anti-burnout. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you guys know that. I take a lot of time
off. You know, like for instance, after this, I'm going to just take two days off. That's not
because I just want to make sure that I'm like ready to go. You know, I take time off each week
specifically to prevent the feeling of like burning out and being like, I got a stream.
I want to do this. I want to do that. I'm getting, it's too much. It's too much. It's
too much because it can, that can happen. What does that say? This is like home of 2015
junior Olympic gold medalist in gymnastics. I don't know who that is. What about the next
one? Home of Brian Kilgore. Original bad boy. MMA 2011 Hall of Fame. Why are there just like,
here are the celebrities that, I don't know, what does that mean? This is a really,
really nice looking place though. I can't wait till I get mine. Las Vegas. Home of the
German 985. What's going to happen? There's a way till I got my own casino. This is, yeah,
this is down south somewhere. Wrong way. Mokka. No, I'm not going to say Mokka S again.
I have my guess. That was so close. Oh, we did it again. I'm just like, I can sell,
I can sell it. I can put an M in there after the S. I can just, you know, I can taste it.
Kibbe Dome. This looks, this looks kind of like New England. It does. I feel like I'm in New
England. Did I recognize anything? Subs go that way. Student Rec. I'm in like a college.
What college am I in? This is a college. Stadium. University of Idaho. All right,
where's the University of Idaho? I don't really feel like I'm in New England.
Where's the University of Idaho? I know it's in Idaho. What are you looking at? I love how
they blurred this out too. Campus Walk. Whoa, what a cool campus. This is just basketball hoops
on the walk. In my college we just played a game of who could put the head in the trash can
the longest without throwing up. That's all we had. No, of course I didn't win. This is
not a drinking thing. This is just a thing thing. It's like, ah, I'm bored. Me, I'm
bored too. I'm very bored. You want to play, you want to play smell the can? Uh, yeah, sure. I don't
got class for like another 40 minutes. I need like a city. It's gonna be like admissions or
something. Teaching and Learning Center. Why don't you just name this the Education Center?
Isn't that too wordy? The Teaching and Learning Center? The Education Center. Too many words.
Idaho Comm. I gotta get out of the college. It looks like the exit. I gotta find the
signs and find the exit. Is this Campus Walk? No, it's over here. Life Sciences. This way.
University. Let's get out. Out. Out. University. Get out. Admission. No, I get me out of the
college. How big is this college? All right, I made it. Welcome to Moscow. Moscow, Idaho.
Okay, so it is Russia. We were right. Every time. Watch this be actually in Russia. No,
that would be impossible. All right, Moscow, Idaho. Let's go look it up. What do you guys
think? Do you think it's um, I'm just realizing this right now. Idaho is just a gigantic flipped
New Hampshire. It's weird. Moscow. Okay, Moscow. We're looking for Moscow. Oh, get out of
here. University. Where is it? University of Idaho. I'll take 5,000 points please. All right,
that's close enough. What's going on here? What's this weird? Did somebody ran my camera over with
a green tire? Why did we get slimed? This camera's broken. 55 speed limit? No, that's
too easy to do that. It's too easy to just bait everybody here to say like, oh look at
those dogs or something like that. Everyone's going to be like, what? That's way too easy.
Look at those lions. This camera is pissing me off. Road may flood. This really is just
almost like concrete how flat this all is. Yeah, I even get like the urge to just sprint
just this way. Just drink a bunch of water and just run as fast as you fucking possibly
can that way. Or just like a sled. You know, one of those body boogie board sleds,
just cover in oil and just sprint as fast as you fucking can and just jump and slide and you
probably go the whole thing. You know, go get in a bowling alley, cover the bowling alley bed
thing with oil and slide on it. I made this fucking joke two days ago, except it was a
much smaller scale. Have we got signs? No. Yeah, this is out. This is out like here
somewhere. This is like, who fucking has any idea? We could be on this road for miles.
This is scary to, all right, those of you guys that live in a place like this,
an area like this, aren't you afraid to go anywhere? You need a full tank of gas.
If you don't have a full tank, this is scary. Even if you have a full tank of gas,
you, something happens out here. Wait, what are you going to go? You're going to walk?
You better get your sprinting ability up because you're going to have to go that way.
Okay. What about, I would feel like I would want like extra gas. It'd be terrifying.
I'll fill the tank up. Can I put like six tanks of gas in my back seat? I would be
scared to do this. I would. I would be scared. I'd be scared. Kent, we are in Kent,
Kent, Nebraska or something. Kent, Nebraska, Kent. Okay. We're in Kent, but where, what is Kent?
What is that? Is that, is this a handmade, a homemade helicopter? This is a flying machine.
This is a homemade flying machine. Oh no, it's perspective. It's going that way. Okay. I
thought this was like one unit. Okay. I thought this was one thing. Okay. No, it's
just like a watering centipede. It's a centipede irrigator. I get it. Look at those dogs. Look at
those dogs. Kent, a human irrigator. What would a human irrigator be this way or that way? Would
you like just put water in your mouth and just spray it? All right. Time to take a guess. I
think this is like somewhere in like Oklahoma, Kentucky, Dakota, one of the Dakotas. What's
that say? Does that say Alabama? Does that say Alabama? Dot Alabama? Alabama? Oh, it's right
here. North. I can't see. Oh, train! That was bad. I know. Look, people are just doing
ASCII art in the channel and I had to, I've been paying attention to that. No joke, until I
was 17, I thought it was Abba Llama. No, no, not me. Somebody in chat said that. I'm
repeating what somebody said. Speaking of llamas, here they are. That's a lot of them.
What does that sign say? I'm about to give up and just fucking guess. Arcadia, Kansas. Arcadia,
Kansas. Arcadia. It's a long road. I'm going to say over here. Arcadia. Opica.
Arcadia. California. Arcadia. Garden City. Dodge City. Jaxmoor. It was in Missouri.
Oh, there's the liberal. Okay, so we weren't in something called Kent. It was close. Close enough.
We go that way. We've got to turn. We're gonna go backwards now. Okay, this is Russia. Again,
same signs. Remember these signs? Russia. Good luck. Yeah, those are universal Russian signs.
I don't know. I have no idea what that is. I don't know what that means. Does this mean
the cars are coming real? Okay, here's what I get from this. Cars on the other side of the
road have a much higher speed limit than our side here. So cars on this side are going to
be going like 80. So be aware of that because it's like 25-30 on this side. And the top is
just like a wine bottle. Or does that... Okay, so that means that the road narrows to a point
where you have to go like one mile per hour through a tiny little opening.
More just like cars on the side of the road. Who owns these cars? Just nothing from
miles. This is this person's house. That's squished. What does this one say? This says
300 miles to... I don't know. What the hell are they talking about?
If you drink two cups of coffee a day, it helps with dry eyes. It wasn't that bad.
This is Ukraine. All right. Did all right over here in America. Not so good over here.
Actually, yeah, it's beside... Russia is... I'm telling you, Russia is hard mode.
I'll do one more. Let's do one more. Same app. Let's go. Now, this is absolutely New England.
Yes, it is. This is New England somewhere. I'd be shocked if it wasn't. This is definitely
New England. How do I know? You just know. Yeah, you just know. Let's get to a main road.
Got like boats in the driveways. That's a big tell. The style of house. This is not
Florida. Let me do a main road. Okay, get out here. Can't see it from there. All right. All
right. All right. Here we go. Here we go. All right. Here we go. This is it. This is
definitely... This is like Cape Cod. This is Cape Cod, Massachusetts. I've seen a lot of
orange plates. That's Halloween. So this is Halloween on Cape Cod. Guys, this is...
Look at this shit. You telling me this is not New England? Here we go. Back it up. Back
it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. I gotta get this one. Watch out.
Risotto. Eatery. Italian eatery. Howard. Hector's Hardware. What's this? Tim Hor...
It's Canada. 800. Benchmark. Eyecare Vision Center. School. School. School. School.
I was right. I was right. I live here. Oh yeah, where is it then? Aggressive
Har... Oh, it's a law firm called JEP. Robo Mart. Mighty Taco. I was right. Benderson.
Benderson. Sounds like a name that I came up with. This looks like Massachusetts.
Oh, go back into the town square. This way. Spectrum. Oh shit. This is not Massachusetts.
Spectrum's not in Massachusetts. You know how I know that? Because it's just fucking Comcast.
There's a pocket this big for Verizon. No, no! Let's go this way. I got it. They're gonna be
transporting animals. Buffalo. That's down here. Would your child even know if they had
poor vision? One in four children have undiagnosed vision problems. Come and spend like 600 bucks.
I thought that was somebody in the window. I think a leaf hit the camera in the face.
What happened to this camera? Somebody like... Is the Incredible Hulk grabbing the lens right
now? This is like a Hulk smash right here. Well, we're gonna go this way because I can't see that
way. All right. Dr. Dr. Expedito. Dr. Expedito. Okay, so this is... Hulk out of my face. Okay,
this is... What does it say? Oficina Sal Severo e Servus e... More... I'd love to do this
one. It's somewhere in South America. Sign over there. Let's see if I can see it. It's got this
terrible view. Wrap around. Sign right here. There was a billboard here. What's this? I can't
go down there. Okay, here we go. What do we got? I want to see that one. Curao de Cima.
Queria Sao Jose. Sao Jose. The Bitcoin? Brazil. Brazil. Sao Jose, Brazil. Brazil's huge.
There's a lot of... There's a lot of places in Brazil. Wait, Sao... That's Rio de Janeiro.
What does it say here? Let's just guess. No, I thought it was closer to Rio de Janeiro.
This is up here. I didn't even say it, too, and it's a completely different name. All right,
next round. Another gigantic highway in Russia. No, stop! So every single time it's been Russia,
it's been the same spot. Maybe it's just never over here. All right, Russia, because that's
where the people live. Oh, okay. That makes it a little easier. You're clicking in the
Russian desert. Everybody in Russia lives in the same spot. There's no life east of Moscow.
I just keep clicking on the wilderness. Putin... Is this Russia again? That was just like Putin-ski.
There it is. There it is on the treasure map. It's right here. Dig here. You'll find it.
Coffee, rent, gas, or hardware? Mutine. I don't think this is Russia. I don't think so.
Duxtos. Duxtos sounds like the name of the town or the place. Duxtos or Duxtos. Same deal.
Further down. Much further. Much further. Much further. It's Duxtos Rio de Janeiro. I don't think
it is. Food and lodging? That's a tree next to a stool. I don't know what that means.
Why is it blurred out? All right, I'm gonna get off the highway here. Here we go. Here's some
more signs and civilization. Golf, swimming. All right, this is a recreational spot. Let's
get over here. What's that? The Meridian. The Meridian. The Le Meridian. Taxi. We're in
Europe. I just don't know where. I gotta get off the highway. I feel like we're gonna be
on this highway for a long time. Now we're opening up into driving through nowhere. I'm
going for it. I think I got it. I think I got it. At least close. Yep, Lithuania. I was
thinking Latvia, Estonia, Lithuania, Belarus. I didn't read chat for that one. Who wrote that?
Nobody did. Cheating. You can say that for everything, okay? Everything could be he read
it in chat. Everything. I don't get any credit. I love when I beat last boss,
Sekiro, and I did it. And you can't say that you read chat. You did it. I did that.
It makes me like, I did that. Remember that? We certainly helped. All right, this is the last
one. And then I'm gonna take off. Thank you for joining me on this relaxing stream. Okay,
I thought that was a tank. So that's a big tank. I have no idea what the hell this is.
Man filter. Okay. Man filter. Is this in English? Is it $33 a gallon? No, this is Russia.
Close. Close enough. View the summary. What we got. It would have been, actually,
I would have been really good. The only big outlier was this. Me clicking on the middle
of nowhere. I would have been up here. That would have been good. And that's it. We're
gonna do the bits. And I will see you all for some more VR on Tuesday. Tuesday. That one
doesn't count? Yeah, it does. Thank you to CAD for the amazing Jerma Slots game. There was a
lot more content in there than I think any of us ever could have imagined. So thank you
to those of you that worked on that game. It was great. Mr. Mosquito was actually really
interesting until that last level. And then, yeah, just another relaxing kind of chill day.
VR is coming back. You've raged quite a porn game. Well, good. That's not a big deal.
Let me move this off. Hey, you want some, like, radiance? That makeup ad has showed up.
I've given that, you guys have already seen ads. Give ads. You've seen this one already,
like, 30 or 40 times. So you already had ads. But I'll see you guys later. See you guys in
a couple days. On Tuesday, to be specific. Thank you everybody for coming out. Back to
the virtual world on Tuesday. Let us move this window here. And let's do the bits
from earlier, about six hours ago. What am I going to do in VR? Mind show. I'm going
to just start. We're just going to do mind show. I'm just going to start and do a
full stream in mind show. I've been putting it off because I know it's going to be a lot of
fun. So I want to have a dedicated day to it. The only reason why I would not do it then
is to do it on a weekend or something. But let's just let's just go for it.
But thank you too, to start it off our Lazy Luke with the $7777.77. Thank you. I've got
footage of you this morning realizing that you can't gamble your life savings on stream.
What is this? This is called another one of those videos. Thank you Lazy Luke for the
$7777. Appreciate it. Also thank you to Clive Ripp. Thank you with $5. These bits are to
give italics a wet willy. Thank you for the $5. How about I'll tell italics a funny joke instead.
Thank you for the five bucks. Hey Smelly Boy, thanks for the $250. Hope you realize this is
a borderline fetish game. Look, I played it for like an hour and a half and I realized
that I didn't want to play it anymore so I stopped playing it. Thank you for the $250.
Avev, thanks for the 10 bucks. Why are you naked if this isn't a porn game? I don't know. Thank
you for the $10 Avev. Dorkcube, thanks for the $250. Holy cow, Cad is an absolute legend. Hope
you make more games dude. I do too. Something to discuss because that was fantastic. Cad's still
here. No, that was a funny little easter egg joke thing that he did. But thank you
Dorkcube and yes again thank you to Cad. This is insane. Magical Marissa, another $10 on top of the
$60 you've already given tonight. Thank you for 10 more dollars here. They say auto. Auto. By the way,
Cad did mention that that game he's going to try to release it at the end of this stream.
But it might have to wait till Monday because of the way Steam works. So if it's not up
today for you just to download and play it however long you want, it will be available early next
week. Right? Is that correct? I want to make sure that's correct. Dermislots is the game we're
talking about. Showcased it on stream earlier. One is the scratch off. I'll make it clear one
more time because I know people are kind of trickling in and out. I cannot do the scratch
ticket thing in Nevada because there's no state lottery in Nevada. I did not know that
until this morning. So I cannot physically buy a scratch ticket. They do not exist
in the state of Nevada, unfortunately. I did not even know that until this morning.
So we will cross that bridge again. I have to drive to California. Road trip stream.
But thank you to omgtayon for the 250. Derma this is your family. We're all worried about
you and your gambling addiction you've developed. Please leave Las Vegas and come home. We hit
it though. We cheated but we hit it. Zanziman thanks for the 10 bucks. Derma I know it's not
much but here you need it more than me. Thank you for the 10 dollars. Zany. I think it's not
it's not Zanziman. It's Zany Zman. Appreciate the 10 bucks. Super Seal thanks for 250. Please
highlight this stream so that future generations can watch you play the best game ever.
Whether I'm referring to Mr. Mosquito or Derma Slots is up to you. It will be saved
forever. Ferodian weapon thanks for five dollars Ferodian. Hope you're having a good night. I
thought I'd contribute to your gambling addiction but seriously this game looks amazing. It even
makes me want to gamble. That's not that that was not my intention. If you're going to gamble
hopefully that you follow some very very basic rules. Rule number one make sure it's legal
where you live. Make sure you're old enough and it's legal. Rule number two if you're
going to gamble make sure you go into gambling with going to a casino or whatever you're doing.
Moderate yourself. Make sure you're doing it for fun not to actually make money. Do not try to
gamble to try to make money. He's promoting gambling. No I'm trying to be I'm trying to
promote responsible gaming. Just go to a casino and bet 221 dollars on roulette for black. That'd
be bad. That's the worst thing you could probably do but yeah thank you Ferodian for
the five dollars. Game responsibly. Tara Alekhren thanks for the three bucks.
Jerma I've been subbed for 32 months. Only a few more months until I'm in the three year club.
You got any plans for a three year sub badge so I can lord it over the filthy one and two year
plebs? Yes three years. Holy shit that's so long. Thank you Tara Alekhren for the continued
support forever. That's forever. That's as long as I've been streaming on twitch. I've been
streaming on twitch for about three and a half years. Four years almost. But yes there will be
three, six, twelve years whatever is available. You know the word I was trying to say. Thank you
something rather for the 250. How much will it take for you to release your hostages? I don't
have any hostages. Thank you for the 250. Pika Banana thanks for the 10 bucks. It's too bad
the scratches didn't work out but this has been an amazing stream anyway. You never failed
to crack me up. Love you Jerma Jerma Heart. Thank you for the 10 dollars and the incredibly
kind message. I had a lot of fun tonight. It was a just a it was like a shower a an absolute
shower of smiles that were on my face. It was great. Thank you for the 10 dollars
and supporting the stream. Dorkcube thanks for the 250. After watching you play Risk of Rain
2 I decided to try it. Unfortunately my laptop is garbage so I had to turn down all the
graphics settings. Did you know the game allows you to turn the textures to 1 30 1 32nd of their
full size? A 30 I can't even read that. 1 32th. What does that mean? How do I say this?
1 30th? How do you say this? Phonetically just put it in the chat. 1 32nd? But that doesn't
sound right. 1 32nd. I had it right the first time. It just sounds sounds weird to say it.
But thank you Dorkcube. Risk of Rain 2 is a lot of fun. I'm glad you're able to at least play it.
Tara Alecran thanks for the three dollars. If he isn't holding Cad hostage then why won't
he show his basement on stream right now? We see through your lies Jerma. Free Cad.
Well there's a funny thing to rebuttal this with. There is no such thing as a basement
in Las Vegas. The judge just tore up the prosecution and threw it in the air.
There are no basements in Las Vegas. Oh that's real convenient. No scratch tickets. No basement.
This is starting to sound fake as hell. We've seen zero proof that you're in Las Vegas.
Except for the balloon landing when I was surrounded by mountains and desert.
It was faked. It was a green screen. I'll end up doing a weird Las Vegas stream. Don't worry.
I'll be out there. There'll be some weird scenario. Well you're gonna see like the
whole strip or something maybe. But thank you Smelly Boy for the 250. GeoGuessr is unironically
my favorite game to watch you play. It's not a joke when we ask you to play. I know and I have
fun playing it and I think it's a lot it's a relaxing interesting fun game we can just kind
of talk about whatever. But the reason why I didn't play it for a while is because
it was sort of a crutch for a while right. We would just play it all the time. There was
like three or four cases in a row within a week or two weeks where it was like uh GeoGuessr.
So I kind of wanted to take a break from it. I played it a lot. It was like oh we've been
playing this game for like three four hours. This game kind of sucks but we might as well
play PictoPix right. That's become what PictoPix is. It's because of Comcast. Yeah that's true
but it was like a Comcast crutch. So I don't really need the Comcast crutch anymore. Although
Cox's as we've been aware hasn't been nearly as bad as what Comcast used to do but still
there's still our problem sometimes with Cox. Switch it out with Google Feud once in a while.
Yeah I really do like just playing browser games and hanging out. I want to do this more
often. We've talked about it already but I want to add more kind of hang out and doing
browser stuff. There's a lot more opportunity I think to interact and have conversations and
come up with scenarios and talk to each other and stuff. So I want to do more of this type
of thing not less. But thank you Smelly Boy. I do enjoy Neo uh it's almost I just said
NeoGuessr. NeoGuessr. Like for The Matrix. I don't know why. Weird. Neopets.
Neo. Imagine a GeoGuessr map in The Matrix. I don't know. Stream The Matrix
video game. It doesn't even work anymore. Isn't The Matrix online completely off? Is
the other one even worth playing? And then we had too many subs to even there was so
many community subs. Thank you everybody that decided to give a community sub because there
was a shitload of them like an hour ago. You guys are too kind. Thank you. Also Smelly
Boy thanks to the 250. Most of Russia in the East is Siberia. Nobody lives there. The
vast majority of the population is always in the West of Russia. I'll remember that for
next time. Flug Boy thanks to the 250. Hey Jerm I hope you're doing well. Just got into
a relationship with a very close friend of mine uh two years and been happier than ever.
But yeah pretty fun stuff. Hope you and Kim are doing great my guy. I always love her
posts of you and her on Twitter. Yeah I'm well first of all I'm glad you're uh doing
well in a relationship. Yeah Kim and I are doing great. She's she's my girl you know.
She's my girl. But thank you for the 250. Glad you've uh glad you're happy.
And here are the ton of community subs. So many of them. Five dollars from Moson.
I was in Boston for packs. Spent most of my time exploring Boston. An amazing city
but the Green Line can eat my ass. Yes I agree. The Green Line is horrible. The Green
Line is always packed. It's always hard to navigate. That is a true state. I'm glad you
had fun. Boston is a really really nice city. Thank you the five dollars. Hope you enjoyed
packs. Kind of sad that I wasn't able to be there. That would be the first time in
its inception. I've been to every single packs East since they started the first time.
Didn't get to make it this year. But thank you Freudian Weapon for the five dollars.
250 here twice in a row. You're as young as you feel. Dressed the way you like. Age
doesn't have a dress code. Yeah I know I was just kidding around. I was just kidding around.
And then they also say if you were to hang up the streaming hat tomorrow I would respect
your decision and wish you well on your future endeavors. Jeremy Hart. Thank you.
Yeah I never it's never gonna be a scenario where I just disappear. It would be something
that you guys would know what's happening. I'd say you know that's it. I had a lot of fun.
I want to move on to other things. But I don't think I would be able to stay away.
I think I would probably still okay let's say if I stopped streaming completely right.
Whenever that was whenever that will be. Or stop making streams or videos or your content
online content media or whatever you want to call it. I would still probably poke my head
around you know once a week or once every few weeks or something. Turn a stream on just hang
out do something fun. I really don't think I would ever be gone forever completely from the
platform. You know I mean it would just be I don't think I would be able to do that.
But that's not in the cards in any sort of immediate sense. I have absolutely no plans to
stop. But I do need to acknowledge the fact that if I ever don't want to do it anymore
and I don't you know not having fun anymore. I've done things that I want to do. I think
I would probably want to eventually you know do something else. I don't know. I don't have a
number for that. I don't have a time frame for that. But I think I need to be honest with
everybody. Sure it's easy to be like streams forever. This is it's until I'm 80. But I don't
know that that's I don't know if that's gonna happen. I'm currently enjoying it.
Something I love to do. I love being on stream. I love being part of the community. I love
seeing all this shit. I love doing all these things. So I don't have it's not gonna stop
anytime soon. There you go. Quarter dime thanks to the five dollars. Just disappear for five years
and then come back with a turban or and telling us how you found faith. Or like just going like
a religious journey and come back. I don't think I would do that. Disappear for five years and
come back as like a preacher or something. Would you be interested in becoming the next joker if
DC contacted you? No. Nope. Now the Riddler. You got an opportunity.
Somebody already said it. I didn't even need to do it. How much would you do it for? 40 bucks.
But I want five percent of all royalties from the movie. No no I want I want 0.2 percent of
all revenue the movie makes. I'll do it for 40 dollars. It's gonna flop. No it's gonna have
at least like a 74 percent on Rotten Tomatoes. I'll make sure of that. Yeah well the movie really
sucked. Terrible writing. Awful awful direction. The cinematography. The story was all over the
place but you just couldn't take your eyes off Jeremy Elbertson's performance. And then
they go you know on Rotten Tomatoes you have the thing with a guy the person would write
the thing. Even the skill of Jeremy Elbertson cannot hold this mess together. I don't care if
it gets a 30 percent on Rotten Tomatoes. I'll carry it. The Great Lord Walden. 50 dollars right
now. 5,000 bits from The Great Lord Walden. Thank you so much for the 5,000 bits. It's my
birthday today. I'm 33. Feeling Jerma old tonight. Thanks for everything you do. I'm 33 too.
34 this year. Happy birthday Great Lord Walden. Thank you for the 50 dollars.
You're not you don't you never you never feel you're never too old.
No you don't feel old. We're young. 33 is the new 20. 40 is the new 30. I know it is. I'm
telling you it is. 50 will always be 50. 50 is not the new 50 or the old. 50 is just 50 and
then from that point forward 50 is just the 50. You're gone. You're out. 55 you can retire.
40 is the new 30. 50 still 50. I'm not gonna feel old until I'm 49 and one day till my birthday.
You're allowed to feel old when you're 50. Jerma can run for president in two months. No I
can't. It's 35. I cannot run for president yet. It's gonna have to be Jerma 2021.
I mean yeah I can. It's 34. It would have to be Jerma 2024. He's thought about it.
No it's just something that you are told in middle school. I want to ask if you're interested
in any game recommendations. If you have recommendations throw them in the recommendation
channel on the discord. I check it all the time. Everyone's thought about it. Yeah everybody's
thought about it. Five more community subs on top of everything. Thank you so much for the
five community subs. That was from BlackDymo. Thank you BlackDymo. Didn't get one. Oh what's
the discord? Here it is. It is a public discord. There is a sub channel but it's open to the public.
It's a great community there. But thank you great Lord Walden for the 50 dollars and happy
birthday again. Also a little bit further back here we had a quarter dime thanks to the five
bucks. I think didn't get you before. We read your message but I don't think I even said your
name. But that was quarter dime for five dollars. Thank you. Juno Upseto thanks for the
250. The leaf in front of the camera is actually GeoGuessr hard mode. It did make it pretty hard.
Great Lord Walden's got 82 gifted subs. Some of you guys you wonder how my sub count is so high.
There are at least a few dozen of you guys that have 50 to 100 each gifted subs.
That's it's just bonkers. A simple way I can share the love. Well I really appreciate that.
Thank you. Clueless Sniper thanks for the 250. No message just 250. Thank you Clueless Sniper.
Novi333 thanks for the three dollars and 33 cents. No message just 333. Novi coming in.
Freudian thanks for the 250. Pretty sure I spammed bit messages tonight.
Whoops a bad habit of mine I suppose. Anyhow happy Saturday. No you've got like three or four
here. Spam? What are you talking about? Thank you for the 250. Have a happy Saturday.
And then we also had Jerma lied about Minecraft VR with five more community subs bringing them
to 220 gifted subs. Yes I guess that you heard that correct. 220 gifted subs.
That's so many. Thank you Jerma lied about Minecraft VR for your monster sub gifting.
Thank you. Crimbalt thanks for the 250. Hello Sire I was just wondering if you saw
the trailer for the sequel to Hollow Knight. I don't know if you ever get to finish the
first one. Would be interested in this one but regardless I love all your streams.
I have seen the second game. I will probably play it. There's a Hollow Knight sequel.
At least there is a Hollow Knight sequel. Let's run the credits. That's it for the bits
for the most part. Thank you everybody. Here come the names. Thanks for supporting the stream.
All of you. Read them. Go go go. Ding. Two state taco. Poopy ass.
I used to, I used to read these. Remember when I used to really give it a really solid
attempt and it was so much slower. Sometimes it would be like this. But it's like this
almost every time now. You guys understand how fucking ridiculous that is? Well Jerma lied about
Gwere. Jerma lied about like Gwere? Like the song thing? What is with these all these
Jerma lied about this. Jerma lied about that. Jerma lied about Gwere. What the fuck.
Somebody asked a quarter dime asked hey Jerma if I were to go watch an old stream of yours
any old stream which would you choose and why um probably sorcery sorcery is the first
real stream attempt that I really did on a schedule or doing twitch instead of youtube
and I would probably say that those a lot of stream jokes and a lot of classic references
even to stuff that's still in the chat now stuff like sus um the green screen stream
was so much fun there's been so many there's been too many all of them except for skate three
don't watch that one don't watch the karazhan stream don't watch the mario tennis stream don't
watch um spell a few others don't watch the neo stream rick and morty that was fine the
handheld game no watch the handheld game stream that's one of my favorites rick and morty was
awful yeah but was that my fault or was that the game's fault maybe it was a little
bit but i was really tired i was so tired when we got to rick and morty both i mean it wasn't
my i was so tired i just couldn't even do anything and i gave up even 10 of the way
through i just couldn't do it it was chat's fault but that wasn't okay it was minecraft
vr and then rick and morty so that stream was good i like that was a lot of fun but
the rick and morty portion of that stream that's not the whole i'm talking about a
whole stream the skate three stream was a whole stream but i'll see you guys in a few days
i'm probably thinking about tuesday i'll let you know the the business will be
changed and updated here look for me on tuesday i'll see you guys real soon we'll do some
more vr mine show mine show coming up i'm gonna make some skits much love to you all
have a great rest of your weekend see you guys in a few days take care ta ta and good
night oh wait i gotta give the loot i gotta give the loot loot loot loot loot i know i know i'll
give you the loot this is the clip oh this is my this is the bullshit clip oh my god
oh man give me a break that was bullshit i will defend that to the death of how
bullshit that was all right let's get some uh loot here if you uh don't know what i mean
we've got got we've got we've got uh stream legends down the bottom of the page there
what is a wrath god
what the fuck did i do this
oh
i couldn't even do it back then all right here you go you ready open up your loot boxes
for free in five four three two no i can't do it i have uh it's 24 hours and it hasn't
been 24 hours yet i did this last night when the stream ended i can't do it i have to wait an hour
in 25 minutes sorry uh all right i'll okay look i'll come back in an hour and a half and i'll do
it i promise i'm gonna go eat some food i'm gonna come back if you just i will do it in
an hour and a half i will do it in an hour and a half because i can't do it all right
good night everybody germa lied about fruity loops thanks to the 250 they say i hate you
don't worry that's still all right bye i know don't stay for an hour on that behalf like
come back in like an hour and a half i'm just gonna do it in an hour and a half oh by the way
yeah here's your ad i'll play the ad good night have a great weekend here's an ad see you
if you did i can't run the ad okay i can't do any of these things i just clicked it run ad
uh commercial break failed sorry i'm not making that up everyone's calling me a liar i'll show you
right now i'm not a liar i got a screen grab right here you ready take a look save it as png
and here you go commercial break failed i can't do it told you that's not fake
that's not a that is real how could that be faked you think i opened up photoshop and
implanted all right i'll see you tomorrow not tomorrow i'm not streaming tomorrow i'll see you
in three days all right good night goodbye take care of yourselves have a great one i can't play
ads goodbye