Hi, sir. Yeah. Spies? You are so scary. Yeah, I- get- no, no! You punk! God damn it, you-
God, every word in the dictionary to describe hatred and pissed-offness. Let's move this up.
This is where we can start to do a lot of damage, right? God damn it!
Put the exit right over here. It's not that far from spawn, but it's okay. It's not that far from
spawn. This teleporter is, like, as far as you can throw a baseball from spawn. Like, oh, let me just,
like, toss a baseball, like, underhand. Underhanded. This is an underhand softball. You headless bastard.
Get out of here. What? What? What? What? How did this happen? I gotta watch that back. What the- what
the hell just happened? This thing blew up for no reason. I'm so paranoid right now. I- it- am I
going absolutely crazy right now, or is there, like, a ghost on Bon Blitz that is killing
my teleporter over and over again? No! No! No! No! No! Thank the old gods, the new gods,
and the gods of old and new, and the- you- get the hell- no, it's okay. It's just a regular bald-ass
pyro. Anytime I see, like, a bald-ass pyro, I just automatically think spy. Just, like, a default
bald pyro just running at you. Just, hey, hi, I'm not a spy. Don't worry, I'm not a spie.
No! God, did you see that crit rocket? Holy di- no! Where is he? Where is this guy?
That just- son of a- ah! No, are you real? He's- it's the pyro back there. What- what I tell you,
what I tell you, the bald-ass pyro running around up here is a spy. Watch this. That's him right
there. Yeah. Could- could you guess? Can I please just get this set up and not have to, like, worry
about this anymore? Okay, I gotta go on- on the guys of Nightfall. Here we go. I got- there has
to be, like- dude, I don't even know which one it is. This has gotta get in here. Hurry. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Hurry up and build. Hurry up and build. Hurry up and build. You stupid son of a bitch! I
hate you. All right, I don't hate you. I did hate you for, like, a good five seconds right there,
but I don't hate you right now. Maybe I hate myself for doing that. See, when there's a spy on the
other team, or, like, multiple spies on the other team, that are just making your day just a living
hell. Like, seriously, playing Engineer is, like, the scariest class to play in this game, especially
when there's, like, a friggin' unusual spy with, like, 20 billion kills on his knife running around
trying to get, like, free kills on you. Ain't gonna happen. You ain't gonna get me. You ain't
gonna stab me. I promise you that. You shut up. Oh my god, what am I doing? I fall off cliff
cuz I'm an idiot. Let's just keep a base out here. Get a teleporter built. Holy hell. I swear. Where
is he? You fucking piece of- Stop playing the Giles theme music right now, guys, because this- it's on
now. Hi, sniper. Get the- Yeah, where you going? You going down here with your dead ringer? Oh, I
heard you. Where are you? Where'd you go? I heard it. You all heard it. Not gonna let him get away
with that. Yeah, get the- Yeah, what's up, bro? How you doing? Oh, you're the real one. I'm hiding
this in the bushes. The sentry bush made from the- I just ruined my desk. Um, this is- Oh, look at
the ad. I found the Spycicle. Can you believe it? It's my personal mission now to kill that spy.
Oh, look. Look who's up there. Now he doesn't have his dead ringer. I want- No, the soldier,
let me get this kill. Let me hit him. He doesn't have a dead ringer right now. It's my kill,
not yours. It's my kill, not yours. You leave me the fuck alone, okay?
Oh, I keep falling off of this cliff and it's gonna make me mad. It's gonna drive me friggin'
mental. Once I get this teleporter up, if I don't get trolled by spies for the remainder of the game,
then we should be okay. Just gotta get it up. Keep having to use my metal on things I don't
want to use the metal on. Screw you! Teleporter up. At least all my stuff is up. You can go ahead
and like shoot from across the map and be a prick. That's fine. I don't even care. All I want is to
get this teleporter up. Who is attacking this teleporter? Who is doing this? Somebody help me.
I- This is not gonna work. It's over. Good. Game. Good. Game. At least I got that.
At least I got that last laugh right there. Oh, look who it is. Oh, look who it is.