Oh hi guys. Do you want to see... I'm a little irritated.
You want to see something that I cannot believe.
I'm trying to figure out how this is even possible.
First of all, sorry I'm a little bit late. I had some controller input issues
because Dead Rising 2 does not actually have native
controller support built into the PC version. So I had to
get an emulator for that and wow what a pain in the ass. But
even worse than that. Somehow. Just skip the intro.
Give me a scenario, any scenario, where at the at the menu screen having
art gallery, downloadable content, and import games for windows live is
more important than the options menu. You gotta go
into the fucking game, into the actual video game to change settings.
Why is this here? Imagine getting this shown.
You're a boss, you're the boss, okay? You're the boss of a video game company.
You make video games and this is what you're presented for the
the the menu for the game? I'd be like go back and redo this whole fucking thing.
This is like advertisements.
Give me the options menu so I can like check to see if my controller works.
Can we change the graphic settings? What?
Yeah import games for windows live. That's more important.
I'm surprised there's a goddamn quit button here. Anyways how you doing?
The game's 10 years old. The first one had it.
The first game had this. Every game has this. It's not just 10 years.
Every fucking video game. Every video game has an
options menu before you start the video game.
Downloadable content? That's got to be hidden in the options menu.
Put these in the options menu. Would you run out of time?
Anyways hi guys we're gonna play Dead Rising 2 off the record today.
Why am I not playing the original game? Well we had a
a lot of deliberation in the chat room and hold on you can't even hear this.
We had a lot of deliberation in the chat room about which one
I should play because I thought they were different games but they're not.
There was a lot of fighting. You have no idea. I'm sitting here trying to set up
my controller, emulate my goddamn xbox one controller.
I look over here and there's a fight. Like a brawl in the chat about
which version of the game should I play and it was just like
people would throw and shit tables are flipped over.
But it came to my realization that they are in fact the same
video game told from different perspectives. The bosses and the
items, everything's the same. This one has some extra content is what
I've been told. By like 70% of the people in the chat.
This is not true. Literally not true. This one's not canon though.
This is a DLC. No it's not. No it's not because I
listen to me. I downloaded Dead Rising 2. This is a separate purchase on Steam.
It's a separate video game. I made that mistake.
This is not a DLC for Dead Rising 2. This is a full standalone video game.
Dead Rising 2 again. He bought the wrong one. No this is the
right one because I want to use the camera too and we're playing with Frank.
Still no options menu by the way. This is Dead Rising 2 too.
So what I could do, I was thinking about doing both anyways.
Going back and playing as Chuck. This is why like constant conflict in
this chat. I may as well open up a Barbie game after
talking about all this. Do a poll. I did three of them before
the stream started. Unanimously it was this game. We're going.
Don't care. Like it was 80 percent. It was like 75 percent.
I clawed my way out of Willamette. I fought hard
to uncover the truth of what happened at that mall.
This is really loud. Turn your speakers down for a few minutes
because I can't alt tab. Things were good.
Real good. It was an options aisle.
Then I let things get to me. I let things
get out of control. Dead Rising 2. The original has options.
Are you fucking kidding me? How is it possible to have this?
I think deep down I knew I hadn't uncovered what was really going on.
Fighting never ends. This is a fight. Things got pretty dark. I'm like dad at
the dinner table while the whole family argues.
To get back at game. I got a huge family. I'm at the very end of the table just
slowly cutting my steak and I hear people yelling about their days and
screaming at each other about what's better and I'm just like god damn it.
How do I keep this fucking family together? I just take a bite.
Excuse me sir. What is it kid? I signed your waiver.
You got my next of kin. Are the vultures circling already?
Everybody settle down. Yeah sorry sir. It's just paperwork.
They want it from everyone. Oh I've lost control. Would you mind if I got your
autograph? This spoils too but this this is too.
Isn't it? It's isn't the same game. Sorry about that.
What's going on? Everybody sit up. It's been a while.
Eat your peas Jeffrey. You've always been a big hero. You never eat your peas.
I was really bummed when your show went off the air.
Wow thanks. So I guess this would be worth quite a bit if anything happened
to you out there tonight. Uh yeah I guess so. Good luck out there.
Maybe this wasn't such a bad idea after all.
TK has a very special surprise for you. He is the original zombie killer himself.
No I'm not. I'm the DLC killer. The one, the only,
Frank Weiss.
So Fortune City. Now for a show. I know it's really loud but I
don't have access. Showing options. That's an awesome
scepter microphone. That scepter microphone is
unbelievable. Bigger than payoffs. Especially if you use those corner
grinders. I do like a good grinding.
But first TK has got a personal message just for you Frank Weiss.
You gotta be willing to risk it all if you're ever
really gonna win. That's so loud. Okay. Hi guys.
Okay kill zombies win money. You got it. Stop. Stop. Oh.
Would have been really nice if this was available.
Fuck a DLC game. Can you guys hear me? God I'm back. Subtitles it's fine.
Uh nope. PC settings. That's all right. Controller. Yes.
Blur effects. No. High. High. Forex. Save those changes.
Keep these changes. Yes. It's at 60 hertz right now.
Oh give me a break. Why did it? Visual. PC settings. Uh oh.
If this crashes. If this crashes the game I'm gonna put a halt from my
monitor and I'm ending the stream. Okay we're good. All right you ready?
Let's go. Why am I not playing two? Because there was a huge fight at the
dinner table before the stream started. And like 70% of the people told me to
play this one. Clip that and and
clip that fucking thing I just said.
And if anybody asks. Oh shit. They were wrong. I don't know man.
I haven't played these games before. I thought I was under the impression that
this was they like redid two and made it with another character and added
features. This is two again but it's not the same. Everybody hates Chuck.
Nobody likes Chuck. I don't even know who that is. They just don't like that
person. Jump on the corner. Oops I wasn't looking.
All right I'm gonna get as many people up here as I can. Go!
Grind him up. Oh the fire comes out. Right.
Almost at 15. Look I'll like speedrun the fucking first game okay?
No jump off. Dammit. 25,000. Why is he not freaking going up?
3,000. 4,000. 5,000. 25,000. They have to be in the ring?
They gotta be in the ring. Gotta be in the ring. Gotta be in the ring. Somebody
get in the ring. No!
I'm so I said every cutscene is fucking pre-rendered and pre-loaded and you
can't do anything about it. Use volume mixer and windows. Well I
have to that I have to I have to alt tap and the game fucking breaks if you alt
tab. Video games suck okay? Can we just be
very clear? These things are being held together with
like Elmer's glue especially on PC like 10 years ago.
Is that Chuck? I can't believe I just did that. I feel like such a sellout.
Hey do you know how I can get the hell out of here? Yeah take the elevator up a
floor and then straight down the hallway.
You can't miss it. All right now imagine my shock
when I put a poll in chat that has three or four hundred votes on it
and 70 percent of those people say this is the one you should play.
Now imagine my shock when I turn the stream on and in comes the flood of
people that say that it was completely wrong.
It was like 70 percent. What about the other three thousand votes?
Imagine my fucking shock. I did a poll three times.
It's over. Well I just this is just this is you want to talk about not canon
stories? Here's a not canon story for you. Here's
some here's some non-canon for you. The fuck? How could this be different?
It's the same audience. What? You guys are doing this just just out of
spite right now. Even still for god damn it. Is he fatter?
Frank wants to use the guide arrow to find a way to the exit. The guide arrow
will always point towards Frank's current objective.
No the mistake I made was playing a game that's more than 10 years old that has
a lot of fans. That's the biggest mistake of all.
60 percent. How many of those people did that just to be a dick?
I wonder. We're doing this. We're doing this because I'm already here and I
already set up the stupid emulator to use the controller.
I'm gonna go back you know just to spite everything.
I'm gonna play through two again as chuck when I'm done with this.
All right save the game visit a bathroom. You can save as often as
as you'd like and it's a good idea to do so. Find the closest bathroom by looking
for the save icon on the map. Okay I just walked away from it. Okay me
and Frank have the same body. That's I mean at least ass wise. Yes
I did just say that. You know it's all out the window at this
point. Who cares? God damn it. All right let's go.
Non-canon spoilers. I never thought I'd get to do something so important.
What the hell are you up to TK?
Frank West is back complete with his photo journalistic skills. Ready the
camera by holding down left trigger? Yeah.
And tapping right bumper. Release left trigger to put the camera away.
Erotica, horror, outtake, drama, and brutality.
That's from the last one right? Take photos when you see the yellow pp icons.
They will get you even more pp. Lock in your favorite pictures in the
picture viewer. Yeah I remember that. New photos automatically overwrite
unlocked photos. Ready camera by holding
LT and tapping right bumper. Right.
Got you. What is that?
Got it. All right I got what I needed. That's TK and Brandon. Don't look.
That's a special special. Better angle up here.
Is that a bomb?
Dead Rising 2 spoils off the record. Got him. All right this is it. I got the
briefcase switch. How could they ignore me doing this?
Not good. I gotta zoom in. Jump down to get a better shot. I don't
count. I think I can jump down. Got it. You're playing for Super Mario
2 as Luigi. Oh all right. I'm all right with that.
Gotta get back to my show. Well looky here. Hey you're a little late for
the autographs. I was just looking for the men's room.
Story of my life. No. Dude that is so funny.
Is it like a dodge roll or something? Third run?
He just spit on me. I know that technique from the last game.
This guy's the same size.
Wait it's scripted. It's scripted. I think you've overstayed your welcome a bit
Frankie. Call me if you're for a photo shoot.
Who is that? Chuck is a man of god and doesn't have scenes like this.
You must have to take pills for that at your age.
Dude I'm sorry the stream pre-orders had me thinking a completely different
thing. Well good night ladies.
This is a sex game. Blood suckers. There's a 45 minute long sex scene.
Imagine how imagine trying to get that into a game.
It would never happen. It's unskippable.
Gotta get one. Horror horror horror horror horror.
Oh Tom Terry. That was quick. Alice is dead. Well I can't save
everybody. All right well let's go.
Anything in here? There's food in here. Not saving anybody. Omega lull. We can't.
All right fire axe. No keep fire axe. He's so
red. This actually got a little stupid.
Why how did it get on my back? Go in here.
Yep that's pretty good. No what are you doing?
Hey there handsome. Take off those shoes now.
This first second I'm able to the shoes are coming off. Anything else in here?
No let's go.
Is there this throwing in this game right? Dale.
Dale's dead. I just triple tapped that guy.
Is this money on the ground? Wait what is this? Keys?
Security box? Wait Jeremiah.
Did he like run his head into a spike? All right I'm coming to think that you
can't actually do anything. Pat and Lucas.
They just keep coming. I can't do anything about it.
Oh fuck.
It's decent.
Andrea can I do anything? Why are there grenades everywhere?
Don't use grenades in close proximity guys. We have five community subs coming
from Kazoo. One of these is Chuck.
There's Chuck. All right get in the safe house.
Chuck. Do I make it into the elevator? We'll find out.
Sort of jogged right in. Time to break the bank Vegas style.
By the way this is Vegas. I can't get a signal. Why?
Why can't I get a signal? It's because you don't have Verizon.
She was looking right at me and they found her and I couldn't do anything.
She went down without a sound and I had to get out of there. I just
ran. He does look like Dan Aykroyd. Whoa whoa.
Name's Frank. Frank West. Oh you're the big shot from Willamette.
Yeah. I seen you on tv. I don't take this the wrong way but
ain't you affected? Hey don't worry.
It's under control. Zombrex. You better have three days work.
You seem real nice. I'd hate to have to put a bullet in your head.
Uh thanks. We ain't got these Zombrex here.
Military have to quarantine first. They'll enter the city at first light
three days from now to get all of us. That's the standard procedure. So we're
stuck here. Where is he keeping that Zombrex?
Not out there. What you think? Probably down the front of his pants.
Damn it. I'm already out of coffee. What a disaster.
Orange juice. I've already seen it. Didn't he just say we don't have any
Zombrex? I know where you can get some Zombrex.
Collie Brady thanks for the five subs. Thanks for the five community subs.
I figured you were infected. Though I don't remember you saying anything about that in your book.
Well it's not exactly something I'd go around. There's a pharmacy
in the royal flesh mall. Back to the mall. I'm Stacy Borsig by the way.
I'm Frank. Frank. Frank West. Plenty of people know you.
Do you know a way out of here? No but if you find one
I suggest you take this. That way we can keep in touch.
There's closed circuit cameras all over the city. These monitors are playback only.
But I'll keep an eye on them. Bluetooth headset. Those must have just come out
right? Frank, if you find anyone alive out there.
I've got experience rounding up survivors. Hello?
Okay got the map. Find Zombrex. Here we go. You've just reached a checkpoint. These
occur throughout Fortune City. Whenever you see checkpoint reached you
have reached a checkpoint. Right. Save often if you quit your current
game or power off you will lose your checkpoint.
Okay. The military will arrive in three days to contain the zombie outbreak.
Of course. Keep track of how much time is left. Press
the select to check the watch right? Always remember that Frank needs
Zombrex every 24 hours. Oh shit. The transceiver will let you
receive co-op calls. Well we're not going to be doing that.
People can drop in for a co-op game at any time. You can restrict who joins in
the gameplay options. Explore Fortune City with a friend and
slaughter even more undead. Me and Star played this like five years
ago. But we only made it about an hour or two
into the game I think. All right so uh where are we at?
I should check out Roy's Mart in Royal Flush Plaza.
Right. That's the destination I've got until
uh 8 a.m. You got it. How do I pick up the uh
how do I put up the watch?
8 a.m. Eastern time? Sounds like it. All right. Give it this flashlight.
Just give me like a give me a palette. No. Give me a piece of wood.
All right. How do I throw? What's the throw object?
It's not right trigger. Left bumper? Right bumper?
Right trigger? How do you throw?
All right. Fuck. Who cares? You can't throw inside the safe room. Okay. Right.
Right. How many safe slots do I get? I have to be really careful then. I have
I get three slots. I had like 10 in Dead Rising.
At least six. Right. I remember being down here and just throwing shit at each
other. You get 12 slots in original Dead Rising
too. Sounds like a much better game. You can't
keep Frank West bottled up. All right. What is it with me and Vince?
Zombrex. So I need to go to here. So we go straight out. Bang a left.
Just make our way over there. I guess. I got nothing else to do. So that. Okay.
There it is. Saw blades. What's in the box?
Just more saws. Can they stack in this game? No they don't. All right. Let's go.
Oh there's a shovel though. I'm gonna replace flashlight with. No. Handbag with
shovel. That's much. Does it have a super punch?
Yep. How do I bring up the watch? Isn't it? Wasn't it left on the d-pad?
Stacy will send you messages about the interesting things she sees happening
around Fortune City. Each mission has a time limit. Right.
You can track the time limits on the mission queue
on the HUD or in the watch screen. Right. Messages will lead you to survivors of
the zombie outbreak scattered around the city. Yes they will.
And that's urgent. Frank. I flush Plaza. Royce Mart is on the other side of the mall.
Blast. Things that I don't say on a. There's slot machines in this game.
Welcome to Fortune City where money is king. People come to Fortune City to win
big. You'll never know when you'll need some
money. Smashing ATMs and slot machines can earn
you easy money. Earn even more by playing winning slot
machines. Collect gambling magazines for a lucky
boost. Look out for money cases and security
box keys. They can lead you to big cash rewards if you see one. Grab it.
So there's money in this game. Okay. What's that? I have like two of these.
Okay. Can I see how many of these I have? All right. Let's do it. Shoes. Off.
In closet. My favorite place to be. All right. We'll just let a brick. This is
bricks in this game. I want a brick. You can throw bricks? Yeah.
I think I've had the same reaction. What a pathetic throw. He threw that
like it weighed 10 times more than it does.
I have to hit somebody in the face with this. Got it. Okay. I can move on.
What else is in here? Vinyl records. Large soda.
Register. Smash the register.
Wow. You actually do collect money. Gun. Get the foam finger. Red spray paint.
I need a big game. Okay. I gotta go. How do guns work in this game?
Are they just as horrible? They're pretty good. They're not bad.
All right. Let's go find. Let's just do this because I'm here.
You can walk and aim. You can walk and aim. What's that? Sporting Good Store?
Come on. It's my turn. What? I need the hammer. Any hammers in here?
They're MMA gloves. All right. Okay. I'm gonna get. I'm gonna use the MMA gloves.
Boxing gloves. Do I get experience for this?
Holy shit. I actually did. Thousand. Come on. Break. Two completely different
recorded voice lines for the same thing. That's Spider-Man PS4 levels of awesome.
Okay. All right. Get out of my way. Orange juice is way better than soda.
The truck only has three recorded voice lines.
Does it only have one? That kind of sucks.
It's a giant craps table. This game is cool. Can I actually do this?
Can I actually play craps? Come on. What do I get? Four.
I have to bet. How do I bet? I gotta put a bet down.
Oh shit. That's outside of the playing area. I have to go get chips.
Okay. I'm gonna get addicted to some stuff in here. It's gonna be crazy.
I like the the feedback on that gun. We got jewelry store.
Money. Gems. Can I just like convert this into money?
Presents? Get off me you motherfucker.
Shopping boxes. All right. I don't want to run out of time.
There's a car. There's a car in the mall. And this is a drivable car.
In the mall. They're already. Oh come on.
I need shit that exists. It actually exists.
I just won 1200 bucks. All right. I'm done. Oh god. He's addicted. I just won
1200 dollars and got him walked away. Here. Am I going the right way?
Uh yes. It's right here. You sprayed on yourself first.
I want some more. I want some more coffee. Shit.
I just got like a little one. Hey. You have something better to do.
Why don't you mind your own business old man?
Just looking for some meds. No need to get ugly.
Well you're definitely gonna need some painkillers when I'm done with you.
Well talking to you is giving me a headache. Crowbar is not a great weapon.
What say you? Hard to swing. It's heavy. And I'll go get some for you.
Yeah. Give us some money grandpa. We'll help you.
Just a block of wood. It's actually. Do you know how heavy a crowbar actually is?
It turned your fucking friends green. Completely green.
Why did I call me grandpa? I'm like 41. I've had enough. I thought he was gonna drink it.
I thought he was gonna drink it. I was gonna let him take a sip.
Psycho. I was gonna let him get a nice swig before he died.
Crowbar. Double crowbar and hatchet. Oh shit. You're alive. All right hold on.
Do you mind if I take all this? Okay. I thought they were gonna kill me.
It's okay. You're safe now. Are you hurt? I think I'm okay. Thank you so much.
You got here before they. Before they. Listen. There's a safe house.
Well you'll be safe. Follow me and I'll take you there.
Dense? Is it Denise? Dense. There are survivors of the outbreak scattered through a fortune city.
Escort anyone you find back to the safe house. Though some might not come with you willingly.
Why is to call a survivor? Or you can press left trigger and y to send them to a location, right?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. Follow me. Agreed. Hurry it up. Let's get the Zombrex. Anybody else here?
Zombrex. Frank will need a Zombrex at 8 a.m. It is high in demand, expensive, and hard to find.
The new and improved Zombrex formula lasts 24 hours. Zombrex overdoses are deadly. Oh no.
Users must never take it earlier than prescribed. I'm gonna have to save all the time.
The Zombrex counter on your HUD shows how much you have at all times.
Frank needs Zombrex every day between 7 a.m. and 8 a.m. If he doesn't get it, he will die.
So every day at 7 a.m. to 8 a.m. just scream at me. Check your watch to see if it's time
for your next dose. Okay. I have Zombrex. It's too early to inject myself. I can only inject
myself between 7 and 8 a.m. Give me that orange juice. Oh, I remember the computer. The computer
joke. It's all coming back to me. A defib. You alive? Now you're extra alive. All right. Let's
go. Quick. Follow me. Oh, there's orange juice everywhere, but I don't really need it. Actually,
you know what? Yeah, I'm gonna take another one. Let's go. So I need to take that Zombrex.
Actually, I should. Can you have the weapon? Here, come here. Give item. Here. I mean, like,
you're the doctor, so you take this. What? You're the doctor. You'll take an axe, but you won't take
a defib? All right. Okay. Uh, guide arrow. I need to go back to the safe house. Uh, is it already
guiding me? Or is this just, I have to take Zombrex at 7 a.m.? I swing. I swing down. Holy
shit. She's actually attacking zombies. All right. Um, where's the safe house from here?
Can I not move around? There we go. So, uh, safe house is, what is it? It's the green one.
Can I zoom out a little bit? It was back here, wasn't it? All right. I'm gonna set a waypoint
to here. Let's go back to the safe house. You all right? All right, let's move. We gotta go.
The bare feet can be accessed through the locker in the safe house. I love how that's being spammed.
Jeremy, bare feet. Is that available? Bare feet available.
What are you talking about? I feel like I'm superhero from Mystery Men.
I'm the defense. He's a wrestler. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. This is one of the,
this is one of the people that they passed on during that whole montage. They're trying
to find superheroes. Look like Deadpool 2. Pick one. Come on. Speed it up. Keep up. Hey, I'm
waiting on you. Yeah. Deadpool 2 for zoomers. Mystery Men for boomers. I'm, I can, I make sure
that I address all audiences. She's like dead. Don't die. I can't lose the first survivor.
Right through there. Maybe get an actual weapon. I'm fine. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die.
I thought she just had a giant syringe for a second. Did somebody just say Monka S bare feet?
Why is that? Firecrackers. Dance. Look, those guys were stealing everything. Thanks for saving my
life. Where on earth did you find them? Nevermind. I don't want to know. We can't afford to have any
more infected in here. One's enough. Okay. Hey, any, where can I change into bare feet around here?
What the fuck are you talking about, Frank? Just take off your damn shoes and socks. What are you
talking about? Earned PP by killing zombies. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Let's you level up. Yep. Leveling
up, up, up, up. Let's you gain new skills, attributes, and even combo cards. Yes, it does.
New skill. Roundhouse kick. Hold right trigger and hold A. Drill bucket? Wait, what do you mean
combo cards? Pylon and spray paint is a bullhorn. Okay. Uh, status. Skills. Jump kick. Yeah.
Dodge roll. Click left stick. Good to know. Roundhouse. Hold right trigger and hold A.
All right. So what's the problem? Hold right trigger and hold A. I'm in the safe house. Nevermind.
All right. So, um, what time is it? I got to inject myself. It is 6 17 a.m. I have to take
an injection in like 15 minutes. This is fine. Safe house fun. Just chilling before an injection.
That's right. All right. What is that? Which one is it? This one here? The locker? Sweet.
Okay. Oh, I just put on like tap shoes. Oh, whatever. All right. Time check. It is 6 30.
Time to take an injection in a few minutes. Just going here. There's probably a cut scene here
after as well. Glad you found some zombricks, but it's not time to take it yet. I need my daily dose
between 7 and 8 a.m. I'll take it then. Can you take this anywhere? Can you hear me? Can anyone
hear somebody? Somebody. Don't run with scissors. This is a zombie outbreak. All right. 6 35 a.m.
Give me the fire extinguisher too. And okay. Cool. Hey, is the Star Wars game any good?
Anyone like know anything about it? The one, the one just coming out like in three days,
four days, whatever it is. Is it good? Anybody know? That's a lot of orange juice. All right.
Few minutes. I can take it. How the fuck are we supposed to know? I don't know. Have you guys been
paying attention to it? I don't know. Did anybody like play it? Any, any journalists in here?
Although that you can't even tell me anyways because you're probably under like an NDA.
The previews look good. I don't know. I just know it's coming out in a few days. I don't know if
some games, the review copies have already been out for a while. Maybe I just didn't know if
those views are out or who's there? All right, we go. 651 incoming. Reviews come out on Thursday.
All right. 653 incoming. Drama. Go do stuff. I feel like I'm gonna have to be right here. All
right. I've got only got like an hour. I'm done. It's time to take it. You can do it anywhere.
Oh, okay. Okay. Well, it says destination safe house and that doesn't know the destination is
7 a.m. That's it. Okay. So now what? Start at 8 a.m. Nothing to do now. But wait, Stacey will call me.
Fuck. All right. Well, let's set a waypoint to, um, let's go out to, is it a gas station?
That's a car. Whatever. Just go this way. Go out and try the sweet roundhouse kit. Get the scissors
suck. Just don't gamble for an hour. No, I'm not. I'm just gonna go kill stuff
and go find some more costume stuff. Okay. Well, I can. Hey, I can take you right now.
Lady, it's Sandra Dawkins and hell no, I ain't all right. My good-for-nothing husband left me out
here. I remember this part. Don't you have to? Okay. I've played the first couple hours of this
game. Okay. Watch out behind you. Watch out behind you. Watch out behind you. Watch out behind you.
All right, let's go. All right. What did you say? Oh, you got a weapon. Oh, yeah. You got like a
wrench. Oh, my. I'm hitting her in the head over and over again. All right. Um, I didn't, I, where
was it? Was it right here? It's like right here, isn't it? Cafe. Casual gals.
Keep up. Here. Take some orange juice. Here. Take orange juice. I'm trying to stop. I know. You're
locked in. Like aggression is taking over. Come here. No. Gordon Dawkins. There you are.
All right. Come here. Come here. I hate to break up this lovely reunion, but this is not safe out here.
Take this. He's right. Let's go. Yes, dear. Gordon has joined. Here. Take. Drink it. Okay, you have
this back. No, no, no. Come back. Come back. No. Take this back. Take this back. Take this back.
Yes, use that. Take it. No, I didn't want to. Okay. Okay. Well, we've all been well fed.
Take this. Okay. Let's move. You want orange juice or what? All right. Back to the safe house.
Let's go. That way. Let's go. Roundhouse kick. It's a pretty shitty roundhouse kick. It's really,
it's too low. Let's go. Frank is my age. How old is Frank in this game? 50. Follow me. You guys
making it? Yeah. Can I have, give me your stuff back? I want that back. Sorry. Why does nobody
want this? I want to throw them. Keep up. It's because it sucks. Urgent. Frank, they're starting
to report the outbreak on the news. You should come back and watch this. All right. Well, let's
go back to the safe house. Two more people. It's all that we have received a broadcast from our
Phil Kachang who is inside Fortune City. Don't tease me like that.
I wish I could drink that right now. I love just shitty dirty
coffee pot coffee. It's like my favorite thing.
Okay. This is how fucked up my brain is. I was about to like just send Kim a text.
Hey, could you throw on a pot of coffee for me? And I opened up Twitter
and was about to write, Hey, can you throw a pot of coffee on for me?
That the man is reality as their complete no statement of response has been received.
This horrible act of terror appears to be an escalation of violence for the protest
group. This is the picture on that screen. Where the hell did that come from? Liar. It came from
the security cameras, lady. What the hell were you thinking? Your group's got a reputation,
but come on. Cure had nothing to do with this. It's pretty easy to say that, isn't it? You're
going to need more than that. Better start talking, right? I'm telling you, we're being set up. We've
been accused of things before, but we don't believe in violence. Did I just send that to the wrong
fucking person? It's someone's convenient excuse. No, really. What am I going to say? What is wrong
with me? It's not the first time members of Cure have been falsely accused of being involved with
an outbreak. I've got to find whoever leaked that tape. Like an old real estate agent or something.
Hey, can you put a pot of coffee on for me? What's going on with this game?
Where is she? She said she was in the hotel. I know this could end up being a big chance for
your career. It's not internet related. It's just... This could mean my life. Video game
hardware reception. Level up. New skill move acquired. All right. Case one two engaged.
I need to find out what that Rebecca Chang knows. We got it. Would you like to save your progress?
Sure, I would. Dead rising for the switch. Pretty great, actually. You found yourself caught in the
Fortune City outbreak. Track down clues to uncover the truth about what happened.
Restore your name and escape from the city. Okay. Time until the military comes 72 hours 56 minutes
55 seconds. Leveled up. All right. Back to exploring. All right. That's really cool.
What move did I just learn? Find the reporter in the Fortune City hotel. I need to find that
reporter in the hotel lobby. You got it. But for now, but first front kick. Hold R T and press A.
I got... I'm good. Get out of my way. Maintenance room key acquired.
Maintenance room key acquired. Promise everyone. Maintenance room key lets you access all maintenance
rooms in Fortune City. Maintenance rooms will let you make powerful combo weapons.
Maintenance rooms are located throughout Fortune City. Bright red doors and neon signs are easily
visible from a distance. Good. Maintenance room is always within reach. Just check your maintenance
rooms map. They're always marked with the wrench icon. Cool.
Take it. It's yours. Thanks. Okay. So they have... Oh, they all have little things on them.
There's a guy playing the slots. Okay. You don't have to read it.
I'll go check on him. I'll go sit down with him and join him.
Know when to fold them. I'm going to go join this guy. So that means it can be combined. That's
cool. All right. Let's craft. Yeah, let's do it. Know when to fold the slots. Spiked Bat is
baseball bat in box of nails. Combo cards give you the recipe to build powerful combo weapons.
Cards you have found are all in the combo card screen. Killing with combo weapons gives you
bonus PP. You can level up faster and kill more zombies. So that's like... I want to make that
thing. That's like Barney the dinosaur eating a bunch of rocket pops. Whatever that thing does.
Explosions. Fireworks. Try building more combo weapons using items from around the city. They're
easy to spot. They all have a wrench. Speaking of which, I want one of those bad. All right.
Let's see what I got. DFib. Baseball bat and DFib. They only combo if they blow. Oh. All right.
Well, can I do anything with this? DFib and bucket. DFib and cone. How about cone and bucket?
What would that make? A bigger bucket? All right. I got my spiked bat. Wait. Oh, thousands.
How many gallons of milk do I have in my fridge right now? I don't like, I don't have like none.
I don't have like regular milk. Regular milk gives you diarrhea. It does to me.
What you got? One of those looters. Looks like one of those looters has set up a pawn shop inside
Moe's imaginations. He might have something for you. Okay. Well, I need to, we gotta go because
just trying to get pp with poor Grace. Nice shitty weapon. They can only be combined. I'll
figure out the combinations. What? Holy shit. Oh man. They have different, oh that's awesome.
They don't got this shit in the base game, do they? Yes, they do. I know.
I know. I know. Is it a wheelchair? Wait. Funny costume stuff. Can I put it on? Kids superhero
boots. This is like Santa wakes up at 3 a.m. to drink milk out of the fridge. Which by the way,
gross. And what's the point of having, all right, I, this button's at the top. But what on earth
are the buttons on the back for? Is that to change, is that to change like a diaper or something?
I don't know. I've never known what that is for. This is to poo. Why we, that's disgusting.
What the hell was that? Who's talking? I hear somebody talking. It's a onesie. Look at the top.
It buttons all the way down to the, to the, to like the crockery area.
Shit, this is ridiculous. Okay. Somebody's in it. Get out of the way. Wait, this is a whole casino.
Oh no, I'm never going to get out of here. I'm never going to be able to leave.
Oh shit. Okay. I got to find this guy. Don't play any of these machines. It's a waste of money.
This roulette, you can actually play roulette. No, you can't.
Damn it. I thought I had the big one for sure. Oh well, I'll go again.
Bill, Bill, we got to talk. Bill, buddy, you doing okay? I like slots too, but you might want to
wait things out the safe house. That's a nice idea. But I got money to win back. I ain't leaving
without it. Might not be the best time with all these zombies around. Hang on there sweetie. Good
things come to those who wait. You can gamble. Why don't you just break them? Just smash them.
You can run along to your safe house and be like, I'm down $20,000 and I'm not going
anywhere until I have made that money back. Oh my, I have to give you $20,000? What if I break
his machine? How about another $5,000? Bill, a little advice for you. There's some pretty
greedy folks here in Fortune City. Might do well to keep some cash handy. Bill, here. Okay. Well,
take the knife. All right. Now watch out. Let me show you how it's done. Hey, back up.
Come on. One more. I didn't mean to drink the fucking orange juice. I meant to switch to the
bad. I got it all back. Don't worry. Okay, let's go. Bill, come with me. Case one, two. Not yet.
One man's trash. We're close. Not that close, but see if we can do it. This is the pawn shop.
Holy shit, there's a bolt. Ride the thunder. What do I win? $2,000. Oh shit. I'm wasting all my money.
$5,000.
It's like just my sweat covered hands is what happened. All right, Bill, let's go.
Drinking all the drinks. No. Let's go to the pawn shop. Bill, are you good?
It's time for the casino later. Who cares about Bill? I'm going to get the PP from Bill. He was
$25,000. 70 hours. All right, let's get this pawn shop. The knife sucks. I need to combine
this to make a better knife. This thing's terrible. No. I gotta get Bill some food.
You can do it. Snacks over here probably, right? $100 for snacks? Quick, eat, eat, eat.
No, I'm trying to pick up the bat. Bill. Bouncing beauty. Propane tank and rocket fireworks.
Eat these. All right, I need to get that fucking bat. Here, take this. Keep moving.
All the health you just gained is gone. How do you not? He's lost more HP. Bill's gonna die.
You were $20,000, Bill. My chest. God damn it. Shit. Loot him. He had a gun this whole time?
Holy shit, he had multiple guns. Bill, I just want the gun. Get away from me. Go. All right, out.
Save scum? No, I can't save scum. No save scumming. It's my own damn fault. Holy, I just got that
guy from across the world. All right, one man's trash. Here we go. Stuff for sale.
See what I just did? Wait a minute, you. You're one of those punks that tried to jump me in Roy's
Mart. Whatever. Might have been one of my pals, grandpa. We're just businessmen seeking out
merchandise for our shop. Feel free to browse any of our four pawn shops set up around Fortune
City. There's this one here and the others. We've got lots of valuable merchandise, pal. I wouldn't
turn your nose up at it. We can really help you out if a GM will do it. Let's go. Wacky hammer?
Okay, I'll take a wacky hammer, please. Is this costing money? Soldier goggles. $2 million.
$1,000 bucks. 15,000. Zombrex. 50 grand. I need that. Hey, any leads? I can see two guys.
Can I wear this? What? Can I please wear this? How do I get on? How do I pedal?
Okay, yeah, I remember this. All right, let's see what we got. Welcome to the family. Let's do
welcome to the family. Welcome to the family, son. This is slower than walking. This cannot
go upstairs. That's next level. That deserves at least 2,000 pub champs in the chat, I think.
Upgrade. All right, welcome to the family. Is everybody in the casino? I can't take this with
me. Oh, you guys are in the casino. Oh, damn it.
Excuse me. Is it downgrade if you ask me? I know. What was the new move? Just a kick. Nice. It's
pretty good. Atlantica. What's that on ground? Beer? I'll take a beer. It's the same thing
because it was a dolphin this time instead of a bull. How did I miss you? I have to drink beer now.
You can combine it with Molotov, I'm assuming, right? Yeah. Treasure chest. Money. I'm just using
my wrist to try to break that. That's not going to happen. I don't want to break this. I'm going to
play them later. Get off of me. Dude, go on the pirate ship. Eventually. Pirate ship now. No,
not yet. We'll get on the pirate ship in 15 minutes from now. We've got dynamic lighting in here and
it's making me drop down to like 50 fps. You're a shit PC. That's where you're wrong. I have
a intermediate level PC. This is nice. Come on. All the way out. Whipped cream can?
What? Oh, wow. Really? Oh, I want to eat this. Why is there a chainsaw back here and a key?
Use blenders to mix food items together and to mix drinks. Yep.
I have special bonuses. There are different types of mixed drinks. Each one with its own special
power. Yep. I gotta move. Where is this? In the corner? I dropped the chainsaw. How the
fuck did I do that? Get that dang thing off your head. I'm here. I brought the wheat cutter.
All right. Kenneth and Jack. Is that Proto Man? Is it Zero? Proto Man? Who is this? Are they all
gone? I hate those things. We gotta get out of here. They're more coming. I can get you to safety.
Why is he looking at me like that with a knife out? What's he doing? What is he doing? I really
love my wife, but it's like he doesn't like me at all. Can you help? Thanks stranger. The name's
Kenneth. Me and my loser for a son-in-law are trying to bond as my daughter says.
Follow me back to the safe house. It's too dangerous out here. Sounds good, but my daughter
Casimina would probably kill me if something happened to her dimwit poker fiend of a husband.
Better see if he's up to leaving. He's the fool over there in the helmet. All right. We're all
going. Let's go. He's trying to kill me. I'm not like a snake, man. Stop. Let's go. I want to play
a little poker. Let's go. Jack is joined. Kenneth is joined. Okay. Bowie knife. Here. You need this.
What else we got in here? Cleaver. Here. Stop like taunting at ringside. Here. Take this.
There's food. Anything else back here? There's like french fries and shit. Hold on.
All right. Let's move back to the safe house. Take the bow and fucking arrow. This thing sucks.
That was a headshot. I have french fries and bow and arrows. The side. No, I'm taking the side.
This thing sucks. Take the claymore. Oh god damn it. Claymore? Where's a claymore? Oh fuck. There's
a giant sword in here. Somebody open this. Where's the claymore? This is the claymore. I thought you
meant a bomb. I thought you meant like an explosive like plastic claymore thing.
Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. He's played too much cod.
Kenneth. God damn it. Holy shit. People die so much quicker in this game. Take some french fries
before you die. Take some french fries quick please. All right. Let's go. Right. Take a lot.
There's a large soda here too. I can't man. I don't want to swing. Get them soda. Get the large soda.
I look like I'm trying to be a Mega Man character by and saving money while doing so. All right.
Here. I want you at full health. Kenneth. Here. Just eat everything on the ground. All right.
Any more? That's it? Here. You take the bone arrow. Idiot. All right. Let's go.
Save point. Where's one? All right. I'm right here. There is a save point. No. I gotta go back this way.
There's a save point right in the middle. Is there a bathroom? There's no damn bathroom over here.
I have to go over here. Bang a right.
Let's go. He doesn't have weapon. Take this.
What is going on?
What? I had two people with me. What happened to Ken and um Mega Man fan?
Meat. Bobby Hill? There are lots of zombies around here. Maybe she could eat those.
No. Please. That meat is rotten. He needs meat. Fresh meat. Sure. Sure. I can get some fresh meat.
Steak. Maybe I'll go look for some. No. This guy's wearing like a leaf tarp for pants.
People not been very good to me. Like snowflake. Snowflake my friend. Listen. Let's talk this over.
What's your name? Theodore. We talked about Dan Aykroyd before.
This is actually his Ghostbusters outfit when they when they're in their pajamas.
We just need to slow down this over Ted. And they don't have the actual like jumpsuit on. They're
in that. See people not nice. This is really did I walk into a boss fight?
I have to fight a tiger. The last time I saved was so long ago.
Oh this is bad. This is really bad. All right Jack. Kill him. Get him. Ted. Somebody.
Dude. That was fucking easy.
The tiger sprinted away and then he stood there and got stun locked. No loyalty apparently.
Wait was was this person not going to attack me?
The cat is uh fucking running around back there. Gems and leaf blower.
Uh okay. So we need to get the fuck out of here.
Uh all right let's go. Wait. A tiki torch. Okay. No I don't. Oh my god it's right in here.
Okay. No no no no. Run run run. Run run run. Run run. Is it a cat jump?
All right. Go go go go go. No no no no. Stop fighting the tiger.
Oh no please. Motherfucker. You opportunist asshole. I don't have any food.
Oh shit. I was supposed to save the game. Oh my god. I have to fucking. Give me a beer.
Somebody. Do it. Fight something. Cat come. Can the cat come downstairs? Just beer on the ground.
Meat on bone. Yeah they take so much more damage than this one. Jack dead. Jack dead. Feed the
tiger. Um I think I got more of a problem on my hands here. Feed tiger. Go tame the tiger. I'm
dead. And so are these two guys that I'm with. They're both dead. How the fuck am I supposed to.
Wait is it food? Holy shit. I thought these. I thought this was meat. I thought it was meat.
It's foam hands. He's puking. He's dead man. It's over. Holy shit. This is a disaster.
Oh I'm gonna die too. I'm just trying to save the damn game and I walk into a tiger.
Shit. Oh well. I gotta get in there. Uh Frank there seems to be a dancer throwing up in there.
So? What do you. The janitor. Somebody puked in the uh by the uh you know by the where's the gold
slot machine. Uh I guess I'll take. Well sure. Very cool. All right. Wait what time is it?
So this is find the reporter which is straight ahead here. How much time do I have? Not very
much but that's not that far away. The save point's right in the mill. I'm so sad right now.
I'm so sad.
I wanted to save those too. There's a weed whacker right here. There's a maintenance room in here.
Oh shit. Hold on. Excuse me. Goodbye. All right. So wait. Hold on. Place item. Wait. Knife and
battery? Wait a minute. Knife and. Knife and weed whacker. Holy shit. Okay. Um what can I do with
bow and arrow? Bow and arrow and battery? Can I make like electric bow? Damn it. Lawnmower
and knife? Lawnmower and battery? Lawnmower and board of wood.
Oh yeah. A port of mower. Scratch cards let you know what you need to make a combo weapon
but they're not as good as combo cards. Scratch cards mean less pp from combo weapons. You also
cannot perform strong attacks. Replace your scratch cards with real combo cards as soon as you can.
You can find combo cards everywhere. Scratch cards? Okay. Shit. I can only bring one
which is better. Oh I gotta go. All right. Where's that save point right there?
That's a lot of pp. Just in case I run into a huge problem.
Okay let's go. Game is saved. You just have to bump into people with this.
Exactly. These things are actually great. You don't even need to use it. You're not killing them? I
know but it's just I'm just trying to get through. Now what? Cat is back.
out here buddy um thanks rebecca chang channel six action news frank west
i know you you used to be a kind of a hero of mine before you got washed up you homesick for
zombies what are you doing here hey i came to help with your story i think cure's being set up
up my exclusive tape says otherwise and i don't exactly need your help it doesn't have to be a
contest lady i help you you help me simple where'd you go nobody's gonna shake your hand darlin
orders don't be pretty gross sources frank not real ones anyway i wouldn't underestimate
frank west sweetheart i got some pictures you might be interested in no that's right we're
both journalists okay see what you got not so fast you gotta throw the old dog a bone before
he does any tricks okay maybe i'll let you tag along for a while that's more like it that's
the point in the video where you cut to her being eaten by 30 zombies and dying there is a central
security room that's pretty good cut point i think footage of everything that happened there
i can show you while spamming y and she's not following you show me yours i show you mine
where's your crew equipment i guess they just didn't want it bad enough i'm gonna steal that
for my youtube video that's fine i want eight percent royalties on that video though rebecca
won't tell me her source but she'll take me to arena security so don't hold that out
that we have to do this like now follow rebecca um how do i talk to you without cutting you with
this let's get going try to keep up all right is there any food can oh wait key nice give me that
back give me this back why would you i just need to lean down where we going where we going there's
a bathroom here for me to take a breath i i know how do you play the game what i'm ready we don't
have time for this i already went to the bathroom what's yes a guy on a yellow motorcycle
oh this chainsaw i don't need him this thing's blinking what does that mean
mario autos um oh no he's spraying me minus 1500 dollars what are you guys doing
money hacker all right all right i'll take care of this i'll take well i'll remove all of their
shoes shit i'm nothing without my weed wacker i'm nothing without the weed wacker if you're
nothing without the weed wacker you shouldn't have it but my weed wacker but why we wacker
okay we're good cutscene saved by the cutscene damn it you would survive out here just i don't
have to do everything for you just admire your skills ha ha oh whoa whoa by the way i played
luigi's mansion three for like 10 like 20 minutes i have not heard more ah oh hoes ever in a mario
game than in that game don't leave me where's the checkpoint is there a checkpoint right there
nice i need a different weapon
but no what i said earlier but what i was saying is it so it doesn't matter what happens
luigi if it's scary if it's exciting luigi always has the same reaction
oh yeah oh oh it happens every 15 to 20 seconds can you do something about this guy
i didn't say i didn't like it it's a really fun game
journalism school could have fooled me hey bro what a mess well this just gets better and better
going to school for journalism lol it looks like somebody didn't like the show much you should get
this on video you guys the internet may have changed a lot of things they didn't want us to
see what really went down but like 15 20 years ago you couldn't do it on a computer zombies don't
use guns not so sure here's not involved but it definitely proves someone's covering up what
really happened not a bad lead kiddo those pictures frank frank those are laptop motherboards
what is it stacy yeah he saw the report can you get back here wait who is that just a friend
the leader of cure gotta go i gotta get out of here he can't ditch me for long that's what the
lag i have no idea someone's destroyed the security room well i lose the game um okay so
i lose i have to go out i need heels i'm dead why did i break that i need the fucking
just stuff inside i think i'm gonna i think i'm locked i think i'm locked out
so something that i didn't have to do in the last dead rising
uh but i'm probably gonna have to do here is
you realistically replay dead rising like three or four times we might have to do that
let's go 100 bucks for cheetahs yeah that's kind of insane
but i i don't know exactly how much time i have left it's not very much
yes it's sort of possible it is it's maybe remotely possible how far away am i
it's gonna be it's gonna be impossible but we'll see i might actually be able to do it if i just
haul ass at the last save that i had use a wheelchair i'm about to lose yes damn it
it might be possible if i can there's a money machine well this just became one of my favorite
games it's right here it's gonna be so close ah nobody breathe oh i can do it i can do it
without getting snacks i can do it without getting snacks it's the snacks it's possible
without snacks and a wheelchair i can get one oh fuck there's a checkpoint here too
i have to load the save all right i gotta be quicker i can do it i'm just gonna skip
the cutscene and we'll go from there shit all right truth has vanished so the last save was
right when i walked out the door so this is day two at 2 30 okay i can do it from here
yeah this would be fine yeah this is good because now i just gotta go all right we're gonna do this
quick this is this is a good place to be because just follow me i'm just gonna run to where i need
to go i still have some time just don't get hit unnecessarily by anything skip this here we go
so where'd you learn all right i'm ready let's go go go go go go go wheelchair can i can i put her
in the wheelchair yeah i know hey uh yep let's go i'm ready come on i'm supposed to be bleeding
and then right out of this just run to where i need to go and in a wheelchair just run just get a
wheelchair and run in the wheelchair from and just don't look at anything don't wait get a snack now
get the snacks now and i want a better weapon than that that thing's too slow
i didn't know is you have to it's right stick to aim
it's all right we're fine i still have time i have enough time with a wheelchair
go go go go go go run the way you're supposed to be running oh fuck
what's he throwing me
me what did you hit me from that far away that doesn't make any sense okay leave i got a new
checkpoint the axe trying to save you because you're in the way all right that was faster than
last time no get the game bar off the xbox game bar just i just got an xbox game bar i can't
fucking believe i just got game barred what is what is the xbox game bar why is it on what is
this thing i got time all right where's the wheelchair need a wheelchair right now wheelchair
did you just kill me in the air all right need a wheelchair where's the wheelchair
i see one of course i run on the fucking other side like an idiot all right i think i'm gonna
make it pick up the wheelchair go the door open open the door open the door open the door open
the door open the door i'm coming i'm coming i'm almost there it's so close oh i have to go up the
stairs i have to go up the stairs not now i don't have time oh made it hey a man like you real
american helping out trash like this you don't need that kind of publicity bell sullivan i think
you're being set up i saw it on the tv with my own eyes explain how that little trick works
there's something else going on here sullivan i found some evidence at the arena of a cover-up
i've got a feeling tk the host of that game show was on the tv i saw him backstage at his show
swapping a briefcase of money with the guy they showed on tv starting this outbreak
you could have told me that the front door was locked smash that camera smash it quick
hey just snatch the camera out of the hand smash into ground as hard as you fucking can
i'll make you a deal done you two do your little investigation you see if you can help this
troublemaker but ain't no one gonna cover her ass when the military arrives and she ain't
allowed off the premises i'll be guarding the door don't think i won't do what i have to do
there's not even a battery in that camera what was that all about he just takes this job too
seriously tell me you found something we checked out central security someone's definitely trying
to hide something everything was smashed to pieces yeah i hired her for some behind the
scenes footage when we cut up the second dvd stacy rebecca chang channel six action news
i'm here to help you'll forgive me if i don't think it's very helpful that you accused my
organization of a crime we didn't it's for the collector's edition look i don't know what's
going on here but clearly things are not as they seem i put out the information i had at the time
hey i love a good cat fight but we're not getting anywhere unless we work together ladies
oh my back works for me why do i have a turtle shell i just want the truth
thanks for the vote of confidence but okay we'll work together ogre i'll keep an eye on these
monitors and i'm going back out there to see what i can find out i'll let you know if i see
uh ogre really is such like a funny fucking word
doesn't matter you know what an ogre is it doesn't you don't even need to know what the word
even is defined as it just sounds like what that looks like all right save and continue
case two one good all right i got time don't i need to get i need zombrex too don't i this is
kind of awkward um i need zombrex let's save it frank is just the apple from the community
content stream yeah it is you just saved i know okay so let's just get out of here uh we got a
couple things i could so on 6 30 p.m i don't have that much time where's this this one's pretty
close yeah i can't do this one they're on they're on a bike i think i can do luscious lady go do it
it's not possible i can't do it no i can't i can't be up against the clock every single time
every time i don't want to be sprinting back here going oh no oh no oh no oh no please
like yeah that's i don't want to do that anymore that makes for good content i don't want it to be
every time spray paint fire axe and nails i'm gonna make another bad the bat was good
ready to rumble bat and bat bat and bat wouldn't that would just be two bats
all right luscious lady check the recipes combo cards drill and bucket this is a pole weapon
that's kind of cool port-a-potty weed tendonizer spike bat gem blower i kind of want what do i need
to leap over this all right if i come across another i mean nothing's funny but is it really
worth it i want to do an air horn i have the paint is there i need a cone seriously
i'm just gonna drink all the coffee cream over here no no get your own get
wait in line like everybody else brownies oh that healed me to full all right let me
get a uh spray paint back fuck the bow and arrow it's not good all right i'm good i gotta go this
way uh i wonder i wonder what kind of brownies yours were right money all right i got a little
bit of time uh they threw open here right no how would you do that stop being a i didn't make any
anime reference what are you talking about okay i don't even know what happened there this fucking
emulator all right somebody puked back here i gotta take care of them you all right hi there
wait you're not josh where'd he run off to josh yeah he was in that nice little bachelor party
that kept buying me drinks man a lot of things died out there listen lady there are zombies
everywhere we gotta go oh yeah hiccup there's that terror is reality show in town tomorrow
that tk is tested blood yesterday that last thing i remember was josh and those boys buying
me drinks i must have passed out okay well this this is probably like here have a brownie have
a handgun come with me it isn't safe out here and i can take you where you can lie down and get
something to drink there's a safe house take it that's not what i meant never mind let's just get
out here let's go a little sloppy there take no what i have to carry you you can't do anything
about this here take a gun i have to carry you this is not good okay let's think i can open doors
thank god all right um let's get you back to the safe house because what do you i can't just
leave you wheelchair get in the wheelchair this is perfect get in the wheelchair can i put you
in the wheelchair you can't do that if i can push the wheelchair that's absurd oh god let's go
so you can what there's a guy crying where is he he's fucking far away yeah you're far away
now we get we gotta i gotta bring it back he reads every time it's because the i just played
dead rising one i had to read them all come on hurry up read movie posters do people like us you
killed chuck at least give us this well thanks for the spoiler i appreciate the spoiler
i wonder what that mission is no it has nothing to do with the other protagonist
where is it people like us i'm gonna save the game and if i have time to do it we'll see
boilers for infinity war read posters all right i'm gonna i'm gonna save the game in the bathroom
this is important jeremy take erotica pictures it's important go talk to stacy i need to actually
oh there's a full orange juice in here okay cool um take a picture of somebody who should i take a
picture of where are they in here it's important to me oh i don't know where she is oh there we go
frank we've got to find out who's framing cure and we will frank west doesn't know how to give
up on a story okay i'm gonna go oh give me this instead of um the wine i still want this so now
it's that and what was it and it's spray paint i don't have spray paint shit dude i'm already in
the red i'm just gonna have to do the case yeah i mean he should i got a full like day to do this
don't i is there any spray paint in here yeah i have like a whole day so i'm just gonna go
out here and explore for a little bit i want to try to get spray paint go get zone bricks yeah i
need to this paint right there all right let me uh replace the hell do i want to replace alcohol
just drink it okay let's go make this
i swear to god okay this uh so much back seating well i already we already talked about it this is
what happens when you play like a beloved 10 to 15 year old game right all right i got a
an air horn now this thing's stupid already at 87 i'm gonna hold on to this though i feel like i'm
gonna need this it's just uh grind i see two guys we got two's company where they're right here
people he's it's right here let's see if i can do them both it's saved right before this anyways
he wants money you get it from me there's no time it's all right this will be around for
zom i need zombrex where did that come from oh it's you
the kidney shot almost level seven flashlight flashlight stop pushing this
okay flashlight got it that didn't even do anything it doesn't do anything all right i have a flashlight
now uh somebody said i can do i can combine this with wasting time well i i'm not gonna be able to
do the people like us i've come to the conclusion basketball urgent frank can you come back to the
security room see i gotta go all right yeah this this one these will be around for a little while
security guards nightstick home run i'm playing porn why do i look like a gta online character
uh well it's because i wait no i can't do it that's a good answer um well because i haven't
gotten any i didn't done any other clothes i'm up against the clock i've got to get out there and
i've got to make shit happen which game do i like better um that's not a fair question i don't
think not yet man ask ask me like in another couple hours ask me what about my angriest
yeah we'll see what's going on i'm pretty sure i saw somebody dragging a girl into the washroom
over here oh yeah well maybe if we watch these monitors for a minute what the hell that's the
guy i saw taking money from tk oh no not him he's 240p you guys have noticed that security cameras
are like company computers i'll get your office building that guy was a new recruit hear me out i
never saw him before there are office buildings that are still on vista and xp and shit of course
why are security cameras still on cell phone camera from like 2004 oh yeah it's because
it's cheap but you think the thing the thing to identify people coming into your store
and potentially stealing something or hurting somebody or don't you think you want to be able
to have a good image of that person why have something that like like smearing peanut butter
on the lens it takes up hard drive space you don't have to have like super hd 4k resolution
frank said slime them what older systems have less vulnerability really all right here we go
case two two a familiar face i got lots of time now i need to go here we have a game plan who said
that somebody just said that i just read that all right let's start i need zombrex otherwise
i'm dead so let's start back here at art appreciation and then we're gonna go to his company
and then people like us all right let's save the game i know i just did and everyone's gonna
be like you just did this i know and look at movie posters i will and get gems all right
any other requests anybody want what do you want you want you want a large
with two splendor okay what about what about you you want a just you just want a small black
ice coffee okay good anybody else want anything i can make another one yeah i'll make another one
just in case i'm gonna need it
this shit is so loud i have to turn it off okay fmv pre-rendered cutscenes
yeah okay anything else i need gems somebody said get gems get gems get gems
hold on let's rock okay get gems get gems get rid of this i've got good weapons
now i don't want case two two to just go all the way down to yellow because that's how you get
screwed universe of optics are we looking for a gem store on the way wait oh yeah no i hate this
i've seen like a video where does somebody have this on i can't work this is your video
points still standing it's a pretty nice dodge okay we got i need money i have to start i can't
believe what this all went so so wrong was when i gave that guy 25 000 dollars
that ruined the whole place and he died 10 000 bucks that's kind of crazy what have i got the
shoes are you chasing me no shoes i can't take what are these no how did you even get it in here
what a throw leave me alone die already speed increase nice thank god and i got a new skill
the money hacker get money hacker get money hacker snapshot hold right trigger press right bumper
hold right what was it give me the hacker flashlight and computer case that is gone
immediately that does not have any durability at all okay i didn't know it was like that crazy
it hacks money all right okay let's keep i want that head this bathroom right here let's save it
uh anything in there no he's a funny user it's a maintenance wrench and then what else is in here
oh shit can they come in here is this a safe spot am i safe in here okay drill and
and machete frank you better get to public gold why did i not hit him then i just
killed him i just killed him give me the jesus christ i just exploded this guy's brain
all right give me the broom what are you fucking doing in here jeez no i want to pick up the one
that's on the ground sir okay cool i'm ready and i want my uh bat back too this thing's awesome
it has a pretty long line but but this thing is incredible no i don't want to both break anyways
let's go it's me in my wheelchair that's right
art appreciation okay checkpoint reached looking for somebody in here over this way art is somebody
freaking out over here right this is fish oh shit there's a key where are these security boxes too
i need to get those 800 bucks all right i need 50 000 for that zombrex is there saving here
where's the last time i saved it all right right i'm gonna save it through here this is the right
way right is it no is the same point in here it's down no it's not i can't even go in here
god damn it it's locked it does you're right chainsaw you never know there could be something
wild back here okay i've got how much healing do i have i probably have one decent hero
playing why are you not playing the slot machine because i i'm trying to get stuff done
i don't want to run out of time just when i put an 800 put in 100 and i got 800 back
you get extra money 27 000
is it like a super jackpot the money booth shit you're right no no time i want to clean some of
these things up all right this isn't yellow let's get this done all the way down here
all right now if you look at the poster right car shop upstairs art appreciation
so somebody talk chris's fine foods i gotta remember that quick enough
that guy's got a money machine thing he's got a money hacker give me that thing
things seem really slow all right money machine i don't what do i need this flashlight for
be done what i have for a good weapon not really anything i gotta keep the crowbar
things but that thing's gonna break gun gun instead of um gems gems gems gems gems
give me them can i just break them okay gems all right i'm ready i don't have a weapon
just eat the fish let's go gems and flashlight now i need a maintenance room there's one uh across
from the across street over there i'm gonna do this first meat on bone yeah this is a really
shitty weapon um poster
that noise okay let me just do this pretty good bait here we go gems flashlight let's take a look
if this is not one of the best items in the whole game i'm gonna be really upset
the amount of times that i looked over it and saw in all capitals gems and flashlight
i mean it's cool it's pretty cool all right newspaper and what whiskey whiskey and lawnmower
this is a mall top it makes a super whiskey yes firehands okay two by four and oh i can do this
oh yeah oh what about the money machine all right fuck the gun take the port-a-potty let's go
i need a safe point it's across the way okay i i know what i'm doing
this is exactly what a lawnmower sounds like i feel like somebody's actually
going to the safe point save it here uh we'll take slot power attack power attack
attack power attack holy shit that's 250p all right let's keep going okay online let's work with
failure all right hey don't worry about it up here randolph you and me look at you all right
we're looking at this and i'd like to work this my first painting to make sorry about that it's
not safe up here follow me no no you don't understand it's not worth getting on such a
failure if no one buys it then i'll die with my dreams if i lose another 10 20k right now
two thousand bucks that's how much my dreams cost take it or leave it please take it thank you near
shoe for the five subs he's just gonna end up dying it's all yours you made my dreams come true
horror that's a nice touch i like that wait i gotta get you in the photo
all right here you want to take the lawnmower what can you take you want the lightsaber
how would you not want a lightsaber what's wrong with you
is this a joke there take a vase weirdo oh painting wait make him use his own painting
smash it over his head here you take the painting not fuck your painting okay so i have you now
let's go to company i need zombrex investigate the laughing guys does anybody have zombrex
dead in 12 10 hours all right let's go you guys can't hear me it's okay this thing's about
to be done in a second anyway all right looters why would i throw the why would i holy shit his
brain exploded this thing's great okay i i i i agree it's very good all right let's do it
go hustle how you doing on hell you all right okay we're good check point reached
oh shit okay i did the laser sword
where is this guy watch your head
all right you need to drink this drink it drink it drink it drink oh my god
like i wait i can't kick i need to give him food if the back swing is he's gonna die
the jump kick doesn't do a jump kick you swing the sword follow me this way
keep up let's move stay stay stay stay stay stay i'll get you some food i'll find something
let's move treasure chest right here uh who cares you need this gun take this gun gun gun gun
just take it just take take down take the gun take it take it take take take take
i need food
this thing's almost broken um
what is in here food come on yep get in here drink until there's nothing else here
here drink another cocktail take another one give him the lizard mask take this wine you need to heal
what are you done he needs to be healed you don't understand okay i have enough i'm gonna take
what the hell is going on here with this weird clan music all right you ready
i need to give him a weapon he's so i have to carry him he's so slow all right let's go let's
go let's go let's go we don't have much time broken oh shit come back in here i need a i need
all right oh shit there's a full lobster in here all right we'll need that later
wait take this bucket okay let's do it all right where is this person straight and then right and
then people like us is right there but once i need zombrex how am i ever gonna do anything
i just want to throw that get that back get that back free zombrex that i would wear this
free zombrex in there well hold on i can let me save i'm gonna go save it and do this uh mission
i need to find zone bricks okay there the actual mission is straight to the right i'm gonna go to
the safe point funny alien mask funny alien mask no no don't do it it's not even that funny
vending machine what's this do what the hell was that no stop i want to pick it up
is it a grenade he thinks it's funny all right no time hey i'm waiting on you
you safe point straight ahead straight up no you can make it stop swinging stop swinging and run
run hey wait have some have a was it a sandwich no i have a lobster you need a lobster in a minute
case two two all right i'm starting to hit that moment where i need to uh
hey i'm waiting on you i'm at that moment where i gotta start to think about doing the actual case
now accomplish nothing i've got randolph come on speed it up that the whole point was to go get
randolph let's hustle it up let's see what happens here there's plenty of food right here we're
just get over here and we need this up here whoa there's a broadsword up here this is
there's a shield and shit here eat eat something we're gonna eat it's my lobster give me your money
i'm just gonna start it again germa why i hit him with a woogie sword in the back
and he's defected which one is this one right day two is in red error day one is this one right is
this one right which one is it total pp it's this one right here level six this one top one
okay don't be such a fucking asshole we're trying to do this together i'm safe scumming for randolph
but not for the tiger i it took i had one health during that tiger part i was fucked during the
tiger part come on speed it up okay don't have repeat what just happened give me no give me the
broadsword well how did so many end up holding it he's not gonna defect i need to get rid of
just eat the lobster randolph just take it it's yours get in the bathroom get in the bathroom
is is unrediculous get this is not even the bathroom just take the lobster and eat it
eat this okay you good follow me quick i don't care if you don't have an item now
no i gotta eat popcorn and shit
go no way are you funnier i've been telling jokes for a long time yeah i can tell you until you're
so old a couple of joke tellers whoa a living person he must not have heard you said maybe
you could settle this randolph get in here leave it alone okay who have to decide who's funnier
i could see two construction workers trapped at the work site in the south plaza
doesn't look good you better hurry hey buddy can you help us out here yeah just follow me i can get
us to safety hold your horses there sport you have to settle an argument first okay what's the
argument let them explain our little game first come on it will be worth it normally i make a
living doing just that but i'm serious me and my friend here in town for the fortune city comedy
festival go on we were both up for the committee of the year but these zombies stole the show and
they're one hard act to follow we will each tell you our best joke and you give the trophy
on the counter to the who you think is funnier okay so i have to decide who's funnier all right
you walter go first what does a vegan zombie eat grains get it grains you automatically lose
if you're a tasteful man like myself and you're sick and tired of old comedians trying to be
funny and just ending up pathetic it's just sad allow me to lay down some fresh lines from the
new hotness of comedy okay what do sloppy zombies get on their clothes when they eat
stains oh stains oh no this is this is really that's actually that's way funnier
don't cry to your wife about this oh tell her i said thanks wait walter doesn't join
you just had to encourage him didn't you oh ranged attack increased new skill move all right we need
to get you guys weapons here can you handle spear okay good um i i'm gonna let you keep that
trophy what else we got uh yeah at least you'll be do something here okay music discs what else
we got a stick pony can i actually run with this on in fact you'll be more useful this
shooter let's hustle it up okay you guys ready let's go find zombrex i gotta find this is the
case i'm gonna bang a right save the game and then i'm just gonna go for the case yep bring
them back first oh that's all the way back here get these people back first look how that's so far
away i mean let me save it right here and i'll figure it out
at least enough to start it it's already green i mean it's already yellow
hurry it up this is not the bathroom move it what the hell is the bathroom it is the bathroom
oh yeah keep up where's the bathroom and this is on brick
this way this is on bricks back here where climb can i climb up i have to make this jump
oh this way
um spotlight am i wasting time right now this is a lie yeah it's a big
oh give me a fucking break good wait i wasted a full like one full minute
do you see my predicament though for every for every like 100 people that say climb the
zombrex up there there's another like group of people that are also doing that about
combine the flashlight and the gems this way let's move so some of them are real
uh i'm gonna do another slot just in case something horrible happens
all right let's do the case case is all the way over there it shouldn't be i say not that far
let's hustle it up
what is going on over here randolph pretzel pretzel no oh how did he get out
go this way follow me this way follow me this way go
randolph you're doing a great job standing still very good job
nobody's done i'm just trying to see there's a food place you guys are all right food
is it food right here bagels bagged damn it just do it
hurry this way is growing soon will change
god hey you uh it wasn't supposed to go down like that sure i see how radical it is
now my life has meaning again are we fighting in the bathroom it's perfect this way
so i'm on board now it's the only way man what about tk i'm a soldier
so was you that started the outbreak first it was horrible the zombies the zombies we've been
trying to save killing people eating people but then i saw how brilliant the plan is it's
the best way to end the oppression it's so radical it's beautiful man there's a person back there
don't worry don't worry zoomer santa's got this
hey all right all right boys sick of good good picture randolph's gonna die
wait wait wait just everybody just swarm watch out watch out what is he doing
okay so what did we learn
that i need to drop them off first because they just bait he really is shaggy okay this is we're
here i got enough time to he's not even using 10 of his power so on the way back
okay there's still a little bit of time and how are we doing on food people good
what's the fastest way for me to get back and can i grab anybody on the way back all right so it
looks like this in industrial fashion i don't think i can do this i think i just have to go back
so far away look at this across the whole damn game all right um the fastest way is to just go
through just bang a left and just go across through the uh fortune park let's go everybody
has a weapon let's go let's just try to make it happen just stick together stick on stay on the
walls just hang onto the walls here good broadsword another one lucky
give it up bang what the hell are we going i gotta bang left why is it trying to get
me to go this way i gotta go left good right everyone's here all right i'm gonna take a
hot dog anybody want hot dogs yeah heal up hot dogs there's like four of them one of them's green
all right randolph hot dog take an extra hot dog for the road
throw it up is he still puking it was poisoned it was spoiled oh okay that makes sense
this is dangerous we're gonna stay on a wall
all right all right all right all right over here oh shit walter you all right okay you good
shit take a hot dog quick i ate it go go go go go go everything's fine go go go go go go go
who needs it who needs it take it no thanks you're gonna keep your trophy are you dumb oh no
quick no no no no no okay wait this hunt this is chef this is chef symbol chef symbol chef
symbol chef symbol right here there's nothing in there okay where are we oh fuck i gotta go
let we gotta go straight and left there's no fucking way to get through this shit
get a weapon it's too late but get off me oh keep going keep going keep going it's fine
i'm waiting on you keep up move it let's move the door was right there i can't fuck it i just
was too panicking because everyone was surrounded i wish i could get a fucking car and there's a
snack machine right here this way no not you i want to give it to royce just fucking kill me
this time i'm gonna make sure i have two weapons you gotta bring these guys all the way back
my favorite part about this game is when i'm trying to die nothing happens look at walter it
just took him so long to die but if i was actually playing this game we're all dead instantly why
does it always happen like that okay so just make them wait make them wait if i leave them here
they're not gonna come with me all right you you won't put the trophy down you've got that
that thing's stupid here take take the broadsword so it doesn't break there's another broadsword
coming up take the broadsword get rid of this stupid thing okay get rid of this too what a waste
i need a weapon i need a what do you have a spear just here i'll trade you alcohol for a spear
i'm not gonna listen okay let's see if i need to get a weapon there is the the stage is right here
which is the broadsword get this shit quick get them both keep going before we get overwhelmed
move move move all right now back here let's do it so now he's gonna go turn right and go straight
just keep running let's go come on speed it up move it keep up pretty good spot
this way not a whole lot of zombies right here oh come on how the fuck did you get grabbed
like how and how did you get out oh my god what a joke anybody want a fucking hot dog
remember this no give me the spear hit the spear
why are you over here why did you go this way oh he won't put it down he won't put the
fucking trophy down which item am i gonna pick on the ground in the thousand items that i put on
there he's already dead at this point i don't give a shit when randolph is too far away
okay why do i have to go across the whole fucking game why and it's broken oh this is a disaster
this is a trillion zombies fire bomb i
all right so half the comments say just run the other half say
stop running fight what get in the car get in the car get in the back get in the car
he's alive how the fuck are you alive go over there how are you alive there's no way you're alive
man there's no way you gotta be fucking kidding me i can't fucking believe it are you serious
so you're telling me that if i just run like this and just don't stop they'll find a way to go
through the zombies but that doesn't make any sense because sometimes they do get caught
they just break free it's not like the first game
i can't believe it i can't believe it you just have to run and don't look at them
and they'll make it through thank you man he won the comedy trophy but he didn't win his life
okay that's pretty awesome all right i gotta do this case i gotta save the game do the case
i'm like trying to like keep up with them and give them weapons no just walk forward
family kidneys thanks for the 5 000 bits thank you they say hey just got my first paycheck
wanted to get back after all the years uh years of later you've given me and many uh laughter
laughter okay so much laughter you give me so many others love you germa hart thanks a lot
first paycheck hope it was a big one wait no i don't have time for this i have to go and i
told you i didn't want this to fucking happen and it's gonna happen and now i'm gonna get
soft-locked that's what's gonna happen isn't it i'm gonna get soft-locked on two case like two three
right this is gonna fucking happen magazine oh it's the books from the first one okay
we'll lower the cost of items in the pawn shop by 10 okay i still need some bricks oh my god
oh my god okay um hope i don't get soft-locked so we gotta go all the way down here this is just
done so wrong i can go to the shop okay yeah it's 50 000 right to get a wheelchair and just run
price increases each time you buy it get on it what am i stuck for i this is a boss
um this is the boss this is the guy i i need to save it now what why is this happening
hey chill okay sorry didn't know it was yours it's a nice bike though
they just run out of time to animate the person on his back was a doll one of those crazies
i just can't trust people anymore i've been dealing with not bars all day long these zombies
they're annoying sure but they're easy he's gonna get bit kind of kind of funny real threat is the
an outbreak like this does things to mid violence the death seeing loved ones die
change it makes people snap just like a really cool character i think i connect with this character
more than frank was together really should have played the first second one instead anything
listen to the safe house katie needs her zombrex every 24 hours you do
hey baby oh your daughter do you know what would happen if she didn't get her zombrex every day
you never let that happen we still have some time katie i'll find some if it kills me look
let's get you and your daughter back to the safe house so don't touch my daughter
you're just one of those not bars you just want to hurt from getting your
bumblebee your messes with my kid i don't think i'm the crazy one here i don't have time for this
i don't have time for this oh shit this is not good i have to leave all right it's a
bye oh a key
look at this i don't have any weapons i know time anymore is gonna happen
like an hour ago i even said i was like i don't want this shit happen again and here we are
i need an axe give me this tomahawk i just have to win
okay you can get hit by that thankfully didn't do very much damage just win okay i'm gonna try
to just win but that's just a bottle of alcohol oh what is it okay what does he do here
here
no so i have day two at 326 i have day two at 208 i just tell your survivors to stand outside
like outside of here you mean no but i still have to win all right let's go
this thing's broken this thing is stupid this thing's worthless i got the money that's the
ball i had a money come with me guys just go remember what everybody told me they said you
don't even have to look at them who cares they'll just make it that's what they told me that's what
they told me except when your hitbox is five times bigger than you want okay now we're just
gonna go we're doing case two two follow the arrow hey keep up i was calling you hurry this way
but i need food though i have to get like the pretzel i have to eat a pretzel and then eat i
have to eat a hot dog and take pretzel no it's not my mother my mother has a different ringtone goes
so i go oh fuck that's my mother i didn't get the heels hey i'm waiting i need fucking heels
i need heels i need food did i walk by it where's the food there's no food anywhere
just defend that area here we go okay eat got a pretzel got a pretzel all right you guys stay
right here no right there so you don't get put in the cut scene okay i'm going why am i doing
forward at fucking r2s try to get the backstab on me it's not gonna happen burger boy technique
make them wait outside make them wait outside make them wait outside make them wait outside
wait are they gonna why are they coming in wait what are you guys doing here you're not supposed
to be part of this all right kill him i need to heal i have to heal i have to heal they're blocking
me in make them wait outside so they just die out there and then call them in and then get body
blocked and then hit your face on the stall and break your neck and die have him go in the other
bathroom oh for the love of god okay let's go just run i'm gonna just run i need to pick up the two
i'm gonna pick up the broadsword and the training sword put them both there's a bavarian pretzel
outside i'm gonna drink the whiskey let's go same thing like i did here okay now we go this
way get the bavarian pretzel we're gonna save in the women's bathroom that's so stupid drink
this get pretzel just ready ready drink it pretzel all right come on i got what i need
women's bathroom there's no safe point in the women's bathroom but just stay in here
hide in the women's bathroom i'll be back get a two by four instead of the link sword stay there
damn it what are you doing in here what are you doing why are you in here get out of here kill him
oh my chest i pressed y i must have matched
no oh he did it i was the guy on screen that was behind him by the way
urgent what i mean urgent they're all cheering like they did something
all right what have i saved this so i don't get soft-locked ever again
i was gonna go far back so like eight so yeah one they saved you they did not do anything of the
sort yeah okay now i want to give um now we just have to make it out of here save the game i
already just did okay save it again okay we need to find an atm you guys all have stuff
you guys all have weapons good so let's go ahead i got a lot of time to do this one so
fellas what do you say we save somebody else
keep up go i need to get an atm oh shit there's money over here money case oh my god why was
there a money case in fact you know what here's a heel who needs this you do take this
i tried to take a fucking photo oh my god it's not the same as the first game i've got the burn to
my brain it's right trigger and then right bumper that was a loud scream okay
um industrial fashion people like us i'm gonna end up having to do this again
can i avoid this where's the pawn shop is there a pawn shop close there's one right here is anyone
closer than that doesn't look like it i guess i could go up this way right here and then do this
i hope we don't run into whatever his name is there chuck all right use the technique
turn it off hey remember the members is the run strategy remember the run strategy move it
can we ride this royce is dead he didn't even get hit by it get away
okay
i need that photo does anybody care if uh if royce is dead i need that photo
same timeline so it doesn't matter let's go walter we gotta go
come on walter's too far away what damn it walter follow me okay let's fucking just
i gotta get out of this oh my god chuck just run run run run run run run run i'm just bringing
fuck it run just run shit
we lose that photo but just you can take a screenshot of it i might be able to get all
three of them to stand there where the hell was it which one was it two one all right everyone's
spine let's go i'm just gonna try to run and just forget it i gotta bring these guys back
they're just dead they're just dead meat they actually are bring them back make sure get the
money get the money briefcase make it back hey i'm waiting on you good okay let's hustle it up
what he got hit by it when oh no he's on the roof
okay this is the one shit
walter just got hit by it on his own this way let's go well it's this one keep getting hit by it
why are you hitting each other walter hurry up walter walter oh you idiot okay move please
all right now we'll make it back because i'm just gonna skip oh how am i gonna do this
i have to i can we what if we go to the left will it trigger the cutscene still
cutscene hasn't triggered what randolph why is randolph getting killed okay almost there
why don't i heal them you guys are contradicting yourselves every 10 seconds
why are you not stopping and healing them run run quick why did walter just take 5 000 points
of damage he took him into a swarm of zombies i thought that okay that's they're doing something
funny but it's i don't have time that i could keep going with 5 000 individuals that don't know how
to play games what are you talking this is for me not for them let's move keep up speed it up
who did we lose whatever i ain't going back let's hustle it up spot anything frank it looks like
there's someone cooking at kuchina danachi in the food court you better check it out you made it
dead at the finish line quick royce lives got you back in one piece so two zombies walking into a
bar you haven't heard this one have you all right 40 000 pp i would have gotten more but
i had to walk these idiots across the whole damn game let me save i had two people last time
although hold on let me be fair here for a second i'm gonna be really fair because i'm being very
unfair i tried to make them get hit by the pirate ship like five to ten times each this is very
unfair so that's a completely incorrect statement what i just said like i trying to get a photo of
them dying so i killed them okay um i'm accepting my my fault there and the picture wasn't even very
we're gonna go right in the middle just in case i get sad was the uh the picture viewer case file
no the other one was so much better unfortunately it was so good oh well you can pull it from the
stream yeah all right let me look at my combo cards okay machine gun and wheelchair
so case three one has a lot of time i need the zombrex pawn shop then there's also industrial
fashion which that's kind of far away tastes like chicken i gotta get a better view of this let me
let me get the zombrex first and put a waypoint checking moves yeah okay snapshot hold take a
picture with your new buddy zombies hold right trigger and press right bumper so is that a selfie
while the camera is out grab the head of a zombie and smash it into the floor
otis would hate to have to clean this up hold the right trigger and press b
so wait it's i can't do it in here
i guess hey rare pepe body lotion thank you for the five subs all right let's get the map out
uh i want to zoom this out we need to go here no pawn shop there's a pawn shop
like this closest one probably right here yeah it's probably the closest one
let's go that axe isn't there orange juice and shit yeah there is change outfit um i'm not sure
i can i do have these moon shoes on so i agree it does look pretty stupid all right i got
let's go oh second floor right here okay let's move when do we get a health upgrade
would you care what someone did i have literally i'm not going to read the rest of that
well i'll read the second part what would somebody would do with your body in general after you're
gone like organ stuff yeah if i like died and they like somebody needed my liver then fucking
take it i gotta be dead though you get it when i was like alive
oh okay i have fifty seven thousand dollars i also need to find an atm
it's up i'm here to buy that zombrex it's a lot of money well there goes my retirement fund
um what the fuck is going on what is happening to me are they killing me
where am i i'm not in the vent there's just bombs being thrown
oh
give me a weapon give me a fucking weapon can i take a picture
what who is taking this photo wait wait wait wait don't kill me no i'm trying to get the
camera in the face the other way what do i do now take a picture of my own ass
oh zoom in i can't zoom in
um i'm outside no i'm not turn left left some more left turn left a little bit more i'm almost
outside i'm outside i think i just jumped off the balcony oh do i have a checkpoint after buying
the zombrex you didn't even get it yeah i did it's okay let's try this again so i'm trying to think
of how that may have i'm trying to think how that may have happened and the one thing i can think of
is when i bought the zombrex at the same exact time somebody tried to grab me and the game
freaked out one of those thieves tried to grab me right because that's what happens
and see what happens if we do this again because it was immediately right when i pressed the button
snacks all right up the stairs maybe it probably put me on the table that the zombrex is on
that's also another good theory atms here we go all right let's hope this doesn't happen again
because i'm about to get money out of the atm 40 grand okay this time here we are just wait a
second okay here he comes he made it in here much faster battle axe he's got one of those
devices too another one i'll take it um i how many how many he's getting
really he was these three
am i really that far away
so um
that's what this does items you fucking asshole what did he take oh god i just want to buy the
zombrex leave me alone hi oh no what is going on with this and i can't i can't change any
way weapons or anything go in the vent try a selfie so it's right holding right trigger and
then right bumper say before buying go to the other store how do you do a selfie is it left
trigger right trigger right no it's right trigger right bumper right well time to die again um do
i have it do i have doing i don't have the zombrex it's just on the ground there it is
is um i'm afraid to buy anything else the sports car keys a million dollars
should i get a paddle axe serve bot mask no like this is so bugged i gotta get out of this
what time is it right now it's 5 a.m all right industrial fashion i might have time to do this
game yeah that's also part of the plan that's also part of the plan atm show this evil people
bunch more money i could buy another one all right well not yet see if i can do this
i gotta save the game too let me eat some shit all right save game we're gonna go down
and then there's a save behind us
okay save the game uh i'm gonna end up triggering the cutscene i don't want to fight him right now
i'm gonna lose i mean should i just fight him how do i i don't have anything i got nothing to
fight him with though i have money makers broken axe not with this attitude
well not with any attitude don't drink that orange juice whatever you do this is bad
just give me the knife give me the snacks it's an apple right here anyways
move what the hell is this leaves lawn dart well don't remind me never pick that up ever again
well i'm gonna have to beat him with a knife this ain't gonna this is not gonna happen
no way i'm gonna be able to do this there's a maintenance firm right in front of me
i'm i know i'm talking like it's got out of the dentist i don't know why i'm doing
then there's a safe point to it is it possible if i make the weed whacker in his weed whack him
maybe no don't drink the weed whacker okay so give me uh give me this right here okay chair
and do we have any guns or anything chair and knife chair and board chair and battery yep
push electric chair are we actually gonna try are we gonna do this
chef knife and okay let me save the game i feel like this is gonna be bad for me holy
fuck okay pick it up all right uh save the game with the electric chair
let me see if i can kill him with the chair all right let's go where is he all right let's do it
three two one action i don't get what happened he's got shit on the on his bike is it over there
where is it oh it's right there don't even do it don't even need to do it he's stuck he's stuck
what wait i just have to get behind him just get behind him okay ready surround him oh come on
it's okay he's like an imbecile oh no i'm not dumb in the tree in between the tree
get stuck in the tree i gotta get stuck in the tree i need a better weapon give me the weed whacker
a plant
look at him he's so glitched out i can't be getting close to him whoa do the weed whacker
heal he's gonna get stuck right here i got stuck i got stuck right here i got stuck right here
okay left your chair not gonna work i'm putting the weed knives on
this book i'm gonna have shit back here this thing this thing doesn't work
i'm going to lock him in that corner where the tree is and then just we'd whack the fuck out of
him or lawnmower no weed whack him let's go and give me a two by four fun to go over here
pulls this way wait can i get in the car hold on a second why is it driving why is the car driving
that should not be happening all right i got a bigger car than him this might actually work
out pretty well all right where is he whatever okay where's the weed whacker where's the weed
whacker where's the weed whacker all right let's do it here's my spot bring him over here bait him
into the tree get him stuck and then weed whacker there he is he has a lot of health oh fuck is it
gone what about the weed whacker can you break it turns off when you drop it but what it's just
dude that's a lot of damage just hold it heal i don't have any orange juice on the ground
heal i don't have any heals okay weed whacker sucks too okay um new strategy i think
um new strategy is uh who cares combine two wheelchairs give me this rake
rake and battery electric rake it's a it's a little stabbing motion this might actually be
pretty good i just can't put it down just don't let it go let's see if i can do it go ahead cut
scene okay okay i never put it down except for when you have to lock him into the wall
oh yeah baby oh yeah baby oh yeah baby yeah okay hold on hold on okay all right don't get cocky
all right just just hit him i can't get too close or he explodes on me and there's a cooldown
to cool down on how many times you can have these guys do i get the bike the rake is insane by the
way katie katie katie okay you're safe now i can't imagine what i would do if anything
that guy was a few screws short of a workbench it's not canon don't worry guys i know everyone's
peke sad ice is nuts new skill move bike trailer key acquired new combo card molotov whiskey in a
newspaper all right i got the bike i got i can use a bike bike trailer all right what time is it
6 30 that's kind of cool all right let me uh actually have to hold on to this
so uh i'm gonna need zombrex one spit what else can i do i need to save it first of all
go back to the maintenance shed and i also i'm going to go to the bathroom
i'm gonna take a pee i'm gonna grab a water i'll be back in two three minutes i came back and
looked at chat at the perfect time oh you guys are fucking hilarious somebody said this is what
it sounds like when 500 people are sleeping at the same time in the same like huge room
that's really funny and we're back so what did i want to do i wanted to
have the game saved let's go back and just make sure i got cool weapons what's this i gotta start
three let me look at the cases because i might be in trouble all right there's two parts to case
three so i've got to get started i'm good to go uh chef's knife now let's let's move
i got the electric chair oh but i yeah i need it i gotta dump it i've got to dump it i've got to
use it all right i'm gonna how far away is once bitten not that far that's right am i shocking
this guy oh yeah absolutely it's kind of very very very loud let me fix that better
all right it's done atm atm there they are atm 129 000 all right hopefully i don't need any
weapons for this rocket fireworks cool what do these do holy shit i gotta take the zombrex
we're good here just get started what's this fortune
finally some good fucking food all right get away from me what just happened
i want to do this like two more times
job felines or eat meat playing in the sand can unearth wonderful treasures okay any others
all right there's probably this one for five grand definitely the prestige is growing i see good
things ahead of you 5000 anymore there's another one that's a lot of money people you help in life
can help you in return ask them and dark times are quite hard as required heroes show the way
you look always borrow money from a pessimist he won't expect it back when was the last time
i saved the game i i was assuming i was gonna get like 50 000 p or something i saved it okay
let's see what the next one is you're prestigious and your actions great and small all right that's
a lot but how much was the next one 50 000 that's not worth doing somebody kill me
okay uh checkpoint i saved um 638 checkpoint is checkpoint further in i don't know no it's
not okay we're good uh what happened to where's the where's it wasn't it just right here didn't i
make something just keep the rake uh can i do like battery and knife i guess i'm just gonna
keep it i'll keep the rake two by four on lawnmower yeah i've already seen what it does
let's go i'll just keep the rake it probably gets a good money farm
well now it's actually all right let's go let's jump into this guy's arm like this motherfucker
was waiting for me he was waiting for me to jump into him okay get out of the way all right take
the zombricks all right atms uh i wanted to go oh fuck i was gonna do this first
shit i thought it was already on it but i had to go back and save it um shit shit kill me kill me
yeah i wanted i i took too much damage it wasn't selected on my watch because i had to go back
okay so once bitten help the wounded man pub of gold a bleeding man has managed to find temporary
safety in pub o gold in the silver strip that's where we're going i'm gonna go there fast i know
people gonna say but what about up up up up up up silver strip once bitten where are you
i think i passed an atm but there'll be others like right there what's the matter with this thing
i'll take a handgun
give give give give give money 129 000 very good i was gonna say very not good but very good
beer frank needs zombricks yes he does all right let's go i got a gun i'm just gonna bring this
to you guys hey hey buddy you okay no no dude not so much i just came here to party and look
what happened you're bleeding pretty bad if one of those things get you yeah man i'm i'm bit man
like a tasty morsel on the hose if i don't get zombrick soon game over it's game over for me
really why won't you die you've hit that so did you find some zombricks
yeah i did uh good luck okay i can't do that one i need zon zombricks to do that one
so there's tastes like chicken which is a little bit further up let's try this save him that's
asking a lot i know it's save the people save the people but that's asking a lot to give a zombrick
to somebody what do i get from that person 10 000 pp for bringing him back i don't whatever
that is that gets angering me all right what's the save point there's one
one kind of behind me over here that oh my god that's a big slot machine that's a huge one all
right i'll be back i can look at the money i got i gotta save the game uh it's uh okay just
i'm kind of freaking out right now i can't climb over that this hit my mouth
what the fuck was jesus what's that ufo spaceship toy
it's a maintenance room here jewels and oh hold on how about all right just get rid of this thing
leaf blower and jewels this is gonna be radical am i gonna make the pyromaniac update gun
he's gonna shoot bubbles right so is it oh fuck i didn't turn it on no put it down i don't know
it's dangerous uh okay what about knife okay i can do maltov slick okay i'll just take the
toy just in case i need it for anything you can't well let me just at least see what it does
i mean that's fun but who cares gem blower absolutely give me the uh zelda sword
okay what's up there oh shit what is this alien probe what is all this stuff
ray gun alien head this is actually hurt things i want alien probe drink the beer
see something hiding in the elevator in the hotel what happened to my leaf blower
where's my leaf blower all right i got it let's move okay i've got alien probe alien head
is there anything else in here there was like a katana right here
okay no i need two hands shit hold on um what do these stairs do i can combine the katana with
something all right i'm gonna replace the gun got it all right let's go alien head alien head
alien head what alien head and gems i don't have any gems
and it goes
i'm gonna say this in a different slot so i don't fuck myself uh 8 30 a.m let's do the one that's at
six face cam yeah sure all right i gotta go now see i told you i was gonna be in trouble if i
didn't do this now and that's far away far away incoming softlock i spent so long just sitting
down in my chair with my feet in the air was that zombie food okay if i thought you could eat them
i should be fine they're turning into super zombies now hey i remember you
oh i'll finish them up this still works it's not gonna work they're different
six of the same guy it's just a bug don't lose your head over it checkpoint
let's go let's go i feel like this main character gets batter every cut scene
can we talk about that for just a second though um back in 2006 2005 maybe when did like san
andres come up even red dead redemption 2 did not really do that good of a job what if it
happened to when you eat too much food you get fat or if you don't eat nothing you get really
skinny you did you that used to be able to you they lost that somewhere along the way
what game had that san andres like one of the greatest games ever
and then fable fable had this shit what is going on right now keep the grip man
how many bits will it take for me to do for you to do a full beatbox
that was pretty good i'm pretty good at it i think i'm just doing dug transitions all right
i kind of need food and i also need a save point this is so far away what on earth is going on here
save point please but fuck this is kind of all right fish i have to use it get all right all
right all right all right all right all right all right all right all right just get out of the
where are you even coming from just put i need to eat this fish
all right this the probe thing sucks give me my gem blower money case no just go it's blinking now
and whatever is in here i probably have to kill before the time runs out so just get over here
and use your gem shotgun i gotta just do it one and done i gotta win there's no save point right
i gotta just do it one and done just don't lose jared is dead who the hell is jared stop dropping
your oh what a pain in the ass whoops i let go of it don't let go of it what i did somebody
touched me okay just hold on to it i need to eat something too all right no save point here
fuck this is such cool shit over here i do have a fish all right here we go do i have enough i
don't know do i have enough time to even eat anything i'll try i'm drinking another thing
all right now i have the gem blower which is best item in the game which is what like this
what 10 20 000 people watching at least 10 000 people told me that this is the best item in the
game and i'm talking about over the course of the whole stream not like right now at least
people cycle in and out look over the course of the stream the 20 30 000 people have been here
already i got that in analytics why am i going underground god damn it this is bad every time
every single goddamn time whatever it is kill it instantly i'm gonna lose i don't have enough
time for this i'm gonna have to go back to say no this is not gonna work
this is a picture mission this is not even a boss fight whatever this is i'll need evidence
it's over
i needed to like five to ten full minutes to do this mission
how can i not jump maybe it'll just play out and you'll be done
hurry up you guys are so slow just get it into the truck so i could be done with this mission
that chunk photographer frank west set up my shit let's get out of here leave that
yeah please leave so then i can finish this mission case three two completed
case three four one begin yeah well uh i needed way more fucking time
oh i gotta go so far back three one three two nine a.m i gotta do day two at like 8 30 135 000
dollars so day two 8 30 let's see if i can get there from here i'm gonna lose all my cool weapons
all right no i got i got some time here just let's go hurry don't dick around yeah no dicking
around i'm just gonna get there and i should have enough time there's a pineapple up there i'm not
gonna touch it that's taking a lot of strength so it's not touching the suit that's right there
or playing that slot machine we're picking up that money all right let's go let's just go right in
the door and then run right back out i might need to get uh transportation too of course of course
like where's the fucking anti-grab goo just jump oh that's infuriating to me i am going to scream
i just i'm going to scream even with that much time that's like a full
i would be comfortable driving my car with that much gas in it like i can't even i can't get all
back there from here i definitely can let's go don't save it yeah actually save it no don't save
it we're good go ahead frank there's somebody
hey can i eat that zombie no i didn't even do it this time there was so much less time i
think by this point don't lose your head over it all right let's see just run quick if i see a
shopping cart it's game over for me i'm gonna win fuck it i don't care leave it leave the damn
thing i am not slower because of the leaf blower but it don't matter it don't matter because here
we go give me that give me that give me that give me that god frank why would you let it go
there's no reason to let this go this might be enough time i just need a heal my god that's so
i hit the lip stop no you ram over that damn thing you run over it you ram over it
i already have fucking no health for this shit get off of the wheelchair get off of the wheelchair
i want to go in i want to go in the door i can't believe i can't go oh god it's all right it's
okay well you hear my teeth you hear my teeth are just like squished together you're asking what
are you doing in here jeremy because i have to heal before i do this mission and i've got one
heal i'm gonna go over here and i'm gonna get these other ones there over here there's a whiskey
bottle i'm gonna drink it and now i've got full health let's get back to business please
okay thank you i still have plenty of time this is gonna be just fine oh the teeth are out tonight
i'm here with way more time i had what like half of this last time i think it's still doable
i just can't fuck up this train part and i don't have any saves so i can't mess it up and if i mess
it up again then well everyone happened last time when i was up against the clock and for the
motorcycle person i'm gonna have to have the optimal 100 impossible to fuck up route like
just for tomorrow okay go it's still kind of doable is there a shortcut in this game
or do they just want you to run straight that person is running on screen all right save time
oh shit which is the one this is the safe one this is six a.m this is nine a.m day two uh eight
thirty this is the safe one this is a really safe one it has to be three jeremy why can't you just
use the emulator to save um i'm emulating an xbox 360 controller not the game i wish i could
take a photo there is definitely a story eat this
okay just run in just run in oh fuck wow here we go yes no no give me the gun give me the gun
please
i have to tie every oh i wish was hold me oh i wish was hold me
oh my god give me a break i have to shoot him with the stupid
by the way why do i have this it's so bad it's a it's a nerf gun i thought it was an alien laser
no not the alien oh my god there's a million people holy shit what happened what is going on
in this game there's food it's food okay i'm going too fast the yellow squares are your health
this is all right i guess is that what it is i have absolutely no clue
no idea where's the food onion rings oh i don't want the jelly beans this is home alone
let's do my bullets snack on what is that why is this guy made out of wood okay did i do it
what the hell are you up to tk just enjoying the liberty frankie you paid cure to start the
outbreak didn't you need to dwell on the details when we all come out ahead come out dead you're
not gonna get a profit frank i'll put you back in the public eye don't i even get a call that
run a jump right between the guys it's okay i'm actually really glad that they disconnect there
because that means that the case is over if i had to actually climb up there and fight him
with four minutes to fail the case i'd be very very upset stacy same as ever are you all right
i've been better bastard tk tried to take me out the outbreaks yeah unfortunately looks like he's
up to something it's not over yet i didn't take a picture of bad ending you've got to stop that
is that real maintenance key thank god case done goodness september 26 at 1 p.m plenty of time
okay the next case is at 1 p.m so now i'm gonna hold on to the assault rifle
let's take a quick look at what's over here there's a maintenance room
it's already yellow i know that means i have to go do it all right what we got we got a saw
a saw gun plates there's a vacuum okay plates and saws no plates and shoot saws out
shoot plates out why would i do this this seems way worse than shooting saw blades
plates plate launcher vacuum cleaner saws gets his shark tank i have this thing that shoots
plates out this thing looks crazy the x i can't even read that um well i'm gonna keep the alien
head but this thing can go away this looks insane you can also do saw and saw blade yeah all right
cool i'm gonna use this yeah this is a blood-borne weapon that's why i'm using it what about sludge
hammer and blade no all right let's just do the case all right fastest way i got a maintenance
key now should i get in the car so will this direct me towards maintenance doors or no yes
so as you could be going this way so i need to get in that car all right i'm gonna store this
i don't think i can put the canine up i don't want to lose the
fucking saw it's okay i can walk you have the alien mask you're fine i don't want to use this
until i need it no it's right here i'm fine case 401 we're good there's a motorcycle up there too
oh that's so cool how many heels get rid of this thing okay um
um i need to pick up shit no i need the beer no i don't just drink it the rain is so
it's not where i want to go i want to go up to where is this taking me am i wasting time on
purpose no i'm just following the arrow uh i didn't want to get in the car i just made this thing
i didn't want to lose it in the car that's such a waste yeah i'm gonna make this cool new item
throw it on the ground behind you get in the car all right we're almost there and i would
not have found that would i so there it is don't need to go hunting for that maintenance room
let's test it on pretty damn good what is
okay um amplifier and escape pod no amplifier and an alien head
no what about the fire extinguisher oh shit yes the cryo pod um i have to carry
around i don't want to carry this around but this is like a giant look okay this is the firework
that you light at the very end this is the one that's going to be huge and awesome everyone's
going to sit there and watch for five straight minutes i'm not i have to bring this just use it
in as i know i'm going to go in a very very dense area i need the most amount of people to see what
i'm doing not here i'm gonna put it in display right over here let's see what happens okay now
what we don't get to see the fun thing because we don't we don't get to see how cool it was
what is it doing oh it just floats around oh what a waste i think this thing sucks
it doesn't even keep frozen what a disappointment that was i'm not buying that one again
let's go this way still got a way to go
uh spathem wait what is up here so this is the final area where is it briefcase pan
there's bacon in here very cool all right what about this toy helicopter this is cool all right
let's go back dude you found bacon epic dude bacon strips epic stop doing that
let's just do the next case or anything on the way to the next case
here comes the groom what time i'm going to be over there but for case four one by 1 p.m
um it ain't that far let's do it that's just when i have to be back there by
not i'm not burning that much time i just need to be back there by one
right that's this is not softlock yeah that's when the case becomes available not
cats around here what the fuck randall son randy father call me randy should have brought the
chainsaw thing get on with it do you oh he has a chainsaw
honey once didn't mean anything to me to remember to say i do i mean take away the gora
this is just bowser
marry me no i like that person you're trying to ruin the happiest day of our lives
oh my god he's running really fast wait i got a fucking gun
oh shit that didn't really work like i thought it was going to
fuck i'm gonna die oh my god he's so fast bacon where's he going where is he where is he
where is he where is he i don't know where he is i got a psycho mask what uh he runs a hundred miles
per hour and i unloaded the whole bag i i unloaded an entire assault rifle into him
oh
and he runs a thousand miles per hour let me try that again it'll be right here right
i wonder if i just try to headshot him it's great till he slows down he catches his breath and then
shoot him all right he needs to run out of breath and then i'm gonna go back does he have a breath
no
can i kill him with like a backstab shoot him in the pig shoot him in the pig dip
that's too late i don't have bullets out of breath yep here goes oh shit i didn't knock him down
that's not a very good picture oh no
no that's a good one oh i thought he was slowing down
i gotta take out the link sword oh shit oh shit
excuse me oops
oops greedy that was really greedy something sucks it's a toy i what am i gonna do punch him
i'm gonna hit him with a handbag it's over is he going oh you gotta be kidding me you gotta be
kidding me somebody said combo with it and yo yo yo that oh no urgent i'm a little busy i can't i'm
a little busy there's something going on right now why do i have the toy why do i have the toy
is there anything over there i could wait no it's too risky i have to drink that shit over there
i need to go get the drink ready slow down stop nope go get it what's over here cheeseburger
cheeseburger
oh my goodness i hit this is about to break too this is really bad what do i have to kill i what
i'm gonna kill him with the handbag is there any weapons back there it's a briefcase in the
briefcase i'm gonna go for the suitcase i'm gonna run out of time for this case run out of breath
motherfucker i should have just used that from the very beginning baby turn to a zombie
i pressed the confetti button okay and then a smiley face
thanks for doing that okay we gotta go come on gems i never thought i would i never thought i
would see that i know me there i can't okay come to save us with me let's go
let's go let's go are you injured eat this here eat this wait there's a chainsaw
keep up can i i gotta pick you up no not that not the chainsaw do i pick you up keep up
let's go she'll make it right oh i hope she does i hope she does it's not that far it's very far
oh oh no it's very far it's it's extraordinarily far i would have had plenty of time if i didn't try
to beat the guy to death with a sword come on danny go go go go go danny danny you'll make it
just break through i was told to run is this correct i was told just to keep running i hope
you're not lying to me i hope so if not then this is bad she's not gotten out yet
she's dead i was specifically told that they'll i would no i not only was i told i was screamed at
that they will get out and follow you no that was not one guy that was 5000 people oh shit unbelievable
oh i have to do the fight again is the checkpoint the fight because if it is i'm going to pick up
the fucking briefcase is it after it because this one is 1015 this is right after that is it the
checkpoint what will it be let me see if this is fighting the boss okay all right let's go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go get in the chair get in the chair danny get in the
chair
get her in the chair come here wait where are you going what's going on get in the chair all
right let's go what no get in the wheelchair please i had to stop to puke just puke and run man
even if it goes behind you it don't matter look at what people have covered in
danny we're almost there oh my god how did i run out of time i even it was slower okay what
oh check what we're doing i got it let's go
get in the chair what are you doing
fuck it display every machine your chances increase here eat this here take this quick use it
oh she's laughing she just
okay if if she actually gets in the chair and doesn't glitch out and fly across the screen
this will be work this would be fine there's still time we're close we're close we're close
we're close we're close we're close we're close there it is okay open the door open the door open
the door open the door open the door just stop open the door in in what how is it two people
sitting in it what you did it's going to happen it just has to be done right i don't have to
restart it i just have to get it to sit in the chair i need to chainsaw watch go
chainsaws already lit i'd why am i doing this okay get in the chair get in the chair get in get in
now if she should that's over i i'd answer you perfect okay it's definitely possible
but the zombies just complete fucking surround you if you stand still for five seconds
i'll try this one more time that's how the game works yeah but like they seem to come out of
fucking nowhere there's like four people in front of us and then all of a sudden i turn around and
there's 45 people around her get the fuck over here get over here stay with me look there's like
five people stay over here get over here get out of the chair yeah use the car i don't have the
keys to the car oh shit she made it she made it she made it she made it she made it if only i
had a device that made me go very fast we're gonna be right there you would be daddy you would be
i can see it i can see it i'm coming home i can see the end of the tunnel i can see it i can see
it i can see it i can see it daddy it's possible it's possible it's possible it's possible
let's go get over get in and in and in you're wasting time you've already wasted too much
time this can't break avoid zombies pretty damn good
oh god i can do it guys trust me just stick
with me on this just stick with me on this just stick with me on this it'll work it just has to
work it just has to happen drop this just a little tap get over here whack whack you're in
let's go you're not in you're in now don't let them come in don't let them go
okay good go that was not a whole lot of time lost it's got to be perfect don't bump into the
goddamn the first one is so good i just bumped into a fucking kiosk this is important this has
to play out correctly here we go ready check this out there's nobody around us stop open door get in
oh good i got i made you go farther come on daddy let's go you gotta be with me on this one
it was the beginning faster route than that you're right okay i think so foolish it's over it's over
already over it's over it's over it's over it's over it's over okay there's too many people
randomly spawned here let's reset it reset reset how do i just reset how do i just reset
i can't believe i drove into a goddamn kiosk i can't fucking believe it can't believe i drove
into a kiosk that was the one it's got to be a good scenario coming through the door give us
a good run here do the most direct route but then i break the thing like a bad zombie it's okay all
right let's go you got grabbed by the get it come on come on you stupid idiot what are you thinking
what's wrong with you why have you done this why did you do it like that direct even if we'd run
up a zombie's again i just don't like it it's gonna break but we're gonna have to run shit
i can't believe it it's over chainsaw broke the chair
let's move let's move good no why
no it's bad spawn bad spawn bad spawn that's too much time don't kill the first two zombies
they're the ones that grab good spawn really really good spawn i mean like spectacular spawn
get it this is the one one of these one two three four go out open door get it
get back in okay good job nice work good excellent okay good go go go go go go this is one
i tried to press it i tried to press it i tried to press it fuck okay everybody relax
bad spawn but it might work terrible spawn all around bad spawn the chair is looking
fucked up i know it's gonna break nobody at the door nobody at the door nobody at the door i'm
just gonna spam b when i get up there like get and whoa that was clean okay spam b spam b spam b
oh i got faster oh i got faster i got faster that time it's a checkpoint is fucked
go just run hold the button down i just gotta get in there
i just gotta get in there i just gotta get in there i just gotta press the button oh it's
oh no oh damn it i thought it was gonna just go into the cut scene when i went in there but
here i have to do this again give me some weapons no oh i'm so saddened by this news
give me a give me a we're just going up the door we're going to the first door kill the groom guy
like no the car keys a million dollars what about the zombrex fuck okay i gotta get the
zombrex i can do this where's the zombrex maybe if i got the motorcycle up here in the first place
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but i had the i had the fucking tuna can opener thing that i didn't want
to lose all right where is the zombrex i is it down here i think i have to pass it this way
right the brake i already saved enough time to make it into the in i i i already saved enough time
to make it in to the vent i went the wrong way okay it's all right just go this way
i'm just i'm like i'm so stressed i'm like ultra stressed what are these no no time oh
there's dynamite yeah i'll take them go wait what's in here oh i remember this remember how dumb
this was this thing sucked yeah fuck it this remember i wasted time there no not this time
no not this time not this time what's in there nothing okay better time good all right look i
got plenty of time we're good check it out i just need a couple more better weapons and we go
i do have a full i got a heal there is actually plenty of time now there is i am going to um
take a lead pipe i'm good and i'm gonna take another lead pipe because this sword is about
to break preparing this time this is the one here we go let's do it here comes the run
one checkpoint emmanuel is dead wasn't jared wow it's okay he's gonna stun lock me in the
all right i'm gonna dynamite him seems like a good play
could do a lot of damage when he slows down again this got destroyed what
you slow down here goes wait a minute i thought he slowed down right there
it's got slapped
come on fat guy this is going faster than it was before i gotta hold down i gotta hold down the
button again all i got is pipes they gotta work you gotta work come on why am i not getting a
slow down here oh my god i'm getting too cocky just one hit that's all i need to swing at him
once he'll do the rest wow that freaked me out had to get something swing at him what the fuck
dodge i press the button in i press the button and accidentally
dodge roll left mouse button whatever the hell it is that was close how the hell would you do
this out regardless how would you oh my god dodge dodge he runs so fast and he's gonna
he's gonna flip through the wall and hit me
he tried hitting him yeah i look at his health i've hit him a hundred damn times i shot him with a
full magazine i was hitting him twice does less damage than the holding one who the fuck is that
what just happened what somebody just flew out why did i throw that i think i was like in a bath
towel i can't go in i can't go in it's got he's in a bad spot i could i'll kill him on this next
one oh shit kill him on this next one here comes okay okay that guy had issues skip skip give me a
lot soda give me the uh let's go let's go let's go look at how much more time i got
so it's still red but we're almost there i was gonna go through one push the cart no she's not
gonna i'll lose her no i'm gonna lose her i'll lose her i'll lose her one i'll lose her i'll lose
i got plenty of time just think of the time spent of me not come on danny danny danny danny danny
danny danny danny danny danny danny danny get close oh my god what is happening this is a scenario
okay thank you softlock don't think so softlock i don't think so you got a softlock no i don't
think so you got a softlock i don't think so just whatever go okay danny danny please
speed it up look at how much time i have hey i'm waiting head over there acceptable
i win you're so sweet i was trying to have the bucket land and hit it right in the head when i
took the photo softlock i don't think so anybody here got a softlock i don't think so
you got a softlock i don't think so a softlock i don't think so i'm here i'm ready for my next
assignment hey i don't know what tk is up to but he's the one i'll see you tomorrow tk are you sure
he paid that poor sap to do it for but that's not possible why would he let his own zombie supply
sabotage his own show end of the stream voice yeah we're gonna pick it back up tomorrow
wait a minute is he the one who fed you that tape it's been like almost seven hours guys it's
been a long time it's been seven hours man not again it sounded like it came from outside plus
i want enough to uh have a whole stream tomorrow is really brave or just really stupid
all right how many cases are left we got seven eight all right yeah this is perfect perfect time
to end this right here because then i got five six seven yeah we got like we're good we're like
almost exactly the halfway point yeah you look at how much time i got because i ain't just i'm
not just gonna do case four too no no no no no i look at all this other stuff i can do no no no
no we're gonna do this tomorrow save the game and i'm not just gonna go right to four two why
would i do that he's gonna ditch us tomorrow what why would i i'm streaming tomorrow what do you
i don't think so yeah we'll finish uh we'll finish this tomorrow i'm gonna do it but first
hold on i gotta save some photos here that one didn't work out as well they thought it was gonna
do i mean whatever i mean this is this is fucked up why is there a share button these still exist
how do those still exist now it's because it happened again right okay case five all right
so a game is saved everything's here to go and we'll uh we'll do the bits we'll probably end at
the probably seven seven and a half hour mark and i'll see you guys tomorrow i'll start earlier
tomorrow the reason why i started like 20 minutes late today is because i was i had a ton of
troubleshooting problems trying to get this xbox controller emulation to work because this game
cannot natively take any controllers unless it's like from 2003 but i'll see you tomorrow
we'll finish it tomorrow and let's do the bits and everything hang out for a little bit see you
tomorrow see you guys later i have to check it every time let me check it one more time okay
does this work this is just not it's so broken it doesn't matter what i do but uh that's i have
to get on top of that the next like next like day off i have i'm gonna spend like a month fixing
that to see if i can get it to work because it's been too long anywho thanks for joining us see
you tomorrow but those of you that are sticking around for a little bit very cool we're gonna go
back kazi gave five subs touched on it but thank you for the five community subs uh homeless sperm
thanks for the 300 bits hi germa dead rising one and two off the record are all on the ps4 if you
didn't know also there's a game called w a t t a m from the creator of katamari demasi it'll be
out on the 17th of december really that's interesting didn't that wasn't like fat princess
dead rising one and two off the record on the on the ps4 well this on pc you would figure
i don't know i thought that this was like a pc game that they brought over with like 1920 by 1080
does it run at 1080 on ps4 or is it like 720 yeah i mean like fuck me for thinking a video game is
gonna work when i buy it and open it right i mean what the hell how dare you think that
says the game developers and publishers that continue to sell it
anywho um i want to play the katamari that's on the 360 because i have a 360 now and i want
to do katamari again we'll see uh vo don't thanks for the 300 bits is this an out of
season april fools joke wait what playing dead rising two why would that be a joke
i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know hey bink video thanks for the
thousand bits where are the poopoo icons i don't know not here dark soul thanks for the 250 really
great stream glad i caught it you're in a coma please wake up you wake up you're in the you've
been a coma you've been in coma five years you were being a karate kid and you've been unconscious
since please come back jeremy really looking forward to green screen too i genuinely love the
variety you have with the content it's a lot of fun jeremy wake up you're in a coma imagine like
that's like the funny meme thing but imagine if you just like your eyes just opened one day like
after 20 30 years of being alive and you were just in a hospital bed and you were like 12
that's scary collie brady thanks for the five subs i'm not sure i saw this one but thank you
dark soul uh green screen dlc for free should be really fun that channel will be open soon
probably after tomorrow's stream the day after that i'll make it and make all the rules and
everything it'll be very it'll be almost the same exact things last time abomination zero
thanks for the 250 bits jerma i'm sick of arguing about this the cookie sitting in the milk is
objectively bad it doesn't mix like cereal it just sits in the bottom and gets gross if you drink all
of the milk it's still there it's of course it's gross um yes it's gross do you know what else is
mcdonald's i still eat that and i go oh that was pretty good the greasy pizza from
7-eleven is disgusting but i've eaten it and like all right whatever this is not a bad argument
they weird gross things they still are it tastes good they're still edible if it's there i'm gonna
eat it your burgers aren't on the bottom of a glass of milk oh are you sure about that are you sure
about the preparations of your pristine big mac that you ordered who has any idea it's all the
same in the stomach somebody somebody gets it sad vega you get it eating is kind of a pain in the
ass don't you guys ever think that sometimes i'll be like in the middle of something and it's just
i just i just want to continue to do that thing and you got to take an hour plus sometimes to
prepare and eat food even if you get fast food it's still it's like a significant portion of
every single day we probably spend like three to four hours plus eating every day it's like
that's too much not time it next time the next even okay if you go no no seriously it takes
about it takes at least two to three hours to eat every meal it's not yeah it depends sometimes
if you okay if you like buy if you buy food from the grocery store and you make it that it takes
like 40 to 50 minutes sometimes to make food what if do you do you do you guys make food
half an hour this ain't rachel ray some of that shit works that's cooking not eating yeah but the
the act of eating requires the cooking so that's time that's added guys even craft macaroni and
cheese the orange box shit takes like 25 minutes to make to make it right what do you mean it does
how long does it take to boil water i think you guys don't understand time management skills
i play dead rising i know these things it takes like five to ten minutes to even boil a pot of
water you boil the water you put the macaroni in there let's see craft mac and cheese directions
you boil you make it doesn't take you three minutes to make craft mac and cheese
uh-huh bring six cups of water to a boil cook the macaroni for seven to eight minutes drain
the water from the macaroni that's another 20 30 40 seconds spinning on hot it is
place macaroni margarine milk and cheese sauce into the saucepan stir it up takes about two or
three minutes to stir that up and get it ready and then guess what you eat it out of that pot
so the second that it comes off the stove you go oh oh oh my mouth what you let it sit there for
like a few minutes so it cools down it takes like fucking 20 fucking it takes like fucking 20 fucking
minutes mate and then you have to sit there after eating like a whole a whole carton of craft mac
and cheese and you have to you do like the oh oh you said you did that for about 15 minutes
before you can even go back to work that's a 30 minute ordeal yeah that's just mac and cheese
20 minutes equals three hours that's how long it takes to make macaroni and cheese out of the box
is that what you eat every day three meals a day that's a side you you make others don't just
eat mac and cheese i hope you don't do that i went to college so did i i know that life
just eat it raw and don't even get me started if you make us i've got a casserole or something if
you're baking like a turkey in the oven or like a ham see you in an hour you guys have a slow
cooked before that shit takes like six to eight hours in a slow cooker am i being really told
that it doesn't take more than a couple hours to make food for a day an hour for a turkey this
takes wait it takes like three hours who bakes a turkey every week oh okay that gets me thinking
that gets me to think about this turn the music off this is actually fucking funny so today
so today i was uh i was pulling out of my i was pulling out of my spot right and i'm like pulling
out into the road and i noticed oh there's um just like oh and like in like the neighborhood
there's like there's like people outside there's like kids playing oh cool okay and like they were
playing uh like wiffle ball or something these they went probably six years old or something
right so i'm out there and i see okay everyone like watch out here comes the car everyone gets
out of the way and i'm like okay everyone's safe and they're the parents were out there and it was
just like a very quick like oh hello like neighbor kind of thing i was like hey how are you and i go
playing and they go yep we're playing and i go hey who's winning and they go everyone because it
was like 10 kids i was like oh hey who's winning and i was thinking to myself like oh i look like
a fucking asshole like i'm saying like who's winning the game that's what i care about
and then i just get they were like no everyone's winning haha and i'm like yeah
yeah that's great that's exactly what it should be and then i kind of was like okay bye and i'm
sitting the driving away going like i look like a fucking dick that only cares about winning
to like six-year-olds that's not what i meant though but it's like that's how i looked
you know i didn't slam the accelerate that's a normal thing to say i don't know i was like
really thinking about that that does not sound like normal when i think about it like a million
times in a row who's winning six-year-olds is it normal how does this relate to turkeys
because somebody said you're eating a turkey every week like what are you some kind of like
rich asshole hey who's winning turkey done yet like i bake a turkey three times a week
like i know i don't i don't do any of these things that's that's kind of a stretch well i
really wanted to tell that story uh seven hours ago what about the kids answer everyone yeah
that's fine you don't want like a little kid to like be losing what did you want them to do
be like oh yeah well uh jeffrey uh and caroline they're winning uh stacy's losing right now and
losing yep oh i thought i was and i was playing that would be bad all right moral the story is
it takes more than 20 minutes to eat three and cook and prepare and eat three to four meals a day
and i know some of you guys eating once a day and you're like what are you talking about it takes
me 10 minutes i eat one giant piece of meat don't do that anymore spread it out you should be eating
like three four plus meals a day snacks sometimes in the middle smaller portions you could eat the
same thing but just spread it out put it in the fridge it's really hard i know it's real hard
because i know exactly what you mean by that because when you buy the steak and cheese sub
you get the large and it's in front of you and you're hungry and you get through half of the
large and you're just like i have to eat the rest of this i have to i know that i shouldn't i just
just put it away and eat it later and have something else no you house the whole thing
it's like 1800 calories of food and then you're slow for the next four hours and then you don't
even you're not even hungry for dinner because you acted like a goddamn camel and you eat like
you ate that one large steak and cheese for breakfast and now you're not even hungry at dinner
over encumbered yeah i i i still do this and it's bad you shouldn't be doing it the most recent
science does not support that conclusion and has more than a decade intermittent fasting is the
healthiest thing you can do one meal a day is actually the best for you please google uh hold
on a second here one meal a day a huge meal is that's how you like that's how you gain a bunch
of weight well you're not eating like a 2000 calories and then going to bed right yes as
long as it's under 2000 calories what one meal a day i'm gonna look this up the one meal a day
diet is a weight loss plan that requires a person to only eat one meal per day is it safe to eat one
meal a day this is called okay this is called the oh mad diet the this is called the you mad diet
what the fuck is this fasting from food for 23 hours a day and eating whatever you want for one
meal this sounds like a scam you can just eat whatever you want as long as you eat once that
meal can range from a double cheeseburger and fries to a what the fuck is this is this real
the you mad diet i tried the extreme fasting oh mad diet here's what happened to me let's see
what happened you could eat pizza and burgers every day drink beer and still lose weight
now this is like this i've seen this commercial as long as you eat less than 2000 calories a day
you can eat whatever you want one but i would don't if you ate 1999 calories in one sitting
i feel like i would want to fucking puke i feel like i would be so full and i would it would hurt
what does the science say like a lot of health trends just because people do it doesn't mean
it's good for you the research is mixed when it comes to whether or not it's safe to eat one meal
a day one 2007 study connects eating once a day to an increase in blood pressure and cholesterol
yeah because people were told you can eat anything you want frank oh really and they eat
fucking four mcdoubles fasting can improve the body's resistance to diseases yeah i know like
fast but but well i would never be able to do that i did it for a year in college it's just
calorie counting for idiots people who binge on these diets typically can't maintain
low calories and eat shitty food if you don't binge and aren't exercising
you it's fine just take a multivitamin i guess that makes sense because if you eat this one
meal a day you just have to be like okay uh just eat once and i hope i didn't eat a whole fucking
pantry worth of food an entire 100 pack of pizza rolls yeah i would get too hungry i don't know if
fuck me up i feel like i already have like enough problems with like foods and shit i like all of
the intestinal bullshit if i did this i would probably like i would go into a coma you'd be
doing it would be like the wake up jeremy in real life what happened well he was eating once a day
and he was trying he was so desperately trying to get a pizza roll sponsorship so that's all he
ate he saw supersize me and then thought he could do that with pizza rolls and then maybe get like
somebody would pay him he actually he actually may have been dead for the last like four days
i don't know intermittent fasting would probably be good for me yeah but here's the thing about
fasting for me when i had my colonoscopy you can't eat solid food for three straight days
that was un fucking bearable that was the worst thing ever even by day one or day two
no i wouldn't be able to handle it i don't think i'd be able to do it and yeah you'd get used to
it i don't think i would my brain my brain is so misfires in every direction somebody would open
a jar of pickles at day one day two and i'd just be like give me those pickles and i'd just start
eating them and i'd be like i don't care it's over but anyways that's really interesting i
don't think i could ever do that but let's keep going let's do the uh this thing in fact
let's switch it on over oh shit do it again hey look at that thanks for all the subs guys
appreciate it we'll see you tomorrow only a few more bits to do what's doing we got on that
because somebody talked about the cookie and the milk thing right okay sad vegan thanks to the 500
bits i'm at a loss for words i seriously expect you to be faster and better that you are killing
more people this time around when they have a smarter ai you're amazing i truly mean that in a
good way they die quicker in this game and you have to go further distances in this game they
die five times faster i don't think the ai is smarter yeah they lose hp much faster
in the first one somebody could get grabbed and just sit there for a full probably 30 seconds
they die quicker here than in dead rising 2 i don't know why but off the record is weird is
that real you need to clear paths and strategize all right well you need you need to like get in
a fight with the other people that are in this chat that tell me that that's the worst idea
just you just say you guys should have seen this pre-stream chat it was like people fighting i've
never seen such division fight fight fight fight constant conflict i still think it's a lot of fun
no i think it's great if i wasn't having fun i wouldn't play it that simple i love it germa
also as a pro tip knife and mop got me through a lot of this game early on it's a deadly weapon
mop have you even seen a mop it's a spear it's the most combat superior weapon known to man
throughout history now that i agree with yeah we've talked about the spear before it's just a long
stick that has a knife at the end you can kill somebody before they even come near you how was
the spear ever fair if you knew that you were going up against spears wouldn't you also bring
why would you bring like a sword to a spear fight spears were the guns of like the 1200s
hey near shoe thanks for the five community subs don't think i saw it before
freudian weapon thanks for the four dollars and 94 cents thanks a lot for you
gnarly thanks for the 250 how many bits will take you to a full beatbox 250 fucking bits that's
what it takes a real one and you might not even be here it's all i can do it's the only talent i
have i got on stage one time at a talent show back in high school and i did that and i remember
like people were cheering and then one person in the back just screamed and it ruined me they said
change the beat you do the same beat every time and then i got and i walked off stage hey sly
thanks for the 250 jerma just wanted to let you know this was the that this version of the game
is literally harder than the original version why did you do this to yourself because i go hard
i'm on hard mode yeah sometimes you have to do like the hard one and really test to see if you
can get to the true end i got to the true end in i was gonna say demon souls i need to go to bed
the differences between dead rising 2 and off the record it's a more difficult game
with a tougher frank west and a tougher fortune city with more aggressive zombies than featured
in the same city and dead rising 2 it actually is hard one oh maybe that's why it's hard hey frost
troll thanks for the 500 bits just got to swallow it whatever that means flood boy 250 thank you
can't wait for green screen dlc for free i need to dust off my torrents of every editing software i
didn't say that well i didn't say that you did also death stranding is great it's been sucking
my life away and i'm currently transporting stuff i don't want to read any spoilers thank you glad
you having fun i heard it's great plank thanks for the 500 bits jerma i eat all the raw ingredients
and make the meal in my stomach that you know this is a diet for everything it's like a raw
diet there's a raw diet there's a i eat only fish i eat only fucking spaghetti i have raisins i only
eat raisins and cucumbers and i i turned into superman this diet it does million different
diets but i'm glad you can do that uh thank you childish gambino for the five dollars 500 bits
thank you reaper thanks for the 250 jerma i did the you mad diet for a while and i did lose about
60 pounds but i also worked out and the one meal i did eat was somewhat healthy like baked chicken
so it does work to an extent that's glad you found something that works that sounds that's a lot of
weight that's a lot of weight to lose good for you thanks for the 250 and then finally sticks
renegade thanks for the 250 bits for a beatbox how much do you draw how much to draw my fursona
i will not draw any fursonas i'm not going to draw anything i will only draw urinals that's
the only thing i draw on this stream that's it all right so i will see you guys tomorrow
but before we go before we go i want you guys to go say hello to blordow if you don't know
blordow is the the person that is that made all the stuff you're looking at right now all the
music you're listening to they did it all every piece of art that you see on this channel was
done by blordow and i believe that um his brother is currently very sick and i think he's raising
money go give michelle and if you have anything to contribute by all means he's been a very very
very close friend and colleague i've known him for almost 15 plus years we're gonna raid blordow
right now i'll see you guys tomorrow much love to you take care of yourselves see you soon cue it
up can i now do it from here there we go see you guys soon see you tomorrow take care