Hi, how are you? I'm a little late. I'm a little late, but there's a reason why I'm a little late.
I'm not six hours late. I'm two and a half hours late because I needed a cable. I needed to get
the table set up a little. It's just a little. I'm just a little bit late and I don't want to
get too loud because I don't know the acoustics of this room. And I guess I said acoustics.
Well, here's my problem. I said, oh man, 2 p.m. or earlier, dude. 2 p.m. sounds good, man.
But then I was like, you know, I, me and Holly was setting up a table.
What, what are you, what are we even doing today? Okay, there's one guy two nights ago that said
we were doing tier lists and we talked about my candy preferences, my snack preferences.
And I, there's a lot of stuff that I have in F or D, right? Don't blame it on Holly. I didn't,
I said we're setting the table up. It's, I, it's my fault. I should have, I should have taken
precedence and started setting the table up yesterday. It's my fault. How are you? I'm
doing good. I'm doing good. There's going to be a system here too. So people that,
there were a lot of people concerned in the pre-stream chat. They're like, dude, um, but wait,
wait, wait, wait, back up, back up, back up. Don't call me a 2K Andy. It's been five seconds.
At 2K, 2,000 live viewers is a shitload. That's a fucking shitload of people.
So 2K Andy, that's huge. Anyways, and that guy for like a few minutes. All right. So listen,
here we go. We've been doing tier lists. People in pre-stream were kind of concerned.
They're like, oh, hey, oh, so you, we got, there's a lot of, there's a lot of history.
Let's back up like two days. I said, I never have eaten a trolley before. Trolley, a trolley. I
don't know. I don't, I don't eat these fucking things. I put it in F tier and everybody freaked
out. It was like, dude, you can't put a trolley in F tier. Like, and I'm like,
they're gross. It's a gummy worm. They're stupid. And then they said, you have, you eat one on stream
and prove that you don't like it. I was like, okay, fine. But how about we eat 45 of all the
candies and snacks and breads, fruits, sodas, stuff that I've put in F tier and see if I'm full of
shit. He's absolutely insane. So I, we, there's a lot of stuff here and I, I, I, I'm not ready
to show you yet. This is going to kill him. This, I'm not, this, listen, I have a system in place.
Okay. My system is going to go as follows. I'm not going to eat every piece of candy. I'm not
going to open, for instance, the gross Almond Joy and eat the whole, I'm not going to eat the whole
bar of Almond Joy. Holly loves those. She's very upset about this. No, I'm not, I'm not going to
eat the whole bar of candy. Are you crazy? We're going to go from category to category. We're
going to start because I, there's, there's fruits here. We're going to start with fruit. I'm going
to eat, I'm going to take a bite, a few bites of fruit and I'm going to move it onto the side.
Something that I forgot completely. I need like a separate table to put the stuff that, oh, you
know, it doesn't matter. It can just stay here. I'm not eating the whole thing. We're going to go
category to category. We're going fruits. Okay. Take one bite. Contemplate it for a few minutes.
Place it on a new tier list. Then we're going to probably to chocolate like Almond Joy, Mounds,
Tootsie Roll. We're going to go category to category so I don't throw up. If for, look,
if for some reason I'm going to puke, it's not going to happen. I'm not going to puke.
Everybody's relaxed. Okay. Anything that I don't open is going to get donated. So if I don't get
to something, if I'm like, you know what, I'm not even going to fucking open that. I don't want it.
It's going to, I'm going to donate it. Anything that is opened is going to be eaten. There's going
to be like six months worth of candy here. I will eat these Milk Duds even if I don't like them.
Okay. So don't worry. All these things are shelf stable for at least like a few weeks, at least.
So yeah, like let's, let's say if I'm full of shit. Yeah. I'm not, look,
Holly likes some of this stuff. I, you know, I, I might like it too. We'll find out.
This game sucks. Can you play something else? I'm not going to puke. Everyone's so, I'm not
going to fucking throw up. Okay. Am I on camera yet? Okay. Hold on. I don't think you guys are
ready for this reveal. Yeah. I like, look, one guy made this whole fucking stream happen
and that's kind of how it works. I did this bread too. I actually probably will eat,
we're going to eat this bread. So don't worry. All right. Just go ahead and reveal it. Let's just,
like, let's get it over with. Yeah. Go ahead. Go ahead and show, show the table. Okay. Hi.
There's a lot here. Uh, I thought I'd like a fun, maybe like a funny joke would have been, uh,
would have been to do this. Are you ready? Like, okay. This looks like all those food eating
videos. What the fuck is he doing? You're going to get fat. Nice shirt. It's a Millennium Falcon.
Relax. All right. So already like all this shit is here. I got to do this. This is for me.
Ready? Like, okay. Now somebody edit in like a bunch of noodles going in my mouth for the
thumbnail. Ryan's toy review. Okay. Now hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I got, you got, you got
to edit a big mozzarella stick right here. Ready? Like, you know what I mean? You got to get the
mozzarella stick. Nice plate. What? I actually kind of don't want to eat that, but whatever.
All right. Yes. Look, I know people like don't waste food. I'm not going to waste this. These
bags of, I think it can be rolled up and sealed and they can be eaten later. I'm not going to
throw any of this shit away. I will eat it. This bag of Tootsie Rolls is going to last six years.
This is going to last six years. It's going to last a very, very long time. So don't worry.
I don't want to mess up the setup. It looks good. How long do Tootsie Rolls even last? Does anybody
know? Happy birthday. Drink the hot sauce. All right. Let me, let me reiterate what's going on
here because people are confused. Nice window behind you. Just let this on in. They last,
they last a long time. Six years, hundreds of years. Is there an expiration date on Tootsie
Rolls? Is there actually an expiration date? I don't think there's an expiration date.
The Last Supper. Yeah. Remember when Jesus ate a bunch of fucking chili cheese Fritos with like
Joseph and Peter? Remember when they had the hot tamales and like Jesus, like Jesus, like gave a
hot tamale to Peter and he fucking, he didn't like it. He almost puked. No suit. Guys, I was already
30 minutes late and you wanted me to have a suit on. I was going to take me like another 40 minutes
to get here. So I'm sorry. There's no suit. There's no telephone. It's all right. So let's,
let's go. Let's go. Here we go. Just to show you kind of how this is going to work. Right here
would be, this should be the tier list, right? I'm going to show them for a second.
I'm going to, I'm, we're going to face my own bullshit. We're going to see. I got, if I don't
like it, it's going to F. Star Wars shirt. Yeah, I know. Suit next stream. I'm not just going to
wear a suit for fun. We got to start with the fruit because it's going to go bad if I don't
eat it like right now. So everything on that list right there. Okay. Everything on that list right
there is stuff that has been an F. All my F candies, all my F chips, all my F sodas. Hey,
well, hold on a minute. That's not F. Why is this up here? Oh, right. Cause I was going to,
I was going to do on stream. I was going to do the, the, the, the Coke versus Pepsi taste
test challenge. I mean, I already know which one I like, but do you stick around for the whole
video to find out? I'm doing that at the very fucking end. Make sure the fucking algorithm
gives me extra views. Okay. So this is a red delicious apple. They taste like shit. They smell
like shit and they kind of look like shit. I know that I don't like red delicious. Everybody. Who
does? I don't think anybody does. Are they warm? These are freezing cold. I just got them out of
the fridge. We're going to find out if I actually really hate these. I have not. Okay. Here's another
thing that really important to understand. Everything that's on this table. I don't think
I've had in like five to 10 years because I know I don't like it. Right. Why would you eat
something you don't like? You ready? Red delicious apple first. Here we go. Oh, that was like a,
there's a growth spot right there. Can you see the growth spot? Hold on. Let me do that again.
Okay. No, a spit bucket. Oh, apples. No, I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I have to swallow it. Right.
I got to, I got to come on. I got to be a man sized sandwich. I got to swallow it. Okay. Well,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Important. Actually really isn't that bad. One more. I don't, I can't
take more than like two bites. The skin sucks. The skin is like weird. These are actually really,
they're very sweet. That's, I think that's one of the reasons why I don't like them.
Need a big bite. That, look at how big of a bite that is. What kind of mouth do you have if that's
the one bite you take? Why do I have like a joker mouth? I, this is not F. It's not F. It's not F
though. Fuck. This is actually kind of good. I wouldn't like one of, okay. It's not, it's not B.
It's probably C. I think Red Delicious Apple is going to C. This table is shaking. Because
like the AC just turned on. I thought like the fucking room was shaking. Yeah. That's a C.
That's a C. It's not an F. Don't, no, no. I got like a million things to eat. All right. So that
Red Delicious, not an F. It's a C. They're a little too sweet. I'd rather, okay, for sweet,
I'd rather just get a green apple, which is sweet and sour. It's really good. All right.
Now we're staying in fruit. Next up, this is a cantaloupe. So this is cantaloupe. Cantaloupe
is the thing that I always avoid in a fruit cup. I always just eat around it. I say this is F.
I haven't eaten in probably five years. Shall we see if I like it? Cantaloupe. Let me get the
apple out. Actually, no. Put, put Red Delicious to D. Put it down to D. No, it's D. It's D. The skin
is still in my mouth. I'm still eating skin. D. I'm like eat, it's like eating film. Yeah. D.
Fucking absolutely D. It's still there. I've swallowed 15 times. Yeah. I swallowed like 15.
That's D. Absolutely. Red Delicious Apple D. It's still there. It's still skin in my fucking mouth.
It's in my teeth. It's like popcorn. Cantaloupe. Here we go. Oh, juicy. Watch. Oh my god.
That's all. Somebody said this is going to make me sick. I just, I took a bite out of a fucking
apple. What do you mean? Why? Cantaloupe is, it's okay. You're not using a fork. It's a fruit,
man. What do you want me to do? It's not sticky. Yeah, it is. Okay. Cantaloupe. I said it was F.
Oh, my palate cleanser. Right. I got pickled ginger, but no, I don't think so. I think that
would, I would actually puke if I ate that right now. Yeah. I was going to do this joke where,
you know, when you go to sushi restaurant and you order sushi and you're supposed to use the
pickled ginger as a palate cleanser between each item. I was like, oh, that's kind of funny. What
if like after every bite, I cleanse my palate with some ginger. But I don't think that would,
I think I would actually throw up if I did that. So, no, we're not doing that. Okay. Cantaloupe.
Stop distracting me. See, it's juicy. It's got, it's got a good juice to it. I think it's a C.
So here we go. Here's Cantaloupe 2, which is honeydew melon. It's just, this is, I'm going to,
it's going to be the exact same score. They're, they're the exact same thing. They taste exactly
the same. They're the same exact product. They're exactly the same. This is fucking awful. This is
dog shit. This is literal dog shit. Yeah. This doesn't taste like anything. This tastes like
nothing. All I taste is water and like somebody sprayed Lysol in another room. This is awful.
Honeydew melon. Holy fuck. Literal F. I'm not changing my goddamn mind. It's juicy, but it
just tastes like somebody sprayed like fucking fabric softener in another room. F. F for honeydew
melon. F. This is a grapefruit. The reason why I don't like grapefruit is because it's usually
very acidic, like way too acidic and it tastes like kind of stomach acid and it smells like
kind of good. You're wrong. I'm, I'm literally sitting here telling you that I'm eating these
things and giving you my opinion. I'm trying to make, I'm giving you my honest opinions. I'm
not going to put any fluff on it. Okay. Grapefruit. All these, remember everything here I put an F
at some point over the last few years. Grapefruit. Here we go. Nice Buzzfeed video. I know. But look,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, come on. Here we go. All right. Grapefruit. I actually don't want to bite
this. I like, I know I hate these. Let's find out. It's fucking awful. It just tastes like acid.
It's, it's, it's acid. It's just acid. Are these even, okay. Are these good for you? Are these even
good for you? Are these good for you? You need to put sugar on it. No, no, no. I'm not going to do
the thing to make the thing supposed to taste better by adding bullshit to it. This is just
the way it is. What you, okay. Oh dude, take the red delicious apple and put caramel all over it.
And then you'll like it. No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. These are F. This is bad. This stays in F. Where
it belongs. Yeah. I know. You cut the thing in half and you like shake fucking 50 grams of sugar
all over the thing. So it gets sapped in and seeps into the actual fruit and then you can eat it.
No, no, no. Oh yeah. Are you guys the same people that put sugar on your cornflakes? When you order,
when you order cornflakes, do you put the cornflakes, which goes up in front of your table
and you put sugar all over it? It's the same exact thing. It's an animal style grapefruit.
It's how you're supposed to eat it. I'm just telling you right now, the fruit by itself is enough.
If you add sugar to something, a shitload of sugar, it's like, yeah, it's probably going to be better.
I mean, I could literally probably open up the Fun Dip and like put it on there. And then it's
like the same thing. God, Fun Dip sucks. So if somebody already has a thumbnail. Oh, I want to
see. I'm coming. That's pretty good. That's pretty good. Okay. Fruits are done. I was wrong about
cantaloupe. Red Delicious said, I don't know if they're F. They're okay. All right. In the same
realm, we're going to go to, these are cold. We're going to do these now. So we're going to do sodas.
This is Diet Mountain Dew, which is wrong. Mountain Dew is an F for me. So Diet Mountain
Dew is probably like not allowed to even be scored. Diet Mountain Dew is probably fucking
terrible. It's disgusting. I don't, it sucks. Diet. Why would you make Diet Mountain Dew? Why?
What's the point of making a Diet Mountain Dew? Listen to that. Hold on. This is for the video.
This is for the fucking like eating, like eating channel video. Okay. It smells. How does it smell?
Diet Mountain Dew. You ready? Let's give you the honest opinion. She said you. You guys don't
understand. So I can hear her in like the other room or if she's like working on something
somewhere else in like, in the house, I will hear, I will do something weird and I'll hear, oh,
I can hear it from the other room. Oh, this is very bad. It's very bad. Do I think this is better
than actual Mountain Dew? Weirdly, yes, I do. Okay. Mountain Dew is way too sugary and tastes way,
it's just like pure sugar. So for some reason, this is better than Mountain Dew. What's in it?
Wait, hold on. Aspartame. I'm going to go ahead and seal that. We're going to go ahead and seal
that and we're going to just go ahead and seal that. Does all Diet Soda have aspartame in it?
Put the cap on it. I am. Somebody will drink this. Maybe not. Somebody will drink this.
Diet Mountain Dew? Dog shit. It's fucking awful. It's literally F, but it's better than regular
Mountain Dew. I'm sorry. I just don't like Mountain Dew. I know people love Mountain Dew. Oh,
Mountain Dew is so good. I don't like it. I think it's bad. Here's Squirt. Did I put this in F or
I never tried this? Oh, it's Grapefruit Soda. I don't want it. Hold on. I got a really funny
joke coming up. Stay tuned. This is Squirt. There you go. Squirt. I guess I never had this.
Why did I put it in F? Oh, that's nice. Oh, okay. I drink it. I've had Fresca before. Oh,
did we put Mountain Dew in F? Okay, just making sure. Squirt. I've had Fresca. Fresca's a little
too harsh somehow. This is pretty smooth. I don't know why I just feel like I was being held hostage.
I don't know why. I just like looked up. There's like, I don't know. It's like,
why am I being held hostage right now? Like, what is happening? He loves it. I actually,
it's pretty good. All right, one more sip and then I'll put it away. I think this is a solid B.
I think Squirt's a solid B. It's not, I can tell if I'm gonna start like, it's a lot, it's bubbly.
He's breaking from the simulation. I think this is a B. I would drink this again and I will because
it's gonna go in the fridge and I'm gonna drink it later. Ah, Squirt's a B. That's, I'm actually
very surprised. It's lighter than Fresca somehow. I can't hide. I literally can't hide. Yes, I can.
Okay. I couldn't, there's literally nothing I could do to stop that. I could not stop that.
It was impossible. It was literally impossible. Should I make it lower grade? No, should I make
it a lower grade because like, holy shit, that was like fucking violent. I couldn't even,
I couldn't stop that. Oh, you can mute. That's right. Imagine if I just mute down here. Dude,
I would never be able to like, okay, we've talked a lot of shit about like, like, okay, sponsorships,
right? Like, I'm gonna start doing sponsors. Maybe you've seen one. Maybe you see another
at some point, right? Like if I were to fucking just puke down here, this would never be allowed
on my stream ever. Even if like, okay, yeah, you've said some things that you were like,
you were just joking around. I drank a squirt and I puked down my shirt, right? That would be
impossible to, I couldn't hide that. You guys, the second, it would have been possible. I would,
it would be possible. Whatever. It's a B. I think it's a high B. All right, sodas. We still, oh,
no, I'm okay. I should be fine. This is A&W cream soda, which is only good when there's like
a little bit of ice cream in it. I really don't like this at all. The bubbles are like still
there. I'm all right. What if I just fucking, dude, if I puke and like whatever, if I have like a
soda puke, I will live forever, okay? If I take, if I took a big chunk of soda and like the bubbles
come up and I puke, I live forever. I will live forever. Like that'll be shared for like the next
hundred years. I will literally be the, I'll be the guy that like puked on his stream like with bubble
pukes and I will live forever. I will never die. It'll be impossible for me. I'll live forever.
Okay, oh, this is the joke I was gonna make. No, that's disgusting. Why would I make that joke?
I was gonna make it like a fart thing where I was gonna be like, you know what I mean? Like
you know what I'm saying? Do you guys want music? How you guys feel? You guys want some,
want some tunes in the background? Cream soda smells amazing, but I don't like how it tastes.
No music? No, no music. Okay, all right. You guys can put your own soundtrack in the background if
you want. Okay, so here we go. This is A&W cream soda. I actually am a huge fan of A&W root beer,
but I'm not a big fan of cream soda. Cream soda is, you take one sip and yeah, that's enough.
You've had enough, which I'm sure it's going to happen here because after the first sip,
you get like immune to the flavor. Let's see if it happens. One sip, delicious, kind of sugary,
way too much, a little too much. Second, third sip, I'm immune to the flavor. What the fuck?
Oh my God. Huh? Oh my God. There's 77, 76 grams of sugar in this bottle. Wait, no, yeah. 76 grams
of sugar? I thought it was like 40. What's in a Coke? 60, 65. God damn, that's a lot of sugar.
Okay, so again, like my issue with cream soda is I can tell you, I knew it was going to be bad.
It's like syrupy. It's thicker than a regular soda. It's thick. Yeah, and now I'm immune to
the flavor. I don't, I taste like kind of sweetness and bubbles. The cream soda flavor doesn't exist.
This goes good on ice cream. This goes good on ice cream, I think. Is it creamy? I mean,
I think like this sitting at the bottom of vanilla ice cream, like just like in a little pool would
be kind of pretty good. Are they going to float? 76 grams of sugar. These are all so sugary. What
is the lowest one? Oh, squirt based. 63. What about Pepsi? 69, 65. Squirt's got the lowest sugar so far.
Of course it does, based. All right, that's cream soda. It's uh, it's F. It just is. It's just,
you can't enjoy, I can't enjoy it. I actually, I just really can't enjoy that. Okay, if I wasn't
drinking it, if it was used as a sauce, sure. Okay, bubbles are coming up. Nice, nice based.
Is it Bussin? No, it's not. My root beer. It's just, yeah, it's kind of just shitty root beer.
And again, let me be very clear. I love A&W root beer. I think it's fantastic. It's probably the
best. Mug beats it by a lot, I think, but I think it's still incredibly good based on what?
Epo. What about squirt over cream? Well, I mean, cream, cream soda's F. This is B. All right,
it's time to do... No, no, this is good. I'm fine. I mean, guys, people, here's the thing.
A lot of people are concerned about this stream, but I will tell you right now, I have been high
and eaten like all this shit before. Guys, I've been high and eaten an entire tub of Ben and
Jerry's ice cream. I think I'm going to be okay. Like I've eaten like Cheez-Its, Ben and Jerry's
ice cream, um, like banana cream pie in the same night with Cheez-Its and shit. So like,
I think I'd be fine, especially if I don't do that much. I know I don't like Diet Coke,
but I put it in F so I have to re-remember why. I actually would, I'll use that as a sauce. So,
he's high right now. Does your doctor know about this? You want to call my doctor and say,
hey, hey, hey, hey, doctor, yeah, I'm just very concerned. I wanted to call you about a few
things. Oh, what is it? What can I help you with? I'm eating Almond Joys and I'm eating a bunch of
candy today. I'm eating a Tootsie Roll. I'm eating one bite of an Almond Joy and taking a sip of
cream soda. Am I going to be all right? He's going to hang up on me. This is Diet Coke. Don't blow
up. Oh, okay. Dude, you're going to have to go to the emergency room. No, I'm fine. Guys, do you
understand that there are, there are people that like drink like five of these in a day? All of,
okay, all the concerned Andes in here. How many fucking monsters did you have today? How many
monsters did you have today? How many, how many, how many of those have you had today? Interesting.
Don't take a sip out of cream soda, Jeremy, but like, oh yeah, monster, extra fire, whatever the
fuck it is. Zero, zero, zero, zero to my entire life. All right, well, whatever. You understand
this is Coke and it's F. This is Diet Coke. Whoa, be careful. Yeah, it's F. It sucks. Not changing
my opinion on Diet Coke. Diet Coke just tastes like regular Coke that went through like a
britter water filter. It's, it's, it's, it's, no, no, I don't think so. I wouldn't want to drink a
whole one of these. You know what I mean? I don't, I don't want to drink a whole one of these.
People drink a shitload of this. It just like sucks. Zero calories. How many calories are in
just a regular Coke? 240. This sucks. That's what the mini cans are for. Yeah, dude. Okay.
People, let me tell you something. The mini cans and the mini little ones. Oh, that's good. That's
good shit. You should, that's fine. Drink one of those. You can make those go a long way. You know
how? I'm going to give you a tip here. Here's a tip. Get a big cup like this and fill the fucking
thing with ice. I'm not going to puke. No, I'm not going to puke. It's literally just bubbles.
Every time I drink soda, I get like fucking gassy. Okay. So don't everybody freak out.
You get, you get a big cup like this and you fill the fucking thing with ice. I'm talking to the
brim. When you pour in half of that goddamn can, it's going to fill the whole thing and you can
enjoy it for like an hour if you want to. Right? You don't have to drink that much soda. Fill ice
and dilute it. It's fine. A little bit of dilution is fine. You know, it's not going to make you sick.
Why would it make you sick? Get a bucket. I'm not, I don't need a bucket. All right. The last thing
I'm going to do is I'm going to, this has nothing to do with the tier list. Put this over here.
Yeah, it's up. We're going to do the Coke versus Pepsi blind taste test. Actually,
I think I might need you to come in here. I, I, I'll know. I'll know. Right. Okay. Hold on.
Let's open them both. So I don't want to, I don't want any bias here. This is the Coke. Oh,
the shape, right? Yeah. The different shapes. Ah, it should be fine. I'll just grab it weirdly.
Okay. This, this is Pepsi. This is Coke. Yeah. I'm going to drink pretty much all this stuff.
Okay. So, um, I'm going to, I'm going to hand, I'm going to, actually here. Probably easier
if you're just ready. So I'm going to close my eyes and I don't want to know which one you're
handing me. It could be either one and just stick it in the cup holder. Oh, I know that taste. That
is the classic, classic Coke taste. Okay. Take it. I can tell when it's Coke because it hurts.
Got it? Why does this taste like raspberry? This is raspberry. Is this raspberry flavor?
What? I don't like that one. I'm done with that one. Give me, let me see the other one, please.
Yeah. Let me do the other one one more time. This is definitely Coke. Yeah. Of course it is.
Of course it is. This is the classic Coke flavor. The other one was raspberry. What is it?
Yeah. That Pepsi is way worse than Coke. Coke is way better. Okay. Well, first of all,
like this like tastes like it has other flavors in it. Coke kind of hurts when you,
when you drink Coke, it has that kind of like, it's like a bite, which I like way more than Pepsi.
Let me just do the, not that I can see it. Let me see. This tastes almost like vanilla,
like it tastes like there's something else in it. Citric acid. Is there citric acid in Coke?
Bro, no, there's not. No, that's the difference. It's citric acid. That's the difference.
There's citric acid in Pepsi and this, this, this phosphoric acid in Coke. That's why it tastes
like kind of like, it's like a like fruity. Okay. Coke's way better. Coke is like A.
Pepsi is like, it's not bad. I, I, I, did I put it in F? I gotta hide for a second because I'm gonna
burp. Everybody probably thought I was about to puke. Everybody's probably like, oh shit,
he's puking. No, I just wanted to hide because I didn't want to burp into the fucking microphone.
Pepsi is a C minus. It's not F. It's not fair to call it F. Coke is way better.
I gotta go down to like fucking puke. All right. There's your sodas. The one that surprised me is
probably squirt. The first time I've probably ever had it. I move away from the mic to put the Coke
cap on. Yeah, I got it. These all go in the fridge. I will absolutely drink all the Pepsi. I'll drink
all the Coke. I'll, this will be used as a sauce. I'll drink all this. I'll, I'll drink all that.
I'll have to. Okay. Coke is A. Pepsi is C. That's my opinion. I know you probably love Pepsi,
but it tastes, it's got fruits in it somehow. It tastes like it's got fruits in it. So that's it.
What's in here? Oh, my green tea powder. Perfect. All right. There's your soda. There's your fruit.
We're gonna move on. Let's stay in the sugar realm. Why not? Let's move to chocolate.
This is Almond Joy. These are both, to me, these are both, old people eat these. This is like,
I imagine an old guy sitting just kind of in a rocking chair. Just like, they're like,
these are like 19, like 20 or something. These are all old and old people eat these and I don't
like them. And they're made by this, look, you can tell that the same, the same game company made
these. This is like an asset flip. It's a, it's a unity flip. It's an asset flip. All right. This
is Almond Joy. I'm only going to take like one bite of this. Oh, it's like a little sectioned
off here. Okay. So this is what it looks like. This is what an Almond Joy is. I, I don't think
I've even ever opened this. Have I ever eaten, I feel like I've eaten this and hated it.
Why, but why are they, why is there a coconut on it? It's coconut? All right. Here we go. Almond
Joy. Almond Joy, everybody. Here we go. It's very mushy in the middle. Very mushy. Do you want one?
She's like, you want the other half of this? Wait, it's definitely not F. It's too, it's like too,
it's like too mushy. There's like too much fiber in the middle. I know, but coconut is like,
I like coconut water and coconut milk. Here, take that. Actually, the more that it, the more
that I'm sitting here, I kind of hate it, but I want another one. Hold on. I'm very texture-based.
Same reason why the apple Red Delicious, it's like the skin. If I have to sit there and like chew
your product for more than like two or three straight minutes, I usually don't, because now,
here's the problem. Okay. Well, gross. Here we go. Here's the problem. Problem. Problem alert.
All the chocolate is gone. All the almond is gone. The only thing that's left is fibers of coconut,
just mushed together in my mouth. Still there. Nope. Nope. Sorry. I would treat this the same
way that I usually treat milk dogs, which by the way, I thought I just dumped them. Coming up soon.
I make sure you stay to the end of the video for me to tell you which one I like more.
I'm still showing it. Still showing it. Still there. Oh, it's slowing. It's getting slowly
down past D. It's just D. It's D. I'm sorry. I'm still showing the fucking coconut fibers.
I'm enjoying. Honey, I'm sorry. This is D. Oh, it's still there. I was, I don't want to eat this.
I'm trying to swallow it. I want someone to count how many times I just had chewed that from when
it went in. That first, okay, when I bit it and it was like the textural, like the mush of the
coconut, the fibers, the chocolate, the almonds, that was a B. That bite was a B. That was a B plus.
Then the same problem I have with the fucking red delicious apple, it stays in your mouth forever
and you just chew up a bunch of fucking paper. That's what it's, it is good value. If you like
chewing coconut, that was a B plus initial reaction. And then, and then like a D. So I think,
I don't think it's F. F is kind of unfair. He's muted. No, I'm not. Holly is based. Holly,
you should get him. It's a skill issue. It's not like Apex. What are you talking about?
The initial bite was a B. The rest of it was like a D minus. So therefore it has to go into C minus.
I'll be fair to it. I will be fair to it. It's a C minus. I'm not going to go to the store and buy
a C minus though. If somebody presented me with an almond joy, I'd go, oh, thanks. In my brain,
I'd secretly be going, fuck that guy. But I'd be like, thanks. And I would eat it and it'd be all
right. Almond joy, C minus. It's not an F. Let's stay in the same category. There's mounds now.
Oh, more coconut from the same asset flip. So what's the difference? What's the difference
between mounds and coconut? Mounds and almond joy. That's the only difference. It might be
dark chocolate. Oh wait, the only difference is there's just no almonds in this. What? Oh,
it is. It really, it just is that. But I liked the almonds in this. This is going to be F.
All right. This is, this is mounds. Mounds again. It's dark chocolate with no almonds. Oh,
I don't really like dark chocolate and I didn't like the mushy coconut. Here we go. Okay. You know
those like chocolate shops? You go in and they have like the, oh, pick like 10, pick a box of 10.
And they have like the little things where it's like, oh, this one's filled with raspberry goo.
This one has like fucking peach schnapps in it. That just reminds me of one of those. Hold on.
This is better. Yeah, it's better. The dark chocolate goes with the coconut way better than
the yellow one. And I'm not even a dark chocolate fan. Is he wearing pants? Of course not. These
were both an F. What almond joy a D? Oh, it's already there. Again, same problem. Alert. Red
alert. Okay. If they just, if it was like coconut flavored juice in the middle, these would be like
B. If this was like coconut, like smooth coconut flavored, like nougat, this would be like an A.
Just swallow it. Dude, I can't. You have fucking George Washington teeth. That's why I don't,
man. It's just, it's coconut. Coconut sucks. Get better at chewing. No, I'm, I'm gonna,
it's a man sized sandwich here. That first bite was better than this first bite. I put that in D.
This is going to C. It's not an F. It's like, it's like a C is C. I was about to take another bite.
Shouldn't that prove something? Chew it less. Okay. How many times do you want me to chew this?
What, what are they saying? Like how many times should I chew this before swallowing it?
120. No, all the chew Andes in chat here. How long should I chew this for? 60 times?
Enough so you can swallow it. 30 times. 30, 30, 30. I'm going to chew this. I'm seeing a lot of like
20, 30. I'll chew it 30. 27, 20. We'll go for 30. Okay. I can't. I fucking can't. I can't. It's too
much. This hurts to watch. Why? Because I don't like your favorite shitty candy. It's not shitty.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. It's not dentures. I don't have a baby mouth. It eat
coconut, dude. Coconut is fibrous. Coconut. Yeah, it is for old people. That's what I'm talking
about. Cause old people just sit there and they go. Yeah, that's why it's for old people. Cause they
chew the fuck out of it. All right. It's a, it's a C. And that's all I have to say. And I'm not
saying anymore. And you won't be able to get me to change my opinion. Okay. Chocolate. What else
we got? Tootsie rolls. Why not? Yeah, they're right here. This dude's so out of touch. Why?
Cause I'm now, I'm going to be fishing coconut out of my gums for the next hour. Tootsie rolls
were, were they F or D? I think they were low D or high F. Just a, see nothing here. Not just
no strings or anything. See, there's nothing here. See? Tootsie roll. Just a regular, just generic
Tootsie roll. Why did you buy so many? Do you know how hard it is to buy one of these? You don't
let us tell them. You have to buy a bag that's either this or 30 pounds. They don't make little
Tootsie rolls. Let me get the coconut in my mouth. This is not man-sized. It doesn't matter. Okay.
Coconut's gone. Remember, mouthfeel is very important. I'm a very texture-based person.
It's fun. It's fun to do. Doesn't taste very good. You know why I don't like Tootsie rolls?
We're doing it out right now. It tastes more like candy than it does chocolate. You know what? Oh,
the flavor. Yeah. I was told that I did this wrong because there's like the flavored Tootsie rolls
are better. Not the default ones. This tastes, this doesn't taste like chocolate to me. It tastes
less like chocolate. Like this is not a chocolate to me. It's just like a candy. This, this was a
chocolate. This is chocolate flavored candy. And that doesn't make any sense. So that's why I kind
of don't like it. Midgis? What is a midgi? Is this like, like from what countries did I get these
from? Midgi? Is that like, is that like Finnish? Is that Finnish for like middle? Midgi. What is that?
It's mid. It's mid. Is it, what is that? Like is it a different language? Is it Australian?
Australian is English. It's mid grade. Mid grade. It's not mid. All right. I, we are,
we are, don't say it's mid grade. I didn't say that. I didn't say that. Tootsie roll,
Tootsie roll, if you're watching the stream right now, I didn't say mid grade. I,
hold on. They said that. I didn't say it. It's F. I said it was F, but they're saying mid grade,
which is not what I said. I said it's F. That means that I don't like them very much.
That means I actually don't like them. I see the appeal though. I just, I just wouldn't want,
I just, okay. Look, if they would, these are going to go like this. Yeah. Okay. So this is what's
going to happen to the Tootsie Rolls. They're going to roll up like this. They're going to go
into a box and they're going to sit in a closet forever. They don't, they expire in 2024. I'm
going to go into the closet sometimes. I'm going to go into the pantry sometimes and I'm going to
look at it a year from now and go, oh yeah, sure. I'll eat one. I'll eat one of these,
maybe two of these in the next year. Trick or treaters. That's no, no trick or
treaters don't want little Tootsie Rolls. The trick or treaters want king size Reese's. That's
what they want. All right. This Tootsie Rolls, they're F. They will be probably eaten eventually.
No trick or treater wants a Tootsie Roll. Come on. Oh, stay tuned to the end of the video.
All right. What else? We have a couple of snow caps. I know that we've got somebody here that's
a big fan of snow caps. I just remember these being like too crunchy. I remember the, I hate
these. I'm glad I'm solidifying, I'm solidifying a lot of opinions here. The packaging is cool.
Here we go. Snow cap. The chocolate's kind of, I don't like the chocolate very much.
I'll probably eat this whole box when I get high next time. They're weird, they're like
weirdly good, but in a way that I don't want to eat them right now. The texture is good.
The chocolate's, I don't like the chocolate very much though. This is a flyover state candy.
They're just chocolate chips covered in, they're just, yeah, they're just chocolate chips covered
in like a, these weird like, I don't want to say it because it's like mean. I don't want to say
it because it's mean if I say it. It looks like it's, you know what I'm going to say, right?
It looks like chocolate chips covered in, no. You want some? Yeah, take whatever you want. Oh,
you want some snow caps? Oh, my girl loves snow caps. No, I don't know what they taste like. Oh,
you don't know what they taste like? Here you go. All right, we need your honest opinion.
Okay, here, eat another one on camera. These people, yeah, you could have eaten anything.
You could have just eaten anything. Eww. I think it's like, I like the, I like the crunchy texture
is good, right? I wouldn't buy it. This is movie theater candy. You, but you get this in the movie
theater and you watch a movie and you eat like half of, you don't, wait, isn't there, hold on a
second. Don't people sprinkle this into popcorn? That's like the whole thing. You sprinkle this
into popcorn, right? I could understand that actually. These aren't F. These don't belong in
F. They're just like, all right, okay, stop, I gotta stop eating them. I've eaten too many.
The fact that I keep eating them. Damn, I think, hold on. I actually kind of like these. How tall
is Holly? Six, six, two, six, three. Fuck, these are not F. I gotta stop eating them. I know those
are good. It took me a minute to understand. It took me, it took me like, I was gonna, I was
gonna make fun of them. I can make fun of them now, right? Because like, I like it. I like them. So
like that, these are B. Snowcaps are B, but they look like chocolate with mold on it. They look
like chocolate with like mold all over it. I can say that because like I, they're telling you I
enjoy them, but they have, they have an interesting look. Where does it go? Below squirt, B. Are you
standing right now? Yeah, those are B. Those are, those are very good. Those are very good.
I want to, you know, get, I gotta get those away from me. I think I'm going to eat another one.
Take those, take those. I think I'm going to go for another couple of those. Oh, did you,
did they open? It's like they all dump up. How about that red delicious apple?
What the fuck, man? Why do apples do this? Why do apples do this? This is like,
no, this is not from my mouth. Apples are so unappetizing, aren't they? All right,
that's good. That's fine. I just don't want that to be on camera because I don't want you guys to
look, you guys are going to be like grossed out. All right, what else we got? Snowcaps. They were
F. They were F. Another B. So opinions can change, right? Whopper time. So I have a Whopper. Whoppers
and Milk Duds are in the same category for me. And then these chocolate chip cookie dough bites
are going to be gross. Whoppers. Another old person candy. Another candy you'd eat if you're
over the age of like 50. Or if you go to the movie theater and you really just kind of don't
know what to order. And there's like 10 people in line behind you. So you just go,
Whoppers, I guess. And then you go, fuck, this is an easy F. I mean, they are. They were F for me
before. Here we go. Whoppers. It's like a malt, malted kind of chocolate ball, right? Let's see.
This says be an original. I feel like I'm kind of an original. They've already, look, they're
already speaking to me. They think I'm original. They think they said it. Like sandy. Kind of sandy.
Although it dissipates very, very, very quickly. Very. Suck on it first. Let it melt. Hold on.
Hold on. Oh, wow. That was a good, that was a good tip. Grandpa's passed out with like,
with his mouth? Uh, no. You're turning green. Jesus. Jesus. Now the sandy part is soft.
Geez. Oh, one more. One more, one more, one more. That's it. One more. Yeah, these are good. I was
eating them wrong the whole time, my whole life. I was eating these wrong my entire life. I was
just eating them and crunching them and going, ugh. You gotta let the flavors happen. You have to let
the flavors happen. It's a multi-layered candy. See, there's like this nice, it's a nice, it's
actually a pretty nice like smooth chocolate on the outside. The inside I don't like. But if you let
sit for a minute. Jesus, these are good. I'm very conflicted right now because these are like really
good. But are they though? They're kind of a little too buttery at the end. How do I really
feel? He's a C. He went from F to C. There's a little too buttery at the end. Oh, it's over Cantaloupe
for sure. Um, it's over Pepsi for sure. Pepsi is above Cantaloupe without a doubt. Wait a minute.
No, it's not. Cantaloupe is way above Pepsi. Yeah. Stop nitpicking. I mean, this whole stream is I'm
nitpicking my shitty opinions on my F tier candies. Watch out. Yeah, I'm gonna make sure I don't drop
any of this. Which I haven't, so that's good. Put that over here. All right, so we have a little,
we have only a couple more chocolates left. Very cool. I'm not looking forward to this because I
don't like cashews. I know I don't. Even though, yeah, you put cashews in F. Of course I did.
They taste, they're like the meat. They taste like meat. They're like the meat of the peanut world.
I'm not looking forward to doing that. Okay, so here we go. Um, stick that over there for now.
Right there is fine. All right, so now we got Milk Duds. Milk Duds, the problem I have with these is
after you put this in your mouth and you chew it up, you wanna, I made the reference two days ago.
You go watch that. I'll give you, I'll give you a minute. Go watch the VOD from a couple days ago
and you will see why I don't like these. 30% less? Oh no. Okay, I thought that said 30% less is in
the container. Like what? What do you mean 30% less? Like that's like something to advertise.
So if, when you eat a Milk Dud, it gets to a point, a part, a part. Whoa, whoa.
It gets to a point where they're just kind of chewed up gum and they look awful. Oh, these,
oh wait, are these supposed to look like this? Are they supposed to be like squished like that?
Are they not supposed to be like that? I don't think it's supposed to be like this.
These are crushed. Are these supposed to be like this?
These look like they've already been chewed. These are, these are supposed to look like that?
Are you sure? Don't they look like they've already been chewed? This is what they look like?
Is it? I thought they were supposed to be like circles. These are terrible.
And I mean absolutely awful. This might be the worst one of the night. These, I have to be fair,
right? These might be the worst of the night by a long shot. I would rather eat a full bar of mounds
than eat like another few of these. The texture looks, is kind of, they look off.
Texture doesn't operate. Do the same thing this time. Do, okay, do the same thing. Okay, okay.
Hold on. It looks like rat shit. These are huge. Those are like giant, those rats are huge. Oh my
God. Hold on. That's like a gigantic like sewer rat. It's a, they look kind of bad. These look
like they were left in the sun or something. All right, I'll do it the way you guys say it.
Here we go. Again, the old guy had to sit in the chair. Oh, hold on. Ooh, the chocolate is not
nearly as good as the Whopper chocolate. Not even close. This is more Tootsie Roll chocolate. Not
even close. It's still bad. Not even close. You know why I didn't want to do that? Because now I
have the caramel here. No. These are F. Doing that changed my mind. The Whoppers is not going to
change my mind. It's still bad. It's still F. Who eats these? I feel like it is like a BuzzFeed
video and I'm from like fucking like Britain or something. Who? No, they don't actually,
Americans eat these. Oh, fucking bollocks. No, why? Oh, it's disgusting. No, they're actually
eating these. Yeah, I feel like that's what I'm doing. Oh, the Paper Ruth is right. Okay,
I actually really don't like these. And we're making a lot of jokes. I mean, we're making a
ton of jokes, right? I'm trying to be fair because like they've been around for a long time. Who
makes these? Who actually? They're gluten-free and they're gluten-free. Hershey makes these.
It's just not good. It's just, I just don't like it. I really just don't. I'm trying to be very
fair and I just read their F. Oh, that was stuck. Oh, did you see that on camera? Okay, so now we
got Baby Ruth. What is in a Baby Ruth? Who makes Baby Ruth? Dry roasted peanuts, rich caramel and
smooth nougat. What is it? I didn't say that. I did not say that this is rat shit. Somebody else
did and I've read it. Baby Ruth. Here we go. I feel like this is kind of a, it's like a Snickers
that like went to the gym for like six months. Because like, look at this. This is, this is
full of, look at that. This is full of peanuts. A big what? Do not say cat shit. Don't say it.
Did you say it? Did you say cat shit? Oh, I said cat shit. I thought I was like pretending to read
cat shit. Wait, the gopher? Caddyshack? This looks like this shit in the pool. Oh, it's a Baby Ruth.
That's okay. It looks, we can't go into this with, this is bias. This looks like a Snickers
that has way too much stuff in it, but we'll find out. Here we go. Excuse me. I need total
silence please. I'm just like a dry ass Snickers. It's good. I feel like this has got more,
another thing is like, oh, if you're hungry, eat a Snickers. Who's eating Snickers when they're
hungry, right? I feel like this is what that commercial is actually saying. This has way more
peanuts than Snickers. This feels a little more like filling that, it's got way more peanuts.
I love Snickers and this just kind of just tastes like, you know what this is? You know
what this tastes like? This tastes like a homemade Snickers. Like there's like a YouTube video
showing how to make a Snickers and this is what it is. It's not bad, but it's not, it's not a
Snickers. That's what I want. I did just say it's a dry ass Snickers. I know. Why, I'm not going to,
no, you're doing it wrong. You have to, it's an energy bar Snickers. Yeah. All right. It's not an
F. It's like, I would eat this. I'm going to, I'm going to save this. That's like a C minus.
That's not a skill issue. It's a C minus. That is, oh, is it, is it above mounds? Oh,
fuck. This is hard. Mounds is, oh no, it's not. That's hard because they're both like, I feel
like I would rather eat a baby Ruth, but I feel like mounds tasted better. So I'd say it's below
amount, below amounts. All right. There's that. Uh, we also, that, we're, oh, we're at the end
of the chocolate here. We have cookie dough bites. Egg-free recipe. Our dough-licious dough. I can
always tell how, usually they have like a huge, like five paragraphs of being like cookie, cookie,
yummy, yummy, dough-licious, right? Like they have like a bunch of like bullshit in the back,
but they don't. This contains milk, soy, and wheat. It's also packaged in a facility that it has
peanuts, tree nuts, milk, solids, eggs, wheat, soy. They all, okay. Don't eat, don't eat these.
Don't, apparently don't eat these. Nobody can eat these. Ooh, look at that. That's actually pretty
cool. Nope. No other candy with that. No other candy like this came in a bag. That gets points.
Milk solids. They get points. Don't bat-chest me. That's it. Okay. This is like, I can carry this.
I don't want to like go. No, that's a, that gets points. Pollution? That was a weird smell. That
was actually kind of off-putting. I opened that bag and somebody fought it in my face. Cookie bites.
All right though. But yeah, I mean, come on. Yeah. Not that good though. My initial reaction was like
cookie dough. I love cookie dough. And then it was like, ooh, no. Yeah. Honestly, like I would just
rather not have any chocolate on this. They're good, but I feel like, I feel like I just want
cookie dough. It is a little weird. It's actually kind of good though. Yeah. Nice microplastics
you're eating. Okay. These are not F. You know where this would, these would actually be amazing?
Part of a sundae. I'm still eating. We're good. These are, the more I'm eating, the more I like it.
I picked it up and put it here. It's microplastic Andy. Microplastic Andy. It's a plastic bag. It's
not microplastics in the food. These are actually pretty good. I could imagine these frozen. Like
it says, try them frozen. That would be actually, wow. That would be, that'd be way better. It's
good. It was like, when I opened the bag, it was weird. It was almost like all like the, like the
smelly gas in here or whatever it is. Like it was just like boom right in my face. It's definitely
not a B. I don't know. Is it a C though? What's on C right now? Whoppers are better. Are these
better than a cantaloupe? I feel like that's unfair. Hey, but it's like a, hey, do you like
cookie dough more than you like cantaloupe? Yeah. Oh, okay. Well, that's not fair. It's,
cantaloupe's better. Better than Pepsi. Pepsi's better. I would, these could probably go up to
B in the freezer. Actually not that bad. Actually pretty good. The smell was a little weird. I would
definitely put this in the freezer and put it on ice cream probably later tonight. He's going to
get sick. The amount of candy that I'm eating is less than the amount of candy you ate at the last
Spider-Man movie. Okay. It's less than you ate at Spider-Man. I think that's all the chocolate.
There's nothing over here. There's nothing over here. All right. Now we're going to move into the
gross candy. By the way, if you, if you're just joining us and you don't know what's going on,
I saw somebody said, what the fuck is this shitty tier list? I am, I've taken every item. Well,
90% of every item that I said was F or high or low D. This is all the things that I've said are F
and I have to see if I got to go against my own bullshit. We're going to see opinions can change
in a long time and some of them have. Not for this though. Hot tamales. I don't know why anybody
eats these and like the fireball whiskey. Dude, fireball whiskey. It's fucking heinous. No, Otto's
not going to get any of this. Don't worry. Don't worry. I'm being careful. This is what a hot tamale
looks like. Oh, that smell. It's like a fucking Yankee candle. Yeah. This just smells like a
candle from Yankee candle. Hot tamale. That's what they are. They're kind of like Mike and Ike's,
but hot tamale. They're actually not bad. Don't do that. That was kind of enjoyable. That was
enjoyable. Damn. Really? That was enjoyable, but I don't want another one. I don't know how people,
okay, dude, please in the chat, tell me like, you're not eating all these. Like you sitting
there watching TV and just eating a fucking handful of these. No way, right? How many of
these are you eating? Everyone that's like, dude, hot tamales, bro. Whoa, fire. Like how many are
you eating? Because I feel like they just chew big bread. I feel like that was an enjoyable
experience, but I don't want to like eat handfuls of these. Maybe two at a time. These are better
than the hard candy fireballs, but I still don't really like them. My eyes. It tastes like big red.
Do I put these in F though? But I mean, I feel like they kind of have to stay in F because I
don't, I'm not going to eat anymore. Yeah. What's an F? Yeah, cutsy rose, honeydew,
fucking diet Mountain Dew. Would I rather, but I mean, I don't want to eat this though.
That was a fine experience, but you catching this? You catching this? Still trying it. Okay.
It's better than red delicious apple. It is? I said, what? I didn't say F. They're D. They're
better than an app. They're better than a red delicious apple though. Are they? I don't know.
It's hard because I would eat a red delicious apple. If somebody, if you were like here,
this is a red delicious apple. Eat this red delicious apple. I'd be like, okay,
I don't love it, but like I wouldn't eat more than two of these. Yeah, they're D. I don't,
I just, they just don't do it for me. Yeah. That's fair. That's fair. I don't, not a fan.
They are better than the balls though. Like the fire balls. They're better than those
because you know what? It's one and done. Like this kind of is like a breath mint to me.
Like, oh, I'm, I'm, I'm got a big meeting. I got to like eat like a hot tamale to get like
cinnamon burst breath, right? Like to me, that's a breath mint. I'm making sure you stay the whole
time. Oh, this is staying an F. This is staying an F. Ah, Swedish fish are bad. I can already
tell by how it feels. Here we go. Do you like Swedish fish? Yeah. They smell like, um, it
smells like melted candy or something. It smells like you like, you want to try it? It smells
like kind of like melted candy, right? Like melted. All right. Here we go. I know people
are pissed about this. Everyone was like, dude, you haven't tried it in like 10 years. Try it.
You'll like it. That's the whole purpose of the stream is to prove all you guys wrong
that this is F. Is it, is it an F? But don't say anything to that. I don't know. It smells
like a swimming pool. I don't know why. These are not Fs. Not even close. But again, the same
problem. Like I don't, I don't want to eat. This is this bag. I would eat like one of these and be
like, okay. That was like, I don't know. It's like, I don't want to eat this whole bag. What's the
serving size? Five pieces is a serving. I don't like, I just don't like, I'd rather have a gummy
bear. Why would you eat a bag of this? Please. Don't, don't tell them. Don't please. Really?
Are you trying to tell me that when you buy this little bag of Swedish fish, you're going to eat
five fish for the recommended doctor thing on the back. And then that's enough. What are you
talking about? Like you're going to sit there and eat until you don't want it anymore. Who does that?
Oh, oh hot tamales. Oh yeah, dude. Let me see. 16 pieces per serving. I can't have more than 16.
16 pieces. I wouldn't want five for these. 16. That's a lot. Yeah. Guess what? Do you know how
many cookies a serving of Oreos is? Don't look. Yes. What is a serving of Oreos? Yes. Yes. Don't
look it up. Okay. Yeah. Like two or three or three. All right. All these, all these Andes in here.
I'm not even, I'm not even going to give you a nickname. I'm going to call you Andy. All these
Andes in here that pretend like they don't go to the Oreo sleeve and get as many as they can fit
holding like this comfortably with the glass of milk. Please. Oh, I'm going to take two cookies.
Nope. You're, excuse me. You're going to fit as many as you can. Oh, that was gross. I just spit
a little bit up. No, she thought I was puking. No, I'm just talking and being rude and like not
finishing the food in my mouth. You go like this. It's like one, two, three, four, five seconds,
five. And then you eat, you know, nobody eats two. I, I never eat two Oreos ever. I usually eat like
between three and five. Didn't change my mind. Those are better than Tootsie Rolls. What's,
what's, okay. What is above F and low D? I don't know. Because a red delicious apple is the barrier
to get to D. Okay. I'd rather eat a red delicious apple than a Swedish fish. I don't, people
like hate me. That's fine. Is that I'd rather eat a red delicious apple as a candy. But aren't these,
I just, I would rather have like the Haribo gummy bears. There is a red Haribo gummy bear that's
better than this. Right. Look, I'm not telling you that how you need to feel. I'm not saying,
Hey dude, I don't like Swedish fish. So fuck you. Don't clip that. One minute, one minute, one minute,
one minute, one minute, one minute, one minute, one minute, one minute, one minute, one minute,
I never said that. All I'm saying is that I find them to be off putting. I just don't really like
them. This is like, I just, I don't, I couldn't eat more than one or two of those. All right,
let's keep going. Oh right. This is okay. This is going to suck. This is the Bean Boozled game.
I think I can just pick them out. It should be easy. I said that, okay. I said popcorn jelly
beans were dog shit and everyone freaked out. You cannot just buy an in one day in 120. Remember
this is like literally two days ago. We talked about doing this. I couldn't just buy popcorn.
I couldn't buy popcorn flavor jelly beans anywhere. So the popcorn flavor jelly beans are in here,
but half of them are rotten egg. This might be a little tricky. There's one right here. Is there
a way to tell? Like, can I smell it? I don't know. It's either going to be rotten egg or
buttered popcorn. I couldn't get them anywhere. Somebody said, what's the difference? I want that
person to be very important for a minute. Cut into it and smell it. Okay. I think I can do with this.
Huh? Somebody said they had the dog food one and it stayed in their mouth for days.
This is buttered popcorn. I got it. Okay. Oh, it smells like buttered popcorn. Why? This shit
was made in a goddamn laboratory. Buttered popcorn. This is accurate. Here we go. Is it,
or is this a rotten egg? I don't know. I hope, I think it's buttered popcorn. Is it a rotten egg?
I don't know. I can't, I can't tell. I actually, I can't tell. No, you're good. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. No, I think this is rotten egg. No, it's a buttered popcorn. Why? Who eats this
shit? Oh my God. This is no, I kind of, I need to know if that was rotten egg. I like, I kind of
like what I know. My brain is like telling me, Polly's right here and she's like, maybe you
should cut it first and don't eat it right away. Why? Yeah. Cause like, I'm going to have like
rotten egg breath. I would know. Somebody said just eat a handful. That'd be so fucked up. You'd
probably have like, you'd probably have like a fucking like mental breakdown. It's not designed
for that. Eat a handful. I'm kind of curious. I'm curious. Let's go. It tastes like hamburger meat.
It tastes like hamburger meat. It tastes like raw hamburger meat. Auto filled in. What did you,
what did you do? Auto ate a cookie. Okay. Buttered popcorn is F. That honestly tastes like,
it tastes like raw hamburger meat. I have no idea. What was the, what was the possibilities?
Cause I know I had like a, it was a, it was like two blues, pink. Oh, what the fuck? What's wrong
with these people? Why would you make that? Now I know what it is. Band-aid, an old band-aid with
blood on it. Oh, okay. No, I'm okay. So that was, that was barf, pomegranate, old band-aid,
rotten egg, liver and onions, toothpaste and berry. It just literally tastes like raw
hamburger meat. I'm okay. No, I guess it's all gone. We'll do a palate cleanse. I don't know why,
why people do this. I know it's like, it's like content to do this. And I'm not just talking about
like streams or YouTube. This is like friend content where everyone goes like, well, what is
it? And it's like, everyone like runs away and shit. But like, no fucking just like read a book,
go fucking LARP somewhere. You know what I mean? Go like LARPing. Don't, don't do this.
But play like fucking N64. All right. Well, the butter popcorn is F and I think it might be really
low. What, what, what is in F right now? Okay. Swedish, Swedish fish are way better than butter
popcorn. I know I hate them. My opinion does not change, but I mean, this would be like fun,
friend content, baby. Worse than Twitzy Roll. There's way worse than a honeydew melon. In fact,
you know what? I think honeydew, honeydew, I mean, this is like a bunch of other, the candy shit,
but I mean, of course I would rather eat a honeydew melon than eat a buttered popcorn.
Don't say it's worse than milk does. But what did this person say? He said, look, man, if your
perception of the candy is already at F tier, I don't think a half ass taste test is going to
change the scoring wildly. Tell that to Whoppers. Tell that to Red Delicious Apple. Tell that to
Baby Ruth. Some of these have changed dramatically. Some of these have actually changed dramatically.
Whopper was at F and now I put it all the way up to like C and B. Would you rather eat a honeydew
melon or a bloody bandaid? Well, you know, I'm not so sure. All right, here we go. A lot of people
have been waiting for Fun Dip. Okay. Fun Dip. I put Fun Dip at F or D because it's been a long time.
It's been a long time. I just remember being like, and this is the sour kind. So Fun Dip is S and
that's why this is why I'm doing this. It's all that was available at Walmart. Let's get a stick.
We're going to do stick only first and I'm going to write that. How the fuck are you supposed to
open this? You can't bring this to the office. It starts at D, literally starts at D. How are you
supposed to eat this? How am I going to eat this? How do I do this? How am I supposed to eat this?
I think it's like, okay, there we go. Yep. Okay. Fun Dip executive. How are you supposed to do this?
Look, I'm like, I can't even get into this. But okay, here it is. We're going to try this
by itself. I like the smell. Hmm. Okay. I remember these being a lot chalkier than it is.
You just keep the stick, man. You don't need anything else. Do they just sell Fun Dip sticks?
I would rather just eat this. Yeah, this is like very, this is very nice. Bite it. No, don't. All
right, here we go. We're going to start with the Strawberry Smackerie Dew Dip, then the Watermelon
Wimmo Dip, and then the Tartastic Mystery Dip. Strawberry Watermelon Mystery. Come on, Gwen.
Why am I using crochet scissors? Okay, here we go. This is Strawberry Smackerie Dew. You go like
this, right? I'm doing it right? That's good. Fuck. Fuck. That's good. It is good. It's not too sour
either. I thought it was going to be like, ooh, Warheads. This is, this is fantastic. And they
give you three flavors. I'm actually excited. This is, all right. I was wrong. I was wrong. You know
this is because I was like, oh, like kids eat this. You know what I mean? Like, oh, Fun Dip for kids.
I'm like, why would I, why would I buy this? The strawberry one. I don't fucking need to open the
rest of it. Fun Dip Executive. Okay. All right. I think I got, I got a taste for that. And they
give you two sticks. The value here is actually, it's phenomenal. I'm actually kind of sad. I'm
not going to be able to eat this all. Wait, hold on. Let's check. The mystery flavor could, wait,
the mystery flavor could be barf. We don't know. There could be rotten egg. That's incredibly
enjoyable. I wish I was fucking making this up. I don't, I really don't want to like this. This is
watermelon. I mean, it's just, it's, it's, it's just phenomenal. It's a perfect amount of sweetness.
It's a perfect amount of like sugar. I always thought this was like just an absolute sugar bomb.
That this tastes light. This is, this tastes light to me. Fuck. I thought I hated these. I really
thought I hated this. It's light. It is just sugar. Mix them together. We're not doing that yet.
Throw a Band-Aid in here. Imagine like, I don't know. I didn't know what it tastes like with a
Band-Aid. Okay. Good. What about the mystery? Fuck. I would want to just eat these. Be careful
with these. Okay. There's nothing here for you. I haven't dropped anything. He's good. Okay. This
is blue. This is blue. That's the best one yet. That's the best one yet. What? What did they say?
Pregnancy test? I can't even eat it now. Oh, why'd you do that? This was S. This was S. You,
I was going to put it in S. And now I'm like, there's a pregnancy test in my mouth. What the
fuck? Okay. No, don't do that either. Don't do that either. Okay. Very important. Very, I feel
like I'm going like frost-eyed right here. Okay. Very important. This is, oh, you ruined it. You
ruined it. It was going to be like A+. All right. Let's mix them. We're going to do strawberry.
Okay. Here we go. We're going to do, we're going to do not pregnant mixed with pregnant. And then
we're going to do, um, I don't know, UTI. Oh no. I'm trying to think of other things you piss on.
I guess, well, you piss, like I'm thinking of pee. Like, yeah, but like pregnancy tests, like,
okay, what else is a test? It's just candy. It's just candy. It's candy. It's candy. It's candy.
Why did I say that? I don't know. Cause you said pregnancy test. You said that I was sitting here
enjoying the mystery flavor of sunny delight. That's not what this is. The mystery flavor of
fun dip. And I hear pregnancy test and I'm like, okay, well gross. Well, let me one up. You hear
that. They're all fantastic. This is S. I was thinking of what else, like for the thing like
these, you notice you don't pee on a COVID test. You don't pee on a COVID test. All right. Let's
bite the stick. Let's see how it feels. Tastes like marshmallows. Good. I was wrong. I apologize
profusely. I would keep eating this. I would. In fact, I might, I might actually seal this up.
That's S. I was wrong. I put it in F and it was wrong. I was completely and totally incorrect.
Fun dip is S tier. I'm sorry. I apologize. Should I just get it out of the way? Should I get it out
of the way now? Hey, how are you? Jeremy985 here. Make sure you hit that bell and stay for a while
to the end of the video. I'm going to check these out. These are your favorite. I said they were F.
Hey, hit that bell and check it out. Stay tuned. Probably tomorrow. I've never, I felt like I'm
going to hate those. That's going to be the big reveal. All right. Mike and Ike's. We're actually,
there's not that much left. We're doing good. How long, how long is the streaming going for?
Lower left of the OBS window should be like in the very, very lower left. Like the bottom, like,
like the task manager. Is it not there? Hour and 49. All right. Let's go. I have 30k viewers right
now. What are you doing here? All right. These are original. I know that like, dude, get the tropical
ones. Get this, the, the other ones. This is original Mike and Ike, original fruits,
original fruit flavors. These are the originals. Waiting for Trolli. Yeah. Make sure to hit that
bell. All right. Which one do I eat first? People were pissed that I didn't like these.
Remember it was like, dude, you have to eat the Trolli, please. There's a lot of reds in here.
Red. Okay. I'm going for red. Red. Red. No. Contestant medicine. No. No. You have to,
it's only fair if you try each one. Yeah, this is, that was bad. It tastes like kind of like,
it kind of tastes like medicine. Eat the green one. Well, hold on. I got, I'm all right.
Got orange here. Oh, I'm doing fine. You're gonna, you're gonna have diarrhea. So what?
Do orange. Way better than red. Way better. That was actually very good. I have to be fair though.
I'm going to rate these individually and then average the score. Red. F. Orange. B. Orange was
a B. We have F. We have B. Is yellow. A. We've got an F. We have a B. We have an A. Yellow is A.
I love that like tart lemon flavor. Oh, hell yeah. Okay. We only got two more. We've got, what are
they? Oh, red is cherry. That, I thought it was going to be strawberry. Okay. So that might have
fucked up my brain. This is, this is strawberry. I thought red was strawberry. All right. Let's see.
Let's see what strawberry. That was A. B. F. What about, what about this one? This tastes like it's
not good. What? It's a very specific strawberry, like fake flavor, and it's not good. That was
the worst one. F. Green. Green. You're gonna have to save it here. Green. Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Eventually gave his lightsaber to Luke. Luke had a blue lightsaber. You fucking lost me. You lost me.
I thought that was going to be sour apple. I was waiting for green apple and I got lime. I was
waiting for like a sour tart green apple, like Jolly Rancher flavor. Lime. I'm not going to eat
them all at once. Oh, no. I don't like it. Actually, it's all right. Oh, that's actually
kind of good. All right. What we got? A. B. B. A. B. B. F. F. What's that average to? Is that a C?
A. B. B. F. F. Did he already do the Bean Boozle? Yeah, dude. Rewind. I puked all over the place.
We had to redo the whole thing. So that's a high, that's a C? Yeah, they're all right. I was probably
unfair. I'll be really honest. I'd rather eat this than any of those. Like, whoppers were good,
but like I feel like, no, maybe a below whopper. That was, I was unfair. I said, you know, I said
they were boring and they actually are not boring. It was like a burst of flavor. I don't know why in
my brain the flavor profile of these was way more diluted than that, what just was. Did they change
the recipe? Because that was, that was good. Some of those were really, really good. The lemon one,
perfect. Orange was nearly good. Yeah, that was good. That was fine. I would eat the rest of these.
I will. Let's put it in the storage unit over here. All right. It's getting there. Here come dots.
I don't want to do a handful. I don't want to eat. I'm trying to just do like one or two at a time.
They taste like colors. Yeah. Dots. Everyone says F. Everybody does, but I have to be fair.
Oh, okay. What happened? What happened? Tootsie makes these. What happened? What else does Tootsie
make? Man, I just don't, I don't think I like anything from the Tootsie Roll company. Do I?
Do I like anything from Tootsie Roll? I love dots. I have not eaten these in 10 fucking years.
Let's find out. Tootsie Pops. Yeah, but I know Tootsie Pops are good. I feel like Tootsie needs
more to be good than just be a Tootsie. All right. Here we go. Dots. Sorted fruit flavored gum drops.
Okay. Give it a try. This is old people. Um, I don't think, I don't think so. I don't know
very many old people that would eat these. All right. Let's give it a try. What do I get first?
This is pink it looks like. Oh no. It just smells like, it smells like plastic. Like it doesn't smell
like candy. This is apocalypse food. Like this is, this is like currency. Like I've been like a
thousand years and like the apocalypse happens. This is like, this is apocalypse food. God. The
thing is this is apocalypse food, right? But I feel like these, I feel like this, these will last
like a hundred years. I mean it's, it's, it's, it is what it is. It is what it is. It's exactly
you know what, you know what you're getting. You know what it is. It's just like a slimy,
like waxy F tier candy. Last, this is lasting a very long time though. I could just sit here like
this and it's okay. That's what I'm saying. This is apocalypse food. Like you could suck on a dot
like while you're like going out and looking for supplies and shooting at the zombies and shit.
Like this will last like the four hours. Like let me just say it like this. Go, go, go, go, go,
you know what I mean? Like everybody like hates these, right? Everybody talks shit about these,
but I mean these, the only purpose for these is to put on the top of gingerbread houses.
And then you go like, and then eat like the frosting. I mean it's just a, it's just like
a gumdrop. Does everything have to be flashy with like sour fun dip with like three flavors
and one of them's a mystery loot box. I mean it's just, it's just candy. It's just like regular ass
candy and you can just suck, I mean you suck on for, they last a long time. I think it's okay.
I mean I'm going to put them in F because I think they belong there, but I mean I don't,
this is like, this is like an American staple. You know what I mean? Apple pie, McDonald's,
Dots. Like it's, it's like American old candy. It's a D. It's D. Who sucks on Dots?
Whoa! Whoa, hold on. Yeah! You're supposed to chew them? I like my way, way better. You're
supposed to chew them? Yeah, hold on. All right, hold on. Hold on, hold on, hold on. No. I mean
it's just these. These are the same except this one texturally is better and I think the flavors
are better. They're the same exact candy to me. They're like, this one's just better. I mean maybe
if you don't like the kind of hard outside, this is just a soft outside version of Mike and Ike's.
I think they're D for me. They're D minus. I'm not spending any more time on Dots. They're better
than Hot Tamales. Whoa, wait a minute. Yeah, they're better than Hot Tamales. Are they? No,
they're not. What's, what's in front of that? Yeah, they're worse than Almond Joy, but they're okay.
All right, everybody's waiting. Everybody's waiting to see what the streamer has to say about Trolley.
Trolley. Yeah, the Swizzlers too, but those are F. Trolley? I've never had these. I just assumed
they were F because I don't like gummy worms because gummy worms are for children. Fuck it,
let's go. I'm doing it right now. I got a lot of shit the other day saying that I would put these
in F or D. I'm ready. Let's go. I almost dropped it. Here we go. Moment of truth for Trolley.
I didn't mean to. They don't smell good. They smell very fake. All right, I was told to eat
the pink and blue one first. Here it is. Here we go. Let me cleanse the palette. Okay, here we go.
They're good, but they're not S. Don't say that. Green, green and orange coming up. I thought these
are going to be way more sour, like a Sour Patch Kid. That part is fantastic. Once, once all the,
all the sand comes off though, I don't know, they become a weird, I don't know. That was an A.
That was an A minus. That one. And if that's the best, if that's what you're telling me is the best
trolley, I'm not too excited about the rest. That one's all right. The orange part I don't
really like that much. The green part is good. Stop chewing them. Stop, don't chew them. I thought
I was supposed to chew, I thought I was supposed to swallow them. You want me to just like, like a,
what am I, a bird? Am I a fucking baby bird? Do I look like, do I got a beak? Do I have a beak?
Okay, that was all right. That was a B. You know, but hold on, here's the thing.
I thought these were huge. The reason why I didn't ever buy these is because I thought
they were like these like gross, like, like, like six, seven inch long things. I didn't think they
were this little. I thought they were like going to be these curly Q like blah. I didn't know they
were little. Why are you chewing for so long? I'm just chewing the food. Why would I think that?
Gummy worms are long, aren't they? Red yellow is not good. Okay, well trolley's the best. Get trolley.
Except only eat one of the colors in there, not the other like 35%. Okay, so we're gonna,
okay, after I do the candy, we'll probably clean up a little bit. So after I do these next two
candies, we're gonna clean up. We're gonna move some of the stuff out of the fridge.
We'll do our chips. I'm very excited about this. I'm gonna piss a lot of you off.
All right, here we go. That was bad. Yeah, that was way too harsh. It was like a way too acidic
in the first second. No, I don't, they're all, they're good. That first one was fantastic.
Trolley, nice try. Nice try. It's a B. Everybody thought it, no, that's not an S. All right,
the part on the outside. Okay, if this was a stick, if this was a stick and I could suck it and it
was a stick, I would like it. Why are these even here? Why do I even have these? Apple jacks? Like,
I'm gonna eat a bowl of cereal right now? No, I'll eat these for breakfast fucking someday.
Apple jacks are fucking C. I don't even need to eat them. Oh, we got like red too. All right, okay.
What is um, oh, orange slices. It's cafeteria food.
I didn't want to buy a box of apple jacks though, man. Like, I'm not gonna buy a whole box.
These are the orange slices. Do I even really need to eat one of these? I feel like I'm gonna
fucking hate it. Find out. Orange slices are really good. Yeah, I know, more or less the candy.
All right, orange slices. Oh, these are awful looking. They're hard. They've got a stiffness
to them that I cannot describe on camera. It's Walmart brand. Do the, does the brand really
matter? Does the brand matter for these? They all were made in like 1950. Orange slices. Here we go.
Oh, this smells like a Christmas decoration. Who's gonna buy this as a gas station? It turns into this,
what was it? The brand matters. It's great value. What's wrong with great value brand?
There's an aftertaste here that is very bad. It's a very bad aftertaste. I look sick.
I'm just sitting here like, they kind of look like slugs. Doesn't the packaging,
it looks like fucking slugs. Like, larva. All right, the initial bite was fine.
Uh, after that though. No, these are F. I don't need to take another bite.
But like, what do I, I could decorate a fucking cake with these or something.
That's low F. What do we have for uh, for low F? I think these are the very bottom.
These are below milk dots. These are fucking awful. Those are very bad. Does it really matter? Does
a brand actually matter? Are you going to clean up? Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's only one more candy.
And it's Twizzlers. I'll do, I'll take one quick bite. I know you like these, right? I'll try,
I'm going to try a little bit because I have to do it. I can't, those were very bad. These smell bad
too. Yes, they do. They smell like a, like a new coat. Like it smells like, it smells like new shoes.
Why? Why does it smell like a new pair of sneakers? Like a new shoes, like new coat.
Like what the fuck? It's like, it smells like new clothing. It smells like new clothes.
Why are you, I'm just saying it smells like new clothing. New car. Yeah. No, F. Oh my god. No,
that's just bad. They just don't taste good. That's, they're, okay, they're better than the
orange slices. The only thing to do with Twizzlers is this. It's, it's above, they're F. The peelable
Twizzlers are better, way better. No, I don't, yeah, they're F. I knew my mind wasn't going to
change on those at all. Drink the soda? Yeah. I'm not going to ruin a perfectly good Coke.
Why would it, is that what people are actually saying to do that? Wait, this is a, this is a real
thing? What? You drink soda out of a Twizzler. Who does this? You're saying it has to be a Coke,
right? Never doing that again. Never doing that ever again. No, I'm not doing that ever again.
All right. There you go. There's your candy. I'm going to, I want to clean up a little bit.
We still have, oh, there's still a decent amount. There's like six or seven more things to do. We
have the chips, which I'm only going to eat like one chip, so we'll be fine. I'm going to go pee.
I'm going to go piss out all this like sugar that I just ate. Uh, yeah, we'll go burp. We're good.
All right. We'll go BRB. I'll be right back. We're going to do chips, clean up a little,
and we'll keep going. Be right back. Okay. Hello. I am back. He's dead. All right. So,
all the sugary stuff is gone. I said that Frank's Red Hog was bad. Oh, I got a little spoon here.
Okay. Well, whatever. All right. So, here's how it's going to work. No, it's fine. It's fine. Oh,
there's play. Okay. Oh, I'm going to do this last because it'll ruin my palette. Chug it. He thinks
these chips don't have sugar. Again, if you're joining us and you don't know what's going on,
people have been joining going, this, what is he doing? This is stupid. This guy sucks.
Listen. So, over the years, I've made tier lists of food, candies, snacks, sodas, and I got everything
that I said was F because I am being an asshole and I'm being biased and I'm going to just face
my own bullshit. Do I actually think sourdough is F? I don't eat this. And we've seen a few
turnarounds. We've seen a couple of major turnarounds. So, let's go. Uh, let's go with this.
Here you go. Here you go, internet. Here you go. Takis, internet. Can't wait. Takis. Oh, dude,
I love Takis. Takis crusted fucking mozzarella sticks. Takis mac and cheese. Oh, dude, imagine
if you ate a Takis and put a macaroni and cheese on it. Here you go, internet. Here you go. Let's go.
Takis. I, I, Trader Joe's makes a version of this that is way better. And look, I just picked up one.
Gotta put it down. I can't go back to work. I have to wash my hands. I ate one. I put one in my mouth.
Yeah, I knew it. You know what it is? Takis? Let's have one more. I would like these more.
I can taste the MSG. MSG has a very specific flavor. It's on Doritos. Like these, like it's
that like Dorito, like umami MSG flavor. I can taste the MSG. Like I know what it tastes like.
It's that very deep, almost like Dorito like flavor. Um, no, I'll be all right. Do they taste
good? I mean, they're, they're, I got the stupid ass blue ones too. Um, you're out of your fucking
mind. MSG is tasty. MSG has that very, like that salty kind of deep like flavor taste. Use chopsticks.
I don't. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let me be, I gotta be fair. These are extreme,
by the way. Be careful. These are extreme. No, it's a fucking potato chip. Relax. I don't like,
I put them in F because you know what? I'm a contrarian dick. And when everybody on the
internet loves something, I go, well, you see, I'd rather have the ones from Trader Joe's.
They're a, see, how am I going to shake your hand? They're a high C. They're a C. They're
okay. It's just like, MSG, I can taste it. I would put them definitely above Red Delicious Apple.
What, you don't want me to do like the thing where I go like worst hand 2022? What the fuck
are you talking about? There's not even a category. Did you drink all this? Did you drink that?
Chat, I know you did. All right. So this is, oh no, I've got talky fingers. Oh, Cheetos, man. Whoa.
Hold on. Dude, I like, my favorite part about eating a potato chip or a corn chip is feeling
like you were blocking yourself from having a bloody nose. Oh, I love it. I love like the,
it's like, oh, I had a bloody nose and I'm running to the bathroom. Like, I love that. It's really
interesting. Here's the funny spaceship blue ones. What's the difference? What's the difference?
What's so funny? Blue ones are better. Do they have MSG? They do. All right. So hold on. These
are blue heat talkies. I put these in F and already, like, I've already, what the fuck, man?
What are these supposed to taste like? What are these supposed to taste like? This is the same.
Yeah. These are like, this is, why make them, why make blue ones? You want to try? They taste
like the same. Is it just like a marketing thing where they're just blue and it's like LOL or
something? I mean, I, how do you feel? You like these? I didn't think I would. I feel like if I
say, oh, wow, there's a difference. Everyone's going to be like, read the ingredients. They're
identical. And I look like an idiot. It's like, it's like, I was fucking drywalling. These are
white boy spice level. What? Cause I coughed? What are you talking about? What? I like coughed for a
second. I need you to hold on. Oh wait, thumbnail. Which one's better? Blue or red? Blue or red?
Which one's better? And, and, and put a bunch of noodles in my mouth. The red ones are like
more acidic. The blue ones are kind of better, but why are they blue? Just make them fucking green.
Why? That would be stupid too. Just make them red. Just call them like talkies, like salt and
pepper or something. I don't know. Hold on a minute guys. I just had a snack. I have to wash
my fucking whole body. I take a shower. Oh, was somebody, did somebody get into the talkies? Oh
no, man. Sure. Don't tell anybody. I'm trying to be sneaky about it. All right. So what's next?
What's next? Oh, okay. Blue is better than red. Uh, but blue, it comes down a half a letter grade
cause they're blue and I don't like it. It's stupid. It's artificial coloring. Uh, red is
artificial coloring too. They both see, but put blue, put them at the same. Who cares? Yeah,
it sounds like it matters. Mom cleaning up after her child. I get blue. I only want to eat blue
foods. No, you can't see blue food. Yes, I can. Oh dude, Frank's red hot. Let's go. All right.
The spice, let's just stay with it. So I put those in F, but they're, they're actually not.
This I have, oh, this is F. I always think this is F. I'm going to end up using this for a fucking
stew or something, right? Eventually. But do I actually think this is that bad? You're an iPad
baby. Okay. Here we go. Ooh, what is this? It's not hot. Frank's, the whole thing about Frank's
red hot is it's heat flavor. It's not like hot, hot. No. If I, if I want to, what's that show
where the guy's like, Hey, so on Instagram, what's it called? Hot ones. And then it's just like,
Oh, we got Frank's red hot here. It'd be like, dude. Okay. Here we go. Frank's red hot. How many
Skullville units? Oh boy. Oh boy. 40. It's all right. It's okay. Where's my ice cream? It's all
right. It's just that I, I would rather have, you know what? Okay. Buffalo sauce like this,
it's the default, just buffalo flavor sauce, which is nothing. There's something wrong with it.
It tastes good. Do you want to try it? Oh, I thought you'd come to try it. I was like,
Oh boy, here it comes. No, it's not hot at all. Okay. I want blue foods and I want milk.
It's got a nice flavor. Sriracha is better. Sriracha is a fucking F. I actually like wanted
to have Sriracha up here, but I was like, I actually hate that and I won't eat it. Um,
the initial bite of Frank's is why you do it. It's the flavor is there. They get,
they became famous with having Frank's red hot be the default buffalo flavor on everything.
And it's, it's, it's good. Actually it's not even that bad. It's really not bad.
It's just so easy to say the thing that is the default sucks. Oh no, it's not this sauce that
I found in a fucking antique shop, right? But I think this is, this is C. I think it belongs at C.
More hot sauces. You want me to do a hot sauce taste test with a Serrano hot sauce, Serrano chili.
I mean, Tabasco is S. I don't even need to taste it. Tabasco is literally S tier.
Tapatio, um, not for another day, another day. I'm going to do it because I feel like I'm going to
have diarrhea later. I don't want it to be like that included. Um, because if I had like, you know,
15 different candies and like 20 different like snacks, I don't want to like have it coated with
like a painful sauce. Um, Tabasco sucks. Get out of here. Get out. Tabasco sucks. Get out. Get out.
Tabasco sucks. Get out. Sriracha is amazing. Your opinion is okay. I just don't like it.
I would rather have Tabasco. Tabasco green sauce. Oh, if you never had it before, it's perfect.
All right. That, we know that. Bugles. I mean, it's kind of hard to put a hot sauce above like
a red delicious apple, right? That doesn't really work that way. Cholula. Tapatio actually I like
more than Cholula. I could, wait, you want to face the bullshit with other stuff too? We can.
Oh, I thought there was a grease on it. I thought there was like, I thought I touched it and it was
like a grease stain. Do you want me to face the bullshit with other stuff? All right. These are
Bugles. These automatically start at A, B because you can do this. That one's broken. I can't.
Never mind. Back down to C to start. Okay. All right. That was, I was unfair. Okay. Wow.
Then what? I gave this F? I gave this F before? Did I put, did I actually put Bugles in F?
I can't believe it. These are very good. Your fingers are too big? No, they changed the recipe.
You can't put your fingers in them anymore. Okay. These, I had an idea of what the flavor was of
Bugles. You know when you have that kind of dream memory of like the tasting a certain way
and it tastes like that in real life, but it's like a 10 times better version than what you
remembered because I would, these were like, ew, that gross Bugle flavor. But now that I eat them,
these are really good. I'm very surprised. These are just Fritos, but lighter and like more delicious.
Shit, man. This is bad. These were, these are going from F to A. These are really good.
America's number one finger, finger hat. Let's put that false advertising. False advertising.
I can't fit my finger in there. False advertising for kids. Adults aren't supposed to care about
that. That's true. You're right. All right. Coke is an S. Bring it down to A. Oh, fun difference
is S. Holy shit. Yeah. These are an A. Yep. This is an A. I could eat this whole bag. I could eat
that whole bag. Bugles. What a surprise. What a twist. What a twist. Oh my God. In the beginning
of the video, you, you guys have no idea the twist. Like I changed like four F's.
Keep watching to find out what they are. Chili cheese Fritos.
I know. These are dog shit. And they have Bugle, they have Bugleberries in the title.
Okay. Chili cheese Fritos. It's not that chili cheese Fritos taste bad. They're just too intense.
They're just like too much. Fritos are fine, but it's just like, it's like too. Remember when they
did the like ketchup and mustard fucking potato chips. It's just like, that's, I don't want that.
It's like too much weird shit on it. Oh my God. These are F. F. F. Oh my God. These are bad.
These are fucking terrible. No way. It's like barbecue mixed with like chili. I don't know.
These are bad. It's just like way too intense and deep. It's just too much. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. You know, sometimes you just get one that has way too much powder on it and you,
and it just tastes like a fucking bowl of chili for like a quarter of a second. And I don't like
it. You didn't shake the bag first. Oh, I missed. They're uh, I don't like them, but I keep eating
them. They're like a C. They're not F. They're just like too much. It's just too intense.
Too many different flavors. Just too many flavors. There's just too many flavors and too much dust.
You got to hear the crunch. Oh yeah. You're right. Crunch test. Crunch test. Crunch test. You're
right. Crunch test. I'm going to say eat the one on the ground. Was that the one from the ground?
No. Um, this is C. C. All right. Washing hands. Christy, also keep in mind, anything that is D plus
or higher, I'm going to eat the whole bag. So like these chili cheese fritos, they're going to get
rolled up and I'll eat the whole thing. I'll eat the whole thing. I know that she'll have some too.
Okay. Uh, what do we got? Oh, kettle cooked sea salt and uh, salt and vinegar chips.
Farm to smiles. Farm potatoes. Real potatoes. Real farmers. Delicious chips.
Carefully crafted for you. Shake the bag. Oh yeah. This, everyone had talked a lot of shit.
These are God tier to a lot of you. S tier. God tier. I think that salt and vinegar chips are
gross. I haven't eaten them in five years, at least. But I'm going to do it for you right now
and you're going to get a library action. And make sure you stay tuned to find out what I felt
about the trolleys. They smell pretty good. You want some? So you, you really like these.
Oh, you haven't, have you ever had them? Have you ever had salt and vinegar chips? All right, here
we go. They just taste like chips. That's something wrong with them. Like, yeah, I mean, but it tastes
like, it tastes like chips where there's something wrong with them. I would rather just have them be
salt. Are they F though? I feel that's maybe not fair. I have a pregnant palate. Excuse me?
Oh. Oh, how do you figure I have a pregnant palate? What do you mean? I'm not eating like
ice cream and hot dogs. What are you talking about? They're D. These are D. I just, I would
rather than just be sea salt. Yeah. I want these to be sea salt. They just put a bunch of like
sour stuff all over them. They're D. They leveled up from F, but no, not into it. The bugles though.
Holy shit. I want to eat more of those. All right, here we go. A couple of years ago,
what I'm enjoying. A couple of years ago, I put sun chips in F and I literally lost like
5,000 subs in a day. I lost 20,000 followers. I lost a thousand subs over the course of like
every day because people said that it's insane that you put those there. People said it's crazy
that you don't like these. And even my girlfriend is like, I don't understand that. They're just
plain. It's like a corn chip, but like I was plain. It's just too plain. They're way too
plain for me. Way too plain. Yeah, but there's a middle ground. There's like a way too much.
And then there's like bland nothing flavor. You got to have the perfect amount of spice.
These, I don't know. We'll see because I put those there too. Those are in F. They're just,
they kind of just taste like nothing. They're just a kind of weird like grain. But again,
I have not had a sun chip in at least five, at least five years. First of all, the bag is wicked
loud. You're going to wake up your roommate in college, bro. Boring ass bullshit. No, yeah.
Bugles are better. No, these are, these are fucking, why are you like these? These are just
better. These are way better. These are better in every way. They're like 100% whole grain.
It's 100% whole grain. But like, this is just like the corn flakes of chips. I mean in a bag
of corn flakes. 100% whole grain, heart healthy. No artificial flavors are preservatives. And 30%
less fat than regular potato chips. You know what else has 30% less fat than regular potato chips?
Baked lays. Which baked lays are S tier. Baked lays are omega S tier. This is cope and seething.
The garden veggie. I mean these were very highly rated too. I'm telling you, I'm not,
I'm just giving my real opinion. Are these F? Am I going to piss everybody off by actually eating
these and saying they're F on camera? How do you get the raw, these are, these are just like
sun chip original flavor. I want garden salsa. I want garden salsa. No, this is, this is,
this is it. I don't want another one. F. Not into it. All right. French onion. These were very
highly rated. Incredibly highly rated. Smells much better. This is French onion garden grain.
All right. 10 times better. I would say a hundred times better. Remember 2,000 people left.
Yeah. Enjoy, enjoy, enjoy your fucking like bland ass chips. These are actually pretty good. These
are really good. That's what I mean. You gotta give me something. I don't want to just eat like
fucking corn. Is it S? What were these A? Ingredients. Demented yellow, de-germed yellow corn meal.
Yeah. These suck. They don't. These are better. This is, let me show you on camera. These are made
from the same material. These are made from the same material. This one was made by From Software.
This one was made by, what's a game company that everybody hates? This one was made, can I say,
but I better be careful. This one, this one was made by, I was gonna say, what's like a,
I don't know, this one was made by Blizzard, Ubisoft. No, Capcom makes good games. I didn't
really like Watch Dogs Legion, so I'm gonna say Ubisoft. I didn't, that game was not very good.
This one was made by From Software. This one was made by a game company that you don't like,
whatever that is. The same material. These are good. Why am I so afraid to say that when I like
yell about these, how much I don't like some of these games? They, this does it right. Not a whole
lot of sweetness. Not a whole lot of spice. Not a whole lot of salt. This is a B. These are B. These
are actually good. These are very good. I was wrong. Yeah. These are B. You're weak. Nobody likes
plain chips, but as I'm saying, like these are, it's just plain. I don't want to eat those. I
actually don't want to eat these. I would rather eat one of Otto's Milk Bones than one of these.
These are pork rinds, but what if I'm a, what if I'm full of shit? I'm, I could be full of
shit. Am I full of shit though? I have, I feel like I just pretend like I don't like these. That's the
whole point of the stream. The whole point of this show, this television show. Hmm? They're just like
pork skin, pork rinds. Right, right. I put these at F. Dermot, you're a bad streamer. I was gonna give
you the finger, but I'm gonna be the bigger man. Hot sauce? On these? Yeah, grab it. I can't even
open them. I proved him right. What do you mean? Okay. I don't, don't come over here.
Just don't, I'm telling you, you don't want to be here. No, I didn't fart. No, I didn't.
I'm just going to get a little one. That's a huge one. Pork rinds. Why? It's, it's fucking,
it's probably delicious. Why am I acting like there's a bug in my hand? This is bacon. It's
just like literally like bacon. It's just bacon chips. Very dry. Let's try it with the good old
Tapatio. They smelled awful. And I mean like really bad. Are you saying what, like a drop or two?
Hmm. Hmm. I mean, the smell is truly awful. Like it smells, out of everything we've opened today,
by far this stinks. I don't know why it came out. It sounds so weird, but it's really not good.
They're very dry. Yeah, they're very dry, but a little bit of the Tapatio. It was like just
kind of bacon. That was, that was kind of good. One more, one more, one more. I don't, I like,
don't like it, but it's like, I don't know. I kind of, I could see this being really good.
I don't know. Maybe like crushed up. The smell will go away. Holly, we're going to be sleeping
in different rooms tonight. That's good. That's good. I'm not going, I can't lie to you and be
like, oh pork rinds. I fucking hate being on camera. They're definitely not F, but they're
definitely not higher than like a D plus. Maybe like a C minus or something. What's the, what's
the height? What's the highest thing in D? Salt and vinegar chips better than that. Where's red
delicious apple? Right in the middle. Almond Joy. I'd rather have an Almond Joy. All right. Here we
go. It's hard. I mean, it's hard to do hot sauce. I mean, this is better than Frank's. But you know,
Tapatio, you want a good little bit of spice on your, on your whatever it is. This is the,
this is the best stuff you want. You want to face the bullshit. I will face the bullshit. This and
Tabasco are the best hot sauces you can buy at the grocery store. Tapatio. Trust me. You're going to
want it. Hey, Tapatio. Good till it's gone. Actually, you know what? Let's go. I love this
stuff. It's so good on tacos. It's so good. But you can go to everything. Hey, hey, hey, hey. So,
it's so good. I put it on my ice cream. You know what I mean? It's very good. It's just,
it's just vinegar. No, it's not. That was not based. Okay. So we're, we're almost done. We've
got cashews and bread. If I would, if I got a blood test right now, they would probably think
I was from like an alien planet. What's going on with your levels? They're all fucked up. What
did you do? Ooh, that was a, did you see the freshness? Did you get a look at that freshness?
That was fresh, but they're cashews. So they're disgusting. I fucking hate these. I actually hate
cashews. I think they're the worst. They're just like meaty, like too like, they're just like,
it's just like, it's like gamey. It's like cashews are like the venison of the peanut world. There's
like two, there's too much. Here we go. Oh my God. I was so wrong. Wait, I just, I don't like,
I just don't like them. I just don't like them. I don't like the shape either. Telling you.
Eat these instead. It's the same shit. This is made out of cornmeal. This is made out of fucking
gross nuts. No, I mean, they're different. These are made out of completely, this is way better.
That's D minus. What's, what's at the bottom of D? Okay. Would I rather have cashews or red
delicious, red delicious? I would rather eat five red delicious apples before I had 10 of those.
I know I'm crazy. No, I don't like this. The flavors just doesn't, it's just not good.
This is not good. Okay. That's all the snacks. It is time for bread. We're going to start with
butter bread. I never had it. People said, dude, you're fucking crazy. I'm just going to try a
little bit. Um, no, this is fine. I'm just going to take a little bit. I have whole wheat bread here.
Gross. And I have sourdough here. Even grosser. Butter bread. I'm not going to eat a shitload of
it. I'm just going to have like a little piece. Dude, the zip ties are the USB sticks of the food
world. I, you, I don't, you know, I'm never going the right way. Like I can never get it right the
first way. Wrong brand. What are you talking about? It's just freaking default bread. Wrong
brand, Andy. All right. I finally get it off. Okay. This is butter bread. Wrong brand. Here is a
piece of butter bread. I've done, I've never eaten this and I was like, I don't want it. It sounds
gross. Enjoy the glucose. You idiot. Thanks doc. Butter bread. Why'd you take the third slice?
I don't know. No, we're doing this default. I'm not going to play into your horse shit.
No, what you do, you didn't dip it in, in like butter, put it in the toaster oven,
let it sit for an hour, cut it in half, put a little bit of sugar on it. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. We're eating this as it is. You're not going to, you're not going to do any bullshit on
me. Here we go. Butter bread. Sweet. It's sweet. Sugary. It's like a nice sweetness. It does kind
of taste like, like a little buttery. This is really good sandwich bread. Yeah. Like I could see
like, like a big, like a nice slab of ham on there. Nice slab of fucking Swiss cheese. Nice slab of
fucking mustard. Oh yeah. I could see it. A nice like ham sandwich with this. I think it'd be pretty
good. This is like, this is high. It's kind of like just like a better version of white bread.
What is this? What is this stuff? What is this? What is this? How do they get it to taste like
this? Is it just butter? A slab of mustard? Yeah. I think this is like, this is like a B.
This isn't, you don't even need to put butter on this. I'm telling you. Put this in the toast
oven. Light toast. Don't even put butter on it. I think it's fine. You don't even need it.
I'm just, that's a solid B. Nobody can have this. It's mine. Nobody can have any of this.
All right. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. What do you think? Like, hey, how do you do it? Fold it over,
set it down. That's how I do it. It's glucose. Glucose Andy. All right. I know I'm not going to
like this, but whatever. This is whole wheat bread. I got the wrong brand. Sorry. I didn't
get your like craft beer bread brand. I had literally like less than 24 hours to get all this.
Dude, you didn't, you didn't get like the, the craft, like micro brew beer, whatever. It's,
it's bread. This is a hundred percent whole wheat and it's going to be enough. Let's take a look at
the cola. Pretty nice. Pretty nice marbling. Color is there. That's definitely wheat bread.
IPA millennial bread. Yeah. It's definitely wheat. It's whole wheat. It's definitely is.
Let's hold on. Let's. Yep. Okay. The aroma that comes out. There we go. I already know what this
is going to taste like and I don't like it. It's communion bread. It's just bread, dude. Why are
you eating it like this? That's the worst sourdough I've ever seen. This is not sourdough. We haven't
even opened the sourdough yet. This is not sourdough. It's just bread. Who, yeah, who gives a shit about
any of this? Who gives a shit about any of what you're watching? Who gives a shit about this?
Oh, a white bread is better than wheat bread is better than sourdough. Who cares? But this is bad.
F. I just bit my lip. It's F. It's just F. I whole wheat bread just is so plain. Is it? Okay.
These are the same. These are the same in my brain. It's so plain. It's plain and just like
cardboardy. These are the same. I don't like whole wheat bread. I don't like whole wheat chips, whole
grain. No, give me some flavoring. Get that goddamn fucking fucked up B to come over and sprinkle
the honey on my Cheerios. Like, I need something. It can't just be plain. Here's the sourdough.
And this is, this is, this is Grandma's, Grandma Sycamore's homemade bread. You better be fucking
nice to Grandma, all right? Or I better be. Dude, Grandma Sycamore's sourdough. It was the wrong
brand. There's no right brands of bread. Grandma, Grandma Sycamore. This is Grandma baked every
single one of these. Don't you get it? Sourdough. That's definitely sourdough. That is definitely
sourdough. All right. This is the last thing I'm eating. This is the last one. She's looking over
here. She loves this shit. She's a huge fan of Grandma Sycamore. I know it's not like the, dude,
doesn't have like the Swiss cheese holes. It's, I had fucking 24 hours. Yeah, that's all right.
It's just like, it's just bugs all over it. It's fine. All right, here we go. Sourdough sandwich
bread from Grandma Sycamore. Actually pretty, the thing I fucking hate about sourdough is it's like
made out of glue. Go to the bakery and buy, yeah, all right, Bakery Andy. Hey, Grandma, you got a
good thing here. It's good. It's not like that super heavy like sourdough, like, like sour flavor.
It's good. It's good. Grandma, am I wrong? You gave it to, somebody said I gave it to you like
I was feeding a duck. Grandma went fucking sycamore mode for this because I don't really like sourdough
and this is, this is pretty good. This would like a say, like it's got like that, it's light. Who
made this? Grandma Sycamore homemade bread. Hold on a minute. Grandma Sycamore's homemade bread has a
fresh baked homestyle taste and texture your family will love. True. Our breads are made without
artificial preservatives, colors, or high fructose corn syrup. Just ingredients you can trust.
Actually you can trust Grandma Sycamore mode. Give our breads a try and you'll see why we believe
that nothing compares to Grandma Sycamore's. It has that like sour sourdough flavor but it's not
like fucking tough as goddamn nails. That's why I don't like sourdough. You're holding the bread
like a baby? I was reading this. All right, Grandma Sycamore. Grandma Sycamore. All right,
stop saying that. Grandma Sycamore, that's a, all right, I'm biased because I don't like sourdough.
So remember, like a C plus for me for sourdough might be like a B or an A for you but I'm not a
big fan of sourdough but Grandma Sycamore didn't miss. That's a C plus. I actually, I actually did
not, I will probably have a sandwich for this later. That's, okay, you know what I'm talking
about? Like that sourdough flavor is there but not like the chewy sourdough toughness. Grandma,
pretty good, pretty good. Oh, let me see. Undip, Coke, yep, 7% battery power. All right, Red Hot
is not rated but Red Hot like doesn't, I don't know, doesn't need to be. All right, I think,
what, what stayed an F? It looks like Sun Chips stayed an F, Swedish Fish, Wheat Bread, Tootsie
Rolls, the Honeydew Melon, yeah, yeah. I thought that was an avocado. Jelly Beans, yeah, the
Butter Jelly Beans are gross. Grapefruit is still gonna stay down. The Mountain Dew is down there,
this makes sense to me. Surprises though, we have a few surprises. Bugles, Big Twist, I really,
I thought I hated those. Those were all the way up to A. Fun Dip, I thought was like a disgusting
thing for children. In fact, adults can enjoy it too but you can't bring that to the office.
Fun Dip is at S. Bugles went up to A. Yeah, these were, these were good, the Sun Chips. I would
definitely put the bread, put the Sun Chips above the bread and then put the Green Sun Chips. I
think this is good. Fritos. Whoppers went up too. Whoppers went up from F. I'm actually pretty,
I'm pretty surprised by some of this. Mike and Ike said, those were F too. No, Butter, put
Butter Bread at C. Definitely put Butter Bread behind Grandma because I mean, there's no way that's
better. Yeah, I knew that I still wasn't gonna like Swedish Fish or Tootsie Rolls. You're an iPad kid.
Well, there, there you have it. There, you wanna get, you wanna come grab your phone? There you go.
Hold it that way. Okay, all right. No, Otto. Otto's just been chilling here the whole time.
He's just, he's like, I'm eating like bread and stuff and he's just like, like, no, you're not
getting any of this. What about the Frank's Red Hot? I mean, that's, I, it's hard. You can't like
put, it's hard to put hot sauce here. That has to be a whole another day. Okay, so in the chat,
on a scale of one to 10, 10 being, this was a really fun stream. You should do it again.
And one being, I accidentally clicked on your stream and I'm never coming back. What, where was,
how do you feel about this? Do you want to see more of this? Would you like to see more of these
kind of weird taste test streams? Okay. Seen a lot of eights, a lot of sevens, a lot of nines.
Seen some tens. Seen some tens. Nine, three. Oh, cool. All right. Well, I'm gonna clean up.
That's it. That's the end of the stream. Thanks for watching. There's a lot of food now. The pantry
is gonna be full of food for like a year. I actually enjoyed these as much as I pretend like
I don't. They're actually better. I just wish they weren't blue because why are they blue?
Very cool. Very cool. Very excited. I'm very excited. Really? Okay. Maybe we'll do like some
more taste testing eventually here. That was a lot of fun. I had a good time. I'm not clapping. I'm
not clapping because like I did a good job. I'm clapping because there's like shit all over me.
I kind of want to eat more of this grandma bread. Does this hit the ground? Very good. All right.
Well, I got some stuff going on this weekend so I won't be around. When I come back, I'll be around
on Tuesday? No, Tuesday. On Tuesday, we're going to do blood wash and murder house. So he's clapping
his ass cheeks. Where's Monster Rancher? I don't know. Grandma went sicko mode. All right. I'll
see you guys later. That's it. I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Thanks for watching. The nature of
this stream. I kind of need to just go to the outro. So I'm going to clean up and make sure
nothing's on the ground for auto so I don't eat anything. So I'll see you guys later. See you
Tuesday. I'll come over there. I'll see you Tuesday. Thanks for watching everybody. See you soon.
Tuesday at four o'clock. Can you hear me? Tuesday at four o'clock tonight.
And thank Holly for helping because that I couldn't have done this alone.