Good afternoon. How are you? Hope you're having a swell day. What's up? Not much. This is unprecedented
amounts of early. We're fairly early, at least today, because we have to be. I've had to be
early over the last few streams for various reasons. How's Otto? Otto is good. I had him checked.
He just has some dry skin, so he has a special shampoo now that Kim and I have to use for a
couple weeks. Yeah, it's kind of like a dog lotion, kind of, but he'll be just fine.
This is the first time he's ever been in Vegas, and it's really dry and really,
really irritating weather out here. It's like 100 degrees. He's not really used to it, so
he's been very itchy. I wanted to make sure nothing was wrong with him, so
he's good. And the reason why we started like an hour or two early today is because I have to
get on a plane. I got to get out of here. I've talked about it a little bit, but going to
visit family and going to put like triple time into this stream that's coming up here.
I will be gone for just over just about a week. I'm going to be gone for like a week,
but this is planned. At least the family stuff, because I'm not going to be seeing a lot of my
family members for a very, very long time. There's a lot of movement in my family and
siblings and relatives. I probably won't be seeing them again for a long, long, long time.
So we decided we would do a little thing, and I also decided that why not take the
opportunity to really, really put a bunch of work into this upcoming dunk tank carnival stream.
So as of next week, I will have that stream in motion. So I will be away from the stream,
but I won't be away from the stream, if you know what I mean, in a live sense.
And speaking of streams, I'm going to wait until people triple in here, because the last stream
before Deep Rock Galactic, we had a little bit of a problem. There was a crash.
I lost a bunch of progress on the movies, but guess what I did? I got it! I went back and I
finished it, and I did it. And it's exported, and I have it right now. So we can watch it
before we do anything else. Also today, there are a bunch of mods installed, so I don't know
how stable the game is going to be. I have a shitload of new characters, a bunch of new sets.
We're going to try to make something in the time period that we have. So I hope to be able
to... I should be able to be live for about five hours. Maybe a little bit more. Maybe a
little less, depending on how much Kim is trying to get me to pack and get ready,
because she was like, hey, are you ready? Are you packed? No? Well, did you check in? No? Well,
what are you doing? She's not just like that, too. And Otto... Italics is going to be
dog-sitting for us, because he's going to be sticking around. So that's really nice of him.
Really good. For an ancient game, this is going to go well. I have tried a few things,
so it is... it does work. I've seen the characters, and I can't wait to use them.
This is going to be such a joke of a stream, because I'm going to just be wanting to put
characters in where they don't belong. I have a plan for what I want to make for the first movie,
and it's going to ruin everything, but it's okay. So let me just... let me be back in,
like, one second. I want to move something over here, and then we will watch the E3
presentation video. I'll be right back. Oh shit, the mic was muted. Are you guys ready?
Here it comes. It exported at like... they all export at 30 frames a second, or like 25 frames
a second, so it might... it's a little sloppy, but I got it. And there's a dog, too. All right,
here we go. You ready? Three, two, one, action. Wait, what? Wait, what's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong? No sound? There's no sound. Oh fuck, okay. Can you hear it? Can you hear it?
You can hear it, right? Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise. You can hear that,
right? All right, all right. And three, two, one. Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise
and welcome our president and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Greg Strongs.
Hey, that's who I'm talking about. Welcome to E3, everybody. We're so happy to be here. We
are beyond excited to show you two new releases upcoming in our catalog of Oh My God Entertainment
games. That's Osmond, that's Michael, and that's Gary, the three of us. So excited for you to be here
at this E3 event. I can hear that. I can hear something over here. That's me, I'm sorry.
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone up. Turn the phone up. You're gonna come to
E3 and try to come to my conference? Fuck you. That's two phones.
Come on, get up there then. 42%. What are you gonna do?
World premiere. Don't die on me. Die on me. Come on. Co-captain. You were my co-pilot.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature. I don't know what it could be. Possibly an
organic compound. What is that? Thank you for joining us at this year's E3.
We look forward to seeing you next year, where we cancel half these games,
and the other half are dumbed down to a point where you're not gonna have them.
Oh also sorry to say, we have canceled from last year,
Booger Eaters 3. I decided it was not part of the planning.
I had to end it. I had to just end it somehow. I don't know, some of the audio was in like
the wrong places. In the very beginning when he's like, I, that's who I'm talking to.
I don't know why the first like three seconds has cut out. But look, I salvaged it. I
actually salvaged it. I'm happy. I was so sad two or three nights ago. I was so depressed.
But, why don't we just transition from there? Does someone just give a hundred bucks?
That phylactery lich just gave a hundred dollars. Thank you so much for the hundred bucks.
They say bravo. Well we have, there's more to come, because today there's,
I, you thought that may have been off the rails. Just wait until like, wait until R2D2
shows up in one of these. I, I don't know what's gonna happen. The game might break
over and over again, but it'll be worth it, I think, at least to play with it.
So, thank you so much phylactery lich. It's a lot of fucking money.
Why don't I open the game? Oh my god. And 20 community subs. Holy shit.
Uh, thank you Herbert1234 for the also huge amount of money. Thank you so much.
Both of you. All of you. Two huge monetary drops right now. Thank you.
Let's see what we can come up with. Thank you guys. So I have it saved exactly right after
the release of E3 presentation. Oh my god. Phylactery lich. 50 dollars from phylactery lich.
Uh, I will not be upstaged in this manner. Well that's another 50 dollars. Thank you.
And then right after that, back in gave 50 dollars. Movie sucks, Kappa. And we got acid base.
I don't want, I don't want you guys to see the new sets. Because some of them are fucking
hilarious. And they're just blasting acid base right now. I didn't do this.
But back to back, both of you, thank you for the 50 dollars. Dead-O 15 community subs.
Thank you guys. Thank you for all the fucking huge amounts of money. All the community subs.
This is ridiculous. Thank you. More community subs. Make it louder.
Oh, all right. Let's make a movie. Oh my god. What the fuck is happening right now.
Phylactery lich. Again, a hundred dollars. Shut up and take my money. Love you, Germany.
I will shut up and take your money. But first I'm going to say something.
That's a shitload of money. Thank you for it.
That's 250 bucks in 10 minutes. I'm going to be eating this steak tonight.
Thank you so much guys. And then camp, Karen. Camp F Karen. Five community subs.
We've got a little train going here. Thank you guys. Just wait. Just wait till you see
what happens here. The first thing we're going to do. So let's get a new script going.
Where's my script writing office? This isn't pretty loud though. Why is this so loud?
I'm like drowning myself out. There we go. That's a little better. That's a little better.
Okay. Now I can hear myself talking. All right. Script supervisor office. We're going to make
a new script and we're going to see just how much this works. We're going to do,
we're going to do a Batman movie. Uh, Batman and Robin versus Mr. Freeze.
And maybe some other cameo. There it is. Come on. I don't even know what the hell it is.
There it is. Okay. Advanced movie maker. We're going to call this one, um,
Batman. Should I call it Batman or is that illegal? How about like, what if it's,
what if it's like a fan Batman? That makes it fine, right? Fan Batman and fan Robin.
They're just fans. How about in just, in how about that the movie just called
they're just fans. Rat man and Robin. No, but they're not rats. Okay. I'll show you.
So first of all, let's take a look at some of the new, uh, mods that we have here.
We have Robin, we have Superman, Batman, and then I'm going to say this is the Burger King,
but that's like for, you know, should we do the Burger King one first? We do like the
Burger King King. We got R2D2. We have like Warcraft characters. There it is. There's like the
Iceman. Here's Darth Vader. I think I want to do the Burger King movie first. Yeah, that's
Batman and fan Batman and fan Robin versus fan Mr. Freeze. Make him gold.
Light bulb Vader. Yeah, I got Chewbacca. I don't even know what this is supposed to be.
There's no dick, right? All right. Good. Should I make the king? I think I'm going to do the king.
Let's do a Burger King. Yeah, I think we're going to do a burger. We're going to do where
I got. I've got plenty of time. Don't worry. No, not burger alien. Okay. We need, uh,
this is the, this is the sneak king, right? Whatever his name is. What does his hair look
like? It's like, isn't it like blonde or brown? It's like this, right? That does not look
like the king. All right. Facial hair. That's just like closest it's going to get.
His hair is much different than this though. Holy shit. There it is. Okay. I got it. It's done.
There he is. There's the Burger King. Oh, it was just, all right. All right. All right.
We're good. Same, uh, hair color, right? Yeah, it's that. What color are the Burger King's
eyes? They're like green fan Burger King. Yeah. They're not red. No, this is fucked up.
Demonic Burger King. No, it can't be like that. There we go. That's better.
Okay. All right. So let's get you in that costume. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right. You're good. What happened to your hair? Why did his, why did his hair just turn
into a plastic bag from the grocery store? What the fuck just happened? Oh, his age went
all the way up. Okay. Okay. That's better. All right. We got that. We got our Burger King.
I'm protected. All right. We need, who else needs to be? This would be like a promotion,
right? This is going to be a promotional video. No, I gotta, hold on. I gotta,
I gotta protect myself here. Okay. I think that's, I think I'm more protected here.
Um, so what do I want you to see? Maybe just a couple of customers.
They always do like a DC. No, the Batman and Robin is later.
I don't have any other like McDonald's characters. Should this be a fan of Star
Wars promotion at a fan of the Burger King? No, I want, hold on. Why, why is this empty?
Why is it just an empty space? Why does this one not work? I think this one might be broken.
Oh yeah. We could do a clown. Yeah. Okay. We could do, but yeah, we're going to save our
modern. We'll do a clown. Did I have any, I think I put some more. Okay. No, it's an angel.
Patient. What if they just said like, no, no, I can't do that. I'm a fan of Burger King.
Perfect. What's Burger King's colors? Red and, uh, red and yellow, right? Wait, what?
Burger King's colors are red and yellow? Just like McDonald's. Holy shit. That just
hit me like a ton of bricks right here. It's red and yellow. Wait, it's red, yellow and blue. Okay.
That saves it. No yellow. The uniform is brown. This is just standard, standard waiter.
It's all right. There, you said brown, right? Sorry. We'll just like,
we'll YouTube their hair to be like Burger King. Okay. Hold on. What about
just like cover him in tattoos. Evil Burger King. This is not an evil Burger King.
All right. That looks all right. This person's married. All right. Then let's also do,
uh, and because everybody knows that at Burger King, there are fucking ants everywhere.
So, holy shit. It's a Burger King ant. It's a burger. Is it a Burger King ant? I can't,
no. If you're, by the way, if you're a fan of Burger King, you know that like when we make
fans of Burger King, our fan restaurant has ants in it. There's a Burger King ant right here.
Yellow and green, right? There it is. Which one, this one or this one? No, it's this one.
That's Burger King colors, right? It kind of close enough. This, this one, I like this one
too. It's like so ugly though. I don't think I can look at this. Make it a French fry ant
like that. You like a French fry ant. Okay. And this is slick. Driscoll is already like
an interesting name, but I'm going to change it to the cashier and then French fry ant.
Okay. This is a, this is a comedy, obviously. All right. So we have our, our base here. So
we are going to go to a new place. This place is called, I know I have like a restaurant
somewhere. These are the new ones. Heaven, a hospital bedroom, hell, metropolitan subway,
city destroyed by volcano, which I mean, that would be, I mean, that's kind of makes sense.
City destroyed. Oh, should I save that for Batman? Oh, here we go. Hit Pizzeria.
Pray that this works. So this is where the, we're at the, the burger, the fan restaurant.
Give money. Yeah. The King burger has to pay everybody. How much money is he given?
He's like an abusive boss.
I think I like that, but wait, hold on, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. This is fine,
but we're not going to, it's not going to stay there. Undercover boss, burger king edition.
Wouldn't you just know who it is? Order. All right. Hold on. I got to think about this
under cover boss with the kid, with the, with the burger king. He's already here.
All right. Let's start with like a card writing. Maybe he's like doing the menu.
Let me see what this looks like. It's a birthday. Is he eating the pen? Why is he
putting the pen in his mouth? Sneaky. He's like the sneak king, right? That's not very
sneaky. Okay. I like that. I like that little look over his shoulder. That's sneaky. I like it.
It's staying. Okay. So sneak king, the sneaky for a minute. He's paying his employees.
He has to pay the aunt too. So that's important. Just like the start of a regular day,
pay phone, give money. Here we go.
Well, this does the same thing. It's like angry. You better step in food
and breathe in the walls. You better gross out at least two customers today.
Okay. So we can, we can cut these up. Let's open up with him
writing the letter, paying the employees, pizzeria. Okay.
All right. I look, I know that everyone's, everyone knows that this is going.
We don't even have to talk about it, but like we need to get there first.
We need to get there first. So somebody has to come in to the store, enter,
uh, to, to enter. These can just be extras. Uh, they could just be,
it could be that Sandler don't matter. How's their costumes? Pizza.
All right. Let's check. Uh, let's get some costumes here. It's fine.
And you need a costume too. Uh, this is all right. No, this is fine. All right.
They're like nursery rhyme twins somehow. Uh, that's how big we need them. They both enter
their matching clothes. And then we need a order at the window. There should be a drive-through as
well. Order a drink. Here we go. King doesn't need to be here, but, uh, you do. Let's see.
This is just a bartender.
Why is Burger King a refuse? Burger King is a bar. Oh, this is so stupid.
Serve and press. You should do like tricks and stuff. You're going to do a trick. I like it.
Okay. I also need, is it like food? Eat food. Order food. There we go.
Oh, who's coughing.
Okay. So let's, the, the aunt. Okay. I'm going to compose myself here for a second.
So he's going to order because he's already up there. Yeah. I'll go back and add extras
in a second. The aunt can take the order. That's fine. There's gonna be something wrong
with the food as things as the catalyst here. Uh, it doesn't matter. It is an extra.
Who did it? Who's the, what did I just do?
Oh, there's also, hold on. Let me, let me see if I can do this.
Props. How do I add props? Cause this is a shitload of props.
No, this is like the employer. Here we go. Okay. We need you. There you go. Sure. I get you. That's
fine. Um, this is an evening gown. You go to Burger King in an evening gown. Classy night
tonight. What are you going to order? They have the same voice. People coughing in the
background. It's disgusting. This guy is naked.
Hold on. Typical Burger King. I'm going to put a bunch of coughing and sneezing in the background.
Okay. That's fine. No, it's fine. Everything's fine. Everything's fine. All right. We're good.
Okay. Next we're going to do pizzeria and there's going to be an issue with the food.
I need a serve or serve food, food, eat food. Okay. Here we go. Let's see what happens here.
Please tell me there's like a choke. The king is eating in his own restaurant and he fucking
chokes and dies. And then everybody panics. What? Wait, what? How did he choke? It's disgusting.
It's the assassination plot.
And then have him fall down. What is disgust?
Fork and knife at Burger King. Are we still eating it? That's much better. Okay. I like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's not the king. It's random people.
We should cut between like two or three people eating and like being disgusted.
I'm going to change the camera angles. Is there a choke? No, there's fire choke.
Uh, food, eat food. Jesus. Okay. Let's get in there and do some camera work.
Let's go here. I need to go alt and then down. All right. This is good right here.
And then I want here. Let's see. Camera one, camera two. Let's see how that plays out.
Okay. Pretty good. Pretty good. Let's do another extra. We have,
did I do this person already? This is somebody else. Let's get in there.
Let's get in real close on this one. Or maybe, no, maybe not. If you like, like right here.
Okay. Why is people eating here? If it sucks this much?
Is this the same person eating with the, oh, she's eating too.
Okay. Now we have to have a problem in the back where it's like,
what the fuck is going on back here? This is going to be like an intense talk.
Three-way conversation in the back. No, baby. Bartender cleaning. Let's add this.
Holy shit. Even more money came in. I wasn't even paying attention.
Filactory Lich gave another hundred dollars. This is gross. Keep doing it.
And my bank called me and asked if everything was all right. I told them I was giving money
to a man I watch play video games. They remain concerned. Thank you for the hundred
bucks. Hopefully everything's all right. That's a lot of money.
All right. Let's go. Wait, why is he cleaning? Why is he tending here?
Somebody said this might be slander. It's not. This is not Burger King.
This is not. I'm going to make that really clear. This is not Burger King.
I'm going to change the name of this. No, it's not. It's not. This is not that.
I made that really clear. I'm a huge fan and this is my shitty restaurant.
All right. Don't worry. I'll fix it. Ready? Watch this. I'll fix it.
Everything's going to be fixed. No, I don't like that.
This is the real Burger King. He's like not even here. He's somewhere else.
I told you. This is a fake Burger King. You got me all paranoid.
Are we going to have to change it? You're going to fucking jail.
All right. Well, this is fine. This is the real Burger King
and he's not involved. Back to the pizzeria. All right. We have to have exit horror.
Wait, why is it like that? How horrifying. All right. Walk and talk. Let's see.
Heated argument. They sneak out without paying.
Okay. Angry. Angry, angry, angry. Let's try this.
That's not very heated. I would not classify this as heated.
Fight. Is there like a not extreme? Oh, it's ready fist fight.
A constant conflict. Burger conflict. There's always conflict. Is there argue?
How about conversation? Burger talk? Oh, what the fuck is that?
Oh, it's just the same scene from before except now he's doing it on the other side.
Holy shit. Phylactery lich is up to 400 bucks. These are the last bits. I want the next badge.
Don't worry about my money, Jeremiah. I'm set. I just wanted to share some with you
since you've been watching. I've been watching you for so long. Much love. Well, thank you
so much. That's an astronomical amount of money to give anybody. So thanks for the
400 fucking dollars. Hopefully your bank doesn't call you anymore. This is fine.
We need those extras to get out because everyone's leaving. Is this the only option
I have? Yeah, it is. Making a deal. Crystal ball. Is this like in the future? Is he looking
into a crystal ball? Have somebody choke and then go to sleep. That's not a bad scene to
put over here. Maybe somebody in the bathroom. Is there like a comedy chase in the bathroom?
No. Dilemma. Okay, that's what I want. Hold on. No, it doesn't exist. I'm gonna go down here.
Ghost Kung Fu.
Okay, well.
Hold on. Feature. What? Someone smokes a cigarette and dies.
This doesn't make any sense though. This like can't be here. All right, so then he's gonna
knock. All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Comedy chase. Tired. That looks so dumb.
I like this one. Okay. We need more people to come into the restaurant.
Okay, this one. Let's go back to, we need like a couple of a little finale here.
Enter flowers. Enter scanner. Somebody walks in with like a health inspector's scanner.
All right, I need another actor. Who's not in this? Yeah, and he finds the ant.
No, Adam Sandler was in it in the beginning. What looks the most like a,
no, no, no. This sound is probably the best. All right, he's gotta change out of these clothes.
No, that makes no sense. Here we go. R-T. No, it shouldn't be R. All right, he comes in.
No, we're gonna clean all this up in editing. Don't worry. And is it gonna be a confrontation
between him and the ant? He's gonna go in with the back. Maybe order food? Maybe he orders
food and he's like, what the fuck is this? Should he slip on a banana peel and be like
that? What's going on here? Reaction, calm, laughing, angry, angry. Watch your reaction.
Laugh. Or contempt. And then there it is. You don't just, you don't have to be in here.
The health inspector's pissed. Okay, now we need, I gotta get these like characters out of this.
I gotta, you have to be over here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What am I
thinking? What am I thinking? Am I insane? What am I talking about here? Where is it?
No, no, wrong guy. That is so loud. Camera one's better. Okay. Is it like a three person
fight? Two people attack. Here we go. What is horrific. Oh my God.
Okay. Well, these are the wrong characters. This has to be,
no, this is not an extra. No, no, no, no, no, no. Here. No, not Howard.
Okay. All right. All right. All right. No, we're done. We're done. We're done. I'm
not gonna put this together. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, hold on. Let me, hold on a second. Okay.
Hold on. Hold on. I need to change something here. Okay. I, I'm sorry. That's like no fucking
way. It's not a fucking chance in hell. You understand? You understand? Like I didn't want
this to be connected to any brand and that's what I'm doing. I want to make sure that
that's not what this is because that's not what my intention was. And now I'm like seeing
like through the fucking rear view mirror here. Burger Palace is a real company. God
gimme it. There's no fucking way that there's a burger pyramid. Okay. Absolutely zero chance.
There's no burger pyramid. There's a burger pyramid. Is that okay? Is that right? Am I,
am I in trouble now? Okay. All right. See? It's not, it's not even close to the same person.
All right. That's it. Okay. Back to normal. You're gonna get claimed for using the term
French fry. Yellow end. Old man with crown. All right. I'll, that one's fine. I'll change that
one back. But I'm not, guys, I ain't fucking around right now. Where the hell were we?
Back here? Someone's on the phone. This is perfect. Okay. I'm okay with this now.
This is no longer, this is now, this is a pretend fucking little place. This was never
intended to be anything else ever. And I said that in the very beginning. Okay. Just
make sure everyone's clear. All right. Now the fuck he would never do this. That's right.
Cause that's not the same person. All right. Now we gotta throw away. Give CPR to immediately.
Dilemma. Tame. Moderate. Frenzied. Okay. Let's be easy here. Okay. Okay. We killed them.
We killed them. The police come in. Police come in and arrest them. And that's the end.
Case closed. More ants. Okay. Why are they so happy? Okay. We gotta change this prop too.
That's like an old, kind of old rifle. Okay. And then you, I need, this is gonna be,
now you're under arrest. Take photo. Investigation. Here we go. Double sneak.
Oh, who the fuck were they again? I have to do their costumes again.
No, no, no. What, what are you doing? Okay. Good. Okay. Find rocking chair guard. Wait,
why is he in a rocking chair? Disturbance. Feeble. High. Mood. Confused. Did he get like,
did he get like a shot? What? No, that makes no sense. All right. Well, how about happy?
Same thing. Disturbance. Normal. Surprise. Angry. Angry. Okay. Here we go. No,
that's don't work. Chat up. Throw away. Should he just drink poison? All right. And then
where is it? And that's it. It's just this one. No, he's not alive. I have to change it.
No, not this one. Dog attack. Jump escape. No. Flank comedy. Wait, where is the alleyway again?
Let me see. They're gonna throw him out. Quick. Here we go. Complete. That's gonna be so long.
That's it. That's not it. Didn't he just drink poison? It's the ant.
We need an extra here like a police work. There we go.
I love the looking back. Can I make it? I'm not sure. Let's see if I can do it. I'm gonna try.
That's just, you're trying so hard to land on your back. You are jumping. You are trying
to hurt yourself. This is, please God try to hurt me as much as possible.
You're dead. You die from that, right? Do you die from that? I think you do. You might make,
will you? I don't know. It would be, you'd change your whole life. Like you would change everything.
Okay. Good. Great. He doesn't even notice.
Cut to the hospital. Just cut immediately to the hospital.
Where's the hospital?
What is going on?
No, no, no. I'm thinking they could arrest him in the bed. How is this a hospital?
Hospital bedroom. Slow start. No. Wake up. Wake up. Confused.
It doesn't really look like a hospital. Just cut to a funeral of the ant.
That makes more sense. This is not, if this is a hospital it would be better.
Or hell. Should it be heaven or hell? How is this heaven? Heaven.
Don't ask me. Okay. I think it's just supposed to be bright.
Yeah. He's just going to walk around aimlessly and then you disappear
because you're not going to be in this. Yeah. He's just like, wait, what?
What? How did I get here? No, the old man in the crown also died is what you meant to say.
Do the dumpster scene again with the old man in the crown. But he ends up in hell.
No, but he already died. No, no, no, no. I can't do this. I can't do it twice.
I do that every time. Somebody told me, they came in and they said you do the,
you do it every time. You make the thing happen twice.
All right. If I can have him do it in hell, I will. Okay. If I can jump into dumpster in hell
and then he wakes up somewhere else, I will. Okay. Hell. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We got to go. We got to go back inside of the pizza place. Okay.
Okay.
He's lifting his arm. No, no, no, no, no. Carry him to the dumpster. No, no, no.
He's just going to wake up in hell now. No, no. What are you doing? I want you. Got you.
Throw into dumpster. The ant is my favorite one. Like ever. Where is it?
Alleyway. Alleyway. Am I stupid? Oh, it's got to be, I got to have a close-up of her throwing
and then it cut to this. Oh my. So it's going to go from here. Like from here.
No, no, no, no. What's going on? Whatever. I didn't, I didn't mark it. Oops. I didn't think
I had to. That's so fucking horrible. So now a scene before this, I need to have like a
close-up of putting the body down or throwing or throwing something. So let's just go,
I wonder if there's a good, yeah, throw will look all right if I get close enough.
Throw away or thrown out will be okay because there's a very clear shove. There we go. Yeah,
this is perfect. Now who was it? Was it you? Was it somebody? I think it's you.
Let's get rid of you as an actor. You're not going to be in this frame.
We also need to respect the line here. We should get rid of the door.
You know what? It actually works if that was the Kim. Oh, this is perfect. Yeah, this works.
I was afraid that I, because I didn't know if it looked like it was going to be falling or not.
This is going to be horrible. I hope you guys understand. Why did the hair change?
It's a wrong actor. I thought it wasn't Lola. Who was it? Marine? I mean, no. Who was it
before? Let's see. We can see who it is. No, it is this. It's this girl. I think their
clothes change and their hair change every time. No, this is, it's fine. All right. Mark it.
And then she falls in too because she walked off. Then we got to be in hell.
Heaven. Hell. Oh, I get it. It's just, all right. Should scream spin and then pull the whole
thing up and he's in hell. Hold on. I do have like a demon. Group chase all the demons.
Yeah, absolutely. I need the, where are they? Just need some monsters. An angel in hell.
That's so stupid. Yeah. I'm going to put like a devil on the, on the horse.
Scream spin or riot. Scream spin. Scream spin. Scream spin. Are you sure about that? Are you,
you're sure you, you, I a hundred percent. You sure about this? Like, are you sure?
After seeing that. Just keep the cheerleader. Do, do all red ants. I can put red ants like
around the corners. Wait, hold on. Here. There'll be a red ant on the horse. No,
nevermind. Sorry. I can't do that. I have to change this. Here we go. I will add a scream
spin before this and this would be, this will play us out. I got this. I got this. I got this.
Scream spin. By the way, backwards shot eyes and then the run. Now he's going to put
this piece of shit together. All right. I'm going to change something here though.
I need to add an angel here just so, just so it's very clear.
Because is that, is that soul? That could be its soul. There's a lot of meaning here.
Ready? Print it. Stamp it. Now let's get to real work. Let's go. Save the game.
Pea pants mod. Yes. Shoot it. All right. Uh, begin casting. We're good. We got everything
we need. I need the sets. I need the sets. I need Howard as the director. Okay.
I need sets. I need the pizzeria. I need hell. Pizzeria. Okay. Anything else?
Think I'm good. Ready to shoot. Shoot it. I know you're upset. You'll be fine.
Wait, wait. Tropical beach. Tropical beach. I need the wild west saloon. Hold on.
What the fuck is tropical beach for? I need heaven.
I gotta start deleting some stuff. Yeah. Let's delete this. Actually hold on. I need more space.
I need heaven.
I'm out of room. All right. I got to delete this. This shit's gotta go. How do I raise
a building? I know there's a way you can do it. I think I have to get a builder.
Yeah. I need a builder. I don't think I didn't have any.
I don't have one builder. All right. You come here. No. I have to go like this.
Delete. Thank you. Well, I didn't need that.
I got the pizzeria. Western saloon, right? Tropical beach and wild west saloon.
Wild west saloon. This is enormous. Can I just delete the scene that this is attached to?
I have to get rid of more buildings. Okay. That's it. That's it. Done. All right.
Save it. Pea pants mod. Here we go. It's ready to shoot. Let's hope the whole game doesn't break.
No, not PR. Shoot it. Three, two, one, go. We're being ruined.
No, this is the scenes. The scene placement doesn't matter because we can change it in editing.
No, if you weren't here in the last few streams, you don't. That doesn't matter.
All right. Here we go. Post production. This is where the fun begins. Fix it in post. That's
true. That is what we plan to do. It's so funny how this progressed to, oh, this is a funny idea.
Oh, yeah. Look, it's the burger thing. Look at this. How it fucked up. I'm terrified now.
I'm scared. I don't want to get in trouble. I got to change this. It progressed. But that's
what happens in the editing room. You figure out what you can and can't do and then you do
it. So first things first, the most important thing I would say is we need to move. We need
to do some rearranging and we're going to cut everything. What's the music, first of all?
It's actually kind of perfect. Okay, so this is way too long. Maybe I should start with
them just holding it. How long? This is like 40 seconds. This doesn't need to be this much.
I think it's right here. All right. No, no, no. We're going to do some inner cutting here
because this inner cutting is because this is like weird fucked up plans. I was like running
the restaurant in the ground. So like right here, we'll cut like, let's see, right here.
We're saved. So let's go like this. All right. Let's take a look how this looks.
Sooner. Sounds like sonic music. Bang. Money. Cut back. There it is. Paying the
ant right when it comes up in the air. I think right like here. I'd say right here.
Let's take a look. You're like right before it comes up. I think right here is safe
and that goes over here. Actually, I think it should be shorter. There it is. That's good.
Right there. The rest is now he gets in something. There's no getting people's faces too. I'm not
sure we even need that. I don't think we need him getting in somebody's face. Maybe a couple
more of those beats like right in everybody's face. Where's another one of those like
big hits? All right. Let's use the we got this one. It's right like here. Right. Bang. Right
there. Get rid of this portion. Just add it to the extended edition. Let's see what it
looks like if I just put it over here now. I don't understand. What is that? Oh no. It's
the song. It's the song. It's the song. You can't edit to. I forgot. You can't edit
to sounds and songs. I forgot because it changes everything. Yeah. I keep forgetting. I
can't treat this like final cut or premiere. This the song. It still works. No. It's still
fine. No. I don't like how that is. I think I want the close up one. Yeah. I want the
close up. Where's the close up when he gets right in his face? Right here. What is this
movie? This is a food store, a food, a restaurant that is in like trouble and
shit. And there's nothing to do with any restaurant you've already known about.
Well, I don't know. Where is it? Right here. There we go. All right. Let's see.
Oh yeah. These guys have to come in. I do want to have this one pop in somewhere too.
He's just constantly berating his employees. Let's cut it right there. Back to back.
I'm like doing it to the music and I shouldn't be. I don't know why this is
a music video. I don't know what I'm. I don't know why I'm doing that. It's just
becoming a music video. I don't know why I'm. I don't know why it just is. That's
where it's going. Okay. Now they come in. This has to be like right here. Looks good.
They walk in. It's not perfect. It's not perfect, but like it's hard to edit with this
timeline, but I think it's pretty good. I like this like West side story type intro.
By the way, he's serving him poison. Everybody catching that?
Everyone's like sits down and starts like eating and choking. Let's get rid of this.
Let's see. How does it be together so far? You can already start to hear people coughing.
Boom. Like food. I think this is wasted space here. I'm going to save it just in case. Well,
I'm going to actually save it. I don't think we need all this.
We definitely need this though. I need this over here.
Let's keep this clip for when we need it. I'm going to put so much like somebody fucking
sneezes and shit back here. Wait, she goes back to eating after that.
It matches perfectly. All right. Need another one. And cut to them ordering right here.
I will take this please. This is not even a central character. Why do we care?
What is going on on the left side of the screen? There we go. Right here. Right when it
goes in, like in the mouth, like right here. What the hell does he do back here?
Oh, he's just cleaning the bar. It goes here.
All right. I think that's, I don't think we need any more of that. Let's watch it from here.
Oh, no. Wait, wait, wait. I'm just tending bar. Is he in his pants? Is he daydreaming?
He's daydreaming. All right. Let's see how this looks over here. It was right here.
Sometimes the music feels like it doesn't line up the way it did previously.
You know what I'm saying? Because I have to cut more off the snow.
It's not going to be perfect, but it'll still be funny. Right? It'll still be fun.
And he's like, oh my God. He's self-serving. Okay. This is where he doesn't notice people
are coughing. And this is when they leave. That looks good. Because what's going to happen
here is it's going to be like bang. Like what the fuck is that? New music? Well,
this is not going to be a music video anymore as of like once the song is over. And we're almost
at, this is almost dead. Okay. Somebody gets like, okay, what's going on here?
Something else happens. Yeah. They go, they leave. Like, I don't like this place.
Oh, then there's like a fucking huge fight here. Everyone leaves. Why is he sleeping?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I should probably put this.
Hold on. He can't be doing both things. He can't be doing both at the same time.
It's a dream? No, but he, okay, he's tending bar, but he wasn't actually, he's asleep here.
So these two things didn't happen. This is happening. So then why would he be daydreaming
about himself sleeping, dreaming about himself on the beach, which is a daydream of him tending bar?
Why would he be doing this? That doesn't make any sense. Why would he be daydreaming that?
Hold on. What do you do? Okay. That's about it. That's going to be quicker.
Right here. All right. I think that's better. Okay. So here's the cough.
Make sure I got it in the right spot. Yeah, I do. Somebody has to choke this.
Yeah, this one right here. So we don't need this guy anymore.
We got a great shot of him already. Just put a transition in for the dream.
Yeah, but which one is the dream? Yeah, we don't need that anymore.
So that brings us to here. So this is a daydream of, this is so fucking odd.
Okay. So fade out, fade in. So this is the daydream, but this is him sleeping.
But this is also a daydream at the end here. You understand?
Save it. Save it. Save it. I will. Let's flip these. No. All right. I like it.
This is like too much. I liked this better when it was just him sitting there
daydreaming about himself serving himself a drink. This gets too meta.
Yeah, it's out. It's out. But I'm not going to delete it though,
because what if I want it somewhere? Okay. So let's see what I got.
I'm taking off the fades too. So it needs to come in a little quicker here.
Okay. It's fine, but the king sleeping cannot be here. This is the argument.
So let's put this over here. Keep it. Keep it. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Cough, cough, getting out, sleeping and getting out. Let's just see how it looks.
I want to give it a try and get these transitions off though. Okay.
Why? He goes. Oh, this part sucks.
All right. What else happens? There's the big fight and then the...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on. Hold on. No, excuse me.
He's going to smoke just in the restaurant and more people are going to leave.
And then he gets confronted. Are the people still in the restaurant?
Oh yeah. The person that really likes the food. I forgot. Yeah. She likes...
Wolfs it down. All right. Yeah. That has to be intercut somewhere in between the fight.
No, we already have him drinking poison and dying. We don't need like another
death scene for the king. Yeah, I can get rid of this. This is a, this is a,
I got what I wanted from it. I don't need it. I have poison death.
Okay. So this is where we need to start to figure out how, let me just see how this looks.
Oh my God. That's, that looks just awful. It's just awful, but I don't think I want to change
it. All right. What else? Oh yeah. What else can I put here? Wait, they come back in?
Who comes in? Why do people come back in? Is it too cold outside? Are these the same people
that left? No. Are these the cops? I forgot about this shit. Okay. Then. All right. All
right. All right. All right. So let's do this one by one here. Argument. People come. Then
okay. That gives me a transitional piece. Here they come. And then we get the shove
right here. So I don't need this portion here. I got this and then they're going to fight.
Let's get rid of that. In come the people enter cold. That is not long enough at all.
We're almost at the end of the song. What the hell do I do now that the song is over?
All right. Now, right when the first punch is thrown, that's when we get the like action
song. So like, this is fine. Let's go like. You want it? Let's see if it fits.
No, it's got to come in when they're arguing.
Someone kicked to the jukebox. I don't think it fits. We need something quicker.
We need something that comes in quicker. Sorry, guys. I tried.
That's too quick. It would have to be something like this.
It escalates in a thousand percent. We need her eating, like eating the food like really,
really fast. This will match with this song too. I think her like, let's see.
Yeah, like cut it right here. So like you think that she throws up right into the camera.
This is this is a run.
I think it's just, oh, I hold on. Let me see how this looks.
Cyanide, zero with 10 community subs. Thank you. Thank you so much for the 10
fucking subs. A lot of community subs tonight. Today, should I say? All right,
get me in here. What does it need to be? I'm thinking like the wicked dumb run
and then instantly throw them out the window and then the eating and then like the puking.
I don't need this anymore then. Is that is it? How is that stupid?
Kick before out the window. That's true.
Yeah, it could do. Oh, I hold on.
I need to cut this in half. Bang, right here. That should be enough to make him go out the
window. How does he get in front of him like this? Actually, it kind of works because he's
behind him. What window is he going out of? This one? He's going out of one of these side
windows. Let's see. Let's move some stuff around. See if it looks better like this.
Oh, that's great.
Okay, now we have, how the hell am I going to do this? Yeah, new, I got to get new music
let's play this. Let me see how this plays out from like here.
Oh my god. All right, we are about, I'd say 40% of the way there. The best is yet to come,
if you could believe that. Delete the sleeping and messes with the sink.
Uh, here's the unfortunate thing. And I figured out how this game works. So when you play from
any part of the timeline, it has to load the music separately. All the sounds are loaded
separately. So sometimes it just puts itself out of sync. Unfortunately, no matter if you move
anything around, it's like rendering two things at the same time. It's weird. Because if I
delete this, the whole thing will squish down and the music too. It's really hard to actually
get anything in sync in the movies, especially if you have a lot of sounds. Yeah, I got it. I
saved it. I got it. I'm good. All right, let me, let me take this opportunity. It's been
about three hours. Let me go, I'm going to go pee. So I got it saved. We're about 40%
of the way. Maybe a little bit more. I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back and
we'll continue this, uh, absolute atrocity of cinema. See you in a minute. Hey, I'm back.
All right. So we've got
the music can now change to like, here comes a situation where a guy's coming in to sneak and
take pictures of the restaurant, right? Because that's what comes up next. But then
he immediately just falls down and then they hold him down and beat him up. And he's supposed to be
he's dead here, right? Oh, and then the, then they come in with the, the police come in
and he's sitting in a rocket. How am I going to do with this? Why does the ant go to heaven
again? Well, you'll see. You'll see very shortly. All right. So let's back it up.
Let's get this out of here because I don't think I need that. Wait, maybe just one quick.
Let's go like this. The guy with the Ghostbusters
ecto gun thing. All right. Let's go with, hmm, how about eerie house? See how that looks.
Well, we don't need all this. We just need this. Like what the fuck are you doing here?
Mom, I got to call you back. Uh, something just went down in the pizzeria.
In fact, can you like come fucking pick me up? All right. Let's, so first of all, he comes in,
maybe he should, it should like, he steps on it here. You know what I'm saying?
At this moment, this is like too much lead in room. I mean, do, do I just not give a shit
and have this happen like this? What if he just walks in and they grab him? Let me see what happens
if he just walks in with his health inspector radar gun and then they just grab him. This guy
didn't even do anything. He's the health inspector. Just having new music. This is
like, this is like not, not nice movie. This is like, this is bad. This is just mean and
Oh my God. Settle down. Oh, okay. This is back here. I need another song though. We need something.
Hmm. Fantasy battle. Femme fatale. Give me 24 hours. Haunted house. What's this one called
again? A lone fight. Haunted house. Let's give this one a try. Oh, not that far. Too far.
Like right here. Actually it's in the right spot. This, I already had this one on here.
No, this is not, this is eerie house, not haunted house.
Hold on. No, that doesn't, it keep going. That's, I kind of like, oh, stupid. That isn't a problem.
All right. I don't think we need the banana peel. Yeah. These two scenes can go,
but after that is the kind of the panic, right? Yeah. We just killed the guy.
Panic, right? It goes here. Nope. No, no, no. Wrong spot. Wrong spot. Here. Hold on,
hold on. I can, I'm going to, I'm just going to move these around.
Wait a second. Did they, the clothes switched? Oh well. Okay. We need, it needs to be on that
same beat. Come on, you little twig. See if that adds a little bit to it.
It's not long enough. Actually it might fit if I do this. This, just delete these. I'm not going
to use the banana peel. There's no reason to use it. It's just kind of wasted space here. Although
hold on a second. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait just a second here. I like that reaction from the ant. I like that. That's motivation
there. I like it. Kill him. Bang. Right here. The ant is like, oh fuck, this is not good.
Right, right here. Although he switches sides, unfortunately. Let's see if it looks, let's see
how it looks. Hold on, let's see. No, no, no. Wait, wait, what? I shouldn't have done that.
I could put it, hold on, let me see. Yeah, maybe before, before the attack. That's not a bad
idea because he doesn't want to do it and he tried. Hold on, let's see. Let's just take
a look and see how it looks. It's perfect. He wants nothing to do with it. He has a conscience.
I like it both ways. I like it. He has it. He's like, I don't want to do that.
He's like, oh no, someone's here, but ready? Check this out. Like here comes a health inspector
and then you've got, he knows what's going to happen. Like, oh no. And he's, now I have to
go do this. The other way is we did it and then, oh no, we did that. We should not have
done that. Hmm. Hmm. It's tricky. Yeah, it's, it's, I like it this way. You can even see
shaking his head left and right. No. Oh, fuck. What if we don't, what if we don't know?
This is a little too long. Wait, wait, wait. Back, back, back, back, back.
Right there. It looks all right. No, but we get the, no, I like, I like the king
like doing like the, you're dead. We'll just come in here. It's like a tiny little piece
that's just sticking out here. Who the hell is it? The best part is how he says,
you're dead. And he like thinks it's great. And then instantly with his hand still going down,
goes, oh, whoops. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You're dead. Hand still in the air. He
immediately comes down into, oh fuck. What have I done? It's gotta be right. It's gotta be
right here. Let's just see, make sure it's correct. Yeah. Killer beast. Yeah. Oh.
Perfect. What people say in voice acting. I don't think I want to voice act this one.
I think it's perfectly fine as a silent film. I think it speaks. The whole thing speaks
already. All right. We're, we're almost done. Pretty perfect. All right. Moving on. Save it.
You got it. Got to go in and get rid of this one. Where is it? Come here. There's another
little, just tiny little piece somewhere. Where is it? Oh no, it's just this. This
can get out of here. We don't need this anymore. He said now he's just waiting. Yeah,
he's waiting. Okay. We're going to do some intercutting here. He stands up. Ant is like
going out the back. I don't need this anymore. We got the ant sneaking out the back. Okay. I can
pull this back out. Um, we'll go two. Sounds good. There you go. So I need to bring this
here. Yeah. The ant's like on his way out. What are you doing? What the hell was that?
I gotta get out of here. Which way? Which way? Okay. Hold on. Hold on. This is the big,
this is the shot here. This is the shot that matters.
Why would you try to escape like this? He does it with his trash.
He does it with his like fall. That's so funny. He even looks back. Why would you
think it was full of stuff to break your fall? Doesn't make any sense.
Okay. Um, he already is dead. All right. Hold on. This is now, you gotta move this over here.
Oh, my fucking stomach. Okay. And then this is where the throw happens. So I gotta get this
right. So like right here. Let's go put this over there. Oh, this is gonna be, I'm gonna
fucking, is it gonna hurt? I already know it's gonna hurt. I already know. Okay. Hold on.
I gotta get in close for this. I think I need that. I'm gonna cut it. I'm just gonna see what
it looks like. I'm not gonna remove it, but I just need to move it to here.
It's so, it needs to be like right there. Okay. There it is. I think I got it. That's so
horrible. It's so fucking horrible. Wait, hold on. Let me pull this one back. Get over
here. Get over there. It's so small. I can't grab it. I just, I want that little piece
right there. Shit. Is it, I think it might be too small. It's alright. It's, it's perfect
the way it is, but I'm just trying to make it over perfect. Just move everything to the right.
Hold on. Let me see. I could just do that and then I need it to be here. This can,
are these too small to move? These might be too small to move too. I guess they are.
Too small to move. Now we gotta keep, we gotta keep it the way it was. Wait, hold on.
It's better the other way. Look at that, right? God, that's fucking so horrible.
That's just horrible. It's just, this is like you throwing something over about and into a
dumpster. Okay, then I can just delete these. Can I even delete these or is this just gonna
be at the end of the movie forever? No, I can delete them. Make sure this is actually
gonna delete this. Right? That's, I'm on that scene, right? Okay, good. Alright, we're good.
I love this one so much though. The original is always going to be my favorite because it's the
ant and he's trying to escape. He's so dumb. He just doesn't understand. Alright, now we need
hell. Let's zoom back out. Let's go with two pumps in there. Alright, hell. This is where
he wakes up. He wakes up in hell and then he gets chased by the monsters. Let's see how this
looks. That scene can be deleted. Yeah, I'm gonna use different music. I'm just trying
to get it in the right spot. It's done. Now we just have to make it, we just have to fine-tune it.
Alright, perfect. Post-credits scene. I can't do post-credits on foot. Yes, I can. Oh, why not?
No, he's dead. He's, he's very dead. It's, he's dead. No, no, no, no, he's dead. He's dead.
That cheapens, that cheapens the fall if he's alive. He's dead. That cheapens the fall.
Look, he can do, we can do an ant in heaven movie. Alright, it's done. Now we have to
change music, add some sound effects, and print the damn thing. This is almost, this is three
and a half minutes long. You just dropped it a whole letter grade. Alright, so let's go back to
here. This is fine. This is, right? This is like the music video, right? We get, we gotta
add some like, some song in here. No, song. Uh, some sound effects. I'm thinking just,
just like yells and shit and like anger. There's gonna be tons of coughing. Yeah,
this is gonna get, I'm not gonna overdo it. Breathe heavy. Let's put that over here.
Yeah, he gets right in his face and like breathes in his face.
Another breathe heavy? Or maybe like a, is it like an anger? Yawn? Slurps? No, no slurps.
We're gonna add those later. Scream. How about just like, just like a little like,
that's not really,
I always put scream one. What, I didn't know what scream two is. I don't think I've ever
touched it. Right. There's probably two because it has two chest bumps forward.
Let's do scream two. Scream three. No, I'm not adding that. Let's just see what it does.
All right, I gotta ask, does, does this ruin the music video portion?
Yes, it does. It does. So I don't need anything here. Yeah, we don't need anything here.
This is like good. Good. I'm gonna emphasize these though. Double cough.
I don't like this one. I'm not sure it needs it here. I don't think it needs it. So let's add,
let's add like a puke sound here. What was that? All right. Am I George Lucas-ing?
The puke would sound perfect with the music. Just hold on. Like,
hold on, I gotta get the right spot. This way. Come on. Damn it. Damn it.
Got it. Why'd it change? I had it right. I had it. Okay, hold on. Okay. I'll meet you. I'm gonna
meet you guys halfway here. I'm gonna meet you halfway. This shouldn't be here because
it, this is a big deal. This is like the everyone starts to leave and it doesn't match
up with the music. But this is like the, somebody pukes behind us and we're going to
leave. Let's see. It kind of like ruins the, I like that because, yeah, let's delete this one.
It ruins this whole music video. And it's like, well, hold on a minute. People are like,
something's wrong with somebody back there. This is not good. I don't think I'll ever,
I'm never going to grow up. This is never going to happen. I'm sorry. This is not going
to happen. I really don't think so. Change, change the music here. Like, oh wait. Oh,
okay. Hold on a minute. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is important
because I need a song that can be, I can't, I don't think I can because I have the music
all blocked out already. Imagine if you were sitting at a restaurant and you had just ordered.
You gave your order to the giant aunt. That's red flag number one. And then you hear that.
Apparently like whoever this is, they don't really mind. You look at this is just like,
excuse me. What is going on back there? All right. Let's play. Keep going.
We need like a big sniff here. You know what I mean? Like watch his eyes. It matches with
his eyes blinking. No, he doesn't. I don't think there's another one.
Okay. There's like, there's some changes that need to be made here
because this, this music just kind of, this music needs to come in sooner.
No, no, no, it doesn't. It can't. It matches up too perfectly here with her eating.
Is there like a sound I can make? Once I start fucking with George Lucas audio here
is when I've made a bunch of mistakes in the last one. I don't want to do that now.
Let me think. Hold on. What about just like horror sounds?
Is there like scary sounds you put in silence? Unfortunately, no. That is the one
large downfall to the movies is they were smart enough to put a timeline editor in here.
And it's really, really, really fun to use, but you can't individually edit audio files.
This is just for the whole track. You can't make it per audio clip. You have, there's
no muting. It's just, if you put a song in here, it does the whole thing.
And all importing silence would do is just layer on top because it just keeps whatever
is underneath it too. Unfortunately, add bone crunches, edit the song in audacity and then
import it. I mean, you know what? That could work, but I would need to do it to every
single song. And that would take, I mean, that would take a significant portion of time
for me. I mean, we're currently live right now. That's a lot of work for what is effectively
an ant falling into a dumpster. Just add a new song that's silence.
Well, it'll just layer on top. Put in a record scratch.
All right, let's see. Dirt falling, metal, pour, splash, phone ring, toilet flush?
Maybe this should be a toilet flush somewhere. Fire extinguisher. I don't know if there's a
phone ringing. He's George Lucas-ing. He's George Lucas-ing. Let's see. Human sounds.
I can click them. Yeah. Somebody told me I could double click them and it would play.
That person is a fucking saint. All right. Violent sounds.
Play some of those dialogues. No, I actually, I tried to bring in a, a song. I tried to bring
in a laugh track and it crashed the game. And we all know what happened the last time
this game crashed. It screwed up everything and I had to re-edit everything. So I am
not leaving this screen. Not again. Because even saving it, those of you that weren't here
last time, this doesn't save everything. It just saves this weird kind of configuration
file that keeps the audio and what clips you use. It does not keep all the edits to the clips.
So this is like a, if this is like a crash, it's literally like a landmine. I'm holding
on top. I'm holding a landmine right now. All right. But anyways, um, what the hell?
How am I going to, I need like an electrical sound. Okay. Alarm. ATM. Hey, that's,
that's like, uh, no, uh, uh, don't think so.
There's no record scratch. Let me just see.
Was it a metal detector? What is it detecting?
That's really loud. It's just letting you know somebody came in.
That's not going to work. Hold on.
Are they groceries?
Is that like a barcode on their leg of heads?
I need like a wham. I need something to do something violent. That's just
says shit is going down right now.
No, but that's like a, that's like a YouTuber thing. They put like that. Oh, look,
the camera zoomed in and two tenths of a second on my face. Hey, what? What? No,
I'm not doing that. Guys, can we hit 200,000 likes? Can you? I don't think we can.
Yes, we can. He shattered his rib cage. He's got like a bunch of expensive
glass and watches in his bag. Shattered his ribs.
No, no, no, too much, too much, too much, too much, too much.
Too much. Too much. No, don't. That's fine the way it is. I don't need anymore.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is, this needs to come in sooner. I think I'm going to, I'm just going to put this here.
So everyone in chat quiets down. It's going to be removed, but I'll put it in there for one.
Just you get one shot. You get one take. You get one. Disgusting. Revolting. This is,
that's just a disgusting person. Shoveling food down your throat. Perfect.
Oh my God. The game is so loud. I know. I know. I can't turn it down. I have to go
like into the source and turn it down. Hold on. But I can't, I'm so, I'm just,
just, just turn me down. I'm so afraid to alt tab this game. I just am. I'm terrified
to because the last time I've been doing that I crashed it and then we lost everything.
So I'm sorry, but turn your volume down just a little. I'm sorry that I can't do anything for
it. Okay. Where am I? Here. Okay. Yeah. The volume sliders, but I have to remember to turn
these back up. Unfortunately, it's only for what is recorded here. As you'll see,
it doesn't affect any of the stuff in the actual scene. Only affects the music and the
sound effects I'm putting in. So for instance, like when, when they have,
when he gets pitted through the glass, it's not a sound effect I put in.
So I can't, I can't lower it. Unfortunately. Okay. We need a transition. We need something
to happen. I want to pull this, but it's the shift in music between the scene transition
sucks. Yeah. But the, I, I, if, if, if this were like premiere or final cut, you know,
I would put transitions and spread them out and crop them up, but you have to have music
on top of music unless I go into audacity and rerecord every single song. So I wish I could
do that, but yeah, you use the tools. A craftsman only blames his tools if they don't work
as intended out of the box. What was that? Oh shit. Is it like a little ant sound
this is like a little I'm concerned sound nature and animal sounds.
Just get a real animal. I don't know. I never understand this.
This is just a person going, Oh, just record an animal. Just pull it from like a nature website.
Oh, wait a minute. I think we found out transition.
I wish I could just shut this off right here. No, I think it's when they're panicking
thunder kick, thunder knee.
It's Zeus. Yes. That is who this is. That's who you that's who's on the screen right now.
That's who it's always been. And I'm talking even four hours ago. It's been Zeus.
Please just please keep that in mind. It has never been anybody else.
All right. Um, this is all right. I want to add some like creaking sounds
just like that. It wasn't for the beginning part. Jesus. Hey, why would you do that?
I, why would you do that? I want to click this. All right. Fine game.
No, it's not even necessary. I don't think it's necessary.
That's fine. The two is too much. Thunder knee. I know, I know, I know. I'm going,
I'm going, I'm going, I'm getting it. We need a police siren. Lower your volume.
Hope you did. Damn it. Miscellaneous maybe. Is it no siren? No, I thought I saw one.
They're like, uh, no, that's, I thought that's a patrol car.
That is that as close as I'm going to get. All right. Stop.
I got one shot here because I can't move it anywhere else.
Another puke. Here we go. That's my favorite one.
Okay. We need music. So it needs to be, oh my God. Okay. So bang. Right when it changes,
new music. I can't come in. Why can I not add new music? I'm full. Oh, I can zoom out. Okay.
We need, we need where's the, what's it called? The one from when I did this like three years
ago, happy stride. That's the one. It has to be this in the perfect cut. Here we go. Let's
see. Shit. It's gotta be a little bit further because it transitions between them.
Okay. Now we cut to new music back to haunted house. That's so fucking funny.
Keep it. Hold on. Let me, let me just see what happens when I do this.
Well, okay. I'm going to, I'll play it out with it on. Let's see. No,
no, it's not going to have it like that. We need to cut back from happy stride again
at a good cut. And then hell is going to be like heavy metal music.
And then we're done and we can save it and we can watch it closer. It's close a little bit earlier.
It's going to have to be, yeah. All right. That's fine. We can go back to turning these
up again. All right. We're good. I don't know why I forgot that that happens.
I somehow forgot that's what, how this ends. Come on, pull it out.
Ah, no. Why? No, I need the music. I can't preview these. Oh, that's unfortunate.
Does anybody know off hand if there's a, like a heavy metal, the last stand,
the art of war, the last stand. We'll try it. Oh man. Once I get this one. Okay. I gotta,
I have to go back and redo these. That's perfect. I just got 10 more community subs
came in from cyanide. Thank you so much cyanide. 10 more subs from cyanide. You are too kind.
It's right here. Shit. It's not, it's fine. Oh, it really is not good, but I have to change
it all. I have to like go like this and then delete it. Okay. All right. All right. Here we
go. Another one, something else. Record doom off your phone. Doom OST. Just that first
song. Oh, that's not going to work because it has to be layered. That's not going to work.
It's not going to cut over the other music. Yeah. Sorry guys. I gave it a shot.
I'm going to do that one. Dark horizon. Pursuit. Action theme. The art. Try acid bass.
No, that's it. No, it's not that it's only going to play for like eight seconds. I'm going
to try the art of war. What did I do? But I didn't do the art of war last time. Did I?
I did the last stand. No, that was the last stand. Let's try it. Come on.
Good enough. Good enough to end it. Let's see what it sounds like. It's not very, it's not
good. Doesn't fit. It's like the end of a rocko's modern life episode. I think that stays.
There it is. It's done. It's done. There's only one thing that I need to do and that is
I need to scan the people when they come in. That needs to stay constant. Fix the heaven
music. What's wrong with it? Oh, I think this just hold on a minute here. I think the
Armageddon is just going to play. You know what? I think it's good. I think it's good.
I'm done fiddling. I'm done fiddling. I'm done fiddling. It's done. It's done. It's done.
Save it. Yes. Yes. We got it. No crashes. No bullshit. So here's what I'm going to do.
I am going to go pee while it all exports because we don't want to watch it like two,
three, four, five times in a row. Export it and then we'll watch it in all of its glory
when I come back. Custom scanning. Thank you very much. I would have just forgot that.
Thank you for reminding me. Let's do that first. When do people come in? Right here.
But is that, oh, that messes up the music video. I don't want to do that one. It's
supposed to be silent here. Here is where it can pick up. Did anybody come in? They do. No,
no, no. He needs one. No, he doesn't. No, I'm not going to George Lucas this. We're good.
All right. I'm going to export it. I will see you guys in a minute and we'll watch it.
See you soon. All right. I'm back. It's still exporting though. It's going to take like
another two, three minutes. Was there more community subs? We're not. Sign out. How
many community subs is this? Just 10 more and then 10 more before that like 10 minutes ago.
Holy shit. Thank you. Did I fix the audio levels? I brought them back up. They were back. They were
at like what? Like 40%, 40% each essentially. You left in the fart. That's great. I did. Of
course I would have. Oh well. We win. Yeah. The fart has a deeper meaning you plebs. And
then we'll see how much this movie makes. This was like four and a half hours for this.
A little bit less from setting up. Dude, I want this ant falling into the dumpster to be
like my phone background. I want to unlock my phone and see that every day.
I just saw it. I just saw it. You know it's worth seeing again. It's worth seeing like
five more times. All right. It's almost ready. Another like minute almost. Put the ant in your
Twitch description. Yeah. We could do an ant heaven sequel. It's possible. All right.
Movie is exporting. You have to play it through one whole time before you export it. But the
export takes a lot less time because it already played it through. It's finally finished.
Now the audio might not be perfect because when you export these it does a lot of
sometimes it moves stuff around. Sometimes it lags in the middle and moves a clip a little
bit forward. So it might not be perfect the way we've been seeing it in the actual editor.
But we'll see. It might actually play pretty well in like that viewing screen. We'll see.
Is this stream for kids? No. I would say no. I don't think so. I'm about to see it in fast
motion. It was perfect. It was awesome in fast motion too. All right. Let me just make
sure it's there. Let me make sure it actually exists in that folder before I close this window
and then we can watch it in the inside of here. Does it exist? But for this I have to
alt tab. So cross your fingers. I have to go into the movies folder. It's all in the
culmination to right now. Okay. Movies. I see food shop burgers available. I think that's the
one. I'm going to copy that. I'm being so careful. I'm going to paste that onto my
desktop and I'm just going to double click it just to see what it does. I think we're good.
And it was very loud. Yep. I got it. It worked. So let's release the movie and watch the movie
and see what it was worth. All right. That should be it. It's saved. It is ready. Exit.
Release the movie. Okay. A new competition. I'll award three healing crystals to anyone who can
tell me three colors of my aura today. It's not difficult. Down here. Where do I release the
movie? Lead role. Where is it? Canon. PR. Where the hell is the release the movie thing?
Because that's PR and then this is post production. Just do make a bunch of
ads for it. Okay. I'm going to spend like a hundred million dollars on it.
Okay. It's stuck in development. Hell. What? What is this snort? I didn't snort. Oh,
oh, I thought you talked about when I went like, Oh, right. Yeah.
All right. Movie's ready for release. All right. It's been, I don't want to do
any more post production on it. Where's this damn building? Shoot it. Okay. There we go.
Fine. Release. Budget. It's going to be as much as I can.
Here we go.
Crisp quality. Two out of five. This is loud as hell. This is so loud, but it's all right.
Just turn down a little. Repair of sets was superb. Average crew experience awful.
Final movie rating was two out of five stars. And are you ready to watch it?
The movie sucks, but it doesn't, the critics are always just mean.
All right. Turn down a little because it's going to be loud because I had to turn it up.
Are you ready? Let's go.
What did the critics say? Oh my God. One more. One more. Last one more. All right. One more.
One more. And that's it. This time I'm going to be silent for this one. I'm going to just mute.
If that ant seriously into the dumpster is, I love it so much. All right. First of all,
Phylactery Lich gave another $50. And they said I'm back. That was hilarious. I'm glad
you think so. This game's a lot of fun. All right. I'm going to mute. Here it comes. Encore.
Last one. Here we go.
There it is. All right. You've got a silent clip of it. Ant Encore. Yeah, that was a fire ant.
All right. Let's see. Success. Stunt rating. Difficulty. They were no success. Scene 26.
That's because they were doing their own stunts. Some of the extras did stunts better than the
actors. Uh, it was $266,000? Or is that $266? No, it can't be, right? This wasn't $2.84.
This was $266. Strange. Pee Pants Liquidated certainly shows some ability here and should
consider producing a third comedy flick. Jax really let this movie down. The crew
what a bunch of incompetent inexperienced cretins. Jax's stinking mood could well have
affected his performance here. Movie packed with originality. The acting was decidedly average.
The set scenes in this movie were clearly in superb condition. Why did I make it a comedy?
Because four hours ago, this was a different movie. Oh, there it is.
The president says he will not lose. Currently, the sand is making no comment.
I'm going to very quickly. I'm going to turn it down because it is loud. It's very loud.
And guys, I'm sorry to say that is going to conclude the stream because
I have to get on an airplane. I wanted to go for a good five hours before
leaving. I am going to be gone for a week. I've got a lot of work to do to work on this
Doug Tank carnival stream. If you don't know what I'm talking about, then just stay tuned.
I'm going to visit family and I'm going to do a bunch of work on this stream.
So I will see you guys in a week. Going back to Boston. Yep. Because on top of just seeing
family, I saw my mother, as you all know, a couple months ago. But some of my immediate
and extended family are coming in and some of my siblings are moving across the country,
kind of like I did. And this is the last time that we'll probably all see each other.
In a very, very, very long time. So I feel like I kind of took the opportunity to come back
because I obviously want to see some of these people for the last time in a while. So I will
see you all next week. Keep your eye on the sus. Don't do anything crazy without me. Behave.
I'm just gonna stick around for the 20 minutes and so we'll do the bits and the subs and
everything. Hope you enjoyed. The movies is always a ton of fun. I still have a bunch of
other characters and other things we could do. If you'd like to see it again,
we'll probably do it again because it is too much fun to play this. Anywho, I'm going to
turn this off. I'm going to transition to the outro. Take care, guys. I think
you're just taking off. Hopefully we see you again soon. See you next week. Those of you
sticking around, we've got some bits to do. Why don't we do them right now? Let's go back.
There was a lot of money today. A lot of high denomination bit donations and subs.
You guys are very, very, very kind to me. Thank you. Let's go back to earlier this afternoon.
7layerwario gave $10. Hey, my partner Wes has been a big fan of yours for a while.
Could you say hello? Thanks for everything. Hello, Wes. Hope you're having a good day, Wes.
How the heck are you? And then I put my hand out. Here we go. Hey, what's up, man?
Hey, what's up? But thank you for the $10. I really appreciate it. We also had
a ton of community subs. Herbert1234 gave $20. Deddo, Deddo, Deddo. $20. We had $50 from
Bakken. $50 from Phylactery. $450 total from Phylactery. Very, very generous. Thank you,
guys. We also had more community subs from campfkaren for $5. Waity, thanks for the $5.
Buxwaity or Waty, when is there going to be an auto stream? I don't think I'll ever have like
a just a purely auto stream. He shows up from time to time on camera. He'll poke his head in
every now and again. But thank you for the $5. Jerma lied and didn't draw sticks.
Thanks for the $2.50. Speaking of Burger King, play those three Burger King games
that are on the Xbox. Sneak King, Big Bumpin' and Pocket Bike. They were surprisingly fun.
Well, we didn't, there was no talk of Burger King today, but I mean, if we were to talk
about Burger King at some point, then yeah, I mean, maybe I would try them. I do remember
those games, though, especially Sneak King. Thank you, though. Thank you, Saturnian Ocean
for the $15. Last week, I got my wisdom teeth removed. They finished in about 30 minutes,
which was pretty cool. Too bad I woke up in the middle of them ripping out a tooth.
It wasn't great. Anyway, keep up the good work, Jerma Saturn.
Uh, yeah, that does not sound very fun. Did your face swell up? Did you look like a chipmunk?
That happened to me. It looked like I had, um, you know when a hamster stuffs like
seeds in his mouth. It's crazy how that works. You just have this inflated face.
How does the human body repair itself like that? That insane, intense amount of trauma
that we can have on our bodies and then be fine in less than a couple weeks. It's crazy.
The mouth is literally the fastest healing part of the body. It just seems so strange.
Human beings, man. Imagine living without any healing. Yeah, imagine if we just didn't
self-repair ourselves. If you got a cut on your finger and it's there for life,
what do you do? It's just wild. Well, you, you'd probably, yeah, we'd probably just die.
Well, that's not good. But anyways, now hopefully the procedure went well.
Thank you for the $15, uh, Saturnian. It was last week, but hopefully you're still in a
decent recovery here. Thank you for the $15. Gordon Burbman. Thank you, Gordon Burbman,
for the 20 bucks. $20. They say, hey, Jerma, I finally managed to catch you streaming.
Pretty hard to do over here in Europe. I've been watching your content for at least five
years. I just want to say thanks for all the laughs. Too many times I've been this close
to burger boy throwing up from the laughter. Here's to more years to come. Well, welcome
from the EU. I've had a couple of EU friendly streams this last two weeks, haven't I? I've
been getting up early is what's been happening. But yeah, um, five years is a long time. I've been
doing this for eight. Once it gets to 10, that's a, I mean, that's less than two years. Think
about that. A full 10 years of doing stuff on the internet. You don't have to have like a
party. Here comes the 10th sneeze. But thank you Gordon Burbman. Uh, I also from these
streams have almost burger boy thrown up because some of these games are just so funny.
They're just so odd and so interesting. So I think you can't help yourself sometimes.
Uh, Siroc, Sirockey Q. Thanks for the $12 and 50 cents. E-clown streamer Jerma is being
sued for defamation by Burger King. Jerma is also suspect of kidnapping, murdering,
money laundering, a clown car without a license, grand theft, ballooning,
cannibalism, uh, slavery, video game, privacy, tax evasion. I'm not accused of any
of those things. I don't know where you're getting the word burger and then the other
word that is also King. I don't know where you're getting those from. Those are two words
that back to back could mean something, but I did not make any references to those two words
that are connected together to form a potential corporate entity. I'd never talked about it.
On this stream today, we had old man with crown who was Zeus. That was Zeus.
I, and people in the chat were saying, is what is this supposed to be? Is this something about
the King? And I'm like, no, no, no, no, this is, this is old man with crown Zeus.
I corrected everybody in the chat at least a few times, but thank you for the 250.
Hey, Reapers Reviews. Thanks for $15, Reapers. Hey, Jerma, just want to say I love your
content and was introduced to you through a friend. Keep doing you also. When is your
memoir coming out? It already did come up. It was like the children's snake book thing.
I would just put my name on that and say this is the memoir. Otherwise,
that was such a fucked up stream. It's over. Did he ever revisit the E3 movie? I did. In fact,
at the very beginning of the stream, if you watch the VOD, if you open up that VOD,
the first thing we do is we watch the edited E3 presentation. I did that earlier. It was done
before the stream started. I hope you enjoy it because it is an absolute shit show,
but thank you. Reapers Reviews and thanks to your friend for introducing you to me.
Freudian Weapon, thanks for the $5. $5 from Freudian. Hey, Jerma, just wanted to wish you
well on your break. Hope the behind the scenes work on the dunk tank proves fruitful.
Have a good weekend, Jerma Hart. I'm gonna do my best. I'm gonna do my absolute best.
Hopefully it's worth it. It should be at least interesting. It's worth a try. Back in,
I missed this earlier, but Back in gave $100 and $50. So sorry I missed this earlier. I was
probably locked in doing something, but $100 from Back in. Thank you so much.
Been watching you for so long since early YouTube. My perception of time is degrading
more and more I feel, but I will never forget the amount of time you brought
joy to my life throughout the years. Keep doing you, Boomer, Jerma Hart. PS,
this Burger King conflict movie is too violent. It's not, it's not those things.
It is a restaurant. It was first of all, it's a pizzeria. I don't know any two words connected
to make a corporate entity with a medieval king involved. I don't know of any pizzeria
that has that on there named. So I first, that's the number one, but it wasn't,
that wasn't even that violent. It was just, I mean, it kind of was, but that's a lot of
money. $150 in one stream is a lot of money to give anybody. So thank you back in.
Hope you enjoy yourself. Hey, Freudian already got you, but $5. Thank you again.
We also had, it was a lot of community subs. My stream labs is just a fucking,
just huge, huge amount of them. You guys are fucking awesome. Thank you.
You guys are too much. Uh, smelly boy. Thanks for the 250. Please make a scrambled egg
breakfast on stream. I'll probably do a cooking stream eventually here. I got to be careful
though, cause I want to do some dumb joke and like, I'll like light the pot pan on fire or
something. It would be bad. It's like the one thing holding me back, but Keldo's thanks
for the $3. Uh, since you've listened to Red Vox, what songs are your favorite? Also,
what do you think about Jerma Fox? Uh, let me see Jerma Fox. Jerma Fox is from,
is Jerma Chomp, but a Fox. I think it's pretty cool. I think it's pretty awesome actually.
It's cute. It's cute. It's cute. What's cute. I see people writing in the chat. Why, uh,
me burning my house down would be, is like LOL quotes funny. I actually had a stream idea
where I was doing a cooking show and why would I even tell you this? Cause it could still
happen eventually. There's like a whole elaborate thing here. I don't like burn anything down,
but there was an elaborate scheme I was going to do. No, no, no, no, not scheme. That's the
wrong word. But anyways, Vinny is a very talented musician. He takes his music very
seriously and shows. Let me just show you. Blood bagels was blood bagel. Give Fox, give Fox,
give Fox. I'm not going to give Fox. Why did I say give Fox three times? Cause everyone's
screaming it. It's a good shit, ain't it? It's very good. Go get it, go listen to it,
go support it. I'm going to get content claimed by Vinny. What if he just like
dropped the fucking hammer on me and like ruined me and like took me to court and like took
every, everything. And I mean everything. I'm like, I ended up like the no house, no nothing.
And he's just, and he's just like laughing on stream afterwards,
but thank you. Kaldos for the $3. And that's probably the, this is probably two more songs
that I think are really good on that album, but are in that catalog, but thank you for
$3. Vinny's a good dude. You hate the rest of the album. No, I'm going to make sure this is like,
you can't like clip me out of context there. Like I know it's going to be like,
here's a few of eight seconds of a sentence you said. Let's get that last four seconds
and then get cut it right. Perfect. Fade it in a little. So it sounds more natural. Add
some more background music to background sounds and then fade the end out and then,
you know, change it a little. You guys, I know how talented some of you guys can be.
I'm not an idiot. What's this? What's this one? What happened? What's this? Oh, fuck. Oh,
what happened? What happened? Hey, RoboLamp, thanks for the 10 bucks. Germa Heart. Hey,
thank you. Germa Heart back to you as well. Thanks for the $10. We have a official Burger
King, $2.50. This is not a real account. I want to make sure that this is very clear.
This is not real. Okay, thank you, official Zeus Old Man Crown for the $2.50.
Good day, Mr. Albertson. We have received reports that you have been using the likeness
of our trademarked name and mascot in your content. Our terms of service clearly state
that any content creator shorter than one of our delicious chicken fries is not allowed to
use our intellectual property. As such, we put in a request to cease and desist with
Twitch who will be removing your channel within 24 hours. Have a wonderful day and remember,
have it your special packets of sauce put on top of a delicious pizza at the crown,
person that's a medieval crown has on their head in a pizza restaurant. Thank you.
I appreciate it. Thanks for the $2.50. Thank you C4G for the $2.50. Is this you? Is this you?
Um, no, no, it's not me. But thank you for the $2.50. Appreciate it. Cyanide gave so many subs.
How many subs did Cyanide Zero give today? It has to be more than 50 to 100. It has to be.
That's a lot. Thank you Cyanide. If you're still here. Oh, we also had a 0.9 for the $5.
Stop listening to the one guy in chat. This is pure gold.
No, I thought I was removing things and changing and checking that. Guys,
that's how I used to make videos. I would sit there meticulously for 10 straight hours
on the same thing. No, no, no, no, no. I don't like that. I gotta move that forward a little.
Look at this. No, I don't like it. Change discolete that whole to get rid of the whole
clip. I hate it. I used to do that all the time. I would just George Lucas the same video
like 10 times. Imagine editing. I know, really, right? But thank you, 0.9. Jack Raff, thanks for
the $2.50. Do you ever think you'll be able to play The Neverhood on stream? Any other games
you grew up with that you'd like to revisit? Maybe. The Neverhood's kind of odd though,
because from every time I've ever gone back and played it, because there's never been a
remaster. There's never been an updated version of that game. It's just the brick
Windows 95 version that I've tried to run on various machines over the years. And sometimes
you can get it to work for a little while. But there's a very specific point in that game
that's about 50 to 60% of the way through the game that you cannot physically get through.
You have to like go download a save file that goes past this one point to be able to continue
to play it. Or run it in a Windows 95 virtual machine. And another reason why, I've played
through that game more than 10 to 20 times. So I would really just, it's the same reason why
I haven't really played Bloodborne or anything, because it's just like, hey, remember this part?
Hey, remember this part? Hey, do you remember this part? I remember this part. You're gonna
like this part. Hey, I remember this part. But there's something to be said to have like a fun
nostalgic stream like that. I'm not sure I would do something like Bloodborne though,
because that would take a long time. I'm open to it though. Kalula Sniper, thanks for the
five dollars, Kalula Sniper. Hey, Jeremy, I just got my two-year sub badge. Thank you for that.
The movie streams are the first I ever watched live, so it's great seeing you come back to
this game. Thanks for staying awesome all these years. Much love. I'm just glad that I could
still have fun with it. One of the reasons why I don't like revisiting old things that
I've done or doing the same thing more than a few times is because I feel like the magic won't be
there. After I stream a certain stream or stream a certain thing three, four plus times, it's
almost like going back to it is like, hey, let me like go make that magic happen again.
So it's not necessarily that I don't want to. It's just it has to be organic. It has to
be something that I feel like doing and know that I want to go back to. The same kind of
thing happened with Sims 4, but enough time went by where that second time that I did it was
just as fun as the first time. But I wouldn't want to be one of those people that,
hey, how much fun have I had on these movie streams? All right, I'm going to do this like
I'm going to do this for the next like two months. I would never do it. I would just
lose it. Magic would be gone. So I guess that's that's the answer, right? The answer to
the question that you did not even ask that I you made a comment and then I asked a question.
But thank you. I do like going back to things if it's worth going back to.
Hey, pigeon. Thanks for the 250 pigeon. Hey, I don't know if anyone's asked this you
they asked you this yet. But are you coming to TwitchCon in San Diego?
You've always been my idol and I'd love to be able to meet you.
Um, let me think. I don't know. Maybe. Maybe. Maybe. But I don't like here's the thing about
TwitchCon. I kind of just like float around at TwitchCon. I don't do like any official
meeting greets or anything. You kind of have to like find me. I've done I tweet like kind of
like, hey, I'm in front of the convention center for a half an hour. So I don't really
do any of the big panels or anything. I'm not going to do. I've wanted to do like a panel
before maybe. But I don't know if they'd want me to do it because that would kind of ruin
everything. I was thinking about doing a or seeing if they'd let me do a panel where
I just put up like slides of like a vacation or something. And like the name of the stream
is like how to make your brand how to make your brand easier to consume with viewers.
And I just talk about where I went on Disney. I don't even mention the word Twitch. I don't
mention like engagements. Nothing. I just show slides. But I feel like they would probably
be like, yeah, so you lied to us. And I'd be like, yeah, well, I'm a fucking liar.
Have you seen the haven't you seen 38% of every username in my channel?
You should have known this. But this this, I probably will. I don't let's put it this way.
I don't have a reason not to go. I'm not moving. Although I've talked about it. You
know, I was thinking about it. But I probably won't not moving not really spending a bunch of
that's not true. That is completely incorrect. You know, I'm not spending a bunch of money
or anything. I'm just like, actively setting up a fucking carnival stream, you know,
I'm not spending any money. But there's really no reason for me not to go.
I probably will. Moving to where I'd stay in Vegas, just if the internet was still an issue.
I would just go somewhere else. But yeah, it's not really on the cards at the moment.
I will be on the west coast probably for at least the next 10 years. I'll probably be in
Vegas for at least three to five, I would assume maybe potentially, I don't think I want to live
in California. I want to stay in this probably Southwest area for a while. Yeah, I'll be in
Vegas for a while. Why not California? California is expensive. It is very expensive, especially
a lot of the places that I would want to live. Hey, let's move to Los Angeles. Oh, move to
wait a minute. How many thousands of dollars a month is it to live in like a one or two bedroom
like apartment in LA? What's that again? How much was that? No, I like Las Vegas.
It speaks to me. It just does. But Sara Bellis, thanks for the $11 Sara Bellis. No
message, just $11. Thank you. Let's get the credits rolling here. And we'll see all those
community subs gambling. No, it's nothing to do with gambling. That's do it. I'm saying
there's nothing to do with gambling. It has to do with I'm tapping my foot to
nothing. That's not gambling. Decide I just give another $100.
Yeah, they did cyanide with another $100. Holy shit. Hey, Gerber, been a fan for a long
while haven't been able to give back for all the joy you brought to my life. I'm at a point
in my life where I can donate and contribute back to the community. I love you'll be missed
this week. Yes, I might change my name to Gerber lied about level up lounge. If you
don't actually do it. Let's let me do the carnival first. Okay. And let me see how much
money is in my like literal Monopoly man open them and have like the bugs come out
because there's nothing in there. Let me let me get this done first and we'll see.
He was so drunk. No, I really did want to do that. I thought it was really fun idea.
Drunk promises. No, they're not drunk promises. They were drunk thoughts.
They were drunk thoughts. But if you want to throw this kind of money down sign, I'm
glad to take it. I just hope you get you're comfortable doing it. And always know that
there is no real monetary obligation to hang out here and kind of care about this channel
and stuff. I just hope everybody knows that. But I really do. That's a lot of money. I
really appreciate it. I will try to put it to good use. Thank you. We also had Oh,
the credits, right? I want to get those rolling because they're going to fly by
lots of community subs tonight. Thank you. All of you. The LUL boys. We also had
and we had Espada Escarlata. $2.50. Thank you, Espada. Just want to show some more love. I'm
starting a job with the census in a month. It's been really rough trying to find work. And
like a lot of people say, your streams are a huge mood lift for me. Oh, and I hope you
have a good visit home. This year will hopefully be my last at home before I head out to Colorado.
Having moved back here and hating it. Colorado is a great state. A lot of interesting things
going on. Colorado was actually one of the states that I was thinking of moving to as
well. This little section of the US, this like Colorado, Nevada, even parts of Arizona
into like, I like, I like this area. Oregon has the coast though. Yeah, it's always Washington,
California. But if you don't really care about the water, if you don't really care about beaches
and, you know, big bodies of water and being on the ocean or whatever, which I don't really
doesn't bother me that much. That's why I can tolerate the landlocked kind of desert that
is Vegas because there is its own charm. Vegas has a lot of awesome mountains. They
have a lot of great, great wildlife preserves and everything. The Grand Canyon is really not
that far away from here. You really like to gloat about Vegas an awful lot. I love this place.
Vegas is awesome. I will talk the shit up of this place. I will talk up Vegas every day.
Australia is better than Vegas. No, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not.
That's what I'm saying. Do I have any complaints? Yeah. Yeah, there is like one
major complaint about Vegas. People around here is the only complaint I really have.
I love everything about Las Vegas and this portion of Nevada especially. But people
drive around here like fucking lunatics, fucking lunatics. And that's not just like a rumor meme.
Unfortunately, like sad and horribly enough, I've seen more horrendous car crashes
on the roads out here than ever, ever, ever before in any place I've ever been.
There is a terrible fucking car wreck on the street in Vegas once a week it seems. Like
we'll just be driving around and it's like, oh, there's another like car fucking wreck over
there. It's horrible. And Massachusetts, that was like maybe once every year, once a year,
once every maybe couple years driving around every day would you see a really bad pile up.
It's a bi-weekly experience out here. So just got to be careful on the roads then. That's
why the insurance insurance is high out here. Just because it's people up fucking drive around
like crazy people out here. That's the entire west coast in general. Maybe. This is my first
experience with it. Just don't leave your house. And you've been on the New York,
New York roller coaster. I have. It's pretty awesome actually. Yeah, but we've been very
careful when we drive around out here just because it's wild. But no, no, that's probably
it. That's the only real complaint that I've really had since being here. Thank you, Jamie.
KW for five dollars. They say Pride 100, Pride 100, Pride 100, Pride 100, Pride 100. Hi,
Jerma. Love you. Thank you so much. What kind of car do I drive? I drive a Hummer. It's the
double XL version. And I put like the seat up really high and I like fucking, I love just
being like big on the road. No, I don't drive a Hummer. Hummers are the types of cars that
you fill that gas tank. And if you drive to the grocery store, you use half a tank of gas.
You probably drive a 2010 Toyota. I do not. I do not. What a little mystery what my car is.
What kind of car do I drive? What a mystery this is for you guys. Maybe one day you find out
what do I drive for a car? It's not a Tesla. A clown car. I bet it's a Honda.
No, I'll tell you what I drive. I drive. Are you ready? I'll tell you the brand. I drive a
Toyota Prius. That is also not true. I do not drive a Prius. That's a 100% lie. I drive a
Honda Civic. It's also not true. I'm just doing this thing where I think somebody already
said it. Whatever car I say, people are just going to be laughing. It doesn't matter what it
is. It doesn't matter what car it is. Okay, guys, I drive. I drive. I'll be honest. I drive.
I drive a BMW 3 Series. By the way, one of those is true. You never know which one it is.
Hey, tell me. Tell me two truths and a lie. Give me. Tell me two truths and a lie.
Tell me three truths. No, tell me. No, I don't have two cards. Tell me three lies
and the truth. Or tell me four lies and none of them are true. Damn, would you guys like to find
out? Three truths. You got a huge garage with like four cars. None of that. That could all
be bullshit and you would never know. I just want to know the truth. Maybe one day I'll
reveal it. I'll do a car reveal one day. But we're at the end here. No, we're not. That's a
lie. Five truths and a lie. Five lies. Thank you, official crown on the head for the 250.
If you continue to say that this account is not official, we will add a count of first degree
slander in addition to copyright infringement. Although if you publicly state how delicious the
last sandwich was, you ate from one of our fine establishments, we may be able to drop
that charge. Well, I'll tell you, the last time I ate a sandwich from a restaurant that you may or
may not be referring to, I cannot confirm or deny what you're asking. It was very good.
It tasted very, very good. Tell us the sandwich. All right. Okay, fine. Okay, but what? It was
the Baconator. No, it wasn't. That's not it. It was the Stacker. No, wouldn't you? You would
like to know what it was, wouldn't you? What kind of sandwich that I drive? You'd really love to
have that information. Could be a, could be Big Mac. What kind of car he eats. Thank you,
though. Hey, Garfield, the Monday Killer. 250 from Garfield. Buckle yourselves in,
boys and girls. It's time for the final Garfagraph. Final, wait, final Garfagraph.
What is this? This can't be real. It's been quite a journey, Germ, with me
talking about Odie and other cartoon happenings. You getting bricked, fumed as you read every single
one. Me only paying you 25 cents to read a wall of text. You laughing one out of 10 of them.
Good times, good memories. I think it's about time Garfield buries this hatchet once and for
all. Garf will be but a memory to the Germs. Thanks for all the laps, Germ, and never stop
killing those Mondays. But who will you become? But who will you become? We need to know the,
the, the, take the, the veil off. We need to know who the, the, the, who's behind the mask.
Garfield. 250 from Garfield. Here we go. Let's see who the, who's behind the mask.
Thank you for the $2.50. Again. Hold on. I'm not back. I just dropped my pen on the floor.
Ha, you know us cats. No pockets and all that. Okay, this is the final Garfagraph. At least
giving constant Garfagraphs. I might like pop in every year or so. I don't know. Don't stop
believing all you Germs in chat. I might even come back one day. Who knows? Does any other
cartoon Germabit donators make yourself known? Remember that Robot Jones guy? He gave like two
bits that one time. Don't forget to update the Germo Wiki. Constant Garfagraphs. Constant
conflict. Well, if this is for real, Garfield, you've been a, you've been a hell of a
contributor to the community. If you're retiring the name, hopefully, hopefully you're not
leaving the community. But if you, if you have some things going on that make it so you can't
participate as often in streams, then whatever it is, I wish you the best of luck. Thank you
so much for your awesome, awesome contributions. Hell yeah, Garfield. Thank you. Hope you're
still here under another username. Yeah. Definitely. And that's my time. Have a good
week everybody. I will update the SUS early. Probably. I don't know exactly when I will be
back in this chair. It's going to be at least a week. Six days probably. One, two, three,
four. Maybe less than that. It depends. Keep an eye on the SUS. You will see. You'll know.
Thank you for participating in the movies streams. Have Kim stream. Kim is coming with me.
We are both going back. Talix is going to hold the fort down here. He's going to take
care of Otto for us while we go back. But yeah, I'll see you soon. Don't forget about me,
because I won't forget about you. Good night, guys. See you real soon. Have a great week.
Tata.