Oh my god, what just- hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2.
I'm so confused right now. What the hell just even happened right there?
I just shot a spy and he like flipped backwards into a bunch of stuff and like broke all- that was as if I threw him
Into a table. What the hell was that? But yeah, Facecam Fortress 2 Mondays edition. How you guys all doing?
How you guys having a fantastic Monday? And they're gonna get that first point. No! Zeppelin, you gotta stop him.
Me and Zeppelin are gonna drop a friggin' Zeppelin on their heads. Oh
No, don't disconnect, please. Please don't disconnect. Please Zeppelin. Here we go. Headshot! Yeah!
That's what I like to say. This soldier is a headshot. If I'd waited another second, I wouldn't have had him.
Whoa, that was a little bit of laggy lag right there. Not too keen on that.
Disp- I think people are just disconnecting left and right here. Hey, I'll use it to my advantage.
Oh, that's three in a row. I call that a three in a row. Welcome to hell!
I'm actually doing pretty- pretty well right now. Question is, can you keep it going? It's the age-old question right there.
That's another headshot. Gotta get that guy. Get him off that point. Get him offa. Damn. Whoa, whoa, whoa. No!
That was a pretty good run though. I killed like five or six people. I think they are going to get it, unfortunately.
Unfortunately, no. Two soldiers. Oh well. What can you do, right?
So today, my drink of choice is a delicious iced tea. Not just any iced tea, it's the pure leaf stuff.
If you never had pure leaf, it is probably the best iced tea you could ever drink. And he had to move. He had to move, didn't he?
You are stuck in there, my friend. Should have hit him with that. Oh, he's still alive. Oh, and there's a-
No, I'm kind of- I'm going to eat a pretzel. I got- Oh, by the way, do you guys reme- Speaking of stuff that I drink and eat and stuff like that,
Who remembers these things? Do you remember these things? The pretzels in the box?
I remember when I was like five or six years old, I used to eat these every day. Oh my god. Oh my god.
They're gonna win. Notify if I have anything to say about it. Oh,
chaos. It's just absolute chaos. Oh, I figured I could have done something about that. By the way, these are so stale.
I just- I just bit into a piece of white bread. Forget that. Let's go again. Come on.
I was- I was on a roll there and I got too busy talking about pretzels and iced tea.
But I didn't do
shoot. Time to time travel. If you remember what time traveling is,
it's when I go like this and we appear at the setup is over. Time travel. The best kind of travel.
So let's kill that guy up top or just totally miss him. Either one of those two things
I'm happy with, for sure. Walk into it. That sniper right there. Is he gonna have a bad day? Oh, what?
I would have headshot him. Oh, things are not looking good right in the beginning here, folks. I knew it.
I could see through all the way down into- look at- my arrow is in his scope. That's ridiculous.
My arrow was through his scope. Shouldn't that have hit him? Actually, no, it's through the barrel.
So technically that's like an eye or like a- no, that's not- that wouldn't be an eye shot.
What the HE double honky stick am I talking about? Should have hit him. Should have hit him.
Oh, I'm doing all kinds of missing here tonight right here. Not on that guy. I- I
Interpreted his movements. I need health though, is that medic? Medic!
Medic! Medic! Medic! Medic! No! You! I'll take you on now. I'll take you on now!
Let's go! Let's go, man!
Oh, give him the old chop chop spike. Oh, I just freaked out. I stole that guy's health so bad.
I'll get him this time right here. Right through the trees like a real sniper. Oh, yeah, there it is! There it is!
Gotta be careful here. Smart. Smart demo man. You are smart. What is your name? What is that guy's name?
Oh my god, that is not a
PG name.
The best part about Steam is the fact that you can just make your name something just absolutely ludicrous and that's- Spy,
what are you doing, man? Is he still alive? I don't know.
I would only think you'd do that if you had a dead ringer. Crap!
Oh, no! At least he got it. At least one of us is not going to burn to death.
Give him the old chop chop. It's the same guy. It's the same like really nice guy.
I love how it was that guy and
chicken. That killed me. Oh, this guy like xx like- and chicken. Gotta love chicken. Did not mean to click, by the way.
That was a misclick. Let's go! At least I killed him. At least I killed-
Oh, I gotta- I gotta like relax a little bit here. I'm being a little too crazy.
I gotta get- I gotta step back a little bit. Take a breather.
Okay, now it's time to bring the headshots back. Time to bring it back to headshot, Phil. And if not,
then you know what? What can you do? Headshot. Where- where are these-
That guy just came out of nowhere. Oh, this is bad. They're pushing us all the way back.
This is really bad. It started off really good, too.
Let's go. Me and sellon88. Damn, this is not good. Come on now. That's a spy right there.
That is not a spy. I'm so paranoid right now. Where's this other guy? No, I hit him right in
the back of the head with the stupid thing. Walk into it. We got a cactus. Get on the point here,
fellas. Spy? No. Keep it going here. Keep it going here. Even if I die, you will remember me.
Nice, nice. Oh, dude. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, Heavy. I didn't realize he had that little health.
He had like no health. I have to say sorry. And then sad face. Heavy, I'm sorry. I took that health.
We're gonna get it, though. Oh, by the way, speaking of just weird things, I have a hat on
today. It is a backwards baker boy. I think I've had this hat on before in previous videos.
The vintage baker boy. That's a miss. That's a miss as well. That's- oh man, he got me with such
a crazy meat shot right there. Health so bad. I'm gonna die. Oh, get lit. I might have to change
here. We might see a change. Huntsman ain't really working so well at this moment in time and
history. We got the point, at least. That's a good thing. Get him with that G-Rawdy. That sniper's
gunning for me. Good. If I can keep that sniper preoccupied, I'm happy. Oh, man. Nice shot. All
right, it's time to change. We gotta change to- we gotta go medic. We need one so bad. All right,
let's go, fellas. Let's do a super push here. Except I don't want to get myself killed, so don't
go too far away from me or else you're not gonna get healed. No, don't go down. Actually, yeah,
go down. Go down. That was a big mistake. Big mistake on my part. I should not have gone anywhere.
Are we gonna cap it? Are we gonna win? Oh, get on it. Yes. Oh, we did it. Hooray. Nice job, guys.
Good game all around. That's gonna wrap it up here for Face Game Fortress 2, Monday's edition.
Thank you guys so much for watching. Really do appreciate it. And I will see you guys all next
time. Clink. Mm. Take care, everybody.