But, you know, I gotta move on and I've gotta like order 600 nuggets.
Alright, give me Siren. This game is gonna take like 30 hours to beat.
And I got some bad news for you. No, I don't.
Siren! This is a PS2 game. This is not a PS1 game. This game seems interesting enough.
And we will do facecam for this one.
I'm probably gonna be... What time is it?
That would be plenty of time.
I need a PS2 memory card though, that would be...
That would be ideal, wouldn't it?
You guys just want the facecam.
Oh, right.
This is not even correct.
But it's like too wide.
Well, I need to reset this.
Oh, there's still... There's like filters on this.
Oh, that's why it looks so fucking weird.
No DualShock 2 analog controller inserted.
Oh, come on. I can't use the PS1 controller for this.
I have to...
I didn't think I needed to buy one because I had a DualShock.
Buy a PS2 controller in all caps. I'm not going to. Ever.
And I'm gonna not because I want you to be very angry about it.
Somebody said you're a millionaire. Just buy one.
Well, that's not true.
What the fuck was that?
Stop doing that!
This is a scary game, by the way.
As scary as it can be.
I need to change this to that I'm playing Siren.
I don't know. What should I... Should I call it Sound the Alarm?
I don't know. Sound the Alarm?
What is this game about?
Really good game. Really bad voice acting.
Oh, okay.
I'm not. Okay. How about like...
Sound the... Whatever. Who cares?
Time to get up for school.
Okay. Well, that should be good.
So should this at this point.
We're gonna get a cutscene?
Well, this looks like dog shit.
All right. I'm gonna have to do some changes here
because this looks like dog shit.
Like... Like hard to play.
This is still wrong.
I'm like... This is still like squished.
Oh, I don't care. Let's go.
All right. This is Siren.
This is Blurry.
All right. New game.
Both headphones.
How... Is it loud?
It's desynced. Right. I know. I'll fix it.
That's a lie. It's not desynced.
Turn your lights off.
What is she doing?
Subtitles. Fuck.
Who is it?
This looks pretty good on PS2.
It's like the graphics look actually pretty damn good.
All right. I need to turn my lights off.
It's the middle of the night.
It's the middle of the day, guys.
He tricked us.
Who's there?
Son of...
Zombie. Turn around.
Is he aiming the gun?
Why does he have sentience?
Mission objective.
Escape from police officer.
That's all I got right now.
Okay.
I did it.
We got to see the end of that story.
Okay.
Where do I go?
Oh, there he is. There he is. There he is.
Just run away?
Is there a... How do I...
Is there like a... That's okay.
Circle is crouch.
It's shut tight.
It's locked.
I can't like hide in the porta potty?
Can I get in the car?
Did this door open?
Okay. The front door just opens.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Give me the key.
A car key is lying on the table.
Press triangle button to access the list menu.
Pick up.
We picked up the car key.
All right. Anything else I can grab in here?
Before a guy comes in and shoots me.
There is a copy of the town newsletter on the table.
Honuto community newsletter.
It has been added to the archive.
Oh, my God. He's...
Lockers line the wall.
Let's go.
The door is locked.
Press triangle at list menu.
Do I drive the car?
Used car key.
Get in the truck.
Unlock the door and not go in?
How do I start the car?
The ignition is below the steering wheel.
Insert the key.
Turn the key to start the engine.
Letter grade plus one.
Doesn't count.
Mission accomplished.
I got into the car.
I didn't get to drive it.
We saw a cut scene of the car driving.
Does not count.
Day one.
So this is...
That was yesterday.
This is day...
What are we...
What is that?
What are we getting that for?
24...
Excuse me?
Are you okay?
Hello?
Why would you do this?
The person is trying to shoot you.
What do I do?
Call an ambulance?
An earthquake.
The car driving.
I thought...
Guys, I've been listening to cars blast by driving 100 fucking miles per hour by this place.
And it sounds like that.
Oh.
This is Source Filmmaker meme video.
Yes, I'll save the game.
Why is it taking so long to save it?
Is it fake bar?
Okay, now we're at...
This is two o'clock on day one.
Like, what?
Two hours have gone by since I fell down?
Yes.
Dead.
I'm not dead.
My cam is too big.
Is that blood?
Blood.
Okay, you know when...
People are linking me images where I look like I'm fucked up.
How do I understand the politician thing?
Where like politicians would be eating like ice cream or taking a bite out of like a hot dog
and somebody will find the one frame where they're like...
You're not safe here.
Follow me.
All right, reach road.
This red water is now coursing through your veins in place of all the blood you lost.
Ugh.
You have the water to thank for your recovery.
The water.
I know you're still shaking, but you will be better soon.
I'm so relieved.
I'm telling you, this is...
Anyway, we must hurry now.
That's... those faces.
Close your eyes.
Relax in your thoughts.
You're right here.
Sight jack.
Press the L2 button to enter sight jack mode.
Push the left analog stick in the direction of the character to sight jack
and align it so that the image is visible.
Press zero...
Circle X triangle squared to assign it to a particular viewpoint.
The hold is canceled when the left analog stick is pushed again,
but can be recalled by pushing the same button again.
Okay.
Sight jack mode.
What the fuck is happening?
What?
Okay, I put it on X.
It will be a while until you can move freely.
That's the monster's POV.
Please, follow me.
Do you got...
Do you got like a spear or anything?
Or maybe like a broadsword?
I'm used to that tonight.
Anything, a weapon, a gun.
I've seen a handgun.
I know how to walk.
Go back to the burrito game.
Running creates more noise than walking, thus attracting the attention of enemies.
Follow Hisako's instructions and head to...
This is a very sensitive analog, too.
I think I'm going to do tank controls.
Wait here.
Concentrating on our surroundings.
So I can't watch over you the whole time.
Turn this up a little.
You'll be able to feel me calling you.
You can also eavesdrop with sight jack.
Sight jack Hisako and follow her commands.
Where is she?
Which radio station is she on?
I swear to God, a funny joke would be if like all of a sudden like...
Your local NBC news station shows up right here.
I just saw it.
Where is it?
Ah, shit.
Too much.
Go back.
I just had it.
Gently moving the analog left and right.
Wait.
Is that her?
That's not her.
That's not her either.
Is that her?
What did she say?
Where'd she go?
Alright.
Why am I so out of breath?
I haven't even moved in like five minutes.
Are you shitting me?
I have to tap into the radio waves to find out where they are.
What the fuck was that?
There was a noise.
There was a noise in the room.
There's an issue.
Because there's like 30 Kinect games all over the floor.
I still haven't...
It could be anywhere.
Whatever it is, it could be anywhere.
This is why I don't ever have two headphones in.
I need to be completely aware of my surroundings.
How long ago was that stream?
Was that three months ago?
Well, because I didn't finish it.
Alright, let's go.
That was not three months ago.
That was like a month and a half ago.
How do I turn it off?
Square is the flashlight on and off.
Turning the flashlight off will decrease the chances of being spotted by enemies.
However, using a gun in the dark will decrease accuracy.
Oh, that is...
Is this a flashlight or a floodlight?
Because that is a huge amount of light I don't have.
I don't know where she went.
Where'd she go?
Climb up onto the roof and turn towards Hisako.
Be careful.
Pushing the left analogs are too far will cause you to climb back down.
Okay.
If the companion is a distance away, wait until they are near the appropriate spot.
That's not...
Hey!
That's Shout.
Oh, I have to get up there first.
Alright, get up.
Why can't she just climb up?
I don't know.
I'm alright.
Alright, pull up.
This game looks like it sucked.
I'm leaving.
Thanks for coming.
Alright, press square for more detailed instructions.
Okay.
I feel like I need to...
This is what it's like when you don't have your glasses on.
Okay.
I can't.
R1 and X is attack.
So holding R1 and X is attack.
R1 is draw weapon.
And it's also lock on if an enemy is within a target area.
Okay, R1 button plus the left analog stick is directional.
Okay.
Okay, move sideways.
L2 is enter sight jack mode.
Alright, I think I'm ready.
What?
Let me sight jack.
Alright.
There's more monsters though.
Is that a sniper?
Is that a crosshair on my head?
There's a monster in here.
Where is she?
Oh, it's you.
Oh, it's her.
Okay.
What time is it now?
The crosshair is basically located for where you are
compared to whatever you're sight jacking.
Oh, okay.
That makes sense.
Alright, so now this is day one.
Tam and...
So this is the same time, but this is a different person.
Professor?
What is this place?
Where are we?
I just don't get it.
What's going on?
The eyes moving back and forth.
I told you to wait in the car.
But what's happening?
What is this?
Why is this happening?
This is exactly why I told you not to come.
Professor, we need to find the villagers.
They must be panicking.
Please shut up.
Somebody's sight jacking.
From now on, you will do exactly as I tell you.
What?
Until I call you, keep your eyes closed and stay still.
Do you understand?
Professor, a real gun?
No.
It's fake.
Okay, come on.
Okay.
They always ask that.
Is that a real gun?
That's one time I just wanted to not be.
No, it's part of a costume.
I did a Wild West thing.
It's just been in my bag ever since.
I haven't cleaned out my bag.
Have you seen my fucking connect room?
Reach road to Kuruwari with Yoriko Anno.
So I'm supposed to concentrate and...
What the fuck was that?
...and listen to your voice.
Somebody just shot me.
Somebody shot me with a gun.
Did you shoot me?
Who shot me with a gun?
What?
What's going on?
All right, I keep...
Going back is too dangerous.
I...
Okay, I...
It was me.
Okay, the two...
I can see the two crosshairs.
I'm supposed to concentrate.
Where is that person?
Oh, there you are.
Where are you?
All right.
So you're in...
Okay, I'm over there.
So he's to the right.
That's us.
So he's up like that way.
He's up there.
Like up there.
How do I get by this?
Where's the other guy?
There's two.
Okay, that's...
All right, I'm gonna put you on square.
So then that's...
Okay, I've got X.
And square.
Okay, now I want to find the other one.
There's somebody walking around.
Right here.
Okay, circle.
So I've got square.
Square is her.
X is sniper.
Circle is person walking around.
She needs to follow me?
Come here.
Hey!
You coming?
Don't get sniped.
Why are you going...
What was that?
Okay, let's go.
That's it.
I don't have anything else on the radio, right?
There's only two enemies.
Okay, stay with me.
I do have a gun.
I hate this.
I don't even know where that is.
Should I go this way?
I can't go this way.
I don't get sniped either.
You can fall off this edge.
Don't fucking do that.
All right, he's at the house.
There's like a crate in a house.
Aim, head to...
Okay.
Wait, where is that?
There's a well here.
Move around so I can see where I am.
Oh my god, we're right there.
What do we do?
Where are we hidden?
Are we hidden at all?
Can he see us?
He can't...
Shoot him!
Is it dead?
It looks like it's just down.
Okay, let's go.
I'm not going to stand around and find out.
Let's go.
Where's the sniper?
Can't see us.
All right, let's go.
Are there any more monsters?
Probably not, right?
They can't be.
Which way do I go?
Wasn't Jerma playing as a little kid earlier?
Wait, don't go that way.
Holy fuck.
Oh my god.
This way.
Don't go that way.
I'm going to tap into the...
And see if there's anything else I can...
What?
Oh my goodness, there's other people.
Shoot.
Okay, let me tap in.
Sniper, is that it?
It's you.
What is this?
Oh, there's a person on the ground.
Okay, I get it.
Go.
Don't move, don't move.
Don't move.
There's something else here.
Who the hell are you?
No, it's you.
Oh, I hate this.
I really don't like this.
There's a radio on the shelf that appears to be broken and only receives static.
That's it?
There doesn't appear to be anything useful here.
There's nothing else in here?
I can't talk.
Looks like there's a book right here.
There's an old album.
Nothing about it particularly catches your attention.
Look behind you.
Okay, I'm not gonna lie.
I thought that right there.
This, I thought, see that black right there?
I thought that was Kim behind me.
About to like grab me.
So what am I supposed to do here?
I just have to get out of here, right?
But I can't, can I?
Wait.
I have a context menu.
Hide.
Pick up.
You picked up the broken radio.
Junk.
Can I pick up the book?
I don't think so.
All right, I have the radio.
All right, come here.
All right, let me see where they are.
He's always up top there.
They're still on the ground.
And you, well, I don't even know what you got.
You're walking around the shed.
Can I go down here?
Well, I need to help you, don't I?
No, all right, you can do it.
Good.
Wait a minute.
Is this right here?
Turn around so I can see if this is right here.
It is.
It is, it is, it is, it is.
Okay, all right, it is.
Get over here.
So we're behind that side.
Which way did they go?
Did they turn around from here?
All right, they're gonna be right here.
Fuck.
Where are they?
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Don't put your hands up like that.
Where are they?
I think we should get moving.
Shh!
Where'd you go?
Where did they go?
Where are they?
Are they behind the shed?
There you are, there you are.
Run!
It's time to run!
No, don't!
This way!
Hurry up!
Hello?
The...
They tripped.
All right.
Still this person on the bridge with the rifle.
All right, where do I need to go though?
I need to get...
In...
What's the mission?
Get out of here, right?
Did I miss something up here?
Classic snipers.
I keep running into doors.
What's the actual mission?
Reach the road to...
Okay, reach the road.
All right, so is that right over here?
Why is this person standing up?
Where's my friend?
Oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck, oh fuck.
I don't even know where that person is.
Come on.
Objectives.
Do I have to...
Do I have no bullets at all?
I'm done.
I have no bullets.
I'm out.
Where did...
Where did she go?
Because this is where we came from.
Are you here?
Hey!
Where are you?
Oh.
Is she dead?
I need to find her signal.
I'm out of bullets.
Okay.
This is gonna be a really, really odd reference.
But...
He sounds like that old British cartoon character, Mr. Bloppy.
I gotta find her sequence.
Where is she?
Is this her?
Oh, she's just standing in that same spot.
The sniper.
Oh shit, the sniper.
This is gonna be the sniper.
Fuck.
Reach the road.
I gotta go wrap around.
So, I'm supposed to concentrate and listen to your voice.
I was there.
Well, I'm doing something kind of strange.
All right, let's just go.
I know where I'm going.
Who saw me?
I got you.
I got...
Okay, you are X.
You're gonna be square.
Okay, let's move.
You're looking more defo than Franco.
All right.
Why do I know about Mr. Bloppy?
Because I know everything.
All right.
Give me a topic.
Okay, I made it across the bank.
Come here.
Now, we're just gonna go this way.
I gotta get the radio.
He knows.
Ah, can you give me a talk?
Throw a topic over here.
What's the RGB code for magenta?
Uh, pound pound or pound FF 0022234FH.
I almost shot her.
That's the hex idiot.
I'm sorry, I was going...
I'm sorry, I was going next level on you.
All right, where am I going?
All right, this is...
This is a pay attention game.
I have to pay attention.
So, I'm gonna go...
Can I open this?
Is this like a mailbox?
What's the hex?
That's hex not...
Yeah, that's fine.
What's the RGB?
Wait a minute.
The sniper.
You're not gonna shoot me in the head, are you?
So, I'm supposed to concentrate and listen to your voice.
So, how do I...
How do I get up there without them knowing?
Something kind of strange.
Hey, just got here.
How long has he been streaming?
Oh, like three and a half hours, just about.
So, what the...
What am I...
I guess I don't even have to take him out.
Just keep going.
Because this...
I get around him.
Right here.
So, I'm just gonna keep moving forward.
Why does he know that?
Right, that's good.
Can I open this door?
No, it's ported.
But why?
Why do I know that?
Just do.
Why can I do the ABCs backwards?
Z-X-Y-W-Q-T-S-V-U-T-O-P-N-L-O-A-G-H-A-B-C-A.
Why can I do that?
Shit.
Sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper, sniper.
Turn the light on.
Made it.
Okay, this is where the other guy is.
All right, I see.
You should...
You should do a blobby stream.
What does that even mean?
Somebody else is there.
I want to know where they are.
You are down.
Okay.
And the sniper is still available, but we don't even care about the sniper.
Let's go.
It's the radio.
I remember this.
Pick up the radio.
No, no, no, come here.
Okay, I have the broken radio.
What's it got to do with that piece of junk?
I really don't know.
I have no idea.
But this is kind of the end of the line here.
I guess I could go...
Can I go around here?
Is there anywhere else I can go down here?
What, am I stream going down?
I guess, okay, I could go down this way.
There's a guy.
Where is he?
He's right next to the tower here.
No, he's not.
Where is he?
I have plenty of ammo.
In fact, I'm going to reload.
No, I just want to say F.
Oh, all right.
All right, there's another guy here.
Nothing else around here.
Okay, where is that?
There you are.
Bring us back here.
I haven't been in here yet.
So...
Oh, that's the sniper.
How the fuck do I get out of here?
Oh, drop down here and then bang right.
Right?
Okay.
All right, I made it.
This is the end.
We have to sneak over here and then bang right.
I don't think he sees us.
Because this is the road, right?
This is the...
Who's doing that?
So confused.
No, I did this already.
So what the fuck am I supposed to be doing?
It's like, oh, go to this next area.
But where is it?
This is back where the radio was.
Oh, there you go.
I have a map, do I?
All right, now we're jumping back to Kyo-Yo.
It's not a dream.
Are we winning?
Um, sort of.
Okay.
What do we do now?
All we can do is wait here until Makino and the others arrive.
Are you...
Is this a place of worship?
I mean, it kind of looks like one.
But it's different from the other ones I've seen.
It may seem strange, but this is our faith.
Well, I don't know anything about it.
So what a random pose.
It must be a sign.
Outsiders like you don't normally possess the sight.
Stereo.
Audio, I heard that over there.
Book of Deliverance, Chaos at the End Times has been added to your archive.
Okay.
I won't be reading it, but at least I know it's there.
A new character.
We keep getting new...
I can't even...
I can't establish any relationship with any of these characters.
We've seen too many of them.
What's this?
My ears.
All right, reach the road.
I've just reached the road.
Head towards the road.
I don't have anything.
I don't have any weapons.
I'm just a guy.
Wait.
Everybody seems to have this power though.
Are they gonna fight?
There's so many people here.
I said...
Some of these people said, I can't hear you.
Never mind.
It was just for a second, I thought, why did that kid pan?
The camera went down and I thought he...
I don't know.
I don't even have a flashlight.
Oh shit.
Is there a sniper?
All right, somebody's at the end of this bridge.
No, it's not a bridge.
What an optical illusion.
I thought that was a street lamp.
I think it's safe this way.
Can I push these over?
There are gas cylinders here.
I don't shout.
Don't go into the light.
I'm gonna try not to.
That's the person with the mallet.
Okay.
Just get to the place I need to be.
And this doesn't open.
There's a ladder.
No, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Stop doing that.
Open the door.
The person...
How do I get up?
I think I have to go up this way.
The person fell off the roof.
Okay.
What should I do?
Is there anything up here?
Like a gun or something?
Okay, they're climbing up here.
How do I push?
They're all coming up here at the same time.
There's too many up here.
Cast a spell.
Stupefy.
Oh my god.
That was, that was very funny.
That was really funny.
Cast a spell.
I lost my wand though.
So I obviously have to go up there.
And I, this is just a runaway.
There is a sniper.
Where are you?
Where's the sniper?
The sniper was probably up in the roost that I climbed up.
You gotta be kidding me.
An old lady just killed me with a fucking mallet.
What is that?
I don't even know what you're holding.
Okay.
I gotta go around.
There was a spoon.
Spoon could be a mallet.
It's rounded.
Somebody has a gun.
I died of being scared.
Okay.
Slow down.
Okay, there's mallet guy.
There's guy with gun.
Old lady with spoon is right here.
I'm pretty certain that I just did the original like AT&T jingle.
All right, I got you.
This is what I wanted.
Get out.
When's mom is late?
When mom is late with the chicken tendies.
Why this?
I don't even know what that means.
Why did I read that?
I don't, because I was trying to figure out,
I was trying to process in my brain what that meant.
So I'm reading it out loud to try to figure out what
that, what that person was trying to say to me.
Then why do they have to be always talking to me?
What do you mean no one said that?
Yes, they did.
You're going to smash brothers me?
Really?
You're going to like quadruple grab me?
I got gun.
I'm dead.
Go.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Now it's climb.
Climb, climb.
Climb the ladder that is right here somewhere.
I missed it.
What the fuck is this thing?
Okay.
Now don't go up there.
Well, that was fucking completely pointless.
Why is he still climbing?
No, get up.
Can I go that way?
I can't climb this.
No, I can't.
This is just, this is just what the sniper is.
There's nothing important.
There's nothing here.
This doesn't do anything.
No, this doesn't do anything.
This, this is blocked.
So this, this area is blocked.
I can't do anything here.
Unless I can go this way.
Guess?
Kind of, but I, this, this door, this door doesn't open.
Okay.
It does open.
You have to press the X button.
I thought you had to do is the context menu, but you just have to press X.
I deserve that.
I thought it was, you had to hit triangle to do, to like, all right.
So why is it X is used for doors, but triangle is used to do everything else.
All right.
We're just doing full on ASMR for the next like 15 minutes.
Ew.
Did they hear me?
All right.
I'm going to do this, do Trump again.
You're the only person I think that's ever asked me to do that.
I know I'm doing this so wrong.
I know that I'm supposed to be sneaking around through here.
What did, what?
We held hands and I died.
She just, she break my wrists.
I don't understand.
Reach the road.
I know I'm supposed to be like pinning, uh, I just walked over here.
But I know, but I'm supposed to be sneaking around and I, and I get it.
Right.
But sneaking to where do I have a map?
Do I, is this, what is this?
Next stage, next stage.
No, this is freaking me out.
Guide?
No, mission objective.
No, I don't have a map or anything.
Maybe I just, all right.
Well now I need to see what's over on the left side.
I'm going to get shot.
What if I get shot with a gun like twice?
What a grandmother.
Bending my wrist kind of hard is enough to kill me.
Okay.
This is what I wanted to do instead of going this way.
I'm going to go through here into the door, close the door and I close it.
Okay.
Now I'm going to just hide.
Can I open this?
There's a refrigerator.
The refrigerator is not plugged in.
Plug it in.
This does not open.
It doesn't.
It does.
All right.
What's in here?
There's a cassette player.
It looks like there's some power left in the batteries.
Use it.
How do I play it?
4-1-1.
Oh, 4-1-1.
It's going to play the tape from the thing.
Well, I have a code now for something.
It's a hanging scroll which depicts a scene from a local folktale.
What's that behind you on cam?
Fucking an alien.
And I'm going to be like eaten alive on camera.
Maybe.
Okay.
So I have 0-4-1-1.
Here.
I can't get in there.
So I have this like 0-4-1-1 frequency.
What do I do with that frequency?
I have no clue.
I'm crazy.
I thought that was a bug.
I thought this was an insect coming to fucking sting me.
There's nobody right here, but where the fuck am I supposed to go?
I'm just going to go out here.
Oh, please.
How did you see me?
Oh, wait.
The code.
Combination lock.
Remove lock.
I know it's 0-4-1-1.
There's no time for that now.
Oh, fuck off.
Shut the door.
Shut the door on him.
I know it's...
I know it's comp...
Oh, man.
I'm so close.
But so far at the same time.
There's no time for that now.
Select is the map?
Why?
Okay.
So I have to go down here.
So we go around to the right, bang a left, and then go.
I'm just running for it.
Does it keep me?
So go around, straight take, bang a left, and then go around the whole thing.
Bang a left.
Oh, that guy has the gun.
Right.
Okay.
All right.
I got to do this the right way.
I can do this the right way.
I've got to go around and...
All right.
You're a very good shot.
You don't bang a literal left.
You bang a metaphorical left.
I have to go around and just sneak around.
Okay, sneak.
Fuck.
No, fuck it.
Just go.
That's the only time that I know that I'm able to actually do...
I just got shot in the fucking head.
Oh, come on.
I just...
I don't want to sneak.
Oh, I don't like...
I don't want to fucking crouch around and like Metal Gear Solid, like five enemies.
Okay.
Because you sneak so slow.
You go like you're in slow motion.
Like, look.
That's how fast I have to go.
Four people playing a stealth game and they refuse to sneak.
I didn't know this was a stealth game.
I thought this was a horror game.
I don't want to sneak around the scares.
I want them to scare me.
You put in turbo.
Ejected.
You put in splinter cell.
Bang.
Now that would redeem it.
That would redeem it.
I move so slow.
Is there a streamed splinter cell game?
Is the first three amazing?
No.
Put them on the list.
Let's do it.
Is it a good game?
Is it fun?
It's good.
It is a good game.
I'm not...
I'm telling you.
It's actually pretty fun.
It is.
I don't...
It's interesting mechanics.
Really interesting mechanic.
I'm serious.
I'm not just saying this.
I'm not just saying.
It's a very interesting game.
Try this one more time.
The fuck face stat.
Okay.
He has auto lock on.
No.
I'm going to try to get through.
Is the German runner good games?
We played two great games before this.
No.
Shit.
That means I'm saying it's not good.
Whatever.
Report that guy for aimbotting.
I'm just going to go straight.
Even if he shoots me once.
Just go.
Okay.
I'm good.
This is my chance.
My chance.
Okay.
I got to go left.
Can I go...
So I am going left.
This is me going left.
Isn't it?
How am I still...
Why does it still say I'm over there?
Because I ain't got nowhere to go.
None of these...
Is this open?
Can I like get in this?
Can I do anything here?
This is all blocked up.
Nothing up there.
I can't...
I guess I could try to...
Don't do it.
I can...
Really?
I can climb this shit?
Oh.
Give me a break.
I just found it.
He's coming up.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, hurry.
I just...
I just did it.
Finish the game.
All right.
I'll finish the tutorial.
That was too realistic for me.
Because that was...
That was like a dog is actually in your room like dying.
Are you okay?
Hey.
This place is messed up.
Let's just go to the church together.
And then think about what to do.
The dog's already dead anyway.
I'm sorry, but we have to.
What happened?
Am I going to play Blair Witch?
No, I heard it wasn't very good.
I heard it was actually pretty bad.
Is that true?
As I heard?
That's the...
Okay, so like new horror games?
The last like two or three new horror games that have come out
I've heard have been actually pretty bad.
Will you play bad games?
No, well, not like bad as in like the game's just not good.
It's not like there's nothing there.
Are you okay?
Can't you walk a bit more slowly?
I'm losing you.
What do you mean?
This game is not good.
I'm getting close to turning it off.
As you've just heard about two minutes ago.
You still have more to do.
You know that we can't proceed without you.
Won't be long before someone takes a trip to the other side.
It looks like you've been taking good care of my sister.
Oh, sick, sick watch.
Watch.
Hey.
Let's go.
What?
What happened?
All right, we're reaching a lot of roads, okay?
That's my complaint so far with the game.
First four missions of the game.
Reach the road.
Why can't it be find the...
Find the box.
Climb the tree.
Reach the road.
Find an object that'll act as a weapon.
I can do that.
Are you coming?
Let's go.
I need to find something that'll be a weapon.
What we got?
The map.
All right, cool.
I don't know.
This map is just looks like an organ.
Not the piano type.
Are people gonna go?
No, like a kidney.
She keeps bending her neck backwards and looking at me.
She's just got...
She's got...
Look at that nerd neck.
Where are you?
We are right over this way.
All right, is it two?
It's two.
So you're right here.
What is wrong with some people?
What is...
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong?
Yeah.
All right, I need a weapon.
Weapon.
A poker has been thrust into the veins of the bonfire.
Looks like it would make a good weapon.
Got it.
Okay, you can do that.
You can...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I need to dislocate your left shoulder.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Oh, I'm making you climb now too?
I'm awful.
I'm sorry.
All right, so we got to go through the iron warehouse.
What the hell it said.
Well, yeah, she wasn't the thing.
That's good.
Open lock?
The lock is old and the keyhole is rusted open.
Probably impossible to open with a key.
Oh, well then.
Look at me.
What?
Who is it?
Oh, that guy's huge.
Where did...
Where is she?
Where did she go?
Where's my friend?
It's Bushido Blade.
See?
One hit, two hits.
Did she just say look at me?
Yeah.
I think she did.
But where are you?
I don't know where she is.
Yes, because she lost you.
Well, just yell back to me.
How hard is it for you to yell back?
Now I have to find you.
Found you.
Come here.
Get over here.
Try...
I was thinking of saying...
Oh no, she's shoving vegetables down my throat like a grandma.
That's how the grandma kills you.
But then I got hit twice.
I didn't want to do this again.
And it was...
I know.
That's why I didn't do it and I buried it.
All right, last try.
Last try and then...
What time is it?
It's been four hours.
I'll hang out for a while.
Turn on a light.
Your face game is getting too dark.
Everyone just totally turn it off.
Follow me.
Come here.
Get over here.
What the fuck is she?
Do I really need to like jack into your brain to see where you went?
Who the hell is that?
Okay, you made it.
All right.
Give me the poker.
Do you need help getting up that?
We're good.
Let's go.
Get past the iron gate.
Still follow me.
Make sure you're still behind me.
The iron gate is up here.
Follow me still.
Come on.
I don't even know if this is the right way to the iron gate.
It might not.
There it is.
Iron gate.
Where'd you go?
Oh no, you turned away.
She's infected now.
Imagine hitting this two or three times and not figuring this out.
You have to hit it three times.
Now she should be right next to me.
Head towards the settlement so that they like to go up there.
Okay, let's move.
You're with me, right?
Oh, by the way, a lot of people were saying to play Soma.
I don't think that has to even be a Halloween like stream.
I think I could just play that for fun.
That doesn't have to be like, oh no, it's the 31st.
All horror games turn off.
No, we can do that.
Come here.
It's not that scary.
I'll show you.
Look, I'll prove it.
Don't run down here.
Watch.
Pay attention.
Look how scared he is.
I've heard so much about this guy.
He's so strong.
He's really, really powerful.
That's right, motherfucker.
Get up here.
See?
Now pick that up.
Pick up his entire iron.
Hey, what's going on?
Why wouldn't...
That was weird.
All right, come over here.
Right there.
All right.
All right, stay with me.
I missed.
Two, three, up.
Wait.
Hold on.
She's blind?
Oh, as I'm listening?
No, people were like talking about my Lego hair for like 30 minutes.
Siren.
Singing.
River of blood.
Are you with me here?
So that means when I swung this and hit her in the face,
I just didn't know I was...
It appears to be the back end of the church, but there's a sturdy lock on it.
Well, where is this sturdy lock?
Knock it off.
That's horrible.
What do you mean you didn't know?
No, like...
You know what I'm saying.
All right, I think there's a sniper over there.
A sniper right in front of us.
I do appreciate every major blood-borne boss in the background.
It's like such a tiny room.
Come on.
Stalling because game sucks.
No, that's not...
I'm not.
I'm just trying to see where people are.
It's okay.
Okay.
I gotta go this way.
Where's that sniper?
Not looking this way, but I'm gonna see.
Turn around.
This way.
Doesn't look like it.
Are you still there?
Did it.
Good.
Yes, I wish to save.
This is more important to me.
Than the game at the moment.
Just give me one second.
So I can listen, too.
He seems to be making a lot of fuss about a suitcase.
Okay.
Just to everyone who knew what I was talking about.
Another character.
Reach the road.
Wait, do I have a...
Oh, shit.
I have like a zoomable shotgun.
Play the blob...
I can't even hear what it's doing because I'm not plugged in.
I don't know what it's doing.
There's two of them on screen.
I can't hear it.
I can only hear the game because my headphones are plugged into the game.
With the scramble for trolleys, the automatic doors, and the moving walkway.
No wonder we all like traffic.
Where?
Shoot!
All right.
I don't...
I'm done with Mr. Blobby.
Blame the mouse?
There is no mice.
Just a generic, not official PlayStation 2 controller.
For a second, I had like a mini heart attack.
Because you know, like...
Did you guys' parents...
Did your mother ever put a sticker here that had your name and address on it?
Like, this is who this belongs to!
No?
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
I forgot how old I was.
This is like 25 years ago.
This is before the invention of the cell phone.
Am I...
All right, I'm gonna do this again.
My mom put that sticker on me.
Look at the snipers.
Sniper on the train tracks.
Is there only one sniper?
There's one sniper that's...
But you're not even, like, in the game.
Wait.
They're gonna be right down here.
How the hell am I gonna control this with the analog?
Oh, shit.
Who's that?
Is that me?
Who's shooting the gun up here?
What?
Okay, so they don't...
All right, so they don't come into frame.
You can't do the static thing.
Unless they're within, like, a certain range, I guess.
I know what that guy is, but how am I gonna out-snipe that person?
Maybe sneak?
This game's making me nauseous.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Did I already shoot him?
Yeah.
Crap.
You're right.
Hey, what am I, what am I, what am I blubbing up to?
Oh.
Yes, those moving walkways are certain...
Okay, this, I don't...
I'm just gonna crouch?
It's the guy who's...
It's this person right here, right?
I can't see that.
I guess I can.
Oh, come on.
This is gonna be fucking impossible.
Uh...
I can't, I can't see him.
I have to have to sneak around.
Come on.
We demand Mr. Blobby.
I just exed out of the Blobby window.
I'm mad at this game.
He still refuses to sneak.
Just roll.
Just lie in there, just roll.
Just do, just forward roll.
I've been seen.
Go the other way?
Or just run by and duck?
There's no way you've heard me walking from all the way back here.
Wait, so...
What? How am I supposed to go?
Is the building over here on the left?
Yes?
This guy's stream sniping.
Could be.
There's somebody in this...
There's somebody here though.
Where's this other person?
They're like right in here.
I have to go around.
Yeah, I can't...
I gotta go around.
But there's somebody in here.
What was that image?
Oh my god!
Stop!
Get away from my heart!
Damn it.
Well, I know where to go.
I'm gonna try to...
Oh, shit.
Just don't be bad.
The, the, the, the two or three words that you say to a streamer and I'll look over and they'll go,
Shut up!
Shut up, idiot!
No, I'm, I'm doing fine!
It's this game, the game controls are all fucked up.
It's the game...
Ah!
No, I'm all upset!
Somebody is right here.
I'm just gonna aim the gun.
It zoomed in too far.
How do I pull it out?
Wait, were they...
They were over here last time.
All right, I'm...
I'm afraid...
There you are.
Nope.
Was that just anti-aliasing?
No, that was just...
That was just actual like bad aliasing.
Where is this person?
Not you.
Where are they?
Maybe it's, maybe it's up here.
Oh, shoot the lock.
What?
Why would I be standing this close?
Shoot the chain.
Oh no.
I think your character is smashed.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done playing this one.
This is fun.
It was real, actually pretty fun.
But after that, I'm...
I mean, I have to stop.
I'm done.
Oh no, what will I do?
Who's shooting a gun?
What?
No, please, please.
Oh no.
The fucking neck grab.
God damn it.
Fuck.
This old man joke.
This old man joke gets shot.
Wait, this old man joke gets shot joke isn't funny.
I got him.
I killed him.
I killed the motherfucker.
He's dead.
Holy shit.
Oh, they're coming though.
No, run, run, run.
Please run.
Just jump off the edge.
Please, for the love of God.
I did. I win.
I won. I beat the game.
I beat the game.
I killed the boss.
I won.
That was the boss of the level.
I win.
Found the reload button.
Pog.
Don't ever play this again.
The game's not bad.
It's hot.
I think there's like five of these.
Are we going to see the credits today?
You could try the PS3 one.
It was cool.
That was a cool effect.
It was a cool thing.
So what am I doing now?
That's a really good question.
I don't really have time to start very much else.
We're doing jackbox tomorrow.
So I might just put in...
No, it's not into the screen.
Um, I gotta turn the lights on.
I'm gonna connect.
No, no way.
It's not...
I can't get that set up.
No, uh, no, no Dead Rising.
I have to, I have to like download the game.
And I don't want to start something like that.
I want to, I want to sit down and play Dead Rising for like seven to eight hours.
It's great.
All right.
I'm taking that out.
Uh, you know what I'm gonna do?
I kind of...
Like, this is gonna sound crazy.
But I kind of want to like play, um, I'm Jeremy Lamy again for like a little bit.
I don't know why.
This is why I want to let this one song I want to play.
I want to like play the plane song again.
I was hearing that in the shower the last like few days.
That like, I was like, I kind of want to do that right now.
Plus PlayStation 2 and the...
All this shit is hooked up right now.
I might as well just do it because I'm never gonna play it again.
Oh, sorry.
I just did that to you.
Where is, where is Jeremy Lamy?