Okay, what else do we have to finish up?
Hide behind the table in the camera room?
Uh, uh, no.
Why do you have a filter on?
Why don't I just turn the gamma down?
Do Breath of the Wild?
No, I'd rather, I don't want to start that now.
What can I do for the next like 30 minutes?
What do you think?
I thought, I got a couple other games.
Let me see, what else do I have here?
Five Nights at Freddy's.
Okay, fine.
I will do...
No, I'm not playing that.
I'm not playing Five Nights at Freddy's.
Because I'm gonna have to do Night 1 again and like that's...
I don't want to sit through Night 1.
Please, do you really want me to play Five Nights at Freddy's?
Five Nights at Freddy's, it's Freddy's 2.
Okay, so I want a poll for me to play Five Nights at Freddy's 2.
And it has to be at least 75%.
And I'll do it right now.
What about Faith?
I do have Faith, but I feel like it's too late to start it.
I would come back and play it.
Five Nights at Freddy's 2, yeah.
I would play that next week.
Just because it's not Halloween anymore doesn't mean I can't play them.
Five Nights at Freddy's 2, it's gonna be at least 75%.
I don't think this is gonna win.
Judging by the preliminary amount here.
That's the best one?
Yeah, I think it probably is.
Let me see if I can help you guys.
Vote for it.
Let's make it happen.
I want to see 75%.
I'm not sure it's even gonna get there.
What was the other one?
Hold on.
I swear I had another couple of games that I wanted to do.
I don't think it's gonna make it.
He wants to play it so bad.
I have like the other Dread X Collection stuff.
Let's do that.
What about Dread X Collection 5?
I'll just play a couple of random things.
Yeah, you're not gonna make it.
I'm doing Dread X Collection 5.
You guys are just not gonna make it.
Yeah, I said 75%.
You didn't get there.
Okay, let me capture it.
Video resolution, that's fine.
That's fine.
Field of view is fine.
This is fine.
Okay, story mode on this?
Interesting.
This is number five.
Story mode.
Strangle man's hunt.
Thousand, the place where your party is out of this world.
Locals are celebrating Hanas.
A nightless night and midsummer said to hold magical power.
A ritual must be completed.
The pain whispers in an infamous art gallery
where mysterious disappearances have occurred.
The book of blood?
Kareo.
A late night of karaoke.
A wrong turn singing.
Where did the train station come from?
Where does it go?
Rotten stigma.
Spirit guardian.
We never left.
Mystige.
Resver- there's a lot in this one.
Beyond the curtain.
All right, what's a good one?
This is collection five.
This one's so good.
Wait, what?
I need to get unlocked.
Error.
Please assemble band before musical performance.
Okay.
Assemble band?
Is every single door stuck?
Is it going to the bathroom?
Gas can is piss.
Does that mean that there's piss in the gas can
or does that mean someone with my name?
What is this?
Can I read it?
No, better than go outside when the besides.
Elvin was too long a child.
He hadn't time to be afraid of silly bedtime stories.
Only babies were afraid of the strangle man.
Okay.
Oh, a present.
Take it back to my birthday table to open it.
And here we go.
Somebody said this is the best one.
We'll find out.
Finland, June 24th, 1888.
Farmhouses across the nation are preparing
to celebrate the midsummer Yuhannes.
Considered to be a magical night,
many younger folk participate and play
for rituals and fun games.
One of these games was called the...
It's a black screen.
Huh?
Why is it a black screen?
Hold on.
Why can't you see it?
Oh, no.
Weird.
What if I do this?
Is that going to do it?
I don't think this...
I can't capture this.
Why?
That's weird.
Can you see it?
No.
Yeah, this is with window capture on.
The other one was game capture.
Now it captured the other game.
What if I...
Hold on.
That was very strange.
I cannot have it in full screen.
So it has to be in a window.
Okay.
That's fine.
What the fuck is this?
I know it's hard.
Dude, what?
What the hell?
You can't see it.
You can't see it anymore.
Dude, what?
Okay.
Now the game capture works.
I'm going to keep it on this, I guess.
Let's turn off the window capture.
You were the one to blame last year for talking to others.
You were just jealous.
Don't let others blame you.
Try the ritual I told you about.
Why don't you try that thing I told you about?
Seven flowers down the well.
I don't believe in these things, but that's how I met your mother.
She's still alive to see what kind of a coward you become.
I can't imagine how hurt she would be.
No, don't even remind me you look like me.
Drop seven flowers into the well and you will see the reflection of your future love.
Though anyone loving you here seems impossible.
Okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
What?
What the fuck?
Get the fuck off.
What happened last year?
And stay out of everyone's way.
Hannah's is here.
I hope you remember what happened last year.
Stay out of everyone's way.
The kids are drinking on the roof so the adults don't notice.
You get the feeling they're planning something.
I'm getting somebody pissing on me.
I just got pissed on.
I just got somebody peed on me.
Okay.
That was interesting.
People tend to whip themselves with it.
Vita, when in sauna, helps you clean your body.
Hey, this is not a flower.
You!
That costume is even better than last year's.
Can't wait to see how the little...
It's mommy time?
Why you didn't run into me?
Run up the FOV.
Dude, can I?
I can't.
Celebrate a good harvest.
Dancing around the maypole is said to ensure fertility.
Finland, land of stoic people where every man and woman fends for themselves.
Children learn from a young age to never show their true feelings.
Being different means to be shunned.
You had to learn it the hard way.
Okay, I need to find flowers.
Am I dying?
Guys, I think I'm dying.
Is there a heel?
It's...
That pattern's weird.
I forgot what it means to be true.
Is there a heel?
There has to be a heel somewhere, right?
Hey, look at how fucked up this pattern is.
One...
You didn't even make it through that.
That's bullshit.
They...
That didn't make it through.
Okay, so it's one, two...
When we go, like...
Um...
Three more?
You can feel it inside you, the true meaning.
No field work.
Okay.
Eh.
Found this village.
He defended Finland from invading Viking forces with the help of the gods themselves.
Okay.
Get away from me.
What the fuck are you doing here?
What's that?
Okay.
Hey, everybody.
One of us is in...
Y'all know what to do.
Get the hud's faulty.
Hud's faulty.
Suffering.
Dude, don't ask me where the other two are.
I have no idea.
One more.
Where's the last one?
Ah, where's the last one?
That's it, last one.
I win.
Kill them all, my love.
Jesus.
All right, I did what you asked.
All right, I did it.
Now what?
I did it.
Stop killing people?
I thought I...
Isn't this how I beat the level?
How many people are in here?
I need to feed him.
Oh.
You...
I need to feed this guy?
No, you don't?
Oh, okay.
I don't think there's anybody left.
Is there somebody else here?
Those things?
I have to give it to those too?
I thought they were...
I thought they were on my side.
Got it.
Just one more thing to do and then we can be together.
Go and meet your father.
Okay.
I'm proud of you, my love.
There's nothing that can stop you anymore.
The world is ours.
Now go and make them all suffer.
I got a pig?
That was interesting.
That was very weird.
That was very interesting.
I don't know how to feel about it.
It was just so bizarre.
Pretty cool.
Let's see if I can...
I'm still capturing the game.
Which I don't think I am.
Is it still open?
Uh oh.
I think it crashed.
No, we're still here.
It was kind of weird.
There we go.
Okay.
Another page of the book.
Strangle Man.
Just a silly book.
What's another good one?
Should we do the karaoke one?
Karaoke one's good.
All right, I need another present.
Error.
Please assemble band before musical performance.
I'm gonna play Roblox.
I'll play Roblox on your birthday.
Okay.
Next year.
Oh, here's a page.
Give me a present.
The 10th has been circled.
10th of October.
Uh, I'm not reading all that.
Present is the next present.
I missed it.
Turn the light on and off.
What happened?
Thank you.
All right, I'll do the karaoke one.
I hope it captures.
I think I have to do the window again.
This video game contains flashes of light.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Okay.
Capture the window.
That's so weird how that happens.
I think it's because it's a compilation
and it's loading a different game.
There.
Okay, so that should do it.
Why is this on the screen?
Um, what's going on?
I think it crashed.
Shit.
What?
Uh, yeah, it's crashed.
Shit.
Come on, really?
Can I reload it?
Let me try reloading it.
I'll try one more time.
Okay, new game.
I'm just gonna do new game.
You don't see it, but that's all right.
I'm just trying to get into the game first.
Like right here.
Oh, this is fucked up.
This is very bizarre.
Okay.
Can you see it now?
I think you can see it now.
Hey, it's loud as all hell.
Turn that down.
Let's try it.
It looks busy.
Broken.
I guess it's a karaoke machine.
I have no interest in talking to this guy.
One shot, please.
Okay.
Take it.
Jasper and Lace.
I'm Jasper, the guy by the stage is Lace.
And before you ask, yes, we're identical twins.
Where's the toilet?
It's broken.
What if I have to go?
This is why we only sell shots.
You drank too much before you came here.
There's a toilet in the back.
Okay, thanks.
It's a headlamp.
Okay.
No problem.
Code for the door is 145.
All right, so did I get it?
Thank you.
Lights seem to be working.
I'll keep the headlamp off for now.
This must be Phil.
Better not wake him.
Okay, I'm in here.
What now?
Okay.
That was beautiful.
A rail lever?
One of seven.
Rail lever?
What's happening?
What is that?
Is this a granny-like?
No, I don't think so.
This is not a granny-like.
Okay.
How do I move?
How do I get out of here?
I was waiting for it.
I was like, I thought it was going to come this way.
Nope.
Right into the ground.
There's a bed down here.
Yeah.
What else?
What else is going on?
What does that mean?
You should have just pissed in the street.
Oh, you're shooting at me.
You're shooting a gun at me.
You have a gun and you're shooting it.
Where am I?
My god.
Okay, I'm alive.
Hello.
I'm sorry I scared you.
I'm not used to visitors.
You're not supposed to be up there.
That area is shut off.
I'm up here by mistake.
Well, you better get out of there.
There's a lady with a gun.
A lady with a gun?
Yeah.
I don't have time for this.
You're all out.
You're all the same.
You tunnel people.
You're all out of your goddamn minds.
Tell you what.
Go back up and out the air vent.
Enter the code 789 by the gate to the tunnels.
Take the right tunnel, not the left one.
Okay.
Take the right one, not the left one.
789.
Gate to the tunnels.
I get that a lot from you people.
Run along now.
All right.
789.
It's the gate.
Where is that?
Can I get back up here?
How do I get out of here?
Is there a different way?
I need to crouch.
This is a jump at the...
I don't know.
Let's try that again.
Can I just...
No, I can't.
Oh, I can.
Door's locked.
Wait, what did that just open?
789.
What did that just do?
What did it do?
The gate right next to you opened.
This...
I didn't...
I wasn't even looking.
I didn't know why he didn't want me to go into the left tunnel.
He said, don't go there.
Why would I go into the left tunnel?
What do you mean I want to find out why
he wanted me not to go down the left tunnel?
That's not how this works.
I really need to figure out why he didn't want me to go down there.
No, you just listen, man.
I have a gun.
I've got a weapon now.
Sorry.
Hey.
Five.
Five, eight.
What else can I do?
Is there anything else to see?
I can't see anything.
Five, eight.
Five, eight, one.
I definitely need these.
That song is terrifying.
Where?
Jesus.
You're going to stand up, aren't you?
No.
Fuck.
How far away am I?
It's not that far.
Okay, go down the other tunnel.
Okay, right.
Wait, what?
Yeah, let's go.
Now I get what I'm supposed to be doing.
Speed run time.
Five, eight, one.
And I can just walk.
I can run through this.
Five, eight, one.
I think I have to do it.
Let's go.
This is pretty scary.
It is.
It's just off-putting.
Back where I was.
I have not been hit yet, so that's good.
Okay, that's a lot of shots.
Okay, don't die here.
Jesus.
Hey, where?
Where are you?
I don't know where they are.
Where?
Okay, there's another code right here.
Where are you?
Ah!
Wait, what?
This is just back to where I was.
Did I miss something?
I'm just going back down here.
Number four guy.
Now he's just number three, six, seven.
Oh, shit.
Okay, let's go.
Three, six, seven.
Wait, that's not the right one.
Wait.
Where was that door?
It was back here.
Where was that shit?
There it is.
Where is that?
Where was that?
Where you just were?
Shit, okay.
What the fuck?
Excuse me, where am I?
You're in Potogzow.
Who are you?
I'm Stig, the tram operator.
Where does the tram go?
Down the mountain, into the valley.
Can you see all the...
Can you see the lit window?
The red light?
It's been blinking all night.
It's irritating.
The blinking doesn't...
She have anything better to do.
Who is she?
She's a nobody.
If she were to disappear,
I don't think anyone would care.
How do I get to her?
With the tram.
But we only operate the tram at night
during special occasions,
such as the famous Potogzow
Orienteering Gathering.
What if I need to use it?
Wait till morning.
Then you'll need the approval of Maria, my manager.
How do I find Maria?
Walk along the train tracks
and into the forest.
You'll find her eventually.
Okay.
Am I dead?
I'm not a mortician.
I'm a tram operator.
Okay.
This was a dream.
We'd probably be somewhere else
than in Potogzow.
What choice do I have?
I like it.
Okay.
So follow the train tracks.
I have full health.
To ride, talk to tram operator.
Walk along the train tracks.
Where are they?
Down here?
I am technically...
Technically correct.
That was technically correct.
Run down the tracks.
How am I supposed to do that?
Did I just overshoot it?
Huh?
That wasn't the tracks.
That's the tracks.
That was the tracks.
Okay.
I guess not.
You were just on the tracks.
You mean like up here?
I thought this is the train.
Train tracks, not tram tracks.
Those aren't train tracks.
That's a tram track.
Fucking tram track in front of your eyes.
I thought it was like to go on the train track.
I'm the tram operator.
Get on the train tram tracks.
Okay.
Well, was I supposed to do that?
Oh, they have writing shit.
Okay.
What does it say?
Nine, four...
Nine, four, six?
There's one more.
Nine something four six three.
Nine, four six three.
Nine, two, four, six, three.
Two, four, six, three.
Okay.
What is the camera covering?
Just the amount of bullets I have.
It's 57.
Jesus.
Oops.
Okay.
I think it automatically did it.
Oh.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what.
Oh my fucking God.
There's so many of them.
I...
It's so disorienting.
Okay.
Am I right?
I woke up early this morning trying to get the blood out of my hair.
Can I get on there?
This is long.
I didn't think it was gonna be this long.
We're probably near the end.
Okay.
Am I hitting golf balls or something?
How do I talk to this person?
I don't think I can get up here.
The ladder?
I can't climb the ladder.
Like, I can't get up here.
Maria?
I need to ride the tram.
Why are you telling me?
Did Stieg send you here?
Yes.
He said you're the manager.
Oh, that's funny.
I'm not his manager.
We don't work together.
Stieg is my orienteering buddy.
Bring me back some of my golf balls from the forest and I'll let you.
Find your own way back to the tram then.
All right.
I'll get you golf balls.
That's your handicap.
Four, five, 45.
What are you shooting at?
Okay.
So I gotta go get your golf balls.
I think I should have found one by now.
What is this?
Okay.
Five, five, five, eight.
I probably shouldn't have done that.
I didn't talk.
What?
The train tunnel entrance has a new code.
Five, five, five, eight.
I don't know what I just did.
They're pointing at this.
Can I close it?
Five, five, five, eight.
Train tunnel entrance has a new code.
I woke up early this morning.
What's the twist here?
Right?
There's gotta be some twist.
There's no way it's just this.
What happened to being at a karaoke bar?
I forgot that even happened.
Here it comes.
What the fuck?
Who's shooting?
Where?
From where?
Should have hit.
Shut up.
Where are you shooting?
Oh my goodness.
Come on.
I can't even see.
Okay.
Don't walk off the edge.
What does that do for us?
Shoot like a grandma.
Sorry.
This is not a granny like.
What am I supposed to do?
I was...
Bonzi buddy.
Okay.
So now I can use the train.
Sorry.
Tram.
How do I use the tram?
Hello?
Did I turn it on?
Okay.
I have this guy.
R1, R1, R1, R1, R1.
So what are we doing?
Like.
I woke up early.
Here it comes.
All right.
I don't need bullets.
There's no bullets in this gun.
This is Lace.
The other one's Jasper.
They jumped me in the forest.
Put me in an old freezer.
Kept me in a fucking cage.
I'd be dead if it weren't for you.
Thanks for getting me out.
Sorry for all the blood.
You're welcome.
I need to get back home.
Do you live in Texas?
We're in Texas?
No, I'm from Ptokso.
You probably haven't heard of it.
It's a small little village in the forest.
Maybe you've heard of the Ptokso
Orienteering Gathering.
You have a car?
Can you give me a ride?
That was weird.
Oh, here we go.
I woke up early this morning.
Trying to get the blood out of my hair.
Franking up the sound on my hi-fi.
Out the screen downstairs.
Smiling along to my memories.
Of what we've been lup to.
To my brother and I were laughing.
What else?
We know the lyrics.
What the fuck?
I don't want to sing this part.
I'm not singing this part.
That was good.
My mic just freaked out.
Is there anything else?
So they were singing karaoke about a crime they committed.
And then I went to rescue the girl.
That's crazy.
That was a good one.
That was good.
All right.
I think I'm going to call it here.
That was a fun night of games.
It's great to see Vinny and you guys, right?
The next time you see me will be on Halloween night.
Or Halloween day.
Actually, what time will it be?
I think it's going to be 12 p.m. Eastern.
I will be on Charlie's Cooking Show.
Company time.
Should be fun.
So I will not be live on this channel,
but go to Charlie's channel on Halloween.
Should be fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
And for horror games, I'm not big on granny likes.
I'm not very good at them.
I have very jumpy and I have pay attention problems.
The granny likes destroy me.
But it's still fun.
I still had a lot of fun.
It was a great night of games.
I will see you guys on Halloween.
Please go watch the critical.
Yeah, Charlie, critical.
Is Charlie live right now?
Which is Ray Charlie?
Is he live?
He's doing some YouTube stuff.
Go say hello.
So it should be a fun time.
Halloween day.
See you guys soon.
Thanks for watching.
Have a great night.
See you on the 31st.
And go say hello to Charlie.
I'm going to go take a bath.
I'm sweating.
I'll be really honest with you.
I think after about hour number four or five
after screaming like a thousand times,
I kind of ran out of gas.
I got scared so many times tonight
that I think I ran out of gas
after like hour number five and a half.
Okay.
When your body screams like that, like
it just drains you so physically.
It's so we could tell.
I wanted to stick it through
for a couple of these though
because they are really fun.
All right.
Let's say hi to Charlie.
Good night, guys.
See you on the 31st.
Have a wonderful rest of your evening.
Whatever is left of it or good morning.
If you're just waking up,
it's pretty late for a lot of you.
See you soon.
Also check out grottobeasts.net
grottobeasts.com
if you are interested in grottobeasts
which is the collectible card
trading card game.
Okay.
Let me get it ready.
All right.
Go say hello to Charlie.
12 noon I believe on the 31st.
He'll probably be able to update that.
Follow his Twitter.
Make sure you're aware of it.
That will be where the most
up-to-date information will be.
Good night, guys.
See you soon.