Yeah, a little early. How are you? What's happening? Uh, could you guess what we're doing today?
Do I really need to tell you about my new obsession? This is one of the reasons why
I was afraid of this game. One of the reasons why I didn't want to play it is because I know
if I actually liked it, then it was going away in like four days. And then it's going to be,
oh, I'm just going to hop on dark and darker. And it's just gone. But who knows how long
into maybe like middle of the year or something. It's not coming back, dude. Yes, it is. Yeah. So
here's the plan tonight. There are, uh, there are a lot of people that want to play. And last time I
played almost completely and totally by myself. I was just alone almost the whole time. So tonight
is a lot of people that are streaming right now that I believe I'm going to be hopping around
different groups with. So the one that's set in stone, the one that is set in stone
is stir and Vinny at six o'clock. Now, now hold on a minute here. I'm very aware of the Metroid news.
So I told Vinny, I was like, Hey, I know you, I know you want to play that shit. So don't worry
about like, Oh, I said I was going to play. No, no, it's all good. So we're going to be kind of
cycling people in and out. And there's some other streamers that have wanted to play it.
I don't know how long stir wants to play for, but that's the plan.
Did you end up giving that guy's items back? No, I didn't. I don't think I could. The only thing
that makes me not feel bad about that is the fact that everything's getting wiped in like four days.
Right. Like this, it's, it's, it's okay. The guilt plagues him. No, I'm fine. I told you,
I put it down in a corner of my inventory because it's going to be a constant reminder
of my SIM, but I'm going to give you a small warning, small warning. This is going to go a
long time. This stream is, I'm just going to play it until I don't feel like, until I don't feel like
playing it anymore. This stream could go all the way through to like potentially early into the
morning hours. I just want to play it. Same kind of ideas before just going to chill out and just
go and have fun. Oh, whatever that means. I know I don't think this is going to be a 14 hour stream,
but don't be surprised if it's like eight to 10. I'm going to get up. I promise. I've already
eaten dinner. I prepared for this day. I I've got a nice green tea, like a nice full hydrating green
tea drink, drank a bunch of water, full dinner, pasta, carved. I'm carved up. Yeah. So me,
stir and Vinny in like 30 minutes. And then from there we'll see. There's a lot of other people
that are probably going to be just jumping in and out. I'll warm up a little. I don't want to be a
terrible player when, you know, friends want to play. There's three people. The title needs to
be dumb, dumber and dumbest. Yeah. I made it the dumb and dumber sequel title. Dumb, dumber and
dumbest. No, I don't want to have it that because everyone will just call me the dumbest one.
All right. If it's dumb, dumber and dumbest, I have to be the dumbest one each, no matter who it is.
Of all the streamers I'll be playing with, I'll always be dumbest in quotes. And I don't like
that. I don't, I'm not into that one. I'm not a fan of that. It could be me, stir and orangutan.
And you would probably have the orangutan be smarter than me. Like, oh yeah, the orangutan
smarter than you, Jeremy. What'd you say? The orangutan would be the smartest. I'll give you
a little bit of insight into a stream that happened. The replace me stream. I wanted to
have one of the contestants be an orangutan. Like just kind of walk into the room and like put the
headset on and like play Dark Souls kind of good. And it was like, Oh, wow. Okay. Interesting stuff.
And it was just sort of going to be a real orangutan that just like was an aquatic,
was a contestant. Um, but again, some ideas just don't work and they can't happen.
Cause like, I was like, Oh, wouldn't it, wouldn't it be kind of fun? Cause like, obviously I wanted
to be like, okay, like how do you like, I want to make sure it's done correctly. Like, you know,
some animals that are in movies and TV shows, I would want to have like a real, a legit setup
where it's the trainer and it's a, like an orangutan that was, it knew how to do this
stuff or used to it. And it was like, no, no like animal cruelty, bullshit, right? I wanted to do
it right. And do it like safe and good, even if we had to shoot it separately or something, right?
Um, but it's just, it was like too much of a, it was just too much of a hassle. So I was like,
nevermind. It's not worth it. But can you imagine just like, Oh, like, okay, like number, uh,
number 10, come on in. And it's just like, kind of orangutan just gets up and like sits in the
chair and just like puts the headset on, just like hanging out. Like, Oh, so what do you do?
Interesting. We kind of look alike. It's going to be like a whole little bit. And I was like, nah,
yeah. The more you look into that stuff, you're just like, eh, it's probably not,
eh, nah. It's funny for, it was funny up here for like 20 minutes. And then I just didn't write it
down and it was over. Orangutan would have swept the votes. It would have won by a landslide.
Can you imagine just like an orangutan just sitting on the stage and it's just like, has
like 90% it just has 90% of the votes. What is this? And you sing happy birthday to my kids.
They aren't going to be born until I'm 30. But if you say no, they're going to cry. So stupid.
So what you want to like clip me singing happy birthday. So then in, I don't know how many years
that is from where you are now, but then have that to play. That's actually kind of funny to me
that like potentially five, 10, whatever years in the future, or even like 30 years in the future,
when they're like, I don't know. Oh, it's like George's fucking 16th birthday. I don't know. Oh,
and we got a German to do a happy birthday for you by that. I'm not going to be relevant.
I'm sorry to say guys, that's people are going to be like, who, who, who is this?
That would be so weird though. Cause imagine like some of these like people that have been on like
TV or like other like people in, you know, movies or TV shows. Cause a lot of people use Twitch
and YouTube as new TV. So 30, 40 years from now, that would be so weird. Imagine if it was just
like, Oh, by the way, um, you know, Jeremy, uh, happy, uh, happy 20th birthday. Oh, by the way,
Elvis says, has something to say to you like Elvis. What do you mean Elvis? And it's Elvis.
She's like, Oh, Hey, Jeremy, how you doing? Happy birthday. Uh, singing a happy birthday song for
you. Be like, what the fuck is going on? No, I'm not comparing myself to Elvis. I'm just saying
like, it's, it's that same world of, this is weird. No, no, no. I, I'm not comparing myself to
Elvis. What an ego. No, I get what you mean. Don't worry. Thank you. One chatter. I appreciate it.
Thanks one guy. I think you're going to die on the toilet. That's fine. That, that just doesn't
bother me. That's not a big deal to me. That's actually like, I don't know, to me, that's like
not really that bad of a place to go. Right? Like that's whatever. Do an Elvis impression.
Again, that was wicked funny. No, that see what you're doing is doing the reverse psychology
thing where you thought it was a really bad impression and you were like cringing and
laughing at it. And you, you want me to like, do it again because you thought it was an embarrassment
and you think it's funny that I embarrassed myself in front of 400,000, 500,000 people here. Um,
and now you want me to do it again, to do that again. I understand what you're doing.
All right, let's go. Remember there's only 9,000 people here. What the fuck? No, there's 500.
You guys are not taking into account the amount of insects that watch this stream.
I mean, I got a very large demographic of ants and spiders and each colony of ants, you know,
there's, there's like, there's like, there's like 200,000 ants in a colony. They're big fans
because you're not, you're not, you're only thinking of like the human, um, the human audience,
which is, I mean, come on. You're also forgetting about all the food that watches all the, all the,
you know, your dogs and cats that are in the room. Like I have, I think I have a pretty
unbelievably large sandwich audience and I think that there are probably, I probably have like one
of the, I probably have a pretty large ham sandwich demographic, probably like ice cream. It's probably
like a, I probably have a very large ice cream audience of like all the ice cream that has been
like in front of the, you know, the video while I'm streaming. So yeah, I can say I have a 500,000
concurrent view audience because like you're forgetting the ants, the bugs, the dogs, the cats,
the ice cream, the sandwiches, the soups. It's a lot of things and people to watch. All right,
you guys ready? Stop stalling. I am stalling because I'm just, hey, I'm just warming up.
I actually did not see the direct. I heard there was some interesting things in it though.
Pikmin 4, we should watch it. No, I'll watch it later. Your jokes are minus two old man.
Hey, hey, who asked? Oh shit. Your name is who asked. God damn it. God damn it. Okay.
You can take the, you can take the, the win on that one. That's fine. All right. Um, I'm ready.
I'm ready to play. I was going to do a round or two. Maybe I'll probably get one round in before
Dura's around and Vinny's around. We're playing it by ear tonight because I'm going to be live
pretty much all night. Okay. Uh, let's go. Y'all know mead one. Uh, I have a confession. I, Holly
and I were playing, so I have a few new things. Look at this shit. Holly and I killed a group of
three and one of them had this stuff. And I almost have enough to buy a purple. I also have something
else to say too. Playing this game with another person is 100 times easier. Holly and I played
10 games and we got out, I think seven or eight times. It's so much more of like a ridiculous
experience alone. I think I made it out five times in eight hours two nights ago. It's just,
the stress levels are so much lower when there's another person or another two people.
But here's the stuff I got so we can go over it. Lots more money. I do want to do the high roller
stuff today. Very concerned about it, but I want to try it. Got this candy. Take a look at this.
I had that already, didn't I? I forgot to give this to Holly. No, whatever. Uh, I got this here.
This is pretty cool. I don't want to, I'm going to warm up a little bit. This is all my gear. Um,
I don't, there's nothing down here. Uh, this is just extra space. That's not, it's just,
I don't even have to look at it. It's, it's extra stuff. Um, we don't have to see it. Yeah. I,
I think I have enough money to be able to, uh, do some of that stuff. Try high roller with a group
that knows what they're doing. Can we, can we look at it? I, it's nothing, it is not,
we saw it. Okay. Um, I'm just going to go. Let's go. Wait, I don't want to, I don't want to bring
anything. I just want to like try to just get through. They did a, they actually changed the
goblin caves. For those of you that don't know, goblin caves got a pretty big nerf in regards to
how hard it's been. Um, I believe that goblin HP and goblin attack power, pretty much the whole
thing was nerfed by like 10% across the board. They added another portal. So it used to be,
I think, what two or three and I think it's two now it's three. So now it's like, I don't,
I don't think it's, I think it's actually probably a little better. So they made it not as hard and
they added a portal. He's reading patch notes. Yeah. I like this game. They had to make it easier
because they felt bad for you. I think you're underestimating. No, I think you're overestimating
how much power I have playing this game. I don't, that's not accurate, but I'm going to hop in it.
I mean, I'm just going to go with no gear. Just go by the way, if you didn't know, stop that.
That was awful. Probably get one in before we get stirring here. I thought you're going to play
with Vinnie. Yeah. I'm like 15 minutes. We set six o'clock and I don't want to, you know,
I want to be like, okay, yeah, it's six. You guys ready? Why is it so loud? Why is it so loud?
It's still kind of loud. Is that better? That's better, right? A little too quiet. I'll do this
now. Oh, I, you know, this one doesn't count. What's my, why's my name so weird? What? Fighter
two? Oh, what is that? Oh, I have streamer mode turned on. I actually would prefer streamer mode
off. All right, let's try it again. That was, the game was really loud. I had to fix it. Good job,
streamer. My job to defend auto in every pregame. Sure you want to do high roller? I want to do high
roller with a group of three and a group of three that kind of plays and knows what they're doing.
It's a hundred bucks every time. All right, let's go. First real game of the night. By the way,
I'm going to be obsessed and I'll be, I'm going to be here pretty much all night. So those of you
that are like, oh, it's like 2 a.m. Jerma, it's, oh, I'm staying. We'll see. What? I was holding
right click. What happened? No, that's not right. That was weird. I was holding right click and it
didn't do anything. I swear to God, I held it because it didn't do it. Nice. All right, just
gotta, you gotta, I just gotta get in the swing of things. I already got that. Jerma, you've been
playing this game nonstop for two days. Please bathe. Oh, hey, dude, please bathe. I'm fine.
Oh, fuck off. Oh, also, by the way, hey, look what I'm doing. I am running with everything holstered
that you still caught up to me. Oh, God damn it. I'm, I'm dead. God damn it. Just leave me alone.
He's going to, it's not going to count like that. It's running into that guy. Okay. All right. I'm
fine. I'm fine. This one doesn't count. This is why you warm up. This is why I'm warming up. This is
warm-up shit. He opened the door and like the boss skeleton is there and he just follows me and kills
me. That's why I warm up. It's just, you know, just kill me. Kill me. Just do it. Just do it again.
I'm warming up. So you gotta do three warm-ups and that's it. I'm done. We're good. That was a shitty
start too. I hit right click. I didn't raise the shield. You gotta get over these first. There's
no such thing as a warm-up in this game. Well, there's enough for me to sit here and like kind
of every, you go through, everybody goes through that process. I don't care if you've played, you
know, Dark and Darker, League of Legends, Valorant, Apex, Overwatch. Your first two or three games
are usually just dog shit. And then you like, there you go. Then you're in. You're warmed up.
So check out how this one goes compared to the last two. Pretty bad spawn. This is a really bad
spawn. I kind of just get out of here. Yeah, I'm just getting out of here. Such a bad place to
fight this. All right. Something weird's happening. Sometimes. Okay. Did you just hear me click? It
didn't swing. What's going on here? This is actually weird. I swear to God. You had to have
heard the click. What is going on? I hope that's not a problem. What the fuck is going on? Hold on.
Yeah, I am like clicking and I am left clicking and right clicking and sometimes it's just not
happening. I was gonna, maybe should I restart the game? This wasn't happening yesterday.
Is anybody else having that problem? Or is this just weird right now? I was playing earlier and
it was swinging without me clicking. Maybe it's an internet thing. Maybe like the connection of the
game or something. As long as half of you believe this, then that's what matters, right? No, I'm like
serious. It actually is happening. It's not happening anymore. It happened a couple times
in a row that last game. Now we're in. Now we're in. Don't lose this one. Plus one weapon damage,
movement speed bonus, and it's a blue. This person wants to fight and that's okay. Here's
somebody else. Get over here. Are you two together? Oh, is that how it is? That's how it's gonna be,
ain't it? That's how it is. Oh, okay. I'll take them both on. They were friendly. Hey, that was
not friendly. That was very unfriendly. Hey, by the way, I'm not holding right click. See what's
happening? All right. Something's weird today. Something's weird today. That was self-defense.
Are you friendly? Come here. I'll give this to you. You good? Here, you want something? Spear.
Try that out. There you go. You can't use that? Listen to me. Oh, you're nice. Here, how about
you take... Here, do you want a crown? See? Look, I paid for that. Oh my god. Here, have a... Yeah,
let me give you... Hey, take this. I just gave you a crown. Did you piss yourself? No. What?
That's cool hanging out. All right, let's go together. That scared the shit out of me. Nice hit.
Nice hit. Oh, hey. Hey, look what I got. Look at this. Hey, for being a friend. Come here. Look
at this. Look what I got. No, you take that. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Look, we don't have to argue
over who's going to pay the check. I'm telling you I got the check. Take it. My hand touched it first.
Yeah. All right. We got to get out of here alive though so you can get... You know, you can get
money for that. Yeah, good idea. Just get out of here. There it is. All right. There's our escape.
That's for you. No, you got a blue. You got a blue. No, you get out of here with that blue.
I'm telling you right now. This is my warm-up round. You get out of here with that blue.
Bro, you got a blue. You got a blue. You get out of here with that blue. There's two. All right.
Let's get out. There's one on top. Oh, there is. All right. All right. There's one up there.
Do you know how to get up there? Because I don't and... No, get out of here with that blue.
Do you know how to get up there? You do? All right. Take it easy. Good luck. And we're out.
Does he know how to get out? Oh, shit. Do you know how to get... He was going, go, go, go. He was
like, yeah, yeah. There's one up there. Did you see it? You doomed this guy. Oh, I thought he knew
how to get up. Oh, no. No, it's right there. It's right there. You'll be good. You have a potion or
anything. Oh, he's going to die. No. You did this. I thought it was like... Because he was like,
yeah, go in that one. I'm like, there's one up there. He saw it. I was like, should I... I was
trying to get him to go in. I was trying to get him to go in first. Oh, no. All right. Well,
okay. Oh, that was... Did I even have anything decent to leave? I did. I got the boots. We're
good. I got boots. I'm going to start a blue collection over here. I feel so bad. I thought
he knew his way out. It should have been me. Yeah, it should have been me. I should have just dropped
the boots for him and just died. Let's be real, though. That would have been pretty sick if he
had made that jump. Let me get people on a call here. Here we go. And start. I'm going to give
them a call. Hello. Hello. Hey, there. How are you doing? You've been playing Metroid? It's really
good. Is it good? Yeah, it's really good. That's good to hear. Is it like a remake? What is it?
It's like a remaster, like a really, really well done remaster. Have you ever played Metroid Prime?
No. Well, I love it. And it's really good. Is it motion controls? You could. I don't. You could
just do twin stick. Oh, okay. Yeah. So yeah, I'm enjoying it a lot. How are you, Jerma? I'm doing
great. Good to hear. Good to hear from you again. Yeah, you too. Did you watch the Nintendo Direct
or did you just hear about it like tangentially? I just heard about it. Okay. Is there any other
cool things? Yeah, there's a game where you play like as like a mouse and like you you like draw
other mouses and it's like you're like a wizard. I'm lying. No, Zelda. I was gonna say that sounds
like cool. Get him out of here. What? Hey, sir. Hey, am I not invited anymore? Am I? No, you're
uninvited. Okay. Okay. Well, then yeah, what are we laughing about? Oh, good one. Yeah, it wasn't
that I tried my best. But you know what? It was the Zelda trailer looks good, Jerma. So you you
know, when I play when I finish Breath of the Wild, I'm gonna be able to go right into the new one,
aren't I? Yeah, you're gonna have fun with it. That's pretty cool. I just I had a successful run.
Okay, I haven't installed the game. What's the what are we playing? No, sir. You guys wait for
me. Booking three head. We're playing Darkest Dungeon, right? Oh, I got that. Yeah, it's one
of the two dark games that are available for the steam next best dark and darker. I just want to
play it. I know they're gonna like take it offline. And they're gonna polish it up more. And
I want to play it. Why aren't you playing class? Are you germ? I just did fighter. Okay, I'll go
I'll use my wizard then. I have a lot of random classes. But the only one that actually has gear
or money is this fighter. Okay. Yeah, I leveled a fighter. I have some stuff on a wizard. But yeah,
if you want to invite me, my name is vines art like a wizard, but with Vine,
I couldn't think of a better name. My characters have like, like a little number one next to them.
I didn't even know what to do. Would you say German one? No, mead one. Okay, I'm v i n e z a r d.
There you are. All right, sir. What's your what's your name? I haven't made a character. What? What
should I be? You? I didn't you tell me you played this? Yeah, I think they wiped it like it was like
four betas ago. Oh, I told you I also told you I have no levels and no gear and no nothing.
That's fine. I didn't lie. But you just you know, video games. So you're gonna be you're gonna be
fine. I know. I know video games. Alright, so um, I'm a leveled up, Vinny, you have more experience
than I do in this. Do we like I would say we probably need like, we got a wizard, we have a
fighter. I mean, you could be I mean, cleric, you're leveled, you're leveled pretty nicely.
I would say I only played a lot last beta. Um, you know what ranger and cleric are two good choices.
I would say cleric is good for healing. But Rangers apparently really good with their like,
their arrows do a lot of DPS. So it's up to you, sir, whatever you like. And
rogues can rogues still go invisible or whatever they did before? They can. Okay, I think if you
played the first very first playtester, there's I think there's actually a lot of new things in
the game. I didn't play very much. I just played a little bit of cleric for like an hour. I have like
a couple things you probably could take just to have some stuff. I mean, you're not you're not
getting my blues. But you know, depending what you play. Do you need a green rapier? I have a
green spear. But I can't even use rapiers. You can. Yeah, fighter. Oh, wait, no, you can't.
Rogue can though. So I give it to you stir. I made a rogue. My name is creepo man. Okay. Wow.
Like they like this. I wrote it in discord. Capital C creepo man. I'm not in the lobby.
Enter the lobby. I'm entering the lobby. I'm in the lobby. There you are. All right, cool.
Sent invite sent. I am meed one. I can't sell this. This dude doesn't want to buy this stuff.
Cool. Fine. It's the collector that buys that shit. All right, so stir, I'll get you a weapon
from my stash. I feel like you shouldn't give me anything yet. Yeah, let's let's let's just do a
fuck face run. That's probably Yeah, take off all your good shit. Yeah, let's do a fucking fucking
raw dog my face on this one because I didn't play very much when I played and I only played
cleric and I kind of just healed. Why did you say it like that? Huh? I'll tell you what I have a
shitty rapier as well. I'll give you that one. Okay. Yeah, let's just go in without any. I mean,
he's gonna die. He's gonna die to the first skeleton and he's gonna uninstall the game.
Well, no, because I'm going to stand on a box. Are you guys right? Yeah, we're good. Do you like
do you like you you like played this? You know, how kind of how generally how it works? I think
it would honestly be in your best interest to assume that I don't. Okay. I wait. No,
I understand the gameplay. Everything outside of it, like equipment and selling. I don't that
doesn't make any sense to me. Okay, so but like basic information, like how do I like basic
information? I might have to read buying keys. I'm good, dude. You know, I'm a gamer. You're
gonna be good. You're gonna be good. Let's go. I believe in you, sir. Yeah, just a quick fuck
face run. Yeah, just like a dirty nasty. It doesn't even happen. Stank nasty. I got it.
If anything goes bad, I'll just crouch in a corner. You'll be fine. Okay, just already up though.
How? Okay, I got no stirs stirs stirs a gamer. You'll get it. Okay. I'm actually you've been
playing this a lot, huh? Like you got as addicted as I did. I I'm one of those people that I'm very
much already thinking that this is probably going to be the thing that I care about the most this
whole year. Yeah, I feel that I really like this game. Okay, they're there. I got to turn off the
voice chat because they're just saying voice isn't voice at the best part of the game.
It is until your Twitch channel gets banned. Oh, yeah, it is. When you're okay. Well, I'll get
banned. I'll take the L. All right, it can be fun. I got to hear what they're saying. I already did
a pre record of with voice chat on I was able to convince people not to kill me. I was like,
listen, dude, I'm a real person. Like I'm real. And they left me alone. I did a little RP. This
one here you can have that rapier. It's it's good. You might like it. I'm I'm in the options. Defend
me. Okay. All right. It's good because this is a very slow game. So like it's not like, dude,
we got to go come on the circles. Okay, the circles closing in. Yeah. In the meantime,
let's go look around. So hey, quick, quick TLDR stir everything. You should be picking up as
many of these little jewels as possible. It's like one of the ways to make money. You want to
collect everything. If it's like a little bracelet, a little jewel, a little goblet,
that's how you actually make money. And then we bring it back and it's a socialist society.
And we all share right? No, there's one guy that buys it all and runs the whole town.
What's the inventory tab? They didn't make it high. Do they not? Let me get this. There you go.
Yeah. Spider. Spider. All right. There's another spider. There's a pot over there somewhere.
Oh, my goodness gracious. Okay, we got I got a blue long sword. Watch out mead. I'm going to put
that on. Remember, you can throw a torch on the ground if you need extra light and don't want to
hold it. Okay. This thing's actually pretty awesome. I hope we make it out. Oh, skeleton.
Watch out. Magic looks awesome in this game. Oh, it seems unbelievable. You're not you're not
role playing. You're not like you don't say the spells when you cast them. Oh, should we? I can't
if you want me to. They gain more power the game. If you have voice chat on and you say magic missile,
it gets a can you can you is this better than you have stir the helmet on the leather cap? I don't
dude is I don't know what items are. Yeah, well, I think okay, Diablo. When you're running around
at level one in Diablo and every single thing you pick up on the ground is like, yeah, just replace
it. It's better. Okay, I heard you should go nude because then you get more move speed. I mean,
did you you could I don't know. I don't know if that's gonna work. But speaking of moving speed,
if you holster you do move faster. So keep that in mind. What's the most important x guys? Okay,
I okay, I need a moment to apologize because I'm going to be insufferable for like one or two games.
Just naked. Why are you just a naked guy in our party? Hey guys, dirty loot in there. I
can really use some pants. I am not a conjurer of cheap tricks. I just walked right out of a rust
server. You really do like you're like like rust. Oh, we got a skeleton here. I'm gonna die.
There is friendly firester and it's really bad. So just be aware. Okay. Yeah. Well,
you're the one who's taken the most damage. So I feel like you could use a little advice.
Stir better rapier here for you on the skeleton's corpse. Oh, yeah. And also,
Jeremiah. Yeah, there you go. If you guys want to give me 10 seconds to meditate so I can restore
my magic, that would be awesome. Also stir in the mini map. You notice that the white line
got to get in that line because you understand what happens. The it's like a br like victory
royale is within. I've never played one of those. What happens essentially when the thing with the
goes around the circle and if you're not in the other circle, watch out because you're going to
be taken tick damage. Yes, sir. Have you ever played a game called Fork Knife? So it's like
Hearthstone Battlegrounds. Is it normal that your game should stutter all the time? We haven't know,
but we have we have somebody over here. We don't know if they're friendly. It is just looks like
a single cleric saying yes. Okay. Hey, sir. Careful on the ground. Sometimes there's like,
uh, like spike traps like over here. Like do not step on this. Okay. And if there's a if then if
there's a trap in the wall, you're supposed to walk back and forth in front of it like three
or four times. Yeah, exactly. I know you make learn. Okay, I've learned a lot about this game,
but mostly only from Jeremiah. Everybody does that. It's not just me. Everybody does that.
Watch out. There's a this player down here. We don't know if they're friendly if they who cares.
Okay, so we got we have a little group here. Friend or foe, friend or foe. How are they?
Yeah, we're friendly everybody. If you can hear me. I have voice chat on so they can hear me,
but I can't hear them. So I can't get banned. Shit, I got hit by that. Hey, actually say make
sure you say like, hey, we're friendly until it counts in the end. We're friendly until it counts
in the end. I've been told to say you don't actually say that. Oh, I'm not going to attack
you. I'm not going to attack. Don't know if you're going to have a cleric. It's cool to have cleric.
Why did you hit him? No, now they're going to. No, it was an accident. He's new. He's new.
We really we don't want to. You're cool. It's fine until it counts in the end. We're not going to
kill you. Hey, can you heal? Can you heal our like goofy ass friend people on the other side
of the store? There's a you disabled input, but not output as a chat member. Is that you?
No, there's someone behind the door. They're throwing fireballs. They're getting real. All
right. Let's let's fuck them up. Oh, I'm just taking damage. That's awesome. Oh, no. Oh,
there's a spike trap right here. Oh, my God. Hey, we're friendly. We're friendly guys. I'm about to
I'm kind of about to die. I think. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Oh, the cleric is going to die.
I have a campfire here if we if we needed to heal up.
You're killing the person. What are you doing? Oh, my God. No, he's the worst. He's the worst.
We got to get him out of the fucking game. He's already a fucking problem. He's already.
He's a massive problem already. He had a lot of shit on him. Okay. Hang on. Hang on. Good.
Wow. I went to the trap. He bounced me into the trap. Oops. This is such a bad place to fight to
try to like. Yeah, it's a really bad place. Oh, shit. So he's going to me. That one. You got him.
Okay. Okay. Cool. I think it's just this one of the guy in there, too, right?
I don't know if there's another guy that might have been there is there is one guy. He looks
like a wizard. I can't believe I'm looting the person. This is unbelievable. And look,
this is a nice bowl of shit. That's my kill. Are you seriously looting him right now? You got naked.
I got the kill and you're looting it. I dropped the bow on the ground. It's a blue bow. Yeah,
let's do it. All right. Come follow me. I think we're going to get the safety. Did you get the bow?
Yeah, that doesn't seem good. There's a whole other party over here. Oh, shit. Okay. I don't
know if I can. It's going to take a while to full heel and we got the circle closing in.
Yeah, let's get in the circle. All right. We try to get out of here. The portals are opening.
We start to find some skeleton. Okay, a creepo man like come over to us. Well, there's another
exit. Why don't we take the other exit and avoid the combat? Good. We got to get into the circle.
Yeah, it goes into a circle as well. So come up. Yes, let's get there. We missed a bunch of treasure
too, but that's okay. Beware of traps. This is a this is a trial run for stir. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly. I cannot believe that person is probably so pissed because it was like, oh, yeah, we're
playing it. Oh, there's people here. You any hits? Uh, not really. Oh, fuck. Big, big cast here.
I think I might be able to. Yeah, they're gonna shoot down the hole. We might be able to ambush
here if we pull back. Stir, are you dead? I exit it. What? What? You got out? Yeah. Wait,
where? Where? Where did you go? In the room we were in, there was an exit and he had nothing.
Sorry, I took it. Friendly. We're friendly. Oh, my God. There's they're there. They're right
behind us. They're behind us. Okay. Okay. Yeah. All right. Close the door. Close the door.
Vinny, did you take it? I got nothing. I got nothing. All right. Be well. All right. I'm
gonna do my best. I just need to figure this out. Be well. Wait, what? Wait, wait. Your wizard is
low HP. You the fighter, valiant, noble fighter, just left the wizard with no HP. Well, here's
the thing. So let me explain. Let me explain how this game works. Stir. Okay. I have I found a
blue sword, which is like really good for my class. It's I mean, it's like that's a big deal.
There's no trading unless you you have to like pay or like bring it and drop it. Hey, can you
hear me? You want to share the campfire? It's gonna be cool. All right. Never mind. I'm dead.
It's so awful. Chad, are you sure that my output? Can you guys hear me in game? Germ? I have voice
chat turned off. I had I was off by default. I'll turn it on and I can. I had an issue
a couple nights ago where I had a kind of, you know, somebody, an incident, somebody said
something and it's like, okay, well, now we fucking have to turn it off. Yeah, that's 100%. So I turned
it off. But yeah, I check. So the game's pretty easy, huh? But here's the thing, stir, what you
did was not necessarily wrong because you got a blue bow. But the problem is, so you could like
just stash that. The stash is not shared. So it's not like, oh, I'm going to make a ranger and just
go to my shared stash. That's not in the game. So if you want to put that on a ranger, you're going
to have to like give that to one of us and we have to get out and then give it to your ranger or
trade it on the market. There's a trading market where you can trade with other people.
But it costs, what, 15 gold to do it. You're giving stir an ethics lesson.
Okay, so I got nothing and I can only sell my bow. What should I name this rogue,
this archer chat? I don't know. Sneaky archer. That's a pretty good name. God, it's not available.
Skyrim, you want me to call him Skyrim? Okay, I have a game mechanics question, teacher.
Why are there 12 merchants? Because you sell different things per merchant.
Okay. Yeah. So for instance, the collector, the collector wants to take like gems, jewels, bangles,
chalices. That's who you sell all that to. And I know you, I know, let me, I just want it in one
spot. I just want to hurry up, hurry up, hurry up. Sometimes stir, you got to slow down and enjoy
the lore. Okay. Okay. So the collector, you can sell those little- Who would I sell the bow to?
We're looking at the weaponsmith or the armor. Okay. Selling that bow, I mean, but maybe if you
do have a ranger. I'll take it. Yeah. I just made a ranger. Do you want the bow? You can sell it
if you want. I mean, honestly, I escaped on my first game. I got a kill and I didn't even have
any clothes on, so I don't even think I need the bow. I can give it to you. Yeah, just bring it in
the mission, then drop it on the ground. I'll take it. Okay. Because I just made a ranger. I want to,
I feel like my wizard, I was just getting no, no attacks on enemies, really. I can't believe you
killed that. That person was being so nice to us too. I know everybody's saying, hey, dude,
you should buy the thing for the gold stash, right? But I'm, I'm a weirdo and I want to like
fill half the stash with this because I like the way it looks. That's saying I killed at least two
people. I think, no, I think, I think you, you were part of at least, I mean, the two kills that we got
in that hallway. Okay. All right. Yeah. I might go back to wizard then. I'll try ranger for a little
bit, but then I'll go to, I'll go to wizard. How do you level up? Because I'm noticing I'm still
level one and I feel like I shouldn't be. You just got to kill more rats and creatures and skeletons
and players. It takes a little bit. I mean, all honestly, all leveling up does is I, I feel like
a level 15. Okay. So when you level, look, the game is still making stuff. So if you go to honestly,
you should do this right now. I'm just babbling random words and you took it as they're still
making the game, but hold on, go, go, go up to the top, go to class. You see the, go to perk and skill.
Yeah. You have some perks that you, you unlock perk slots essentially is when you, how you
every five levels. Okay. I was just, well, I was asking this how specifically I was just killed
nerds. Yeah. Just kill me, just kill people. You know, you're saying it was a good thing. I killed
that guy now. Now you're flipping again. There might be something in that perk listed. You would
rather have is what I'm saying. So look, so is this what it's usually like with you guys? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's been like this for 10 years, man. 10 years. I'm, I'm, hi, I'm Vinny by the way,
star. Nice to meet you. Yeah. I think I'd like Vinny. I think he's like Vinny. Yeah. Yeah. You seem
nice. Thanks man. Appreciate it. No, we were, we were, we were dark tide friends for a while. Come
on. Yeah. Yeah. No, me and Jerma, we, we hunt ghosts usually, or we, we hit people with swords.
That seems to be like the two extremes of our gameplay. Me and Jerma argue. Okay. Hold on. I
have to show this. I have to show this on stream. This is so stupid. Hold on. While you look at your
perks, I just need to show this on stream. This is so stupid. What is it? It's, it's just a dumb
picture. Oh, man. That's, that's funny. I like it. Yeah. That's a good one. Didn't take them that
long. Huh? No, not at all. That was a good one though. All right. Are we, are we good to go? Yeah.
I think, uh, I'm ready. So we just get a stir. You need to ready up when you're, uh, one second.
Okay. Sorry. I'm, I'm comprehending. All right. This is a really good sword. Actually I killed
that guy in two hits. I'm not taking it. I'm going to leave it. I don't have the picture. Jerma had
the picture. You want me to capture his stream so I could show you the image? Yeah. He didn't show
it to me. So here I have it. It was posted in chat. I'll show you. I feel like it wasn't meant
for me. I'm ready. Okay. All right. Will you put clothes on? Oh, wait, you, you got out. So you
don't have any, you throw it off. Okay. Let's just go. I was wondering why, cause like you're naked
and that's what that, okay. I get it. I like the lobbies go so fucking fast. I mean, you're there
five seconds. Someone punches you in the back of the head and then you just start. It's, it's
good in a play test environment though, because there are like 50,000 people playing this game
right now concurrently. I can't believe how big this game blew up. Cause like when I was playing
it for December's tests, that was the first time I had even heard of it. And then it just like
quadrupled and then like times 10, the amount of users. Yeah. The first beta was, was kind of a
long wait time, but I think, I think everybody kind of was waiting. Like after that December test,
I remember hearing about it and going, Whoa, that looks kind of interesting.
And then it was like, wait, it's actually coming for the steam demo thing. Oh,
fuck. Yeah. I think everybody had the same idea. Yeah. I was really addicted to this. It was like
four hours. Hey creepo man. Yes. Oh, take orders from your master. What do you need from a creepo?
I need you to, you hold, if you hold a torch, it increases the, you know what? Just get in here.
It's easier to creep in the dark. I'm pretty sure creepo man was a stone temple pilot song.
All right, chat. Uh, we get some pants. What was that thing that you posted about some
songs that like people said didn't exist or something. Oh, uh, I was streaming
corruptions the other night and I was playing GTA San Andreas and people were all like stretchy.
I was like, they look like rubber bands. And in San Andreas, there's a stone temple pilot song.
So I was like, that's a, that's a song from back in the day. They had a song called rubber band man.
It's like rubber band, rubber band man. Um, and people were like, no, it's not real then.
That's not a real song. And then I found it on an old tape. So when I was a kid, I honestly thought
that was a bit from you. I thought it was you singing. Oh, I was like, oh, this is like really
funny of him. Like he made this like rubber band song. Like, and he's saying it's a stone
temple pilot song. Yeah. But it's a real song. That's funny. Yeah. It's real. Yeah. We are doing
like, by the way, we've lost creepo man. I'm in the darkness. Hey, star, where are you? I'm in the
dark. Oh, he's back here. Okay. There's helicopters in this room. I feel like we should catch up with
star. Can I make the plants versus zombies VOD permanent? It already is on the archive channel.
Come on, Gwen. Oh, all right. You got that bug. That's good. All right. Uh, you see any treasure
in here? Yeah. Open up every chest stir because sometimes it just be something in there. You just
take everything. I feel like it's a waste of time because you guys are already doing it. I feel like
as a team, we should also have different roles. Can you one guy's the looter, one guy's the torch
guy? You know what? Um, these pots are also good. There's sometimes really good stuff and potions
in them. There's not be down here. Watch out. We got says, um, I love how you've, uh, you stir.
You've committed to being like the comic relief today. Comic. I'm taking this really seriously.
I have just like naked running around, like killing our friends, the naked vagrant. You
guys said you were going to kill him when it mattered at the end and it mattered to me.
Shit. We, that's right. That was said out loud. I'm at my fault. I feel like I'm getting,
I'm catching a lot of flack back here. I said I'm, I'm calm to that. Here. I'll be torched guy.
Get them. Do you guys see him? Do you guys see him? Do you see him?
All right. You can just punch him. It's kind of dark in here. Oh, we've only had a,
I've only had a creep with a light. How do you throw the torch? Uh, right click,
but you only have three of them. So should we go this way or should we? I feel like we might get
stuck down here. Uh, there's a helicopter down here. I'll let, I'll let you lead germ. Oh,
they have the, we can get the best. They got the best loot because the dragon flies wear jewelry.
Hey, Chad, how do you shoot three hour arrows at a time with the bow? Does anyone know?
I think it's a, it's a skill. Okay. You got to go have that in the skill menu.
It's a skill you didn't choose. Oh, there you go. When is GTA six coming out? Um, I think like,
probably, I don't know, like two years maybe. Hey, sir. Yeah. Uh, can you, can you wear that,
that outfit? Where? Right here. Okay. And I would definitely put it on. Circle's coming.
We got some problems here. This water looks scrumptious. It kind of does.
Looks like ecto cooler. Yeah, it is very green. It's green, but it's very like transparently
green. So it's just like that. Hey, hey, German men, this zombie is wearing some sick pants, dude.
You definitely don't have pants better than that. It's Nyquil. Yeah, I guess you could boil some
chicken in this. Right. This Zambi, dude, you got to check this Zambi. This Nyquil chicken.
Oh, blue. Plate pants. If you need them. What do I even have in my pants right now?
Is this water or jello? Like lime jello. Something in between. I have plate boots.
Want to double it. Want any armor? Okay. Yeah, one of those zombies had plate leggings.
Oh, leggings. Actually, yeah, actually, I probably could use those. Let me go back there.
Slapping around. I mean, I love the sound in this game that I was telling, like,
I was playing with my mods the other day, and it's like half of the sound effects in this game
are just feet slapping on like wet concrete or like dry concrete. The penguin walk.
Just penguins walking. Just sounds like penguins walking around. Yeah, I guess it does. It's like,
now my chat wants to drink the green water. They really want it. I missed. Let's see.
Heavy gauntlet green would be good for you. It is. Thank you. How does, uh, how's healing
working in this? It is red potions, a cleric, or, um, you have bandages or skills.
I have some extra bandages there if you want to come grab them off me.
Yeah. I just fell back in the water. Great. Okay. Uh, oh, hey, Vinny. Yep. On the ground.
Oh, nice. Oh, awesome. Thank you. Uh, hey, creepo man, if you're asked about health,
sometimes there's random shrines that just do different things. This one is a full heel.
Interesting. Yeah. You might, you might want that. I'm praying to my God. Nice. It was an awesome
God. Whoever it is. I'm sure they're awesome. The dark lord bathroom. Uh, portals have started to
spawn and sir, you were asking, like you were asking randomly, like what the fuck's going on?
Only one person can go in a portal and they spawn randomly in the area. So it's just kind of a mess
to try to find one eventually. And there's only, there are not enough portals for everybody to get
out. Indeed. Yeah. And if it's a red portal, that'll take you to the next floor, which is
way more difficult. So maybe you don't take those right away people. Hello there travelers. We are
friendly. We have my head, which would take for you. No, you do not want to attack. Oh, they want
to go. They want to go. They want to go. I would recommend against it. We are heavily armed. I'm
dead. Come on. Creepo man. It's up to you now. Creepo man. You, you gotta, I have, I have actually
a lot of stuff. Yeah. You were at this point right now, sir, just try to find a blue portal and do
not engage anybody and closed doors behind you too. That's a good strategy. Yeah. Your goal is
to go through that room. Yeah. Just, just, just try to find a blue portal as the only goal you have
and do not engage and just hide and sneak around. Oh, I'm a gamer. We'll see. Chad, are you sure
they can hear me with my audio settings as they are right now? I don't think I could hear you in
game, but I kind of walked away. So I don't know. That's so funny. We kind of just, if they couldn't
hear you, we were just kind of seeing how they reacted. We just kind of was standing there and
I got hit in the head with an arrow. Yeah, basically it's like, oh, these, these three,
these three guys just stand still free headshot. Oh my God. Creepo man. What?
That's an escape portal, my friend. Yep. Blue portals where cross the way on that right there,
right next to you. That one, that blue one, you just have to activate it. It takes about 10
seconds to activate and anybody can walk through it. I can't believe you're going to make it, dude.
Creepo man. You're going to make it. You're going to make it. Nice creeped on. Nice work. So now
you go to your, you know, your stash and this is where you make the decision on,
Hey bro, do I want to bring something with me next time? Or do you stash it to make sure you can keep
it? Are you just, you're selling all your chalices and bangles? That's the, they have no other purpose
to the collector collector collector. And then, can you hear me in game right now? You hear an
echo? Yes, I do. Sick. Okay. So yeah, those dudes heard us and then they killed us.
Yeah. I heard you guys talk to them and I walked away. Oh, okay. Um, I'm sorry. I have,
I have a ethical question. I have a purple, I like an epic chest that you could wear right now.
Me? No, Vinny. I have, it's for a ranger. It's literally purple and it's okay. Oh, was I supposed
to drop you that bow? I had it the whole time. Oh yeah. But the reason why it's unethical and I
don't care if you lose it or if you die with it. It's just because I may have accidentally
BM stole this from somebody. What do you mean you stole it from someone? How? Like in game or what?
We fought a monster and like it was a solo game and it was a bunch of chaos everywhere and people
were fighting and dying. And I just, we killed this boss thing and then there's like three or
four other people started attacking each other. And I just grabbed everything and ran in a portal.
No, that's fine. Oh, that's why they make these games. I don't think that's an ethical quandary.
I think that's real. Wait, wait, wait. Bandages are 45 gold. Not what happened. Isn't that a rip
off? That stir. Welcome to dark and darker. It's fucking fabric. Well stir, that's a pack of three.
Also don't ever buy the expensive one. Buy the one that's 10. It's 15 gold. Oh, I didn't see that
they were different. That's for like rich Andes that have like thousands of gold. I got like 35
gold that run. Is that is that better than your second run? I don't know. I was also alone. Okay,
me too. In the end, we're all alone. All right, you guys. Yeah, I'm ready. That's right. As for
that. Yeah, you can hold on to that for if you play an archer. I don't think I deserve that.
I'll die. What's the question stir? Well, I have it in the menu item to purchase bandage.
How do I actually buy it? Okay, so you're going to click it and you can say fill in all stash
because that's like hey, I have the money wherever and just send this a make deal. Oh, I thought that
meant like fill my whole stash with as many of these as I can possibly buy. And how do you
know between your torch and your bandage? Oh, three and four. You're like item slots. You can
switch between them. You just cycle. You have. Yeah, you have three slots per. Okay, I knew chat
was gonna say fill my hole after stir said that I knew it. I'm gonna knock. I'm only gonna bring
a couple bandages. We're still kind of still learning. Well, some of us are, but you know,
whatever. Oh, stir, by the way, come look at the dog. Look at the dog's name. I saw on your stream.
I did watch quite a bit auto. That's man. It's weird. They'd name it like a cat that but close.
Yeah, I heard about that. Do you think that's a reference? I'm probably gonna say no. I kind
of feel like it might be. I mean, it's autos pretty famous at this point. He's a pretty he's a pretty
well known dog. Yeah, but auto is like just a cool name. I think so. I thought you'd I actually
thought it's a dog, right? Dog auto. Yes, because you said cat a second ago. That's the in game.
Sorry. Well, the in the game is a cat. He has a dog is I thought it was a UTO like automobile like
a car at one point. Yeah. Oh, sir. You got that bow. Oh, yeah. Hold on skeleton. All right, let's
get the skeleton dropping the bow down here in the light. Check this out. Check out and check this
out. Check out this really nice. Thank you. I don't think there are charged. I don't think so. But
you do get combos when you continue attacking and the combos are good. Sword here. I'm sorry. I'm
still asking questions. No, no. Push to talk. I think it's B but I rebound it. So I don't know.
Pretty sure it's B. It is B. That's weird. Now ask as many questions you want because this game
is kind of like like what the hell is happening? I don't know what's going on. And I think a lot
of people maybe open this game and play for like 20 minutes and go, this is stupid. And they did
kind of it's like it's almost like, oh, shit. Wait. Okay. I almost like when you first I remember
when I first played Dark Souls, and I remember just running around in circles, not understanding
anything behind us. There's a group behind us in the door where we started. Yeah, creepos going
in the hole. Wait in the hole. Oh, they're here. Oh, they're behind us in this store. All right.
What do you guys want to go hole or creepo strategy and just like, yeah, yeah, why we could
put your torches down? Oh, yeah. This is like, like, Tarkov is one of those games that I just
it just didn't click with me. Yeah. And this is very similar to Tarkov, but I feel a little bit
more user friendly to start. Also, Dark Souls, they're coming through that door. I'm still back
here. They come through. Okay, they might be engaging. I don't know. I think I think we'll
come back here. Let's fight them. And also, but don't come back here because I threw caltrops in
front of the door. We will lose. We will lose. Okay. It was like one. It was like one ranger.
Maybe. Yeah. Games like this because I reason why I'm saying ask as many questions as you want.
I played this for like 30 minutes, 40 minutes, and I was like, this is the worst game I've ever
played. I was like, this is probably the worst game I've ever played. And it took me like an
hour or two to be like, wait, this actually is like one of the most fun things I've ever done.
Yeah, really. This clicks where Tarkov didn't for me, which is weird because you know what
Bloodborne clicked for me 100%. But Dark Souls never did. And I've gone back to Dark Souls like
three times and I still have not. I just have no desire to return to it. But I love Elden Ring,
completed it like fully loved Sekiro, loved Bloodborne. I tried Dark Souls just didn't,
it was just too much for me. And I'm getting shit from that. I'm getting shit for that from my chat
from people who know that story already. God damn it. Okay, no, I am confused how I take out the
bandages. Like no button. They're all on one of your slots. Oh, I see. Okay, I got it. Yeah.
And it takes about 10 seconds. Hold. It's not very much but it's enough to kind of. I think I'm rogue
so I get like the super action speed. Yeah, that would be resourcefulness. It's a stat. It's an
insanely important stat eventually here because it just lets you do things so quickly. Some classes
have awful resourcefulness. Cleric is like one of the slowest in the whole game, right?
But Star, you are going to inevitably take more damage if you're naked. Yeah, but I'm not going
to take any because I'm going to be evasive. You know, I know that I had a dodge. Okay. Yeah,
getting getting over the initial hump of I don't get it. I died to the first skeleton and like I
don't get it. It is if you can get over it and like try to understand it, then it's like, oh,
wow, this is actually really fun, which goes for most things, right? But yeah, yeah, you have to
give it the time. I guess you do have to. Yeah, this one deserves the time because it's it's
rewarding. It's really worth it. But also, sir, if you want to know red, like a red skeleton or
like a red spider is a elite, which means there is obviously elite and they hurt and but they
have more stuff. There's also another mode that I would like to try at some point tonight. It's
called high roller and we have to pay 100 gold to go in, but it's much harder and much more better
stuff drops. I'll tell you when you when you end up playing with like Kraken or whoever,
yeah, you could do that one because I have zero I have no money on this character.
But that sounds that sounds like butt clenching. Yep. Is there any way to tell if a chest is a
mimic? I don't know. You just kind of have to find out. But you you have enough time to run from the
mimic. That's the one saving grace. Maybe if you hit it. Oh, big, big door, big, big scary door.
It is a big scary door. That means there's a big thing in there. Yeah. In there, there's like a
wizard or a champion or something. I'm not mistaken. And also, we're as we get closer here,
tons of people are going to be kind of collapsing on these rooms and we could just get just dumped
on. Yeah, I'm I'm decent shield here for you, Jerma. Oh, I just found a skeleton. Oh, buckler
or I'll take it. But yeah, I got the one I have more defense. You guys want to go in the omega
door or do you want to leave it alone? Let's get the skeleton first so we don't get ganged up on
by skeletons. All right. I closed the door. There's a lot. There was a lot of skeletons by the door.
Yeah, we could probably kill them. Let's go close the doors behind us. Make sure you know.
Well, there's skeletons up here, too. We can systematically kind of like go from up to down
and I can like snipe some skeletons that we can we can make it work. I think. Is there any shield
that the rogue can use? Oh, Vinny, Vinny, you're going to want to take a look at that. Oh, it's
another blue one. Do you need to take advantage? Thanks. You want this? We want this big mega chest
circles coming. You can open it because you can pick locks. I have never picked a lock in the
circles right here, so I don't I don't want to jump in the death room. I mean, it also stirred
that white altar there. That's a shrine of resurrection. Like if you have my if I die
and you take my soul, you can resurrect me. OK, OK. Nobody else is here. I mean, you could just
try to run over there and just snipe it. But oh, there's an exit portal across the hall,
like across the like on the other banister over there. Anybody want to get out now?
I'm kind of like in this the hardcore permadeath mode I'm playing with Creepo Man right now.
It's never known the touch of death. I mean, I do have some decent bows now, so I might I might go.
Oh, and I got a ranger. Oh, man. Yeah. Yeah, I have some decent stuff. I should probably leave.
Vinny, you should you should get out of here. Let me see if I even can. Oh, there's a skeleton
behind us. I forgot the Ranger has food that you can use. Give me a burger. He's in a really
weird spot. Yeah, I can make it. OK, cool. Appropriately, I took the creep perk,
which makes my my crouch walking, I think make less noise. Oh, another one.
Oh, but it still sounds like it makes a lot of noise when I'm crouching.
Is that is that imaginary? I think you I think you you always make noise, I think. But there's a
group in here. I mean, we could kind of and there's a red portal. He went the other way.
Can you get a little greedy stone cleric in here? Just one. They're probably together.
I only see one. You try to go for the jump. No, this too. There's a cleric and an archer.
And now there's three people. OK, well, they just killed somebody. We can we can sneak up
behind him. There's a fourth guy in here taking an exit portal, taking the portal up there.
They're attacking. I'm going to I'm going to engage this to this three chat.
What button goes to first person again in spectator mode?
That's the try to get out of there, sir. Yeah, I'll try.
Oh, it's literally on the screen. Wow, that's amazing. Oh, you're dead.
Jeremy, you're dead. Yes. Three of you one.
Did you have anything? No, not really.
OK, well, stirred for your first time playing. You've been escaping a lot.
When I first played this game in December, I probably it took me two hours of gameplay,
a failure to escape one time. I'm OK.
Dying. I'm OK. Dying and being like the bait there.
So you can leave with blue and stir. You can leave and make some money.
I got plenty of money. I'm all right here. I got plenty of money.
I'm already taking the yell. Good, good man.
Yeah, that's a good man. All right. I can do one or two more if you guys want.
And, you know, I know you'd want to change out, get some other people in.
Wait, what? Yeah, I mean, pretty much we got like a little group here
where everyone wants to jump in and out. Yo, 84 gold.
Yeah, that's how you make money. Are you saying you just made 84 gold?
Yeah, from that run. Yeah, that's that's a lot.
I don't feel like very good. At what point do I like,
you know, like buy a dagger or something?
Money is you really want to spend your money on the utility stuff.
So, for instance, go to at least early on here,
go to merchants and go to the alchemist buying potions and bandages.
That's kind of early where you want to spend your money
because it means you just get to live longer.
But, I mean, by all means, buy a sword, buy a weapon.
I mean, some of them are expensive.
Yeah, and usually end up finding better ones in match anyway, but yeah.
Okay. But slowly, but surely,
you'll kind of increase your survivability because as you notice now, it's just sort of,
oh, I took I'm at 50 percent HP.
Okay, well, I'm dead if we find groups of enemies or something.
Or if you let's say you kill somebody and you're at like 10 percent HP.
If you had bought three potions, it's like, okay, maybe I could keep going and leave and get out.
So you're essentially trying to survive to the point where you get
more and more and more good stuff to then hold on to it.
But then when you're like, all right, this is the time,
this is the run where I'm putting this shit on and we're going to go hard.
That's what you do. Another question.
No, go for rogue specific.
I took the cow traps and it feels like when I use them,
I throw them on my own feet and then roll in them and there's nothing I can do about it.
You can get hurt by your own stuff.
Yes. Well, I mean, like I use it and then I there's not even a chance for me to not get hurt by it.
Huh? Yeah, they suck.
They feel like they are designed for you.
Like you rub them on yourself.
They drop behind you.
Oh, I've been like looking at the ground and then walking backwards to get away from them.
So you're like you're flattening your own tires.
That's funny.
Yeah, I guess I've been flattening my own tires.
It's not like Team Fortress classic cow traps.
That's funny.
All right, we pick pocketing.
Is there? Oh, I don't know.
Rogue, you can steal an enemy's item from the dungeon.
What is that? What does that even mean?
That's pretty cool.
Someone in my chat just said if Jerma had a normal job, he'd be such a nice trainer.
Hey, thank you.
Yeah, it's nice.
I mean, trust me, I do not know that much about this game,
but I know enough to at the very least explain some very small basic details.
And that's pretty much it.
Yeah. Yeah, no, it's pretty important stuff.
So this is good. This is helpful.
Okay.
Okay, you guys make friends with someone.
I will pick pocket them.
Okay.
That's the plan. I'm ready.
All right, I'll try to be really cool and personable to someone if we run across them.
Oh, hold on.
I'll find some clothes so that I can look like reputable.
What's the push talk you said B?
Yeah.
Like burple.
B for burple.
Yeah, what's wrong with my character's name?
Ow.
I don't like the sound of that.
Dude, the one-
Someone just hurt the dog.
I know. It's not cool.
But it's always funny the first one second,
somebody just always gets hit with a sword and shot with an arrow and then we leave.
The devs are so dedicated that made this game.
They killed their own dog for that.
You're a fucking maniac.
The devs.
That is maniacal.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, nice. You got gloves.
Oh, do I?
I didn't even know I picked up gloves.
That's a power move.
There's no clothes, underwear, and gloves.
Those are like Homer Simpson gloves.
These are my pick pocket gloves.
It's like radioactive gloves.
Radioactive.
There's a really big treasure chest in here.
But this room is going to become-
Okay, so there's a mage and that's all spike traps over there.
I'm going to go for the mage.
We shouldn't even get near this
because you probably would range it and kill it.
Well, the spike traps are going to hurt it, too.
Oh, that's right.
Nice dodge.
That was actually very, very well.
That was great.
Yeah, like jumped over it.
Yeah, I don't know how I did it, but wizard robe and stuff.
Oh, stir.
Yeah, pretty well, man.
This is all you.
This one we can open.
You do not have sufficient skills items to do this.
Oh, do you have to?
Oh, because I don't have the perk.
Oh, yeah, I took pick pocket.
Can we break it?
Oh, I think so, but then you lose items or maybe for the regular chest.
Can you open?
Oh, no, you can't open this one either.
Never mind.
Oh, skeleton.
Maybe in the future I could have the lockpick so that I'm useful to someone.
Lockpick seems very, very, very good.
Feels like there's a lot of chests that are locked in every single game.
Okay, can we check the loot here?
Falchion.
Jerma, you might want a white falchion.
It's not bad.
Yeah, I'll take it.
What was that, sir?
What's in there?
Just a couple of flying skulls.
Okay.
All right.
We should probably go towards the circle.
Yeah, there's going to be flying skulls.
So let's get them.
You can't disarm any of these traps.
Or can you with like a perk or something?
I think there was a trap.
Oh, there's spiders.
Red spiders.
Yeah, I got the light.
You got this.
Okay.
Damn, it's a bandage.
You know, is the lantern any good?
Oh, you can aim the light.
I thought it was just like the thing that sat on your hip.
That's what it is.
You aim it.
That's cool.
Jerma, here, why don't you...
Oh, shit.
Hang on.
Let's take care of these bugs first.
We'll talk.
Oh, this is a spawner.
This pot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got it.
Okay.
That's a lot of bugs.
All right.
You look so funny.
I'm pushing here for you, Jerma.
Oh, they're eating me.
You should take the potion at this point.
Oh, this is...
No, I have...
I have healing.
I have self-heal.
There's a lot of shit in here.
I'm hearing a lot of noise.
Yeah.
They're eating her.
And then they're going to eat me.
Oh, my God.
Bunch of enemies in here.
Let's let them come through the door.
I can shoot them through the door as well.
Take a while, but...
Oh, God.
He's got me.
Nice.
There's a spawner in there.
All right.
He had a diamond.
Is that...
Do I kind of make it like a diamond armor set?
Yo, careful, careful, careful.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Who wants...
Circle's coming in.
Who wants the fountain of speed or whatever?
Lockpick.
All right.
Let me get the spawner.
Oh, that's not good.
Oh, man.
Whoa, I just got pulled.
All right, we should go through the door.
Careful, Sturrier.
You're the only one in there.
Hope I didn't just shoot you, Jerma.
Did I?
Nope.
Okay.
You look like such a dickhead when you do that.
Okay, so...
Looking down and just stabbing.
This one is not locked, actually, this big chest.
You guys can take some of the stuff in this big chest if you want.
I have a...
Just to sell or whatever.
I have a lockpick, but I've only...
Oh, what was that?
Skeleton, skeleton shooting.
Oh, shit.
That's what it was.
I got the door.
I'm going to get the door.
Okay.
Another skeleton.
It's bleeding.
Nice, Stur.
Okay.
Is this a shrine of impactful speed, you said?
Yeah, there's that blue shrine.
Sacrifice.
The blue one over there is extra speed,
but it doesn't really last that long, so...
Yeah, if you die, then yeah, that's where you bring somebody back.
Shitty...
Well, it's not shitty if it's green on this guy over here.
Vinny, you should just take this.
You know, I'm going to take the shitty green anyway.
Oh, what's this?
The health?
Sure.
I mean, we all have full health.
We're going to be getting out of here.
Yeah, we got to get out of here like right now.
Vinny, what are your final thoughts on Metroid Prime Remastered?
I haven't finished it yet, so I don't have final thoughts, but it's good so far.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Yeah, let's get out.
It's going to hurt.
Yeah, this is going to hurt.
Out, out, out, out, out.
Trying to speed again.
All right, mine's still going.
Oh, Vinny, you can just take it.
All right.
How do you holster again?
Okay.
What's down here?
Whoa, wait.
Big room.
No, never mind.
Just a little secret passage.
That's a connector.
Don't see anyone.
This place has been looted.
Yeah, we're getting out of the final five minutes.
This is going to start to get a little hairy.
Oh, there's a mimic down there.
I don't know if it's still alive to the north.
Turn the roaster on.
Turn the roaster off.
We should just get out of here because we're going to get in trouble by the circle.
Okay, careful with that jump.
Yeah, make sure you're holstered before doing that jump.
How do you do that again?
X.
Um, shrine of protection.
I would recommend you get it, Star, because you're squishy.
Yeah, you have no gloves on.
Oh, you got us the gloves.
Right here, this red one.
Oh, there's a chest.
Oh, okay.
What is that?
People coming, people coming.
No, I'm just shooting this.
No, there's people behind this door.
Okay.
Oh, no shit.
One guy.
Hey, you friendly?
That's crap.
Okay, cool.
I got my boys down there.
Are they friendly?
We are friendly.
Please do not kill.
Oh, my goodness.
They're friendly.
Uh, open the door.
They opened the portal.
No, by George, we've just...
Hey, no, no, we're all good here.
How are you guys doing?
Good?
Just, just crouch three times if you're good.
That's three.
That's awesome.
That's good.
But I say we should probably try to find a portal together.
Stir lock, pick them.
Or tick-tock it.
He can hear, they can hear you.
Did I say that out loud?
Did you talk in game?
Guys, I was kidding.
Come on.
That was a joke.
Well, no, no.
Oh, wait, they're coming back.
They're coming back.
Are they fighting?
That's a pretty poor joke of you.
We were just messing around.
We'll help you.
We'll help you guys get out of here.
We don't need to hurt each other.
This is hard enough without violence, you know.
Oh, hey, no, no, no.
All of us are friends.
There's like six of us.
It's not worth it.
No, no, no, no.
Trust me.
We're going to get out of here together.
All of us.
Everybody just relax and let's do this diplomatically.
No, we've literally just got in a fight.
We thought you guys were part of this team.
It's all good.
We're trying to get out with the loot that we have, too, gentlemen.
What he said.
I picked pocket like six times.
I found a portal.
I'm getting out.
This is I hate this.
I hate this.
I'm opening this fucking thing.
I'm going to fucking get back to home base and be like, what?
What?
I thought what the fuck was that?
How did I do?
What do I do?
Oh, I tried to open the chest.
I seem to have messed up.
I didn't open it.
See plenty of portals for all.
Wow.
We actually got out.
Probably should have given that lot pick to somebody that knew what they were doing.
I should have kept pick pocketing.
Jerma, just run through it.
Run through it.
Damn.
Is this like just like hang out near someone that's going to take a blue portal
and then just just run in at the last second?
Like a real asshole.
Oh, there's a portal here.
Did you really pick pocket?
Yeah, I'll offer it to him.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Good luck in your journey.
Good luck in your adventures going forward.
Gentlemen, I bid you adieu.
We got it.
I can't believe this worked.
What?
I hate that.
I don't like this.
It's too awful.
It worked.
What did you take?
I'm not sure.
You just like hold a steel behind them and then it didn't like open a menu or anything.
So I don't know what I took.
I have 10 silver coins.
I don't think I had.
It's jewelry usually.
Yeah, I did not have these 10 silver coins.
So you stole silver.
They probably aren't even going to notice.
I'll be honest.
If like a few silver coins are gone from my pocket, I wouldn't even know.
Oh, I got like throwing knives.
I didn't have those.
This is democracy manifest.
That was amazing.
And we all made it somehow.
Like someone in my chat just said, I can't believe
completely one-sided chatting with randos worked.
Like we don't even know what they're saying.
We were just like talking over everybody being cartoon characters.
And then it would like work somehow.
Jerma, there was no voice chat in the game last beta.
This is brand new.
So you couldn't negotiate.
And every time you ran into someone, it was almost a guaranteed death.
Yeah, that's funny.
All right.
Do you want me to hop out or?
Let's take a look.
I mean, I'm going to be playing this literally all night.
So, okay, if you want to stick around and there's other people that are, I mean, well,
I could do one more with you if that's cool.
Yeah, I'll do one more and then I'll bounce and I'll get some of my own groups going.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm thinking about going in with some gear this time.
Not thinking of thinking I should have pickpocketed more people.
Is this is this like a like, let's go for it round.
I'm down.
I mean, they went to the red portal.
I'm wondering if we were like, do you think we have the skill for a red portal?
Probably not.
Right.
I mean, we could try it.
Why not even just try it?
Okay.
If we see red portal, we do.
If not, then we we leave.
All right.
I'm going to bring at least like something like a better like, yeah, it's all right.
Well, you know what?
You know, fuck it.
Let's just do it.
Okay.
Honest to goodness.
Let's play.
All right, gamers.
I'll be in rats.
What do you mean?
I bought a Glock.
People saying do not go in red.
Where do you get that?
Yeah, we can just try it if we want to.
Well, we'll see.
I mean, yeah, the one time I actually maybe two times I went to the red portal.
It was a nightmare.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a yawn.
That was a dog yawn.
I thought someone donkey punched the dog last time.
Honest to goodness.
Let's game.
Ster is slowly adding a piece of clothing every run.
Yeah.
Oh, do you have something new now?
He's got a hood now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I added something.
I'm evolving characters developing.
Well, I'm literally just getting rid of trash.
Don't don't pick this stuff up.
It's bad.
I need that.
Unless you need boots, which Jerma, you could actually probably benefit from.
I could probably benefit from.
Yeah, some of this just random stuff.
The gloves, too.
Fair enough.
Well, I'm so sorry.
You punch me.
Yeah, I clicked back into the game and just wailed on you.
Hey, this is supposed to be a red portal run.
And I'm already down like three or 4% health.
I mean, I can't even exit the door because you're standing in the way.
Well, I'm looking at you.
Oh, we were talking about eternal cylinder.
Yeah, I think generally we found that we were in generally the same part of the game
when we kind of both had some struggle with it.
But like my chat came into your chat and was like Vinny hated this game.
I didn't hate it.
I liked it enough to finish it.
Yeah, it was it was a nice experience.
It just was a little too long.
Yeah, like two or three hours too long.
Vinny donkey punch does not mean what you think it means.
Oh, oops.
Sorry.
I meant sucker punch.
Maybe we shouldn't ask.
Oh, twenty nine damage.
I'm in so somebody's shooting arrows at my head.
Oh, it's you.
Jerma went out was playing Metroid earlier.
I got the morph ball and I said I got the mouthball.
Oh, nice.
All right.
The garlic is coming and coming into your your brain here.
I see a skeleton.
I joined the party now.
Oh, hey, everyone.
No, no, no, no, no.
We we good.
We good.
We cool.
No, no, no.
Don't do don't do that.
We'll still forgive you.
It's fine.
All right.
Kill him.
He's killing us.
I'm I'm fumbling the controls.
I fumbled.
Please do not let me fumble further.
How many fuck I'm dead.
I've accomplished nothing.
I didn't do my heel either.
I got him.
Wait, what do you mean you got him?
He's down.
Like all of them.
There's one guy.
I don't know.
There's literally one guy.
Jerma, did you kill one?
I killed one.
Yeah.
Oh, well, I ran away like a coward.
I thought they were friendly at first because he was making sounds.
But when you were like, we're friendly and he was like, I was like, oh, okay.
But that was him grunting while he was swinging at us.
Yes, not friendly sounds.
Yeah.
I have your heart so we can.
It's a weird thing to say, but it's true.
I can just we can revive you.
We can revive you is what I'm trying to say.
Oh, yeah.
No, I didn't have it.
I had literally just absolute dog shit on.
I had like a I think I had a green helmet on and that was it.
Okay.
Well, I got that.
So we'll try to find you and get you back.
Cool gaming.
People are saying that that was just the barbarian sound effects.
Was it?
No, he was clearly going like over the voice chat, wasn't it?
I don't know.
No, that sounded like in-game.
The guy did not run at you in real life going.
I thought he was being like funny over the voice comms.
I don't think they're funny.
I'm going to head down this way.
We can get out of the circle and try to find a shrine of resurrection.
He was.
Yeah, no, he definitely was.
Careful.
Don't stand up.
Whatever you do.
I won't.
Okay.
My main strategy is letting you go first.
That's a good one.
Wait, I'm an archer.
That doesn't check out.
We got skeleton here.
Someone might be behind us.
Can you stop turning those off?
I'm trying to watch my TV show of you guys playing and it's dark now.
And darker.
Invisibility potion.
Those are okay.
You can't really attack when you have them, but good to get out of a shitty situation.
Oh, good luck.
Yeah, you're not going to kill that dude.
Careful, sir.
There's another fucking spike in the wall.
That Wraith will kill you both in like one hit.
Yes, sir.
There's like random hard, I guess in quotes, enemies.
Like I said, I'm pretty familiar with the gameplay.
So I've seen Wraiths and stuff.
Did you loot this guy?
I kind of didn't want to because there was a Wraith.
I felt like maybe, maybe not.
Oh, they had some gold.
I took a little bit of their gold.
I took their pants.
This is a treasure chest here.
You know, I do have a campfire kit.
If we find a nice quiet area, I can, we can recover all of our health.
Yeah, you absolutely should, especially because you guys are two now.
You're going to, if you go to, there's a group of three that have half health
versus, you know, you have full health.
I'm hearing a lot of footsteps.
I'm trying, like, I get that.
It's like you're doing like a stream.
You're trying to like talk to your friends and shit.
There's definitely people that way.
There's a mummy.
Oh, red mummy.
Pretty good with that right here.
Ow.
Yeah, we got to, we desperately got to heal up here.
Stir, you know what?
You just can't fire down here.
I don't think anyone's going to use it.
I'm going to use it here.
Yeah.
Just do me a favor, stir.
When you get in here, crouch.
Don't stand up and also put up the light.
Maybe.
All right.
Okay.
Get in here before.
How much does the campfire heal?
I know it does refresh on spells too, right?
I'm not sure about this.
Yeah.
I haven't used it as a wizard yet, but it looks like it's healing a decent amount
for as long as you're in front of it.
It's like full health for me from now.
Close.
40, 50 percent.
I'd say it was like 65, 70 percent.
It refreshes most skills, not only wizard.
That's actually a huge deal.
Especially if you have one that gets consumed, like the fighter of heal.
That's a big deal.
Hey, we got a little secret tunnel down here.
Yeah.
Oh, okay, cool.
I think there's an escape.
No, that's a wraith.
He's glowing the same blue.
Now an escape just appeared.
There's a guy behind us from the way we came.
That's so scary.
That is like terrifying looking.
That's a rogue.
You want to take this?
Is that a rogue or a mage?
You take it.
You sure?
Yeah.
All right.
Nice job.
Good luck, sir.
Looks like a whole party.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Just stay in this.
Don't bump me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
They're bumping you.
They might just think it's lag.
They do like he's like, oh, what was that?
They just kept going.
I mean, that's what I would think if I like, why can't I move?
What's going on?
That'd be lag.
You have an invisibility potion too, right?
Nice smart, smart, smart, smart gaming.
Oh, you can't move when you do it.
Oh, that's so lame.
Oh, that you can't.
Close the door behind you.
Yeah, you're in the hell room, sir.
Pretty much everybody's going to be here in a second.
Three minutes.
Oh, it's a perk to do that.
There's a perk to make it so you can move 10 steps.
I have that.
Just just talk to them.
Just just reason with them.
All right.
I fucked up.
I mean, I would have stayed invisible, but I have that perk.
But it's not my invisibility.
So I don't know if it would work that way.
Jerma, I still have some of the stuff.
I don't know how to.
I don't think I can give it to you in the menu here, but.
No, no, the only way you can trade is kind of is we would have to both join the trader thing.
And it's 15 gold to do any transaction, from my understanding.
Or you have to bring it and drop it, which bringing it and dropping it is a scary thing in its own way.
Oh, no, I was going to have that perk, but then I had to take pickpocket.
All right.
You know what?
It's yeah, you didn't really have anything that great.
So fuck it.
All right.
Yeah, I didn't know that the rogue had a timer on his self either.
Well, OK.
Yeah, no, that was fun.
Vinny, if you're still around, I don't know what time frame you guys are both on,
but I'll be up for like at least another like four or five plus hours playing it.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, I might play because I streamed the direct and then Metroid Prime.
I'm getting a little tired.
So I'll tell you what, I'm probably going to play for like another hour.
But yeah, do your thing.
I know you have a bunch of people that want to check out the game with Friday, too.
I was planning on playing this Friday and maybe grabbing a couple of other people.
So anyone want to play on Friday, too?
Dang.
He's going all in.
Yeah, he's going all in.
I might be around.
Just hit me up.
Yeah, let's see.
All right.
See who's available in the group was as always good.
Stir.
Nice to game with you, gamer.
Yeah, nice to finally meet you for the first time.
You too, man.
I enjoyed this.
We'll game again sometime.
See you.
Yeah.
Take it easy, Vinny.
Bye.
Enjoy Metroid.
That's so funny that it's just like, oh, hey, by the way, it's out today.
I feel like that's the people are doing that.
Companies are doing that now.
What did Nintendo do?
What's out today?
Metroid Prime remaster was announced and came out today.
OK, so we've got to fill here.
I'm going to bring in Caleb.
Oh, I love Caleb.
Caleb, Caleb's in-game name is fucking crazy.
I don't even want to type this.
Who's Caleb?
Hold on.
I have to type it, so I'm going to type it.
Let me get him in here.
I add some.
Oh, here we go.
Yo.
Hello.
How goes it?
How are you?
Can you please introduce yourself?
Because people have no idea who I'm bringing into the game right now.
Yeah, my name is Jess Joles, and I'm really nobody.
But I work for somebody cool.
And that's why I'm at Germo.
That's all that matters.
I work for somebody.
Well, if everyone's saying who, who, who, who.
He can't talk about it because it's President Biden.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
We actually invited him to the White House and Secret Service, basically.
Let me add you.
What's your name again?
Oh, God.
Like that, I think.
That's you.
You are awkward.
I don't even know how to.
We're just going to move on from that.
Yeah, we're just going to move on.
We're just going to move on.
You are a player, by the way.
Sterling, he's a player.
He's a player.
Okay, just to let you be aware, in case you bring any important items in,
my main strategy is running away as soon as anything bad happens.
And if you expect me to help you, I just want you to be aware that
I'm probably three rooms down.
Oh, perfect.
No, that's excellent.
I actually like getting all the kills.
He's a new player.
So am I.
I started literally two days ago.
Really?
Yeah.
I think we talked about this in the car.
I think we talked about this game and how I was like literally
just ranting and raving about this game.
Yeah.
So that's huge.
All right.
Let me bring my best gear so I can be sad that I lost it.
Oh, don't do that.
No, no, no.
I only have purples.
What?
No, calm down.
Calm down.
Hold on.
You have.
All right.
We're going to get carried, Sterling.
This is going to be great.
No, no, no.
Calm down.
Wait, wait.
You're a ranger.
Wait, you're a ranger.
I'm a rogue.
Oh, my God.
That's so upsetting.
I have a purple bow.
In the car?
In the car.
What do you mean in the car?
When I.
OK.
When I was for tummy time, I had to hang out with a lot of really cool people
and just Jules was one of those people.
Well, I appreciate that.
I just happened to be there.
Right place, right time.
All right.
I am.
I'm good to go.
I'm geared up.
Actually, do you have a pendant?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I.
OK.
If you maybe I'll bring some some good shit because if you're going to actually
this is probably going to go pretty well because earlier we were doing some Facebook runs.
So it's good to have a quam kuzler.
That's you guys.
It's French.
You guys.
Again, it's quam kuzler.
You guys are going to get along.
I already know.
So we're good.
It's going to be a family name.
I'm already fat fingering my all.
This is good.
Here we go.
So you're a barbarian and you I want to inspect you
because I want to see just how hard we're about to get carried here.
So the beauty about barbarian is once you hit level 15, all you need is a good axe
and I'll and just no thoughts.
You just hit people in the head.
That's all you do.
Come here.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
Can I inspect?
How do you can I inspect you?
How do I do that?
Yep.
I'll turn over and cough.
OK.
That's a big axe.
Yep.
Here.
I'll drop it for you here.
You want to see it?
Oh, my God.
That's scary.
This thing's crazy.
Oh, my God.
He dropped the axe.
Whoa.
OK.
What if I DC or something?
That's axe caliber.
I'll never I'm never speaking it.
I'm sorry.
Anyways, check this out.
Check this.
So these big screen big scary guys over here, right?
Also, my interact speed is awful.
But just watch this.
Just watch this.
Oh, hello.
We are essentially going to be and oh, my goodness.
OK, stir.
I hope you're ready to just kind of like collect items from people.
I mean, that's all I've been doing.
So I feel like this is a good even spread.
So paid actor.
Have you guys hit the dummy yet?
Like with the weapons and you like got your numbers
like to figure out your damage and all that.
I haven't gotten any numbers.
Well, it's kind of hard because the match starts so quickly.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I sprint down there.
I literally pop my rage and I just like run down to the fucking the dummy
really as like quickly as possible.
So the average like arming sword does 30 damage and this axe does 160.
Oh, my God.
All right.
So you have two little brothers right now.
Essentially, what's going on?
That's always what I've wanted.
I will be torch guy.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, God.
Yeah, yeah.
Dead in one hit.
Oh, my God.
I come to this nature.
I feel like this is an advertisement for the game.
Well, you could do this.
This is a very different game.
Archer up top Archer up top.
Mm hmm.
Uh, what Archer?
What Archer?
Should that hurt my bad boys?
I'll leave some mobs for you all.
Oh, my God.
There's skeletons here.
Help.
I mean, like, do I have to hit things to level though?
Yes.
So I'm going to let I'm going to let you tap them.
I'm just going to kill them.
Just give them a little love tap.
Let me know you're there.
Yeah.
Good boys.
Good actor.
I got like credit for the kill.
If you carry me.
Beautiful boys.
That was excellent.
And you have a you have a page on E.
Oh, my God.
Crunchy.
E pal dot com.
I can buy a purple now, by the way, from that store.
I have I got two more crunchies.
A little meta gaming tips.
So if you find something that you like want to give to your friend,
don't leave it in the chest.
Just take it out and drag it out because the interact speed for other
players is trash.
Sometimes you actually both probably have rogues have the highest,
I think, other than Rangers.
Yeah, I'm Rogan.
I need boots or gloves or something.
Oh, excuse me.
I have a question.
Boots.
Do you have boots and gloves?
How do you get down here?
I have wondered the same thing.
Really?
You said we just know.
OK, you think I'd know.
But I actually you know what?
Hold on.
My senses are tingling.
I think if there's a lever somewhere.
Yeah, you can't break it.
I agree.
You can't like smash her.
If I had to guess, it's probably this door right here.
Watch this.
No shot, bro.
I'm a fucking wizard.
There's a gamer behind us.
Gamer behind us.
Where I am.
Can you kill him in one hit?
He's opening this door.
I'm invisible.
Let me let me let me.
Oh, yeah, you got him.
You got him.
Yep.
Boys.
I didn't hit him.
I'm helping.
All right.
The lights are off.
I can't see.
Oh, my God.
There's a mummy.
I lit it up.
I'm lighting it up.
I don't know how I didn't hit him.
I'm stunning the mummies.
That group is still over there, I think.
100 percent.
I'm creeping.
They're looking at us just playing musical chairs with the mummies,
and they're just like, oh, this is easy.
They probably saw your axe and probably just went, oh, shit.
They went.
Do you know what door they took?
There's beds in here if you guys want to take a nap.
Wait, wait.
I think they did the loop, de loop, and pull.
I think they went.
No, they didn't.
Hold on.
Friends, are you still there?
Still there.
I miss you.
I'd say we're just trying to find the portal if you've seen one.
Oh, we're in RP.
But why does everybody hate that voice?
It's not Stewie Griffin.
It's fucking somebody else.
It's it's like the Stanley parable.
Now, would either of you happen to have like any healing of anything?
If not, if not, don't worry about it.
It's fine.
No, I couldn't possibly need it.
I could possibly take it.
I got this full diapy.
Why?
There's not.
OK, let me just go over a few things.
There's not a single solitary reason for you to have said that right now for any reason.
There's not a single reason to say what you just said.
No, he was asking what we had.
So you have shit into a full you've shit into a diaper to fill it up is what you're telling us.
That's all you have.
It's loaded.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God.
There's healing right here.
Praise the heavens.
Nice.
And I just said it out.
You've ruined everything.
I'm sorry.
I'm dumb.
No, no, no, no.
Intelligence intelligence is six.
It's six.
Not you.
I'm talking about creepo, man.
Oh, there's a man.
There's a guy fighting spiders in there.
All right.
What about two people?
Hey, it's your last day on this planet.
Oh, my God.
I was a part of that.
No, you were.
You were an accessory.
If we all get charged for murder, it's all equally on us.
Yeah.
Oh, there's a suiander, too.
That was it.
Oh, boys, boys.
You're making mistakes.
All right.
Look at this.
Look at this, man.
Everybody inspect the rogue.
On this rogue was a ring.
OK.
You guys missed it.
This is a this is a common mistake.
Oh, demonize over here.
Yeah.
Don't miss rings.
Oh, my God.
And a necklace and a necklace.
This is an awful day.
Oh, happens.
Happens to the best of us.
I'm going to put on this suiander.
I mean, I said the typey thing, but I think suiander is worse.
So zwei handers.
Like, if you right click it, right click.
Not close to anybody.
Jesus.
What?
You literally helicopter around.
Oh, please, please, God.
No, please.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Please.
I'm not going to do.
I'm not going to kill you as a joke.
No, I just I mean, you would.
But I not when you're decked out in purples.
If you have all these purples, there's no way I kill you for a joke.
I literally have on a gray armor and just this purple axe.
That's the barbed life.
That's the that's the whole thing right there.
Oh, my God.
A potion.
Oh, beautiful.
So you guys.
What if you say that like it's your last day on earth and then they kill you?
That doesn't happen.
That's never happened in my entire streaming career ever.
What if it does that?
I was thinking it's like what if he just gets like headshot by an arrow?
I have absolutely talked mad trash and gotten stopped before.
It's very upsetting.
I got a surgical kit.
All right, let's go.
Oh, you should take that.
Oh, where where where's that surgical kit?
Well, where I I'm holding it.
I don't want you to have it.
Let's go.
Beautiful.
I feel like you're already strong enough.
Like you really need to heal.
Well, if another barb hits me in the head, I'm definitely dead.
But, you know, honestly, I do get increased strength with lower lower strength.
Oh, sorry.
Lower health.
So if you do die, we need to we need to make sure we get that axe then.
Right?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's it's fine.
It's fine.
I'll I'll just cry about it.
I mean, that sounds cool.
Stir is such a Chad.
Somebody said that about Easter.
I don't know.
They just said it.
Okay.
Well, thank you for reading that comment instead of like the one guy who probably said
something negative.
It's a big moment.
Negative chats don't exist.
We just don't we just don't read those.
There's red portals over here.
Oh, those are those are evil.
I know.
But like I feel like you have a one shot kill axe.
I if you're scared of the red portal, I'm scared of the red portal.
I am.
I am indeed scared of the red portal.
I am a big.
I mean, I'll go.
I'll go.
But I mean, I mean, I've been I've been I've done it.
You know, I think it would be you versus the dungeon and we would just be running behind
you picking up things.
I think so.
What I would do is if I was going to go red dungeon, we would all have to be clerics and
we would just spam the heal spells to kill everything and then bring a bunch of camp
fires.
That's my met.
Oh, there's a blue portal if anybody wanted to guarantee their loot.
Did you I get hit by these all the time, too.
All right.
Are you guys looking for action?
You guys looking for loot?
What's the deal here?
I think I'd like to I have two crunchies and it lets me buy a purple.
So I and thanks for leaving.
I was good.
What do you have on you, sir?
A surgical kit.
There's a blue right there.
I have that three current three countries.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you're going to die to this right there.
I almost got you hit the axe again.
Yeah, I just do you right now.
I would say that would be kind of funny, but I hope you don't.
All right.
Yes, I got two crunchies.
So now what are you going to do?
Are you just let's watch?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Observe, observe not hitting these axes.
Watch this one, two, three feet like that every time.
How does he do it?
I don't know.
But there's four people, there's three people, four people.
And I think you are the one versus three, maybe.
Wait, I hear.
Hold on.
These boxes are in my way.
Pesky boxes.
Hmm.
Does that look funny in third person?
Yes, it kind of does.
Do you?
All right.
So there are three people left.
Are you one of them?
Like on the little indicator over there?
Yes.
OK, so good luck.
Where is the indicator?
We are getting out.
Above the map, all the filled in little columns or whatever,
those are people that are dead.
So you are the only one.
Somebody just died.
Let's go.
Nuts.
Awesome.
That's a dub, boys.
I'll take it.
So OK, very important.
I have 25 of those like Valentine's crunchies.
Yeah.
This is a big decision because I think I can afford to buy something crazy.
Yeah, so that's how I got this axe.
And I'll tell you, it was both the best and worst purchase of my life.
Why is that?
You know, like the gear hoarding syndrome,
like you get a bunch of gear, you just never use it because it's too nice.
It just sits in your stash.
Yeah, that's what I plan on doing.
Don't do that because we only have a week, but we have less than that now.
So.
Oh, but what if I'm going to lose it immediately?
I would buy this.
I'm going to make it back.
Don't be silly.
What should I get?
Treat yourself.
Well, what's in your merch?
Arming sword, which is too magic.
OK, so does magic damage work?
Not for you.
But that this is this is just this is dumb.
Um, let me see.
Let me see.
So you have arming sword.
You have a halberd is the halberd 30 or.
That's 30.
Have you tried the halberd?
I'm a fan.
Some people are not, though.
I prefer the one handers.
I see, I see.
I wish I get the mace.
Yeah, maces high key trash a lot of the times, in my opinion.
Well, what about like a hmm.
Yeah, but does this change?
Well, this will change in eight hours.
Yeah, it'll change.
Actually, you know what you can do, and this is this is meta gaming,
but I can check my merchant, too, and you can trade me the candies
and I can get you something and I can trade it back.
That's meta gaming.
I never mentioned that.
But let me check for you.
That's a really cool idea.
But this whole thing has been for you to take these and then leave the call.
Um, that's how that that sounded.
That sounded like an elaborate scam.
I would never see.
I'll take them.
I'll go spend it and like I'll bring it back.
And then you just unfriend me on Discord and you leave.
And I never heard it ever again.
It's wild that I have this like purple rapier here with plus one physical damage,
plus one additional physical damage and plus one strength.
I would never do such a thing.
Um, I think I'll hold it because I want to I probably want to see what else is
because I like the one hander.
I don't I'm not like a rapier fan.
That's like you like poke, right?
It's like stab in front.
It's like some finesse.
It's got some finesse to it.
It's all it's more than poking, I'd say.
Sir, do you think I should do it or not?
Hey, he's always gone.
Uh, what what I was uh, I was getting a diapy change.
I think the powder god, you are killing me.
What are we going?
Wait, what's what's in your what's in your store?
What's in your valentine's?
What were you asking me?
Why did you need my attention?
He was asking you if you should if you should trust me.
Then you were you're out there doing adult things.
I don't in my store.
I'm confused.
I'll have you know that I I you got me paranoid.
The germa paranoia rubbed off on me and I did get some anti-worm medicine.
Yeah, I figured, you know, why not?
Why not?
Just in case.
Hey, facts.
I love how you don't know even what that is.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Like, you know, of course, who doesn't get anti-worm medication?
We had a brief discussion about health and wanting to always be cleanly and all that.
I just inferred it had something to do with that.
Yeah, but I do have no idea.
Absolutely all just completely flushed straight out into the diaper.
This is a weird one tonight.
Hey, man, I'm ready to go.
You're out here buying weapons.
I just look at my store.
No one can kill him and he just walks around like like what is this game?
Yeah, but I have to I have to put stuff in my inventory.
I have to sell the stuff I got.
Okay, so empty your inventory.
Okay, let's take off all your clothes.
Okay, you ready?
Yes.
Let's go ma no worms.
By the way, I brought a campfire.
Oh, good, good, good.
You can use the campfire not only to heal, but it also replenishes your abilities.
Yeah, that was we would ask that.
So is it all abilities or is it just some of them or?
Pretty much.
It's like it's like a DND short rest pretty much.
Yeah.
So you get some spell slots.
It's actually I'm really glad the whole pork arc happens because now I know that me
and my horse don't have worms and I definitely don't have COVID.
Your horse?
What do you wait?
Hold on.
Did this just turn what is going on?
I need some sort of fill in here.
Maybe I don't.
No, I hear you stir.
Can I give him just this quick TLDR?
That was that was too deep of a joke.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, give him the TLDR.
So stir had it had a backpack and he had he went grocery shopping.
You know, those kind of ready made but raw meals like, oh, it's a pork chop and potatoes.
And it's just like kind of in the grocery store and you put it in the oven.
It's like a ready made thing for you just to put it in the oven.
He left it out for 16 hours accidentally.
Get a backpack on the floor.
All right.
You're going to want to talk to my wife about that.
Nah, wait, take this.
That's worth a lot of money.
She's trying to kill me, dude.
What?
Yeah, actually, who?
That's not a defrost.
That's like a that's like a re like that's making it wrong and like unhealthy.
We're going all like I was just hit him with the sword.
All right, boys.
I'm kind of a boxing match.
There's a guy down here.
Got him.
He's dead.
Oh, yes.
What do you got?
I actually have to I have to actually can't fire now.
I have the surgical kit with me either shield you want to go.
Yeah, I'll trade you the campfire for that.
I put it down.
Oh, my God.
Bless this man, sir.
Do you want I have a heater shield from that and a survival?
There's I don't need a weapon.
You realize if you go to you're going to like we run into a group of three.
I don't think I need a weapon is what I'm seeing.
Look at I move a bit faster while it's holstered.
Okay, so you're full.
All right.
You're good.
Yep.
Hey, Jeff, I would watch the confidence level here because it's so it's so simple to have
somebody have an equal amount of good gear on them and be an equally good player and
wipe the floor with the whole group.
I don't think anyone's better than.
All right, I'm leaving.
Give me give me your candy.
I just got hit twice.
You wanted to say it so bad.
Oh, my God, please take these, please.
What's your name again?
Because his name, the in game name like get educated.
I want to say it differently.
That's what I'm saying.
I know you say it that way.
I know.
So I had to check myself.
That's all I'm saying is I checked like the worms are getting to your brain.
There's no worms.
I dewormed.
Sure you did.
Now, oh, friends, we got friends.
Oh, God, he's a ranger.
He's a ranger.
Stop, stop, stop.
I just took my horse dewormer.
I can't go out like this.
I'm just going to hide over here for a second like this, dude.
Please, please.
I'm one hit.
Don't do it.
Are they coming?
I'm scared.
They are preparing.
Let's actually go for this.
I don't know how we do this.
Somebody has to open the door.
I'm going to run you.
I'm running you.
All right.
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to pot up.
I'm going to I'm going to envis.
I'm going to envis.
And then you just you just run past me.
Just run past me.
I'll fuck him up.
OK.
Here, come over.
I'm invisible as well.
Oh, you're screwed.
Yeah, you're the only one.
They're turning off the only one.
I'll turn lights off, too.
Fuck that.
Yeah.
Who said you get there?
They're walking away.
They walk away.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
Even darkness is your ally.
I was born in it.
And you from the darkness should become blind.
That's pretty good.
All right.
I can do better.
Yeah.
Oh, you think the darkness is your ally?
My God.
You see the darkness now.
I believe that you and I will have a fight in the darkness.
Bruce Wayne.
Where's Rachel?
Where is she?
They're doing the same thing.
I just looked over there.
They're literally doing the same thing.
Oh, dude.
Well, they're the thing is they're bad.
We're good.
There's a difference.
Actually, I can't see.
Hold on.
It was kind of weird.
I'm going.
Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Going, going.
I'm doing alchemy.
Oh, he froze me.
Free tech.
One down.
It's so dark.
I don't know where I am.
Who's alive?
Oh, should I just hit you?
I just.
No.
Fuck.
Sterling, you killed me.
Sterling.
The darkness is your ally.
Oh, my God.
You killed him.
You just killed me.
Never turn off the lights again, you troglodyte.
Holy shit.
Wait, what?
Backwards and not swinging.
Saw you die.
And you're like, oh, it was stir.
I didn't, dude.
You hit in the back.
It's cool.
Pervert.
With your sweet hander.
Oh, my goodness.
That was so scary.
I thought I honestly thought you were going to die in there.
It goes lair.
Do you want to camp?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
100%.
All right.
I killed.
Hey, I did get a full.
I killed somebody in the very beginning.
I helped.
And then I may have hit you in the rib cage.
To be fair, the lights were off and they turned on.
And it was just people around me.
And I didn't know who was who.
I turned on the light.
I was holding the torch.
I was giving you light.
And then you hit your ally and then blamed your other ally.
I thought you were just killing me.
How dare you turn on the lights?
That's why I hit him.
The first thing I saw.
I couldn't see.
As soon as I could see, I just started swinging.
The first thing I did when my vision came back was blindly swing in a circle.
But wait, there's context behind this.
I'm sorry.
It was six people in the same tiny little fucking area.
And the lights were all off.
So it's like, I don't know who lived it.
I know one of them died.
I didn't know that it's hard to see.
I know that maybe two of them died.
When the lights came back on, people are still swinging.
I'm like, wait a minute.
We might be hitting each other.
I hit you accidentally.
And then apologies.
I thought stir was just stabbing me in the face.
All right.
This is the wrong room.
Oh, no, not today.
Not today.
Oh, but you almost just got wrecked.
Yeah, yeah.
If I don't turn around quick enough, I will accidentally swing on you.
We got to I think if I'm not mistaken.
Hold on.
I mean, let me just kind of loud.
Is this a little loud?
Is that echoing?
No, you're good.
Does anyone hear us?
All right.
Come with me.
I think I think there might be like I come with you or qualm with you.
I was about to be over the I was going to go over comms and yell at you.
I was going to be like, stop team killing, team killing, team killing.
But that guy would have been like, what is this fucking kid talking about?
That's a good strategy.
Oh, no, this is awful.
All right.
I followed you to the grave.
I know.
It'll be okay.
You're being dramatic.
Oh, and here's a cleric trying to get a cheeky kill on me.
Oh, he died to a spike.
He was beautiful.
Wait, watch out.
I dropped caltrops on these stairs.
Oh, good.
He almost got used to her.
But he didn't.
It was calculated.
I don't know where they.
Oh, I see them now.
I got to go.
This game is so good.
It really is.
I don't.
All right.
I have these Heelys.
Oh, and I have another campfire.
Can you set this down?
Because I literally have the interaction speed of a walrus with no flippers.
Don't ask.
How long does it take for you?
That translates to when you do medical wraps and stuff, too.
Right.
Yeah.
You see this?
I might as well be like rubbing my wounds with sandpaper.
It's so long.
I actually haven't like measured it out.
But like, what's your resourcefulness level or your attribute?
Because mine's 10.
Oh, my God.
That's low.
Yeah.
You know, big dumb and big bad.
Wow.
In my hands, basically.
32 strength, though.
That's pretty good, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's nuts.
Do you not like lights?
What is up with you in turning off everything?
You are turning all the lights off.
Once shit goes down, I want to be able to go invisible in a corner.
You can do that with lights, though.
Can you?
Yes.
You just stealth anywhere?
This game's super unrealistic.
Yes.
Yeah.
As a rogue.
Not the magical.
This I'm like wondering why the heck you're turning off.
I can't see what I'm hitting when you when you interact so quickly.
Why not?
Oh, you know, that must be nice.
Yeah.
Watch this.
Watch you go turn off one.
Oh, this is a portal over here.
Beautiful.
Oh, no.
No.
These are players.
Oh, no.
This is a bad time.
See, this is where I'm running.
Now, this makes sense.
You run.
I will run, too.
I'll catch up.
Yep.
See, I open that door.
I can't do that.
I can close them.
There's a there's a wraith in here.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Just just just run.
Just run.
I must I must save this V hander.
All right, dude.
Yeah.
Oh, I shut the door on you a little.
It takes me five years to open this.
I hope you know.
You killed the man today.
You killed the Coom today.
I hope you know you did that.
Do you need it open?
I can open it.
No, no.
It's too late, dude.
I opened it.
Oh, no.
You killed the man today.
He's dead.
Sir, are you going to go get that fucking axe?
You killed the man today.
Sir, you killed the man today.
Don't even bother.
It's not worth it.
I can't believe it.
What are you doing?
Sir, what have you done?
Damn it.
It could have been us.
That could have been us.
All you had to do was fight them.
I I don't I'm not a part of this.
And you know what?
The worst part is we lost the Zwei hander.
You lost the Zwei hander, too.
Ah, we lost the Zwei hander.
Is there anywhere to know where portals
are appearing?
It's random and there's only enough for like one or two of you to get out.
They are random in this circle and there's only enough for maybe one more of you to leave.
There it is.
Wow, how poetic, too, just for us.
What do you have in your inventory?
Hey, I'm glad you got out of here with the ancient scroll.
We killed you.
Yeah, that's amazing.
Well, that was well back to remember our carry.
Well, now you don't have the weapon.
OK, that's beautiful.
I have multiple.
Wait, hold on.
Do you have like a whole closet of like Peter Griffin shirts?
Yeah, it's yeah.
Oh, I stay.
I keep that thing on me.
Oh, OK.
All right.
What do you think this is?
That's cool.
That's good.
Yeah, that works.
Yeah, we're good to go.
Actually, I have.
Oh, I know.
Wait, you're a rogue, right?
Oh, God, if you hadn't screwed me over.
I have like this nice blue stiletto dagger that I could give you.
Me?
The guy who left you to die.
What do you mean me?
Are you live right now, by the way?
Yes, yes.
Just in case people want to see your perspective.
I'm sorry.
I was ignoring you and reading a text message.
So I like only heard me.
You know what?
I hope that your horse dewormer was left out for 16 hours as well.
It almost made me want to throw up.
So it might as well have been.
This is a what an unbelievably strange conversation.
It's OK.
Rene, what's your Twitch?
It's just Joel's J-U-S-T-J-O-E-L-S.
So if you want to see the game or perspective.
They don't want that.
Some people do.
Some people like games.
All right.
Well, that was a fun one.
I had a good time.
Yeah.
Let's go again.
Yeah, let's run it.
But I have a necklace that I'm going to bring you so you can stay geared up.
I would recheck your shop.
Sometimes it does switch up.
Yeah.
Even when the timer is not up?
Sometimes it just randomly switches up.
I don't know why the timer is there.
I got to be honest.
It looks at the same.
I'll check it later.
I'll check it tomorrow, whatever.
Honestly, I might even be live during this.
Actually, probably not.
Let me think about it.
I'm going to bring.
I'm going to just bring like a decent one.
Yeah, I don't want to bring it in my blues.
I know.
Don't hoard.
Don't hoard it.
But it's nice to look at.
Okay, it's nice to be able to open my stash and look at all this money and go, wow, look
at that sword.
Look at those boots.
Look at that sword.
Listen to me, Jeremy.
If you don't bring a blue or like multiple blues with you, I'm just going to team kill
you when we get in here.
So the choice is yours at this point.
Bring the blues or suffer the consequences.
If you don't bring the blues, I'm going to shut that door in your face.
What the fuck?
I'm going to leave your dinner out for 16 hours.
How about that, pal?
Okay, what if I bring?
I need you to like strip down when we get in the lobby.
I got it.
I'm bringing a good item.
Two, at least.
That was the arrangement.
Okay.
I do have two good items on.
This thing is actually really good.
Whoever gets this, congratulations.
It's a different colored item.
It's a different like rarity than just the simple, the common.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Yeah, so we're good.
I like to hear that.
All right, let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
Term it ends in a few days.
Yeah, we don't acknowledge it.
It's not real.
Just people saying that what may is when it might be coming back.
If they do a fifth play test, that's kind of wild.
I don't know what else they would add other than like other areas,
kind of like in Tarkov, like you have like storage factory and all that.
And so it's going to go into open beta.
Or I mean, are they going to how much is it going to be free to play?
Are they going to charge for it?
Like, I wonder what their plan is.
I would gladly pay money for this.
And if they don't charge for it, I will still pay money for this.
Yeah.
All right, team killer.
Here you go.
No, that's not you're not team killer.
No, no, that's that's not you.
OK, this is this is for you.
I just want to see what that internet.
Hey, how come we're picking up chalices all the time?
There's a bunch of chalices on this table, but I can't pick up these chalices.
Hey, sir, you actually take this.
Maybe the table is broken.
Hold on.
Sir, you're going to want to wait.
That's how you should kind of hold on.
Oh, you brought me the blue.
Yeah.
So now we won't team kill us.
That's that's that's what team team works all about.
Teamwork, teamwork.
That does like a lot more damage.
Yeah.
So that right click, honestly, the stiletto combo is the best combo from what I remember.
Don't don't even.
Yeah, don't even mess.
Yeah, just just that right there.
You're going to just wax.
Hey, try it on my face.
Yeah.
Yep.
Well, I mean, I could try it on a zombie face.
We actually probably should go.
Oh, no, we can't.
This guy is dying for us.
That's so sweet.
Oh, what a swell guy.
Pretty sick.
Hey, can we start a potion?
Nice guy lights off real quick lights off.
Honestly, I was kind of upset.
I could see the game for a second.
You got to take a cat's eye potion.
How many subs to take out?
One hundred, one hundred subs.
I'll team kill German immediately.
Someone's going to do that.
I just I hope you understand.
That's going to happen in like five seconds.
This is no, no, no, no, we're not paying that.
No, no, I have nothing to do with this.
That would be that would be unbelievable.
And let me tell you something, by the way, the guy trapped in the electric chair.
I have nothing to do with it.
Oh, yeah, I'm going over this right now.
I got shit for spending seventy five bucks on the fucking family guy mobile game.
If you spend five hundred bucks on killing me in this game.
Excuse me.
What do you think?
I have fruit fruitless fucking expenses.
Wait, seventy five dollars.
Explain.
That's a bit that's a bit obsessive.
OK, it was.
But it was I could tap on the houses.
He could tap on the houses.
Oh, my God.
Did give this guy a mobile game and he'll give you a hundred dollars.
Dark and dark.
The mobile game releases tomorrow.
Inventory Management 2.0.
Jeremy, I can't believe you spent like 70 bucks on that game.
That's like what a bad purchase.
Hey, hey, hey, other streamer.
Here's five hundred.
Oh, Jesus.
Somebody paid this motherfucker.
Somebody paid him.
Did you actually get somebody actually give you what I just saw?
I just saw him take you down.
I just I felt compelled to do it.
Like now.
Oh, my God.
What have I done?
Now you're alone and you're not.
You're alone and you've got a really good axe.
And I hope you got a whole fucking closet of Peter Griffin shirts because that one's
gone to listen.
Listen, I didn't do it for the money.
Ethan, I did it for the club to be able to say that I'm a virtual assassin.
Yeah, I've got a paid hit job on my record.
Oh, my God.
He's not to extract quickly because now I feel bad.
Well, you also are potentially going against multiple.
Is this a blue or is this purple?
Oh, this is a perp.
You can press tab to inspect my inventory.
You can see the drip I got on.
Thank you so much, Disco.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, watch this.
Do watch this.
Watch this.
Also, anytime I kill an enemy, I get plus 10 strength.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Plus.
Yeah, plus 10 strength.
I'm sorry.
That's what it is.
Oh, jeez.
And then I get a little buff after that.
It's it's it's amazing.
It really is.
I can't fucking believe that there was just a literal assassin kill transaction that just
played out on the stream.
That's going to it's going to be a real boon to my virtual assassin business.
I'm starting.
What are you going to call your
testimonials?
I have.
Oh, I killed German 985 in dark and darker.
Yeah, you know, you get and you'll have like you have a quote from me, right?
It's like in like a little test, like, oh, man, like, what the fuck, dude?
I can't believe you did that.
And it says like, and then in like brackets, really pissed off.
Yeah, it's already being set up.
I can go take out anyone.
Oh, time.
Yeah, boys.
Nice interaction.
You don't need to do it.
Look what you've done.
Yeah.
Oh, no, this is the worst room.
Oh, don't do it.
Don't do it, bro.
I'm a good.
I'm a good boy.
I'm a good person person.
Well, let me turn off the light so I can't see shit.
Did they actually leave me alone?
These these nerds?
Maybe they didn't.
Maybe they don't know who you are.
Oh, oh, oh, my goodness.
Oh, that.
Oh, man.
He just like, I feel for that guy because like, that's me.
That's your future.
His future was indeed ratchet, wasn't it?
That's me.
Like, I've been in that scenario like 30 times.
I feel for that guy.
I really do.
All right, let's get out of here.
I'm scared.
Just trying to adventure.
Just trying to get gear and shit.
I got a lot of loot this level.
You're dead.
Some say the loot is the friends are made along the way.
All right.
Oh, that dude is crying now.
You did get a lot of loot this level.
That's right.
Very profitable dungeon.
It was a good dungeon for you.
I got a rock.
Will you stop hitting me?
Thank you.
Oh, friends.
All right, here's the weak strat.
Watch that.
I have feign weakness, right?
Don't, please, please.
No, stop, please.
Oh, my God.
Please, no, please, God, no, please.
But you roared and that's a sign of aggression.
I don't know if I would.
I'd probably attack.
I'm still here.
This is where you have to say like your controller unplugged.
Steps is what you're doing.
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck in the gate.
Oh, my God.
These guys suck.
Have you seen that poke clip?
Yeah.
It was amazing.
So fucking unbelievably funny.
Oh, my controller is unplugged.
What the fuck?
He does it twice, too.
That's the best part.
It works two different times.
Do I get style points?
That's sweet.
Do you see that, dude?
Do you see that finesse?
That was actually pretty cool.
I'm kind of rooting for the zombie.
That's why nothing you've done today matters.
Well, I mean, you did kill somebody in cold.
Oh, Jesus.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, he shot me with a crossbow.
What?
He's a gamer.
Oh, my God.
Why didn't you just hit him on the head?
Because nobody paid me 50 subs for it.
That's why.
It's all Chad's fault.
Oh, I'll tell you.
There's a whole battle going on after you died, too.
There was like a whole other group.
I mean, they're going to fight over that.
And it's all right.
You got a whole closet full of those things.
You're fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have the the bardish now.
This this bad girl.
I've been holding on to her.
I feel OK.
You know what's funny?
You've got all this really cool stuff.
And I correct me if I'm wrong here.
I believe your angle here is, you know, you probably would normally would be like,
this actually sucks that I'm losing this this this great stuff.
But you're like, hey, it's over in three days.
Literally, that's where I'm at.
That's where I've been.
I got you.
Since I got in this lobby, that's where I've been.
OK, I got you.
It's it's then I'll bring my blue.
Fine.
Oh, that's that's the blues are standing together.
This is what we need.
But OK, I'm bringing one blue.
But creepo, why don't you bring something about that?
I don't own anything.
All right.
Good thing I brought you a green stiletto broke ass bitch.
OK, I mean, I've got like 100 doubloons.
I don't know.
Should I buy something from those this lonely looking woodsman?
Probably not.
I love the artwork.
Same reminds me of Magic the Gathering.
Hmm.
OK, who is your favorite character?
Like who is who would you like to spend it like, you know,
like, oh, I'm going to go have like a like a beer with this person.
Chandra, the catalyst.
Oh, wait, wait.
Magic or no, no, like in like the Travelers and Merchants.
Dream Blunt rotation.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Mm hmm.
Going you go first.
Yeah, I feel like that surgeon has seen some shit.
I would I would like to have a beer with him 100%.
Yeah, I can see that.
What will you stir?
I don't like any of them.
They all look mean and the tailor looks the meanest.
Like he's going to sell me some clothes with fucking razor blades in them.
Yeah, I maybe Valentine want to figure out, you know,
how he still has hope in such a hopeless world.
Can we talk about how the armor looks like the softest man and the hardest armor?
Like that man is not intimidating anybody.
And that is exactly why you should be afraid.
He's like a baby and like he's like an armored baby with a mustache.
Yeah, I'm picking the alchemist, the alchemist.
And then and then I'm going to like I'm going to like text the goblin
and just just to be like, oh, hey, you've like got a plan,
like doing some stuff just to kind of see like what he says.
And then I'd be able to bail like if it's like if it's a weird shit.
Yeah, you're going to catfish a goblin.
No, I'm just saying like, hey, what are you up to?
Like on like Thursday?
Well, I'm eating.
I'm eating flesh on.
It's like, OK, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm busy.
Like, yeah, I'm just getting I'm getting the lunch.
I don't know.
You wouldn't. OK.
For real, you wouldn't eat some flesh to make a friend for life.
I feel like at least two or three people here probably have eaten somebody
in your chat.
No, here at least I'm going.
But statistically, there's a lot of people here, like maybe three people
at least have probably eaten someone.
I mean, back then, I mean, it probably wasn't, you know, like in this.
All right.
We I'm bringing a good item and let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Yep.
It's weird how the ratio works because I feel like in my chat,
there's probably at least five people that have eaten someone.
There's less.
That's actually like how we get inducted in my chat is we eat people together.
Interesting.
Don't do that.
That's very interesting.
Sorry, I totally forgot to buy health pots because I know the minute
we get in there, Creepo is going to stab me.
So I mean, I'm accepting the fact that no, never mind.
I'm not accepting any assassination contracts right now.
No, and guess what?
And guess what?
If there is one on me, if you got an assassination contract, one of you
to just be aware, I'm fighting back.
I just want you to know.
I am not joining the Dark Brotherhood.
Yeah, honestly, I got to say you didn't do shit when he was just
literally stabbing you in your corneas.
You really just accepted it.
You look kind of dead stared at me.
We're like, this is, it's happening.
I wanted you to feel bad.
I wanted you to be like.
It's crazy how I don't at all.
Like I really got pushed there and I saw it in your face.
Didn't flinch.
Were you just shocked?
Like what was going through your mind at that time?
We're just playing the game.
And watch out for the spider behind you.
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
I'm body blocked.
Okay.
I can't move.
Can you there's I think I dropped a dagger for you.
Is there one here?
Yeah.
Honest to goodness.
Let's play.
Let's play, everyone.
All right.
We got to kill that.
We got to kill a spider spawner.
Oh, oh, beautiful.
I can see now.
This is huge.
The dewormer flushed out all of his feelings.
Yeah, they're in the diaper now.
Oh, beautiful hop, beautiful hop.
Exquisite.
Thank you.
The worms were what made me me.
Oh, that was the good old one, two combo.
Look at that.
The one to buckle my shoe.
I love the long sword, by the way.
It's my favorite weapon.
I jumped.
I jumped over the corner of this and it's still activated.
I'm refunding this game.
That's actually.
Oh, you jumped on that like a trampoline.
I know.
I just wanted to.
I could have walked a long way.
Here's an army sword for you, by the way.
If you want a one hand.
All right.
There are friends directly to our south.
There's a wizard in the room.
A wizard.
Oh, oh, God.
OK, hold on.
We can go this way.
Yeah, I can stun.
I can stun them.
I'll pay you 15 V bucks if you kill stir.
Now, I'm not taking any contracts right now.
Or ever.
Boys, if you take health, we can go back to that healing shrine
at the beginning of the level.
I said nice.
Nice.
Oh, that.
OK, I didn't know that was the second part of the swing.
You kind of really styled with it here.
I got you.
I got you a beautiful little helmet.
Check this out.
Protect that noggin from facial stabs.
All right, pretty good.
Thank you.
I'm going down the secret tunnel.
Secret tunnel.
There were friends down here.
Oh, it's all blocked up right here.
Oh, I can't even hit it because this guy's just standing on the spikes.
That's so sweet of him to take that damage for us.
Oh, he killed a player.
That's so sad.
Oh, oh, this guy is armored.
That's not watch out for the orb.
This is really fun.
I actually really like this weapon of the long sword.
Yeah, you can you can block with it and you can get a parry off.
Sir, do you want to get this hat that I just put on the ground?
It's a guy in.
OK, thank you.
There's a chest that we didn't loot over here.
If you guys I was in the middle of it, but then he offered.
I got it.
It's my I hate.
I'm going to still do it fast.
I'm keeping it closed.
I'm RP opening it with one finger.
Oh, my goodness.
You got launched.
You made a trebuchet out of a that was awful.
And what are these?
What are these sacrifices to resurrect player?
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
There's another big chest.
I'm going to, you know, I'm just going to go over here real quick.
Oh, I don't have the lock.
You take these.
Oh, you're right.
Big enemy.
Oh, yeah.
Come to us.
I can't get them.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
All right.
Close the door.
Good one, guys.
You really had me going.
Oh, my God.
I can't swing in here.
I have to crouch and swing.
That's so sad.
Wait, I think there's.
Oh, yeah.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Uh, help.
All right.
We have to kill these Rangers first, otherwise we're going to get screwed over.
Ranger top left.
Oh, my.
You guys are still on the mummy.
That was just like you.
That was just so funny looking over here.
Talking strategy.
You guys are over there playing patty cake with the zombie.
And I wouldn't trade it for the world.
You boys are the world to me.
Thank you.
What the gas?
Come on.
Do I have any help for healing?
No.
There's a healing shrine right behind you.
Oh, there it is.
Where we came from.
I thought somebody used it.
I was tempted.
You should probably use it.
Can you whirlwind or something?
I have a whirlwind.
What is this?
Everybody, just calm down.
Just calm down.
I'm thinking.
Boom.
There we go.
Kill him.
Oh, shit.
I don't like daggers.
Not a dagger guy.
They're so short range.
Yeah.
Some say it's not the size of the sword.
It's the motion of the blade.
There's a lot of enemies right now.
Yeah.
You guys are getting tons of XP, you know.
There's a purple V hander.
No, there's not.
Oh, there is.
Where is it?
On the floor right here.
Redemption arc.
No way.
Up on the chest up here.
Oh, now you can see it, right?
Holy shit.
Can you see it when I turn that off?
Oh, my goodness.
We got any campfires in here?
I have one on me.
Yep.
Here, if you want to take it
because it'll actually take me four years to set it up.
It'll be 2024.
Holy shit.
The beta test will be over.
This thing is insane.
I thought I heard movement.
Yes, I did.
Oh, we're fucked.
We know we got to get out of here.
You picked the wrong time.
Oh, don't you?
No, come on.
Come on.
Oh, sorry.
Behind you.
German knife.
Oh, my God.
The darkness.
I killed him.
Oh, God, dude.
I was just trying to be the light.
I'm going to die.
No, no, no, you're not.
No, you're not.
Stay with me.
Dedicated light boy.
Honestly, if I had taken that torch down,
we may have actually lost that.
Oh, here you go.
Here you go.
Take this.
Well, it's only one person here has night vision.
It's not me.
Well, yeah, yeah.
Look, I just look.
I just fucked your friends over.
Do not come down here.
I swear to God on everything, brother, brother.
All right.
You do not want this smoke, dude.
I'm not coming down there.
Just don't leave me alone.
Leave us alone.
Look at that strap.
All right.
You have a wonderful evening.
No, the campfire went out.
The campfire just went out.
What the fuck?
I'm running away.
Dude, he was like, I'm literally right in front of you.
I was trying to do like, I was trying to do like, oh, yeah.
Like, oh, man, I'm so scared of you, man.
And like, oh, shit, that guy must be.
He must have beat that guy's friends.
God damn it.
I was I was so concerned.
All right.
Fuck.
This is a cool item.
He's going to come around.
I was.
Oh, my.
Oh, my mother of pearl.
Come on.
Healing healing shrine.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, you should take that.
Yeah.
The strategy was I wanted them to think you were talking to my group
and that you were very strong and to not come down here.
We got it.
Yeah, it was clever.
My knowledge is six.
In RP, I didn't understand that.
But somebody asked in chat.
Out of character.
I definitely.
Oh, well, OK.
Somebody said, what the fuck happened, bro?
And I was explaining it.
All right.
I think there's two portals here.
Nice.
See you later.
Doosies.
Oh, my God.
This is actually crazy.
Come on.
You guys.
You guys are leaving.
Yeah.
100% You guys are leaving, huh?
I I got a purple is way under, man.
This way under arc is just beginning.
I'm sorry.
I had to leave.
No, I understand.
You're a what was that movie?
Uh, oh, my God.
I cannot believe I'm blanking on this movie.
There can only be one.
What's that movie?
I know you know what I'm talking about.
It can only be one.
Yeah.
What?
Highlander.
Yes, the Highlander.
You're a cardigan now for a Kerrigan.
I'm literally right in front of you, dude.
How close was he to me?
Honestly, I feel like he was literally right in front of my like model.
That was nuts.
I don't really know where to go.
All right.
Here's the plan.
What you're going to do is just take the red portal.
No, I'm just kidding.
Um, I just don't want to waste you guys' time.
No, you don't want to take the red.
I just clicked what kind of just happened in the last five minutes.
And I just I just realized what happened.
Uh, do not do.
What are you doing?
What?
Why do you do this?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
What's he doing?
He's causing himself damage to cause me stress.
There's nowhere to go.
Nothing will rival.
You literally avoided the circle just to.
That was amazing.
I was just taking a fucking walk around the park.
Yes.
All right.
I got another stiletto for you.
Luckily.
He's my last one.
I know I'm going to buy you one at this point though.
I could buy one.
I have a short story.
It's not selling any.
Sir, I have a blue short sword.
I mean, I got a really good short sword from someone in that game and then I died.
Well, I have one for you.
And it was your fault.
OK, I'm ready.
What if we all just clicked ready and just went again?
I still have gear.
I'm sorry, stuff to sell.
Yeah.
OK, well, then I'm going to have to go on some like psycho tangent if we don't go right now.
Oh, God.
Oh, he's doing it.
It's the dewormer.
Oh, my God.
OK.
Just stir.
Just wait a second, please.
I'm just I'm just putting it in.
I'm just I'm just.
Oh, sir.
How do you feel about people subs?
They go.
Distract.
That's a meatball firehouse subs.
They make subs.
They make a meatball sub.
Sometimes they get their meatball sub.
It's OK.
It's pretty good.
I think it's pretty safe everywhere.
Most meatballs are too big, though.
Yeah, I can understand.
And there's always the one like cartoon spaghetti plate with one giant meatball on it.
And you know, in the center of that meatball is like an ice cube.
That's actually kind of true.
Interesting.
Yeah, no, I know what you mean.
I like, you know, Subway, the subway meatball sub.
I haven't had it in a while, but they have like the perfect size meatballs.
They're pretty good.
My worms are really like that one.
Have you named your worms?
There's way too many.
That's huge.
I'm proud of you.
It sounds like a healthy colony.
Sir, I got a short sword.
I mean, if you're looking to lose weight, got a couple of tips for you.
You're actually talking to somebody that's very like in the nutrition and fucking fitness world.
Both of you could probably talk to each other and, you know, level.
Oh, well, my suggestion was to get worms.
Yeah, well, I prefer just a worm like a tapeworm.
You know, that way it's like easier to just get that one out.
But hey, I feel like I don't know.
It wasn't a trend for a while to get tapeworms to help people lose weight.
I hope that sounds like something that could have happened.
My big business plan, if I ever really make it and, you know, have some money to invest.
No, don't let him cook here.
He's going to be having LSD drug chairs at a movie theater.
Don't let him cook.
I was going to start talking about putting people in comas for weight loss.
All right.
If you're ever just really bored and you're like waiting for the new like a new game to come out
and you want to lose some weight, just put you in a coma for like a month.
Eric Cartman did that in South Park.
Oh, did he?
Could you imagine, though, like the amount of.
There's a lot of shit in this room.
I'm just thinking, well, yeah, hold on.
Let me stun him, let me stun him.
There we go.
Just kill him.
I was just thinking, like, what would they do with all like this?
Because because people in coma, don't they still defecate?
Like, I don't know.
I've never looked at the logistics of being in a coma.
You're going to need like a nurse to take care of you.
Like, can you imagine how many new jobs be created just from having like
handle the the waste of people in a coma from that?
That might be a brilliant job.
Like, hey, I'm a weight loss shit technician.
Basically, I didn't let either one of them cook.
I'm not even in the kitchen right now.
I'm just saying that like Eric Cartman did this for a game console, didn't he?
You know what?
You want to know something about you, German, that maybe you haven't noticed
is every time I played with you in a group, you shut down everyone else's conversations.
Yeah, we're trying to talk about like shit in a coma.
Yeah.
And you're like, oh, I don't know.
Oh, scary.
You look out for that stir.
Look out.
That's my first one.
Oh, that's true.
It kind of did catch me off guard.
Man, so are you saying there's no like plausibility, like it's not plausible
that you could have a shitting like like profession, a shit handler?
Is that what you're saying?
I mean, are the realm of possibilities?
I feel like it could happen.
Anything is possible.
Check this out.
Check this out, boys.
I got a secret tunnel for you.
Come to come to Papa's secret tunnel.
Stand on the square.
Secret tunnel.
I'm not doing that.
It's going to be like a trap door.
Yeah, I've gone to Papa's secret tunnel before.
Come on.
Come on, dude.
Don't be weird.
Oh, there is actually stuff down here.
Jesus, we've made it this far together.
Is it worth it to do the pickaxe stuff?
I tried it and then I got annoyed when it took so long and I died to a interaction speed.
Change that in theory.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I can see.
You're doing great.
You're waxing with the longsword.
Look at this guy.
Oh, my God.
Look at the finesse.
I love this thing.
This thing's actually really fun.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
That was fun.
Diamond.
I'm going to let the record show that the next time the lights go off
and I'm fighting somebody, I'm just not even going to swing anymore.
Actually, I got two diamonds.
Holy shit.
Don't people do that at nursing homes?
In theory, yes.
But I'm saying like specifically like because you put more people in comas to lose weight,
right?
A lot of people need to lose weight or want to lose weight.
You're going to have a large amount of shit on your hands.
Literally.
Well, I'm typing there's just one guy who's the shit guy.
Yeah, I'm typing in the group chat, guys.
Why not me?
Oh, here we go.
Oh, goodness.
I forgot to wait.
Here we go.
There we go.
I forgot to put a question mark at the end of that.
But here we go.
Look, I'm sorry for everything.
No, no, no.
Kraken was asking of how many we had.
Dude, I'm sorry.
Be better.
Then be better.
Then prove it to me.
Be better.
He's trying to replace me right now.
Be better then.
OK, I'm sorry.
I didn't bring up the poop thing he did.
All right.
You got a jump crowd.
OK, OK.
To be fair.
Yeah, I totally brought it up.
Now, Sterk can't get kicked from the guild.
He's the leader of the guild as much as we want him out of here.
He's the one that put the kick power.
You can't escape.
Oh, oh, oh, this is the big room.
Let's go.
Oh, we're about to make some money today.
Wakey, wakey, eggs and bakey.
That move is so good.
The fear is long sword.
Whatever that like stun, whatever it is.
Does that work on players?
Oh, yeah.
No, I wish.
Oh, my God.
Can you imagine the carnage that would rain down upon these servers?
Do you know what would happen to these people?
It would be a stun and then a kill.
They wouldn't play anymore.
I got three diamonds.
Gamers, gamers, gamers, gamers.
No gamers.
Oh, Jesus.
Let's talk this through, boys.
Let's talk this through.
Come on.
I don't know if they're talking.
Have you seen the leaderboards?
I'm not up there, but I will be.
Shut up, Frank.
Like, play the game already.
Oh, my God, Clyde.
I'm doing my best.
It's just don't game with your little brothers.
Stop talking over me when I'm trying to communicate.
You killed my friend.
Okay.
Where are you going, Clumb Guzzler?
Calm down.
I got to get a fucking potion on.
Just like that toxic fucking shitty raid leader or something.
That's so stupid.
Where's the DPS at?
Live by the bit.
The guy hasn't hit a dagger shot.
Hit him.
Hit him once.
Once.
I dare you.
All right.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, did they both kill each other?
Did we?
I think you did.
No, I just killed him.
Look at the kill feed, boys.
Look at the kill feed.
I'll let you have it.
I got him.
Wow.
The kill feed said I got him.
Yeah, no.
Wait, no, it doesn't.
No, it doesn't.
No, it said I got him.
Yeah, no, it says I got him.
Yeah, I see.
I see it.
You're...
Yep.
For the guild.
All right.
Here's where we're going.
Can you get my sword back?
Yeah, I got you.
I got you.
Thanks.
Oh, my God.
This guy was...
Oh, my Lord.
Hold on.
Let me just double check.
That's a...
No, that's a chicken kit.
Sorry.
Live by the bit.
Oh, this is so bad.
I thought it was...
Oh, thank God.
Did I just throw out candies?
Yes, I did.
Ooh, long sword.
Oh, there it is.
I got a heal, though.
Oh, yeah.
This is going to be a little hairy here.
Are you good?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm used to hairy.
Oh, I got...
I had diamonds on me, too.
Oh, that's too late.
It was too fun.
All right.
You know what?
Let's do a gamer one this time.
Let's go for like a game.
Play the game.
We're going to go for gamer mode here.
Okay.
It's like weird that you're telling us
that that's what you're going for,
but we've been doing it.
Yeah, but that...
I mean, obviously, at the end there,
I literally turned around
and got hit in the back of the head and died.
Hey, can I delete my character?
Just make a new one.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah, can I be a ranger?
Oh my God, please be a ranger.
I have a purple bow
that I don't want to deal with selling.
If you just take it.
The daggers...
I like going invisible and being a creepo,
but I think it would be better to do solo.
You know, I'm just going to be the ranger guy.
Yeah.
No, dude, be our legless.
Okay.
Oh, is it?
Hold on.
My shop is updated.
Beautiful.
Short sword, another Zwiander.
You can just press class change.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, class change,
and then you can...
Yeah, you don't have to delete.
Yeah, you can make a brand new character.
Dude, this...
I think I'm going to get this
and then have this Zwiander.
Dude, I got to be honest,
the Zwiander is awful in corridors,
but I want you to pick
what's going to make you happy
because at the end of the day,
that's all that matters to me.
Well, so there's a...
There's a chest piece that's 61 armor.
It's cloth, though,
and it's two weapon damage,
max health, and spell casting,
which doesn't matter.
Right.
Or I could get...
No, that's 30.
Got bad rolls on it.
The long sword you had
had plus four physical damage
and 1.5 action speed.
This is kind of a god roll on a blue.
Yeah, I think...
You're going to keep it?
No, no, no, I can't even use it,
but I'm going to give it back to you.
This thing's nuts.
And you were rocking with it.
It's five...
Yeah, this thing would be amazing.
So this sword versus the purple I have.
This is plus two agility,
two resourcefulness,
a little bit of interaction speed,
and 53 damage.
What's the one that I have right now?
57, three will, max health, and item speed.
It's probably always just damage, isn't it?
For the variation on the Zweihander?
Yeah, like which...
So I have one as well right now.
Mine's weapon damage, 55,
plus two knowledge,
plus two weapon damage,
plus three move speed.
Spear is nice, too, people are saying.
Spear is a fantastic weapon.
I think you would really like Spear.
I don't have 30, though.
I only have 25.
Here, trade me.
I'll just give you the candy that I have.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Yeah, so go to...
Do you know how the trade channel works?
I don't.
Become a trader.
So go to...
Yeah, so go...
Yeah, you have to spend some gold.
Hopefully you have it.
Yeah, I got plenty.
So just become a trader.
Right.
Yep.
And go to Miss Trade 1.
I'm going to type in...
Okay.
100 subs to kill...
No, no, don't write that.
And then you're going to right click that and trade me.
It should say,
Oh.
All right, it's French.
Fucker.
Oh, yeah, you're the one with the French name, right?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, hey, I'm good.
Can you all invite Sir Dipey?
Then click the check mark.
It's like a RuneScape trade.
Double confirmed.
Wait, no, that's cancel.
Did you cancel it?
No.
Oh, beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
Long one.
Very cool.
All right, cool.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Of course.
So now I go to Merchant.
So the Spear.
This thing is really, really good.
Yeah, and I gave you the additional candy
because I want you to try the Spear.
It's not for everybody.
I will tell you that right now.
But you'd have to be a troglodyte not to use it effectively.
Whoa.
Okay, let me...
Whoa, dude.
Yeah, I got it.
I know, I know, I know.
Is that good?
Did I got it?
Yeah, I mean, I would run the Spear.
I would run it.
All right, let me put it on.
If you hate it, then it wasn't my idea.
All right, okay, this is...
I'm playing this one.
No, I'm not going to go over voice chat and be like,
it's me, now I say...
No, I'm not losing this.
I don't know, where is your voice chat key?
Because you didn't even move to avoid the attack.
Is it the plus and minus?
But what did you have to press to do that?
I wanted them to kill me.
I wanted this to be yelling at you
and they take the opportunity to kill me.
And then they have a story for the rest of their life.
That is so sweet of you.
I guess I'm just not content-minded.
I'm too smooth-brained for that.
What's your new player name?
You put it in Discord, Sir Dipey.
Nice.
Why?
But oh, that's your actual name.
What are you on that tonight for?
I'm on that always.
Dipey has been one of my new favorite words.
Foraging for food, pretty good.
Is that a perk?
I run the Sharpshooter.
I run the headshot one for my first one.
You get like three heals.
No, not the perks, the skills.
It's a heal.
You got skills.
Yeah, heal 25 when you forage for food.
Goated, goated, goated.
Do not take that off.
So let me go into...
I also am bringing you an Arming Sword and a Shortsword.
I'm bringing you a Shortsword.
So I guess you can't even buy anything.
You're a brand new character.
I'm brand new.
Should I just buy...
If I'm going to have the spear on,
should I buy anything like armor?
Are we just going to go for it?
You said this was a real gamer one.
Yeah, so in theory, if you're going to run...
Because like barbs can get away with being lazy
and just having a weapon.
You cannot.
You need a kit.
But then again, armor slows you down.
So if you want to run faster,
you might want like a leather kind of thing
or like a padded situation.
I like to take...
Yeah, I want to be able to take some hits.
I'll get a few things.
So what I would say is I would check like and just...
If you have any greens in the shop,
definitely go for that first.
But just make sure the attributes make sense.
And if not, then don't worry about it, honestly.
And I can check my shop, too.
Just magic resistance, interaction speed, armor,
headshot protection.
Oh, Vinny, thanks for the raid.
I just saw Vinesauce.
Thanks, Vinny.
Thanks for playing earlier, too.
Yo, Vinster.
Thank you, Vinny.
Welcome, everybody.
We're just kind of playing the game.
Okay, well, I'll find other stuff, too.
I was 10 minutes late.
All right, I actually...
Let's actually try to win this one.
Like, because I got to...
I don't want to lose this thing.
Where's SirDykeB's shirt?
That's what I'm wondering.
Should I put a shirt on?
I mean, it's...
I just wondered where it went.
I mean, when you got a body like this.
Facts.
I'm ready.
All right.
That's my body.
My body is ready now.
All right.
Let's call it out of here.
Let's go.
Ready up, SirDykeB.
Aren't you, like, not ready?
I was waiting for you to be ready.
Oh, I got...
Oh, my God.
I got the best thing for you.
Don't mess this up for me.
I'm living...
The Ranger portrait doesn't look like
he's drawing an arrow.
It looks like he's sniffing something.
There you go.
Facts.
True.
This man's spitting.
Here, Magona for a smoke.
All right.
Let's...
Clear comms.
Let's play.
Yep.
Here you go.
Take this.
This is for you.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
Yep.
Take that.
Why did I just hear myself?
That was weird.
I think you did voice chat.
Thank you.
Oh, I did voice chat,
and it's probably using...
What?
My whole ass different...
Hold on.
Your desktop audio is coming through.
That is so funny.
You listed it as your input device.
That's brilliant.
That's such a...
His whole ass.
Do that if you can stealth at all times.
Well, I don't think there's a way to change
your audio channel.
Wait, there is.
You'd have to go to...
Maybe default in Windows first.
I can't.
Yikes.
I guess we're gonna have to be super gamers.
This thing's fun.
Let me make sure.
You feel the power now?
You feel the power of the perp?
Yeah.
This room is kind of awful, but...
It's literally the worst.
There's a bunch of skeeters here.
I don't like mosquitoes on by you, but...
Oh, he's just turning around.
Yeah.
Really think of the rain.
Appreciate that.
Yeah, what's the range?
Oh, my God.
She's got some range on her.
Hold on.
Watch out.
Watching.
How far is it?
Close, close, close.
Oh, that's...
That is actually pretty far.
Damn.
Oh, yeah.
We can.
Yes.
Okay.
We can also hear ourself again, too.
Could you?
Wait, really?
Yeah.
I heard you coming through him.
No, he talked.
I talked as well.
Oh, you talked.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, that is a trap.
Yeah.
That's a trap room.
And you have to pick pocket to get that.
So don't even bother.
But kill these guys.
These guys usually have pendants.
Oh, my God.
It came from...
What the...
Oh, you just hit me.
Do I have to re...
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Don't die, don't die.
Dude.
This is a real gamer one, dude.
I don't...
I think you hit me with your axe.
I think I did.
I didn't.
I think it...
No, it was me.
It's my fault.
I fired one arrow and it is inside this skull.
But good news is you have second wind
and we also get a campfire from the ranger.
So everything's fine.
I didn't do anything wrong.
No, no.
We're good, we're good.
No, we're good.
We're good.
Do any of you guys have...
Oh, wait.
There's a health thing over here.
Sorry.
Oh, shit.
Where you're crouching and it wants you to press F to interact.
We can't do both.
Hold on.
German, no!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Skelly.
Where did he come from?
Where does...
All right.
Can we kill this?
Yeah, we can kill it.
We can kill it.
But don't die.
We can kill if you don't die.
Does that make sense?
I think that makes sense.
I've run the numbers.
If you don't die, we can kill it.
Oh, my God.
I have my fear again in a second.
That's a lot of enemies, friends.
I don't really know how my character works yet.
Okay, hold on.
I'm fearing them away.
Take this time to run.
I'm dead.
Oh, my God.
I died.
Oh, I actually died.
I don't know what I was doing.
I don't know why I did that.
I thought...
Because you said you feared him.
I was like, okay, they feared.
I can take this and run.
Oh, my God.
This is the worst day ever.
No, that's bad.
That's really bad.
I thought I had time.
That's the champion man.
That's the problem.
Oh, no.
Start shooting the champion with the arrows.
The bow.
I am.
I don't want to hit you because Jerma is going to say that I hit him.
No, I understand.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Everyone relax.
Good comms.
Team comms.
I just thought...
I thought that everybody was feared over there
and I was like, I have two or three seconds.
I get it.
He's on me.
I'm going to walk up here and I'm going to lay a trap.
And then what I'm going to do is I'm going to swing on his ass.
Come here, baby.
Are we going to get Jerma's ass here?
Oh, Jesus.
This is a bad run.
This is not a good run.
This is a very bad one.
Okay, you know how...
All right.
Do you know how...
That's a real gamer one.
Do you know how shit just like falls apart
and you kind of just don't even know how or why?
I don't even know what happened.
It just fell apart so quickly.
It was just abrupt chaos that we just couldn't fucking solve.
Once it started going, it just wouldn't stop, man.
It's just like, oh, there's a heal over there.
Oh, it's okay.
We have like five aggroed and there's 10.
I think I can get this heal off and then it's just over.
The whole thing just falls apart and I got...
It's okay.
I still got this way under.
You caused that?
No, what caused it was the big champion skeleton existed
and we didn't all just run away at the same time.
The guild is fucking falling apart.
I hate this guild.
I'm going to go get water because you guys are going to like
re-ready your characters for another 20 minutes.
Can you tell me who the fuck you're working for, Jerma?
Who hired you to ruin my barb legacy?
Oh, you don't have any subs I got for that one.
You don't have any idea?
Zero.
I still have five purple holes.
Let's go.
Okay, actually I do need to pee.
I don't want to get some water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At least it was funny.
No, no, it's fucking hilarious.
It was all my fault.
Do I take the L on this one?
I would say I didn't come that there was a skelly champion
coming soon enough for you.
I didn't recognize that he was aggroed on you.
I thought he was on me and I will take the blame initially.
After that, everything was you.
Respect.
Oh, it was fun though.
That's all that matters.
No, I had a great time.
It was fucking hilarious.
Yeah, I demoted you in the guild hall.
That's fine.
You don't have access to guild stash anymore, man.
I already cleaned the bank out before you did that.
Look at all this.
I mean, you're still in the guild.
Take a look at all this.
A WoW guild?
Okay, yeah, I'll bear it back.
I gotta pee.
Beer pee.
Hello?
Anybody there?
How are we?
Hello, hello, hello.
All right.
Well, that was good.
That was a decent warm up round.
Yeah, I think we're the guild now.
How are you guys doing on time?
I will be playing this until 5 a.m.
I kid you not.
What about Mr. Stirr?
I think he's...
Let's go.
Honest to goodness, let's play.
Okay.
Stirr, how are you on time?
Are you good for a little bit longer?
I'd say I got like a week left before the worms take me.
Well, I mean tonight.
Oh, I don't know.
Okay.
I'm in it till I'm not.
Honest to goodness.
Now, I might make a suggestion.
I can keep on going, Barb, if you'd like.
I can also play cleric.
If you guys wanted to get some more action,
a little bit more blood on your swords and whatnot.
I would like to be a ranger behind your big axe though.
No, I understand.
I'll keep axing.
Because otherwise our frontliner is the guy
who like comedically turns around to talk to us.
And I can't trust that.
Yeah, but that's...
It's funny though.
One time.
But like my life depends on it.
Understandable.
Get in there with your big axe.
Hey, let me get 50 subs to stab my friend
I'm streaming with in the head till he dies.
Dude, like...
But it's me.
You started it.
It's me.
That's the comedy one.
I didn't start that.
There was someone asking for 100 who wasn't me first.
That's true.
That's very true.
Again, a lot of this isn't actually me.
You just capitalized on it.
All right, you guys ready?
Yeah.
Fuck the communists.
All right, let's go.
That's what I've always said.
Exactly.
Honest to goodness.
Let's go.
Dude, are you still mad, dude?
You still suck at it, bro.
Everybody in this lot...
You don't even have time to talk shit.
Yeah, usually I tell them I'm going to kill everybody
and then I didn't do that today.
So this might be a scuffed run.
I think we're going to be fine.
I like your way of thinking.
Beware of interlopers.
Honest to goodness, we're going to be fine.
All right, I'm the commanding officer on this mission.
Leave the fucking lights on so I can hitch...
Oh, wait, you have no reason to turn off lights now.
Thank the fucking Lord.
If I see a light go off, dude, I'm going to know.
He's going to lose it.
Praise Jesus.
It's the arrows bigger than the thing.
This...
Wait, wait, I have people already.
Bro, there are players immediately.
There are players immediately.
Oh, typey.
Oh, good, good, good, good, good.
Hey, hey, hey.
Your friend's dead.
Just come here, just come here.
The run's over, dude.
The run's over, bro.
The run's over.
Don't listen to him.
You should be fighting to the very end.
Like, that's exactly...
Good on you, seriously.
What?
Jeremy, you caused this.
I didn't do anything.
Exactly what I was talking about.
You deserve it.
He hit me through the fucking fence.
He hit me through the...
He stabbed me through the fucking...
I like...
I don't know how my character works yet.
I still have so many questions.
You got...
This is a government operation.
Dude, you got obliterated, by the way.
You turned to look and see down the hall,
and three arrows instantly killed you.
Yeah, I know.
Wait, wait.
All right, all right.
What's your skill?
What's your other skill?
It needs to be the quick shot, the try shot.
Yeah, I got quick shot.
I just want to know if I have to get my arrows back
and how many I have.
No, no, no.
You just reload.
You have unlimited arrows.
Okay.
And if you hit...
If you just hit head...
Honest to goodness, can we ready up?
No, I can't run.
The bar doesn't make sense without a different weapon.
So I can actually equip and then I have to get healing.
Otherwise, I die.
All right.
Okay.
I have a solution.
Turning off voice chat so I don't have the temptation
to be like, hey, let me talk to you
and let's have like a funny thing.
No, you can talk to them.
No, no, talk to them, talk to them, talk to them.
No.
We should do...
That way I can laugh while I'm dying.
Because I'm dying anyway.
We should mute Discord and only talk in game.
Oh, that's brilliant.
No.
I want to role play around.
Fine, let's role play.
You want to role play around?
Role play around.
Okay.
See you guys later.
All right, they're muted.
Okay.
I've got to figure out the right voice for this.
Oh, I thought...
The thing is, I think...
That's a good one.
Well, I believe.
I think that's an idea for me.
I think I'm going to go with this.
Sounds about right to me.
Okay.
Why can't I hear anyone talking?
Oh, I'd like to see you try.
Why is nobody talking?
Nobody's talking.
Hello.
Oh, good thing I can hear you now.
Greetings for our first adventure.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
I am speaking.
Hello, wizard.
Watch out for the wizards.
Great, let's speak.
Spiders.
We have to take out the jaw.
Yeah, the jaw in the corner is the way to stop the spider.
Be careful behind you.
Scythe is full.
Oh, very interesting.
I'm glad you've told us that.
More than five times today.
They're speaking at the braemers.
Ah, I can't hear you.
Your helmet muffles your voice.
Are we ready to continue down this hallway, please?
Listen to me, boys.
Boys, listen.
Oh, why do I sound so smart?
There's exquisitely leaves over here in the library.
Come here, come here.
Oh, the library, yes.
Plenty of books.
I remember reading this one.
That's a good one.
This is an encyclopedia of all the dragons that are in this world.
Have you read it?
The dragon, despite my upbringing, I can't read.
Those are made.
We must go to fight to loot.
Made here.
Nice, nice.
Excellent.
Below me.
Below.
Crystal sword here.
It was top drawer, if I must say.
I'm going to go over here.
I'm going to get the spider into loafers, you say.
I need to get rid of this.
So, Diope, what are you talking about?
Make sure you get the jewels.
Turn oblivion music on.
Okay.
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck?
My God, why was it like that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness.
Sorry, a very loud thing happened.
Why is it so loud?
I don't get it.
Demons of the mind.
Look at his eyes.
There's not much behind me.
All right, gentlemen, I'm ready.
I'm a female.
Yes, I am ready.
Onwards.
Bass, get your wits about you.
I'm very on.
Various challenges.
All right.
Are we ready to take off?
And demons.
Here we go.
Let's go.
This way, follow me.
This is a room, squiz of treasures.
Long ago, this exact cave.
It was filled with treasures, laughter, music, family.
I've been here before.
Yes, many times.
This is my home.
I've been here recently.
Very recently.
But now, ever since the dragon fire, it's all but nothing.
Footsteps in the distance.
The dark sounds upon the cement.
I don't know what could be in these halls,
but prepare for anything.
Wait a minute.
Alas, a room full of treasures.
Oh, yes.
I just remembered.
What is it?
I left my oven on.
There be an archer.
Watch out.
It'll get you outside.
What have they done to my father's old study?
These absolute disgusting zombies,
and probably too dangerous in here now.
Me, don't get too close.
It's a diaphe.
You had a-
I have remembered ovens weren't invented yet.
That's correct.
I don't know why you're saying these things this way.
Long ago, my father created a series of traps
to protect this very room and these very halls
from interlopers like us.
It's ironic considering that we're trying to-
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm sorry.
What were we thinking coming in here without shoes?
Yes, it's very strange.
I have shoes.
It's like men being unprepared.
We have shoes right here.
If you want shoes,
I want to feel the cold stone on my bare feet.
Curious.
Very curious indeed.
Trying to get to my old room.
Unfortunately, it's been destroyed.
You know, did you live here?
I did.
Many years ago.
Skeleton.
We reanimated undead.
Surprise it.
Shoot his face.
I live in dreams.
Oh, my neck.
Oh, that hurt.
Attack, please.
Never mind.
We're not going down there.
It's a diapoe.
It's very scary coming down these halls once again.
What's happening?
Adventure, a friend.
What are you doing?
Stop, stop, stop.
Do you have a history in these halls as well?
I must know if there are other people here.
My family depends on it.
Wizard.
Oh, another one lost to the dungeon.
Where did that wizard go?
There was a wizard here,
and he might have the secrets of my family.
It could even be somebody from my family.
We must know.
We must find...
Hello?
Wizard, it's all right.
He's a blacksmith.
He built this entire castle with his bare hands.
I don't want to...
He was paid very well.
Fortunately, he didn't make it through the war.
The war, he did not make it through the war.
Have you seen our friends today?
Do you know where he is?
Adventurer, do you have business in these halls?
I am looking for an exit.
Perhaps there will be an exit for all of us.
There will be, potentially.
How did you get in?
What's your name?
What is your name, Traveller?
The butler let me in.
You see, I work here,
but I've came through a lot on my way out.
Another adventurer, please.
Let us all come together
and discuss what's happening here.
I'm trying to find my family's secrets.
There was an accident.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
A blue portal has arrived.
All right.
If there are any interlopers here in my family's castle,
just be aware I am not going to go down so easily.
My father built this tunnel,
built these halls with his bare hands.
Just so you know,
I am ready to fight for my family
and for what they have built
and what they have done.
Do you understand?
Are you friend or are you foe?
He's a friend.
Let him be.
Look into the fire and tell me what your name is.
Stop.
You violated the law.
Pay the penalty or rot in prison, scum.
Stop.
Oh, shit.
What do I do?
There's no adventurers to talk to.
There's no players to interact with.
What happens when an NPC has no-
Me.
Can you hear me?
It is me, Kongraza.
Why can I still hear you?
And why did you say your name correctly
instead of the French way?
Sorry for what you had to see.
Why can I hear you?
Just know that I will always love you.
I'm always with you.
Mitch, you didn't get any of those hot hits on me
because you suck.
Is there anyone left?
Please tell me there's someone left.
Someone.
A final adventurer, perhaps.
A final adventurer to talk to me
and give me one final quest before I die.
Please.
Give an old man something.
I made it.
I didn't make it.
How did I-
Don't you tell me you just died in the darkness.
I was trying-
I was hoping somebody was-
I was hoping somebody was going to show up and be like-
Because there was two people left.
I can hear you through it.
There's a lot of audio jungle.
Is it better?
Also, your mic, it might be like a webcam mic or something.
I could not understand a word that QuamCuzzler was saying.
I couldn't either.
I heard like-
Like something about like hot pockets in it.
You didn't say hot pockets once.
You didn't say hot pockets?
Who said they were eating a hot pocket?
Bro, I was-
I literally-
I roleplayed and I forgot that I was a girl in the game
and I just was like midway through.
I just formed a romantic relationship with you and you're-
At no point did I say hot pockets.
Your microphone was-
It was so funny because it was-
The people that we were interacting with,
I don't think I could hear what you were saying.
So you were just kind of like-
And I'm just like, adventure, please.
This RP brought you-
Wow.
Oh, I lost a good sword, I think.
Oh, whatever.
The game is over in three days.
Let me-
But at the end there, was there somebody left?
There was one person left at the very end.
Was I?
Yeah.
It said there were two.
It was like two slots.
So were people potentially just spectating me walking around?
Like having like a sad NPC ending?
Probably.
I mean, that's a great way to go out, I'd say.
I mean, that was the circle.
There was no one else there.
All right, let me know if this is better now.
Is my in-game audio better now?
I don't hear it in-game.
Oh, that's amazing.
All right, I have proposition.
But sometimes I hear Jerma through your mic.
It also looks like my thing is active, but mine isn't active.
Also, I've been trying to get an answer to this question for a while,
but I keep forgetting.
When I'm crouching and I'm trying to interact pressing F on something
to like pick up an item, it won't work.
I have to stand up to pick up an item.
I have never heard of that for anybody else.
Yeah, that's weird.
It's a little buggy, though.
Sometimes, I don't know if it's happening to you guys, too,
but sometimes I will like click to swing and nothing happens.
Yeah, there's also like an auto swing problem that people have.
There's, you know, we don't talk about them.
Okay, it's okay.
It's all right.
It happens, yeah.
It's just some strange things.
Shift makes you unable to interact sometimes, apparently.
Yeah, wait, are you?
Yeah, your crouch is bound to control, correct?
Left control?
Mine is left control.
Left shift.
Well, there you go.
Yeah, to get it off shift,
you're probably double bound.
The game's probably not recognizing
that you're double bound and not changing that for you.
My jump button is also right click,
so when I'm in the game transferring items over to my inventory,
I jump every time I transfer an item.
Sir, you've been using the like tribes ascend control scheme,
haven't you, for like the last 10 years?
Yeah, I'm a mouse to jumper.
That's actually like kind of efficient, but also what's wrong with you?
I mean, I like it, and I enjoy it,
and it doesn't work in a lot of games.
I feel like I've done mouse wheel jump,
but I've never done right click.
I mean, that's you do you, man.
All right, let's get it.
I feel like it's been an hour since we've played the video game.
All right, you guys ready?
I'm trying, but I'm mostly just sitting in this lobby
waiting for you guys to ready.
That's been my experience.
I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
No, you need to hurry up.
Get your ass in the game.
All right, first of all.
This is the one.
Most of this has been me getting here for you guys.
Hello, friend.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Is my audio?
Never.
That's never enough.
I just turned off in game.
It was being really weird,
and I kept hearing Jerma talk through like your mic.
That's very strange.
I thought I just turned it off, too.
That's weird.
Yeah, I know.
I can't hear anything.
All right, yours are actually bleeding.
Gamer time.
Wait, does that give you that little notification
that I'm muting and unmuting?
Oh, okay, good.
I thought when you said bleeding, I muted and unmuted.
Rapier for you, Sir DiPy.
So you have a melee in between.
Otherwise, it's really annoying.
Also, take this.
It is.
I know.
I played Ranger.
I took your battle axe as well.
Yep.
I don't know if you can use that, but have fun.
I murdered your toys this way.
Oh, thanks for the shoes,
because my feet really were getting super dirty
walking around down here.
I want to keep those dogs clean.
All right.
This is loud, too.
I'm going to shoot.
That hit you.
What is?
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
What the fuck is going on here?
The Rangers are nuts.
No, no, no.
I thought that was you behind me.
That was weird.
Ow.
Do you want me to be behind you?
I can get there.
Oh, Jesus.
Be careful.
I thought you were behind me.
No, I was told to be in front,
which I'm probably going to get shot in the back of the head,
but I'm ready for it.
I am.
I'm a gamer.
I won't do that.
I can tell from the right click mouse button jump thing,
whatever that is.
Yeah, that was what truly identifies me as a gamer.
Nice.
He's gaming.
This bat's in here.
Why are the lights off?
Explain this to me.
I have a shitty room.
Interact speed.
All right, all right.
This room is rough because there's a wraith here
and I have a shitty weapon for this.
So we're going to turn around.
Executive decision, I'm sorry.
No, that room is actually a hell.
Worth it.
Yeah.
Like, if you have a cleric, it's fine.
But oh, fun thing, if you guys want to try it,
you can do a brewmaster cleric
and you can drink beer to give you
plus like 11 strength for 15 seconds.
And you can literally just bite you with your fist
and actually down them.
You don't get drunk from it, right?
Yep.
It's a lot of fun.
All right, I got friends up here.
Let's go.
Oh, nice doc.
Thanks, dude.
Oh, hey, man, there's some sick loot on there for you.
There it was.
It was a lot of money.
Oh, great work.
I have a buckler over here if you want.
If you're into that sort of thing.
What's the difference between longbow shortbow?
Any significant thing I should be aware of?
So the recurve bow, I know you can fire faster.
How many arrows do you have on the recurve?
Is it six or five or six?
Yeah, so I think a longbow, you get five,
but it's like 40 damage, usually 30 to 40 damage.
It do be looking like a lot of damage.
Stirrer, you're going to want this on the ground right now.
That's an unbelievably good bow.
Is it a survival bow?
Please don't be a survival bow.
It's a blue.
Where?
Yeah, but if it's a blue survival bow,
it's just actually to tease.
Put it on the ground?
Oh, no.
Oh, boys, this might be one of the...
Wait, hopefully it's in the...
Oh, no.
What happened?
It might be in the texture.
See how there's the actual barrier.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, thank God.
I got it.
Yeah, there's a little piece sticking out.
There you go.
Oh, this is perfect.
Oh, bless the heavens.
We're gaming again.
I think it should be really good.
That's more damage than the longbow.
Yeah.
I think some bows have different amount of arrows too, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So anyways, longbow can obviously shoot longer.
It's a bigger bow and then that'll shoot quicker.
Recurves are really good.
This is just the same shitty room.
Yeah, this is literally the same room.
We can run through it.
It's just...
I have my fear up.
It's just risky-ish, but...
I mean, we don't really have...
We'd have to run all the way around.
Yeah, we can do this.
We're gamers.
Yeah, you can shoot through that hole if you're space back.
Like, you can shoot them if you step back.
Beautiful.
Oh, you can.
Excellent technique.
Yep.
Yeah, I mean, you can also use...
It's not high enough to shoot.
Here, let me turn this off for you.
Oh, so much better.
I was worried.
All right, boys, just run with me, please.
This way.
Doesn't mean shoot.
Ow!
He's aggroing enemies on purpose.
He's griefing us.
Does it matter if I shoot him?
No, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
It was all in jest, my friend.
I didn't like that joke.
That joke was hurtful.
Good.
It means it was funny.
This is supposed to be a gamer run, not an argument run.
We've had plenty of those.
Please, guys.
Now, I'm going to eat my snack.
Oh, this guy was shot with arrows.
Boys, look at this.
Look at this.
We're going to do our Witcher 3 Geralt of Orivia inspection.
Arrows to the body.
Somebody shot him.
That's all I got for you.
Those were my arrows.
Geralt, those were my arrows.
I was trying.
I thought he was on the ground pretending to be dead.
So I was doing it.
I'm a little upset.
My Witcher senses have failed me.
Don't move.
Don't you move a shoe.
Listening.
All right, we're good.
Follow me.
Spiders.
There's a lever right here.
Let's get in this room.
Oh, that's where those spiders are.
I'm coming.
All right, we got to go.
We got to get circling south.
Speed.
Oh, my goodness.
I don't know what this means, but this is cool looking.
Stir.
If only we had a lockpick.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to start being a lockpick guy.
Oh, my God.
I've never seen one of these.
We're about to get cuddled by the circle if we don't get out of here.
Shit.
Let's go.
Let's go, dude.
I wonder what's in there.
I'm out.
Bye-bye.
It's probably all kinds of jewels and gems.
I want to be just a green.
Yeah, that's possible.
Friends.
Hello, friends.
Hello.
This is a gamer run.
We play.
I know.
I was going to.
It was metagaming.
OK.
Hold on.
I'm in the secret passage.
I was going for a deception check.
This old castle.
Just want to make sure everyone's aware.
I just killed them both.
You monster.
I love it.
Look what you become.
I'll take credit for that.
Thank you.
My goodness.
They love us.
Ooh, is that better?
28.
Yeah.
I'm in space.
Oh, here.
Take this trap if you want.
Because you're a ranger now.
You can use those.
Oh, my God.
Throwing axes are so good.
Do you mind if I take this potion, my friend?
No, please do it.
Oh, thank you.
So so coined.
Do you want these throwing axes?
Oh, dude, I yes.
Because I have like a shitload of them.
I love these things.
I also love the oil lanterns.
Thank you.
Oh, God bless.
They're 30 damage a pop.
But they're just actually not an exit.
There is an exit.
Boys, I have a feeling there's...
Wait, hold on.
Let me just kill feed.
Oh, there's friends ahead, friends ahead.
All right.
This is a gamer run, remember?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stop.
In the name of the law.
This is a gamer run.
I'm just going to leave.
They ran.
Oh, yeah.
They're certified runners.
Oh, my God.
They're so dead.
Stop.
This is a gamer run.
They're like, OK.
And what does that mean?
Watch me throwing axe skills.
Watch this.
Is this gas?
Hail Mary.
Oh, so close.
There's a lot of shit in there.
I don't know if we fight in here.
It's fine.
You'll be all right.
There's a lot of people in here.
What the heck?
Ster, where are you?
Wait, you left.
Oh, Sterg left.
I went home.
Oh, shit.
I mean, he was gaming.
He was gaming.
Yeah, you were.
You guys ran off.
I was looting like a secret room.
And then you guys just kept going.
I'm out of here.
I'm sorry.
You're on your own.
No, you're good.
I'm medicated.
Oh, he put the worms on you.
Yeah, I'm out of here.
I have a lot of stuff.
Oh, yes.
OK, goodbye.
Oh, bastard.
You're in a predicament down here.
Was that?
Yeah, there was so many things in that room.
I kind of abandoned you, but I'm sorry.
But I did.
You're fine.
Gamers gamers don't have feelings.
I'm actually offended.
You're apologizing right now.
Well, in that case, um, you.
Yeah.
Well, thank you.
Now I feel better.
I think you are.
Are you going for a battle here?
Because you got a lot of potential.
I think there's somebody in that room.
Well, they have to come to me.
That's the beautiful thing about this run.
I was drinking out of drinking of water
and I just like scared the shit out of me.
Trevor, there's someone in your room.
Get out.
If they're dumb, they're going to come through.
I really hope they do.
Well, what if they just run right in?
Well, if they go around, at least
and then I get the swing on them first.
This is what gaming looks like, boys.
Ah, too bad.
I was kind of hoping somebody was just going to run in.
Okay, cool.
That should be a lot of money.
Do you instantly sell or you just put it in your stash?
Uh, I sell pretty much everything
unless it's something that's valuable.
Yeah, I'm afraid to.
I might get yelled at, so I'm already ready.
Uh, yeah, I'm going to start yelling in a second.
Just take the second.
Hold on.
Oh my God, this guy.
It just takes a second.
Mm hmm. Sure it does.
Look at that.
I'm going to fill the whole thing up.
I got an oil lamp.
Is that irrelevant?
So it's basically just a molly.
You right click and you throw it like a molly.
Oh, I assumed it was like a.
It actually is a light source.
So if you if you left click, it's a light source.
Do you know what I want to do?
I'm going to be such a.
I'm going to be such a fucking weirdo.
But like the last day of the beta,
I'm going to fill my entire inventory with 10 gold stacks
and just and just be a loot goblin and just die for somebody.
And they'll they're going to look at me and take my gear and go.
You know what I mean?
Really fill every single slot.
What are you, Mr. Beast?
Like what?
Like to make somebody's day for no reason?
Yeah, like, I don't know.
Because if that happened.
I hate that.
Why?
I'd rather have worms.
Why it's OK.
If I were to if you killed.
All right.
If you killed somebody with an axe in this game.
And you looted them and their whole inventory was a stack of gold.
You don't think you would chuckle and be like, what the fuck are you doing, man?
I thought you were going to like run around and like leave a trail.
That'd be even better.
Yeah, like when I get hit, like drop five and keep running.
Yeah, just fill my inventory with potions and like surgical kits
and just run around and every time I get hit, just drop five stacks and just keep going.
I mean, you play Borderlands, right?
A little bit, yeah.
Like there's the loot goblins that like you shoot and they just drop.
They just drop gear as you shoot that pretty much.
Sonic.
Same concept.
What in the world?
It was actually pretty good singing.
That's pretty good.
All right, guys, stick together.
Keep your wits about you.
We all might make it out alive.
I mean, we split up.
We still made it because we're committing to being video game players now.
You guys walk through like four rooms of unopened chests that was just opening boxes.
And then I turned to look where you were and you were like the other side of the map.
I was like, OK, bye.
Well, I prioritize getting kills, getting frags.
You know, I don't need that.
You know, getting money is for plebs at this point.
I'm I'm already rich.
Well, unless you want to do your money loot goblin video that I'm doing.
True.
That's that's it.
Did you get hit by that?
Oh, boys, I got I got boys on me looking for a fight already.
Yeah.
I mean, in theory, we want to let them live a little longer so we can loot them later.
But I like killing them now.
Kind of kind of a wild one.
Oh, he made the jump.
He's kind of nuts.
That's crazy.
Don't mess with that guy.
He's good.
What the fuck?
Oh, I killed one.
Yeah.
Beautiful.
Well done, sir.
Yeah, same.
Where are you, sir?
I don't.
Where did you guys go?
You're dead.
I was in the starting room killing the enemies that were around and picking things up.
Should I stop picking things up and playing the core loop of the game?
Are we done with that?
No, he just saw he had bloodlust.
He just ran after a bunch of people.
OK, I don't know.
A guy landed on me.
I'm dead.
The guy made no footsteps and just appeared on me and then I died.
So I got to fuck this guy up real quick.
Please hold.
Oh, wait, you're alive.
I thought they killed you.
Oh, yeah.
No, no, I'm not.
I'm realizing who I'm watching right now.
So you just left me to die.
OK, these traps suck.
Holy shit.
All right.
I just OK, that was weird.
Gamer versus gamer.
If you smarty won't go through.
I almost got his head.
That's close.
But anyways, you know, I usually go for player kills immediately
because you obviously, if you kill them, you get the best loot
because they come in kidded most of the times.
So if you can just get a good kill on them as a barb, you get the loot,
which means we all got loot.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Well, you also level up.
You level quick too, right?
If you kill a player, it's not worth a lot.
Yeah, 100%.
We have like our three actual classes that we have been accidentally RPing as the whole time.
You're like the bloodlust barbarian and that's what you're doing.
Stir is like the tinkerer that wants to collect the loot and the toys.
I thought you were playing the game.
And I'm like the I'm like the fucking stand up comedian
that just walks around and yells at people and dies.
Yeah, I mean, make no mistake about it.
I'm actually a troglodyte.
Stir wants to live more than two minutes.
The bard, the jester, you're the loot goblin.
What class is the stand?
Oh, yeah, you're the you're the you're the barbarian.
You are the tinkerer thief and I'm the stand up comedian.
They need to add instruments to this game.
I think they're I think the conversation was adding bards and either
warlocks or necromancers to the game.
Did they actually have plans on adding more classes?
Yeah, no, I mean, they have they have completely
been transparent on this is Dungeons and Dragons multiplayer.
Really?
Which is going to be interesting with the new Wizards of the Coast decisions.
Well, I look any content is cool.
I mean, I think the game is pretty close to this right now.
Yeah, 100%.
Yeah, the game is just the demo is free.
Some people have been asking about it.
You can just play it right now during the Steam demo week, whatever.
Yeah, I had a wild thought and maybe I'm getting ahead of myself, but hear me out.
Imagine this game with a forge system like Halo Forge,
where they make the dungeons and you have to traverse player made dungeons.
Interesting.
Like a Mario maker thing.
It's like just these nuts dungeons.
I'd love more PvE.
PvE I think in this game could be really, really awesome.
Yeah, any more PvE would be great.
Because it doesn't spoon feed you in terms of combat.
It's more like it's more like a fuck you.
Good luck.
Yeah, let's see what they do.
I mean, it's been pretty fun so far, so.
Yes.
All right, Fearing.
I think the Elder Scrolls does that, the PvE part.
There are so fucking many of these things.
Yeah, make sure you loot every single one of these when you kill them.
Nice job, by the way.
This guy's a game.
Fuck.
Game.
Oh, lockpick here.
Here, you have the highest resource for this.
I think your lockpick chances are better.
Oh, wait, don't don't drop any items on the pyramid that can get stuck in the textures,
the elevated textures.
Yeah.
Yeah, like how that like how that short bow we couldn't remember.
Anyways, look at this little flashlight.
Oh, this one was red.
Yep, the red ones are like the they're the elite version of the death skulls.
But here, take I'm going to drop.
I'm going to put this on the body of something and you can use that to on the
the chest up here.
Mr. Ranger man.
I'll put it in here.
Oh, wait.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm so locked in chest.
You smarter than me.
I take lockpick.
I go take lockpick lock.
You use, you know, minigame of lockpick.
It's very quick, by the way.
It's not like slow.
OK, well, if your character's dumb, it's harder.
I that was like a jump scare and I was supposed to click.
It's very I couldn't even warn you because me saying it was fast.
It's like, OK, how fast?
And it's it's unbelievably fast.
So yeah.
I mean, you like the human benchmark test fast.
And what button does it?
It's left click.
It's really annoying.
OK, I thought so.
My chat was telling me random buttons.
Well, good.
I mean, well, you do have weird vines potentially.
Your left click is probably like a foot pedal.
Yeah, it is.
I don't know how you knew that.
That's weird.
All right.
Yeah, the lockpicking is actually very hard.
It's not simple.
Yeah, I thought it was going to be a whole menu, not like a jump scare.
It's over.
Well, I was envisioned like Splinter Cell Chaos Theory lockpicking
and I was very wrong when I got to do it the first time.
Well done, boys.
Well done.
I'll hit them for good measure.
Teamwork, baby.
We did it.
That's what it's all about.
I saw your you took your pants off.
I saw you.
You didn't see anything.
Stop.
Oh, there's a lockpick.
Do you want someone to try it again?
Are you decent at this dirty?
Want to try it again?
I would like to try.
I don't have any more lockpicks.
There's one right here.
I'm going to I'm going to fully acknowledge that I'm trash at them.
And again, my my character is actually dumb.
Also, I have a rapier for you.
If you need my friend, stir, come on.
Oh, I can.
I'll just give you it on the ground.
Can I hold on?
I'm putting I'm putting 40 arrows in this guy's head real quick.
And some of them are going through.
They're all come out.
Oh, geez.
Oh, my.
Oh, my Lord.
Oh, my God.
All right.
No guy.
For one second, I thought there was somebody in the discord call.
I was like somebody like in somebody's background coughing.
All right.
Stir lockpick.
Let's try it.
And then sort of a melee if you need it.
Okay.
No, I'll take that sword fire.
There's it.
Does it really?
No.
Yeah.
I was I was like, I've been I've been like wondering if there's like a way to clear that forever now.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Do I have to hit like the red part or just the yellow parts?
Yellow parts, I believe.
We're not mistaken within the yellows.
I missed it by like a tiny little bit.
It's so hard.
It's awful.
So what does anything slow that down?
Does resource want to slow that down?
I'm I'm I'm not positive, but I'm pretty close to positive.
I'm not like I've been told that it does by a respected source.
Okay.
Oh, I got I got a friend tango on me, tango on me.
There's people back.
No, but you do not want this dude.
I'm telling you right now in the room we just came from.
There's a guy as well.
Fire above the door behind us.
There's a guy behind us.
Don't shoot me.
Oh, my God.
I need to heal healing.
I'll be right there in a second.
Oh, he just got hit by a mage.
Oh, my God.
Careful.
All right, boys.
Where's he at?
They ran.
There's a mage up here though.
Left or forward?
Forward.
Like over here.
There's a mage in here though.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
There's okay.
Two tangos.
Got it.
Yeah.
Here's my lock pick room.
Bueno.
They're shooting arrows at us, I think.
I don't know if that's fell down the hole.
Fell down the hole.
I fell down the hole.
Oh, no.
Fell down the hole on the other room.
I need to heal before I come get you.
Or help.
Fell down the hole.
Who is shooting?
That's me.
There's a barbarian on the other hallway.
I see.
Nope.
Wow.
I didn't even see the hole.
Oh, we were doing so well.
What happened?
All right.
If you want to lead them up,
and then what I'm going to do is I'm going to fire them.
Oh, beautiful.
That's a beautiful trap.
Watch out.
Hole, hole, hole.
Beautiful.
We're better off closing the door first.
I'm going to act like the door is fucked.
Yep.
Exactly.
Boom.
I didn't watch.
I didn't even see the hole.
It's like blending into my brain on the screen.
Oh, you disabled the trap?
There is an exit down the hole, by the way.
But there's a shitload of enemies.
Fuck you.
Leave the door closed.
I like it that way.
Oh, they're shooting me through the...
I think it's four.
Bro, that's why you like that.
That's why the throwing axes are good.
That's why I like that.
Three or four people.
How did you fall down this hole?
How did I fall down it?
You can't even...
It doesn't make any sense.
It's like the opposite ends of both extraordinary spectrums there.
Like, I just...
I was just teleported down there.
It was just like, boop.
And you are desperately trying to fall through it.
And you can't get through it.
It doesn't make any sense to my brain.
I'm a big boy.
Hard to fit through and you got a full diapy.
We had two groups.
There were three to our right and three to our left.
I may have fallen down a hole.
But whatever.
It's all right.
Let's go.
Go again.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yes, just one second.
I know, I know.
There have been worse people.
I literally cannot get kills without weapons.
That's not the starting weapon on this character.
That's so funny.
You know, I know how you feel after I put seven arrows into one zombie's head.
Yeah, like this is not a game where you use base gear.
Like, you do not use base gear if you're not...
Like, if you're doing a scav run, sure.
Like, where you're literally just looting and running.
If you want to do one of those, we can do those.
There's no...
There's no Fletcher.
There's no traveling Fletcher.
You know, I'm going to prove it.
You know what?
That's it.
I got a lot of money.
That's a good idea.
You should probably buy gear.
You'll kill shit a lot faster.
Yeah, even if...
I'll make more money.
I'm going to buy this.
No, I'm not.
100 bucks.
I'm going to...
You know what?
Let's gamble.
I'm going for it.
I've been waiting to do this for the last, like, two days, three days.
Stuff kind of sucks.
I have a Battleaxe here.
Do you want me to buy it, gamble it, and if it's good, just give it to you?
Yeah, but if it's trash, I'm going to feel bad, you know?
I mean, I have money.
I mean, yeah, dude.
I'll try it once.
Is it worth it?
I have heard bad...
Wait, are you talking about the Goblin Battleaxe guy?
I got a green Battleaxe.
47 damage plus 2.5% physical damage.
Do you want it?
Yeah, I'll run it.
Absolutely.
Okay, all right.
I'm going to try it at least once.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Green, yeah.
Yeah, that's a lot better than what I have, so...
Yeah, okay.
And then I'm just going to...
I have a short sword for you, by the way, Stern.
Okay.
I don't want to bring this.
I'm going to lose it.
I'm bringing two Lockpicks that I'm going to immediately drop.
Oh, who sells the Lockpicks?
I believe Blacksmith.
Let me check.
Or I am wrong.
Maybe...
Interesting choice.
No, the Woodsman doesn't have them for me.
Maybe it's a momentary thing.
They all just, for me, they're all selling default gear
that you don't want to buy for very large amounts of money.
8 to like 10.
Maybe because I'm level 2.
Stern, I'll get you something.
What do you want?
No, I'm good.
I want to start.
Yeah, I hate to bring this up, but there is a Purple's Y-Hander on my merch.
Just wanted to let you know that.
I know you're a big...
I am a pretty big Zweiander fan.
I'm just going to get some default shit.
Why not?
Just don't buy grays.
If you buy a white for eight gold, that makes sense
because it's at least slightly better in some runs.
But if you can buy greens off the merchant, that's fine.
Oh, you said do not buy gray items.
Correct.
Okay.
Just don't bother.
No, so don't bother at all.
Okay.
I see what you mean.
Oh, no.
Make sure I clarify that and I want to make sure I get it right.
Oh, nice.
Is that a gray weapon or stuff from the Armorsmith?
I had it from before.
I just want to make sure I didn't do something stupid.
If anything, if it means anything, you look for it.
All right.
I got a cool axe for you.
Oh, God bless.
Here you go.
Oh, you're a madman.
Do not pick up these because they're crap.
Holy shit.
That's right.
That's the lobby.
Did you just drop stuff?
He did, dude.
He's a madman.
Actually, bro, you are the catalyst of chaos.
Holy shit, dude.
I'm sorry.
Did you get it?
I got it, bro.
But I had to go through Stern's body, too.
I was like, oh, my God, please don't be another player.
All right.
Here's your sword.
Oh, my God.
I just I'm not even realizing.
Oh, God, bro.
Jesus.
I got to get a hold of myself here.
All right.
Did you get the lockpicks?
Yes.
Here you go.
Oh, good.
I thought I killed him.
Jesus.
There is a good armor here for people that like wearing armor.
Watch out.
He's oh, God.
I'm going to hit this lockpick.
God.
Oh, you got this.
So big.
I'm going to hit it big.
Hit it big.
Hit it well.
Come on, Stern.
We believe in you.
Can you just can you watch it go around once?
I believe not.
I think you have to just do it.
It comes up at such a random time.
I'm not used to where it is on the screen.
It changes.
That's the fun part.
Take this.
Take this chest plate, please.
Come on, dude.
Fucking get it.
I thought you're going to run on the traps and off yourself.
Can you take this?
I can't wear that.
I mean, I'm it.
I meant wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, Stern.
Did I just do like 20% of your health in one punch?
No, the punches don't mess around.
They're like 20 damage, at least.
I I thought it.
All right.
I did it once.
You want to even it out?
That's what happened.
Diabe.
That's what's he doing?
Why are you doing this?
You just feel like I just feel like I'm getting bullied.
I'm angry because I failed the jump scare twice.
All right.
Let's fucking go for it.
Civil War.
Secret wall.
Again, that's almost stepped on.
Oh, my God.
I almost stepped on the trap there.
Let us know to be fair.
It really is like impossible.
It's rough.
It shouldn't be as hard as it is.
But I guess the reward is really great
because there could be something really amazing.
I want to be able to see.
Oh, there's a tomb.
We got tangos by us.
Rogue helmet on the ground.
I think they're north.
Maybe watch out tangos.
Yeah, because those don't go off for no reason.
So they're absolutely fighting something.
Well, let them let them get hurt.
Oh, he's metagaming.
I mean, that's what you said.
That's we're going by the smartest gamer in the room right now.
I think it might actually it might be.
I'll calm down.
Calm down.
My knowledge is five.
OK, I have to I have to open this
because I have to go get that health over there.
Watch the spider.
So spiders welcoming.
All right.
Running through running through and spawning these.
Come help me kill them.
Pressing E.
Kill.
Can you shoot the scaly archer jail?
Yeah.
Otherwise, he's going to farm me.
I'm doing it.
I'm shooting them.
He's not.
Oh, there's like loading.
There's like bugs, whatever they are stuck under there.
Careful, like bat things.
Getting them.
I'm shooting them.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
These should be an arrow.
Oh, yeah.
You I was shooting that guy and you know.
Why would it be accurate to me?
That was not you.
Jews in here.
But man, that's an emerald.
Diabla, do you have bandages?
He should have a campfire, which is I believe I have one.
I have two.
If you want to heal without us needing to use the campfire.
I have food I can eat as well.
Oh, that's right.
That's true.
But that almost is like too good.
And well, it's OK.
Although I will say that that health shrine does regen if we chill here for a sec.
Oh, oh, my.
Have you stand next to this altar of sacrifice?
It whispers.
Have you heard it?
It's scary, actually.
Repeat this crap is now.
Well, not quite yet.
I'll keep it for now because I buy a lot.
I got a long suit.
Oh, you did.
I would love to take that.
What do you?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you salute me.
Yeah.
Cool.
Beautiful.
Oh, wow.
Mimic.
Still gets me.
Oh, cool, cool, cool.
I just feel cool with the longsword.
It's just the swing is so cool.
I like the second swing.
It's my favorite.
So do the mimics have better stuff in them?
I was just going to bring that up.
You would think, but I have not seen anything with that.
OK.
This way, probably.
Look through.
If you're through, I don't see anything.
Yeah, we can go.
It will just make two lefts and basically reroute in to the circle.
There have been looters here.
I'm going to deal.
Let's get the full health.
People always want to do it in this little area in here.
This little hidey hole.
Let's do it.
Let's go in.
It'll be super safe when I close the lever.
But there'll be stuff in here.
I'll say that.
For some reason, I had assumed you'd use campfire.
Do you want this helmet?
It's a plus four physical power green.
I feel like you should be the one that has this on the ground.
Oh, wow.
Yes, I would love that.
You are the physical power, important wielder of acts.
You can't break with torches.
Oh, wow.
Maybe I should have just left it closed.
Oh, shit.
Oh, we got bugs.
Poison bug.
Did I get hit by it?
I did.
How?
I was behind the wall.
That poison gas is just such a great zoner.
It's the worst.
Yep.
Did I hit you?
Nope.
Thank God.
All right.
We got to run, run.
You should take Doris.
Oh, my God.
Get out of the fucking way.
We got to get the hell out of here right now.
We'll be all right.
Beautiful.
What the fuck?
Isn't that an archer?
Oh, what is it?
No, we got players shooting for us across the way.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
I need to heal somewhere.
That guy's got a big ass shield.
I'm going to sit here for a second.
Yep.
Careful, Ster.
Oh, I actually don't have heals.
This is amazing.
I have a bandage and I have a potion.
You should put it here.
Let me.
Yeah, if you appreciate it.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, gosh.
Did you get them both?
Yeah, thank you.
It's better in your hands than it is in mine.
No, no, no.
We are a team.
Well, apparently he has a good aim.
And I fucking jumped down.
I did a movement speed buff.
I did a movement speed buff and everything and I didn't make it.
Actually, I'll shut up.
Sorry.
I'm dead.
Like, there's no getting out of this.
Owie.
So how did I not get that?
I the jump there is kind of trash sometimes.
I even did movement speed and I like just I waited as long as I could.
I just didn't make it.
Oh, it's good.
I think I was slow from all the gear I had on.
All right.
I think we should be a little toxic.
I have an idea.
Grouch jump for extra height.
It doesn't really help with distance, but he is right.
I think I just had too much gear on.
I just didn't realize because I thought, oh, I'm going to do my movement speed buff
and I'll be able to get some momentum.
It just didn't help.
Wait.
Nothing's changed.
What's up?
I don't even have it on.
Oh, that's interesting.
I must have changed it and forgot that I changed it.
I haven't been doing movement speed.
I've been doing victory, victory strike.
So every time I press that, I'm just trying to run fast.
Sir, thank you so much for the raid.
Stir to the right song.
What do the raid song?
That's not a raid song.
It's a break song.
But do you want to hear it?
It's actually kind of I actually no, I'm good.
I'm not going to sing it.
I was going to play it in a stream.
Geez.
Okay.
Never mind.
Jeremy, can you do the raid song?
Oh, story.
Are you are you on your way out here?
Um, I can play like another.
I like what I mean.
I've been up a while.
I like this.
Right.
Gosh.
Wrong.
All right.
Let's do let's do another one.
Let's go for real this time.
All right.
Let's run it.
We are arranged kings.
So it's funny.
You rated me right as I put up my BRB screen, right?
Which has a song that I made.
No, no, I just I put it up for a second because I got up for a second
because like anytime I get up from my desk, I still have the ability to hear
because I have wireless headphones.
Anyways.
Oh, cool.
And like when you came in, you like do the raid song.
I thought you meant like my song was the raid song.
I didn't even know there was a raid song.
Oh, I don't know.
That's why I don't.
My brain checked out with the worm.
You think you can test the meat?
Look at me.
It's all gone.
It's always funny to hear the the 0.5 seconds people have in the voice chat in the lobby
and they're just going to get their one sentence out, whatever it is.
Got something over here.
Oh, what is this?
Is this just not is this a weird?
That's where the people used to spawn in.
Remember how like everybody was like like those little boxes on the outskirts of the map.
You just like well, I guess you just you didn't play earlier, did you?
No, I didn't.
This is the first test I played in the earlier play test.
Oh, check this out.
Check this out and fire sword.
Have fun and fire bow.
I'm so afraid.
I'm going to this thing is the fire.
So it's freaking me out.
I don't know.
I can't I can't I can't fucking use it.
I can't play with it.
It's weird.
I think it was a deep off.
Don't give that to me again.
That was a debuff.
All right.
Well, you know what?
Honestly, I'm just going to go off the wizard.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I thought this was a good idea.
It was just too I was so foreign to me too much power.
It just was so foreign to me that I just it was something I'd never seen.
There's a wraith in here that I think we might be able to kill a little bit of.
Never mind.
It's an awful lot.
Why can I not break?
You just got to believe points incoming.
Thanks, Jerma.
Well, you don't know that actually.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Thanks, but no thanks to what?
Oh, friends.
All right.
Watch out.
Hold on.
So here's the fun part.
We get to be so toxic with your arrows and my fireballs.
And my apps and my thank you.
I was trying to get to the exit.
We came in.
It's coming in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'm dead.
Beautiful.
All right.
This one doesn't count.
No.
That one.
Oh, there's somebody behind me.
Fuck.
There's no way we're letting that happen.
There's no way.
I'm sorry.
Nope.
I'm done.
Hey, bedtime.
Get real late.
I got to go get in my crib.
Understandable.
Thank you, sir.
Yeah, no problem.
And it was nice meeting you.
And also thank you for the raid.
It was really nice.
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
Good night.
See you later, Sterk.
Thanks for playing.
Sterk is a good dude.
So what's your plan?
I might want to do some solo goblin stuff now that I have like a cool weapon.
Yeah, absolutely.
But I think that's great.
It's also a great way to get a lot of loot, a lot of money.
Yeah.
The goblin caves are fun.
They are rigorous in some ways.
And then like you will get like shitty teleports.
So well, they just they made it better and they make it easier.
They kind of nerfed a lot of stuff in it, didn't they?
I think it's a lot more like predictable with the circles now.
So maybe.
But I just went into a couple earlier and they were still kind of weird.
Cool.
Well, that's good to know because I was like, oh, they made it.
They nerfed it.
Now I'm going to go in and be a dickhead and die.
Now, the the goblins still mess you up.
If you if you even take one hit, it's a quarter of the barb's health.
And he has the highest health.
So yeah.
Yeah, it's cool to have you on stream.
Thanks for playing.
I mean, I'm going to probably be playing for at least another couple of hours.
I don't know what the plan is, but I know Kraken's got another group.
I know there's other people playing, too.
Probably can jump around again later.
I'll be on.
I'll be playing Friday as well.
So sick.
Yeah, just let me know if you need me.
Yeah, it's awesome hanging out with you.
Thanks for coming out.
And make sure we get to follow the channel, everything, because you're good, too.
Appreciate that.
And I really appreciate going on.
And it was a good time.
Mods show that please spam Twitch.tv.
Slash.
You're too nice to me.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Yeah, but take care.
We'll talk to you.
I'll talk to you soon.
Mods, mods, mods.
Yeah, I met him through when I went to go do the show with Charlie.
He's part of that kind of group.
They're all really cool, really funny, really awesome.
So cool to play with them.
Oh, there we go.
That's cool.
So I do want to try the new Goblin mode, at least for a little while.
I'm not bringing this yet.
This is staying right here until the last day.
But I'm just going in.
You know, I know Omega Lully's level 20 and he's like sucks.
Yeah, whatever.
Who cares?
It's just a play test.
I'll be better next play test.
No one's going to carry you now.
I feel like 70% of the runs we did were comedy runs.
So I think it worked out pretty well.
All right, let's go.
Awful place to start.
But whatever.
Oh, that's oh, this is also not good.
This is also bad.
This is awful.
I am so glad I didn't bring this reander down here.
I think I made it up.
Oh, he swung.
Close, close, close it.
This room is equally as bad.
Oh, my God.
OK, come on, come on.
I bumped into the wall.
Well, this is a bad start.
Maybe I'll find some heals.
Pretty good.
Better than pull you over here.
This time don't get hit.
I don't want to aggro the rest of the room.
Come on, get over here.
Get over here.
Hey, would you look at that?
30.
Look, I asked and God answered.
23.
I don't really know how to use this, but I'll try it.
This thing is like a head bopper, right?
Yeah.
Anything else?
For some reason, I thought that was a guy in there.
I saw like just the shoes.
This stir stream is still on.
It is.
Hold on.
We're not like messing around, right?
Is it actually just still on?
Oh, that's one of these things.
Hold on.
I'm just kind of walking and dying, but I actually don't want.
If he doesn't know that, then I definitely want to make sure he knows.
Give me one second.
I'm going to text him.
I would definitely want someone to tell me if I did that.
Give me one second.
I'll be right back.
Concerned, Andy?
No, but I mean, if you don't know that's happening, it's just like, oh, wait, what?
Give me one second.
I'll be right back.
Okay, just give me two more seconds.
Two seconds.
I just saw the subs come in.
Yeah, dude, I appreciate that.
We should be giving subs to you, though.
Not this way.
No, it was a blast having you on.
Give me two more seconds.
Sometimes Twitch staff hangs out here.
I don't know if anybody from Twitch staff is aware of this.
Maybe they can do something about it.
I don't know.
Sometimes there's staff that lurks here.
Give me one more moment.
Don't worry, I'm going to be live for a while.
Don't worry.
Uh, I'm going to just keep playing.
Hey, look, Twitch staff.
Staff?
Staff.
Yeah, we think that Stirr may have left his stream on.
Possibly.
I think he did a raid and then I think just didn't turn the stream on.
The worms got him.
He fell asleep instantly.
I mean, he did leave very quickly.
It was like, yeah, yeah, okay, bye.
Oh, he's back.
All right.
Stirr came back.
Okay.
All right.
We good?
We're good.
All right.
He said, huh?
Bro, he's going to go another 12 hours.
He put food in the oven and took a shower.
Yeah, I tried texting him.
We pinged him a few times and, you know, I think we even pinged Ashley a few times too.
All right.
Well, that's good.
Situated.
My text didn't even go through to him.
Hold on.
Wait, did he mean to do that and he was coming back?
No, I doubt it.
He got your Discord things.
Okay, good.
No, dude, he has your number blocked.
All right.
All right, that's good.
Oh, my text says not delivered.
Oh, that's weird.
Okay.
Well, we're good.
Okay, he's ending for real now.
All right, good.
Yeah, trust me when I say I would want someone to do that for me too.
If I just like left the stream on for like, yeah, it's like, hey, hey, hey, turn it off.
Because you never know.
Honestly, here's a little tip.
You just kind of don't know, right?
If you're setting a stream up, then trust me, I've been doing this before.
Like, showing up hours later and you put, I don't know how many times I've probably
sat here and fucking farted.
You know what I mean?
Or like just, oh, I have no clothes on.
I'm just kind of walking around in my room.
You know what I mean?
You just need to fucking know these things.
You just need to know.
You've got to know.
What the hell?
I'm staying in here.
How is, I can't fight these?
I have to pull them all individually into the room.
Why did you come too?
Oh, my God.
Are we sure?
Hold on.
Are we sure they didn't add enemies and damage?
Wait, what is he screaming in his house?
What are you talking about?
Is it like, he's doing like a bit?
I think a bat got into his house.
All right.
Give me a better spawn.
Hold on a second.
The channel's still live.
Oh, he hurt.
He hurt.
Fuck.
Yeah, I did.
I did.
That was pretty sly.
Pretty sly.
I thought he was like in danger.
And it's so funny during that whole thing.
Somebody in chat definitely wrote, oh my God, he's so bad at the game.
Dude, this guy sucks at this.
Click.
Fuck.
I clicked.
You heard it like five times.
All right.
I didn't get spawned into a terrible spot.
New hat.
This is actually really good.
Plus any stats is very good.
Okay.
I actually don't want to die because that helmet is very good.
It's better.
I don't think I've ever used this.
I just, should I do a wield?
Why not?
Click.
Pretty nice.
Okay.
Ooh.
Oh, shit.
25 or 20.
That's plus two agility.
Oh my God.
I'm looking how fast I move now.
Jesus.
All right.
Let's keep that on.
I thought there was a player.
Beat saber mode.
Yeah, that's true.
Actually true.
This is the loot corner.
So much shit on these walls here.
Uh-oh.
He's above me.
But holy shit.
That's a pretty, I got to get out of here now.
That's a, that's a diamond.
I run fast now.
Geez.
All right.
Don't fuck this up.
I was going to find a way out because I want to keep, that's it.
That was a cool diamond.
Come on down, please.
Are you all the way up in the ceiling?
What?
Oh, you're full of shit.
Oh my God.
Just fucking run.
What?
This is, that enemy is so fucking weird.
I swear to God.
The thing is a glued to the ceiling and then comes down and goes,
dee, dee, dee.
What have you done?
Why did you bring all this shit down here?
Fucking stuck in the wall.
What the fuck, dude?
I literally couldn't even move.
I was literally stuck.
I couldn't walk.
Fuck that bug.
I was fine too.
Pain in the ass.
Good night, Irene.
I jumped into it.
At least you're not losing stuff.
The thing, well, he kind of just said he had the same idea
where he was just like, you know what?
We're just dead.
So one of us is going to die.
You know what?
I would have rather he killed me.
He knew too that one of us was going to get embarrassed
getting stuck in that corner.
And he didn't want it to be him.
So he got the easy way out.
You married into it.
It is sore though.
Okay.
Somebody asked, why do the skeletons have blood?
Bone marrow.
You know where your blood comes from?
I feel like this is going to be a never-ending spider thing
because my weapon is not.
You're still living.
Why are you still among the living?
All right.
Just don't go that way.
Your blood comes from your heart.
Your, what are you talking about?
Your heart pumps it.
It actually comes from marrow.
Blood cells are made in the bone marrow.
The bone marrow is the soft spongy material
in the center of the bones.
It produces about 95% of the body's blood cells.
Most of the adult body's bone marrow is in the pelvic bones.
Breast bone and the bones of the spine.
Time that person out for 10 minutes.
Somebody's coming over that way.
This is going to get bad, isn't it?
He hears all this, too.
He's probably listening to the door.
Yeah.
Are we cool?
All right, you're cool.
I'm not going to kill you.
I'm just following you.
That sounds weird, but pretend to be fighting me.
Pretend to be fighting me.
Get back here.
Yeah, pretend to be fighting me so we can trick somebody.
Don't even think about it.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Ooh, it didn't work.
I thought someone was coming through the door.
And then get him.
Well, that was fun for a minute.
We have to be in this room.
This is awful.
I'm going to go around.
I don't want to deal with that side.
I don't have any items.
What the fuck have I been doing?
All right.
I just need to find a portal.
I really didn't do anything this round.
I kind of just walked around in a circle.
So many concentrated enemies right there.
I need to at least get some loot or something.
There are so many people that are left, too.
Still aggro'd on him.
Nice one.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Nice job.
We got to...
I mean, we don't have to get to...
Ooh.
All right.
What do we got?
Something good?
May your journeys be long, your ale fresh,
and your carrots crunchy, and your stew hot,
and your goblins easy to slay, and your friends plentiful.
All right.
You go.
I have nothing.
I have literally have no reason to go through that.
Like, I really just don't.
I mean, 10 gold maybe.
There's a lot of people left for how tiny this circle is.
I'm the last one.
Oh, no, I'm not.
There's like three people left.
I just wanted a portal.
Oh, wait.
I heard one.
I think it was above, though.
Yeah, it was above.
That's OK.
Yeah, I should have just dropped all my shit,
and he could have just taken it.
The next adventurer.
You can make it if you run.
If there was something good in that treasure chest,
then I'm glad somebody got it.
My last message from Stirr, like 15 minutes ago,
kind of disrespectful to ask me to end stream.
It wasn't even bad.
Hello?
Well, he's such a shit.
Oh, hi.
10 enemies.
There really are so many.
You weren't even close.
That's a pretty decent amount of money to start with.
I'm going to try to just get out of here.
Oh, a diamond.
OK.
Oh, if only I had somebody to guide me.
If only somebody was around to show me the way.
Oh, oh, stuck down here in a dungeon.
If only there was an adventurer that could help me.
The promise of jewels was not enough.
Oh, if only there was an adventurer that could come
and help me and accept my quest.
Oh, thank you for accepting my quest.
Oh, it's been very cold down here.
Where are you?
Where are you off to?
Oh, if only there.
All right.
We need to.
There's too many people.
Oh, dear.
The dungeon is so strong, brothers.
So dark down here.
If anyone were to lead me to a portal,
I have a diamond that they will have if they complete my quest.
I look in the door this way.
Hurry hurrying behind you.
Is that acid?
No, it's safe.
It is safe.
See, it's green jello.
So much mountain dew.
All right.
Oh, the poison, the poison stings.
Does anyone have a close the door behind us?
We're fucking dead.
There's no way we're getting through this.
Oh, my God.
That's so slow.
Oh, shit.
I almost closed the door.
Would any of you happen to have a healing pot?
Watch out behind you.
There's a mummy and a bug and a snake.
Please, if you get it out alive, I have a diamond on me.
Even though you failed.
There's so many things.
We were just being followed by 25 enemies.
I want to be an escort quest for somebody so bad.
Oh, I would be willing to give anybody all of my items
that they would escort me to a portal.
Find me.
Find me if you could.
Okay.
You're mean.
I need to find like a blue diamond
and then just be a quest for somebody.
I'm into that right now.
I'm down on the southern end of the map.
I don't know how far my voice travels.
Next time, I'm just going to bring like 15 bandages
and like 25 potions in the corner.
Oh, my goodness.
These fucking enemies.
Jesus.
There we go.
A magical amulet.
Oh, my God.
There's so much gear over here.
I can do it.
Just don't die.
Look at all this shit over here.
What are you doing?
What the hell is this person?
What were you doing?
Look at all these.
Oh, my God.
This is such a quest reward.
I need an adventurer to help me get out of the dungeon.
I have gold.
I have trinkets.
I need some help to get out of the dungeon.
I have plenty of goods.
Is there anyone out there?
Can anybody hear me?
I need an escort out of the dungeon.
Anyone?
Can anyone hear me?
I need an escort out of the dungeon, please.
I have gold.
I have treasure.
If anyone's out there, I have gold.
I have jewels.
I need an escort out of the dungeon, please.
Fuck these bugs.
They're the worst.
I'm on the lower level.
There's no one here to help me.
Is there anyone that will help me?
Adventurer, adventurer, I need help.
Oh, there's a lot of fucking spiders here.
Oh, adventurer.
If you...
That's a fucking enemy.
I just saw the shield.
All right, we're going...
We're doing a real one this time.
Well, howdy there.
I need an escort out of the dungeon.
I will pay gold and jewels.
If you can please find me,
I will go to the southern end of the map.
Please, please.
Okay.
That was such a reluctant okay.
That was the most reluctant okay I've ever heard.
That was like...
I'm going to die on my way over there.
I hope he finds my body.
Quest accepted.
All right, I got to get to the southern end of the map.
Please.
Look at that.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I found you pretty fast.
Will you accept my quest?
Sure.
Okay.
I don't know very much about the dungeon.
All I know is that I don't want to be down here.
It smells.
Yeah, yeah, that's fair.
I see you're a wizard.
Very helpful.
Claire.
Oh, yeah.
Careful.
This dungeon is known to have all kinds...
Adventurer!
There are goblins!
I'm back, I'm back.
Careful.
With the great power of
Phineas Davidson.
I smacked you.
Oh my goodness.
Behind you.
Look out!
Not swinging.
These caves have so many scary things in them.
When I was younger, I used to explore here.
Onward!
Well, that way seems dangerous.
It does.
I would say we should probably go south.
I remember when I was in the poison swamp one time.
The amount of damage and disease it causes.
Onward with sick in a moment's notice being down here.
Truly a disgusting...
Adventurer!
Goblins are afoot!
Don't let him run!
Poisonous.
Very, very disgusting.
Anyone would take five points of damage if they walked down here.
Adventurer!
Goblins!
Hold on, I know...
These halls are full of all kinds of dangerous things.
Ah, that feels better.
Oh my god, is it you?
That feels better.
All right.
We are safe here.
The dungeon was built...
I would like to participate...
...back in 1500 BC.
It stood for many years.
Poison is actually dragon's breath, if you didn't know.
Five million years ago, the dragon Allora died down here.
And their spit is what causes most of the poison, if you didn't know.
Adventurer!
Goblins!
Oh, I'm about to die.
A portal!
There's the portal!
The portal!
Want to leave?
The dragon breathed four thousand percent five million years ago.
I thank you for helping me.
Listen, don't forget about me, general.
Here is the...
Don't forget about me.
Here's your shitty reward for me.
He...
He took it.
Here's your shitty reward for your level one quest.
Thank you.
I will go in the portal now.
He took it.
Hey, there's people here.
Adventurer!
Goblins!
Use the strength of a thousand sons!
Here, take this, Adventurer.
You could use it.
Oh, shit, he escaped.
The dragon five thousand years ago was the shittiest NPC of any fucking game ever.
Hey, they played along, it was fun.
All right, let's do a real one.
Oh, the dragon...
Alloro?
I don't even know what the dragon's name was.
General, you could have donated those seventy five...
Do you mean...
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just want to make sure I'm very clear of what you're asking me.
Are you talking about the family guy money from ten years ago?
Why are you bringing that up right now?
Anything?
Okay, easy.
Good start.
Let's go.
I ain't going that way.
Actually, did I just get one?
Yeah, I did.
Okay, don't screw this up.
It's really easy to screw it up in solo.
You always think it's safe and it never is.
Okay, come on.
Through the door and then I'm going to close it.
That's how you do it.
Cool.
There we go.
That's actually really good for a green.
Oh, shit.
I didn't want to press that button and I did.
I didn't mean to.
Oh, don't panic.
Just fucking go.
I fucked it up.
I was so afraid of going back into this room.
This is not going like terribly.
This weapon is really good, though, for a green.
I don't want to lose it.
Fuck.
Open, open, open, open, open, open, open.
Somebody was already here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, thank God.
A lot of stuff running down here.
I got to look for a portal.
Oh, yeah.
Strength, too.
These have stats.
Six, agility.
Where are you?
You?
Oh, he's gone.
Oh, somebody closed it.
You got a shield.
I don't want to fuck with that.
You can have half.
That's how it works.
I was hoping he was going to just attack me.
I just took way more than half.
No, this is yours.
I took way more than that.
Okay.
Traitor Andy.
What is going on?
Oh, I thought he was swinging at me.
Sorry, be safe.
I don't have much, but whatever.
I do want to get out with this weapon.
Nice work.
Shit.
It's too dark.
Oh, boy.
This is very bad.
Stuck.
I'm stuck.
Oh, fuck.
Look out.
Be careful.
I'm going to bleed to death, aren't I?
Oh, they're right here.
Be careful.
It's not safe.
You literally saved my life.
Before we leave, I'm going to give you a trinket.
Is this the last portal?
Oh, I don't know if there's any more.
There's one more.
It'll spawn when it's closing again.
Okay.
Good to know.
Shit, there's no portal in here.
This is so annoying.
It's probably up.
That's so annoying.
The portal's probably up.
Okay, cool.
I mean, didn't really get very much, but I did.
I actually really wanted to hold on to this.
This thing's pretty good.
I feel like I haven't traded anything to the merchant in like an hour and a half.
No, no, no, no.
Keep those two.
Get rid of these.
And one strength.
I mean, that's kind of good, though.
Only three gold.
That's kind of terrible.
Let me get rid of some of this silver.
I know if people are saying to buy these, but I like having...
Not yet.
I don't need it yet.
Once this comes down to halfway, I'm ready to show this off to anybody,
but I'm afraid to use it.
I'm still holding this.
I'm going to do it again.
I have gear.
Actually, I'm going to buy some potions and stuff.
Bandages.
There's four portals now.
That's good.
That's actually really good.
That went down.
No, really?
Oh, don't even.
Trying to hit them both.
What?
Well, glad I brought these.
I did it.
I killed the goblin king.
I've done it.
That wasn't the king.
That's a lackey.
You don't fucking know what you're doing.
No, I killed the king.
I killed the king earlier.
It was me.
You didn't kill the king.
It was me that did it.
Here, take this.
Let's have fire.
Can you just give it to me?
On the ground, right here.
Yeah, worth a bunch of money.
I'm a cleric, so if you ever need patching up, little, you know...
I'm a loner.
I'm a loner, and I don't really have a party or anything.
So it's really nice to meet you, though.
Like, what kind of party?
Are you throwing, like, a birthday party?
Or it's like a...
Wait.
Hey, now.
We should group up.
Are you good on here?
I'm supposed to stand there, get poked again.
Right into the ear.
Do you have any potions?
Are you good on potions?
I got too many potions.
I also got this wine bottle.
We could have a little cabaret dinner.
That looks dangerous.
The hole is not dangerous.
You almost got poked in the ear again.
Yeah, it was close, though.
You got a little beetle.
Calgimus, forcimus.
Watch out.
Oh, he's dead.
No, wait, how did he die?
Oh, no.
He stopped talking.
I was about to...
I was going to do, like, a...
I was going to do a face turn.
Oh, no.
I was going to do a face turn and beetle...
Oh, God.
I hit him.
No, I didn't.
I was just trying to be, like, the weird guy in the dungeon.
Get me off voice chat.
I can't play the game with this proximity chat.
Turn it off.
I have to stop this.
Just closing the door and then he opens the door.
I'm just standing there at the end of the hallway.
One normal round.
Turn it back on.
I'm not going to do an L-M-O-R-P.
You're trying to, like, make 10,000 people leave.
God, how did that not reach?
Actually, thanks.
That helped.
Why am I so slow?
Oh, that's a debuff that I'm...
Okay.
Oh, no.
You're going to heal, aren't you?
Cool, but I can't use it.
Somebody's coming.
Crouch.
RP where you pretend to be really good.
I can try that.
I'm sorry.
I probably just woke somebody up.
Trying to, like, freak that person out.
I just lost a fucking torch.
That's all that happened.
Not...
No.
This room is awful.
I'm going to go up.
God damn it.
It's junk.
SpongeBob RP.
Look at all this crap.
I have to get out of here.
Shit.
How...
I'm...
How do I get up there?
I don't...
Can I get up there?
I think I'm, like, trapped.
I'm going to die.
That was pretty close.
Any scraps?
Oh, my goodness.
Am I invisible?
Where the fuck are the eggs at?
I don't know.
Ow.
Did you just get caved in on?
What?
You got it.
Yeah.
I think there's one more.
What the fuck was that?
Was that Elmo?
That was weird.
Who is doing that?
Shut up.
Is it anybody else?
No, it's just this guy.
It had to be me.
There's nobody else in the lobby.
I thought there was two or three people left.
You watch what...
You have to watch him.
Let's see if he can escape.
I wish you luck.
Is that...
Ooh.
I think you're going to get out.
Yeah.
There we go.
It's all good.
Eugene.
I'm going to throw a little bit of a curve ball here.
I'm going to do one more round.
Yeah, look.
I didn't really get anything.
I'm going to try a different class.
I'm going to go level one.
Not that it matters, but that's the wrong button.
You can sell from the stash?
Really?
Will I play the Metroid remaster?
I never played Metroid Prime.
It always looked interesting, but this was something I never really grasped.
For me, the Wii was always...
All the FPSs that were on Wii were so good.
Resident Evil 4 for the Wii is my favorite version of that game.
Obviously before it came to PC.
But even...
I don't know.
Even still, I really liked it on Wii.
It was really fun to aim with it.
Seemed pretty responsive.
All right.
Let me do...
Let me do one in the normal place.
But then after this, I'm going to change.
Wizard?
I don't know if I'm a wizard player.
I usually like to play casters and RPGs or whatever.
But it feels like there's a lot of micromanagement with wizard.
I'd rather just swing at stuff.
Helpful.
I did?
Yes.
Okay, you can't come through that.
No.
Do a golem RP.
Armor or magic now?
I mean, I'll hold on to these.
Oh, shit.
Let me in there.
I feel like that's really, really, really good.
It's just one of those unbelievable stat things.
That's really good.
I actually don't want to lose now.
Not like I wanted to before, but you know.
Damn.
Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
Oh, my God.
All right.
After this, if this is good,
I'm just going to literally sneak around.
Shit.
RP is you're drunk?
That's going to be so annoying.
People?
Somebody's here?
Oh, I don't even know how to play.
I don't even know where the hell to go.
I don't even know where to go.
Down here?
I don't know.
I literally don't know where to go.
I tried to do the drunk RP.
I don't know where to go.
And I was just...
Drunk RP means easy kill.
Yes, I'm realizing this right now.
That's...
Hey, this dude's shit face.
He probably has no idea what he's doing.
Just kill him.
Destroyed.
Just act crazy.
That was some good shit, too.
The mistake was going into that room.
I should have just turned around and ran.
Wait.
I got health here.
Whatever.
Oh, my God.
Good start.
I'm going to take that in a little bit.
I have to play really, really passively.
Where is this spawner?
I forgot to buy potions again.
I'm going this way.
Okay.
Here's somebody.
Oh, shit.
Uh, where's the lever?
Stream sniper!
Actually, I'm going to stay here.
You got me right in the head, too.
There's stuff in here.
Is that locked?
Oh, my God.
I'm dead.
I don't know, man.
Like, that just did almost my whole-
That just killed me in one hit almost.
How do-
All right.
How do you fight those as melee?
I feel like they just blow up the area
like 15 feet in front of them.
How do you fight those mages as melee?
You have to jump dodge.
You don't.
You run.
You have to bait the shot.
That was an elite, too.
Yeah.
Let's fucking go.
Don't ever buy grace.
I don't care.
I'm going hard right now.
And I'm getting out.
Hey, like we were saying earlier,
beta ends in three, four days.
Whatever.
Are we ready?
This is a-
This is a big deal.
I'm about to do this in the goblin zone.
And by the way,
I ain't fucking around.
I ain't friends with anybody.
Nobody's friends.
We're not-
I'm not friends with anybody.
I think I'm ready.
It's locked in now.
Every single person is my enemy.
Not-
I-
I'm not wasting any time.
Congratulations to the stream snipers
that now are going to get a nice sword,
by the way.
Or you got to get me.
You got to kill me by the-
By the way.
I'm going to be silent as well.
What do you got?
Good start.
After these chests,
I'm going right in the middle.
Is there a potion?
I didn't see one.
Holy shit, there is a potion.
Good eyes.
I'm on a way out.
He ducked.
His animation-
Stop!
His animation made him duck.
Start looking for portals really soon here.
This thing is fucking unbelievably good.
All right, portal time.
Oh, I made it.
I had a choice,
and that was to open the portal and take a hit,
or lose the portal.
Thank god.
My adrenaline is like on fire.
It's just so-
Oh my goodness,
because you don't want to lose this thing, right?
Oh my god.
Okay, let's put it away for another three days.
I might actually-
Eh.
Oh, I don't have a weapon now.
Buy one?
You gamble?
Actually, yeah.
What do we got?
Try to gamble for like a decent weapon?
Or-
All right.
Do a weld, Andy.
I'm all right with this.
Thankfully, I didn't die,
so I get to keep the potions and everything.
I think I'm good to go.
This is pretty good.
Yeah, let's do it again.
Oh shit, I don't have any torches.
Do you have any feedback for the game?
I think it's in a really close spot.
I think that some of the-
There's obviously some of the weird bugs
when you click to swing or click to block
and it doesn't happen.
Or sometimes you just get stuck swinging permanently.
I really don't have torches.
This is kind of awful.
Besides like the gameplay-wise,
I mean, I would obviously like to see more-
I really like the PvE stuff.
I'd like to see Elmo,
like an officially licensed Elmo boss.
I don't think that's asking a lot,
which I mean, a lot of people might think it is.
What?
I thought somebody just hit me in the head.
Pick it up.
Am I crazy or is this not?
This coin doesn't exist.
Get this out of the way right now.
Heal.
Anything?
You got anything?
Oh, okay.
I'll take it.
That's it.
Oh!
Oh my God, it scares me every time.
I swear to God.
It's good.
Pick it up.
The torches.
Is it gonna do?
I've got a lot of heals.
That's why I'm doing this so much.
Oh shit, I gotta go.
I think they're above.
That's a big scary red bug.
Somebody in here?
They're up top.
Oh my God!
No, fuck.
I-
I slowed-
I fucked up.
I saw the fucking guy behind him
and I just-
I thought that boss was gonna-
So here's what happened.
I saw the boss running at him.
I thought he was gonna back up.
I didn't think he was gonna just be swinging, swinging, swinging.
I thought he was gonna back up and get hit by the boss.
I didn't know.
He was just walking forward and just clicking.
I thought he was gonna back up.
I played that wrong.
He stopped attacking.
All right, I do have a complaint.
Here's a game complaint.
The dual weld swinging is weird as fuck.
It's like right click, left click.
It feels weird.
There's something about it that just feels off.
It's like I'll swing twice
and then try to start my swing combination again
and just don't do anything.
It'll be like one, two.
Click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, one, two.
I'm not doing dual weld anymore.
The amount of times you have to click with a dual weld,
it's like left click, right click, right click, left click, right click, left click.
One of those clicks ain't gonna work.
You can hold left click.
Wait, I hold right click or left click?
Because when I try to do left click,
it just swings the left hand, doesn't swing the other one.
Hold down both buttons.
Hold both left and right at the same time.
What?
Hold right click, then hold left click.
I just wish I could just, I don't know.
I wish I could just click left click and swing them both.
Every other weapon in the game is left click.
Whatever.
I'm just going with nothing.
Everything else is a single weapon?
Yeah.
It's just finicky to do left click and right click at the same time
or differently, it just feels weird.
That's my opinion.
If you don't like it, then you know what to do.
I beg you for forgiveness and hoping that you don't hate me.
It's the next day?
Yeah.
I told you this is gonna be an omega stream.
Oh, I meant it.
There's a lot of spiders.
Where is the, okay, right there.
Eh, do you get no loot for the bugs?
Like the spiders.
What the fuck?
Why?
This is just kind of a pain in the ass, isn't it?
Just look at this trail of spiders.
Let's show how many of these do I have to, just get it.
God damn it.
Okay.
Yeah, that was worth it.
A lot of experience.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Very true.
I hear somebody.
I spent so much time killing those spiders.
Someone's mining in here.
Sucks, I'm just gonna go across.
I'm coming to get you.
Oh my goodness, look at all this shit in here.
I got hit by something really awful.
No heals.
I want that shit so bad in there.
I don't know what that means.
That's not, that's not the crouch crouch.
Oh, good.
Fucking God, how did I fall down before he did?
Hey, there's a, where is it?
I just heard it.
You are decked out.
Damn, be careful.
Smart.
I don't have my heal anymore.
Okay, if I go up this,
can I, hopefully I can turn around.
Whatever, it's worth, who cares?
No, I'm not going, I'm not doing that.
I'm not doing that.
Did he hear me?
Fuck.
Oh, okay.
I guess I'm doing it.
Where?
Oh, no.
No, I don't know.
I don't know.
It just spawned.
This, this two right here.
What's the, it's got to be some kind of mathematical equation
where they cannot be like five feet fucking next to each other.
There has to be some kind of mathematics.
They get spawning right next to each other.
It should be at least 50 to a hundred feet apart.
They spawn within the circles.
I mean, me and that guy were walking around in circles
for a full minute or two.
And the fucking bugleberry over there had two spawn next to him.
That's life in the dungeon, bro.
Yeah.
Oh no, I know.
Doesn't mean I can't die and just complain about it.
Do a bugleberry RP.
I can change class after this.
Okay, actually getting, this is a, this is a bait coin.
Been bugged the whole time.
Oh my goodness.
What if that was a blue?
Whatever.
Okay, this could be good.
I strafed that.
What?
I hit you in the head five fucking times in a row.
What the heck?
What the fuck?
Does my weapon just suck?
Bad weapon.
I mean, how many headshots from a 22, what 22 damage?
Two, four, six, eight, 10.
I mean, well, that would have to have been a hundred plus.
How much was that?
Three potion.
All right.
There was at least three or four times in a row where it was like headshot.
Back up.
Headshot.
I get hit twice and I'm dead.
God, we, we had the same clothes on.
We had the same clothing.
They had the shrine of protection.
God damn it.
Oh, I was gonna say something.
Change class.
I know, I can't go out on that one.
I felt really good about that fight too.
So bandy.
Goodbye.
Okay, we're not doing this either.
I like it.
I could take one.
No, I get killed before I open the door.
Yes, good luck.
Did you do it?
Oh my God.
He's gonna get killed by the fucking mage.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Just.
Oh no.
You actually almost killed me.
That was actually really well done.
That was a lot of perseverance.
Seriously.
Oh shit.
I'm just wearing all his clothes.
Wait, what if I take it and resurrect him?
Oh, Jack is style.
Boy, where are you?
Where is this character?
I don't, I actually don't see them.
Where is this?
Where are they?
There's no way you.
There's no way you're shooting me from up there.
From back there?
Aiming down and in the hole?
Dak and daka, you know.
Why didn't I run?
Because I wanted to go through that way.
Dead and bald.
Class change?
Yeah, after this.
Is this game good or are you just bad and make it awful?
Go download it.
Go play it for 45 minutes.
And then I want you to come back and report on how you did.
And then play it for like another 100 hours.
And realize that it's dak and daka.
Doesn't matter.
People will just screw you over at every turn.
People will kill you.
People will try to be friends with you and then backstab you.
People might lock you in a room with a bunch of monsters.
And then, you know, it's dak and daka.
But you died by standing under an archer on purpose.
See that?
I thought he was dead.
You have to seriously block me in here with all this.
I was going to say, there's a lot of shit in here.
Hold on.
Now we're talking.
Did I loot this already?
I'm going to stay up.
Oh shit.
Oh, yup.
People are coming and I don't want to do well.
I'll have you.
Hold down right click.
Hold down right click and left click.
What is with this barrel?
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
Do you have any shielding?
Let me check.
Sorry, I do not.
I would have.
I would have given it to you.
I promise you.
I'll stick with you, dude.
I don't know how to play the gun.
It's very hard.
It is no joke.
I've done high roller twice.
And I've lived times.
And I don't think I've lived once during this fucking cave.
So be careful.
People are known to double cross each other here.
Especially if they say they're a friend at first.
Goodbye, dude.
See, I told you about this spider.
You know, I'm not going to double cross.
I'm going to die.
That was a little rusty.
I'm a little rusty.
All right, let's move.
Look, man, I know there's a pot of spiders back here.
That's all I know.
We need light.
Why are there so many?
This is like, where's the spawner?
Is there like 10 of them?
Pot of spiders.
You need to, oh, good job.
All right, let's get out of here.
Come on.
Yeah, we got to get out of here.
Shit.
Hey, get in here.
Get in here.
My buddy told me about this door.
I present to you Golgotha.
You think we can take him?
You think we can do it?
You got good gear?
Nope.
But it's too late now.
He can't make it.
OK, I'm sorry you didn't make it.
I don't know if we were prepared for this.
This is like a boss.
All right, I got to get out of here now.
I think I'm just dead.
Is there another way to get out?
No, I have to run.
I'm stuck.
What is going on?
Let me fucking out of here.
Where is it?
It's up top.
I'm dead.
I don't know.
I have no idea where it is.
We're in a lot of trouble.
Yeah, I don't have very much help though.
Will another one spawn in the circle?
Got to make a choice and go.
I got to make a choice here.
Yeah, we got to make a choice.
I got to make a choice.
I don't know how to go up though.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know where to go.
Do you know how to go up?
I just don't know the layout.
Like this way?
Oh, we're dead.
Map?
I don't even know what up looks like.
No, I'm dead if I go that way.
I'm dead.
There's nowhere to go.
I wouldn't have made it.
Were there any left?
I think somebody got it.
I just don't...
The amount of levels that are in this zone,
I feel like a handful of people just get screwed
because they're not on the right level when the shit spawns.
And it's like if I don't have health,
I'm just...
I'll just die.
Go back to the side ramp where you got to the troll.
I just...
Yeah.
Guaranteed extract on here is represented by the stairs symbol.
It means the stone's collapsing earlier.
The rock slide is a secret escape.
Really?
I thought that person went in there and got crushed by the rocks.
The rock slide means only one can come out.
You know what it is to me?
It's just kind of getting that object permanence
of just where everything is on the map.
That's always been hard for me to do.
Because to me, those...
All those hallways are just the same hallway in my brain.
It's just the same hallway.
It's just like a shredded up piece of paper.
I don't even...
I can't even...
My brain can't translate it.
I think I'm dead already.
Okay, bye.
Bye, I guess.
Light orb.
I want chain lightning.
Zap is kind of bad.
Fireball, magic missile, lightning strike.
Haste is good.
Slow is...
I think slow would be good too.
Use it on people and run away.
Try this.
I really have no idea what I'm doing, but I'll try.
Ouchie, ouchies.
MOU using the lobby is consumed.
Oh, that sucks.
Okay, well, oops.
That's funny.
Oh, I got a thing or two to learn.
Shit, that's a lot.
Oh my god, that's a lot.
I'm just going to hide and leave.
I'm going to...
Okay, I'm going to sprint to the middle right now.
I'll have enough to buy another purple.
Rock slide?
Where is the rock slide?
Oh, come on.
Fuck you.
Fuck!
Okay, it's kind of fun.
It's kind of fun, but I got...
I had to fight like three enemies
and I fucked up and I blew myself up in the first two seconds.
I was thinking like slow him
and then maybe get him with a magic missile.
I don't know.
Haste always first.
Can I cast it on myself?
What do you got on you?
Nice...
Oh, nice duck.
Haste then invis.
Yeah, you can give buffs to enemies.
That's true.
I've actually seen it happen.
You're yelling a lot.
Oak is a good mage.
You can probably give some pointers.
Maybe, yeah.
It's happened to my buddy Eric.
Oh, shit.
Buddy Eric died, nice.
Did I do it?
Okay, I did it.
Fuck, that's a long lead time.
What is happening?
Oh, they're homing missiles, kind of.
Is that for me?
Move speed, weapon damage.
Wait, does it actually count as a staff?
Like can I use it as a staff?
What's the meditate button?
This is very dangerous.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I didn't know what to do.
I feel like I was just dead no matter what there.
Use invisibility and run.
I should probably put that on.
You cast haste on him?
That wasn't slow?
That was definitely slow.
Wizard is really hard to play on the Goblin map.
I feel like Wizard's probably really hard to play
on any map.
And you just really need to learn how to play and get good.
But yes, I do agree.
This is probably a bad place to try to learn how to play Wizard.
If I just, okay.
So is that always on me?
It is, all right.
I just missed every single shot.
I thought I was homing.
Oh, shoot.
Okay, that's pretty fun.
I need, okay, I need to meditate somewhere.
I'm gonna do it here, who cares?
You almost chain lightning to yourself.
That can happen, that's true.
Like everything, kind of.
All right, what about anything?
I need to meditate again.
Is it going on?
Is there a way to get spells back better than this?
Or you just have to do, you just have to get, okay.
That's not too bad.
I think there's a portal underneath me.
I saw a bunch of blue.
Whatever, don't cast that.
Oh, fuck.
Oh no, I didn't see this.
I just need to get out of here.
If you get out with some gold, Alchemist sells spell books.
True, I'm gonna try to get out though.
I have nothing to do with this shit.
Oh, this is ugly.
Look at all these fucking spiders.
Oh, come on, man.
Oh my God, there's shit everywhere.
What killed me?
A trap on the ground.
It's so stressful.
I juked so many people there
and a trap on the ground is pitch black.
I was the last player too.
I feel like I'd rather go against groups
than any of the PvE.
I feel like I just, when you run out of spells,
you kind of just in trouble.
Crystal Sword is good.
You can always buy one too.
Drink some water.
I got a big, big water right here.
I'm good to go.
One, you're gonna let one bug kill you, man.
Come on, what's this?
How did I end up in the same corner?
Oh, it's because you're red.
Okay, I get it.
I didn't want to do that.
Did that waste a spell?
Get off that!
That, I was so far away.
That goes very, oh, don't breathe that.
That goes really far.
Water makes it go farther.
Very good to know.
Thank you.
You're in the worst possible spot you could be in.
I want to just get out and make a little bit of money.
Hey, I'm showing my friends at college your stream.
Can you say something funny?
All of you in the room right now, go do your homework.
If you already did, good for you.
You should eat Cheetos.
You should split a bag of Cheetos.
Not one bag each of you.
Split a bag of Cheetos.
It's battening shit.
Hey, what was that?
Where did, what happened here?
That was very strange.
Very strange, very strange.
They went through the ceiling.
What?
Hold on, what happened?
Was he behind the pillar?
I heard footsteps, footsteps, footsteps.
And then he was above you and jumped down.
This is not the kind of class I can play.
It's too much like micromanagement.
Picking up items, like going like this.
I'm like, what spell is this?
I don't know how to do this one.
And then attack and then meditate.
Someone's going to just going to,
I'm literally going to be tunnel vision.
Someone's going to jump down and axe me in the head.
Why do that when a barbarian can hit you in the head
and kill you in two hits?
Better for when you're in a group.
I've actually seen some cracked out wizard gameplay.
I watched Moon Moon play with wizard for a little bit.
And he was so unbelievably good.
I thought he was hacking.
It was like, he was just like,
he like killed six people at one point in a row.
And I was just like, holy shit.
He's so good.
How do you get that good?
It was mind boggling.
Get this fucking shit off my screen.
I can't play wizard.
I actually could see how this would be like in a group.
Standing still in this game for more than a second or two
is just, I just, I feel naked.
I'm like already dead too.
Oh God, fuck that.
I've got nothing to do with this.
Your loot sucks.
You may as well be.
Please don't kill me.
Please.
I'll try this one more time.
But I need to play in a group.
You can fireball the door.
Oh shit, I didn't know that.
Please try rogue.
I'll play rogue next time I play.
Next time I stream.
I'm streaming this on Friday.
Friday will be rogue day.
Let me at least try to get
at least somewhat anything going with this character.
I just made fucking popcorn.
Anybody want some?
Go back to, so bad.
Yeah, I got, I don't, I gotta learn,
I gotta learn how to play with this character.
I've played, almost every moment of my time
has been on fighter.
I'm like holding right click to block.
It's been like 15 hours on one character.
What did you eat for breakfast?
Two ovaries, the eggs.
Early game, no gear wizard.
I feel like if I, if I, I feel like I can't engage.
I have to stop engaging enemies.
Only if there's like one or two.
You can't just like walk around.
I have to get out at least once.
They have to be really far away too.
I keep walking.
Oh, there's enemies.
I'm gonna cast my spells right here.
And they're as far away as the fucking torches.
They're just dead.
Okay, anything else?
I think the fire on the ground.
I can't believe you actually hit me.
That's weird.
I feel like you shouldn't have.
No, don't.
Water sap is strong.
Magic missile seems really, really good.
Oh, that was unfortunate.
What the hell just happened?
Was that a player?
Oh, I'm so fucking in trouble here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
Why is, what is going on?
This skeleton's a barbarian?
What?
What's happening?
He's, oh, he's got the skin.
I thought he was a fucking NPC.
What?
I thought he was one of the skeletons in this room.
And when he started just chasing me like crazy and throwing bombs.
And I was like, what's happening?
They all have it?
Damn.
Okay.
Oops.
I didn't mean to exit the whole game.
I'm going to do three more.
Three more and I'll play Rogue.
Bloody mouth.
How does this work?
Let's find out.
Lockpick.
The next successful attack causes the target to bleed
because this is the bleed and this is stealth.
Okay.
If you're hiding, you can move 10 steps.
Let's give it a go.
Yeah, I'll do three more.
Only three more.
I want to, I don't know how to overdo it.
This does not have a right click.
That's, now if I stab, it's going to be poison.
Let's try it on somebody.
Okay.
Three more.
So how to, biting NPCs.
PVE.
Run around, dodge and stuff.
Press the wrong button.
That's poison.
Is there anyone to tell if it's ticking?
Or is it just on them?
I just have to assume that it's on, right?
It's fun.
Let me try this.
So I'm, all right.
So I'm invisible right now.
So I can go one.
Wait, I thought I could walk.
I thought I could do 10 steps.
Oh, it's only while crouching.
Okay.
Well, I'm just dead.
We're, god, dude.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
No, yeah.
Listen.
Listen to him.
No.
Help me.
Help me just go.
Help.
Everyone in this room is going to die.
Everybody in this room is going to die.
I'm just saying.
Like this, they're not going to make it out of this.
There's so many people.
I hit exit game again.
Oh my god.
I'm just getting fucking tired now.
Shit.
Somebody saying I'm not doing poison.
I think I am.
Rupture?
Oh, wait a minute. That's not poison. Wait. Poisoned weapon.
Mmm.
So this is just a bleed. Bleed and poison stacked. They stack together, I'm imagining, right?
Yeah, there we go. Okay.
Alright, two more.
Why are we resorting to violence?
You gotta do three more and one comedy run.
Hmm. We'll see. She knows.
Bro sucks.
That's a horrible room.
I'm friendly.
Yeah, I'm friendly, bro.
Excellent.
You need any healing?
Uh, let me see.
Nah, I'm good. How you doing?
Alright, bro. I'm chilling.
Let's loot this room. There's a lot of stuff in here. Be careful though, there's demons.
What the hell?
Wait, hell just kind of just went to zero. I don't know what happened. I don't know.
The poison killed me?
The goblin spell did a U-turn.
That guy is going to be talking to me because there's no possible way that I die there.
He's probably still talking to me. And I've just been gone for 30 straight seconds.
Hmm. This game is so fun.
Alright, let me get a good one. I feel like I haven't had a good one in at least five to ten attempts.
It's been a bunch of horse shit.
Everybody stop everything we're doing.
Little Caesar's pretzel crust pizza is back.
My jaw is hitting the floor right now.
Can I actually break this with this weapon?
Or what? That's weird.
No, I can't. That's annoying.
Okay, I got a big problem.
And it's called, I keep forgetting which is bound to what.
I got to...what? Okay, it's on my thumb buttons that's why.
And they're right next to each other and it takes me a minute to figure it out.
I'm not going this way.
That's so annoying.
Stuck. Stuck. Stuck.
I'm going to step on the trap in a second, aren't I?
Oh my god, do I not have that perk? Did I switch it out? I was crouched.
I'm so confused.
Oh, poison.
Swing!
It's doing that thing again.
I hear somebody.
Fuck you.
Barbarian?
There's a barbarian somewhere right here.
What happened? This is a wall, I think.
Shit, I got to put that on a different keybind.
I keep, like, almost accidentally pressing it.
I need to pick it like a Q or something, because it's so hard for my brain to be like,
thumb button one.
And it's like, which one is that?
Is that the one that's closer to me or the one that's further away?
And I'm like, thumb button four. Which one is that?
Is that the one that's closest to me?
Thank you.
Stuck again.
Oh my goodness.
I was, like, wedged in between all three of their heads.
I have to leave at least a dollar.
So, stabbing.
You have to get it.
So, let me just make sure I know what's happening here.
Is it only that tiny little crosshair where you can actually hit?
Because I feel like I'm trying to hit the blade sort of on them.
It has to be directly like a little plate fighter for way too long.
Hey, we'll get a couple bucks.
That's pretty good.
14.
Let's go!
Oh, I only have 11.
Alright, last one.
This is the last one.
Yep, the demo's on the Steam Playtest demo thing.
Till the 13th.
If you want to play it, you've got three and a half days.
Three days or so.
No thanks.
Shit.
Alright, fighting people on stairs.
It's just not fun.
That's better.
Does the rogue get some kind of self-heal eventually or no?
Is somebody coming?
You gonna come down this hall?
Hmm?
Wait, yeah!
They weren't aggro'd before.
What?
I didn't even, I walked further away, not closer.
This sucks.
Out of the fryer.
And into the fryer later.
As they say.
It's good, bro.
Out of the fryer later.
And into the frying pan.
Hey.
Need some help?
If you had a heal, I would be so happy.
Yeah, I got you, bro.
Oh my goodness, that's so good.
You saved my life.
Here.
I got you, bro.
As long as you don't, you know, like stab me in the back or something.
But you will.
Thanks, bro.
So?
Yeah, we're friendly.
We're friendly.
Need all the friends we can get in this dump.
How the one of you need healing at all?
Can I have another one?
I don't want to be greedy.
I got you.
Not so good.
Go.
Let's try.
Wait, we're all friendly.
Let's go kill the main boss guy.
He's right over here.
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Yeah, what are we doing?
We could also play Duck Duck Goose to see who has to get killed.
The real boss is down here.
Jesus fuck.
It's just, you know, to get by.
For the guild.
Oh my God, he's gonna kill me.
No, I'm fine.
I've never seen this thing die before.
What do you have on him?
Well, sanctuary.
Come here, come here, come here.
Purple mace, bro.
Oh, that's pretty sweet.
Oh, hell yeah.
Thanks, bro.
Some really nice people.
You take it since you just got a purple thing.
Yeah, get out of here, man.
Thanks, bro.
Take the thing and stash it.
Does anyone need any extra healing at all before I go?
All right, I got you.
Hold on.
Hot.
What?
He's lied.
Oh my goodness.
And right when we talked about friends and friendship and companionship.
Bro's backstabbed.
I thought you just hit me and I was about to cry.
There was a spike in the wall.
Okay.
Did he die?
No.
Okay.
I thought he died.
What a dick.
Guys, I already killed the troll.
You did?
Oh, good stuff.
He looks dead.
Any scraps?
You got the purple.
You should take it.
And then he just walks in it.
Oh, I don't know which side it is.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
We got to find you a portal.
Friends.
I'm going to open this up.
The cleric's got to take this.
We're all going to pick numbers.
Okay, that works.
Bro, just fucking run in.
No, no, no.
Unfortunate.
Chill, chill, chill.
We're all fucked here anyways.
You be having it.
How do we get you out of here with that purple?
I don't know.
I should probably stop saying that out loud, by the way.
Yeah, probably.
Come here.
It's like I'm trying to get him killed.
You need to get out of here with that purple.
I'm trying to be like...
What?
Was that him?
Where is it?
I need to give it back to him.
How did he die?
What if this is not it?
Somebody took it.
Who took that mace?
I need to know.
What mace?
Who took the mace?
No, I tried.
I had to get revenge.
That was so sad.
That was sad.
I was sitting there talking to him, and he's dead.
What killed him?
That guy was so nice, too.
He was healing.
Hey, anybody else need to be topped off?
Oh, yeah, sure, man.
I do.
Oh, yeah, here.
No good deed.
It was unfunished, unfortunately.
Hey, I was trying to tell him to just run in.
Can't trust anybody.
You really can't?
Yeah, a shitload of subs came in.
Oh, my God.
I don't really shout subs out.
I don't shout subs or bits or donations or anything like that out.
But Jesus, it's completely unnecessary.
But I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Oh, boy, I'm already dead here.
Not if I go invisible.
Whatever.
That one doesn't count?
No, it doesn't.
Let me play one more to get the character I know how to play.
This game is so addicting.
There's something about it.
We're getting the comedy run.
Oh, I think that one was a comedy run.
Last one, Larry?
Yeah.
Can't trust anybody.
Oh, man.
It's a cool purple, too.
And it's like, wow, a cool purple.
It's not always a bad start.
Swing.
Sometimes, man, this game ran away.
I feel the most safe with Fighter.
I know it's a default class, but still.
Are they actually going to put a bard in?
That'd be fun, actually.
What?
They use it now, unfortunately.
Was the pretzel cross pizza thing actually back,
or was that person just saying that
and now just severely pissed me off?
Got your back.
Ooh, that's good.
We could get that middle group.
Actually, I got to leave.
Coming soon.
Want to go for the middle group?
You think we can take them?
Think so.
Oh, my God, that hurt a lot.
I'm so slow.
Oh, my God, that's doing so much damage to me.
We got to loot and get out of here.
Actually, pick it up and give one of them.
We got to go.
I'm going to use the campfire.
Let's go in a safe place and use the...
Nowhere else really to do this, and I need it right now.
We're in the circle.
Yep.
Oh, shit.
Portal somewhere around here.
Shit went down over here on the portal.
This is dangerous down here.
I don't think we want to go down here.
Yeah, that's just certain death.
Friendly.
I'm not one of those backstabbers.
Oops.
He's looking around.
Oh, no.
Ah, shit.
I almost did it too.
Can I have another one of those heels?
Oh, shit.
Hey, come take this cabinet.
You got any more of those heels on you?
Oh, no.
We got to fight for this.
We have to fight for this.
I'm sorry.
Don't we?
All right, good luck.
I was willing to do a duel for it.
You know what I mean?
If I want to go, you want to go.
I mean, we could have fought to the death for it, I think.
And I think that's a fair way to do it.
Still a clerk?
Can live a pretty long time in the dust.
Is there still a portal?
Oh, there's one right there.
You got it.
It's so close.
Please.
No.
Oh, yes.
All right.
Good.
We're good.
Damn.
Just barely.
I want to make sure you made it out alive.
That's a lot of stuff.
Get rid of it.
Damn.
85 gold.
Nice.
I'll keep the...
I got to start collecting kind of middle of the road shitty gear.
I feel like I just dump everything.
What's that in the corner?
It's been like a weird bug.
I can't like scroll over it.
Weird.
It won't let me.
It's like a little force field or something.
All right.
Last one.
Final one.
This is truly the final one.
It's like 2 a.m.
And I got to eat some more food.
Oh, well.
This game really is really fun though.
Even though I'm not very good at it.
There's something about it.
The treachery.
The companionship.
There's so much...
You know what?
It feels like there's so much heartbreak.
It feels like every two or three rounds,
there's a story that's been told.
It's cool.
I like it.
It reminds me of the way people acted in the TF2 days.
Just that goofy shit that was constantly happening.
People just randomly RPing for no reason.
People walking into traps and dying.
Not the sandwich heavy shit.
Like it just reminds me of those old days of...
You kind of never know what's going to happen.
Which means it's worth playing over and over again.
And I'll be honest, if anything can scratch that itch again,
I'm going to play it.
And that's what's happening.
I think the guy running in to try to fight the troll.
Oh, hey, yeah.
Let's fight it.
And he dies in one hit.
That person told a whole story in two minutes.
It was hilarious.
You're going to hate this game in a week.
Well, I won't be able to because it's not going to be playable in a week.
So getting just enough.
No, no, no.
We got to fight.
How are you still alive, man?
Come on, dude.
Archers still right here.
There's two archers.
This is bad.
What?
I'm so tilted by that that I'm like...
Two archers.
You may as well just leave the room.
Because your opportunity to attack is just gone completely.
That didn't count.
This is actually the last one because I'm starting to get like foggy.
This is not the type of game you play when you're like foggy, tired.
Oh, this is exactly when I wanted to play and how long I wanted to play.
Yeah, this is it.
Let's do it.
Definitely not bringing this weander out.
No way.
Oh, yeah, foggy, foggy.
It's like I'm looking through a fucking foggy window right now.
You're going to do this to me twice in a row.
Don't get overwhelmed.
They're going to be spawning over and over again, but they're not red.
Good.
Coins.
I would like to get out of here with a bunch of stuff.
Oh, that's good.
Very, very nice.
What on earth are you doing?
Stop doing that.
Why is it doing that?
Let's go.
Good morning.
How are you?
Who is your daddy?
And what does he do?
It's better not be a mimic.
I'm going to ask you a bunch of questions and I want to have them answered immediately.
Who is your daddy?
What does he do?
Well, I hope you leave enough room for my fist because I'm going to ram it into your stomach.
Goodbye.
I heard portal and I would love to find it.
Was that behind me or this is the place to be to look at?
Yes, he missed and hit me.
Shit.
You fucking around?
Oh, you are fucking around, aren't you?
Oh shit, portal down there.
Fuck.
I don't care anymore about fighting anybody.
Portal down.
I don't want to fight you.
You're shooting arrows at me though.
Where is it?
What the fuck was somebody behind me?
There was a fucking guy behind me.
It wasn't there.
I would have had that too.
Fuck.
Goblin was hitting me from behind.
How much damage?
Did you take more damage from behind?
I feel like I could have gotten out of that too.
I tried to jump around, but I bumped into the fucking lamp post and everything is just collision in this game.
I just fell straight down.
I don't want to use it.
That hurt somebody who's behind me right now.
Okay, I got some pretty good stuff.
I got to actually hunker down here.
Why you both have the same animation right now?
You became an EU streamer.
Yeah, technically, right?
No bullshit here.
That's the secret escape tunnel.
Are you going to shoot?
Why are they all acting like this?
They're scared of me.
I want to loot this room so bad, but that's not happening.
I guess maybe I could.
Oh, you little shit.
Just die.
How many hits is this guy going to take?
I've hit him five times.
Oh, would you just fuck off already?
Whatever.
I heard it.
Where was it?
I don't know where it is though.
You know what?
You little fuck face.
I'm going to enjoy this.
So much good stuff.
So much for the tunnel now.
How do I go through the tunnel?
Is it just open?
Wait, I can just leave?
Did I win?
Holy shit.
Yeah.
It's worth a lot.
Goodness.
No, I'll keep these.
Why do I have this?
All right, one more.
I'm going to stab him.
I'm going to stab him like this.
I'm going to...
Tell me if this sounds funny.
If I kill somebody, I'm going to...
I have to say that.
I want to be able to see you.
Do it when you die.
Yeah.
Okay.
Was it supposed to be a voice filter?
Yes, there is.
Can you not hear anything?
There's not.
Yeah, you can.
Hey, you guys are messing with me, right?
Too subtle.
How about this?
Is this subtle enough for you?
Don't run.
You've ruined everything because now I can't open the chests.
Blah.
Oh, this is very bad too.
I'm going down.
Fuck it.
Not putting up with...
There's a bug behind me.
The worst bugs in the game.
I hate those things so much.
Dark and darker.
Oh shit, bro.
What have you done?
What did you bring in here?
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh shit.
Oh no.
All right, I'm going to bed.
I'm out of here.
I can't end on that one.
I wonder what that must have looked like on their screen.
So many things were buying them.
Oh, please.
I feel like I've picked this up a lot.
You made it through my entire work night.
Yeah.
I mean, well, it's not going to be around.
And I know if I don't get my fill of this,
I'm going to be disappointed that I didn't.
Shit going down over there.
Swing, please.
Now's the time to bug out.
You kill one, two more spawn.
Very nice.
Hot inside of a pod.
Double lantern hog.
Who's breaking those pots up there?
Stop breaking my pots.
It's taking me so long to put them in those pots.
Stop doing that.
Let's freak that person out.
Come on.
Nice.
Oh my goodness.
I didn't even realize what was happening.
I'm taking my sweet ass time here.
I don't care.
I want to.
I'm looting it.
Fuck you.
Where is it?
Fucking just heard it.
Fucking die.
Oh my God.
Why do you have more health than these assholes?
I wasn't trying to sneak up on you.
I was trying to go around you because I thought you were going
to try to kill me.
So I tried to avoid you.
There's a portal right now.
These red spiders.
They're going to screw everything up for us.
No.
Of course.
Why are they aggro to me the whole time?
They're aggro to me.
He's standing still.
Why are they just running in a circle around me?
Why did they not attack him?
What the fuck?
Where is it?
Is it not up right?
I heard it.
It's up or down a floor.
Oh, I hate this shit.
Because by the time that this stuff spawns,
you're fucking in the red.
And everyone's beat up.
Everyone's happy.
I thought that was in the person.
Go down?
I honestly just don't even know how to go down.
I'm going to go.
I heard another one.
No, I thought it was over here.
Stay here?
I mean, I hate that it spawns below you
and the fucking red circle's already here.
They've all already spawned.
God.
Good luck finding it.
The fact that there's three levels here,
at the very end, when there's nowhere to go,
if one spawns above or below, it just fucks you.
Too many layers.
I was going to win that one, too.
You know what?
No, I'm not being nice anymore.
I'm just killing anyone I come across.
To be fair, though, I wasn't being nice.
I was genuinely afraid of that guy.
It's different.
Running around in circles with these two spiders.
And this guy's just like, do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Nothing even attacks him.
I'm running around.
I got these spiders chasing my ass.
That guy wrote a whole book report.
Nope.
That's not happening.
Whoa!
That actually scared the shit out of me.
My whole body hurts.
I thought that was a player.
Goodness.
Please.
Did I even aggro this many monsters?
When did that happen?
Oh, it's over.
Oh, come on.
I can't go out on that.
That sucked.
God damn it.
I mean, maybe if I just keep walking them around.
Where are they all coming from?
The whole fucking floor is aggro'd to me.
What the hell?
All right, no matter what, this is the last one.
Is it?
This is the last one.
If this is not the last game, because I need to go to bed.
If this is not the last game, then I will eat a pair of shoes on camera.
The last game for tonight.
I'm going to play again probably on Friday.
I mean, just for this period right now, this stream right now,
I will eat a pair of shoes on camera if this is not the last one,
because I got to go to bed.
But I love this game.
It's fun.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
What are you doing?
You okay?
Things going all right?
The game lagged a little.
You saw what happened.
Elderly man in Las Vegas.
He won't go to bed.
Final attack.
I didn't even want to aggro these and now I have to fight him.
All right, please just leave me alone.
I'm going to close the door.
Whatever.
He was just acting weird.
What?
Oh, well, come on then.
You're going to come down here then come over here.
You got to be kidding me.
Oh my goodness.
This is bad.
This is very bad.
Stupid.
You're stupid.
Do I just eat the pair of shoes and not even care?
Shit.
All right.
I'm out.
I'll see you later.
It's fun.
I still think this is too hard though.
I love it.
No fun didn't for you.
I want to do this.
I this is so stressful, but I want to do it.
Part of me feels like you gear up here and you take your gear here,
but I almost feel like I could play here without needing being being
able to be geared because you need to be kind of geared for this.
I went to sleep and you're still streaming.
Show stash.
Right.
Let me make some people very happy, right?
No, no, no, no.
I like my stray gold coins.
One more.
No, I just thought I was going to eat a pair of shoes if I did one more
and I yeah, I'm very tired.
Oh my elbow.
I was going to smell it.
Fuck you.
Just so anytime I open my stash people just like whoa, dude.
What is going on with you?
I'm going to bed.
I'll see you later.
I was going to write a huge you.
Well, now I got to fix it.
Let me fix it.
Is there an auto corrected like an auto stash button?
Waiter.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Yeah.
I'm out.
Take care.
Thanks for watching everybody.
See you guys on Friday for more.
And then I think what's probably on Saturday or Sunday,
unless I don't know.
Ster and I were planning on doing some Elden Ring,
but you know, who knows?
It'll be dark and darker again.
Ster is going to be very upset if he hears that.
Don't tell him that.
Hey, dude.
Jerma was talking about how he wanted to maybe play dark and
darker instead on like Sunday.
Don't tell him that.
No, we probably we all jokes aside.
We probably will do Elden Ring.
I don't know.
Maybe Ster gets into it.
We'll see.
So everything's all up in the air.
Everything's good, but that's going to be it.
Thanks for watching everybody.
See you guys on Friday starting kind of probably around this
maybe a little bit earlier defending but probably around
the same time kind of a night streamer.
Now, I really like it.
I like this schedule.
I know a lot of people are not going to be happy to hear
that, but yeah, that was a lot of fun Friday going to try
to cycle in some other people.
I know Italics mentioned he kind of wanted to play it.
I was kind of pinging people to see me and Will.
Me and Will Neff were talking about it to try to find the
right opportunity to play.
Maybe he's very good people.
So also if poke wants to play like I would play with poke
and a lot of people are playing this right now.
So obviously want to try to jump around and play as many
people as I can.
Well, it's while it's live gonna be a lot of credits.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
Yeah, all the all the subs from Ashley.
Yeah, I don't those of you that don't know.
I don't shout out subs anymore.
I really appreciate anybody that subs to this channel,
but there are a lot of people on Twitch on YouTube,
whatever.
I think your sub would probably better used on them.
I do appreciate the support.
I know it's some it's crazy to see that kind of support
but there's definitely a lot of people on this platform
that you should be given that to but I appreciate it.
People are already in pokes chat telling you want to play
LOL.
That's how this that's how the streamers communicate.
You know streamer one says, oh, yeah, that would be fun.
And then streamer ones chat goes to streamer twos chat
immediately saying let's go that's how it works.
Yeah, we communicate through proxy.
That's true.
This game sucks play Steve Jackson sorcery the greatest
game ever made in the history of mankind.
This game definitely does not suck.
Please finish sorcery.
Yeah, I know once some of this new stuff dies down.
There'll be a lot of stuff to just jump into was last time
we felt this way about a game maybe Fistful of Frags
Elden Ring Bloodborne.
I mean if you're talking about multiplayer games and
Fistful of Frags is probably the last one I would tell
I think Fistful of Frags is one of the best FPS is to
ever be made that game was so unbelievably fun.
I've said that on camera before that's one of the best
FPS is playing Fistful of Frags when you got that
that 007 Golden Eye Golden Gun the thing that killed
people in one shot, but it was super slow.
It was ba-boom, ba-boom.
I loved that weapon.
You found it.
It had six bullets in it Walker.
Yep.
Maybe we'll play that too.
Some point that game is so good.
Don't worry.
I'm going to send more to smaller streamers.
Oh hell.
Yeah.
Good to know also take care of yourself too, though.
I don't know what your financial situation looks like
and I'm not going to pretend to but take care of yourself
too.
That's important.
They added horses ones.
You can ride.
I'll see you guys Friday Friday evening.
Thanks to obviously the Vinnie, Ster, Caleb.
I want to try to jump in a game with Kraiken too.
Kraiken and the group he was playing with.
We had a DM group where we just kind of like oh who's
around and they we kind of filled out and we had two
different separate groups going so try to get a few
games to Kraiken as well this Friday.
Yeah, take care of yourselves.
Good night.
Get some water get some sleep or good morning.
See you soon.
Have a great night or enjoy your breakfast.
See you later.