Well, you have to put it in the pot for two hours.
Yeah, but what's the temperature in it?
It sits in the pot for two hours. You have to cook it for two hours, otherwise it's not gonna work.
I get it. What temperature does it have to be set at?
It's a fucking pot roast. You can't screw it up. Get out. I'm doing a video.
What's the... I need to tell you...
Get out!
Oh, Jesus.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here.
And today, I've got a special fucking video for you.
Because I got access to Cube World.
Okay, so this is Jerma's file. We can go ahead and fucking delete that.
Start a new file for Grandpa's character. Let's get going there. Create. Click it, baby.
Was that a guitar?
I don't want to play the musician.
There's a musician, we got ear musician, we got drunk guy, we got Gremlin from Gremlins 2.
It was a pretty good movie, but I don't really want to play as a Gremlin.
We got the drunk goblin. I don't like the drunk goblin. The lizard, I like lizard people.
Undead, I don't think I want to play. Fucking frog people.
I'm playing as a fucking frog man. I'm not even going to go any further on the characters.
So what you do in Minecraft is pretty simple. You go around and you collect resources and you fight monsters.
What the hell is that? What the fuck is this? What is going on here?
What is this, a Ninja Turtles? What the fuck are the Ninja Turtles doing in this game?
Look, it's Leonardo that's trying to tell him behind him.
What are you doing in this game? I don't, I have no, what am I supposed to even be doing?
Does anybody know what you're doing in this game?
I have not figured out, all I've done is, was that a bee? It's a fucking bee.
Come on, you bee bitch.
You see, the real awesome part about this game is the fact that I'm battling right now as a frog.
There's never been a game in existence where you could fight people as frogs.
It just never existed and that's why I like it.
And that's the five experience points right there, ladies and gentlemen.
I just figured out how to play Cube World.
I'm concerned about the people who made this game because they're going to get fucking sued.
First, this is Ninja Turtles and then look, it's the Seven Dwarfs.
Disney is going to have a field day with these guys.
I can look at the Snuffy, that's Gruffy, that's Poopy and Snoopy. See, that's the Seven Dwarfs.
How are they not going to get sued by this?
I really am concerned. Let me go get a closer look here.
All right, Fluffy, you need to go back to Disney World because I said so.
What? They just melted me.
The Seven Dwarfs didn't have those fucking powers.
Would you look who it is, everybody?
It's Donatello by himself without his boys.
Hey, Donnie, how are you? How are the rest of the Ninja Turtles?
Yeah, without them you aren't so fucking tough now, are you?
Got something to say?
I have my own house.
Donatello, I think you might have a brain injury.
Somebody help me, somebody please help me.
I got a bunch of animals following me.
I got like two animal bug birds.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Leave him alone.
What did he do?
Why did they do that to him, you bullies, you savages, you beasts?
No, leave him alone.
All he wanted was some bird seed. I have it in my pocket.
What about this bird? This bird's like, fuck that.
I want nothing to do with this.
He has absolutely nothing to do with this.
Well, it looks like all your friends are dead.
He's like, fuck that, dude.
All right, I guess I'll help you, you know, whatever.
I can't believe I'm still dead.
I'm dead.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay, I kind of feel bad about what just happened.
How did I end up in a tree?
What?
Hello, Mr. Peacock, how are you?
How are you today?
Yes, I smell good, thank you.
I've got some trouble here.
Oh, my God.
Kick his ass.
Kick his fucking ass.
Look at this animation.
Look at this awesome animation.
He's skiing at him.
Look at this.
Oh, my goodness gracious, you are...
Oh, he died.
Now I'm sad.
I keep killing birds in this game.
I feel terrible.
I'm a bird killer.
But to be fair here, guys, he did do that on his own.
I didn't ask him to.
He just flipped the fuck out and started skiing at the guy.
And you know what?
That's what we shoot in the clouds.
I like this game.
Some kind of encampment over here.
Looks like there could be some food and some supplies.
There is nothing special.
Well, there is some stuff here.
Is this yours?
Hey, Mr. Swimman, hey, come on up here.
I want to talk to you.
Do you own this camp?
How did you build this?
Come on up here.
You want to make some food and stuff?
We could be friends.
No, okay, don't want to be friends.
You just dug your own grave.
See you later.
Get fucking rapid fired.
That's how you do it, ladies and gentlemen.
You take his money.
And then you go back and you take his food, too.
That pineapple is mine.
You had your chance to be friendly.
Just wanted to share.
Mmm, this is going to taste real good, baby.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.