Hello, good afternoon. How are you doing? Are you doing good? Good. Peaceful Haley, thanks to the
six community subs right now. I'd like to welcome you away. You welcome, you can welcome me back.
I'll welcome you back at the same time. Ready? Welcome back. What are you guys saying shoo for?
Shoo, shoo. Right, right, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I can't fucking make a joke on Twitter.
Not allowed to make a joke on Twitter. That's what that was about. I mean, no, no, no, no, no.
Season premiere. I am not going to eat a shoo. Like, at this point, the shoo thing is,
that's like a channel joke at this point. That's a channel meme at this point. It doesn't, it doesn't
mean anything. It's, I'm not actually going to do that. If you think I'm actually going to do that,
then come on. You lied again. I didn't lie about anything. It's a, we make jokes on this comedy
stream. That's unfunny. Unfunny riot, right? We trusted you. Just what? Hold on. Comrad Castro,
thanks for the five. Community subs, appreciate it. You make a statement about fucking sans in
Smash Brothers. One day I'm going to unsub from you. Jeff, one day I'm going to unsub from you.
God damn it. Oh God. Can we please get over this? Guys, as a community, can we? All right, hold on.
Can we please? Can we get over this as a community, please? Why is it so big? Why,
I look professional right now. That shouldn't be happening. Nice hair. I can't get a haircut.
I was actually thinking about this. I was thinking about going and I was going to have Kim do this
for me. Oh shit, I moved that wrong way. Can we get over this shit though? Please? Yes, I'm still
in the old place, but I got news for you. Every place in Vegas, whether it's an apartment, a house
or a condo is the same house. They only make like three different places out here. When eventually
I'm in a new place, you're going to be like, oh shit, that looks, I'm not even going to tell
you when I move. You'll have to figure it out. Squeegee? Why are people saying squeegee? I know
there's a delay. There should be because we're about to play the Wii. We had a pre-stream chat
vote, but it shouldn't be delayed. Hold on. Let me do this. I mean, it's going to look, it's going
to look a little different for the first few minutes. It's delayed. You look sleepy? It's
because I am. It's because I am. I got like a fucking weird neck. It's an extreme delay. Shoo,
shoo, shoo. I, I, we gotta, I'm, I'm, get it off! Is that what you want? Can we get over this, please?
Can we get over this shit, please? If you think I'm going to eat this, you're out of your fucking
mind. Yeah, I'll take, can I take a bite and will you guys get over this? If I take a bite of this,
will you get over it? It's not as bad as I thought it was going to be. It tastes kind of like shit
though. Wait a minute. I'm not even stepping shit. Relax. It was a joke. Okay. I'll take,
should I take another bite of this shoe? This fucking shoe? I can't believe it. Eat the bottom.
I'm not going to eat the bottom of the shoe. I'm going to eat, I'm going to do, I'm going to do it
the way that I want to do it, not the way that you want me to do it. You can't eat a whole shoe
in five seconds. Holy shit, guys. Put it back on. I can't put it on. Not yet. I can't put it on.
Come on. I'm going to try over here. Wear the socks. It's fucking winter time. You don't wear
socks. Fucking Sans. It should never have been in the game. It's not even a Nintendo character.
If Sans is in Smash Brothers now, then Scrooge McDuck better be next week.
I don't need any more shoes for new characters. Strong teeth? No, these are special shoes.
No, my shoes are made out of fucking cotton. I have very dainty, I have very sensitive feet.
So they need to be put into these comfy shoes. This is gross. But you have to be a man of your
word. And I'm a man of my word. Should I put it back on? One more from the bottom?
He's a starving crack addict. No, I'm a man of my shoe eating word. Oh, it's not good. Oh,
sorry. Oh, I got some shoe residue on my hand. It's hot out. It's hot out here in Vegas. So
shoes melt. If you wear shoes made out of glycerin or whatever my shoes are made out of. I don't know.
The doctor does them. I don't. Oh shit actually says that. It doesn't. No, it doesn't. No, it
doesn't. No, it doesn't. No, it doesn't. No, it doesn't. Oh, excuse me. No, it doesn't.
No, it doesn't. That's, that's, that's water. I can't eat any more of this. This is
it eat the heel this is a shitty shoe i've told these were 600 dollars i don't know how you go
about eating through this wear it i can't wear it right now okay do you understand i can't wear
this right now i don't have any socks on i can't put this on you guys i'm looking right at you
no now i am i'm looking over the chat but i can't put this on right now i need to put on a pair of
socks and i'll put it on all right one more bite one more bite from the back god damn it i'm gonna
have fucking diarrhea later guaranteed i can't i can't okay it's like when you order the big mac
and you and you like and you have to open your mouth really wide to take a bite the first bite
the first bite of the big mac is always the worst one i know this is what it tastes like you're a
freak this is kind of weird isn't it this is real weird this might be the weirdest thing i've done
on stream ever i've done a lot of fucking weird things this is pretty odd huh huh pretty odd i'm
gonna put it on non-branded by the way i'm not go okay let me i'm gonna let's be let's be really
clear here this is real close to being fucked up okay i'm not going to like go like that okay
that's this is real close nope this is real close to being weird like really fucking weird
oh by the way this stream can't be pre-recorded can it i'm gonna go put it on i'm gonna i'm gonna
put this shoe on it i'm gonna i'm gonna walk around the room give me a second give me a second
those of you that don't think this is a real shoe by the way those of you that those of you
scientists in the chat a shoe could be classified as anything that protects your feet from the
weather okay give it back how do i get it back on i gotta get this back on it was on before
let me put it back on hold on let me let me hold on let me let me move the camera so it's in a good
spot it's gonna be the most fucked up image you're gonna see all week and it's and it's
already it's only monday all right let's put this back on move this let me just get my shoe back on
this is a this is a cheap shoe this is a cheap shoe imagine getting this shit in the fucking mail
you boy shoes oh i got these new shoes online dude they're they're supposed to be working
comfortable and it does this out of the box you'd be so fucking mad you'd be like hold on dude
these hoes were these 220 dollars they made what is it made out of all right goodbye i'll be right
back i gotta clean i gotta clean my shoe up right back we're gonna delete that one from the never
what do you mean first time viewer first time viewer pause fucking god come on i haven't started
what is first time viewer hold on wait wait wait let me see please watch this is
fucked up why is this fucked up oh no no wait this isn't even what just happened this is
i'm telling you i can't oh god who's this oh no fuck man god damn it
it's in the same spot as this yeah yeah i know i got it but i i can assume this is like somebody
with an incredibly realistic totally a total reaction that makes perfect sense
well for the stupid fucking thing that i do on the stream sometimes let me see this is probably
going to be an actual reaction that like a normal person would probably have let's see so it looks
like deal or no deal isn't really working what the fuck is this who's this
all right i'm gonna switch it to whatever fucking game that is
why does he sound like that this month so it looks like dealer no
deal why do i sound like he's bright he's bright he's got plenty of points look all right
okay i just ate a shoe on camera if somebody finds this stream and they don't know what the
fucking the the oh that's a perfectly normal reaction to have you're probably going to show
me a clip tomorrow of somebody that found this stream today and there he is eating a fucking shoe
and like screaming okay well let's go to the next stream because i don't want to i'm not going to
be here for this one what do you want why is he doing this hey by the way we're going to play
the wii today share the shoe clip that all that does is benefit me you understand that just brings
me benefit maybe not maybe not socially maybe not socially and twitch tv sense and and and view sense
numbers of how many clicks of video has received yeah doesn't help me out in any situation where
i've got to you know meet some of these people at twitchcon and say hello big bits do we oh shit
hold on oh my god i've been i've been live for like almost 30 minutes that's wicked funny though
that's unbelievable oh my fucking god holy shit so much money came in and i didn't even i wouldn't
even looking at it wicked i say yes i'm from a different part of the world than you i say
i have different cadences anyways phylacter lich 50 dollars from phylactery huge fucking money
ridiculous you actually did it it was worth the wait glad you're back good to be back good to be
back and we're going to talk about being back i'm going to talk about a few things we're going to
go over a new that's right a new a new way i'm going to do the stream i'm going to do it but
the whole what is he talking about here what's that mean just hold on tight you'll find out uh
thanks for the 5 000 bits dude seriously it's a lot of money some of you guys have given it stupid
amounts of money today and always so thanks uh we also had 10 000 bits from germa lied about
half-life alex hold on a second here if this hold on a second here why do i have to be so much
look i get it okay i don't want to even look at these there that's better listen all vr vr will
return i just have to get a little bit stronger up here and i have to get a little more less tight
i've actually been feeling a little better but there's a reason for that i think and i've gone
over it a few times it's part of the reason why we're going to change the streams this is an
important stream you don't want to miss this one stay tuned don't go anywhere what what is wrong
with me what why am i like this what that person's right why is he acting like this i don't know what
the fuck am i doing i'm excited i'm very excited about a lot of things uh but you're gonna have to
i'm sorry you're gonna have to delete that account in probably like a couple months that's the way
it is you that's not going to make any sense in about one to two months uh but thanks to the
hundred bucks germa lied about half life alex that's your name and that's your comment thank
you thanks for the hundred fucking dollars a great canadian had 15 dollars it's just it's still a
lot of money does that mean if i don't wash my socks for a few weeks i can use them as shoes
no because that doesn't protect you from the weather socks can get wet socks can you can
step on like a fucking rock and go like wow and like hurt your foot that's not accurate of one
one one m1 gave a hundred dollars in bits ten thousand bits they say best joke of 2020
we'll see we'll see there might be some competition down the road here for worst
joke oh no that was best joke right oh sorry yeah of course it was best joke of 2020 thank you
thanks for the hundred bucks freddy dread gave 200 fucking dollars we get like thousands of
dollars from freddy dread thanks a lot freddy it's fucking that's insane that's 200 fucking
dollars instantly just like that dropped into my twitch bank account thank you it's insane thank
you it's fucking a ton of money no message either by lactory another 50 dollars oh my god what all
right there's a lot of money there's a lot of money uh another 50 dollars dude that dude was
so upset that your stream had more viewers than him i don't think that's accurate i don't think
that's accurate we don't want to put words in other streamers mouths we don't want to do that
when that's not what we do here i don't think that's necessarily accurate i don't think it's
accurate okay sorry don't worry there's no no problem here but thanks to the 50 dollars
comrade castor thanks to the 5 000 bits you're looking good today gerbil hope you're enjoying
your time in quarantine keep up your streams love you thanks a lot castro we're doing our
best right everybody's trying to do their best during this whole scenario so hope you are as
well and then we had five community subs from yellow jello fellow four that's five subs that's
a lot of money that just came in oh right okay now let's talk about some things okay here we go
you ready i have i have to give you i'm not going to say the thing i'm going to say just hey let's
talk about something i'm not going to say i have uh that's 10 subs from snobosis and 10 subs from
nondescript civilian thank you guys both of you thanks for the fucking 20 subs back to back well
i am back and we should be back to kind of normal here but what is what's normal what's this is the
new stream schedule is what's going to happen i've noticed over the last six months or so
because if you don't know let me let's go over let's let's just go over very quickly tldr
i have a issue with my rib cage in my spine i have some problem we don't know if it's
costochondritis if i have arthritis we don't exactly know what exactly what's causing it
but we do have an idea right i've noticed over the last couple weeks of not really streaming that
much right so i've been moving around kim and i have been packing boxes we've been moving and
i feel a little looser and we did some streams that were shorter that were like three or four
hours last week and the week before that and i'm a little looser and i think what i'm what i'm
coming to the conclusion of this is what i've had discussions with this very thing is how do you how
do you say this word sedentary sedentary sedentary sedentary sedentary sedentary right so
when i sit here sedentary for more than four five six plus hours it hurts a lot and i've noticed
that the shorter streams i'm it doesn't hurt as much and i'm i can it's it it's easier when
i move around i can stay moving i can stay mobile so here's what i've decided to do
right all right i'm streaming i forgot um here's what i've decided to do what's going to happen
here is instead of six to eight hour streams three or four days a week i'm going to pull it back to
like four to six hour streams four to five days a week so there's going to be short and then i've
said this before like hey i'm going to do shorter streams but more we're going to pull back times
and stream more often because doing like four to six hours in and then being able to get up and
move around and i it's i don't just sit still for a very long time it helps a lot and i've been
noticing a very very huge difference only because i haven't been streaming and i've and the streams
i've been doing have been short so i'm going to keep that up i'm going to see if it helps i'm
going to see if it works so yeah you can expect instead of like three seven to eight hour plus
streams you'll get like four or five like four to six hour streams starting now starting until i
decide i want to change it or do something else it was also the idea that it was also the idea
that i would stream potentially twice a day so instead of a four to six hour stream five days
a week maybe i do like two to three hours take like a 30 40 plus minute break and come back in
an hour get some food and come back and do like another two or three hours i just have to move
around i have to there's also the idea maybe get a standing desk but the reason why i don't want to
do two streams in a day is because i i like i burn up quickly i know that a lot of guys understand
you guys get that and a lot a lot of guys know that by now and so some of these streams were
very high energy and after like three four plus hours like it's like a um what's a good analogy
to describe like something that like lights up real quick and then it's gone so if i were to do
a funnel fireworks okay yeah um no but i don't want to say that that's like a cheesy analogy
i'm a firework oh no you're not oh you you eat potato chips on the fucking couch all day like
relax but if i stream like three or four hours and then i go take like a two hour break i might
just like lose all my energy and that'll be it your sneeze yeah it comes out real quick
and really strong and it's uh no but it's like and it feels like kind of good for a second
and then you don't after like three or four you're like i want this to be over but that doesn't make
any sense because everyone around you doesn't want to be around you you guys want to be around
you know what i'm saying i don't think that works who's the sneeze in the scenario don't drop
anything you're no okay anyways i'm going to change the schedule we're not changing oh i'm
going to do monday tuesday wednesday thursday or thursday friday saturday sunday monday no the days
are going to be just kind of whenever they will be brief like no more than that like four times
five times in a row maybe four times three times day off and then one day two days i don't know
up rocks yeah yeah he's still going to be late guaranteed absolutely probably every day
okay are you ready so today we're going to do we're going to start this is deadly creatures
this was voted on by pre-stream chat oh and i'll give you i can give you this week right now
are you ready for this week's schedule today nothing tomorrow wednesday thursday friday and
maybe saturday there you go i just gave it to you you like when i do eye contact or you like when i
look at you because right now i'm i'm giving you eye contact right now like this is eye contact
but this is me looking into the webcam which one do you like more because like i'm reading your text
that's eye contact to the screen for your text webcam like this like that like addressing you
directly i'll give you three spots right here right here you know you can always tell when
someone's not looking at you directly in the eyes when somebody's not doing eye contact but
they're like pretending to right where instead of like this like this i do that all the time
i do that i do that shit all the time you like you look over like right over there like right
where their eye could be i it's hard i i'm not i'm not bad with eye contact but i it's hard for me
to do it for a long period in a row like this if i'm talking to somebody like this and we're
like having a conversation i'm what i have to be like looking around and like
oh yeah yeah so i can't believe it yeah that's unbelievable i can't do it i just get i get i get
like bored of looking at somebody's eyes i have to like look all over the room because i don't
like there could be a crack in the wall right there i just saw it to get that fixed oh sorry let me
look in your eyes and tell you that that's adhd yeah probably yeah definitely all right i'm gonna
get the fuck out of here and we're gonna play because why do i need a face cam that's unnecessary
you have a cracked lip do i another 50 fucking dollars just came in you guys are nuts 50 more
fucking dollars holy shit thank you do i need chapstick do i uh this is by sigmatic thank you
sigmatic for the 50 fucking dollars come back come back come back there once was a streamer from
brew whose chat wanted him to eat a shoe he looked up at his cam shook his head and said damn as it
seemed that the joke had come true it's pretty good all right now i gotta i gotta hold on
i gotta it's pretty fucking good this is deadly creatures this is voted on this is for the we
there's a game you play as mean scary bugs like tarantulas and scorpions and bees and shit and
apparently it's very good i have heard this is a cult classic nintendo we mode game it's supposed
to be very good and very fun we're gonna play here we go make sure you don't put a hole through
your monitor and we've got well not good why is it always a vase i'm i can't um what what do you
got a vase that close to the in the living room for does anybody have a house that has that
with this just a gigantic pillar with a vase on it like to right next to the couch well like right
next to the coffee table that's yes people do that that's aesthetic vase vase vase vase i have an
accent i'm from the shitty of washington i that's i talk like this deadly creatures
rated r let's do adventure empty are you sure you want to create save one pretty sure i do
chapter one scavengers new leaf crickets and grubs this is gonna be fucked up play easy play normal
play deadly uh we don't really oops what the fuck do we have to prove he's gonna play on normal
deadly i'm not doing why would i do that do deadly or don't play i'm gonna turn this up a little
greed can poison a man's soul turn him into something he ain't this is billy bob thorn make
him deadly even more i wouldn't say i got my revenge much playing deadly creatures on normal
that old gas station seen us last day faulty gas turning the game up hold on george strugs
no matter what the news said the cops found a stash of gold coins with spanish writing on
why is this so quiet believe it in cursed treasure i think it was just my bad choices
bad instincts that got me this time same as always same as always and george strugs the cops ask him
what happened right before how much do you think billy bub thorn charges an hour he kept mumbling
something about well the deathliest creature in this whole god there we go now you can hear it
they can rot in that hospital all right i need this back now i can see you're ignoring the lore
i mean i'm not really ignoring the lore as much that was just billy bub thorn just saying a bunch
of words this is all i heard from that we had all sorts of trouble when we saw the law and then we
saw this this thing and that was the day that i don't i didn't hear anything was words oh shit
it's a scorpion versus spider who wins definitely the scorpion start here no why is the screen all
the way up there oh shit what did i do here we go sick all right so i play as the spider
okay this is okay strike press the a button to strike there's a locus right here got him i'm
ready to turn the brightness up this is a little dark hold on wait okay that's pretty good do we
have to fight the humans press down on the control pad to reset the camera behind you
useful it's not dark for us is it not okay maybe it's supposed to be like this this is pretty cool
all right do i just eat everything is this a game about eating stuff info windows one out of four
hundred and fucking fifty a skull icon appears in the upper left when new info is available press
the minus button at any time to view the information window press left or right on the control pad to
scroll through the messages rubs can be found hidden throughout the world approach a grub to
feed on it and regain a small amount of health as you collect more grubs you will unlock concept
art galleries which can be so you lost me you lost me it's not like oh you get a health upgrade
or you get that max damage no yeah i don't you lost me i mean that's cool uh but i i stopped
reading after that just because i don't i mean that's pretty cool all right now get rid of this
it's concept i know it's cool but i thought it was gonna do something to the game somebody's
got 50 fucking subs 50 50 community subs that was fatal finale fatal final fatal finale fatal
finale oh our first enemy beetle oh shit holy fuck what is it a stag beetle combo strikes after
pressing the a button to strike swing the we mode in any direction to follow up with a heavy strike
really all right let's go oh fuck all right is there a lock on holy shit hold on spiders
throw fucking haymakers what wow okay wait this grubs should i get these okay get them might as
well we'll we'll see some concept art you can climb on the walls too oh man that's definitely
the secret power of the spider yeah that's definitely the spider's secret power is to be
able to just appear in your peripheral vision and have you go that's a spider right there in
my peripheral that's a spider right there in my i knew it and it's right fucking next to me
yep that's their power it's not really a secret jeremy you didn't say jeremy i just i said jeremy
oh press z to jump it's a jump what the fuck wow okay another five subs from chris buck
thank you chris buck for the five community subs do you actually have to eat like fight people oh
fuck okay wait oh it was just a loading zone should i jump over this wait there's a beetle
can i do a falling r1 red another 50 dollars holy shit red planet of mars gave 50 fucking dollars
another 50 dollars for the chat sanity say the line and sing the tune you know the one i did get
up shake the wiimote to get up quickly after being hit oh all right this is fucking actually
pretty fun is there a lock on oh my god fucking jesus christ that's a that's a that's 69 subs
from phylactery from phylactery dollar signs 69 community subs this is fucking into the
thousands of dollars right now holy shit guys thank you that's insane it's actually fucking
crazy thanks for the fucking almost 100 subs dude and and and you're collectively like 15
thousand total probably more dollars you've given the stream maybe even like 20 grand at this point
it's insane do i have to stalk anybody oh man boss fight this is the tutorial boss has to be
holy shit it is oh what do i do what do i do what do i do how do you fight a spider
i mean oh fight his tail oh it's jesus all right do it again is there a dodge jesus is
there a block or anything how do i get up there i gotta crawl up i gotta jump up ah how do i do
this how do i do this equip a shield he's blocking his tail walk on the wall i i can't oh dodge the
rattlesnake strikes by jumping out of the way after it hisses so z is dodge there it is how
about z was jumping here we go he's bat rolling dodge all right probably one more
put your tail down idiot fucking moron idiot snake oh shit one more to the right
i don't think you can kill the snake no look at those eyes i'll get you sometime later
our tarantula is poisonous if you get bit by tarantula doesn't like shouldn't it kill you
how about kind of tarantula am i some are did i miss something there if you get bit by a tarantula
you turn into stone right you like turn into a rock person but that's medusa um what happens to you
complete adventure goals as you progress through the game to earn points only one adventure goal
is active at a time it's a quest you are actually correct so what's the goal right now you can also
hunt and kill enemies to complete predator goals and earn points as you earn points you will
automatically unlock upgrades and new combat moves for your character your current adventure goal
and the predator goals for the current chapter are listed on the adventure status page with the
plus button to view the pause menu and select adventure status okay predator goals we have
beetles wolf oh there's a wolf spider no current goals an x combat upgrade so you have 150 points
okay i don't have any goals no adventure goals okay i need full health here why is he supposed
like that stop what the hell is that bite him bite him bite his leg crack the scorpion what the
fuck who crashed their motorcycle whose web is this is not my web how do i can i get over this
how do i get out of here there we go oh shit all right jump strike press the oh they actually
fight each other too it's another spider that i actually don't like that i hate that i don't
like that okay i you okay this is i'm being dead serious here a tarantula you could have 10
tarantulas crawl all over my face and crawl in my mouth and shit and i wouldn't even care
but just a regular wolf spider like house spider i think scared the fucking shit out of me
i hate i don't like them i like this i don't know i don't know what i don't know what it is
they're like weird or somehow like i don't like that thing i don't like that i would let i would
let my character crawl in my mouth i would not let that touch me i would run away from that
oh i hate it i don't like it i don't like it it's trying to kill me they block too how do you jump
and attack like this ah fuck it's the legs probably what was that tool tip it was to jump and
oh i just bumped you this is the dark souls of bugs kind of oh it was it was z and then a right
yeah it was oh shit that's how you get them to stop blocking all right that's it right you lost a
roach wheel move unlocked spin attack swing the we mode left or right to launch a spin attack
that's so cool it's not roach wheel thank you trans scout for the 5000 but you guys are just
dropping 50 fucking dollars a shitload of times another 5000 bits tarantula in mouth on stream or
riot i i probably could i would be fine if you have like a doctor and like two like zoologists
tell me that this if this bit me inside my mouth i'd be fine i would let it happen i'd be like
that's fine i would do it i would let a tarantula crawl in my mouth i would but why would you do
that that's like stupid and dangerous and there's a scorpion scorpions to get the shit out of me
and the worst part about scorpions is out here out here in vegas it's not the big ones they're the
big ones are not a problem they're not it's there may be a bit scary looking but they're not really
the big ones out here it's the bark scorpions that are the problem they're tiny they're like
an inch and a half long maybe an inch long they're flat and they're fucking poisonous
and they're everywhere they're like these orange little flat scorpions and they're
fucking poisonous bark scorpions thank you to
somebody that's on thank thank you on fire for the 10 community subs thank you uh why can i
i can't say this i don't know why thanks for the 10 subs though that's tits tits on fire there you go
thanks for the 10 subs hold the two button to bring up the hint arrow the hint arrow always
points towards the location of your current adventure goal that's awesome i mean like seriously
what a fucking good game this is so far i'm liking it i think you're gonna do here get spin attack
dead the idea of being an insect fighting world is so cool it is pretty cool nice i get i'm assuming
i get new combos too eventually here that's pretty cool this plays pretty well too it's actually
flow the combat's like kind of fun it's very very basic but it's very simple it's very good
this is what bugs do when you're not looking yes actually kind of is this this is what bugs do when
you're not looking i think we've talked about this before but bugs are just in a constant
constant state of war always like bugs are living in like world war two times a million
every day and you'll just think about like world war two how many countries were involved how many
people were involved like imagine if in the bug world we're talking about not like 20 30 40
different countries we're talking about um maybe six to seven million different species all fighting
at the same time so it's like seven to it's like 20 million countries all fighting together at the
same time at like 50 million times uh the conflict in world war two just every day in your fucking
backyard you didn't even know it just under the soil this shit's happening constant conflict yeah
it is that is a bug's life that movie that they made a bug's life where they like drink coffee
and like go to the fucking grocery store no no no no no that movie would be accurate if it was
just like fighting and swords and screaming and shit where is this guy up here is there is that
gonna get like in the tree trunk ants a bug's life how do i get in here i climb it no underneath
wait hold on i'm gonna get like in there we go all right we're in what about b movie yeah b
movie is not accurate either they're in a constant state of war with other like hives and wasps and
shit they don't drive around in cars bro okay gotta keep going up look hold the one button and
point the weave remote at the screen oh that's gonna be annoying but okay where is he is he gonna
be like up on a mountain somewhere he's gonna be at the top of a cliff i guarantee it he's
gonna zoom in on him what if he was behind me where is this motherfucker if i was a bug what
bug would you want to be um that's very easy um what's the shit that when you lift up a rock
there's a bunch of them they're like the silver ones like if you if you go into like in your
garage and you lift up like an old mat that's on the ground and there's like yeah like the
silverfish yeah like if you go in your backyard and then it like rained last week and you lift
up like the damp rock and this is like just a hundred silverfish that's what i would want to be
because they're safe they're protected and they just exist under there you want to be one of the
bugs that just exists just exists people go oh man i would want to be a scorpion i'd want to be a
spider i would be a praying mantis really no you don't what am i supposed to be looking at here
over there is that him roly polys or silverfish is he down where is this guy he's definitely down
here yep i hate those things i hate those things i hate them oh i don't like the way they move that
they don't like the way they walk oh i don't know where they fucking wiggle their legs
and they have velociraptor noises too i why do you have to make them so fucked up
oh he's kicking my ass all right give him a hand maker but this game needs a sequel or a remaster
who made this game well what company actually made this this is pretty cool this is a really
great idea i wish they had like 100 million more dollars this thq it doesn't surprise me thq made
a bunch of awesome cool like interesting games why is it always the companies why is the company
that makes like the cool shit that has to be the one that gets liquidated you know what i'm saying
i bet the fuck is up with that oh we're gonna um i could shoot a web point at the screen with
the wiimote hold the c button aim release the c button to fire a web shot what the fuck that's
so cool hold on i gotta get him all right i'm gonna die if i don't get him he dodged it oh okay all
right i'm gonna have to try that on somebody else it really makes you feel like a spider i guess it
does all right we good that's good all right what am i gonna spider-man ps4 like thq had
so many cool random games like why couldn't they get like 500 million dollars in funding
we're gonna go this way i came from this way arrows pointing over here they didn't sell well
as other companies yeah but i want them to be doing well so it should be doing well what did
that just say what did that just say something about upgrading health earwigs eat silverfish i
want to be an earwig then i don't know i'm not paying attention well pay attention will this help
will that does it help you pay attention i don't want to be like this this to this degree i don't
like the way this is pay attention to me yeah see we like checking the game out together give me
attention give me attention no is this what it's like well get out of the way holy shit he just
stabbed me i'm gonna die why are they on the same team why am i going for the why would i go for the
fucking cricket why does this motherfucker get boxing gloves back up back up back up
oh two hits all right just get two just get two don't get greedy there's no reason to be greedy
there it is nice wait ute's are in this game what you're delayed but i think i play as the
scorpion huge delay i'm playing as the scorpion now oh fuck sorry i play as the scorpion now
that is a massive delay i didn't realize that i had to switch it back holy shit okay
do i get like a stab oh that's cool what about the sides what about sideways no i only have one move
stab and claw it's still delayed it's still decent what the fuck all right what's happening for like
ready what does a bit happen first or after ready oh it's fine the one guy oh so this is a liar is
in here okay find a way out of the underground all right you gotta stop pretending that's a bad test
press the a button to strike with your pincers string together you'd be on the screen for more
than a second man who would see the scorpion is a three hit combo one two three one two three four
four hit combo are you fucking hogging serious kind of fucking relate to you guys swing down
for a stab i fucking hate wolf spiders i seriously do you can block you can block as a scorpion
where oh he's huge i fucking hate i i don't like this don't hurt me
right his fucking head right his fucking skull is he alive no okay ah they don't sound like that
why do they have to sound like that doesn't one hit kill no it's not c what does c do c oh it's an
intimidation i have a taunt as the scorpion well you don't fucking fear me oh man i'm all talk
tail whip tail whip all right scorpions i think a little cooler but you don't can't jump and just
flow scorpions are the most feared insect uh no that's the praying mantis dash holy shit that's
terrifying praying mantis sucks um talking about pound for pound the pound for pound the most
deadly and the most powerful pound for pound inch by inch species on earth they're like
hold on i don't want to fix my hair i just did anyways they can't even hurt people praying
mantis is all right i'll give you this frog is fucking way stronger frog like eats praying
mantis frog okay frog eat praying mantis all right tiger eat frog fine i'll give you that
frog eat praying mantis praying mantis eat scorpion scorpion eat spider spider eat
mosquito mosquito eat you it's a cycle of life guys how do i move very dark where am i going
it wants me to go this way but how do i get over there oh all right what do we eat uh fruits and
vegetables and sometimes uh hamburgers and then vegetables eat water and dirt ass what uh oh i
thought that was i thought that was a big like white spider or something and i was about to
fucking shit my pants oh it's a person's body that's a dead that's a body that's a hand that's kind of
fucked up got greedy well it's doing the thing that they do on walls i feel like they're like
above me right now like in real life oh that's a double don't look behind it's when they go up i
feel like when they go away from the screen and out off of like stage left and stage right that
they're going to be on my walls you know they come up from here and then all of a sudden there's
one right there oh it's one under your neck is there dude what the fuck spider rub what the
hell was that oh shit was that silverfish am i dead was that a silverfish he was just existing
i told you i wanted to be in it oh that's too bad that's too bad what the hell is am i in like a
person's rib cage holy shit there's a dead body down here oh it's me it's me from the past fuck
fuck he's he can go through my block when an enemy is weak enough grab it with c
oh oh that was right in his head that was directly in his head enter the correct
gestures with the we mode and nunchuck when prompted to end the battle with a deadly finishing move
you don't perform such a move we're getting a small amount of health oh whoa so we found out
who wins you gave him the stone cold stunner oh that's stunner to shane mcmahon though in like
2000 oh it's the best stunner ever best stunner ever stunner to shane mcmahon you know if he's
not you know you know what i'm talking about unfucking believable it's like the most fluid
most unbelievable thing i've ever seen in my life and he like spits the water it's like boom and
he gets it's like he springboarded up oh shane mcmahon did the best stunts that was in stone
cold steve boston's book by the way he said shane mcmahon was the one that did the best stuns show
it fine we'll go over it is this the one somebody i'm trying to find it it's like the best stun ever
i'm gonna write best stun somebody got it no it's not no no no not shane mcmahon didn't have white
hair this man is capable of any this is it this is the one this is the best let's go over this shit
right now whatever we'll put this on pause it's all good this game's fucking fun we're gonna keep
playing don't worry god it just it's so satisfying what it's like i thought he was pretending
why would i ever pretend on something so important this man is capable of anything
steve blackman is the one who ran over stone cold steve boston
oh
you can tell look at as he wasn't ready for it stop stop what's a stone cold steve uh what
okay see his knees are supposed to be hitting the ground at the same time and they are not steve
uh what's this guy's name steve wasn't correct check out the knee placement and the spring look
at the knee placement here you've got an incredible fucking incredible absolute symmetrical 90 degree
knee angle boom then he pushes his hands up springboards up i know this shit trust me it's
the best done ever check it out again another good exhibit here take the knees and go right there
launches himself up this is at 0.25 percent speed now that just reminded me of one time
so back in the day uh somebody may have heard this story i might be telling it again but we're
going to show it um me and mlc stealth were in a uh a skype call i believe we were just talking
we were hanging out we used to do skype calls all the time and we would watch wrestling clips
and at the time i i had a machinima partner manager somebody that was a machinima partner
person that you know if you have had a problem with youtube hit me up uh let me like contacts
and shit like that right so the way that skype was worked out it was you know had the names if
with somebody that you were you know you had their username and then the little chat window
well i accidentally uh linked to my machinima partner manager instead of mlc stealth uh stone
cold stuns the entire mcmahon family by the way i didn't speak to this person for probably seven
or eight months before i sent them this link and it was kind of weird but whatever well i was like
oh sorry i've been sent uh delete imagine imagine getting this shit from like one of your partners
you haven't heard from in in like a fucking year so you got a busy night ahead of you hey don't
leave i wanted to show you something that right he stuns the entire family oh there he is
changing fast he's gonna do the springboard again the best one the best one's coming up
when he stuns when he stuns he stuns him off maybe uh i do understand i was just gonna conduct an
interview and ask you a few questions what fragrance are you wearing do you have an answer
it's perfume he's gonna just he's gonna just stutter i get it imagine being in minute number
three imagine being minute number three as the machinima partner manager
oh fuck that was bang where to go where to go where to go where's my stream where's my fucking
stream oh there it is i'm kind of glad you did oh that was a good that was a good fall that was a
good trapfall see the cement you see the symmetry by the way it's not over all right just
just wait this one is fucking look at it right by the way this like kills you apparently
when you get stunned oh man i'm unconscious for like 12 straight minutes if you were unconscious
for like 15 straight minutes like that's bad they're all just like dead i gotta say that
stephanie is a precious piece of trash where is it thank you
look at this shit this is like the best thank you right just watch watch like the balls
they neither one was prepared either let's take a look at the symmetry on this one
okay so let's just very briefly go over the fact that yes this is the link that i sent
to my partner manager at the time and i hadn't spoken to him in about a year
why why are you sending this to me man what the fuck are you doing hey man check out
check out stone cold stuns the entire fucking mcmahon family what do you think about that
isn't that cool man god all right let's keep going back to the scorpion game you're out of business
now yep us too thanks for sharing dad you're welcome son did somebody give enough of 50
fucking dollars is that is that act hold on is that actually me though fuck it is scorpions eat
these how do why do scorpions eat these i thought scorpions ate like fucking human meat and
from all the scary stories and shit they eat like fucking birds and humans and stuff don't they
and like animals uh phylactery lich another 50 fucking dollars holy shit wrestling was
fucking crazy show the vince walk but the like the vince walk is just like one like step away from
the thing that i do except the thing that i do is if you want to know some some heavy lore here
that is actually claiming from the neverhood that i that's that like walk is claiming from the
neverhood that's where it comes from that's like what i'm imitating there you go but thanks for
the fucking 5000 bits dude that's a lot of money you keep giving huge money show the walk update
the wiki uh someone will get it someone will get that i got i got my hand i just got my hands full
i'd say to shoot okay oh so what the fuck i can't is there another tarantula that was terrifying
wait that was this stream yeah it was like an hour ago all right let's go he dodged it
oh yeah i still got him what do you gasio gasio gasiou gazzio gazzio gasio gasio gazzio like
Heck yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh that's at the thumbnail oh it'll be don't worry it'll be updated in like two minutes
shit why does this keep happening because i keep opening up the youtube videos in the middle of
these streams this is the scary music ah this is a real reaction so i'm not like putting this on
for the camera of course i am of course i am but you know but that actually i when they're in the
webs and shit three at a time fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck oh you dick where did he go
oh shit he just ricocheted please germa please what do you want what please please please please
please please oh i don't like this thing what the fuck is this why is this possible what the fuck
hold on a second this is important what the fuck is this have we gone too far probably yeah i mean
how did you do this seriously how did you do this not that this is obs no i i want a reddit
streamer that's a reddit video hold on we got a link to like the just the actual video was like
how do i get how do i like just get to that right isn't there a way i can do that it has audio i
know oh let me i'll get this no that's how reddit works i feel like actually just physically go to
the page hold on oh hold on i gotta open up i can't i forgot i can't use i forgot i can't use
bozilla fuck i gotta turn the microwave off this is important though hold on okay now let me get
this over here there's audio too apparently why is the reddit player so bad this is like the worst
thing ever this is like the worst thing ever why can i fucking capture this what the fuck is going
on here i can't even capture the fucking window somebody got it there we go thank you thank you
this doesn't even fucking work either i have never been a quitter i fucking hate this why
all right something's wrong with my obs i can't like pull this in i'm just gonna have to do it
like this it's like fucked up you're a quitter i i mean i'm just at the mercy of trying to get
my window to capture it i can't it won't capture okay there we go so you took the picture of me
that's this i have never been a quitter to leave office before my term is completed is
abhorrent to every instinct in my body but as president i must put the interests of america
first america needs a full-time president and a full-time congress particularly at this time
with problems we face at home and abroad to continue to fight through the months ahead for
my personal vindication would almost totally absorb the time and attention of both the president
and the congress in a period when our entire focus should be on the great issues of peace
abroad and prosperity without inflation at home therefore the point the presidency effective
that noon tomorrow vice president ford will be sworn in as president at that hour in this office
i have never okay um okay what the fuck is all what is this is it what what technology is this
what technology is this shit this is this is too much this is too much technology we got to go
back to writing on paper and shit we got to go back to fucking sending mail in the mail
okay that was interesting that was interesting um fuck we're doomed as like a whole society
aren't we shit like holy shit you can have a picture to say anything you want and it can
look kind of real what happens in five years when it looks very real and it's like anybody you can
tell anybody anything you can make anyone say anything you make any picture the picture of me
with my girlfriend at like disneyland can't be used for me to say anything you want read the
top comment on germa resigned why 100 of germa saw this he would go on a five-minute rant about how
fucking scary technology is today uh because you can do shit like this and he would be right this
is terrifying i that yeah anything any i think anybody that sees themselves in a photo they took
three or four plus years ago doing a resigning president nixon presidency speech it's a little
unnerving i think for the future of our children he's doing all right i'm not doing it anymore i'm
not doing it okay we're playing a fun game over here don't you think let me switch over my audio
to the speech i already did the speech resign or riot resign hey dude fucking resign all right
or riot jesus okay let's go well i wonder what what other um creatures do you get to play as
but those things hatch i hope not stop being a streamer i'm gonna keep streaming four times
how do i get up i'm supposed to go up up this thing i guess i could go this way oh wait a minute
hold on like no i can't go up and around this is the wrong way wrong way and i am resigning
and and i will it's just so fucked up the eyes like like they go fucking all over the place
oh they don't they don't do that do they oh oh is it a black widow that's a black widow isn't it
or it's a it's a foe widow how do i save i can't save him how am i supposed to save him i can't
he's just like he's getting eaten i can't tell i can't help him holy shit they can attack all
right i gotta be careful block block block block oh he goes through the block you kidding me
me get out of here hey with that shit oh right oh he dodged there it is fuck i was just walking
by oh i was just walking by i'm so useless we go up in the wasps the worst hold on wait wait wait
wait wait till he lands wait till he lands okay recycling uh content that people really liked
okay wait till there he goes here it comes good smoke yeah you know the one somebody said it looks
like i'm cut off no i'm just bad at streaming i learned how to stream like four to five years
ago and i learned one way to do it and i have not changed it ever since i only know one way to
stream and it's like 2013 way to stream i've not made any progress in regards to like quality this
is there just from like 2014 it shows king he's a classic streamer
ten Eddie's still fine oh scorpion versus scorpion
what kind of scorpion is that what kind of scorpion am i oh shit mirror match we like
emperor scorpions i think we are oh shit i got it tail whip tail whip come on get
it yes oh how do i kill a wonder nice got it do i eat do we they eat each other
dig you can now uncover passages and hollows in certain places i can dig
why is it not working dig at the crummy walls yeah okay oh i didn't know that they that was
just me just trying to hang out under the rock why does it always have to be me well right because
i said that's the kind of animal i was what kind of animal would i actually be guys what do you
think if you would say like what what kind of animal or bug a rat that's an easy answer though
penis i don't anymore comedy 100 holy shit i just exploded his head was that his head that flew
behind me i just i just like chopped his head off it was like an axe i wonder if we see that
snake again uh something here you'd be a hyena or a squirrel yeah i could see the hyena part
yeah that makes sense a weasel but i'd be i'd be a cool weasel though all right i don't i want to
be like an animal weasel not like a disney cartoon weasel you know what i mean oh now we're getting
dark look at all these dead bugs oh it's gonna be a frog isn't it it's gonna be a frog isn't it
it's gonna be a it's gonna be a frog i told you the predator of all it's gonna be frog then
scorpion this is a big area full health i dig in it's like it looked like i could
i told you it was gonna be a it's a lizard holy shit what kind of lizard is this
oh man escape from the gila monster oh wow it's like a it's like a monitor lizard
how do i where do i just get out attack him where do i go how do i get out stab him in the stab in
the big fatty ball no do not do that run away just get the hell out of here up there cut the tail
cut the tail i'm just trying to get the fuck out of here climb it climb i think he does he lost me
dig all right dig do i dig dig oh i get it i don't know what to do he's gonna weigh too much he's
gonna weigh way too much i get it he's gonna crash through this all right one more okay get it
maybe better to flee than i know what i'm doing i'm trying yep how much is left
oh fuck this is another one where is it this guy sucks shut up i just did an adam sandler
ha ha shut up whatever he's almost got fucking academy award and all you guys hated him it's
right here it's fine fine fine fine it's literally it's right here literally it's literally here
okay okay dig out all the junk you have to resign now i'm not resigning anything all right go i know
what i have to do i know it's gonna he's gonna get we're gonna watch him get eaten again i really
like this concept though where the bosses are just like a snake a lizard it's probably gonna be
like a frog and this is probably gonna be a frog right it has to be all right let's go dig what
the fuck was that why is this not working okay this hello excuse me what the fuck are you doing
you you guys are watching in real time you're watching in real time you shake this fucking
thing shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake shake i can't wait for
resident evil for a week either dude you're gonna see this the bug game is too hard no it's just
like evidence on the screen it's it's not z z blocks do you understand you gotta be like
brr brr brr okay i get it manka s he's losing it so sorry okay yes sorry about that
when you play resident evil 3 well um people could vote on resident evil 3 and they didn't
pick it because they said hey actually we got a lot of people here right now i've heard
remember i'm a huge fan of resident evil 2 huge fan i heard the resident evil 3 is like half the
length of resident evil 2 and this is not very good so i'm just telling what i heard all right
i'm not gonna fuck this up here we go all right all right why is it working this time am i stupid
or something fuck wait till next time what am i i hope i don't understand what i'm doing different
buddy stop digging
oh there's one more here oh i thought i he just double tapped me fine fuck you
this is it oh he almost got me nice work nice work you hey nice work you thanks this is a 10
minute game oh yeah but so um go back to the spider now so resident evil 3 is not that great huh
i'm still gonna play it though i mean am i not gonna play it remember i can jump now when do
we find a human what the hell is this like a briar patch oh a regular lizard bees oh my god
what are those mites holy shit they just disintegrated that lizard try to avoid the
mites what am i doing get off me i could just like feel those on me can i jump over them
this is kind of a scary game kinda wait watch it they have they have a they have a pattern
we'll just avoid them jump over them i think i have to just i have to go through them underneath
them can i make it if i run now i think you just have to just get through them they'll just suck
your blood okay they're like a they're like a laser you just have to avoid herma has mites it's the
very opposite of a laser no i'm talking about like in a game where it's just like
rare rare to go through you have to run through before you get hit by the laser
figure maybe you can knock them down they're running away oh the mites the mites are going
after me fuck i get too many there's too many around me i gotta run away
uh one more why is my stream 720p um there's a few reasons for that uh
1080p actually uh in my opinion this is my opinion is i don't think it's worth streaming
because it takes a lot more bandwidth it takes a lot more resources and 1080p doesn't really even
look any good until about eight to ten thousand k up so twitch really only allows six thousand up
to pretty much anybody to stream to the platform so a 1080p stream at six thousand up i mean you're
talking about a 1080 footage really needs like 10 000 up like look good at least eight to ten
that's why i don't do it now you can do like eight some people do 900p like 870 880 i could
do that but i got a 1080 maybe in the future we'll see we'll see where's this other spider
that's apparently alive just talking yeah i'm talking bitrate like 4 000 up like bitrate like
a 6 000 bitrate where does this want me to go what just happened did i just like skip a major
part of the level oh it's these things it's the other spider i don't like the other like weird
spiders like the black widows yep i hate these look i know it's cool i know like yeah you got
a tattoo of a black widow i know like but no i don't like them i'm gonna die find the widow's
cathedral hold the b button to build up your venom and then swing the wiimote down to deliver
a venom pounce it's a dot oh okay that's fucking awesome that's so cool all right let me give me
these grubs it's the cathedral we gotta go find the cathedral they have organized religion
all right uh there's another grub over here okay this way and then
all right germa has a mick chicken tattoo and then that would be a pretty cool one
but i'm talking like in the wrapper like the the solid wrapper wrapped mick chicken sandwich
that sounds pretty good that would be cool running away i want to try the venom pounce on somebody
remember do you eat the wrapper shit you're bringing back some weird like memories when i
was younger what was the bubble gum that you chewed the wrapper i remember there was a gum
that like you people chewed with the wrapper on what was it i swear to god this was a thing
it was like i think i was lied to when i was a kid it was like oh yeah you eat it with the wrapper
on you chew it with the wrapper on and i would chew the gum with the wrapper on this one specific
brand for some reason there was a reason for it and i remember it was weird and it didn't it was
just like this doesn't feel right i shouldn't be doing it like this but i did it and i have to take
eventually you take the like mushed up wrapper out of your mouth why did i do that does anybody
anybody else do that any of you for any reason starburst no i'm not talking about unwrapping
i'm talking about in the wrapper it goes in your mouth and you chew it with the wrapper on and
like break the wrapper down with your teeth chewing it it was stride it was seriously it was trident
trident it was trident it was trident was it trident maybe it was trident oh i did it first
no you can't do it ban everybody that says it let him fight i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm
gonna poison one of them oh shit it's orange needed smog oh i can do that too dickhead oh
i missed i missed again oh it's okay he died it was a poison aim for smog oh snake what a
fucking callback what a callback creature nice and then it's ready grabs a snake like a uh i don't
know like a orangutan grabs a snake right and then like an eagle gets the orangutan and then oh you
guys know what i was trying to say do the walk all right that's a family guy joke look okay when
family guy has like 28 seasons of show and the whole point of family guy is they come up
with like 600 random references a an episode they're talking about 600 times 30 episodes a
season so and so 30 times 28 it's like there's like 25 million there's like this probably like
55 000 family guy references over the years oh wait we got we got a fog window here
freeze him nice all right back it up again poison nice this one was fucking pretty good
that was an instant kill eat the shoe you're not you're a little late oh never mind when
are we gonna get another muffled when we're gonna get another muffled like 60 000 dollar line from
billy bop Thornton that just goes
it's coming up soon why are there so many of these cell phone
wait that's that might not be synced up that's not going to be synced up because the delay
that's not going to be synced up correctly hey what was it oh oh oh oh i wanted to bring this
up on stream so i've got every service that you call right let me get away from the fucking
loud beep thing is there a reason why every time you call any service that's ever existed
the first thing that happens is the please listen carefully as our menu options have changed
it's like that for like seven to eight straight years why do they say that every time are they
so terrified that you're not going to listen to the fucking menu that well okay the menu has
options have changed i better listen now is that that's the tactic right that's the strategy
because if you call like for instance if i were to call uh like a utility company or like a cable
company or something it says that every fucking time and it's that same exact thing every fucking
the menu doesn't change it's just that every single time it's for old people right i used to
work telecom and we did that so you never changed your options that's a Seinfeld joke well guess
what like cox cable has had that since Seinfeld was on the air do you understand that's my point
it still works i could that's an epic kramer moment fuck i thought i could get a big one
and i was gonna make a tweet i didn't though because like i'm lazy and i don't fucking use
social media ever there's something wrong with me i was gonna make a tweet that was a phone and
you know like the oh name a better duo tweets right it was gonna be it's gonna be a phone picture
it says please listen carefully and then like another phone as our menu options have changed
and it's gonna be like college shit that's pretty good like comedy tweet like name a name and name me
it better do all right thank god you didn't do that why why what's wrong with that that's like
funny that's like name me oh name me i better do like please listen carefully as our menu options
have changed that would have been shared around like some circles right that was a new animal
that's boomer here i didn't i didn't do it i was just i you guys act like i did this i should do it
anyways my aunt would find that funny yeah i'm trying to work on some new demographics here
you know we we can we can only ride the like scare every new viewer away and have people open the
stream and go what's i hate this guy demographic for you know i gotta branch out to like aunts you
just split a phrase what yeah but it's namely a better duo because everyone knows what that is
and everyone's like gets it you get it your aunt does your aunt gets comedy your aunt is a
understands comedians what's just flew by the fucking screen did i not get that double strike
combos but i can do a move list what was that i don't know i'm not i'm not i'm not gonna i'm
not gonna go like flood some stream so because you guys are like fucking like pranking somebody
or something don't do that shit what i mean it's me what uh yeah yeah yeah you can't you can't be
doing all right no you can't you actually can't be doing that you can't like be streaming like
movies and shit and then like me naked uh so that stream is probably going to go away pretty
quickly um yeah that's probably not that's probably not going to last very long um it's probably i
would assume that's probably not going to last a whole lot longer uh okay so i have to say about
that i have nothing else to say besides uh streaming movies on twitch is not allowed unless you use
their feature the twitch plays sees watches together feature if you have it uh which that
stream does not have okay uh yeah let's go oh spikes how do i jump go around oh like the
crunching noises it's a nice added effect please listen carefully as our menu options have changed
maybe you better do oh like oh i was on the phone the other day and i heard that that's not even
realistic i don't don't fall bugs have like a terminal velocity of like 600 million miles per
hour or something like you can't if you drop like an ant like off a building it's like just lands
normally right isn't that isn't that accurate like they can't they literally can't like die if they
fall off like a high thing or something no that's true tarantulas do not they die from being oh
oh yeah today i learned tarantulas are not ants right okay good to know only a third of what you
said was accurate oh do i need to be accurate i got one of those he's so strong he hates links
no i don't hate links i just hate clicking them all right hold on this is like the that pardon
i'm not gonna say i gotta stop saying the word dark souls all right one of you one of you is
getting poisoned right now i know you're still alive no the great hollow yes bugs lifestream
is gone can we get an f in chat what did you think was what did you think was gonna happen
guys if you if you take a bowling ball and you hold it over your foot and you let it go over
your foot on purpose and smash your foot and break every bone in your foot are you really
gonna be surprised that you did that like that's the equivalent of oh man like this is i really
hope nothing happens here i'm gonna let this go over my foot oh my foot's broken how did this
happen why did this happen to me stop talking over the movie what am i doing you don't even
know this is the movie's not even on my stream i'm just fucking up my own stream i have nothing
to do with somebody streaming a fucking movie what am i supposed to do like hey twitch like
there's a guy streaming a fucking full movie over here with my face on it what am i supposed to say
stop rant rant no i'm not i'm not i'm not gonna talk about it anymore i'm not gonna talk about it
anymore let's just don't do that that's fucking don't that's not all right you do that's not
all right don't fucking do that you're gonna get in fucking trouble it's against it's against
terms of service don't do it it's not unless you have the amazon presents watch movies together
which you don't have so you can't do it i'm telling you okay i'm gonna fall off again how
do i get around this kind of hurting my head how did i do this last time oh shit okay all right now
don't jump stay on here all the way around don't jump nice okay keep going do i do i
jump over there how do i get over there should i jump i'm like scared to jump if i jump i'll fall
off oh right here okay right then i have to jump from here to there that seemed like it shouldn't
have happened that seemed like that was the wrong idea but apparently it worked all right this is
fucked up um i jumped this no okay this is trippy because we're upside down and then we're not upside
down and then we're right side up and then we're sideways and then we're not sideways
and now we're going this way and now we're not going this way and then i gotta go down here this
guy sucks what am i gonna do for you this guy i haven't stopped talking what's wrong with you
now bitcoin is up i guess give me that come here i'm gonna ban everyone i can't ban everyone
somebody got it somebody got it somebody got it somebody got it somebody got it somebody got it
the mean machine gave 10 bucks first of all but somebody got it this is it for the record you're
thinking of cinnabarst gum they marketed themselves as an extreme gum for hip kids in the 80s and early
90s and used a fast dissolving material for their wrappers it was safe to digest but was more of a
safety precaution for dumb kids than intended feature yep i remember this led to a popular
urban legend that chewing it with the wrapper on enhanced the flavor crystals
but they never intended for you to actually chew the wrapper that's you got it cinnabarst gum yep
because they put crystals and it was wrapped up and you chewed through the wrapper and shit
wow thank you thank seriously i was gonna drive me nuts i was gonna drive me nuts wow all right
nice cinnabarst right because it crystals lost fight oh they're coming they're getting in they're
coming in they're coming in they're coming in ah ute fill i tried it you watched it in real time
what the fuck am i playing this is called deadly creatures nintendo we all right let's try this
again thankfully it's right here like i look at the dry eyes i feel like i haven't blanked very much
linked oh there's a big one right there oh i hate this they're coming faster
oh this actually is fucking with my head it actually fucking go what does the red one do
double strike combo oh the moves list right right right go for it i just got fucking poisoned
how do i stop getting poisoned is there a way i can get it off i watch it
eat him god new ability web jump you can now fire a line and instantly web jump two patches
of spider web silk we're close enough to do a web jump patch c and then aim oh that's pretty sick
use web jump to find a way out of the brambles so right over there and we let it go
wow spider has way more interesting moves and the scorpion does that's for sure scorpion
scorpion why does it sound like i'm over pronouncing that scorpion yeah it's a scorpion
the scorpion scorpion it's a scorpion yeah i got it okay now another one right there
too far away shit is there another one that i don't see how long can it can sew to last i don't know
look at the expiration date dude why are you asking me i don't know how can i not reach this
oh okay yeah i can one of these is longer than the other i think is this one there we go bug's
life or riot you want to put on a bug's life and get my twitch channel suspended
because i was already gone for like six straight days you'd like me to add another like four or
five days to that i just got back i just got back what are you losing it use the watch thing
okay is a bug's life on the amazon prime watch together list is it is it on there god damn it
is it on there i don't want to watch a fucking bug's life that's gonna take the place of a stream
you know that right that's gonna that's gonna be exhausting to me that's gonna be exhausting
i know it's like dude you're just watching a movie in a chair but man i don't i do i don't want to
do that like i could think of anything else i could possibly do with my time and watching a
bug's life is is absolutely not anything wonderful i you everyone's saying you're lazy lazy no i i
just i don't i don't want to watch a bug's life but i will if it's on there why why why would i do
that why would i need to say that i would do that that's so meaningless that's so pointless it's
not imagine showing up to that one and your aunt's not gonna like that one wait why wouldn't why
wouldn't your aunt like that watch hereditary i've already seen hereditary it's fucking nuts
oh he's fucked up my aunt loves a bug's life oh well that's cool maybe we'll watch it
i was too rice to figure out he put his brother in the coffin with the other part of the map still
in his coat force opening all right what is this yeah just it's what do you mean host host what
wrong side no i was pointing to the left corner all right excuse me i've got to listen to philly
pop Thornton get fifty thousand dollars per fucking vowel host a bug's life no no no
we're doing this no i am no if you want if you want to go get your channel fucking compromised
follow me don't do it all right i feel like i've went in a whole circle did i here we are see this
is the thing about all the people that are saying dude fucking you should do we'll do like the amazon
watch party thing together in a bug's life it'll be so it'll be so funny and those people are
gonna come to the stream and they're gonna watch for 10 minutes and they're gonna fucking leave
they're gonna be gone they'll be gone in less than 10 minutes less than 15 minutes and then we're
we're holding the fucking we're holding the earth up that's absolutely true snake ah it is pulled
him out did billy bob Thornton just pull a snake out with his bare hands a rattlesnake
we made it to the citadel would you expect anything less a citadel all right over under
here what's the over under that we're going to get like uh in the background what's the what's
the over under 50 50 you think but we haven't made it to the citadel yet so that's not accurate what
am i talking about i don't do i actually have to explain that right in his head right in his head
dad it was another one all right all right can we can we stop giving the terms of service breaker
attention at the moment can we can we refrain from from having this stream be a stream that
is directly connected to a stream that is breaking terms of service as we speak right now he's
draining you all right i'm gonna put the foot down here stop stop it stop it stop it stop it
i'm like the fucking principal that comes out during recess okay kids it's time to come in for
recess oh none of them are listening at all no one's listening to me come on kids
recess is over back to school and there's like a full kickball game still going on and it takes
like 30 fucking minutes for all those kids to come back yeah i i have no control at this point you
guys are gonna go play your fucking game kickball until it's just like until like seven or eight
adults come up and all of us in chorus okay kids come on that's enough all right last at that last
at that then bring it in okay all right that no no all right we'll just let him do it for like
another minute or two how many adults is it gonna take to get you guys come back what do i need to
dig what do i dig what do i dig where do i even dig why is nobody helping me why is nobody helping
found it oh it's a hornet versus a tarantula new enemy super hornet those things are terrifying
that's a tarantula wasp i should be okay then because i'm a scorpion okay bye he's gonna watch
out when he swings down like that okay got it right the fucking head parry there is no parry
oh this is bad am i finally gonna get to the surface invade the tarantula hawks cactus hive
that's a terrible idea use dead eye really this far this far after 2000 like 16
i'm gonna say that still come on really i'm so high right now and i love how some of you guys
just decide to tell me that every stream what is happening oh it's spitting at me dude i'm
fucking wicked high here all right we want to oh burrow strike quickly burrow down into soilless
sand by turning the remote upside down and swing the remote upwards to burrow strike
what come on do it is this working oh you have to be on sand i get it i have to be on dirt
this game is pretty awesome actually i really like this game no that was not a pretend voice i know
it sounded like it but it's not the ranch of the hawk cave happy birthday man it's not my birthday
time to fuck up those wasps i don't why do you guys you guys you guys just love like
chaos you love just carnage you love just chaos a rat no big lizard i could holy shit i'm huge
okay the dodge and then he does a big dash like his big brother does oh yes what oh come on
this is bad i'm gonna lose holy shit that was lucky he's dead almost kill kill kill oh oh that
was fucking horrible i like pulled his neck oh there's another one he was right behind me
shit use your new attack yeah i gotta look it up yes is online another 50 dollars comes in
there's been like a dozen of these 50 dollar fucking more than one there's been like 15 50
dollar donations tonight holy shit guys this is from yes is online bro pawn stars is on that
watch party list so you could theoretically get on the pawn stars show since they're in vegas and
then react to yourself being on pawn stars uh what do you think i have that's valuable here
oh let me think of the most valuable thing that i own the dreamcast
the 3do but uh why why would the pawn stars guys want an old 3do i don't i don't have like an old
civil war musket to bring in i don't have anything like old and valuable all right let's let's kill
this lizard all right what's this new move that that people are screaming screaming in my ear
or screaming at me for a move list double jab yeah interest mass stick block dash tail whip yeah
uproot yeah the claw yeah we've been doing that scorpio a a thrash okay dig i've been doing it
yeah i've been doing that i've been doing it oh fuck we have to fight the ranch of the hawk again
so you tell me that that nature decided to make a hard counter for the tarantula it's kind of
strange yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah invade the nest it just fucked you missed a wink oh maybe i
should oh by the way what do i have that's valuable nothing they don't want me on that show what the
hell do they want me on that show for just ban the word wink yeah probably just do it
yeah he should probably do it like an hour or two chibi robo no gotcha force is more expensive
than chibi robo gotcha force is a lot more expensive than chibi robo which by the way
nobody trusts that by the way in the pre-stream chat we're trying to figure out what i would do
today and unanimously i think like only four people voted for it out of like five or six hundred votes
you didn't buy chibi robo oh i didn't i didn't you didn't i didn't buy chibi robo i don't own
chibi robo you don't own that game but um what the fuck is this then what's um what's in here
what is that interesting it looks like uh this looks like a gamecube disc and it's it says chibi
robo on it i don't own this stuff i don't own that game all right whatever you get it you get it
things fucking things pretty valuable i've got did it well it's a fake i faked you out i'm not
gonna do that with chibi robo i just kind of did no i didn't i would never throw it be serious
that's a commodity we rented it for a blockbuster that probably wouldn't even available on that
blockbuster gotcha force is expensive gotcha force is really hard to find with a box and original
manual that shit's like three or four hundred dollars if you just get the disc gotcha force
that shit's like uh it's not it's not cheap and it's just the dumb disc not even the fucking
manual i sold mine for four hundred dollars last year well you made some you made bank
that game's worth a lot of money that might be the most besides cubivore cubivore and gotcha force
are the two i think most expensive games you can find on the game somebody's gonna be like actually
i know i know which one it's like cubivore is like 600 bucks cubivore is like five or
six hundred dollars that's a lot of fucking money for a game cube game here we go wait somebody say
six hundred dollars is not a lot of money for a game cube game what do you consider a lot of money
got it oh he's dizzy he's dizzy dizzy dizzy break his neck again is it i wish you would stop
pretending to own chibi robo bad angle bad angle like the bad angle got it ah i dodged trying to
go that way you fucking idiot one more was that it who proved you own chibi robo put it in the
wheat i'm in the middle of something right now if you can't i'm not sure you can tell but i'm in the
middle of something go inside the eye show the receipt sure okay guys yeah what what do you know
i'm not gonna give you that i'm up i'm on this ceiling he doesn't have it when you guys drunk
only you your credit card security number to tell me you know there's there was this idea that i had
you guys remember the like the christmas stream right where i was like hey i'm gonna give you guys
like 500 bucks to just buy random shit and i'll just cover it whatever like i'll just pay for it
right yeah there was this like theory that it was like i don't think i could have ever done it
where you guys like have to use like i would just it would be terrible and i it wouldn't
work out at all and the idea got thrown in the trash can immediately when it popped in my head
but like if i bought like a fucking visa gift card and just like showed it and just like see
what somebody bought but that's a bit that's a fucking that's not gonna work out like it's
not gonna work out like what would happen what would actually happen you know what i mean have
like the statement over here on one monitor and be like one two three there's a number and just
like capture the window of the statement and refresh it every five seconds and then i think
okay that's like that's like that that would never work because people would just buy a bunch of
fucked up shit and it would come leading back to me so no what was that for um can i am i gonna
move this rock oh damn all right let's go frog no i thought it was a frog i got excited boros
yeah i know boros strike i know boros strike i know this shit already yes fuck your chat is
lewd i'm trying to make them i'm trying to make them better you guys can be better you i'm trying
to make you guys i'm gonna try to make you guys better get this off me you can't are you sure
this is the right place we're burying a body be doing this all day if it ain't this is it just
no wait they're digging for gold oh my finger get the fuck off me that hurt my fingernail
you have to kill them well hold on hey man is this valuable no it's quartz well that's some kind of
crystal right you know like all them shopping networks on tv get digging all right fine
whatever i'm keeping it yeah two three one two three got it all right we're getting into the
tarantula hawk nest lay your eggs come here are we gonna get a super tarantula hawk what do you guys
think in the comments here what do you think we're gonna get big tarantula hawk what's the next boss
you tell me what do you think holy wait am i crawling up his leg no oh damn we're in
oh there's a lot where is my team i don't think i get a team nope i'm trying to see you later
elimination matches that's kind of what these are isn't it guys triple triple triple triple kill
kill kill kill kill you're gonna be more funny why is that better quick hurry even make noises
and faces into the camera ready how about this one i call this one all right wow wait is it
ouch oh my funny bone nice beetle juice joke does that happen in beetle juice
what a great movie can we watch that on amazon prime what else is available i always move with
the way i have to who framed roger rabbit well you talk about that that's one of the best movies
ever made so that sounds good i'm poisoned but who framed roger rabbit's one of the best movies
ever made did somebody just say no it's not not true no it's not no it's not holy shit
this is unbelievable to see that in this jet who framed what roger rabbit is it's like at least a
nine and a half out of ten it's terrible oh man we would not we would not get along we wouldn't
get along i don't think you would say that you'd be like nah that would be stupid man who's a
fucking leg zero and i would do like the blink blink blink blink blink blink fucking furious but
like i'm not gonna say anything you know what i mean like i love who framed roger rabbit it's
a really good movie that movie's fucking stupid it's like it's like a fucking it's like a fucking
ada like it's not like a low fucking seven i love seven yeah dude it's fucking low seven maybe like
a high six uh high six driving by with your fucking loud ass car dust to dust how many
chapters are even in the game everybody know salty because people have taste
i'm just floyd as the judge you that's not even no you don't really think that do you
he's going to rotten tomatoes no no no sorry i'm going to step over rotten tomatoes
i'm going to the library of congress who framed roger rabbit is so good that they put it into
the library of congress they only do that for movies that are considered to be pieces that must
be fucking preserved forever they must be this isn't like cars too like this isn't pineapple
express i'm sorry i'm going to have to overstep you here what do you mean i hated cars too wait
it's hold on library of congress cars too shit fuck all right whatever it's point still stands
cars too i mean cars is a multi billion dollar multilingual multinational franchise that has
seen hundreds of billions of views in the movie theaters it makes sense that that would be in the
library of congress it's multi localized it's been seen in 500 countries okay it makes all right yes
okay are the minions in there the minions what is it what's the minions movie minions
library of congress the minions are in the library of congress right okay
no they're not no the minions movie is not in the library of congress um apparently it doesn't
classify the minions don't get to be there it's literally porn in the library of congress
yeah is what's the problem there if an asteroid hits earth and like six million years in the
future aliens land and they find the library of congress archive i mean there's we want them to
we want to show them what we got i guess wait then i i mean let's be realistic don't you think they
would be curious remember an asteroid hit earth and we've been dead for 5 000 years don't you
think they'd like to know how we like procreated for all they know we could like link up tubes on
our heads and like they don't know why would they know we've been just we've been distinct
we've been extinct for 5 000 years point is roger rapston library of congress what a great
fucking movie that is those cars multi-fucking lingual multinational movie all right how do i
how do i get the fuck out of this i have to go down can i switch the scorpion what the hell is
lizard down here oh shit all right i'm gonna queue it up oh i missed oh you dick got him
knock him out knock him up yeah despicable me is there but not the minions god damn it whatever
that's where they're from yeah but that's not the minions movie that move that's a that movie is
steve carell plays a cartoon character the minions are not that's that's come on how do i get over
this your web huh i can climb that way oh that was fucking horrible i hated that
6500 people heard that damn that's bad that's all right that was fucking horrible that was like
that was really bad my voice like i was like trailing off a little too long yeah that was
terrible that was really really really bad remember get in front of it like if i like
people can't clip that now and go wow holy shitty sounds fucking like stupid here i told you i sound
stupid i win wait the tarantula hawks are going after the tarantula what am i supposed to do
oh you're a bad tarantula hawk oh really three come in whoa oh you're making me so fucking mad
fuck come on do something i get it got it what was what's with this be funny in all capitals
what the fuck are you talking about
okay uh what do you say to uh uh what do you say to a guy that uh walks into a bar with uh
two liters of coca cola what what did he say what this motherfucker just ate a shoe
i think you can play a spider game for an hour just be funny now hold on
oh i gotta give myself a comedy injection okay uh is that better
what do you think is gonna happen here what do you think this is
community crack dude you have to make wacky sound effects every 30 seconds
do do what no shit bugs this stream was fucked up what am i supposed to do in here
what is it one a skull something inside the skull oh shit i need that help give to me
look at me this is pickle rick some of you guys man it's like that whole thing like uh like oh you
do funny tell me a joke okay dad oh yeah i heard you're quite the funny guy i heard you stream on
twitch and you fucking do funny stuff why don't you tell me a joke right now son um okay mr
stevenson um i would um i i can't i thought you're supposed to be fucking funny kid yeah
you know when i was younger i told all kinds of funny jokes about this one like oh you're
clown make me laugh i ripped off louis ck he's very he's got a very good point let me tell you i
guess i guess i don't know what what's going on here oh that was another bad one that one was
not intentional that that one was just bad that one was way worse but it was not even really
intentional god oh here comes billy bob thorton to say this and that and that's
and there and i'll take two million that was a seinfeld noise if he doesn't say a joke soon
i'm gonna leave well i good nice good to see you oh look at all these jumps no no this i'm not
going to click on illegal streams no i'm sorry you guys do have fucking one on your own chair
i'm not doing it i'm not clicking on a terms of service like cars 2 stream okay no i'm not
gonna do it because that if i do it then it gives precedence for you to do it and then we all get
in trouble did you don't look at that zip you guys are fucking crazy that was a one hit kill
stealth pounce and then press a okay let's try it holy shit that is like hunter in left for dead
range for me your existence alone is funny with smile what was that supposed to mean
what is that supposed to mean your life is a joke when when when when did we release all the rude
viewers then where do they all do they all come out at the same time what time is it they're
always here dude that's the best move in the whole game who's hitting me rude he thinks this is rude
just watch this i know i know i know i know you're gonna i know i know he thinks that's rude i'll
check this out i know i know i know okay grown man plays a wee on stream you grown uh grown
man ate a shoe an hour or two ago not much there's not much else you could probably say
at this point spiders are rude i don't know all bugs are rude what do i get in here is there
enough am i missing something i can't get in this it wants me to go like up here the game's level
design is actually kind of good it's interesting the game like this could be really really fucking
confusing and it's not the arrow helps if you need it which i do game you can go upside down
it's i appreciate the fact that there's a little arrow just it's so easy it's such a simple little
tool it's perfect happy birthday you go fuck yourself what are you talking about the arrow
is cheating this is rude all these rude viewers today isn't being so rude the heck is going on
in here the heck are you doing this is why it's my birthday today you can't be rude to me on my
birthday all right i gotta pay attention i don't want to restart this whole fucking area no i know
what's going on i know what's going on this is because i didn't watch the bugs livestream and
i told you guys to stop watching it now i get it that's what happened that's where all this
comes from oh my god there's two of them ups ups did i miss fuck one dead good what stop looking
at chat all right damn is there nothing even in here it was just a secret fight two dragons what
no you go up the hole three to 17 you guys are like often some kind of fucking stream crack drug
did i watch wrestlemania i did not actually never it's my birthday in a couple months say
happy birthday to me happy birthday in a couple months first time we've seen this
look that's all the progress we were all the way down to the trunk we got all the way up here
watch classic wrestling doesn't that wwe network or the wwe app or whatever allow you to watch
full episodes of raw from like 2002 and stuff is it a full moon tonight i could have guessed
i could have guessed my god don't fall don't fall don't fall there another web right over here
right over here jeez okay we're gonna be going uh no what is it where i was
uh oh over there okay i see don't stay stick on that oh perspective is freaking me out
all right we go ikaruga waiting room i i beat ikaruga i beat ikaruga on stream actually okay
i beat ikaruga on stream with a little bit of help i i i beat ikaruga on stream by cheating on
some of the levels on all the levels i cheated on ikaruga on on the on the normal difficulty
finally we're gonna what's left oh wait was he buried no this don't make any sense
what are these squiggly things all over it puts cactus come on grab the shovels
interesting jump do i go into the coffin i think i'm gonna go in the coffin this is gonna be weird
got it journey to the citadel cactus there's no uh singing by the way i lose feed oh i he's dead
feed now feed now oh well reach the lizard den wait for him to come back holy i hit the
fucking cricket are you serious i i did all that to hit the cricket that was next to him
oh good move he's dazed get him play viva piata i don't think you want me to do that
feed feed feed no i'm not gonna i'm not gonna play viva piata got him in the air shoot again
oh play mario kart you're just saying that because you know how i feel about mario kart
you beat him all right this is like a big long corridor climb up there right there
then it was the next one right there oh i'm upside down no what what's happened
did i really just fall on my back i'm flat on my back how far away was that
who wwe network stream oh that's pretty far watch wwe no i'm not gonna watch wwe right out
i'm trying to play the spider game end of the stream voice uh not quite coming up here soon
though not quite not quite did i like ray mysterio ray mysterio was fucking awesome
all right i'm gonna go over here when is hulk uh so because of the coronavirus amazon is not
shipping a lot of stuff or it's where it's delayed like prime two-day shipping doesn't really exist
so it's kind of just it kind of just coming it's going to come when it comes it's going to get
here when it gets it will get it when it gets here you said you would buy it a month ago i know
and i know he's lying no i'm not go to go to hulk ultimate destruction on the game cube right now
on amazon and find one and the shipping dates are within like the next couple weeks things are coming
faster than you think it's just giving out a date just in case well okay there we go i don't lie
about everything guys just the most stuff 30 webcams yeah that's also impossible too because
also due to the coronavirus webcams are in very short supply right now
and so they were either completely out of stock or they're two hundred dollars for one that's
also another unfortunate thing why is the game why is this game 77 dollars why is the game 77
wait why is what do you mean microphones too yeah but it makes sense though it makes sense because
tons of people are working from home and conferencing from home and people are communicating
over you know the social distancing so it makes sense as to why the webcams wouldn't be really
um something that's very very readily available right now uh but yeah we just we have to figure
that out whenever those come back into stock maybe we can see how things are and get them done all
right i gotta okay i'm like upside down let me see what the hell i'm doing
play visceral let me just let me just get through this part first
okay so i think i've done like every level in district cleanup haven't i
no play house flipper well when they add something new i'll play it
house flipper has been the same game since garden flipper i played that they did when what do they
add what is it what is it they added space wait are we talking about this for cleanup we're talking
about house flipper let's see anything i'm going right away house both all right we saw this we
can't skip it though you got the map these guys what's this like any sense what are these squiggly
things all over all right somebody's watching another movie on twitch with my likeness on it
grab the shovels explain the plot you're a fucking mean bug see i didn't even do that he did that on
his own all right let's go this part was hard and i got killed i fell off the fucking thing
get into the top of the cactus and only then can i stop this stream bug wars 24 hours no
it's not gonna take that long this can't fall off the edge i want a spill joke i can't do spill
jokes not that they were on purpose anyways but like a spill joke is bad and i have spilled
shit on on this desk when i first put this desk together if those either remember i spilled an
entire fucking 16 ounce thing of coffee on it that's like the third or fourth day that i got it
and it was infuriating i the stream was delayed by like an hour and a half
and i was so fucking angry on stream some of you guys might remember it
yeah but i don't want to i don't want i don't want to i like this desk i don't want to just
roll it with like a soda or like a coffee when was that like a year and a half ago
i don't remember anything yes you do you remember what no jump on him finally i got him feed why
didn't i just kind of feed on him feed hey and then what he's that didn't work all right this
is where i fell off when are you gonna watch the march 12th episode of brah why i don't even what
i don't guy you didn't okay i don't watch brah i don't watch wrestling anymore the last time
that i i actually saw last time i watched wrestling was hell in a cell it was like a few years ago
and i remember watching and going well this is not this is like really not good every event they
took they tried to like break a table like four times and it like didn't work i think that like
they was like here comes the table and like they couldn't get somebody to break through the table
i remember being like well this is they like can't do that now why
just watch wrestlemania 17 i don't even know what when are they on 30 what wrestlemania are
they on right now i didn't eat him around 30 36 okay all right here we go let's go i'm not closing
hey hey oh okay now we gotta go this way did i do it again i do the same thing i did last time again
oh go up here it's starting to hurt my head starting to this area in particular is starting
to make me sick okay i made it stop squishing your face well i have to look as it otherwise
i'll throw off here comes a puke i'm sure you guys would like that there we go save all right
so what was the what's the deal here i wonder how many of you okay i've reached the lizard i did it
well there's a trap it's just two it's not bad i did this before i'm going for pounds no i'm not
that was dumb just don't get hit feed feed feed feed feed how come it only works like some of the
time i don't get it it's like double dragon just keep doing the kick what the fuck some more
how many more do i have to kill oh i don't know why i'm trying to do that
there's gonna be a huge one that falls after this i guarantee it oh fuck all right that was stupid
that was really dumb all right get up i get i can't die here shit dodged it got it beat crawl
upside down you can now crawl upside down i couldn't do that already into the octopus canyon
why do i have to go into octopus canyon we want a spill joke what the fuck are you talking about
all right you know the last time i played visceral people were like doing resident sleepers and shit
you guys gotta come to like a consensus you guys are gonna come to and even if you do remember
i've got the ultimate veto this thing i stamped that down i'm the guy with the ultimate veto we'll
see what i want to play right ultimate veto stamp what does that say veto capital is red all red
letters in a big red box v e t o oh oh oh oh t t you're quick i'll give you it extreme extreme
paint brawl that game doesn't even run that game notoriously is known for the game it doesn't run
smash brother's brawl now that's a new one okay here we go here we go everybody everybody just
yell out your favorite game all right let's go i'll i'll do it too
play math game play math play math game my question is my own comment this is cool looking
octopus cavern cool math games we already did that oh a horned lizard oh i can't jump on him
he's hurts i don't want to hurt the horn lizard he's kind of i like horn lizards they're cool
wait he called an ad what is this a fight that you would really happen in nature what a torrential
fight fucking horn lizard that seems kind of oh they spit blood out of their eyes i remember that
shit they spit blood out of their fucking eyes don't they yeah yep i remember this thing this
is the blood spouting eye lizard i think that actually has another name oh he's in the spikes
i don't chat his chat is ignorant what because they didn't know that the that that lizard shoots
blood out of its eye check the spider moves check them jump strike swipe overthrow that's when you
like lift them up jump strike we do that spin attack i do that web shot i do that venom pounce
that's hard to do it takes too long double strike yep and then you buzz saw so a then hold a and
then shake left and right okay stealth pounce speed let's try buzz saw is that am i i don't
think i'm doing that right spiders shoot blood out of their eyes i don't think so i don't think they
can no more spiders too okay that's the new thing now when i'm about to like end the stream when
the stream's coming to a close okay and that's how you guys know ah here we go it comes again
i'm not i'm no longer gonna be like all right so this is kind of cool
so we got uh what i think okay um i yeah it's uh hold on just a second here
that's my favorite bug that's praying mantis we'll see once and for all who fucking can win
we'll see remember i told you what it was frog then praying mantis
chop that he got me one hit got him it's a good fight and i thought i'd press c
fuck he's fucking hard praying mantis is so strong in the fucking real world in games and stuff i
guess he always it was close it was pretty close you can now chop your pinchers super monkey
ball waiting room you're gonna be waiting a long time how old do you know how old everybody
oh by the extreme caps and screaming at the streamer i've gotta assume that you're under
the age of fucking 16 so let's find out uh let's just write no cap to the streamer
uh let's see i have i'm curious let's find out i'm 35 oh fuck 17 idiot i'm the bully but i'm the
bully it's me it's me the guy i have two boxing gloves and i'll hold them up like this well
and i peek out i go fuck you what do you want can i oh shit did i get anybody
okay all right all right there's 200 people there oh i can't fight y'all those are weird punches
what was i saying i was oh i was angry let me be like all right so uh we can beat him if we work
together oh yeah can you because what i'm doing here is i'm building a fucking energy and i'm
just gonna fuck it it's gonna be a god there's gonna be a spirit bomb that comes out of me you
don't want to punch me when i'm in my closed position you don't it's just gonna the meters
filling up my head and then i just go and it's just light it's just light blue it's blue light
and i just throw it into the big mistake man he's on crack derma shoots poop out of his eyes
okay i'm gone i'm out of here i'm fucking out of here i'm out of here i'm done today i'm done
too much crack today i'm done today we're gonna come back on wednesday we win you don't win you
don't win i was gonna stop right now anyway i was gonna stop anyway poop out of his eyes you're
gonna i'm gonna fucking sneeze watch ww i'm not gonna fucking this all started because of like
watch bugs life guy guy gonna get twitch arrested put on bugs life put on cars
put on roger rabbit put on put on this tv show put up put on hey all right that's enough
i don't you don't want to do this it is blue okay um you couldn't you couldn't really
couldn't really tell that was like a big explosion but it was so
cool it was blue the light was blue and i got i got you that's what happened old man tries to
bully kids well i think if people are gonna just write in all caps their favorite video game what
right right right he's out of touch you still haven't played beautiful joe
i haven't this game is fun though i like this one what's wrong with having a fortnight game
what i can't understand you i can't even understand you say that again i can't understand
what you're saying oh oh okay speak speak up sonny all right here's the deal so uh we're going to
continue with our new plan here of four to fiveish hours four or five days a week i'm
gonna start it today i'm gonna i'm i'm gonna call it here we're gonna give it a try you have to
stay longer i'm not done bullying you and that person for 30 minutes 45 showers a day that would
be fucked up uh all right so on uh we're gonna do so today we're gonna do wednesday thursday friday
probably saturday we're gonna do nothing tomorrow i'm gonna do four days in a row so we're gonna
try this we're gonna try like four five hour streams four five days a week am i gonna do
animal crossing yeah it's just that's been the one thing that we can do that's at the other place
reliably so it's not here it's for three streams per day that'd be a lot but uh we're gonna give
it a try this game is really cool this game is really cool this over this week we'll see
i don't know about that i'm gonna otto that one uh anyways uh we got plenty of things to play
just a question of what we want to play next i still want to play resident evil 3
oh maybe maybe hulk ultimate destruction actually will come in and it won't be the
shipping date that it actually has we'll see there's also no more heroes there's also
i do have the beautiful joes i do have a saw for xbox 360 which don't ask me why i own that game
but i do please play that and then yeah community content night exists as well
but we'll see i'll see you guys on wednesday we're gonna try this new schedule out i'm gonna
give it a go thanks for uh sticking around a lot of fucking people here today where's the shoe
go watch the beginning of the stream i promise you that there is a shoe somewhere in that first
little while you'll see it i do i eat it that's something you're gonna have to find out on your
own take one more bite it's gone i can't all right i'll see you guys on wednesday we're gonna move to
the bits and subs and all that good stuff there's a lot of fucking money today a lot i will donate
fifty dollars if you watch wwe right now i'd rather you spend that fifty dollars on yourself
not on me because i'm not gonna watch wwe use that and buy yourself a wwe subscription
buy yourself a wwe subscription sir for like six months but anyways let's go back earlier
to lm man 500 bits from lm man germa you are a coward for not eating a shoe
hey sure did have to eat hey you sure had had to eat those words didn't you like i did hey wembley
ttv thanks for the 250 boopers chads rise up i don't know what that means but i said it hey
dedicated thanks for the 250 for sale streamer shoes never eaten peaceful hailey thanks for the
250 hey i don't want to seem weird but you look good today also the shoe bit was stupid
did good thank you though lm man 500 bits i apologize germa i was too rash
you are a brave wild man for eating a shoe something that chat will never do
for we are true cowards some of you may have eaten a shoe before i don't know
oh this is gonna be so many fucked up images from that i can i can already
smelly boy thanks for the 250 i didn't know they made shoes with untied laces baked into the side
so you don't know anything uh mad thanks to the five dollars haha funny shoe eater streamer
has sensitive baby feet has to wear sugar shoes like an oompa loompa very stinky streamer haha
stream joke who poopoo peepee put it on reddit get his toes for real good luck on house hunting
i can't man you guys all right let me you guys you guys dialed it up a little bit here
you dialed up like the the crack some words shouldn't be spoken i had to turn the stream
off because somebody said he poopoos out of his eyes and shit like i i i you were gone for a week
is this the the pent up energy of of everybody that just is gonna scream at me you just shouldn't
have read that comment that's like asking a bee not to produce honey it's all they do they don't
do anything else all i do is read your comments that say crazy fucking shit it's i i have to
anyways let's keep going hey jason thanks for the 250 jason thank you if you're getting stronger
for vr streams does that mean 500 sub bicep germa is coming back no no that just means
i'm staying loose the looser that i stay the better that i feel that's kind of the reasoning
for pulling streams back but adding stream days so i can stream essentially the same amount of time
but spread out for less time per stream because i can stay loose easier that way that's the idea
see if it works uh but thank you jzzb for the thousand bits sorry you had to eat that shoe
it was probably really gross and sugary isn't that bad it actually was pretty good i didn't
hate it click the link click the link click the link click the link click the link full moon crack
full moon crack full moon crack oh god got the hair down perfectly oh jesus
it's fucking i should you know i know you know why it was like a cry you know why it was a crack
stream today because i probably should have saved the eat the shoe for like the end of the stream
because eating the shoe in the very beginning was like oh whoa we're going to fucking a million
right now and we got i got everybody too excited you opened it up too early
so i riled everybody up and then it's like all right let's play the spider game
you can't you like can't go play like the spider game after you eat a fucking shoe on camera
that's my mistake we're kindergarten children
four movies stop saying that you all right you're freaking me out stop stop all right stop stop
linking people streaming movies here like you're gonna get us all fucking in trouble
stop all right give me a little bit give me a little bit of slack here like half the time
when i looked over during the stream it was somebody somebody linking the legal movie stream
four times the illegality it wasn't that often oh it was it was it was every 10 seconds i'm
embellishing but i whatever it was every like four minutes it was every 10 seconds officially
endorsed no oh my fucking god that person's gonna get banned you're gonna you're gonna get banned
for life just saying just want to let you know if you do that you're gonna get banned for life
you're gonna ban you for life they're gonna ban you for life and then you're never gonna be able
to come back all right all right i'm moving on i'm moving on moving on moving on moving on
moving on moving on moving on moving on moving on moving on moving on moving on moving on
snk thanks for the 10 community sub yeah thanks for the 10 subs snk really appreciate it lonely
animator thanks for the thousand bits is this turning into another the thing money stream again
there was a lot today there was a lot today staff is here good good i hope they're here
i hope they're here it was them it was these guys these people right here i didn't do anything
i have been saying since the stream started no don't do that it's not okay it was them it was all
them i didn't do anything why why are you cuffing me i didn't do anything what hey he's snitching i
but i didn't know i was very adamant saying don't do this shit it's not all right and that's what i
said i made my statement and i made sure that i said it to you and all of you you told you what
was gonna happen i told you was gonna happen this is like when your mother told you wear a fucking
helmet on your bike if you fall down on your bike you're gonna get hurt and you fell down you
didn't have shin pads on you scraped up your whole fucking knee and you came home crying where are
you shin pads i told you anyways uh boikey gave a shitload of money that i missed it was five
thousand bits fifty dollars fifty bucks i missed it is this the guy who beat a shoe on stream with
eat in brackets the house slipper update is real all right so you ate a shoe like i ate a
fucking shoe like it like it turned everybody up to a million i ate a shoe on stream and it made
people start streaming movies do you understand how fucked up that is all right let's keep going
there's so much ripple effect this guy's eating a fucking shoe he's eating a shoe on stream holy
fuck oh fuck i gotta i gotta lash out somewhere um he just ate a whole shoe all right uh stream
movies scream i gotta scream at him scream in his face yeah i gotta lash out at him i gotta lash
out now fuck the scorpion game no no no no fuck this guy where's the uh where's the other shoe
you're wondering i didn't have to eat two shoes because sans is a fucking me costume that was
part of the rule that was part of the game why do you even twitch chat is twitch staff is
were you here for the shoe eating hey windar thanks for the five dollars hey jeremy loving
the content that shoe looked like shit i just want to say fuck you but in the nicest way possible
what the fuck is going on today hey jeremy loving the content the shoe looked like shit besides
that just want to say fuck you uh in the nicest way possible because i've started making baby
noises after you did it i'm doing it right now i can't stop i don't understand dragon bro i i
ain't ever taken i ain't ever taken more than like five days off ever again it's like there's a clog
in the drain and then you like there's so much water pressure behind this clog well it's like
the clog's been there for six or seven days like when i undo the clog i just get sprayed in the
face of what like the water just sprays everywhere it's just it's flushed this is a germa torture
stream no i think it's fucking i think it's oh shit i can't i'm gonna say the thing no i think
it's funny but uh yeah uh i know i think it's funny right the thing that everybody fucking says
oh no no this person you don't think that's funny at all you're actually annoyed by that
no i mean like i think i think it's funny but like you really shouldn't be doing that
oh fuck he's melting down frack what happened it's not even may what's wrong with may
what who's he talking to what's going on you guys are freaking me out watch wwe and then ban me for
life fine write that name down i've watched my i will watch my favorite uh old moments from wwe
at some point soon and then we're gonna ban that person for life uh shark shark oh supreme thanks
for the 1500 bits 15 dollars simpsons hit and run broke his fucking spine no it's just too
it's too long in a chair i was having problems way before simpsons hit and run was i where was
simpsons hit and run in vegas simpsons hit and run was in vegas yeah i was having yeah this was
i was having problems before that yeah no i was having problems before i moved to vegas
that's when it started but unfortunately i think there's gonna have to be no more of those
there's gonna have to be no more of those 10 plus hour streams so we can put in the history books
the longest stream ever is going to be that lord of the rings the two towers stream it's going to
be there's 13 and a half hours that's going to be the number one most streamed dime ever in one
stream it's never gonna get past i don't think that'll ever happen hey goo berry juice thanks
to the 750 hey shoe chewer 985 i'm still amazed you actually did the shoe bit i'm also so sorry
we missed your birthday last wednesday what nonetheless happy birthday hopefully you can
keep making amazing streams like this one love you dude where's this birthday thing coming from
what's the birthday thing i feel like i'm on a different planet today okay i you're just you're
fucking gonna be gone like yeah i that's just not what the fuck do you want me to say to that
that's a wicked fucked up what how would what's my response the correct response to that image
what's the what should i say there cool nice
i'm into that no can i stop thank you goo berry juice for the 420 they say nice nice
thank you tits on fire for the 10 subs we got it earlier i think lonely animator again no no
that's why it's pop up twice looks like another the thing money stream to me no no this is different
yeah no this this is this is the same no it's not the first one was 10 lonely animated give 10 000
no no 1000 and then 1500 okay i don't know why they popped up strangely thanks for the 15 bucks
looks like it is another the thing money stream sometimes you guys just smoke crack and give me
five thousand dollars that does happen and it's fucking crazy the thing stream was god tier
the game was so hard fuck that game man that those bosses and shit i mean i loved that game
in like a jokey kind of way but some of those bosses were so stupid it was just so bad i loved
it for the wrong reasons the thing face yeah that did happen there too thanks for playing that so i
don't have to welcome autumn dragons thanks for 250 hey german glad to have you back tarantulas
are normally very docile even in the wild and rely shooting out the irritating hairs they have instead
they aren't exactly great animals for petting but they're still very shy and cute don't you all agree
chat i would let a tarantula crawl in my mouth i already said it yeah that wouldn't bother me
now if you put it put me in the same room with a general small house spider i will i refuse to go
in the room until somebody else takes care of it it's funny how that works really uh thank you afro
mancer for the 1500 bits cheers to you germa thank you for the years of laughter and for easily being
the best streamer on twitch i appreciate that thank you you deserve it your pal ethan thank you
thanks for the 1500 bits and thanks for the incredibly kind message appreciate it
large 27x thanks for the thousand bits germa do the funny after you read that i assume you did
the funny so thanks dude i have what we talked about this earlier i don't even what what is that
i don't even know what that means i'm gonna do something funny i okay okay how what do i do
how do i do that what buttons do i press how do i press the right button to make the funny thing
say the line um ranch where the ranch did it work it works every time hey topac thanks for the 250
hope you're staying safe during these times i was quite intrigued with the products you had on your
amazon marketplace the other day glad you're providing means for some people to stay indoors
what germa adult toy rusting what okay what what what why does that exist i don't even know that
okay thanks with 250 uh shibir shib shibir shibir ear wha i think i said that right hopefully
thanks with three bucks here's to you clown known about you since rat movie but only really started
watching on and off since the salmon mac streams just started going through the archive recently
because of this uh covid lockdown and your brand of insanity has helped me keep me sane during
these trying times anyway here's a few chocolate coins uh from a newish loyal viewer i hope you
and everyone stays safe you as well and that goes for all of you thank you for 300 bits and
welcome to um maybe being a regular viewer maybe glad to have you goo berry juice thanks for the
three dollars and 16 cents 316 show the vince walker is there a gift everybody says everybody
seen the vince walk is so i feel like the vince walk is the we've all seen the gift so many times
that you don't even need to click an image you just it's up to there it is i see it all right
i showed it like i showed it already i mean like i you you thought it so you saw it because everyone's
seen it a million times i don't know what this is all right you guys you guys can't automatically
assume that just because something says the word germa on it that i i know what it is judging by
the like 400 red bubble merchandise pieces that are on there gnarly thanks to the 250 when will
glue man stun the entire elbertson family maybe someday soon uh large 27x thanks for the thousand
bits do the walk i believe i did when you asked me to sir canine thanks to the 250 still in spider
land omega lull the game's good the game's good sir canine again thanks 250 also i'm fucking appalled
that you didn't instantly put whoppers into the trash tier on the candy tier list they're literally
the equivalent of chocolate coated chalk balls um they're okay like i like that like crunchy
gritty kind of texture to them sometimes it depends if you feel like it they're okay they're not
i wouldn't i wouldn't order them but if they were in a candy dish and
i was awkwardly talking to some friends or something that i haven't seen in a long time
i would just keep eating them to make it so i had something for my mouth to do besides talk so i
could just listen forever and like i'm eating your i'm eating your entire fucking bowl of
chocolate to make sure that i can't really speak and i can nod and be like like like very very
clearly like yeah i mean you know i'm you see i'm eating that whole bowl will be gone uh og don't
uh og john dude thanks for the 500 bits love you jerma glad to see you having a good time i'm always
having a good time that's not exactly that's the line um maybe like 98.9 percent of the time
sometimes i don't i don't have fun in a video game and i get angry at it for a minute that's
only like one percent no that's like 0.2 percent and 98.5 percent yeah that's right well i did i
did yell at somebody today and call them a 16 year old didn't i i did that today but i wasn't
mad though that was me trying to make like a like a like a like a like an edgy joke
right it's 17 it was 17 and it was me and i am 17 he's so edgy uh today was a wild one
today was a wild fucking stream you're fucking bully no we already went over it
okay if you're like holding a bunch of groceries and you take the time to like peer over and like
scream at me while i drive by and be like stupid idiot and you drop like the milk out of your
grocery bag that's not my fault wait does that make any sense for this context no no no no no
that doesn't make sense does it no do you have bad groceries and you're like fucking screaming
at me you stupid dumb idiot god like i walked by you on the street and you drop all your groceries
no no yeah that'll make sense i didn't do that no i turn no no no no no no no no no no no no i
got it i got it i got it just wait wait we're walking down the street you're coming towards
me and i'm coming towards you you have groceries i don't so we i'm um i'm i've got a camera in front
of me and i'm facetiming my grandmother or something and all of a sudden when we walk by
you just go shut up stupid idiot you stupid dumb fucking moron and i go hey i'm like what the
fuck was that and i turn and i'm like hold on a second grandma hey and you turn startled and
you drop all your groceries oh yeah oh you what did you just do to me you asshole that's what
is this real that's what that works right that would not be my fault no wouldn't no i would be
responding to you i'd be like hey what did you say and like oh you what you didn't think i was
gonna respond back long story short double bag don't carry more than you can fucking hold it
don't be uh don't be one of those don't be one of those fucking people i have to take it all in
one trip from the car i gotta do like a full clothing rack on my right arm and an entire
suit rack on my left arm and then i walk in it's turning into like a stand-up routine all right
let's go i'm done thank you tar alecran for the 250 durham i just saw the clips from the beginning
of the stream if i did that on stage at an open mic remember we were gonna do that that's still
on the table by the way is for me to stream me at an open mic night and just try to do like comedy
and just do shit like that let's see what happens he's gonna bomb so fucking hard
well you'll see it live if it happens please don't do it why why what's the concern funny
should i be should i get introduced as the funniest man in the world that's a good idea
now introducing jeremy the funniest man in the world elbertson automatically people would be so
mad like shut the fuck up like that's so that's so funny okay go on do your fucking thing
anyways uh we had five community subs from finch and what do you say we show the community subs
right now on stream and the regular subs and the subs from today all the subs all of them
i'm gonna show them all right now thanks again guys as always let's no no no no no no no
excuse me that was going real fast holy shit how many subs today okay that okay um that's
400 that was like 450 subs today holy shit this is three and a half four and a half hours
you guys spoil the fuck out of me i mean i could i gotta eat more shoes
thanks a lot though really appreciate it and right here at the end wingman won
five community subs thanks wingman thank you and wingman won gave five dollars earlier as well
when i was in summer camp in 2010 i felt something crawling on my face in the middle of the night
i picked it up and tossed it over the bunk i still don't know what it was well the terrifying thing
about what you're saying here is it was big enough for you to grab with your hand if it was big
enough for you to hold in your hand and throw that's terrifying i think everyone's had a scenario
like that play out potentially in their life where you just don't know what it was and it
could be anything and then you just never know and never knowing is awful because what the hell was
it and what could it could it be possible that that could happen again it actually happens not
super frequently but not infrequently enough where you don't realize it's happening
how many times do you feel just something like touch your arm or like your leg or something when
you're lying down in bed and it's just like rip toss throw as fucking hard as i can in that
in left direction and you just have no idea and you'll never know it could have been a piece of
hair and you'll never know an anonymous cheerer thanks for five dollars 500 bits just 500 bits
dropping him right here thank you reaper thanks for 250 hey since the rumble is until september
because of covet 19 can we maybe get a sneak peek event advertising the rumble it's been too
long since we've seen our friends from the ring um yeah yeah the plan is this is the plan the rumble
and a few matches will happen in september before the marathon but probably gonna do
do a small card of kind of a pre matches with no rumble so instead of having the the big main event
being the 30 person rumble and it's like an hour we'll just do some matches with some new characters
and the rumble will be in september so maybe like a few weeks leading up to the the rumble
we'll do that or maybe we won't and maybe i'll just save everything and just have a huge event
because that rumble is going to be for charity that's going to be a charity stream those that
don't know all the money that's going to come through that stream is going to be directly
given to charity there's going to be a direct link it'll be tracked it'll be easy we'll have all that
set up so it's just completely just transparent and there it is and it open so it might be better
to have it all be one big you know three four five hour event rather than one small one that
would be much better i think we'll see but that's the plan still scheduled for september not sure
we want to do before it hey demonic cucumber thanks for 250 i haven't given any bits in a
while because i've missed a lot of streams from my new sleep schedule i didn't really know what to
say when i did thank you for all the entertainment and being an actual inspiration sorry that chat
got kind of rowdy today but i did like this game a lot and you're only halfway through it i'd love
to see you play the other chapters another day lots of germa love to you i thought no i thought
it was i thought chat was all right until they started screaming their favorite video games at
me and um please click on the guy that's streaming seven movies at the same time and get your channel
banned that's when i had to draw the line that's where i had to draw the line you told us to no i
i i was reacting to i was pretending to be you that's why i was doing like the oh hey let's do
this he still isn't banned that's fucking crap i don't know how that's possible i love a marie rpg
fuck what the fuck no anyways thank you trans scalp for the 500 bits germa i struggle with eye
contact too it was oddly comforting to hear that my favorite streamer is also not great at constant
eye contact thanks for the weird brain representation also don't forget about the
tarantula mouth stream uh i i will now just all over the place you know the thing is i
i talk out in just in so many different directions that nobody fucking cares or knows or notices
like i go bang over here eye contact bang at the wall bang looking at my phone bang in your eyes
again over here what's that there's a light over there my eyes are that way i'm talking about my
hands my hands are moving and then and flashing my palms up over that way right in your eyes eye
contact again right like i'm just i'm just so all over the place people just like oh that's what he
does oh that's good he's got laser eyes hey wolfgang thanks for the 500 bits i donated ten dollars
since you didn't watch wwe on stream wait what i did though laser eyes rtx 4 20 69 ti great name
i say it every time 250 during a while back you said you wanted a pet reptile of some kind
have your feelings changed do you have an update for us i was looking around for something that
would be something i really want to take care of and but the move has been a lot more complicated
because of all the coronavirus stuff so it hasn't really been a simple process to kind of move and
get everything done and situated and that's it um so that's kind of been put on the back burner
for a while until things sort of settle down and decide if that's something that i actually
really want to do i do though what was that pinball that was uh odama odama dobski dude
thanks for 250 here i just wanted to recommend you a game called rain world it's really difficult
and has beautiful pixel art visuals plays a little like jump king i think you'd love it just don't
play it for only one hour and then ditch it for boomer games like river piata haha but we know
you'd never do that haha you know what i mean haha where is my rain train boys at choo choo
okay i hold on a second here uh i i you want to talk about the bully i was bullied into playing
rain world remember i was doing something else and it was just like this constant spam of play
that wasn't my choice i did that because people were screaming at me i didn't i i didn't go hey
guys today we're gonna play rain world i was doing something else and it was just a sea of rain
train crew members that was my first choice and i played it and i thought it was interesting i
thought it was cool and i just stamped a fucking veto on it oh god damn it this thing is always
gonna fall down this thing will fall down every single time i have to like i'm gonna like drill
this to the top of the monitor otto he's breaking everything it's a wee sense of bar you can use two
candles it'll do the same thing true act that's actually true actually no that's true true that's
actually wow no he's right he's right he's right he's actually right l u l that's correct actually
correct i know i know hey razzle thanks for the 250 it's my birthday tomorrow it's my birthday
tomorrow it's my birthday tomorrow it's my birthday tomorrow it's my birthday tomorrow it's
my birthday tomorrow okay happy birthday uh razzle 250 again can i cast a curse on you
i'm not gonna read this out loud no don't do that somebody remove it this i i don't want
any i don't want any good curses no more curses don't i'm not gonna read that out loud i don't
know what the fuck that is no curses just somebody somebody decurse me can somebody this gotta be
somebody in here there's 3200 people watching right fucking now one of you one of you has to
be kind of into this shit right like one of you is gonna be into this shit like the whole cursing
and and like witchcraft is it just take it off now take it i know one of you does seriously please
i know you will somebody's gonna listen to this and be like oh actually i i am into that that's
like i'm into like kind of the energies and of like the earth and and and spells and shit just
do it take please take remove the curses from me there's like six of them on me right now and
like people keep doing them to me get take them off just take them off take them off take the
curse off somebody in this chat is gonna do it i'm gonna be so happy when you do i all i can do
is make your penis smaller don't don't do that either don't do that one if i wake up tomorrow
and it i will be so mad don't do that use a different one use okay no no i use like every
time i like eat a tomato i fucking cry or something i'd rather have that please no no all right i gotta
go hey wingman thanks for the five subs already got you don't curse me everyone's gonna do the
small penis curse to me and it's gonna be it's gonna be gone tomorrow can you fucking imagine
like in the mirror in your house and you you're doing it like an incantation to make a streamer
on the internet's penis smaller can you imagine doing that and and like going to sleep in your bed
and being ah that was a good day i'm gonna lose my fucking mind all right so if half of you're
gonna do it half of you make sure you do the one that makes it bigger okay i'm gonna address you
directly now i'm gonna address you directly um it's it's been like a week and i've only
streamed like three or four times in the last like 16 days or something we're shaking off the cobwebs
a little bit here we're getting back into the swing of things and sometimes a streamer hasn't
been streaming for a while and he says things like half of you do a curse on me to make my penis
smaller and half of you do one to make it bigger sometimes that happens when you haven't streamed
in a while and i just want to apologize um for uh the sort of uh under construction that we have
here you know what i mean um i i apologize the balance must remain why would you want some people
to do it smaller no i don't did i no no i was saying like if that's gonna happen that i need
for you guys to do the other just take them off all right i'm done goodbye see you tomorrow no i'm
not even streaming tomorrow i'm streaming on wednesday all right it's been a while i forgot
how to stream we're not even done with bits this is not even the right screen the music's not even
playing yes it is hey couscous thanks for the 250 hi you're my first live stream i've caught
been watching you since tf2 you're the reason i have a twitch account this is even better than
the second channel on youtube hey thanks i think they both work very good together i think they
both work hand in hand it's like chocolate and peanut butter combine them together
only eat the eggs though or the trees you're getting ripped off regular rices suck get the
trees or get the eggs because you don't you get way more chocolate cream you don't get that like
gross ridge bullshit but thank you hey skunkos thanks for the 300 bits also love from boston
it's nice to watch your streams being holed up in my room they say he's so cracked it's not even
funny what you guys never had rices eggs or rices trees before the holiday ones the regular rices
have the ridge of chocolate and then the center is peanut butter you guys have never had a rices
tree before or rices egg what do you what no no you've never had a rices tree for christmas
like the holiday ones for easter and eggs and how come every time i say something that sounds so
normal everyone looks at me like i've got fucking 12 heads the eggs and christmas trees slaps yeah
i know i'm i'm what you aren't normal i'm very normal i was about to turn the webcam on and be
like would somebody normal do this and like fucking i was gonna put my fingers like in my eyes and
like screaming shit hey red ranger thanks for the 1400 bits hope all is well with you
i highly recommend pet reptiles i have worked with them for a few years now and they can be
amazing to keep good luck with the move your bearded dragons are awesome they're super fun
they're really chill or a crested gecko there's another one it just seemed like you can just
kind of hang out with them let them give them a bunch of cool stuff for them to hang out with in
their uh tank or whatever this is a clint's reptile shill i yes i've seen every single one
of his videos you don't think i would be a consumer of clint's reptiles crested gecko is a 4.6 out of
five that's from clint bearded dragons make your house smell like petco for your information
my bits are a d cursing spell by the way thank you thank you hey egg scramble thanks for the 500
bits hey you have a great stream i was very cozy drinking coffee listening to you they made me
happy love you and chat sleep well tonight guys hey that's a that's a wicked nice just really good
nice comment to everybody your penis is oh stop why did i even read it i saw i started to i just
saw the p word i had to start reading it it came true i would never tell you guys if it came true
what am i going to start the stream on wednesday hey guys uh peter shrink just in case anybody
wanted to know it worked i'm not going to open the stream with that hey wolfgang thanks for 500
bits now i have to explain myself i was going to donate 50 dollars but you didn't watch classic
wwe later on in the stream so i had to donate only 10 if you watch classic attitude era wwe
first stream i would be very happy i plan on it i plan on watching i well maybe not whole episodes
of raw i don't think i can do that but my some of my favorite moments like the some of the best
stunts like for instance i can give you a moment right now one of my favorite moments of wwe wwf
is what it was back in when i was watching uh i'll give you top two top five no this is probably top
10 moment uh ken shamrock being in an iron cage and chris jericho walking around taunting ken
shamrock and by the way ken shamrock was was an animal person back in the old wwe he didn't like
talk he just screamed and was like stronger than 500 people at the same time uh during this bit
ken shamrock grabs both his hands onto the bars these iron bars and hulk pulls the fucking cage
open i forget how he gets in the cage but chris jericho like trapped him in the cage or something
and he gets out he screams and bends the iron bars to get out like fucking superman
and attacks chris jericho and like beats him up this is hysterical don't forget to ban me before
it wasn't why do people want to get banned is this like the hot dog bear thing where it didn't
actually happen no no this actually happened he's in this weird like rascally wabbit cage
that elmer fudd would make for bug's bunny and he just be pulls the bars open and gets out
it happens but we'll do that at some point thank you stripes beast for the 300 bits
well i don't want to read this i can't remove the curse for myself that's not how it works i don't
know anything about uh witchcraft me saying that out loud is the equivalent of me being the fucking
idiot that reads the inside of the necronomicon i'm not gonna do that or anything about this
for all i know that could be that could be a shrinking uh so that could be a shrinking
solution you don't know how curses work do you no i don't why would i know how curses work
i went to school for radio and i streamed video games why would i know what how curses work
i went to like film and radio school they didn't teach uh there was no sorry guys there was no
defense against the dark arts at the school i went to you say them all the time hey bs
18 all you had to do was read it no minus two and yeah yeah yeah yeah thank you bs for the five
dollars hey germa it's my birthday tomorrow as well gonna be weird in lockdown times thanks
for keeping us all a little more sane take care of yourself supposed to get supposed to get kind
of wild here over the next couple weeks in the states please take care of yourselves guys for
real trans scout thanks for 300 bits plus two and minus two actually correlate to penis size
and i i'm saying it again no that doesn't you know how fucked up that is do you understand like
you you you imagining this stuff all of you in chat right now is freaking me out it's just next
level odd and i did this it's my fault and now i know what all you were thinking when you see all
this i know exactly what you're thinking this
you need to stop thinking that because we're done with that i'm it's all my fault it is hey evil zoe
thanks for 300 bits babe it's time for your dick shrinking oh untold sewage thanks for the five
dollars germa can you do your best impression of the pall bearer stay safe oh yes the undertaker
he will destroy you thanks for the 500 bits uh goo berry juice thanks for 250
germa my dad is god i can make a potion to make you immune to all curses champion of pog and germa
super frog turn up the heat make sure to say feet say when the dwarf begins to wink his penis it
shall shrink eat the candied shoe and from thine eyes shall stream poo hope that helps once again
i'm glad you're back no that didn't help at all now you just took uh lighter fluid and poured it
on the fire i've still cursed and that's it i'll see you guys on wednesday this is the worst crack
chat yet and it's weird because it's like feeding into me like the the crack chat is just feeding
into me and i'm getting like cracked out it's i'm getting cracked the fuck out now too the last like
couple of hours it's been like i've been like kind of getting cracked out all right i'll see you guys
wednesday wednesday thursday friday and probably saturday as well we'll try these three to six like
four to six four to five hour streams for a while and see how we do keith king crimson thanks for
the 250 that's a jojo's bizarre adventure reference uh i'm freezing i just froze i think the camps
are not enough to lift the spider's curse simply recite a bible verse sure how about um this is a
weird thing to google bible verse about lifting curses okay here we go oh we've got the um there's
a viticus there's a leviticus leviticus that's where that's from i say that all the time okay
breaking curses uh psalms 144 one blessed be the lord my strength with teacheth my hands to war
and my fingers to fight how does that break it did it work i'm just gonna curse him again
what do you think there's no cool town period oh i got my curse removed you can just do it again
but there's got to be like a curse like immunity or something for a while right just hit him again
i don't know check you yes see you guys on wednesday good night take care see you soon and goodbye