Alright Michael, we're here on your special day.
That's right, it's my birthday today, not anybody else's.
Alright Michael, calm down.
Mom, shut up. I get all the presents Cathy doesn't get any because she's an idiot.
Come on Michael, you ruin your fucking birthday every year for everybody else and we get it.
I went through so much trouble to get you this rat's mixtape. I know how much you like them.
Can we just dance together as a family for once?
This year I got something new and exciting and different for everybody.
Hey kids, it's me.
It's a clown.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, easy.
Get away from me.
Please.
What the hell is happening?
It's a clown.
This clown's out of control.
Just chill out, everybody calm down.
It's my birthday.
Everybody calm down, I'm just a clown.
Oh whoa man, that clown.
Why did you invite him?
Rats, we're rats, we're the rats.
We play at night, we stalk at night, we're the rats.
I'm the giant rat that makes...
Hey, wait, hey, wait.
I'm stuck.
I knew this was a bad idea.
How did you...
You're making us late to the birthday party.
I'm the giant rat, I make all the rules.
You need to help me out of here now.
You know, you say that but...
No.
Hey, happy birthday.
Dad, those are rats.
Yeah, happy birthday.
A special box inside a treat for you here.
Thanks for the guy.
Bye.
Oh, I remember that box.
I shit in that one.
Oh dad, it's definitely something really cool.
A super cool toy that everyone's gonna be jealous of.
Hey, what's up?
I'm your new best friend.
We got a problem.
The fat guy doesn't fit y'all in the toilet.
Alright, honest opinions.
What did you guys think?
That wasn't good at all.
Yeah, why?
That was bad.
That was terrible.
Well, that's the beauty of this whole thing, son.
None of this even matters at all.
As a sequel, we're trying to do one very important thing.
That's sell toys, sell books, and sell audio tapes.
Now the movie itself could be about a blue toothbrush.
And as long as we sell the merchandise and keep the suits happy,
who cares about the subject matter?
But, what if I don't have a suit?
Prepare the drop.
And please, hit the right target this time.
Yes, sir.
You don't need to know what I had for breakfast this morning, alright?
Just let's talk about the deal.
Wasn't there a guy that was just right here?
Huh?
What's this guy doing here?
This might be the pizza delivery guy.
Yeah, I'm gonna go get the car and I'm gonna pull it around.
Save me a slice.
Don't eat the whole thing.
I don't know.
It might be a pizza.
Maybe I press it and I'll get a pizza.
Yeesh.
I'm going home.
I want a chicken nuggets.
Oh, what was that?
Welcome, Bratikin, to the dog capital.
I trust you alright?
In that case, walk with me and talk with me.
I'm going to show you something that I haven't shown anyone in over two thousand years.
What do you see before you?
Yeah, a toothbrush.
It is a toothbrush.
One of the most important in the entire galaxy.
Oh, cool.
This toothbrush holds the DNA of every single animal on Earth.
It must be protected.
Yeah, I know.
If this would have fallen to the wrong hands...
The infiltration was a success!
We've been breached.
We have been breached.
Sound the alarms.
What's happening?
I've been in a nightmare for two weeks straight.
That's a pretty good toothbrush.
Now hold on just a second.
Pause the movie.
Hit pause.
Did you hear what they just said?
That toothbrush has got the DNA of every animal on Earth.
Well, mate, it's just a movie.
I don't buy that for a second.
You're telling me it's just a movie?
Was Finding Nemo just a movie?
No, that was a documentary.
They had cameras down in the ocean.
I've never seen them filming it in Philadelphia.
Hang on a second.
I'm just going to get up right now because you're fuming me.
I'm just saying, we rented this film from Blockbuster.
Oh yeah, Blockbuster clothes.
Good joke.
I'm going to go to the sewer.
You coming with me?
Well, no.
See you later.
I mean, you can't...
Bloody hell.
Nice and easy.
You don't want any cops to see us pulling in here.
All right.
We're going to have to split up for this.
A lot of junk.
Yep.
Tell me if you find anything.
I thought I'd be doing real jobs.
Robbing banks.
Stealing paintings.
It's pretty good filler content.
I'm waiting through shit to find a dirty toothbrush.
This is just to make sure you understand the story.
Fucking day off as well.
Yeah.
None of this even matters.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Oi!
I've got something for you.
You found something?
Yeah, I got something too.
What do you got?
Well, it's a blue toothbrush.
Yeah, they're fucking everywhere, man.
So I'll just grab a couple.
You know, we could probably sell these.
Get in the car.
You know, I've got an idea.
I know exactly who we can sell these to.
Just put your seatbelt on, because I'm about to step on the gas.
I would go to a doctor, but I'm just scared of what he has to say.
You know?
That's why I asked you about it.
That is just grimp.
Quiet down here.
Let me do the talking.
You keep your mouth shut.
How we doing this evening, cat police?
We don't have time for small talk.
Did you bring the product or did you not?
Did you get my text by any chance?
I have Verizon, so maybe it didn't go through.
Enough.
The least of your concern should be text messages
and how we are about to decimate your disgusting planet.
The $20 is what I was told.
So you don't get shit unless I see 40 bucks.
Not so fast.
The rats have told me everything.
And if you think that I, Gary, guardian of...
This ends now, cat police.
What do you have to say about this one?
Yeah, it's pretty cool, huh?
Now let's see what happens when you fight me.
And what I'll win, I'll beat you up.
How did you guys sort this out?
For centuries we have tried to find the Noah's Ark toothbrushes.
And for centuries we have failed.
But not tonight.
You intergalactic space beings will never win.
We will always band together and stop you.
At any cost.
Such a pity.
It's too bad, really.
Our DNA would have fused together wonderfully.
Now let us show you our true power.
Oh, shit.
Now witness the power of over 2,000 galaxies come bad.
And yours will be next.
Evil will never win.
Quickly, hero.
There's not much time.
Take that toothbrush and cast it into the fires about noon.
I will hold him off as long as I can.
Take that!
Maldome.