All right. Hello? What is this? I'm not muted?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just turned the stream on. What do you mean I have 20 minutes before my solar system is destroyed?
Oh. It's like we just- I just turned the stream on. You have 20 minutes before the fucking solar system is destroyed, Jeremy.
You're five minutes late. No audio? Oh, there we go.
I didn't even know there was a direct today. I had no idea.
I don't even watch these.
Wait, did they spoil the game? I'm so disheveled right now. I haven't even brushed my teeth yet.
I was getting out- I was getting out of the shower, and somebody just goes,
Hey dude, you're missing the direct.
I was like, I don't- I don't care.
But then I was like, I kind of do.
I haven't even brushed my teeth yet. I got up like 10 minutes ago. Did not wake up 10 minutes ago. I'm kidding.
All right. Get me out of here.
What game is this?
Famicom Detective Club?
Isn't that the Nintendo?
That's the Nintendo- That's the Super Nintendo.
I got a tweet that I'm streaming.
I'll turn it up.
Put the cam back on. Hold on a second. I wasn't ready for this.
Why did I rush to turn this stream on and freak out at direct?
Hold on.
Did they already announce who the next Smash Brothers character is?
Did they announce who the next Smash Brothers character is?
They did? Who was it? Johnny Bravo?
I really hope it was Johnny Bravo.
It was a Xenoblade girl.
Oh.
A new age of ba- Hold on. I gotta tweet this.
I'm not even paying attention. I care more about like tweeting my stream out. I'm not even- What's- Hold on.
I'm like screen capping this window, by the way. I didn't even get the- I didn't even get the embed link.
It wasn't in my froggy sleepy voice. It sounds like I just got up five minutes ago.
I may have.
Alright, I gotta tweet out. I'm ready.
Samurai Warriors 5.
I have no idea what's going on.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
I'm dreaming.
I'm watching Turbo 985 stream right now. I'm dreaming.
Am I awake? This would make sense if I woke the fuck up right now.
And I woke up like-
Sweat just dripping down my face like I've got- I've rushed to get a stream on to stream a Nintendo Direct when I've only streamed like one Nintendo Direct in four years.
I don't think I've ever done this.
Have I ever done this?
I- This is what I'm saying!
First the world's gonna explode, then I'm gonna dream.
Shit, I gotta shut up.
I have a snowman.
That snowman was pretty cool.
What game is this?
What do you say?
That looks kinda cool. Somebody said egg yolk hair.
When you mean there's egg yolk in my hair.
There's egg yolk in my hair.
And you know what? Here's the proof that I didn't brush my teeth.
Because my tongue is probably still blue from the blue drink I had last night.
Yup.
Is it?
I mean the screen is blue.
Why'd you need to prove that?
You don't fucking believe me.
Wait, is this Monster Hunter?
Why did they not put the Monster Hunter world on the Switch?
Because they were making like a Switch version kind of, I guess?
It's too powerful.
It wouldn't run.
Well, this one does.
Why the fuck are you watching this?
I don't know.
I think somebody said, dude, the direct is on.
I'm like, fucking, I gotta hurry the fuck up.
I gotta hurry up.
I'm watching this.
Go back to bed? Fine.
This is cool though.
Actually, I wanted to...
Recently I wanted to download Monster Hunter World.
On Switch.
But it was like, oh, it's not on Switch.
But okay, this is Monster Hunter Rise.
Cool, alright, that's cool.
We got a release date now.
Did we have a release date already and I just didn't know?
And I'm just...
Is that like a big reveal or did we already know that?
That was the latest trailer for Monster Hunter Rise from Capcom.
But it's still cool though.
How will our heroes fare against these ferocious monsters?
Stay tuned for the latest installment in the Monster Hunter series.
Launching March 26th.
Can I play it?
Next.
Please take a look at this.
Mario Golf, I mean, this is a huge deal.
Mario Golf Super Rush.
Okay, that's...
I can't wait for this game.
I want a new Mario Baseball too.
Is it multiplayer?
It better be.
I hope there is.
Use features on the greens like a shot gauge to see how your shot will curve due to slopes.
Ooh, that's cool.
And a scan that lets you examine a course's terrain.
Online multiplayer?
Right, it has to be.
These features can help you ace your shots.
In addition to button controls, you can also use motion controls by holding a Joy-Con controller like a golf club.
That's kind of cool.
Gently swing the controller to have your character swing in the game.
Dude, Wii Golf, they brought it back.
Enjoy the sensation of golfing.
You run around?
On top of all that, there are several modes with new elements that truly bring the heat to Mario Golf.
Wait, you're running around?
You have to fight each other?
Wait, what?
It's always your turn.
Everyone tees off at the same time, then you'll race through the course to reach your ball.
Wait, is this so unsafe?
Then keep going.
Luigi's gonna take a ball off the forehead when Mario's driving.
These skills aren't the only things at play.
Make use of dashes and special shots to beat the competition.
Oh, did we mention story mode?
There's a story mode.
You'll start out as a rookie and develop your golfing skills while interacting with various Mushroom Kingdom characters.
Okay, I hate this so much, but it might be my favorite game of the year.
Then allocate points to different stats.
You know what I mean?
This is amazing.
I hate that I love this so much.
You can also use your Mii in versus play.
You have skill points and shit in golf?
When Mario Golf Super Rush swings onto Nintendo Switch, June 25th.
I hate that sport.
Pre-orders begin on Nintendo eShop after this presentation.
I only care about golf when I play it as Super Mario, that's it.
But I care about it very deeply when I do.
The latest game in the Mario Golf series adds new gameplay for multiplayer modes, as well as the familiar golf gameplay with easy-to-learn controls.
This is really fun.
This is cool.
I like this.
You look forward to this game on Nintendo Switch.
Let's move on to more Nintendo Switch headlines.
Headlines.
Hey!
Check out these games coming to Nintendo Switch.
That looks good.
Return to the unforgiving world of Pandora in Tales from the Borderlands.
Play as the Hyperion lackey, Reese, and the quick-witted con artist, Fiona, as you set out to recover a mountain of cash.
This is not a new game.
But you can play it in the bathroom.
That's really important.
You can play it in the bathroom.
Couldn't do that before.
Every single game that comes on the Switch that's been out for five years, they really should just be serious about it.
Be real about it.
And Tales from the Borderlands is coming out on the Switch bathroom edition.
Just call it bathroom edition because that's what everyone's going to do.
Skyrim bathroom edition.
Go back offline until the Direct is over.
In this action game from Aspire, you'll build your zombie horde and take revenge on the city by turning humans into your undead allies.
Replenish your bodily arsenal with sputum head.
This is an incredibly highly requested game, by the way.
This city ain't no match for a dead man.
Stub the zombie and rebel without a pulse.
Eat its way onto Nintendo Switch March 16.
Pre-orders begin today on Nintendo eShop.
This looks pretty good.
All right.
Put that on the list.
That will be good.
Quiet.
Everybody quiet.
When is it coming out?
You'll have to do some odd jobs around town and earn enough to pay off the entry fee.
There's a mining one.
Against the slew of unusual opponents.
Most of them aliens with some crazy tricks up their sleeves.
Study their tactics carefully to gain the upper hand in combat.
With a new and improved death glove, you'll have access to a variety of deadly skills that can be customized and upgraded before each match.
The fate of the world is at stake.
Oh, man.
So be ready to kick some whatever aliens have that you can kick.
Well, it looks a little rough, though.
August, okay.
August.
It looks a little rough.
They all do.
Yeah, they do.
I'm going to play it.
I'm going to love it.
But that looked like really brain-brainy and kind of rough.
It's your PC.
Wait, is this a card game?
It's a shooter?
What?
I'm absolutely not going to play this, but it looks like a great game to watch somebody play, play very well.
Looking forward to that.
Cool.
The DC Super Hero Girls are here to save the day.
Hi, everyone.
My name is Barbara Gordon.
DC Super Hero Girls Teen Power.
He's inventing new gadgets.
This is Super Girl.
She's super strong and has heat vision.
Plus super breath.
Super breath.
And let's not forget Wonder Woman.
And, of course, Super Breath.
You don't want to be, you don't want your move to be classified as super breath.
Along with our friends Green Lantern, Bumblebee, and Zatanna, we fight evil supervillains to keep our city.
I feel like that's kind of rude.
But we're not justified.
Like, wow, you got super breath today.
Like, okay.
There'll be clean breath?
How about like minty breath?
She used her new super move.
Clean breath.
Hey, that sucked.
That's a shitty superpower.
You brushed your teeth this morning?
Yeah, but it's a ton.
It's a huge air.
Clean breath.
...figures out our secret identities.
DC Super Hero Girls.
Teen Power.
Heroically sourced onto Nintendo Switch.
June 4th.
Ready the juice cannons and prepare for battle.
Are we?
This is what Plants vs. Zombies.
Battle for Neighborville.
March 25th Switch.
Fleet Edition.
Is this just Plants vs. Warfare?
Plants vs. Zombies Garden Warfare.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
Everybody get up.
Everybody just stand up.
Put your hands up.
Everybody just get up.
Just get up.
Get up already.
Come on.
Get up.
No, sit down.
You're playing a video game.
It's Plants vs. Zombies Garden Warfare.
Sit the fuck down.
You're gonna get in the way of everybody else on the couch.
Don't stand up.
Sit down.
Stay seated.
It's Miitopia.
Makeup.
I feel like I have to play this.
What do they do?
Do they just live in like a house or something?
They live in like a town?
Ooh.
This is cute.
Oh, cool.
Miitopia.
Yeah, I turned on the facecam for the raid.
I saw it.
I saw Kitboga just came in with a fucking monster raid.
So I turned on the webcam.
Thanks a lot.
Welcome, guys.
We're watching the Directive.
We're gonna play Slime Rancher later.
That's Super Mario.
Wait, what?
So play some however and wherever you'd like.
That's awesome.
Whoa.
It's Mario Maker Animal Crossing.
But thanks a lot, Kitboga.
Welcome, everybody.
Thank you.
That's a shitload of people.
Hope you had a good stream.
Have a good rest of your day, dude.
Hey, why not try recreating the Mushroom Kingdom?
The raid song?
A free update for the game launches February 25th.
After downloading it, Super Mario Bros. items will be available via Nook Shopping starting March 1st.
I was off camera, but I was going like this.
Trying to find a way to do it.
I was going like this.
I was getting ready.
I was getting ready to be like...
There you go.
This is your raid song.
Welcome.
Thanks for the raid.
Thanks.
Go follow Kitboga if you don't.
What are you, out of your mind?
A new launch for the Super Mario 3D World plus Bowser's Fury game.
We hope you enjoy that Mario adventure as well.
Next, we have another game to show you.
Another one.
What's this one?
Zelda.
The Legend of Zelda.
Tipping the scales.
Legend of Zelda.
The weight of time.
What ideas will you expose?
What is that?
The latest in the HD 2D series.
He leaves us no recourse.
Oh.
S-Frost will answer for its crimes today.
Are these the wages of loyalty?
Raised earth and burnt corpses.
You and no other must decide how we proceed.
I would love like a Christmas, like Santa RPG.
It's like top down, like isometric Santa Claus.
You like play Santa Claus and Mrs. Claus.
Like Rudolph and Frosty and shit.
What is that?
Why make that?
It'd be cool.
I promise to do all in my power to see us through this safely.
Every last one of us.
Triangle strategy?
Far, far away lies the continent of Norzilea.
Comprised of three nations and limited deposits of salt and iron.
The constant feuds among the nations over these precious resources
eventually ignited into a great conflict known as the Salt-Iron War.
Though the hostilities ceased with an uneasy truce,
decades later the flames of war threatened to engulf the realm once again.
Can I ask a question?
What's with the burning embers that go across the screen on every trailer ever?
Caught in a tangled fiery web of plots and conspiracies.
It's always like the edges are burning and embers are floating across the screen.
In like half of every trailer I've ever watched.
That would orchestrate their downfall.
Our benefit you say.
Just pay attention, you'll see.
In this new tactical RPG, battles take place on terrain
with different elevations.
A character's attack range is determined by their location and their equipment.
The range can be extended by attacking from higher ground
with long-range weapons such as bows and arrows.
Thus, your forces can use the terrain and other elements
to gain the upper hand.
An enemy outflanked is susceptible not only to your angel attack,
but also a powerful blow from the ally positioned behind the enemy.
What have we here?
Charge into an enemy to see them flying into position for a follow-up attack.
Link attacks together by first casting ice magic on the flames to create water terrain.
Then, electrify the area with lightning magic.
Power up!
It is of the utmost importance to survey the battlefield.
Electrify the battlefield with power up!
Throughout the story, you will be faced with making important decisions
in a variety of situations.
Utility, morality, liberty.
Collectively, your decisions will establish your conviction
affecting how the story unfolds and who will join your cause.
Once more, I would ask you plainly.
Do we or don't we relinquish Prince Roland to Azeroth?
Critical decisions that may determine the fates of nations
are settled by vote on the scales of conviction.
Use information you've gathered to sway allies toward your favored cause.
The story will significantly change based on how the votes are cast.
So they refuse to relinquish him to us.
Lies! His hand was forced!
Once more and more critical decisions are made,
your journey may take you down paths divergent from those of other players.
You will see what true might is!
Project Triangle Strategy, a brand new tactical RPG.
I'm sorry, ever since Peter Molyneux told me that like,
they're fabled too.
I remember he talked about trees and shit and how the world was going to change.
I don't trust anybody anymore.
That tree that you plant there will turn in a hundred years into an ice cream truck.
I was like, holy shit, how the fuck's that going to happen, Peter Molyneux?
What are you talking about? That sounds insane.
And that tree's roots will go into the ground and create ten cities of ants and mice.
Like, okay, cool.
And I think the biggest decision in that game is like, you have a dog.
A dog? What kind of dog do you want?
There's like two different, three different kinds.
Oh shit, quiet.
Oh, I spelled Pog.
I was...
He's just winding the toy up, ready to like, Pog!
Pop up and Pog.
I didn't get a chance.
Gorgon love battle.
Gorgon use many weapons.
Triple-bladed war axe, spear of misery,
Hades soul-devouring crossbow.
A princess is supposed to lead her people,
not be stuck up in some tower waiting for a hero.
In my line of work, bullets are constantly whizzing past you.
Flaming longsword, blade of doom.
Just once, just once, I'd like to catch one of your bones.
Are these all Fortnite skins?
I don't know, the background's messing me up.
Look, it's simple.
Gorgon want new weapon.
In Knockout City, I'm like a kung-fu master.
I can catch bullets.
That's cool.
Alright, hold on.
Is this dodgeball?
Let's find out what sound your face makes.
Is this dodgeball? No, it's not.
No.
You can throw people.
We're losing to a bunch of farmers.
Okay, team.
They may have won the battle, but not the war.
Why is the switch so small?
Why are the switches so t-
Oh, no, no, no, they're controllers.
I was like, why do they have tiny, like, iPhone switches?
Because the other people had the switches in their hands looking down.
We went up to- there was no TV, we were told of.
The big- the big orc guy had it in his hands looking down.
But there was no television they're looking at.
This is cameras.
No, I- I'm telling you, like, two people had the thing looking down at it.
The fight for survival starts now.
Hang on tight.
Because you're all going to play a little game of fate for me.
They're not real.
From the creators of the Danganronpa and Zero Escape series comes the fight for your life.
Literally, disoriented and trapped in an underwater theme park,
the twelve of you, known as the Go-Getters Club,
must now survive this game of fate at all costs.
I don't want to die yet!
Sorry to scare you all, but-
You are going to play this game.
I'm not going to play this game.
Well, no one's going to play it, I guess.
They got a call?
Hey, uh, cut the direct off right here.
This thing's not coming out.
I feel like that would be really hard to do that.
All it takes is one person to fuck that up, the rhythm, and the whole fight goes down.
Ooh, this is a good game.
Physical release?
Oh, cool.
I thought I was going to say, I hate his original game.
Wait, what?
He played the Switch one.
And it comes with a PC code.
So, you don't have to play it on Switch.
That would be so funny.
What a great game.
Ninja Gaiden?
The four Dark Souls.
This was the Dark Souls.
This was like the hard game, right?
This was like the hardest game.
This was like the old Dark Souls, right?
Does this still hold up?
I don't think so.
It does.
Ninja Gaiden is fucking hard.
Yeah.
Some of them are shit.
What's a good one?
This is harder than Dark Souls, yeah.
What does this say on the difficulty tier list?
Oh, a better question.
Where's Dark Souls on that tier list?
Is Dark Souls A?
B?
Ninja Gaiden is S tier?
Is it like one of the hardest series ever?
Dark Souls is like B+.
EOTW sucks.
I didn't say it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I never played it.
Zelda sucks.
No, it doesn't.
Okay, can I...
I have...
This is important.
Do I get...
Do I get to have an opinion on like the current Zelda games if I have not played one since...
I gave up two hours into Twilight Princess?
Okay.
Yeah, I got to the part of Twilight Princess where I went in a chlorine filled pool and
then got out of the pool and opened my eyes and turned my head and looked at lights.
I got to that part.
Yeah, I got to the point of Twilight Princess where you had fucking chlorine eyes and I
stopped playing.
He got scared.
I don't remember any of these.
Remastered?
I don't remember any of this.
Were these games that came out like a decade ago or something?
Two decades ago?
It was in the Dreamcast.
Oh, okay.
Dinosaur?
Going good.
Super Mario Galaxy 3.
Coming up.
I'm the producer of the Legend of Zelda series.
I'm sure a lot of you saw me and thought there might be news about the sequel to the Legend
of Zelda Breath of the Wild game.
Unfortunately, we don't have anything to share right now.
We apologize.
Development is proceeding smoothly and we should be able to bring you some new information
this year.
For now, we'll have to ask you to wait just a bit longer.
Just kidding.
Here's the trailer.
While you're all waiting, however, this Legend of Zelda game will be coming to Nintendo Switch.
Please take a look.
What you've just seen is the Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD.
This game originally released in 2011 on the Wii console and now it's coming to Nintendo Switch.
The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword featured a control scheme in which players would use
the Wii Remote Plus controller as a sword and the Nunchuk controller as a shield.
With the increased processing power of the Nintendo Switch system, the controls here
are smoother and even more intuitive.
And we've recreated the controls for the sword and the shield here by having the player
hold two Joy-Con controllers.
Oh, it's motion control.
Okay.
Nevermind.
I hate it.
Swing it to have Link swing his sword in the game.
The Joy-Con controller in your left hand is the shield.
You know how many times I'm going to be like, I'm getting the fucking sensor bar.
The sensor's not working.
I can't see anything.
This is stupid.
It doesn't work.
Look at the screen.
It's glitching.
It'll be half the picture.
These physical movements add a sense of urgency and tension to combat.
But we've also made it possible to play the game with button controls to ensure it can
be played in handheld mode or on the Nintendo Switch Lite system.
After mulling over how to assign different gameplay elements to different buttons, we
decided to apply the sword motions to tilting the right control stick.
What?
But how do you...
Tilt the stick down when you want to swing the sword downward.
Oh shit.
Swing to the right, to the left, or diagonally, just tilt the stick in the respective direction.
This looks actually, that looks pretty good.
Saved, saved, saved.
Here's something else we've been working on.
Specially designed Joy-Con controllers.
The right Joy-Con controller is themed after the Master Sword while the left features a
Hylian shield motif.
The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword as the game depicting the earliest story in the Legend
of Zelda timeline details the events around the creation of the Master Sword itself.
We hope that people who played the original game on Wii and those playing it for the first
time will enjoy discovering the origins of the Legend of Zelda.
Joy-Con Drift.
Isn't that problem?
The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD launches July 16th.
Following this Nintendo Direct, you'll be able to pre-order the game on Nintendo eShop.
And the specially designed Joy-Con controllers will launch on the game's release day at your
local retailers.
Many of you may already know this, but the Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword was the last
original console game prior to the Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild game.
And it was still following the established conventions of the Legend of Zelda.
However, it gave a glimpse into many features and innovations that would eventually be adopted
in the Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild.
Using the sail cloth to descend in midair.
Oh, that looks fun.
A stamina gauge that depleted as you scaled walls.
Would I like Breath of the Wild?
Would I? Don't bullshit me here.
Give me the real story.
Would I really like this game?
I don't play Legend of Zelda.
I'm not a big fan of it.
I respect it as a series.
I think it's great for everything.
Without Legend of Zelda, we would have nothing.
We would have nothing.
It is the Dungeons and Dragons of modern adventure games.
I understand that.
Please look forward to the Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword HD.
Would I like Breath of the Wild?
Well, what did you think?
The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword has been optimized for Nintendo Switch.
It includes intuitive motion controls and button controls by tilting the right control stand.
How long do I cook bacon in an air fryer?
Okay, the next game will be our last announcement for today.
Epic.
Please take a look at this.
I don't know, but that was epic what you said.
I don't know why.
Something in that sentence.
I don't know.
Put bacon in an air fryer?
Cook it in like the fucking pan or the oven.
Be careful.
Is this...
Oh, shit.
Is this Splatoon 3 or is this like Splatoon RPG game?
Fallout Splatoon.
Here it comes.
It's like, what the hell is this?
Splatoon Rust.
What the hell is this game?
It's gonna be a skateboard.
Skateboard.
Splatoon...
It's Splatoon 3.
Oh.
Where are we dropping?
Come on, give me that one.
Of course you're gonna drop right there.
It's two teams on either side.
Come on, that's the comedy.
That's the humor in that one I just said.
What the fuck?
2022.
Hold on.
What you've just seen is the latest installment in the Splatoon series, Splatoon 3.
This game is scheduled to launch in 2022, so it'll be a while.
We hope you'll stay tuned for more information at a later time.
I didn't really play it.
Today, we showed you a sampling of games coming to Nintendo Switch.
A variety of games are in development.
And we look forward to sharing more news with you in the future.
That's all for today's Nintendo Direct.
That's not...
Thank you for watching.
No, it's not.
It's not over.
Well, that was the Nintendo Direct.
So, let me give you my thoughts.
What do we see?
We saw Super Mario Animal Crossing skins.
Kind of cool.
We saw...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
No, I have...
It's my five o'clock shadow.
That's a five o'clock shadow.
Are you talking about up here?
Okay.
Well, I banned that person for three days.
It's like a beard.
You missed Team Fortress 3.
What did we saw?
We saw...
Why did I even turn the stream on for this?
One person told me to turn this on.
Somebody was like, dude, you're missing the Direct.
The fucking Nintendo Direct.
And I'm like, fuck, I got to get on there.
Why did I even stream that?
I mean, there was a couple of cool things.
What did I see?
Oh, Travis Touchdown.
No More Heroes 3.
It looked like it was going to be fun.
We got a release date, too.
August.
Kind of far away.
Mario Golf, that's right.
Mario Golf.
That's right.
That's a PogChamp moment.
What else was there?
Ninja Gaiden.
All right.
Yeah.
No, that's true.
I mean, I could have rolled over in bed and opened Twitter and seen the first somebody
going, hey, there's a new Mario Golf.
That's so cool.
And I would just be like, yeah, that's pretty cool.
And I would just go back to bed.
That's like a rollover.
Like, that's a good surprise on Twitter this morning.
All right.
I'm going back to bed.
One Voice Andy.
What do you mean, One Voice Andy?
What are you talking about?
This is me.
What do you mean, One Voice Andy?
One Voice Andy.
You're a liar.
You made that up.
You have to lie.
All right.
Well, now we're going to play a game.
I'm going to get off the camera here because why would I need to be on camera anymore?
I'm going to play...
What the heck are we doing?
Slime Rancher.
That's right.
I'm going to play Slime Rancher.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let me get...
Just let me get BRB for one second.
I'm going to brush my teeth.
Get back on camera.
Hold on.
I need to like change the Switch stuff.
I'll be right back.
Just watch Look at the Mart for a second.