I just want to warn everybody, I've changed my microphone settings.
I haven't really talked into it properly yet.
But a lot of you guys turned me way up and I'm just going to be very,
very quiet because people turn the stream way up because they say that the
sound is super, super quiet.
So I'm about to talk normally here and I think I may have finally
figured out what the hell has been going on with the stream
for the last like eight years.
So I'm going to talk normally now.
So here's the thing that my microphone right now.
How does it is this louder than normal?
Is this like, okay, this is perfect.
This is you.
This is way better because it's I can actually hear you now.
You're not like fucking 30% quieter than the game.
This is Howard Stern audio.
Well, let me tell you something about Howard Stern.
Wait, hold on.
No, see not now.
It's now it's Howard Stern.
Okay, so here's the thing.
I'm dancing with the stars.
We had a couple of things happen.
Okay, I think I may have fixed everything.
Well, I'm going to get loud.
Let's see what happens when I get loud.
A lot of people said, dude, when you get loud, you sound like you're
on NPR sound like you're 45.
Well, I changed to set the setup again.
I'm going to scream into the mic and I want people to understand.
I'm going to yell every time I've gotten loud over the last two or
three weeks.
It goes like, oh, it sounds horrible.
So I'm going to scream.
I'm going to not scream, but I'm going to be loud enough for you.
You know what I mean?
Here we go.
Ready?
Oh my goodness.
What the hell happened here?
Somebody somebody somebody somebody somebody somebody somebody.
How's that?
Was it okay?
That's way better.
It cuts out a little bit.
Okay.
Well, I mean that would have been un fucking bearable if I didn't
have this set up correctly.
Somebody somebody somebody somebody.
It's not really loud for us.
Okay.
Good.
Very good.
That was a good bugs of bunny.
Do it louder.
Okay.
How's that?
Is that okay?
Is that being compressed down?
Is that being pulled down and is that fucking up?
It's not bad.
Okay.
That was fine.
All right.
We look ladies and gentlemen, I think my audio is now fine.
My audio has been completely fixed.
It got a little crusty.
Well, it's going to get crusty.
You can't you if you scream into any microphone.
One of two things is going to happen one.
There's no gate or compression on it at all.
And it hurts and it actually hurts people's ears and it's like
a huge problem or there's too much compression and and you
sound like this, right?
I've been doing I'm telling you I've been sitting here for
at least an hour to two or three straight hours screaming
into this mic and like listening you were born crusty.
All right.
So so I've turned up myself a lot a lot.
So there's been complaints on this stream for almost a half
decade of how quiet I always am.
I am turned the fuck up now.
You understand and I figured out what happened.
So on my by the way, the internet I found the right server
took me like 45 minutes.
I tested some streams to different servers.
This one should be good.
We shouldn't have a single problem.
You ready for car?
Kari, are you ready for Kari?
Are you guys ready?
Is everybody?
Are you guys excited for Kari?
Is everyone excited for this because this is like my favorite
game ever made.
Get excited.
Get turned up.
You were boxers or briefs.
I I don't know depends on the day.
It actually depends on the day.
All these all the okay.
All these brief haters, please.
It depends on the day right like box or briefs.
I actually don't really love boxers.
I think there's not enough support there.
It really just isn't enough support for me.
So I like I like the support.
I'm sorry.
What do you want me to say?
There's not enough support on boxers.
There just isn't that's not the wrong answer.
It's I'm just it really isn't okay.
So we're good to go.
I've got my audio fixed.
Let's do one more test.
Okay.
How's that?
That fine and we're gonna if you don't know what's happening here
if you do it didn't watch the stream yesterday.
Where have you been?
First of all, second of all, we played sorcery across a million
followers.
It's kind of cool.
It's really cool.
And we're gonna play more sorcery.
This is the tutorial is now over.
I hope you guys have decisions you're ready to make.
I'm very interested to see what you do.
Let's see if we how close we come to the original playthrough.
God do I like this new audio setup makes you just want to
get nice and nice real and close and we talk to you directly
about how things are going.
Okay, you guys ready?
Turn your stream camera on.
I want to see spongebob.
What the hell?
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
So we're about to start.
We I did the intro already.
So people understand that this is where we are.
This is where we started and as you see here for people
that weren't here yesterday, I I want to make sure people
get like so this is where you start and here's the game
map, right?
It's right here.
It ends about right here.
So the big we storm the castle.
It's about like a 45 minute experience.
You still had no idea.
They had no idea.
I am so happy to play this again.
It's bigger than Elden Ring.
Yeah, Limgrave is this big on the map.
That's how big Limgrave is.
This is going to take us two to three thousand hours to get
through this.
Okay, so we have who's the God right now.
The God is the ape.
We already used the ape, but they don't really care anymore.
This dude's on gas station weed.
Watch out.
What?
Wait, do you think I'm on gas station weed?
You can't sell weed at a gas station.
That's wicked funny though.
Gas station weed.
That's such a huge insult for some reason.
I don't know why.
I don't know.
Why am I like, why am I so insulted by what that person
just said?
No, you know, I got one guy chat moment of the year earlier
in the pre stream chat.
Somebody said their name is Psycho.
Psych.
So I have to give credit here because it's hilarious.
Jerma downloaded his consciousness into his Samsung
Galaxy fridge and he's playing fart simulator with the
crisper draw settings.
That's just that's just funny.
It just is and I have to give credit for it because like
what if that's actually funny.
Like genuinely funny.
Crisp the draw like okay that you made that comment funny.
Like the only reason why that's funny is because the
crisper draw settings comment that makes the whole thing
funny.
You get it.
You understand comedy.
I'm glad.
All right.
You guys ready?
I'm ready.
I'm excited.
Here's what we have.
If everyone let's take a look at what we've got for items
to remind you from yesterday.
We have two quantities of these wax cloth skull cap a
bamboo flute 12 goblin teeth and a giant's tooth.
We have a lot of teeth.
Actually, I'll be honest.
I don't think I've ever had this many goblin teeth in an
entire playthrough.
I think we got the maximum amount of teeth we could
possibly get for goblin teeth so we can use whenever we
want all the time.
I'm just gonna be throwing this at people for fun.
Here we go.
Twilight already.
The great city of Kare has loomed large on the horizon
all day but has been slow to reach the path tracing great
loops back and forth through a deep and narrow paths.
Look at that.
Look at this artwork.
Dude, look at this artwork.
Fuck on.
You've not seen a living soul except once when a dark
figure raced across the hilltops overhead and it was
lost from view.
So you're naturally curious.
You're naturally cautious when you round a bend in the
path and see a beggar crouch low against a rock muttering
to himself.
The beggar.
You stop out of sight behind an outcrop but the beggar
does not look much like a threat at all.
See what he does.
You watch in silence.
The beggar is an unfortunate soul.
His head twitches from one side to the other every few
minutes and he mutters and murmurs to himself.
You're hiding in the rocks, sir.
Hiding in the rocks.
And approach him or we can try to get by.
One voice.
There is one voice, but I do it good.
Approach.
You call a greeting and stride over and he leaps to his
feet drawing a short stick from inside his cloak.
Who goes there?
What's your business in Kare?
Greetings old man.
I'm a traveler.
I'm on a quest.
Get out of my way.
How about greetings?
Yeah.
Get out of my way.
You can't don't just be mean for no reason.
I'm a traveler.
The man pokes his stick at you.
A traveler?
Traveling where?
The backlands.
Kare.
This is my business, not yours.
My business, not yours.
I mean, that's my business, right?
I mean, I could say I'm just going to Kare, right?
Why would I want to be on this road?
Kare.
Obviously Kare, but why?
Ah, why?
Answer me or you'll face the consequences.
I said ow as if he was poking himself.
You know, you get it.
What consequences?
Step aside.
Who are you?
Who are you, you ask?
You're certainly very brave.
The man beams with aging pride.
I am the city guard.
No one enters Kare except through me.
And then despite his age and clear ill health,
he comes at you waving his stick.
Fight him.
I won't fight you.
Let's get the first pull of the night here.
For the day.
Do we fight the old man?
Or do we not fight the old man?
Gonna fight a beggar Omegalo.
Fight, kill.
I won't.
Well, let's see.
What do they say today?
He poked us with a stick.
Yes, he did.
Well, it looks like you've decided.
All right.
That's pretty, that's pretty, don't say unanimous.
They hate that.
Yeah, don't say unanimous.
All right.
We're not going to fight.
Resident sleeper chat.
I almost clicked fight him.
All right.
Don't, I won't fight you.
You are unarmed.
He waves the stick close to your face jabbing a few times,
but you push the point aside with one hand.
All right, then.
He declares.
We'll settle this fairly.
He tosses the stick to one side and raises his fists.
The knuckles are blackened with scabs.
Okay.
You get another opportunity.
So we fight him or don't fight him?
Scabs all over his knuckles.
What do you think?
I can manually end the poll after 30 seconds.
Yeah, that's a yeah, definitely.
Yeah, they don't have these don't have to be 60 seconds.
You can manually end the poll in like 20 to 30 seconds.
Would you I wouldn't fight this person.
Oh shit.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Oh fuck.
Oh man.
All right.
I don't I don't think anybody's ever clicked this button before guys.
Fight him.
Sighing you roll up your sleeves.
Should I just go full blast and just punch him right in the face?
Oh shit defense.
The beggar is not a powerful opponent.
You should be able to easily overpower him.
So you begin with a heavy punch giving it everything you have.
The beggar lifts his fists in defense.
So you land the minimum amount of damage against him.
Prepare to see stars.
He declares you better put him up.
Oh fuck that.
Okay.
I didn't think he even had that much.
That's annoying.
The beggar tries to knock you out in one swing.
This is much higher than your attack.
So you are hurt.
You suffer more damage because you left yourself so undefended
and he leaves you winded.
He is breathless and about to swing with a little force.
However, you are also weakened.
So you should defend and rebuild your power.
No, fuck that.
That's it.
You play it carefully and punch with a weak attack overpowering
the beggar who tries a low careful attack.
He is wheezing and breathless.
Why am I doing so little damage?
You tense your biceps and swing with a strong arm overpowering
the beggar again who tries a weak attack.
This time I'll knock you down.
He declares I could have killed him.
You defend yourself the beggar attempts a strong attack,
but you receive only a small amount of damage.
You'll be weaker now.
So his next attack will be lower.
Why you he grumbles preparing a medium swing this time.
I've got you.
I should think if you want to try it.
All right, he's done.
You level a powerful blow beating the beggar the beggar pants
and groans and then collapses into the dirt.
You roll your sleeves back down.
All right, then he murmurs into the ground weakly waving a hand.
You can pass walk on or help him up.
I mean help him up.
I'm just I'm helping him holding out a hand.
You help him upright.
He sits up and dust down his tattered clothing a gray cloak.
That was once a uniform.
He's shivering.
The evening is drawing in and it must get cold out here.
You don't have any food.
Do you?
He asks sadly.
No, I don't actually.
I actually don't sorry.
No, you shake your head.
I'm sorry.
The man sighs and shakes his head.
No matter then.
There's plenty of meat on a grass vole.
If you know how to nibble him.
Farewell.
Good luck or come with me.
Anytime I play a video game and there's a opportunity for an old person
to come hang out with you.
It's just if I made the Wizard of Oz today, like if it was me like I was
like, oh, I'm going to make the Wizard of Oz.
It would just be three old men in their fucking 80s.
I that's the only people that I ever like apparently hang out with.
It's like, oh yeah, that's that's yeah, I want to get my companions.
I'll take the old guy, the old guy, the old guy, the old guy.
No, I don't want the strong person.
I don't want the cool mage.
No, no, no, just give me three or four old people.
We they always come with us.
I'm dropping frames again, aren't I?
I don't get it.
That's weird.
I literally streamed to the test server of this server that I'm on right
now for an hour and 40 minutes with no drop frames.
I don't get it.
I literally did the exact same thing.
I don't understand.
What's happening here?
Are you guys seeing any of this?
Only shows six skipped frames.
Why is it showing that on mine?
Really?
No, yeah, I'm definitely seeing it.
What the heck?
I literally just did it.
I mean, okay, I streamed to this server with the test server settings
and it was fine.
Why is it doing this?
What the fuck?
Okay, whatever.
If it looks fine, it looks fine.
Okay, here we go.
It's a text game.
So it's fine.
Yeah, but that still sucks though that for anything other than what
we're doing right now.
This is a huge problem.
Okay, it's actually fine for us.
Um, let me open this.
Hold on.
Give me one second because this is this actually makes no sense.
I mean one sec.
Like how could it be possible that I would stream to this server
and then turn it off and turn it on again without the test server?
And it's a bunch of problems.
That makes no sense.
I'm literally streaming to the same exact server.
The same ingest server.
No, no difference.
Zero difference.
What the fuck?
All right.
Well, whatever.
I mean, I apparently have dropped 2,000 frames in the last five minutes.
If you guys aren't seeing that then I don't understand.
It's very weird.
Okay, whatever.
If you can't tell you can't tell but I'm pissed about it.
Okay, so should we he's going to come with us.
You take pity on the man.
Come with me.
I'm going into Kare.
Soldier considers your offer for a moment.
You sure?
I know the word for the wall, but they will not want to let me through the gate.
Okay, sounds like we can help each other.
He clamors slowly to his feet.
A gleam of hope is entered the poor man's eyes.
Very well then stranger a trade.
All the paths.
The beggar walks a few strides ahead the ghost of a military pace in his step.
What's your name or walk?
Yeah, what's your name?
Let's find out.
What's your name?
Captain Thomas of the fourth Legion responsible for the southern perimeter.
He knocks his bony heels together.
At your service.
Okay.
What are you doing here soldier?
I think you're delusional.
What are you doing out here?
We were sent to investigate sightings.
He replies still panting for breath.
A whole Legion of us back when the council felt bold,
but then they locked the gate and wouldn't let us back.
Where's your Legion now sightings of what they locked you out of the city.
They locked you.
Well, okay.
They locked you out of the city.
They locked the goblins out too.
He replies if the goblins were gone, they'd let us in but they aren't gone.
They're in the rocks.
I don't see anything.
What are the goblins doing?
This is a teeth opportunity more teeth.
It's time to get more teeth.
What are they doing?
What are the goblins doing?
He shakes his head.
I don't know.
They can't get through the walls, but then I think I've heard them digging,
scraping at the mud in the night.
The path winds through gorse and thick grass.
Kari squats in a basin in the hills like a stagnant festering pool.
You turn one corner then another and the stone walls of the city are looming over you.
The end of the path.
So we're going up.
Where's the gate?
It's gate time.
The walls weren't built to keep anything out.
They were here before the goblins Thomas says.
They were built to keep people in.
Kari is one gigantic trap itself.
Why?
I'll be leaving and you want to go back?
Don't talk.
Why?
Are the people inside not happy?
Would you be happy ruled by pirates and thieves?
He points.
Cast your eyes up.
You can see them.
Archers.
Facing in both directions.
You could scramble up the slope to the right to get a better view of the wall.
If you wanted to.
All right, we're going in the clearing.
We're going up the slope.
I guess I could make this decision.
Let's go up the slope.
You scramble up the slope for a better view of the wall leaving Thomas below.
Seems your new friend was right.
Standing atop the huge stone block is a guard with a long bow.
Slung across his shoulder.
What do we what do we do here?
Ask for advice.
Watch the archer look into the yard.
Let's watch.
You keep watching the guard above the gate looks this way and that but doesn't shift from his position.
Run for it.
Wait like run to the gate.
Start sprinting to the wall.
I'm so far away.
I'm going to get insta-killed.
Run for it.
Let's go down into the pass down into the pass.
I'm not going to run for it.
That means that's dumb.
There's nothing else for it.
You put a hand up and call out.
The archer lifts a hand to shield his eyes against the sun.
Who goes there?
Friend or foe?
Friend.
Foe.
Neither.
This is the dumb thing to do, right?
This is how you're going to die either way.
If you say this you're dead.
If you say that you're dead.
If you say this let Thomas answer, right?
Yeah, okay, Thomas knows the...
He knows.
You wait and Thomas cries back.
Friend!
And the watchword is catapani!
The guard pauses a moment
then lowers his bow.
Approach!
Thomas turns and smiles at you.
Okay, approach the gate.
The south gate stands before you.
It is as tall as two men
and would be broad enough to ride three horses through.
If only it were open.
But instead it is locked
and there's no other way into the city.
Luckily, of course, you have a key.
Over to you?
Says Thomas stepping back.
Knock on the door.
Unlock the gate with the key or cast a spell.
What's available right now?
I wonder.
Is this Doth?
Okay, so you can throw a fireball at the door.
Which would be insane.
I don't think I would make it out of that alive.
We could do big.
I have the key.
I just use the key or just let him do it, right?
Why would I do this on my own?
Should I impress everybody that I can do it?
It's a waste of stamina.
Okay.
Unlock the gate with the Swin Chief's key
or just knock on the door.
Yeah, but am I allowed in here?
Wouldn't they think this is weird?
I'm going to do it.
You quickly remove the Swin Chief's key from your pack
and slip it into the lock.
The tumblers
click
as the key turns.
Thomas hangs back.
Good work.
But do you think it's safe to go through?
It sure is.
Why don't you check?
I'll go first.
Let's wait.
Why don't you check?
You do it.
What do you guys think?
Let's do a poll.
I'm curious.
What do you guys want to do?
Push the old guy in first.
We need to keep Thomas alive.
Clueless.
Is it safe?
What do you guys think?
You're doing the polls
because you want chat to choose the mean one.
I mean, well, I'm doing the poll
because I want chat to choose the mean one
and I want nothing to do with it
because I probably would have chosen a mean one
and everybody would have gone,
oh my God, dude, go back.
You left her.
You left her there.
Why would you do that?
So that's not on me anymore, right?
Remember all of yesterday?
Dude, you actually should rewind.
I didn't like that.
If you picked it,
you all would have been yelling at each other and not me.
All right.
What are we doing?
Is it safe?
We're going to wait.
Okay.
Let's wait.
Let's wait, you say.
Thomas nods.
A few heartbeats pass,
but you hear nothing from inside the yard.
Then he shakes his head.
I'm going for it.
Thank you, stranger.
And with that,
he dashes away inside.
You hear nothing for a moment
than the sound of shouting voices and feet rushing away.
He just didn't give a shit.
Go in after Thomas or wait.
Okay.
So a few heartbeats,
that's kind of funny.
Considering a few heartbeats is like two seconds.
He didn't even sit there for two seconds
before he got impatient and went in.
Go help him.
What did I do before?
I actually don't remember.
What did I do?
I don't even know what I did before.
Go.
I'm going in after him.
Slipping inside,
you find the yard deserted.
The old soldier has cleared it out for you.
You push the great gate closed.
He's still in the lock.
Whoever the next ruffian to visit Carré may be,
he will be grateful for your little gift
gotten through the gate.
How fast is your heartbeat?
What are you talking about?
A few heartbeats is
That's like two seconds.
That's not even two seconds.
You pause just inside the shadow of the gate.
To your left is a low stone building
with metal bars for windows.
Duck behind the building.
Hurry out of the yard
or try the door to the low building.
All right.
What do you guys want to do?
This is important.
What do you want to do?
Duck behind the building.
Get hurry out
or try the door.
You got to hurry up
before the guards get back.
But wait, who knows?
Do you hide?
Do you try the door?
Do you duck?
Do you run?
All these choices are up to you.
In sorcery.
Part two.
Carré.
City board of traps.
Stop doing the game show host voice.
I know you didn't say stop doing that,
but that's what I said.
All right.
What are we doing?
Try the door.
Okay.
Try the door to the low building.
You go over to the door.
It is locked.
But the key is still in the keyhole.
At that moment,
two soldiers march around the corner.
Dive inside the building
or greet the guards.
Oh, hello.
How are you?
Good to see you again.
What do you think?
Should I just greet them?
I haven't done anything wrong, right?
Like did I do anything wrong?
I was let in here.
I'm not...
Okay, the old man ran in
and did like a bunch of weird shit.
Why am I not allowed in here?
I'm going to greet them.
There's no time for anything but a gamble.
You stride right up to the guards.
You there!
You declare.
Why wasn't there anyone to meet me
at the gate?
The man looks baffled.
What gate?
Who are you?
I'm the ambassador from Anorland.
I'm the new chief mage of Kaare.
I mean, which one of these is more believable?
Probably the first one.
The chief mage?
Should I say chief mage?
I'm the ambassador from Anorland.
I'm the chief mage.
I'm the new chief mage.
I'm the new chief mage of Kaare.
The guard looks panicked.
No one.
No one told us you were coming, sir.
I should turn you into a frog.
No matter.
Sir.
What can I do for you, sir?
Take me to the north gate.
The guard peers at you.
The north gate?
Why?
No one goes there.
It's haunted, cursed, and locked.
That's exactly what I'm here for.
Are you questioning me?
Then I'll handle this myself.
Number two.
Yeah, I like number two.
You questioning me?
No, sir.
This way, sir.
All right.
Hey, let's go.
Follow the guard.
The guard marches along the road and you follow
until you reach the top of the south gate yard.
Sir, I can't leave my post, sir.
The guard says.
But if you follow this road, you'll find your way into Kaare.
And from there?
The quickest route to the center is the main road through the fields.
The guard answers.
Avoid the less pleasant areas of town.
You should avoid the festival too, sir, if you value your purse.
The guard clicks his heels.
You frown severely and take your leave as quick as possible.
Interesting.
The quickest route to the center is the main road through the fields.
Avoid the less pleasant areas of town.
Well, that's not up to me.
It's going to be up to you.
So I guess I'm I guess I'm going to go this way for now.
Interesting.
Ooh, this is interesting.
Okay, show the map.
I will in just one sec.
Night is falling.
Luckily by the roadside is a small inn, which will make perfect place
to stay before you lose yourself in the winding streets of Kaare.
Alternatively, you could walk into the fields to the right and sleep
out under the stars.
From somewhere nearby, you hear a low baying howl.
Where we going?
Where are we off to?
You want to see the map?
Here is the map.
This is where we are right now.
And as you can say, this is there's a lot going on here.
It's cat.
All these animals.
What do you guys want to do?
Actually, you know what?
I I want to go to the inn.
We got money.
I'm making a decision.
We're going to the inn.
A sign outside the inn proclaims it the crooked finger.
Look at that map inside of a map.
Let's go in.
You go inside and find an empty bar.
The bartender is snoozing at the counter.
Clearly trade is bad.
Sleep outside in front of the inn or approach the bar.
Get a good look at what it looks like in here.
I'm ever going to the bar, right?
The bartender wakes with a snortle as you approach.
Greetings traveler.
You'll be looking for directions to somewhere else.
I suppose.
I need to eat.
There's no food here.
I'm afraid.
The innkeeper says no point since the rats get it all but a bed
for the night will cost you seven gold pieces.
That's way too much.
Actually too much.
Seven gold pieces is robbery.
You tell him the innkeeper shrugs.
Carray prices might not be what you're used to but you can
sleep in the street if you prefer and then maybe you'll see
why they're as high as they are.
That's too much.
Seven gold seven gold pieces.
I do I need to eat though.
Otherwise you'd lose.
I think I think you lose max stamina if you don't eat for
a day.
I could sleep with the rats.
Um, no, no fuck you.
It's too high and you turn to leave.
Wait a minute.
The innkeeper says he reaches under the counter and produces
a handful of dice.
You want to play swindle stones?
Maybe we can settle this with a game.
I don't play games.
I know.
I don't know the rules.
I'll play you in swindle stones.
Let's go by the way.
Excuse me.
You you want to start a new twitch meta guys swindle stones
new twitch meta.
Let's go is literally liars dice with like one small change,
but whatever I'll play you.
You reply taking a seat at the bar.
Excellent.
The innkeeper rubs his hands together clearly thinking he
will be able to hustle you out of some money.
So what's the steak?
No steak at four at the cost of the room.
The cost of the room you suggest seven gold pieces.
You place a stack of coins on the bar.
The innkeeper grins and rubs his hands together.
Sounds like my kind of game.
The innkeeper counts out five dice each and takes first bid.
Okay, so swindle stones is an interesting game.
It's just liars dice.
Essentially the game is simple.
We roll and bet on what's come up.
So for instance, I might start and bet that between us we've
rolled at least two threes, right?
Well, we don't know what's on the table.
So you have to essentially you have to guess of what how you
want you bluff.
You're trying to catch people in getting it incorrect.
So I could call right and say I don't think there are two
threes between the two of us and that would be a really
stupid idea because if I did that he might just have two
threes and have started with that.
This is in The Witcher.
It's Witcher's Yahtzee.
No, it's Steve Jackson's Sorcery Swindle Stones.
This game came out like 50 years ago.
I'm sorry, but this is the one that it's based on.
What I have here is I have three fours.
So I could essentially just go I got we got I got two.
Hey there I got there are two fours, right?
Because I know I have at least two of them.
That's what I'm going to say.
Indeed.
So I can't see your dice and you can't see mine.
You only have what I tell you about what I've got, but you
may be trying to deceive me.
Okay, so that means he has so he has a four.
I wonder if he has two fours because this would be correct.
I have three and he must have one to say that he must have
one unless he's lying, which I don't know.
Let's find out call it.
All right is no fucking way, right?
If you believe my bid is too high you can call and we and
we check otherwise we keep getting higher and higher.
I that means he has to have two fours, which he might I
don't buy it though.
One two, three.
He what's the what's the chances that he has two fours?
This is squid game.
It's not squid stop saying quit squid game call there.
So you did have two fours you piece of shit.
All right.
So now I lose a dice and we keep going squid game.
Whatever squid game.
I don't care.
All right.
So let's say I'm going to say there are I'm going to say
I got two twos.
This is absolute horse shit, right?
This is a complete and total fabrication.
So he's going to be like, oh this motherfucker has two twos
three twos.
Oh you think so you think so call it that he has to have
three fucking twos.
No way.
There it is tied up again.
So you're new to our fair city is you how can you tell?
Okay.
So you're saying two threes.
I have one so that means he must have at least one.
Let's go three threes.
Let's just let's just pull it off right here.
Three threes.
Let's go.
Yeah, fuck it.
He's not going to call it.
Oh my God.
What an idiot.
Wait, is he an idiot or does he have three of them?
No way call advantage player.
So now he only has three dice.
So it becomes harder and harder and harder.
If you've ever seen squid game, apparently it's in squid game.
Apparently I guess.
Okay.
So now so he only has three.
So I have I could just do this right.
I think there are one there are one.
I only have one.
So let's go one for two twos.
So he only has three.
He has to have two doesn't I don't I'm calling it.
That means he has he has to have two of his three dice have
to be twos.
I don't think he has two twos.
He would have to have two.
No, it's you can just make it up.
Three twos, but if he calls that then he his bluff worked.
I'm gonna say two fives because I have it and if he calls it
I don't care three twos.
All right.
No, I'm sorry, dude.
But this do you think do you guys honestly think he has three
his whole hand is a two.
No, fuck you call it.
I win.
I would have won last time anyways.
No, I wouldn't have I would have yeah, I would have all right.
He only has two dice left.
You do reach the North Gate.
How will you open it?
I don't intend to.
All right.
So he's one of his he's saying he has a one.
Try to just fuck with them here.
Two fours.
I have two fours.
All right.
So he might have a one and a four so I could call them out
here and do three fours.
I mean three.
Sorry.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Wait, what?
Yeah, free whatever, you know what I'm saying?
Because if I if he calls what if he hey might have that I
think he has a three.
He definitely has a three.
Why you're gonna just lose if you don't I'm gonna be three
threes.
All right with this.
That's physically not possible.
Like you just lose roll dice one more time.
He has one dice and I have four.
Okay, so I get to start.
There are I got one one.
So make it up.
He's gonna say two ones one two.
Okay, so you have a two.
Let's say two twos three twos.
I will take that free night in the inn by the way seven
gold.
I don't got to spend anything.
Let's go.
I win.
Don't I talking to people will provide clues to help your
quest.
You can review your clues on the inventory screen collect
your gold from the counter once more and the innkeeper
reluctantly counts out another seven into your palm.
I was unlucky.
It happens.
You want another try?
I've played enough.
You tell him happy with your winning streak very well from
cost seven gold pieces.
And as I said very cool.
Wait, I could also sleep outside.
Should I not even spend the money?
I think I'm gonna sleep outside.
I'll be on my way.
The innkeeper looks surprised but I thought but you are
out of the door before he finishes heading to find a
field to bed down in for free.
I got 24 gold.
I got the ape.
Now the ape the ape hates me.
You strike off into fields and find a muddy Dell in which
to stretch out the stars are out forming the constellations
of the ape and you feel a certain piece despite the
hulking shadow of the wall settle to sleep you settle
quickly the sounds of the city drift to you on the night
air shouts and screams and the occasional distant howl
distinctly you doze off fitfully turning over in your
mind that what the innkeeper told you of the four spell
lines required to open the North Gate didn't pay any
attention to that.
I was too busy gambling then halfway through the night
you will wake into the sound of something scratching in
the earth nearby sit up ignore it or draw my sword.
They're in the rocks.
You're gonna get robbed.
I'm gonna sit up you sit up and peer into the darkness
you see red glowing eyes and slavering teeth in the
gloom.
It's a werewolf but how can that be the moon is only
crescent.
What do we got you deal with it and go back to bed.
We also got of course law laws expensive, but it's really
helpful.
Shield Raz sharpen blade rock turn to stone and then
I'm assuming probably hot right how fine safe passage
safe passage.
That's interesting and this also hot as well.
No zap.
No one.
Oh yeah, there's hot gob.
All right.
Let's just let's go for it.
Let's go.
I have 12 teeth.
Let's go you toss down a tooth and cast your spell
across it tooth appears to ignite sending up a wisp of
smoke.
Which then fattens out into the shape of a goblin
warrior performs a ridiculous salute and then sets to
attacking the werewolf the fight is tense and close
and the goblin gets a few good strikes in but one
strong charge from the werewolf is too much one
moment.
The Beast has the goblin throat between its jaws.
The next the goblin has vanished entirely more you
throw down a second tooth a second warrior appears
rattling his sword and shield to try and scare the
werewolf away.
Amazingly it works and the Beast turns tail and runs
off into the dark.
The little goblin disappears in pursuit and you are
left alone.
Why would he chase him?
I could have you could have hung we could have hung
out man.
All right.
Well back to bed.
I got 10 more teeth.
Your dreams when they come are of the wall like a
towering monster drenched in moss and slime the gate
it's wide open ma on its back is a host of guards
chanting a mantra too quietly for you to hear as
you watch it reaches down with fingers made from
flagpoles and skewers the old beggar man lifting him
flailing into the air.
Oh my God as you make your way inside guards appear
and disappear from holes in the ground like burrowing
moles a wolf and shining armor howls at the sun and
it is there as though you can see the crown sitting
in the dust on the far side of the North Gate so
close and yet out of reach found a new clue.
What are the clues?
North spell gate the North Gate requires a spell
made of four lines to be opened without the lines
you will not be able to leave the city port.
First noble Sansus knows Lord Sansus is the first
noble of Kare and only he knows the full spell to
open the North Gate of the city port.
Armored wolves werewolves capped in their lupine
form by magical plate armor are stalking the city
at night.
We did learn about Vic.
A man named Vic runs several businesses in the
city port.
These two know each other.
Andrigor and Vic were once comrades.
Turn the music down never.
Okay next morning.
Why did what am I saying meow because all the cats
that are meowing in the background.
Can you not hear them?
Do you not hear all the cats?
Is it too low?
You guys can hear the horses right now, right?
Yeah, okay.
So you didn't hear the cats earlier?
You wake early ready to begin your exploration
of the city following the track for a few minutes
you reach a junction where three roads begin.
These are the outskirts of Kare.
Huts huddle like beggars on either side of the
tracks leading uphill into the city port.
Pause to look around.
It must be clear to everyone around that you are
a stranger in these parts.
The city's inhabitants a multitude of malevolent
creatures who would kill for the laces of your
boots turn to watch you as they pass.
You are sport a figure to be jostled and robbed
and one who will most likely fall prey to the
strange elaborate system of traps laid across
Kare by the early settlers to protect themselves
from one another.
There are more people here than you've seen in a
long time.
You cast an eye across the faces to see if any are
flanker the assassin you met outside Torrapani.
You look left to the left you see a group of scruffy
youngsters walking up the road with packs on their
back.
Ahead is the main road into the center of Kare its
surface rutted from cartwheels further in the
distance you see fields.
This is the route taken by supply wagons to the
docks to the right the track heads towards fields
a hut stands proud a little further on the business
of this place is confusing but you'll have to simply
strike out somewhere in this city must be the
information you need to find the spell lines for
the North Gate that the innkeeper told you about
just at that moment a cart rolls down the road from
the right and careens around the corner to take
the main track ahead on its back are stacked several
crates one teeters for a moment and falls near
your feet.
It's lid cracking open look at the crate wave for
the driver to stop or leave it look in the crate
kneeling down in the mud you pry open the crate
with your fingers inside is a pile of smashed
bottles thick purple liquid swills about littered
with shards of glass.
There are perhaps four bottles still intact, but
you recognize the smell it is splinberry a potion
with many healing properties take all take two or
leave them take them all all healing is important
take all of them you take all of the bottles wipe
them down as best you can on the grass nearby and
put them into your pack a lucky find indeed it also
can be used as a meal.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, it's time for one
of the most major decisions of the whole game.
This is important as you see we have three choices
ahead of us.
You understand what's at stake here.
Do you want to go to the left route this way?
Do you want to go up this way or do you want to
go up around here?
Honestly, I think realistically this probably
leads to here this probably this is probably going
to go like this right.
This is probably going to go like this maybe in
whatever in this vicinity and of course this is
going to go over here.
This is one of the more major probably decisions
the whole entire part.
We need to pull where do you want to go left center
or right?
Look at how big this is.
This is a major decision.
I want Squirtle.
I'll give you a bigger bigger picture so you can
see up here.
We've got dwarf town the artist quarter a couple
of towns here a lot of houses.
Whatever this is up here some interesting large
house a few houses to explore whatever this is
this big farm up here something called Mansion
Row right looks to be the Festival of Thieves
Festival of Thieves.
It looks like a carnival going left.
Okay, here we go turn left.
You follow the children with backpacks up the
road homes hovels line the track and strange
faces appear at the windows watching you as you
pass and from around the bend ahead a troop of
guards appear dart into a hut keep my head low
blend in with the youngsters or ignore them.
We need another poll here.
I'm going to be tapping into you guys a lot more
because a lot of these decisions are branching.
This is no longer the tutorial and this is fun.
I think this is cool.
I like doing it.
It's fun to do.
So what and you know, whoever is doing the polls
would have a mod is probably simple just to
sometimes just do like 1 2 3 or 4 that makes it
probably a lot easier to like type everything out
literally, you know, just 1 2 3 4 you guys can
count right Twitch plays sorcery will not every
decision.
I'm obviously I've made half of them already.
So and stuff like this we can end in like 20 to
30 seconds.
You're overestimating us.
Hello fellow kids.
Well, that would be option 3 there's dart into a
hut keep your head low or just ignore them think
about what we've been doing so far.
What why would we be running from the guards,
right?
Do we need to run from the guards?
Do we have to why would we be like, oh shit?
What have you done?
What laws have we broken so far?
We might run into somebody here.
This is this is a nearby hut.
This is not our property.
Keep head low whatever who are these youngsters
you impersonated an official and they don't know
that yet.
Oh fuck.
Maybe they do.
It's true.
All right, we're going to go blend in with the
youngsters.
You stride quickly forward to join the group of
youngsters and attempt to mimic their way of
walking.
The group are talking about where they will stay
the wayfarers rest or the meat and cleaver.
I think the meat and cleaver is the best place.
Listen to our what I don't listen.
Don't speak.
Why would I suggest something that's weird?
That's actually that's weird.
I mean if somebody was walking around, I don't
know right.
I don't I wouldn't do that.
I don't maybe I would if it was like in a different
I don't know what kind of setting you'd be in if
somebody was walking around and they were like,
oh gosh, I just don't know where to eat.
I've I've missed my first time in Vegas hash house
ago go at the link, which it looks okay.
I haven't heard much about it or or Dave's pizza.
I'm not sure.
I mean would I be like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
I'm telling you tell you what hash house at Lake
man.
It's gonna be good.
I don't think I would do that.
I would probably just be like, yeah, I'll just
leave people alone.
What should I do?
All right, run another poll one two or three
because I don't I actually don't know what
happens with these.
I'm not going to be responsible for this.
Where should we stay?
Where should we suggest that they stay?
I wouldn't say anything or you could also do
the thing to where it's like, okay, so oh,
hey hash house ago go at the link.
Yeah, we could pick there or we go to Dave's
pizza and I could pick up I could like, you
know, but answer my my my cell phone, right?
Oh, hey.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, hey, what's up?
Hey, what's up, Joe?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm here.
You got you coming.
You guys coming?
Yeah, cool.
Yep.
Where were you ever meeting up at the hash house
ago go, right?
Oh, yeah, it's my favorite restaurant.
Yeah, that's probably the best restaurant
and that's probably my one of my favorite
restaurants in Las Vegas.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
I'll see you there.
Right.
Do that.
No, not with my fingers.
I'm not like holding up my fingers with
the gag with a cell phone.
Listen, don't speak.
All right, you keep your weary face down
and you must have the right slump to your
shoulders as the guards pass straight by
with nothing more than a derogatory comment.
A pleasant herbal smell drifts from the
doorway of a nearby hut.
Should I go in the hut?
I'm going in.
Let's go.
We're going in this hut.
I'm going in.
Inside is dark with a smell of rotting straw
rising from pile of mattresses that circle
a low table.
It is only after a moment that you notice
these mattresses are occupied.
Three ugly faces peer at you through clouds
of smoke rising from a hookah pipe that
sits on the table.
Examine the people smell the air.
I should walk in and just go.
Oh, that's good.
What the fuck?
Why are you so rude?
Smell the air.
All right.
I need a pole.
Are we?
Well, I mean, I think we could probably
just in case this option goes away.
One, two or three.
Do I even need to run the pole?
It's right.
Maybe not.
I mean, it's it's going to be by a long
shot.
It's going to be two, right?
It is just it is.
I already know it.
Smell the air.
You sniff the air tentatively and your
head spins.
The smoke of the hookah is sweet and
stupefying.
It is weed plant.
Sit and draw on the hookah.
I mean, you just sit here and smoke weed.
This is the this is that gas station
weed we were talking about.
This is not gas station weed.
This is like a hookah place.
I'm going to sit and draw on the hookah.
Fuck it.
Whatever you gesture to the nearest
elf asking for permission to sit down
beside him.
He does not even notice you putting the
pipe to your mouth.
You breathe in a cloud of sweet apple
tasting smoke.
You begin to feel lightheaded weed plant
affects different people in different ways
and you cannot be sure what it will do
to you.
As you wait to find out,
you find yourself staring up into
the clouds.
Shapes seem to form themselves.
There.
Is it a dragon or a milk jug?
That's a milk jug.
If I've ever seen one before.
Milk jug over brimming at its lip
carried by an old man smoking a pipe
or is that a young girl dancing
in a wide billowing dress?
Oh, it's an old man, of course.
It's just smoke.
Oh, come on fleek.
A girl or old man?
I don't know.
This is this seems pretty divided.
This is an old man.
An old man.
Yes.
Your father perhaps before he passed on
smoking a pipe himself
and telling you to train harder
to be cautious to eat well.
He never followed a word of his own advice
and now he is no longer around to
hand it out.
The effect of the smoke is pleasant
and relaxing like a long hot bath
or a good rest.
You feel yourself regaining some strength.
You turn to the nearest elf and nod.
It's really good to meet you.
You say the elf nods back in return.
Is it your hut?
I want to buy it.
I don't have enough.
I have 24 gold.
I don't have like a thousand gold.
Is this your hut?
I want to buy it.
Yeah, I haven't even said anything.
It's good to meet you.
Oh, yeah.
I want to buy this place.
I feel like you they're going to like
kick the shit out of me, right?
Like I want to ask you for help
or I'm new to Kari.
I only have 24 gold.
How am I?
Yeah, don't say that.
All right.
Maybe the hub.
Maybe it's cheap.
I don't know.
Why is this your hut?
I want to buy it.
The elf nods deeply in reply.
I've been sent by the first noble.
I hear the North Gate is locked with a spell.
You have anything to eat here?
This is too obvious.
Maybe.
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna need to eat.
Do you have anything to eat here?
The elf nods a third time more profoundly now.
I feel like I know you already.
I'm an ordinary trader.
I'm on a vital mission.
I feel like I know you already.
Talk to one of the others.
I think this guy's too high, right?
I think we have to go somewhere else.
He's just nodding.
I feel like I know you already.
The elf nods once more.
It is only then that you realize that he is asleep.
This is useless.
The smokers are too confused and vague.
This is why I should have went to somebody else.
Try something else.
Enough talking.
You look around the hut once more.
One of the elves takes a long draw on the hookah pipe
then sighs and settles back on his mattress.
You look at the three creatures who are staring at you with lazy disinterest.
They are the black elves.
Normally dangerous, but now they seem like they could barely stand.
Leave this place.
The atmosphere is putrid.
You go straight back into the fresh air and then continue up the street.
Okay.
Why couldn't I talk to anybody?
That's stupid.
Wait, what if I just wait till everybody's like sober?
All right, there's only one way to go.
Imagine talking to smokers.
There's only one way to go.
You continue up the narrow road.
It is packed either side with mud brick hovels.
But most are deserted.
A few creatures pass by, heads turned down.
They do not look at you.
This part of the city port is barely inhabited.
So you're unlikely to find clues to the North Gate spell here.
There'll be more people to talk to near the docks.
You pass a drinking fountain,
dribbling water into a chipped stone bowl.
Excuse me.
Drink from the fountain.
This is like the worst idea.
Let's get a poll.
Go back and smoke more weed.
Let's go for it.
One, two, or three.
Stop a creature, drink from the fountain, or just keep going.
We need to test your immune system.
By drinking out of a fountain?
I mean, it's probably just a regular fountain.
Or could it be not?
Maybe it's something else.
Should I stop somebody?
Like, hey, excuse me.
Do you know the spell?
The door spell?
All right, what do we got?
The hookah was probably worse than the fountain.
I got healed from the hookah.
That was a good thing.
The real RP mode is to drink because of the weed cotton mouth.
All right, what do we got?
Two, drink from the fountain.
You lean down by the fountain and cup your hand to drink.
The water tastes cool, if herbal.
Perhaps something is growing in it.
Good choice.
Oh, now all of a sudden chat, everyone's going to say spit it out.
Oh, spit it out, spit it out.
Never mind, never mind, never mind.
Or how many of the, like, drink giga chads do we have here that don't care?
Let's find out.
Run another poll, please.
This one can be quick.
This is a free drink.
Go in for a second.
We must commit to the bit.
It's bong water.
I don't know.
It said it was herbal.
It says something's growing in it.
I'm sorry.
If I lean down and I drink out of a fountain and I see a bunch of, like, green mold all over the spout and all over where I drank out of it, and I've cut my hands down and drank it and there's like mold in my hands, I'm going to spit it out.
You swallow boldly.
If the fountain is still running on a busy street like this, it can't be too poisonous.
In fact, the water seems quite fresh.
And you swallow a few more mouthfuls, finding you would not realize how thirsty you were.
All right.
Okay.
I'm stopping somebody.
You stop a stooped orc-like creature.
I...
Hey, you.
Yes?
I'm new to Kari.
Okay.
Fucking leave me alone.
Why would you do this?
I'm heading for the North Gate?
I'm heading for the North Gate.
The North Gate?
I heard about that once.
What did you hear?
Oh, I don't know.
I think maybe they took it down.
But then I've never been able to afford to cross the river.
Is it expensive?
I don't know.
It's all relative.
Excuse me.
I have to be going.
With that, he shuffles away.
There's nothing else to do here.
You continue up the road.
So it's expensive to cross the river.
The corner of a wall.
This part of town feels abandoned.
Like the drying strip of sand left behind by a falling tide.
A little further on.
Hold on.
Sorry.
I'm still getting over this cough.
A little further on.
The road approaches the first stone building you have seen since the hut by the gates.
It has windows of glass and a wide yard inside its uneven high wall.
Whoever lives here is wealthy and understandably cautious.
They have, however, left a fine stallion only loosely tied up outside.
Do we go to the horse?
Go to the house or just keep going on the road.
Steal the horse and run.
All right, we're going to call this one, two, three.
Okay, one, two, three.
See the pole.
Do I even need to run the pole?
Do we need anybody to do that?
You wouldn't download a horse.
Out of the way that you can predict all the outcomes.
Well, because when I look over the chat and I see in all capitals
horse by five to six hundred different people.
I mean, I know you'd only a thousand two thousand people vote on the pole.
It's going to win.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
The horse is free.
Well, we don't know that you approach the horse.
It snorts nervously wary of your presence.
You might be able to claim it calm it or even talk to it with the correct spell.
Oh, come on.
We can't talk to the horse.
Wait, hold on.
We need a green wig.
We didn't.
We never got a green wig anywhere.
We could have talked to the horse.
We could make ourselves invisible.
Sus could sense danger.
We could finally cast sus for the first time.
It's not a bad spell to do in a lot of scenarios.
There's also sap is also.
Oh God.
Uh, why?
Why would you do that?
Just throw a fireball at the horse for what?
It's going to cause a huge problem.
Uh, we have yeah, okay.
So there's your options.
We don't have to cat.
We don't have to cast a spell, right?
We don't have to do that.
We could do sus sus is not a bad one to do.
I'm going to cast us.
Here we go.
You cast the spell and a calm voice enters your mind.
It tells you that the horse is a strong powerful and willful beast
and one unlikely to be tamed but it is not cruel and does not wish you harm
and the voice fades talk to the horse.
Should I talk to the horse?
You try a few words in the common tongue and then a few whispered in the more
gentle language of your boyhood in Chawberry wood.
The animal listens with its ears cocked giving you a strange distant look.
What of course it does.
It's a horse still it appears calmer in your presence.
Now, perhaps you've made a friend keeping your eyes fixed on the beasts.
You slip the reins from around the hitching post and hold them firmly
and in one movement you pull sharply bringing it round so you can jump onto
its back the horse friendly or not is having none of it.
It winnie's loudly and rears up in the air and then with you barely settled on
its back.
It bolts at terrific speed along the road heading back the way you came for
our stuff.
Hold on for dear life or jump free.
Hold on for dear life.
Hit the Yankee splinky now.
We hold now.
We hold use a spell.
This is what happens when you try to steal a horse.
Okay, I'm going to.
I'm going to have to do a poll.
Look at all the holds hold on for dear life.
You cling on as best you can trying to calm the beast as it stampede along
the outer streets of Kare.
You plunge madly through a market past a shrine and down a wide ruined
Street just as you think you're doomed to crash into a building something
makes the horse startle and it leaps throwing you to the ground.
You land awkwardly the horse winnie's and races away.
Where the fuck are we?
Oh my God.
You pick yourself up off the ground.
You are on a wide road that winds along the edge of a cliff.
You're lucky not have been thrown over it.
The road passes through the ruin of a grand building.
It would must have gone what must have been a glorious morning room.
An ornamental pond is all that remains moss grows from the cracks
in its tiled sides.
Okay, so where did we?
All right.
So should we rewind here or do I get three rewinds per part?
What we seem to have done is we were going down this route, which would
have led us probably somewhere over here.
This route would have probably ended up here or here and then up this
way with though.
Okay.
So we may have been able to get here by going this way.
You can only rewind if you fireball the horse.
We could roll with it too.
No, I don't want to do that.
No, no, no, no.
I was reading what somebody said on chat.
I don't want to actually do that.
It's horrible.
All right.
That's funny.
And that's funny.
I mean, I'm going to rewind.
I'm going to use one rewind here.
I'm going to go back to the horse or okay.
Do I go back to the horse?
Or do I go back to the choice of or the horse?
You should just roll with it.
All right.
I have a choice here.
I could make.
I'm going to go before the horse.
Yep.
That's my decision.
One rewind is gone.
We have only two more.
So I have to be careful.
I'm going back.
So here we are again with the horse.
I think I'm going to go into the house.
I don't want to fireball the horse.
That's three stamina.
Do I have to fireball the horse?
Or are you guys going to not, you guys are going to, that's rude.
It's an evil horse.
No.
When I cast sus, it said this horse was very kind and was not going to cause me any harm.
No, I'm not going to haunt the horse.
I'm going to the house.
You step through the gate of the house into its wide front yard.
It was once a magnificent, magnificent place with fish ponds now stagnant.
Fountains now cracked and dry and small groups of quiet trees now overgrown and gnarled like whispering old men.
The building itself has fared no better.
One side has collapsed in on itself completely and the other leans perilously to one side.
Oh dear.
All right.
Look at the trees.
Approach the building or look at the fountains.
Oh, don't resident sleeper because I didn't throw a fireball at a fucking horse.
I don't want to kill a horse.
Okay, you understand if I fireball the horse and mayhem breaks out in the streets and I have to fight 10 people and I'm going to have to rewind again.
I, I, I don't want to throw a fireball at a horse in the street.
I'm going to have to kill like I'm going to have to kill like three people.
You understand that I'm going to get attacked.
The guards are going to chase me.
I only have three.
We I only have three rewinds.
I can't say rewind.
Hey, by the way, sorcery is currently on most platforms.
You can get it on Xbox.
You can get it on Steam.
Choose your adventure.
Maybe you'll throw a fireball at an innocent horse just sitting there on the side of the road and cause mayhem.
I want to go to the house.
All right, let's go look at the trees.
You pause to look around in the trees and shrubs and that's when you notice the two gleaming eyes staring back at you.
A giant bat hangs upside down from one of the branches watching you.
God damn it.
Mud.
I got rid of my quicksand at the, uh, the manticore.
Slowness.
Dud.
Illusion of treasure.
Why would a fake treasure make a bat?
Unless, unless it's not a bat.
Is it like a vampire?
Gack is fear.
God is illusion of worship.
Oh, I can pretend to be a god.
Is there a goblin?
Nope, enough of this.
Um, we could go for a dumb.
Clumsiness.
That's a lot of stamina.
Dud.
That's a lot.
Clumsiness.
I'm going to go, I'm going to do it.
Let's do dumb.
You cast a spell over the bat hoping to make it confused and clumsy, but the spell causes enemies to drop their
weapons and the bat is not carrying anything.
So it comes at you quite unaffected.
Fuck.
What?
What are you talking about?
I thought it made him stupid.
Wait, where's, where's the spell book?
What does it say in the spell book?
What?
Dumb.
When cast at a creature holding an object such as a weapon, the spell will make the creature clumsy and uncoordinated.
It will drop the object.
What?
Oh, dim is stupid.
Oh, come on.
I, I have to, I, I, that's a, I can't waste a rewind.
I can't, that's two rewinds.
No, I can't do that.
Dim.
To muddle its mind, it must be handled with caution as a deranged creature may act unpredictably.
God damn it.
I don't, I can't rewind.
That would be two rewinds and I only have three.
Look, look at my stamina.
This thing's dead.
It's just a bat.
That's great wings buffet at your face.
All right, just, I can kill this thing easily.
I'm so much more powerful.
It's fine.
We're going to get full blast.
Got it, easy.
That's it.
That's how you do it.
That's fine.
Creature is now afraid.
Swinging up from a low crouch, you aim for the beast's heart.
The bat falls to the ground and the light in its eyes goes dark.
You turn to face the house once more.
Okay.
Well, we can't go over to the, this now.
Approach the house.
The front door is as wide as two men and stands imposingly sealed.
A small path winds around the back of the house.
Go to the front door or go to the path at the back.
It's time for you to decide.
What do you want to do?
The front door could be trapped.
Could be hard to open, but maybe more direct.
Or the path leading us around the other side.
Maybe a back door or a window.
Which way would you like to go?
This is the exit here.
So this is the main junction.
This goes back uphill out here.
So this will pull us this way.
This will pull us.
Ooh, wait, this will go this way.
Potentially too.
Ooh, okay, interesting.
Wait, what?
Hold on, this is important.
There's no VOD for this stream.
Disable automatic VOD taking.
No, I didn't, I didn't do that.
Is there no VOD for this stream right now?
Hold on, let me check that.
Because I didn't, I didn't turn it off.
There isn't a VOD for this stream.
Why?
What the hell?
What are they talking about?
Hold on.
Is there a copy?
No, they wouldn't, that wouldn't be.
It got set to private?
Limited edition content.
The lost episode here.
Wait, people, other people have had this problem?
You just have to manually publish it after the stream.
What?
Why would they change that?
Are you kidding?
Hold on.
VOD settings.
Store, pass broadcast.
Always publish VODs.
VODs will be published by, yeah, turn that on.
Excuse me.
Why was that off?
It was off automatically.
That's new.
That's new as of literally today or yesterday.
I just turned it on.
Can we check and make sure that it's here?
Why disable that by default for a new feature?
Hopefully this is actually still here later.
But I'm sorry about that.
I did not know that was even a change.
Well, okay.
I turned it on.
You don't see it yet, but it might, maybe I can do it afterwards.
Okay.
Well, I'm really sorry about that because this is kind of annoying.
God, I just sound so annoyed.
I turned it on.
All right.
What did you do?
Was there a pole?
I didn't see.
Uh, go off the horse.
All right.
Well, did we pick the door or do we pick the path?
It was, it was a path.
I don't remember.
Did we even do one?
It was a door.
I survived the meat grinder incident.
There was no meat grinder incident.
You made it up.
Stop making things up.
Stop making things up about me.
I'm sick of it.
All right.
Here we go.
Door or path.
Door is winning by a shitload.
We're going that way.
Door.
You stride up the steps to the door of the grand house.
What can we do?
Sus comes in handy a lot.
Sense danger.
Is the door trapped?
I can't zap the door though.
It looks like it wanted me to be able to at some point.
Hot the door.
How the door is.
Save passage.
Dop will just open it.
Although I could hold on.
Just try to open the door.
But what if there's a home alone scenario?
And I Joe Pesci go grab it and I burn my hand, right?
Is it trapped?
I don't know.
It might be.
Sus.
Cast a spell on a calm collected voice tells you that inside the
house is nothing but death, despair, and destruction.
The voice having delivered its warning fades away.
We still going in here?
Now what?
Giga Chad.
Enter.
That seems pretty sus to me.
I'm just going to open it.
Try the door.
You try the door locked, of course.
A slate skitters off the roof and smashes itself on the
ground to one side of you.
Wait, what?
Well, I can just break the door down.
That was just for me touching the door.
Break down the door.
Does this hurt?
Just blast the house.
That's too I'm going to be at 13 health.
If I do this, I'm going to burn the house down.
We're going to have gone in it.
Find safe path.
I'm going to do how you cast a spell and you feel your mind
reaching out exploring possible paths and meandering avenues.
Strangely, the spell seems to ignore the house entirely.
In fact, it reaches towards a road heading off on the left.
The spell doesn't want to go in here.
That's safe passage.
I mean, that okay.
Why did I do how how is okay?
They're very literal.
The spells are incredibly literal in this game.
It's just going to tell me what is a safe way to go.
It's information about the safest way of escape.
Of course, I'm standing outside.
It's going to go.
Hey dude, just go that way.
Don't go in.
Why that's not safe.
Go this way.
All right.
Let's break it down taking a short run up.
You charge at the door.
It rebounds heavily, but does not break a cool wind moves
through the trees in the yard making evil whispering sounds.
I just bounced off the door.
I'm knocking on the door.
You walk up in the door to the door and knock just to make sure
nobody answers knock again.
You knock a second time louder as you wait to see if you
will be answered.
You notice a curious detail.
There are deep grooves carved into the wood of the door radiating
outwards from the keyhole.
It is as though something had exploded out through it or
perhaps attached itself on the outside to force its way in
through the lock is a bomb on the door.
If I look through the keyhole, it's going to fucking hit me
in the eyeball.
I'm wasting so much health doing this.
I got to just burnt the fucking whole thing down.
I could do Dopp.
Let's just open it and let's open it and just jump out of
the way hot you coward.
Oh fine.
I'll do it.
Fine.
You cast a spell crafting a flaming ball of fire in your
palm, which you then hurl against the door.
It explodes into a rain of hot splintering shards or the
dark hallway beyond is revealed.
We just blew up whatever was going on there.
That was a magical door.
I have 11 health.
You step inside the great stone house cold silence descends
quite different from the dusty heat outside.
This place feels like it has not been lived in for decades.
Although judging by the lack of dust, it may not have been
quite so long.
Floorboards creak underfoot at the end of the hallway is a
sealed door that a chink of light just visible underneath
the frame the light beneath the door flickers now bright now
faint as though a figure pace back and forth its shadow
coming and going but you hear no footsteps.
We're dead in this house by the way guys like we're going
to die in here.
I just want everyone is aware of this.
Throw another fire.
Roll a fireball down the hallway.
I do have potions.
Okay, we're gone.
You make your way along corridor the walls on either
side are lined with large portraits of dusty looking
men and sour-faced women.
We sneer at you as you pass look at the paintings the
figures in the paintings are all finely dressed, but they
also have knife scars on their faces and nicks in their
ears.
These must be the thief kings of Carae's murky past you
pass a large metal coal scuttle sitting against the
left-hand wall.
You are fucked.
Look at the scuttle.
You stop to look inside the scuttle, but the inside is
blackened and in the darkness.
It seems as though an infinitely deep pit was contained
inside run the pole.
Am I put my hand in this thing or am I going to put it
down?
We're going to get sucked into this thing put it down.
I'll put the hand in the while this wrong shit.
What the hell is that?
So while this runs while the pole runs.
I have a very important question.
So the VOD shit can I publish the VOD at the end of
this stream or is it just gone unless I'd like restart
it?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, we'll be there.
All right, that's cool.
All right, then I'm not that concerned about it anymore
then.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean it was obvious what was going to happen
here.
Actually, I could if it's there privately, right?
Let me see.
Yep, it's there.
All right.
Thank God that would have been horrible.
Yeah, I see it privately.
I can publish it later at the end of the stream.
Thank God.
All right.
Put my hand inside.
You are not afraid you reach into the scuttle blind scuttle
feels empty.
Then your finger touches something sharp so sharp.
It stings take your arm out or search for the sharp thing.
I mean, okay, you put my hand in here.
I'm not taking it out.
Search the sharp thing you feel around in the scuttle
searching for the object and you find it earning another
sharp prick more you keep feeling around and have a clear
sense that something is climbing up your arm to your
wrist.
Shake it off.
Shake it up.
You shake your arm vigorously and then with your other
hand try to bat the thing away, but you feel a stinging
pain in your other hand and a moment later you feel the
same biting sensation on your neck.
That's when you realize there's still something wrapped
around your hand as well.
It's a snake kill it or run into the light or run into
the light just sprinting into the light.
I'm going to run into the light.
You have had enough of this torture in the dark.
You race out of the house.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I want to do.
That's not what I want this one.
And this is a this rewind doesn't count.
This rewind doesn't count.
That doesn't count.
That's not what I thought.
That's not what I wanted that rewind does not count.
Okay, so here we were for my hand inside.
Okay, search for the sharp thing.
Keep feeling around.
Okay.
What is it?
Yep.
It's a snake kill it you make to raise your sword and
kill the beast, but it is wrapped itself tightly around
your wrists and now you cannot move your arms at all.
You've had enough of this torture in the dark you race
out of the house.
Oh fuck what as you hit the light the serpent hisses
and rears back and drops into the shadow.
It must be a dark snake a creature whose bite is luckily
not poisonous just itchy.
Oh, we're fine.
Back in the house.
You take a moment to collect yourself and then you
step back into the darkness of the corridor determined
not to leave the house unexplored.
Yeah, we're good.
You reach the far end of the hall.
It is only a short way from the entrance, but all is
now in shadow.
The only light that comes from the gap around the
frame of the door in front of you more darkness wells
up to the right.
You can just make out the first few steps of a flight
of stairs leading away upwards to the second level
of the house.
He just wants you to leave so bad too.
All right, enter the study or up the stairs.
Pull please study stairs.
I need to heal.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
I'll just drink one.
I have three more potions.
Where are we going?
Oh really into the study.
Okay.
You push open the door and enter a wide paneled room
with a thick carpet.
It is a study of some kind the source of the light
under the doorframe becomes quickly apparent a roaring
fire burns in an enormous grate on one side of the
room.
Okay, let's explore a little here.
I'm gonna I'm gonna look around you search around the
room.
The furniture is grand carved and stained and inlet
with patterns of Goblin bone, but there are no
possessions to be seen.
No ornaments.
No jewels.
No treasure and no sign of the owner.
It is as if whoever lived here had moved out or more
likely as though the place had been thoroughly robbed
with the door shut.
You'd expect this room to be sweating Lee hot like
the rest of the house.
It is icy cold.
No loot.
This is not a quest German.
This is a burglary.
Yeah, well you want to be lawful good.
Hey, you go get it.
You go over to the fire to warm your hands only to
find it emits no heat at all.
It burns no fuel either.
The enormous great large enough to roast a whole bore
is entirely empty of wood ash or coal, but the flames
are nonetheless brilliant and as high as a man.
Great wind know how there is sus though fog summoned
darkness is also magic protection protect from magic
no need for sus.
I mean I have to assume that it's probably I think I'm
trying to remember what's in here.
What if there's anything here I'm going to do I'm going
to do magic.
Let's do protect from magic.
You cast a spell in a veil of magical protection
settles around you should any enchantment attack
will be well protected for as long as the spell lasts
what no no no no I want to oh shit.
No no look at look this up.
Okay, you can't show up.
I'm reminding this doesn't count.
Doesn't count doesn't count doesn't count doesn't count
doesn't count look at the flames.
All right doesn't count doesn't count peering deeper
at the base of the fire.
You see there's definitely nothing burning there.
The flames spring into life fingers with above the
great they're so bright you can make out nothing beyond
but it seems that the hearth goes back some distance
wait, but I didn't cast the magic protection.
Oh fuck it.
Whatever stealing your courage you duck your head
and step into the great the flames surround you their
crackles whispering in your ears as though you stood
in a pit of snakes, but you feel no heat your skin
does not blister and your clothing does not ignite
you stand in the middle of the fire like some kind of
demon and feel no ill effects at all from here.
You can see that the hearth extends backwards much
further than you might expect.
Is it a tunnel or do you stand inside of a trap its
jaws about to spring shut we go in you creep forward
across the great through the flames and beyond into
a low stone alcove hidden by the fire the walls are
made of solid slabs of stone and there is nothing
here.
No treasure no secret doors on the fall on the far
wall or a strange set of markings searings of long
grooves like scratches radiating outwards from a
small hole.
What can we do?
T what is T?
We don't have it.
I hate that.
I hate not.
I hate knowing that there could have been something
here.
We don't we don't know the spell.
We don't know the spell.
We got top this is open locks and doors, but I wonder
if that work here.
We have ought and how is also sap cause depression
is also sus course will do top you cast the spell
across the groove wall in front of you, but nothing
happens.
Perhaps it's not a door after all or perhaps it is
locked with a fearsome magic your own spell cannot
overcome.
It's impossible to be sure you run your fingers through
the grooves in the stone wall.
They are a lot like the grooves you saw around the
keyhole of the front door.
Good thing I blew it up.
They have been carved lightly and roughly with a
dagger point rather than a chisel perhaps, but the
small hole at their center is much more cleanly
formed.
I blow this one up too.
Bucket whatever you cast the spell creating a
fireball of powerful heat and light in the palm of
your hand the dead end quickly heats up but in the
light you can make out a few suggestive cracks in
the left hand wall seems like one of the stones
might move but how there's no way to tell then the
fireball flickers and fades the cracks fall into
shadow once more and the sweltering heat fades to
your I just hurt my I threw a fireball myself.
Oh, no, I didn't.
Well, what did I do?
What did I do feel over the left hand wall you run
your fingertips of the left hand wall, but can no
longer find the cracks you saw in the light of your
fireball.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Let me in here.
Examine the hole you put one finger into the small
hole.
You cannot find the bottom of it and it seems polished
and smooth.
It looks like the bolt hole you might find in the
stonework of a fortress doorway except for its
position in the middle of a blank wall that a keyhole
you look through your pack for something to use as
a key insert a pipe.
I have what I have a pipe.
Where did I get a pipe?
Wait, wait, like my my musical pipe board if it
breaks.
What if I break it?
It's the flute.
You might lose it.
Oh, no inventory.
Oh wait other items.
Apes teeth to snatocats teeth 204 gold a sword
beeswax skull cap.
No, it has to be that I'm doing it.
Do something else.
Fuck fuck.
Free free.
Okay, free rewind free rewind free.
I got a free.
I get a free rewind.
Okay keyhole insert the pipe you slip the bamboo
flute into the small hole in the back of the
fireplace.
There's a click for a moment.
Nothing happens.
And then very slowly the stones begin to move a
passageway has opened.
I do I get to keep it I do.
All right.
I get to keep the flute.
Let's go you peer through the secret passage,
but can make out nothing but darkness beyond
you'll have to go inside to find out what you
have discovered flipping through the narrow
opening.
You find yourself in a slightly wider space.
The walls are cool stone and there are no
windows, but the room is not dark in one corner
and idle stands on a small shrine lit by two
candles, which burn with thin cold flames.
This place reeks of death and decay.
The shrine is covered in thin blood soaked strips
of cloth.
All right, let's look at it.
The shrine is poor and cheap.
Unlike everything else in the house seems to
have been hastily built out of uneven stones
and a plank of wood and the small statue of a
fat God that sits on it has been molded from
humble clay.
This is a cloth.
The bandages are each an arm span long and as
deep as your thumb each is bloodied in two
places spaced a few fingers widths apart.
There are 30 or 40 such bandages here running
down from the shrine like streamers.
Someone was injured for a long time.
You glance behind you suddenly terrified that
the secret door might swing shut and leave you
trapped in this place.
Oh, okay.
Let's let's look at the God.
It must be some local deity at the base of the
statue is the name Corga above his head is a
plaque with a short inscription and on his
face are painted for red dots.
You're starting to get the jitters down here.
Read the inscription.
The inscription is scrawled as though in the hand
of a child.
You have to squint to read it.
Give me back my eyes.
Okay, the dots on the idol seem to have been
daubed with a fingertip.
They're perhaps directions on how to worship
the God but there's no indication of what to do
or in what order only the places both eyes the
third eye in his forehead and his mouth.
Give me back my eyes.
Should I search the bandages out out out get out
get out get out you sift through the pile of
bloodied cloth strips quickly.
Something gleams from within the pile and you
want to cover a silver badge.
It is the badge of a noble of Kare.
The badge is solid silver and probably valuable.
You place it carefully into your pack.
There's nothing more to be seen in this terrible
place.
You slip back out of the small room out of the
fireplace and into the hallway.
You found a clue.
Okay, the ritual of Corga and I got a silver
badge.
Where is it?
Badge of the seventh noble.
Ooh, do you look at that?
All right, let's head back out compared to the
little room.
You've just left the dark and empty hallway seems
welcoming and friendly but not so much that you
plan to linger.
We're going upstairs.
Are we going?
Are we leaving the house stick around go up go
up go up go up.
Okay, we're going up you place your foot on the
first step of the stairwell and suddenly it
begins to move.
Is it alive or some kind of thin flat beast or
is it a trap grab the handrail stay still or
jump hole time jump back stay still or grab the
handrail.
So none of those rewinds counted, right?
I still have two they all counted.
I have two real rewinds remaining.
You have none remaining.
They counted.
No, they didn't count doesn't matter.
You change the rules every time you have two
rewinds.
They don't exist.
They don't count.
I don't change the rules every time look the
first time I rewind.
I made the wrong choice.
I thought I was going to be able to walk through
the end of the fire, right?
I that was come on.
All right.
What are we doing here?
Looks like I'm grabbing the handrail you grab the
handrail to steady yourself only to find it is
moving as well.
I'm going to hold on here.
I'm going to hold on you cling onto the rail to
keep yourself upright.
It seems the rail is moving at the same speed as
the step underneath you.
You rise to the top of the stairwell in a smooth
motion and jump off in perfect safety.
It was just an automatic stair thing.
It's just like an escalator.
There's nothing scary about that.
It was just a way to go up the stairs.
Okay.
Well, we made it if you jump you probably get hurt.
You look around you're on the upstairs landing with
doors on either side.
I have to assume we're probably going to get to go
to each of these will start with the bedroom and
then well, maybe we'll start with the library.
This is a library in darkness at the far end a
pair of eyes stare back at you.
Who's there you call out the creature at the other
side of the room makes no reply.
In fact, it makes no sound at all.
The distant eyes have yet not blinked you step
forward boldly your own eyes fixed on those across
the room from you did you not blink they don't even
move as you approach.
I mean, you know harm.
All right.
I'm going to say stare it out.
I'm going to say I mean, you know harm you raise
your hands to indicate you mean no harm.
The eyes do not react and you see why they're the
eyes of a large portrait that hangs over the far
wall in shadow, but for a dim Sunbeam falling
through a gap in the roof above.
All right, but wouldn't you do the guys this world
of thieves creatures robbers killers assassins
your you're going to do the same exact thing.
The painting is of a proud and stern looking man
dressed in loose leather armor with a serpent emblem
stitched along the length of one arm the painting
fills the entire wall of the room.
It must be twice the height of the man who posed
for the likeness.
Look at the man you step back a little to regard
the man in the picture.
The most striking thing about him are his eyes
cold and cruel.
They seem to gleam with cunning and the will to
survive.
They are the eyes of a man who would harm you if
it suited him knowing full well what it did.
I'm sorry.
I've ruined that moment knowing fell.
No, sorry.
Let me restart.
They are the eyes of a man who would harm you
if it suited him knowing full well what it was
he did.
Otherwise he stands tall and proud with one hand
on the hilt of a sword and the other wielding a
tiny dagger.
Everything about him reeks of power in a threat.
The picture must be of the man that lived in the
house for anyone else.
It would surely cast too long a shadow to live
beneath the eyes of the painting seem to follow
you as you move.
Audiobook Andy.
You raised one corner of the frame from the wall
and here up behind it, but it's too dark to see
if there's anything hidden there.
I take the painting off the wall or no, don't do
that.
Take the painting off.
I mean, why not?
You grab the base of the painting between
outstretched hands and heft the frame up and off
the hook that holds it to the wall.
There is a moment when you think you have it under
control.
Then you are holding the true weight of the picture
and begin to stagger backwards.
I got it.
I don't what if it explodes?
I'm going to try to balance it you backpedal across
the room trying to keep your balance.
The painting threatens to topple at any moment.
If you can just get turned around, you'll be able
to lean the painting against the wall.
Stay still step back.
I got hurt.
Step backwards into the left step backwards into
the right left gang.
No, I don't know though.
Left step backwards to the left.
You step backwards into the left and bring the
painting down to the floor to rest safely against
the opposite wall.
You rub your arms with relief.
Really?
I thought we were dead.
You by the way, you probably can just get squished.
You can just get squished probably by the painting
and die.
What a shitty way to go.
Okay.
Look at the back of the canvas.
See I didn't want to break it.
This is the reason why with the painting tilted
against the side wall.
You're able to slip around and look at the back of
the canvas in the weak light that trickles in through
the door.
It is unremarkable which is the single inscription
near the middle of the canvas.
Theta Seventh Noble of Kare.
The painting looks like a noble all right, or at
least it looks like the painting a noble would have
made of themselves.
Theta Seventh Noble of Kare.
You look over the wall to where the painting had hung
but there's nothing else of interest.
It's just a dark outline.
You turn your attention to the portrait.
There's nothing left.
You found one new clue and another clue has been
updated.
All right, we know who the Seventh Noble is.
Lord Theta is the Seventh Noble of Kare.
Lord Sansus is the First Noble of Kare and only he
knows the full spell to open the North Gate.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I remember this now.
Yeah, the spell and the nobles and oh, yeah, this
is this is this is nuts.
I remember this.
Okay, top of the stairs.
You return to the top of the stairs.
We're obviously going to go in here because why
not explore the whole thing?
You step through a doorway into a simple bedroom.
The bed is unmade and looks as though its owner
left in a hurry.
Personal effects are scattered all over the floor
as if the place has been ransacked, which it
probably was.
A cane leans by the bedside.
You see nothing else of interest.
Look at the cane.
The cane is a simple straight stick with a leather
loop at the top to slip around the wearer's
wrist.
It does not look like any sort of weapon.
It does not appear to be magic.
It's a cane.
Should I take the cane?
Why not?
It's a cane.
Take it.
You take it, although you cannot think what it
might be for.
Second door leads further into the house or you
could return to the stairwell.
I got a cane now, boys and girls.
Look at this.
Walking cane.
Let's go.
The further door leads into a bathroom.
There's nothing in it, not even a mirror.
Only a gap where one used to hang.
The only fixture is an empty iron bathtub in the
middle of the tiled floor.
Look under the bath.
You crouch down and peer under the bath.
Something darts at your face and you leap back.
Look again or run my sword under the bath or leave.
We need to pull here.
Look again, run the sword underneath.
Stare.
What's under the bath?
It could be a creature.
It could be a monster.
It could be something harmless.
It could be.
That's right.
All right.
It seems like look again is the answer.
Yep.
Okay.
We're going to look again.
You crouch down again and peer under the bath a
second time.
Just in time to see a rat disappearing through a
crack in the floorboards.
You head out of the room.
It's just a rat.
Return to the bedroom.
Think that's it for the house.
You walk back out of the hall.
There's nothing more to explore up here so we can
go downstairs.
There does not seem to be anything more to be
discovered.
Stairs are quite normal now.
Okay.
Out of the house.
This house is home now only to ghosts.
You hurry back out the door into the sunshine of
the front garden.
Outside.
We made it out.
Made it out.
Outside the house.
The sun is shining brightly.
It is almost the hottest hour of the day.
Interesting.
Okay.
So we can go the path around the house.
Leave back to the main road or just go look at the
fountain.
Go hot the horse.
How come you're rattling around a plastic cup?
I'm going to look at the fountain first.
It's just I mean it's easy here.
A fountain by the door is still bubbling.
Cupping your hands you drink a deep mouthful and
feel much better.
Oh fucking hell yeah.
Easy.
All right.
So now what?
Now what?
Okay.
All right.
Main.
So we're going to say one, two.
I'll give you a big look.
One, two.
Which way?
Nice optometrist.
This is 50-50.
All right.
I might have to let this one go because I don't know
that's an important decision because obviously we
can go this way.
There's a lot of random stuff here.
There's also a lot of random shit over here too.
It's unanimously 50-50.
It is.
All right.
Actually, I'm going to go pee and I'm going to get
refill my drink.
I will literally be right back.
And please have one of the mods tell me what happened.
You're back.
All right.
Have you guys got some?
Ooh, that's some nice sounds.
He's looking under the bathtub.
Two, one by three boats?
No.
Is the VOD going to be?
Yeah.
So Twitch changed something with the VODs.
They didn't auto publish anymore, but I do have
access to it.
So I will be able to publish it after the stream.
So it's there.
Yeah, that's unanimous.
Yeah.
All right.
So we're going with option two.
Sounds like it.
Okay, let's go.
You guys good?
You guys ready?
You follow the path around the back of the building.
The rear is simply boarded up and secure with no new
ways in that you can see.
There's a low stone wall partially ruined for which
the path continues turning into a track that runs
away through fields.
Oh, we were not going back.
We're going this way.
Follow the track.
You follow the track clamoring over a fence into a
wide stretch of grazing land.
A rocky bluff on the left-hand side throws the path
into a shadow.
On the top of this rise is the bulk of Kare squatting
like a gigantic toad.
The fields themselves are on the lower plane.
All right.
So we don't, we only have this decision to go this
way, which is going to probably give us a few things
to do here.
So here we go.
Keep going.
You continue along the track leaving the buildings of
lower Kare behind.
There's no one can leave the walls of Kare.
They do their farming here inside the walls as best
they can.
After walking for a half an hour or so the path meets
a wide road.
You hear a groaning sound from a nearby field like
someone was being cruelly hurt.
Look for the noise.
Half a dozen fat pigs are grubbing in the muck to
the right.
Just beyond them, a group of creatures huddle around
a fire pit from which there drifts a mouthwatering
smell.
Kare seems to be filled with creatures you can't
place.
Half one thing, half another, but from the way the
strange creatures of the fire pit sit and talk, it
seems they do not see their own differences.
One sees you however, beckoning with a large clawed
hand.
Okay, so we're being beckoned over to the fire.
Oh boy.
All right.
Approach the fire, turn down the road or up at the
next junction.
This is going to dictate I think at least we might
be able to do this, but this is going to be a major
decision here because we're going to go obviously
down and probably down through here or up and then
around here.
Should we should vibe out with the new friends?
Um, yeah, fuck it.
Let's go vibe out with the friends.
You clamber over the fence and stride towards the
creatures.
Within a few paces, the smell of cooking meat reaches
your nostrils and you see a large pig turning on a
spit above the fire.
The creature who waved to you has watched you approach.
He grins hooked teeth and cocks his head at you in
greeting.
Perhaps using magic might give you an advantage.
What do we got?
But I do hold on.
Dud?
I can just be like look at all this treasure I have.
I've got millions of dollars.
Hot cannot become the new Zap.
All right.
Just all right.
Imagine seeing a guy like a cloak.
You're like, hey, come over here.
We've got fresh meat.
Delicious pork.
And you see the guy like kind of waving his arms
around and doing two or three crow hops.
He's like, what's he?
And then he just fucking from the outfield and
centerfield throws baseball.
Like literally at your camp and it's a fireball.
Why would you do that?
Sausage is also available too.
I don't remember.
I forget.
I don't remember this.
Just do jig.
But that's so easy.
And I don't know what it's gonna do.
They have oh because they have weird teeth.
Yeah, that's why.
Are we close enough though?
We might not be close enough.
Are we close enough for jig?
I think you have to be within.
I think they have to be able to hear it.
Why did that guy just pull out a fucking flute?
Yeah, we could just say hi to but I don't have to
be a threat.
I'm gonna greet the creatures greetings.
That smells good.
It is the creature agrees.
We pick the best one to bite into come come here.
Come here.
Sit down and you understand his generosity.
They're poachers pull out your pipe and cast the
spell and begin to play the leader poacher gets
to his feet and to the amusement of his fellows.
He begins to dance dragging up two of his friends soon
the whole encampment is on its feet clapping jumping
and falling about and enjoyment.
In fact your spell quickly wears off but the poachers
continue to enjoy themselves after they tire the
pig is fully roasted the lead poacher claps you on
the back and gestures for you to sit down you take a
place in the circle around the fire the creature shuffle
and shift to make room for you.
Okay, so they that was that that was a great time
to them ask for some pig.
I haven't eaten.
I think I have to eat.
May I share your pig you ask the poachers laugh.
It's not our pig and there's plenty there help yourself.
So they say this is this is this is bad.
This is evil.
This is evil behavior, but I'm going to eat reach
over the fire and pull off a leg of the pig and devour
it the meat is succulent and rich and the best meal
you have had in a long while you thank the poachers
who shrug indifferently asking about curry.
Let's start with this.
I'm new to curry you tell the gathered poachers as
you bite into the pig meat.
What can you tell me about the city the creatures look
between each other entertain entertained by your question.
They suck their teeth and humming her car is the big
place one finally answers full of people pushing each
other for power.
He pulls a leg from the pig making the meat tear
and stretch to demonstrate you want to avoid all them
if you can what about the North Gate?
I won't be staying here long.
I'm headed for the North Gate.
Can you help me find my way the lead poacher looks at
you with interest you're going out into the backlands.
Why go there my business is my own I'm on a quest my
business is my own you reply unwillingly unwillingly
to trust these ruffians lead poacher nods taking no
offense and accepting your answer.
The North Gate is a hard thing to open.
I've never heard of anyone doing it the spell lines
from across the field of woman begins to sing the
poacher smile and clap each other on the back.
Oh sirisi is coming three seat.
You talk to sirisi.
I don't want to talk to anyone who is sirisi audiobook
Andy.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's fine bro.
Who is sirisi?
Sirisi is our treasure sirisi is how we know what we
should do.
You'll see by now the woman has reached the group.
She greets the men with a kiss on either cheek.
You notice she's carrying something carefully in a
cloth the man beside you beckons her to sit down beside
him.
This is our visitor greetings.
What can I help you with?
I need no help help me how I need to open the gate help
me how I need to open the gate tricky very tricky as
she speaks she squats down onto her heels and places
the cloth on the ground unwrapping it slowly.
She reveals an orb of crystal.
Give me that fucking thing and just run.
You're a fortune teller.
All right.
Let we we're gonna have to give it an option here one
or two do I just wipe this thing and then fucking
throw a fireball at the camp and run.
Or do we play do we play the we do we do a little bit
of lawful good here.
This is I don't I could pick either one of these
either one of these is fine for me.
You got to play the long game.
Don't be such a psycho.
This orb of crystal steal the orb of I mean, I don't
know.
Will we have an opportunity to get an orb?
Do we keep talking and do I eventually get what I
want?
I don't know when has sticking around ever been a
good idea.
It usually isn't but you know, it's fun to see the
options chat is lame and smart.
All right.
Well, we're going to okay.
Well, obviously all the all the throw the fireball
of the door chatters of being squished here.
You're a fortune teller.
Cerise sees all one of the poachers calls out for
instance, which fields will be left untended says
another I'll hear my fortune persuade another to
have their fortune told.
Do we hear a fortune or should we have somebody
else do it first?
I'll hear my fortune you declare the men cheer and
you kneel down on the mud across from her.
She holds out a palm cross my palm with silver.
She says, oh no, I want it.
What is that gold?
She's going to know city noble badge.
Will she take it?
I don't know.
Well, these are all these are like poachers guys.
What if she's what if they why are we believing
this by the way, this could just be completely
full of shit.
They're poachers and they're like eating a pig at
a campfire.
What if this lady just doesn't even what if she's
not a fortune teller this gives me some person
that's not a fortune teller.
I'm going to do it.
Gold piece is not this is not going to work.
No way do I there are friends you have to rewind
I'm going to do it off her the city noble badge.
I'm doing it.
I did it.
You remove the nobles badge you found in the
abandoned house and place it into her palm her
eyes widen suddenly she recognizes it for what it
is and looks suddenly to your face with a
searching expression then that expression paces
passes into puzzlement.
How came you buy this?
Are you a noble?
I found it.
I killed a noble.
I am a noble.
This is a fucking lie.
If she's a fortune teller.
She knows that I found it.
I found it.
You told them you're new.
The woman looks into your eyes for a long moment
then nods very well.
It is silver and will do.
She closes her fist and nods.
It's acceptable.
She places her palms on the crystal and begins
to hum watch out for this one.
Sirisi one of the men calls.
He's a sorcerer himself and all it doesn't look
like any fortune-telling spell you have ever
read about wait and watch a minute passes and
then sirisi's eyes flick open.
I see a long journey.
She says to you to a distant land.
I see danger and excitement.
All right.
This is I could get this a Chuck E cheese.
This is nonsense.
This is clearly nonsense.
She's a charlatan her little performance continues.
I see more you must watch or a dagger and a fish
see a road paved with white stone leading to a
place of great sadness.
A blind man who will stab you in the back.
She lifts her palm from the glass and smiles.
Someone gets her some pork to eat offer to read
hers in return.
I'll do yours too.
Let me try reading your fortune.
You declare into the quiet that follows her reading
you will tell everyone else's you always do that.
You must be curious about your own sirisi stops
eating to stare at you.
There's a murmur of excitement from the group.
This is the most unusual you and what do you know
of fortune-telling I doesn't look for I'm a sorcerer.
She raises a thin dark eyebrow in a cool surprise.
Are you you hold out a hand for the crystal orb
not taking her eyes off you.
She puts it in your hand.
Then she sits defiantly down in front of you.
Well, then tell me what you see for poor old sirisi.
She declares her eyes flashing with the challenge.
You take a moment to collect your thoughts.
The orb is pleasingly heavy in your palm.
See, whoa, I could do it.
I can do it.
I can actually do it.
I know the zapper hot is not available.
Hell.
Wait, I could just read her mind.
Dud create treasure and create stink.
Oh what?
Hey, I'll read your fortune.
Let me see your pie.
Pull my finger.
That's that's like what like a fucking drunk uncle does.
You know what I mean?
Like that's what I was about to do that.
I'm not a sorcerer.
What else is there?
I just float in the air.
That'd be stupid.
I can do it.
Should I do it?
Do I read her?
Do I actually see her future or do I do I just read her mind?
All right.
All right, let's do it.
Cast a spell placing your hands on the crystal orb.
Your mind clears and a vision forms, but it is not of Cerise
and her future, but of your own.
You see yourself in a low stone shrine somewhere here in
the city of Kare.
A man in a long white robe stands at your elbow.
He is speaking.
What is the answer to the question that has never been asked?
You see your own mouth opening to reply.
You concentrate as hard as you can struggling to maintain
the vision of Thanos.
Don't stop.
Stop.
We're getting into this here.
We're getting into this.
Kylo Ren.
Come on.
We were getting into this.
We were really engrossed in this and then you had to say
fucking Thanos.
It's thematically accurate too because like what the fuck?
You concentrate as hard as you can struggling to maintain
the vision.
Then as it begins to slip, there is a touch on your hand.
Another presence joins yours.
Cerise.
You breathe.
In your vision, you see the man in the white robe bow his
head, defeated at the word.
The vision fades.
Cerise is watching you intently waiting to hear her
fortune.
The crowd around lean eagerly in.
I see your fortune.
You begin.
I see you losing several friends.
See you telling great fortunes.
That's so dumb.
I see you.
See you losing.
It's definitely one.
I see you losing several friends.
You say and you see her smile slip a little.
Is that all?
She asks.
I see you giving me this orb.
I see you divulging a secret.
You continue.
Cerise looks stunned by your words.
She clearly believes you are a true psychic.
A great and weighty decision seems to pass across her
face.
She looks to you for a moment to confirm it.
Then nods once more and turns to her friends.
Please be quiet.
All of you.
Stranger is right.
I must make a confession.
Why would you slip away at this point?
Wait and watch.
You wait and watch.
I'm not a fortune teller.
Cerise continues sadly.
That's my secret.
What?
The poachers cannot believe their ears.
One denies it.
Another claims to have known all along.
A third who it seems lost a lot of money on a bet once
becomes quite enraged and is held back by two more.
Within a few moments the whole group are rolling around in
the mud enraged in the most almighty punch-up.
Let's get out of here.
Slip away with the orb or we could I mean friends or like
do we just fuck off with the orb?
Pull one or two.
What do you want to do?
Break up the fight and keep talking or get out of here
with the orb.
Neutral Andy.
Hey, I'm making a lot of decisions.
I want to leave some of them up to you too.
It's more fun that way.
The poachers helped you.
They did.
But this is a crystal orb that I can use to read people's
futures.
It's not guaranteed that we're going to keep this.
Maybe they'll give the orb if I break it up and
or maybe I go to break it up and one of them grabs a
battle axe and tries to hit me in the head with it.
I don't know.
I actually don't know.
I don't remember this.
The best part about games like this is there's like thousands
of options that after five to six plus years, it's like
I'm playing the game all over again.
Anyways, it's great.
All right.
What are we doing?
It looks like we're looks like we're going to run away here.
We're going to slip away.
That's called forgetting.
All right, let's get out of here.
Slip away with the orb in the commotion.
It's easy for you to get away until one of the men
shouts, it's all his fault.
Run.
You try to run, but a man the size of a horse dives for
your legs and a moment later you're down in the mud in
the middle of the bruise up of your life.
You crawl out from under a pile of 15 men.
Wait, where did these other people come from?
Where did these other people come from?
You find the precious orb has shattered to a million
fragments and several of those fragments have cut you
in the leg inside.
You what?
You limp back to the road.
What?
No, where are these other who are these 15 men that
showed up?
Why would there were three of what they're like three
people here.
They were literally three people sitting at this fire.
Why they have 15 people here now.
They were just grabbing people off the road and
punching them.
It's rewind time.
Is it?
I don't it's his fault.
It's like I just I pictured it.
There he is.
It's him and I turn it.
I don't know why I'm just seeing this image in my
head of like I've got a bunch of food in my mouth and
I've got a big bag.
You don't need a big bag of food and I'm stealing
the food and I've got my cheeks to puffed out like
a hamster right like me.
I don't know why that's what I see.
I only get two rewinds.
I don't know.
I think we have to live with it because I don't I
don't want to waste a rewind because what if I'd
messed it up all the way through and it's probably
okay, there's like probably three or four different
ways to get that orb.
What if we pass that point shit?
You go away with the orb and get tackled by the
get tackled by the safety, you know, that was in
the back apparently.
All right.
I'm going to use it.
We're going to rewind.
I only get one more.
Okay, so we're going to we're going to do everything
the same way I did before.
It was gig.
What should I say?
Fuck it.
Just throw a fireball.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're going to break him up.
But what if it doesn't work?
What if it doesn't work?
It was greet them.
Oh, greetings.
That smells good.
It is.
Okay.
All right.
So I don't need to, I don't need to waste any
spell.
I can just sit down.
I'm just gonna sit down.
Just cause mayhem immediately.
Just do everything the same way.
Okay.
Just retrace the steps.
All right.
Everyone's having a good time.
Ask for some food.
Yes, take some.
That was delicious.
All right.
Ask about the gate.
Hey, why you want to go there?
That's my business.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Um, okay.
Uh, wait, what?
Did I change?
What happened?
I just, did I do something wrong?
The North Gate is a hard thing to open.
The spell lines.
He nods.
Okay.
Did I do this already?
What?
Who could I ask about the lines?
Ask him about Kari.
I'm new to Kari.
Okay.
All right.
We're good.
Who is Cerise?
Oh, here she comes.
Okay.
Help me how?
I need to open the North Gate.
Right?
That's correct.
Oh, tricky.
That's very tricky.
Oh, you're, you're a fortune teller.
Yes.
Okay.
Let me hear my fortune.
All right.
And then of course we had kind of run.
Okay.
Take the badge.
Yep.
Okay.
I found it.
Should I change my answer?
Should I change my answer here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
But what if I say something different?
What the fuck was that?
Okay.
I got like chills for a second.
Like, you know, uh, chills and I was laughing right when I was weird.
All right.
I found it.
It'll work.
Wait and watch.
See a long journey.
I said, this is nonsense.
She's a charlatan.
All right.
Let me read yours in return.
I am a sorcerer.
Really?
Okay.
Let's go.
Read her mind.
No, I have to do it the same way.
I can't do it.
Oh, I can't change it.
I'm okay.
You can't.
I could have done hot and run.
All right.
Here we go.
Keep listening.
Cerise.
Yes.
You breathe in your vision.
I see your fortune.
Yes.
I see you losing several friends.
Okay.
Wait.
You have a secret to do.
Don't divulge to the secret.
She.
Okay.
This is what causes the brawl.
If I just say, I see you giving me this orb.
Right.
Because this is, she goes, I have a secret.
I'm not a real fortune teller.
And then people start punching each other in the face.
And then 15 people start fighting on the road.
Should I do that?
She won't give it to you.
Do we know that though?
She won't believe you.
I see you divulging a secret.
Okay.
But I don't have the orb.
All right.
I must make a confession.
Wait and watch.
All right.
People are fighting.
People are fighting each other.
I'm going to break them up.
All right.
Break it up.
It's a messy fight.
You weighed in trying to hold the poachers apart and keep the men from throwing each other into the fire.
There's nothing you can do to keep them apart.
A moment later, someone snatches the orb from your hands and cracks it over another man's head.
You crawl up under a pile of bodies and hurry back up to safety.
I fucked it up halfway through.
I have to tell her to give me the orb.
I have to tell her to give...
I just got like snow globed in the head.
Okay.
I have to go back and say give me the orb.
I'm going back.
I want this fucking orb.
And I'm going to say I see you give...
When she tells the secret, everybody starts fighting each other.
I'm going back.
I swear to God, last try.
Hold on.
I just want to see what happens.
You cast your spell building an enormous fireball in your palm doing three or four crow hops, which you'll hurl at the roasting pig.
The fire pit explodes in a wide shower of sparks that knocks the poachers onto their back.
The pig is charred to a black hulk and the fire turns to ash.
The poachers are furious.
But more than that, they are terrified.
They quickly scatter, leaving nothing behind.
Capture a pig for myself.
You waste another half hour scurrying around the fields trying to catch a pig to eat on your own.
But without help, it's impossible.
And the pigs, though fat, are quite nimble enough to avoid you.
Eventually, mud soaked and hungrier than ever, you give up.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go for real.
For real.
I promise.
I need to get this fucking orb.
Hello.
Greetings.
That smells good.
Excellent.
Would anyone care to dance?
Okay.
Excellent.
Can I have some of that pig?
Mm.
Delicious.
What do you know about Kare?
Kare?
Yeah.
Why do you?
What's the North Gate?
Oh, well, somebody, yeah.
What are you doing here?
It's my business.
Okay.
Who is this lady?
I don't know.
Who is that?
Can I help you?
I want to open the gate.
Oh, that's very tricky.
I could read your fortune.
You could?
Tell me.
Are you really a fortune teller?
I'd like to hear my fortune.
Oh, sit with me.
Sit with me.
Oh, I need something silver.
Here.
Take that.
Oh, ow.
Where'd you get this?
Found it.
Oh, really?
Hmm.
Well, it seems like you are...
Oh, you're...
You're a charlatan.
You're a stupid charlatan.
I hate you.
Let me read yours.
You fucking moron.
Oh, what a...
Are you sure you can do that spell?
Yes.
Oh.
Okay, do it.
Placing the skullcap on your head, you cast the spell.
You begin to hear Cerise's thoughts.
Who is this idiot?
Is he really a magician?
What if he tells the others that my powers are all false?
Her expression is a fixed smile.
Oh, so you could get around it.
Okay.
So, I see your fortune.
Now, I see you losing several friends.
You missed a fucking clue.
What?
Why did you tell me to do that spell?
What are you talking about?
You're missing an important clu...
Give me this orb!
I see you giving me this orb, you continue.
Then you remove the skullcap.
The spell is finished.
Cerise looks stunned by your words.
She clearly believes you're a psychic.
A great and weighty decision seems to pass across her face.
She looks to you for a moment.
Please be quiet.
Wait and watch.
Fuck, I can't take the orb.
I can't get it.
And I lost the clue.
There has to be a way I can get it.
There has to be.
They wouldn't give you the option if there wasn't a way to do it.
Flip away with the orb.
It's all his fault.
Oh, fuck.
Whatever.
Fuck this.
You know what?
I'm taking the orb.
Such an orb is a hugely powerful artifact.
If you could possess it, then all sorts of secrets might be yours.
Not the least of spell lines for the North Gate.
Grab it and fucking run.
Orb, wait for an opportunity.
Wait for an opportunity.
No clue?
Oh, whatever.
What was the clue anyways?
Who cares?
I...
I'm not gonna get away with it.
Wait for an opportunity.
There are several of them and only one of you.
You'll have to pick your moment carefully.
Okay, wait.
I'll hear my fortune.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Take the...
Take the badge.
Okay, I found it.
Wait and watch.
This is nonsense.
Here we go.
Hold on.
Create a distraction.
She lifts her palm from the glass and smiles.
Someone gets her some pork to eat.
This is where I can get the orb.
Or...
Get the clue.
What do you think?
Is the clue more important than the orb?
Distraction.
If you wish to steal the orb, you realize you will need to create a distraction.
Kick over the fire.
Hold my sword to Cerise's throat.
Point into the distance and shout.
Or...
See...
Oh, we don't have it.
Dud.
Illusion of treasure.
Dose.
Cause slowness.
It could be...
It's probably that.
Fog.
Summon darkness.
Create a force field.
We don't have...
We can't do the smell.
Fog.
Dud might work really well.
They're poachers, right?
If I put like treasure chests all over the place,
they're all going to be like, holy shit.
You cast the spell, summoning a pile of treasure from the mud.
The poachers' eyes grow wide in amazement.
And they begin to stuff their pockets.
Some are faster than others, but then the losers turn on their friends,
pulling knives, robbing them for their takings.
Within minutes, an almighty fight is waging over your imaginary gold.
In the fight, someone kicks the crystal orb and it strikes the brazier and shatters into a hundred thousand pieces.
A hundred thousand pieces?
Fuck!
A hundred thousand pieces, dude.
All right, what?
A fog?
I want this fucking thing.
I don't care.
I don't think I've ever had this orb at any playthrough.
I don't think I've ever had this before.
I know I'm throwing a bunch of rewinds.
But still, come on, man.
I want this thing so bad.
I can see the future.
If I can...
Okay, imagine being able to read the future for like a manticore.
That's hilarious.
I'm going to do it.
Did I have this last time?
I don't remember having this.
Okay.
Wait for an opportunity.
This is it.
I'll hear my fortune.
Here you go.
Here's the badge.
Okay.
I found this badge.
Wow, interesting.
Wait and watch.
Here we go.
This is nonsense.
You're a charlatan.
Distraction.
Okay.
Will this work?
Point and shout is so funny.
Darkness.
Horse field.
Spoiler in mod chat if you want it.
Wait, what?
Don't tell him.
Don't look.
What do you mean don't look?
Slowness?
Slowness or darkness?
I think would be perfect.
Okay.
I'm going to say I'm going to say darkness, right?
Slow.
Slowness.
You cast a spell slowing Cerise in particular down.
You reach over and snatch the orb.
Success!
Cerise gives a slow motion cry like the groaning of a skunk bear.
The men look back and see you orb in hand.
The fist that catches you in the jaw is sudden unexpected and
extremely powerful.
The orb flies out of your hand and smashes into a million pieces
against the brazier.
A million this time.
You run for your life chased by men with pokers.
A million, huh?
A fucking million this time.
I'm reading spoiler.
Oh my fucking God.
Okay, that's oh my God.
I'm actually mad.
I'm mad.
I'm going to rewind.
You cannot get the orb from them right now.
If I can't as I've I can't get it right now.
I've literally it's impossible.
Okay.
So I may have I may have done things incorrectly going coming
forward without items correctly to do this where I can't get
it right now with my current items and stuff.
So we're going to get the clue that sucks.
Okay, I'm going to get the clue ask for some pig take some
pig.
That's so funny.
It smashes to a million faces.
That's hilarious.
Okay, my business is my own.
So I'm going to keep the badge then she's a fraud.
We look at I'm not going to rewind this many times.
I promise ever again.
I just really wanted the orb so bad.
You're a fortune teller.
I'll hear my fortune and I'm going to offer her gold piece.
I'm not going to leave the city's the Nobles badge.
I'm keeping there are people that still are debating on the
Wiki for this game on whether it's possible.
What that's so funny.
Okay, I have nothing to give you.
Should I say that instead I did it.
It's actually possible.
Okay, whatever offer her gold piece you withdraw gold piece
from your purse and place it in her palm.
Perhaps this will do you say she shakes her head and laughs
silver is silver and gold is gold.
I'm sorry, but magic is as magic is because somebody lend me
something perhaps someone can lend me something.
Poachers look around and begin to laugh.
It seems they think that your suggestion is a joke picking
up her orb Cerise moves over to one of the other men who
hands her what looks like a silver tooth and then sits down
to hear his fortune.
She places her palms on the crystal and begins to hum doesn't
look like any fortune-telling spell you've ever heard about
a minute passes then Cerise's eyes flick open.
I see a long journey to a distant land.
I see danger.
Wait, this is nonsense.
She's a charlatan.
Oh, I actually didn't she's doing the same routine.
I oh my god.
Imagine if we did.
Okay.
Imagine if I actually didn't give a shit and we just moved
on I would have been asking you guys about this for the
next like three hours a blind man.
Hey, this guy's a blind man.
He's going to stab us in the back.
I'll read your fortune.
I'm a sorcerer.
Okay, so now I'm going to cast the spell we get the clue.
I get to keep the badge.
What are the what else can you do here?
Okay, here we go.
What is the answer to the question that has never been
asked?
Cerise you breathe in your vision.
I see your fortune.
I see you losing several.
I see you.
There's none of this matters.
I see you telling great fortunes.
Is that all?
I see you divulging a secret.
Wow.
I'm fucking out of here by you make to slip away.
I have told great fortunes good ones Cerise continues sadly
but not true ones.
The poachers cannot believe their ears one denies it another
claim.
Yeah, that was okay.
Yeah, it doesn't matter that there is run for it.
It smashes, but I got the clue.
That's all that matters.
All right.
So yeah, I lost for stamina for this whole fucking ordeal.
What was the clue?
Anyways in a vision you saw the answer to the question that
has never been asked Cerise interesting interesting
interesting where we go and get a poll in the chat room
right now.
Are we going up or we going down show you what's up back
up this way towards Mansion Row and up to the artist quarter
potentially dwarf town or down downhill over here to this
farmstead and potentially the festival of thieves.
Where are we going?
That's not one of the people is still debating on whether
you can get this or not in like 40 years.
This crow is pissing me off.
Sorry.
Up up down down down up up down down.
Oh shit.
I got where my where to go.
Hey, hey, all right up or down up or down a pole is already
active.
Oh, I think a lot of people I use you.
Everyone's looking at dwarf town.
They're going.
Oh, he's gonna go to dwarf town.
All you you know, you all you jokers.
It's definitely it's it's unanimous going up uphill.
Let's continue our class the road climbs between high
fences and then into open fields a little further on you
see another rock face as Kare climbs another level or the
top of this one is a line of grand houses with ornamental
roofs and pillared colonnades.
This is where the richer creatures of Kare live looking
down across the field day on you can imagine them sipping
iron wine on their balconies and watching the toil of the
farm workers through a spyglass.
But the more you look the more you realize something is
wrong.
A tree grows from one roof another has slipped sideways
into the yard of the neighboring house.
These places are falling into ruin you knew Kare was poor
but this is worse than you'd ever heard a junction the road
carries on rising very slightly through thin and meager
fields scarecrows made from skeletons hang from posts on
either side their bones rattling in the breeze.
There is no one about with the hottest part of the day
approaching you reach a crossroads of sorts to the right
of the main road a track lined with colored flags leads along
the line of a cliff short distance from the road is a small
hut built from mud bricks smoke rises from the chimney
and a thick rich smell wafts from its door.
If it is a shop it can't catch they can't have much to
trade stuck out here in the middle of the fields.
Oh well, well one two or three one two or three one is
just take the main road up through into the artist's
quarter who is to enter the small hut which I think we
can do anyways, but we may lose the opportunity to go this
way.
I'm not sure one two or three main road and solidify that
we can actually go that way go into the hut and you know
do whatever is going to happen in here or add to the flags
heading down towards what I'm imagining.
This is probably the others in the festival thieves down
here or maybe not, but I you know, obviously going to give
you the opportunity because who knows if we can do this
after we do one of these there's no way to tell one two
three is it right gang or left gang?
Um, why do you have the stream muted?
That's my question.
This whole thing has been me like reading an audiobook immediately
after you said dwarf town and had did a creepy laugh.
My computer blue-screened.
Well, that's I'm sorry going in the hut the door to the
small hut is a little ajar a pleasant smell it drifts out
but you hear nothing from inside.
Let's knock.
Okay.
Hello, you knock firmly on the door a voice calls back enter
friend, but be careful as you open the door.
I don't get a shit just shove it open shove the door open.
What is going on in here?
Okay, you give the door quick shove and something a jar of
some liquid drops from the door frame and smashes on the
floor.
There it is.
How well the shop is a kitchen.
There is a fire in the great with a pot above it which
bubbles and smokes on the walls hang herbs vegetables meats
and cooking equipment.
But no matter how hard you look you cannot seem to see the
speaker right here, right or is that I don't understand look
under the table look near the hearth I'm gonna look at the
hearth looking again.
You suddenly notice the strange looking creature standing
beside the pot.
Wait, hold on.
He has a human torso, but his head is nothing but a green
colored jelly.
He's hard to spot because of the vegetables hanging on the
wall behind him, but you can tell he's the chef as the long
sinuous tentacles come from his head are scooping with
ladles stirring with spoons waving salt shakers and
brandishing a cleaver.
What do you want?
Ask the creature get over here.
Look around more closely talk to the creature be nice be
nice be nice greetings creature.
I don't have all day.
What do you want?
The creature complains its tentacles go back to stirring
chopping and mixing.
This is a robbery.
I'd like to buy some food.
We actually might be able to get away with it.
I mean look this is just one hut out in the middle of
nowhere.
This is a robbery.
I mean I could probably kick this guy's ass.
He's pretty rude to by the way.
What do you want?
Oh greetings.
Look I don't have all day.
Be a viewer a little more cordial be nice be nice.
I have 24 gold.
Yeah.
Do I want to all right?
Okay.
I'd like to buy no I didn't mean to do that.
No fuck.
I don't I barged I barged right in you step through the
doorframe something falls on your head with a crack and
an oily liquid begins to ooze down the side of your
face.
I barged in last time wipe it off.
You lift a hand to your head to wipe the liquid away,
but as you do you feel tops of your hair coming out of
your palm what from across the hut of voice.
So if you're right intruder you should have been more
cautious, but I was wondering where I left that
potion of baldness reaching up.
You realize it's true.
Your head is now a bald scalp and even your eyebrows
have come off.
You laugh and so does the creature on the other side
of the room is a strange looking thing.
The creature has a human torso and his head is nothing
but a green jelly or whatever.
All right.
Talk to the creature.
Okay.
I'd like to buy some food.
All right.
It's five gold pieces and it's bristlebeast kidneys.
Hope that's all right with you giving his cauldron a
quick stir, but never taking his eyes off you only
one piece of food pay him attack him.
That's too much.
I mean, I'm I that's too much right, but sometimes
bartering doesn't work.
Sometimes I'm just going to pay him because a lot of
times they'll go fine leave and I'm not rewinding for
bullshit reasons anymore.
I'm paying you pay him the money and he hands you a
bowl of stew doesn't taste very nice, but you force a
smile the creature nods and offers you a drink to
help wash it down spill it to create a distraction.
Try drink this this guy's got weird potions everywhere
game really wants you to rob this guy.
Yeah, why drink it you drink it down.
It's actually quite refreshing with you meal finished.
There's not much more to be done.
You're hunger satisfied.
You thank the cleaning creature and leave the hut.
Okay, I don't know what happens if you attack him
or rob him.
All right one or two.
I have bald head now.
Whatever I'll zoom out.
You can see the potential route that you'll be taking
what happens it is that you're a mean person.
I mean, I'm not a mean person.
I'm I'm I'm an adventurer.
We'd make our decisions on the fly as they happen to
is to come down to the festival thieves and whatever
is up here.
Whatever this is one is to head up towards the artist
quarter and Dwarftown bald, you know, it's really funny.
The game is going to remember that and there's going
to be tons of lines through the rest of the game that
say it really grazes over your bald head.
That's going to be there now forever or whatever.
Oh, you feel the breeze on your bare scalp.
We're going to read shit like that every 10 minutes
now.
All right.
This is a major decision.
Which way we going one?
Okay, not by a lot up through Mansion Row artist
quarter Dwarftown.
You follow the road up a slight rise and then down
into a hollow at the very bottom as a solitary thatched
hut the curious wispy statue outside in the distance
the road rises once more was a large building with
a domed roof.
Examine the statue examine the hut make a move cast
a spell.
Sauce is a good option here magic protection.
Obviously is the thing here.
Huff wind is also this is a hot is also Goblin.
Huh?
I could just send I got a lot of teeth.
This doesn't take any stamina.
Go toss down a Goblin's tooth and cast your spell.
There's a thin wisp of smoke and then a column of
fire and then from the flames a Goblin warrior
emerges to give you a jaunty salute.
He looks about for someone to fight but sees no
immediate threat send him in the hut sent into the
statue send him over to the statue you direct him
over to the statue.
He approaches casually and then quite suddenly the
statue moves its arms slicing through the air one
cutting through the Goblin at head height the next
at knee level the poor creature drops to the ground
in three pieces a moment later it vanishes in a
plume of smoke and when the smoke has disappeared
you see nothing but the statue standing just as
before.
Did you imagine it moving?
Holy shit.
Oh poor guy.
Okay.
Well,
this is gonna cut me in three pieces.
I'll just do it but what if it kills me I get a
free rewind.
The statue depicts a man of sorts with long and
spiny limbs sharp edged and cruel its hands are
pressed together before its body as though in
prayer to one of Kare's many gods around its neck
hangs a locket of what looks like solid gold.
Okay examine the hut the hut behind was thrown up
in a hurry its walls are patched with mud and clay
and the door is made from torn up fish crates the
planks still bearing the marks of the ships that
brought them in the statue suggests this could be
a shrine but you do not recognize the deity.
I mean he got cut into three pieces free rewind
they're all free now feels weird man.
Oh no one out pizzas the hut talking about stuff
crust pizza that is you approach the statue curiously
up close.
It's even more ugly.
The limbs are as thin as sticks but as sharp as
sword blades.
The only beautiful thing about is the gold locket
that hangs around its neck.
You hang back for a moment to watch the statue.
That's when you see the statue blink.
That's terrifying.
Keep watching you stand transfixed waiting to see
if the statue will move again to be sure it was not
your imagination.
It blinks again and then the arms move one sword
like edge sharpening itself against the other.
We just watched this cut our friend into three pieces.
Yep.
Talk with animals.
Oh shit, but is this the offer?
It's like a Resident Evil game guys.
I don't shoot the rocket launcher until the last
right before the credits roll.
Daph is available.
Shield is available kid create an illusion summon
a replica creature.
Ah speed speeds probably at one of the ways to get
it.
I don't know if his app is going to do anything.
I don't know.
It's probably walk create a shield.
Can I maybe I can block it.
I hold the shield up with it boom.
I'm going for it.
Oh my goodness.
You place a gold piece on your wrist and cast your
spell creating a shield.
You ready blade the creature is not strong, but
it's blade like arms are quite deadly.
You would do well to avoid even a single blow.
All right, we're going full blaster.
The statue slashes its razor blade arms through the
air.
It tries to scratch you.
You raise your sword and aim to carve the thing in
two.
You land a simple blow creatures losing its spines,
but it keeps coming the mantis man's long spines
stretch.
I have to defend her.
Yep.
Ow.
Oh my God.
That hurts.
That's with defending that's with a shield and
defending by the way raising your shield to
protect your body as much as possible.
The mantis man dashes forward bounding across the
dirt.
You fall over yourself trying to escape its reach.
Okay, you aim a blow for its bug eyes as the mantis
man eyes turn briefly dark at Francis Ford.
Can I do it?
Yeah, I don't think I don't think I can do it.
I can and then again full blast it jumps towards
you full blast.
Got it.
We're good.
Your sword cleaves piece after piece from the
creature's side.
You slice for the statue.
You hear that that was like then your blade lands
deep.
You cut again twist and the mantis man collapses
into dirt.
With the mantis man defeated the street falls quiet
once more.
What do we got with the danger past you go over to
the creature and search it quickly.
The only thing of interest is the locket.
You saw around its neck which turns out to be a
Sun Jewel.
You pocket it time to get away from this place.
Hold on.
I think I can the spell may only be cast upon the
yellow Sun Jewel once cast the Jewel will glow
either brilliantly to dazzle attacking creatures
or just light enough to act as a torch.
Interesting.
So it's a flashlight.
That's cool.
You know how many times it's just complete pitch
black and I can't see anything.
All right, we're going to go in this hut because I
want to.
Yeah, it's fucking starlight kid.
Come on.
You step inside the shadowy hut.
The first thing you notice is the smell thick and
bloody like a butcher shop.
Second thing is something that you kick that rattles
away across the floor and arm bone.
Reborn you pick up the bone.
It is human.
All right, and there are teeth marks.
I think I get you call out here.
Do you search through the bones you pick through a
few more bones male female child a few different
creatures not many but all mixed up in one corner.
You find a number of knuckle bones that have been
strung together into a morbid bracelet.
Take it you take the bracelet and put it on trying
not to imagine that a skeletal hand is gripping
your arm a little sickly light trickles in through
the windows.
What's that?
What I just get bracelet of bone.
That's another one.
What's that do?
Oh shit right here.
Well wearing a bracelet of bone castor of the spell
can concentrate on a particular illusion.
This illusion will become real to others.
However, affected creatures must be intelligent
and the caster must not act counter to the illusion
so I can pretend to be somebody else.
That's cool.
That's two new spells back to back.
Let's go.
I probably should be careful here because I'm going
to call out who's there.
I'm armed.
There's no reply the Hutta at least appears to be
empty shadow falls across the doorway of the hut
just for a moment.
You search you look around the other corners of
the hut.
There are a few piles of ragged clothing presumably
torn from the victims bodies.
Yikes that acting what what I called out as if I
was back home from school.
Hey mom, I'm back home from school.
I feel like I need to get out of here.
Search clothes digging through the pile of clothes.
You unearth five gold pieces.
What this place is disgusting.
You turn and get out.
Oh my God.
I got everything.
Did I do that in the right order?
You step outside the hut onto the street grateful
for the relatively fresh air.
All right, let's keep going.
I need to sleep.
It's getting there.
Yeah, the road leaves the fields heading back
between buildings once more to the left.
A short track leads away and you hear distant
sounds of chanting a squat building at the end
of the track sits in a patch of neatly tiled
field.
You make out a few figures in bright orange robes
working outside all the track the domed building
one to one to big domed building or people in
what was it to say aren't orange robes people
and bright orange robes working outside.
We want to go I imagine this is probably going
to take us through here and maybe up this way
one.
Wait, what did I say was one in one of the mods
helped me.
What did I just say was one and two one was the
dome.
Wait, I don't remember going over here.
The short track ends in a low building surrounded
by figures in long robes.
They are monks a few work the fields around the
building while others sit in contemplation
of the sky the wrinkles on their hands or the
soles of their feet one monk greets you with a
nod of his head.
You step past him to enter the monastery but the
monk reaches out and takes your arm.
You are forbidden my apologies, but strangers are
not allowed inside my apologies.
Let go of me.
I go where I please my apologies.
You reply bowing your head the monk smiles.
Welcome to our humble monastery and puts his
palms together and nods friend sit down beside
me and we will talk the monk pulls out a set of
knuckle bones and lays them on the bench
swindle stone.
Did I play or ask for help?
Let's play swindle stones.
The monk nods a game.
I have contemplated for a long time within these
walls.
He indicates the knuckle bones eagerly.
What's the steak the monk smiles.
I am a monk in case you did not notice I offer
nothing and ask nothing.
I only play for money.
All right.
The monk hands you your dice and waves at you to
bid all the day.
Let me see.
Let's start with 114.
Maybe you could help me.
I'm traveling to the North Gate.
Ah, so you seek the four spell lines to unlock
the gate.
Can you tell me any of the lines to ones?
Okay.
That means he has to have two ones.
I'm going to say three ones to find the lines.
You must find the nobles and that will be difficult.
Dude.
Yeah, you call this.
I will manage.
Holy shit.
He almost had four ones.
If I had even had one one that would have been
bad.
Okay, if you are truly determined to find the
spell lines for the gate.
There was one other route you could try other than
finding the nobles.
You mean a one two.
I have a two.
Let's go tutus.
Not someone exactly but there are other forces
with knowledge to fours.
Okay, hold on.
He has three.
So he might have a really one of the nobles Lord
Mulas was a follower of the gods slang.
If you visit his priest, perhaps the God will know
is only one problem.
Where's the priest of slang or fours?
I could call it but that means but if he has to
he might have to I could call it.
This is dangerous though, because if he had I don't
think so.
I'll call it.
That means he has to have to and he didn't good.
Let me see.
All right.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Well, um, so I just go right for it and just try
to get him to call.
I think there are four twos, right?
This is stupid, right?
I could just get him to call.
No.
Yeah, no way.
Oh, yeah, really?
What do we got?
I got four twos buddy.
Both hands just fucking went through the desk.
Let me see.
I think we got everything we needed out of this guy.
All right.
So he has one one die left.
One one.
All right.
I think there are two ones three ones.
Well, it's literally impossible.
I win.
I get all your money.
You flick the monk's final die off the table with a
grin.
I win.
You tell him do you have time to play again?
The monk asks he glances at the workers in the field
as he asks and play again.
Should I play again more?
Okay, another game.
You agree.
All right.
Do I get more info?
Let's begin at one two ones.
Let's start it off.
Our orders follow the goddess of chance and fortune.
Bro, you have do you have three of those?
Who's that?
The or the goddess of chance and fortune?
No, that's that's not the only way you have three.
Oh, you got to be shitting me.
All right.
Whatever.
Fuck you.
This is the most elegant game.
Is it not?
One four two ones three ones.
All right.
You deaf.
You don't have three ones.
No way.
Got it.
Okay, let's begin.
I'm gonna be a fucking weirdo.
Ready?
Watch this.
Two two twos three twos.
I'm not reading the text shit.
I'm not reading the text.
I'm too busy playing the game.
What do you say?
What do you say something important?
So you are new to our city.
I arrived yesterday.
Okay to let's be honest two threes.
Really?
You're gonna call me on that because I did what I did last game.
Well, that was stupid.
Scroll up.
I will.
He only has one.
I say let's just start here.
Like oh yeah, I got this one four two fours.
Really?
That would be interesting considering.
I don't have any fucking dummy one more the monk suggest.
I'm learning a great deal.
Really?
Am I gonna beat you three times?
All right.
What did he say?
See?
Wait, here we go.
Here we go.
Where's the priest the priest of slang?
The shrine is just before the docks down the middle lane from the well,
but it's not open to strangers all evening.
You must reach it before nightfall middle.
Okay down the middle lane from the well.
Okay, you're new.
You've learned our little game very quickly.
Let's begin.
Here's a bit.
Okay.
All right.
One more one more one more one more.
Fine.
Let's do again.
Okay, to right.
Should I go for the call?
Just do it right off the bat three three fours right off the bat.
Call it.
Thank you.
Any more info?
No, not yet.
I wonder if I've been in three times what happens to twos.
Really?
How about three twos?
Why would you call that?
Wait, was he lying to me?
Yes, I have one too you.
Why would you do that?
What?
I got him again.
He only has two die.
All right.
How about two ones?
Two.
Okay.
I got two of those.
He must have at least one.
Four.
All right.
Dude, come on.
Does he have a double?
That means he has to have a double.
I'm gonna call it.
What a punk.
Okay.
Two.
You only have one.
So two fours.
I have two.
Okay.
Unless he wants...
Should I just call him?
No.
All right.
Dude, I have so many.
Three.
Just call him right now.
No, dude.
That would be accurate.
Four.
But he definitely has that.
I got screwed.
This hand screwed me here.
What?
Okay, I'm gonna call.
What if he doesn't even have that?
That's fine.
The guy won one round.
He's got one die.
I'm fine.
This guy literally has one hand out of like 15 we've played.
This guy's screwed.
Two threes.
Bullshit.
No, that's not what he has.
That's bullshit.
Bullshit.
You don't have a three.
What the fuck?
Maybe one three.
How about one five?
Well, one four.
Two.
Hey, see ya.
Sit down.
I win.
Yes.
The monk nods sagely.
The other brothers are returning to the monastery.
I must go in, he says.
It is time for our midday considerations.
You have been a truly formidable opponent.
As he stands, he grasps your hands between his and mutters a blessing.
You feel a tremendous wellness flooding through your body.
Thanking him, you head back to the main road once more.
All right.
Got two clues.
That works.
Only one way to go and it's this way.
18 HP.
Holy shit.
That works.
That's a big deal.
Road leads directly into one side of a large dome building.
It's some kind of sprawling covered market.
Looking left and right.
You see several other roads entering the building through different archways.
A group of serpent heads are just passing by.
Okay, talk to them.
You stop one.
Greetings.
What is this place?
The serpent head looks back at you, unimpressed.
It's the artist's quarter.
They have to have a roof over them.
Or their paints run and they complain.
Nothing worse than a complaining artist.
Remarks the second creature.
Sounds worthless.
Sounds worthless, you reply.
One of the serpent heads, a female, makes a harrumping noise.
Make fun of my son's lisp, would you?
She asks.
Then with one hooked fin smacks you about the head.
The rest of the group turn their nostrils and march inside the market.
Intriguing sounds drift from inside.
Oh, fuck.
But that was a...
I thought they were, but they're...
Whatever.
What an asshole.
I, uh, what, it's like, I don't...
Shit, dude.
Sorry.
The market is a maze of alleys.
Every inch of space is being used for trade.
With shops, stalls, and piles of goods set out on crates and barrels.
Talkers bellow about their wares, each trying to shout down the next.
People and all manner of strange creatures mill about.
Most are probably pickpockets.
Very few seem to be buying anything.
Into the crowd, you've lost health.
You lose yourself browsing the stands.
Most sell carpets.
But some also offer incense burners, lanterns, and pottery.
You can't see any blacksmiths or food stalls, however.
Okay.
You go.
You move on through the market, elbowing your way between shoppers and hawkers.
To stand below the enormous glass dome.
Through the hubbub of passersby, you spot the exit across the hall.
Noise rolls like thunder around the roof of the market.
Okay.
Back down the market.
The far end.
I could go into the market area, or I could leave.
I could probably do both.
So we're gonna go down this way first.
Alright.
You walk to the furthest end of the market.
On your left, a man grabs your sleeve.
You want to buy a carpet?
He asks.
Find his carpets this side of the backlands.
Made from real moths.
Look at the carpets.
Behind the man is a towering stack.
30 or 40 carpets high.
Each one is gray.
And so dusty that they make you want to sneeze.
A fight has broken out in one corner of the market.
It is quickly settled by a score of passersby.
Moth carpet.
Hog.
Very good carpet, the man assures you.
How large you want?
Size of a bed?
Size of a room?
Size of a palace garden?
I give you same price.
He drags out a carpet to show you.
Look at the carpet.
Show me your very best carpet.
I don't want a carpet.
Throw a fucking fireball at him.
Great wind.
There's all the sus.
There is tell.
I can read his mind.
There's cause a stench.
I can summon the giant.
I feel like that would be such a waste.
God, I need to use the Resident Evil rocket launcher already.
Do it.
Yawb, please.
Just do yawb and rewind.
Is that do I get a free rewind here?
Yawb, I'm doing it.
Fuck it.
You toss down one of your giant's teeth and cast your spell.
It burst into smoke, which makes the carpet seller panic
and rush for a bucket of sand.
But instead of a fire, the smoke turns into a giant
who fills the small shop and then quickly burst through the roof
as it stretches to its full height.
The carpet seller yells in terror and rushes out through one of the
collapsed walls closely followed two gnomes who had been hiding behind
the stack of carpets.
Send the giant after them.
Tell the giant to move the carpet.
Tell the giant to move the carpets.
You set the giant to tidying up the piles of carpets
and discover a pair of nose plugs
and a small bag containing six gold pieces in the process.
You pocket them.
Just as the giant disappears once more and you stride back.
I can do the stink spell now.
But our giant friend, all he did was just scare everybody.
Is it worth?
It's probably worth.
I got a new spell.
We traded.
Is it worth trading the giant for a smelly smell?
I don't know.
You traded a rocket launcher for an air horn.
You summoned the giant for carpets, but not the manticore.
I know, but we got a money and
I'm going to live with it.
I'm going to keep it.
That's my
that's what I just that's what I'm deciding.
The market seems to be endless.
You're quite sure you've seen the same 12 creatures walking
around in his circles.
Now, okay below the dome waste of a giant.
I just destroyed his stall and then stole nose plugs.
It's all right though.
You return to the middle of the market below the dome looking
to one side.
You spot a small artist studio sign above.
It says find yourself in here.
The artist sits outside you a feeling.
There is something strange about him, but you cannot work
out immediately what it is.
Please go back.
Hey, I have to I can't just rewind every thing.
I have I can't just rewind every single thing, right?
I have to live with some decision free rewind.
The fart spell is good.
I'm begging you.
No, no, no, I can't I can't I can't.
You were supposed to rewind that but it was funny and I
want to keep the spell because I want to keep the stinky spell.
You rewind 15 times for an orb.
That's not true.
I didn't get an orb in my inventory after that.
I was desperately trying to get the orb in my inventory
and I didn't get it.
All right.
I'm going to run a poll.
Here's the poll.
This has to be at least 70%
re keep giant.
Yes or no and I go back.
It's got to be at least 70% keep giant.
Yes or no.
This got to be 70% at least.
I don't think it's going to get there.
Lot of people don't want to rewind.
I think you guys understand.
Oh fuck.
Wait, keep giant is winning.
Oh God, whatever keep giant is a rewind.
This is confusing.
No keep.
All right.
Hold on.
If you misunderstand it.
Let me do another one hole.
It's a misunderstanding.
It was too complicated raising.
What do you mean?
All right.
Everybody relax rewind to keep giant.
There you go.
Yes or no, it's very simple.
What do you mean phrasing?
This is exactly what's going on here.
I don't I don't know how people are confused by this.
That how this is not confusing this.
Do you want me to rewind?
Do you want me to keep like that?
I have to do you want me to rewind to keep the giant?
That's there's nothing confusing about this.
Hey, he's stinkers.
Oh, it's close.
Oh, it's going to come down to the last second.
Oh, fine.
Wait, what you said 70 you said?
Oh, whoops.
All right.
You know what?
Okay.
I'm burning this this doll down.
That's what we're doing here.
Okay.
That's what I'm doing now.
Because you know what?
This is what you get.
This is what you get now.
I'm throwing a fireball into this guy's stall.
That's what you get now.
That's what you get.
You cast the spell building a fireball in your palm,
but you don't have time to decide what to do with it.
As it turns out that moth wings are extremely flammable
and this is no mere candle flame you are holding.
Within seconds the stack of carpets is on fire.
The owner of the shop turns and flees as do two gnomes
were hiding behind the pile of rugs.
The shop collapses as the roof catches and there's nothing
you can do to stop the fire spreading.
The crowd around is quickly stampeding as the flames take
hold.
The covered market begins to fill with smoke.
Then you see daylight and race for it.
No, no, no.
That doesn't that doesn't work.
That doesn't work for me.
That doesn't work.
I'm reminding again.
That doesn't work for me.
Okay.
Here's what we're going to do.
I'm going to do tell.
Okay.
Read minds.
You slip on the cloth skull cap and cast.
Okay.
Hold on tuning into the carpet sellers thoughts.
He's thinking about the pile of carpets building up by the
door and how if he just shows you a few more you will be
trapped.
How about this?
He hauls the first carpet to the door and heaves out another
the rugs aren't light and he huffs and puffs as he moves
them around starts to attack this guy.
What are the spells can I do?
Hell sauce.
I don't have a zap.
I got yob.
Do the giant again.
I could just attack yop.
I'm just doing the same thing.
I just did yob times to nod do the giant and then rewind
again.
Why would I do that?
I'm attacking him.
It only takes a single punch to fell the carpet seller.
No, I want the item.
Whatever fuck it.
I don't care.
The market seems to be endless.
I dropped that guy in one hit by the way, you're quite
sure you've seen the same 12 creatures.
Oh, whatever.
I get to keep yob and I punched a guy in the face.
Fine.
You return to the middle of the market below the dome
looking to one side.
You spot the artist studio.
All right.
I was going to go to the artist studio.
This fucking bugleberry motherfucker laughing at me is
freaking me out.
The artist sits cross-legged surrounded by average quality
artwork.
Not surprising really since it seems this painter has no
hands.
You're a fraud.
Why would I ever do that?
Look at the paintings.
You look over the portraits.
He has done a series called the nobles of Carré.
You recognize none of the faces but do your best to
commit them to memory or future reference.
Pictures are not bad considering.
Greeting.
The artist nods in return.
Would you like to buy a painting?
They're all originals.
I assure you.
It does not seem possible.
How does he hold a brush?
The artist beams at you and adjusts his sitting position.
What happened to your hands?
You're a fraud.
Do you hold the brush in your mouth?
This is like fucking rude.
What happened to your hands?
You ask bluntly.
You notice the artist smile slip ever so slightly.
Someone did not like the picture I drew of them.
I think he saw a little too much truth in the image.
I don't want to leave.
I want to...
But these are rude.
This is this is rude.
I don't want to say either one of these things, but I don't
want to leave.
I want to like unlock more stuff.
I'm going to say it.
Do you hold the brush in your mouth?
No, no, nothing like that.
The artist shakes his head.
Ah, but to know my secret, you must step inside my hut.
There is a painting I'm working on even as we speak.
He points with his chin.
Please step inside the hut.
Okay, SpongeBob.
The walls of the hut are covered in sketches and the floor
is splattered with paint and ink.
In the center of the room is an easel and working furiously
behind it is a floating brush seemingly guided by an invisible
hand.
Okay, look at the...
Watch the brush.
The brush moves with hypnotic speed darting in and out of
different paint pots on the floor and then whipping across
the canvas.
Whatever is being depicted, it seems the brush would like to
finish it as quickly as possible.
Um, this is freaking me out.
This is actually freaking me out.
Look at the canvas.
You cross the room to look at the canvas and your heart sinks.
The brush is painting an image of you.
Now that it has had a closer look, the brush begins to edit
the picture refining its impression of your features.
Um, should I grab the brush?
Or what if it's just a cool picture?
Wait, you wait to see what the finished image will look like.
The paintbrush works at furious speed until the painting
is completed.
It is not a bad likeness, but then the image on the canvas
begins to move.
What?
Should I wait?
Run for it.
Wait.
You watch, transfixed, as the painted duplicate of yourself
clamors from the frame to stand on the ground.
From outside you hear the artist commanding the painting
to grab your money.
The duplicate lumbers forward, its sword drawn.
I don't have any...
I could throw a grenade if I could.
Zap.
Dodd.
Illusion of treasure.
Probably doze.
Yep, dop.
Lock doors.
Wrap.
Talk all languages.
Raz, sharpen your blade.
Sun.
Wait, I can like...
Fireball.
Dodd might work.
He wants money.
You gonna do the Gandalf spell?
This makes sense.
Cast a spell and create a small pile of illusionary treasure.
But your opponent is not in the least bit interested.
You lift your sword ready to engage your double.
He may have your strength and weapon, but will he have your skill?
I just full blasted like an idiot.
All right, we're good.
We're good.
Okay.
He did.
That was a full blast.
I'm going to go about...
I'm going to go like four.
I'm going to go like three.
I'm going to go 2.4, 2.5.
Whatever.
It's okay.
That was two.
We're going to go full blast now.
Got him.
Okay.
Defend.
Good.
I'm going full blast.
He's going to go hard.
Ah, I could have beat that.
I could have beat that.
I actually could have.
Got him again.
Is he going to come in hard?
You think?
Yep.
I couldn't have done it.
I think the damage is fine.
One more full blast.
He's dead.
You do not make things easy for it.
You rush at it swinging a masterful slice.
Your blade cuts through the fabric of the picture and suddenly
its fibers unravel in part.
The painting moves forward tearing itself in two.
The pieces collapse to the floor.
The magic broken.
The hut is suddenly very still.
Where is that motherfucker?
Time to teach the artist that such behavior will cost him dearly.
You search his hut thoroughly.
In one corner is a stack of pencil sketches labeled
Shinva, fifth noble.
Theta, seventh noble.
And Sansus, first noble.
It is a set of likeness of the nobles of Kare.
You roll them up and put them in your pack.
You slip out of the hut once more.
The artist tries to stop you with his foot.
You buy?
He asks.
Give him a gold piece as charity.
Your painting just tried to kill me.
Walk away or not today.
The artist shrugs.
My art is only what it sees.
He answers.
I'm not responsible for your heart.
Now buy or leave.
And he gestures away with his nose.
I've taken my reward already.
You retort indicating the stack of sketches.
The artist shrugs apparently not too concerned.
Those nobles won't be worth much soon anyhow.
He replies.
Wait a minute.
What do you know of the nobles?
Oh, Vic for first noble.
The artist nods.
He salutes you by spitting at your feet.
Mind how you go.
Here we go.
Pretty good.
The market stalls smell of soot and spice.
Back down.
Should I go?
I go this way?
I'm gonna go this way.
You return to the lower end of the market.
The air grows thick with the scent of perfumes,
incense, and flowers and then a darker smell soot.
Smoke is coming from a fire master's stall outside of which
several ornate fires of different colors and shapes are burning.
Definitely going in here.
The fire master's face is a patchwork of scars and scabs
and he smiles a ghastly smile.
Hello there.
I hope you're interested in fire.
White, green, blue, and black fires burn side by side in a
row like flowers in a window box.
They are quite beautiful and almost hypnotic in the way they
move.
What are they for?
Different things.
Maybe for relaxing.
Maybe for making the ladies fall in love with you.
Some is for cooking.
Others are warm, but I don't sell so many of those.
My favorite dough is inside.
He glances meaningfully at the hut door.
Okay, show me.
Be my guest.
In the center of the fire master's hut, a fierce fire is
blazing away, frightening to engulf the entire room.
But the flame is giving off remarkably little heat.
You're not even breaking a sweat standing this close to it.
I'm going closer.
Take a few steps closer.
From here, you notice that in the very heart of the fire,
there is a wooden chest.
The fire reminds you of the one in the grate of the large
abandoned house you explored earlier.
So I can just go in it.
Oh wait, we can read minds here.
We can, we can do sus.
You can read the minds.
Cause sleepiness.
This is magic protection.
I feel like sus and tell essentially do the same thing here.
Hmm.
What does sus do?
Sus is sensed danger.
It tells you if a voice goes in your head and goes, I'll
be careful of this, this and this.
We'll do tell.
Tell is sometimes more fun.
You place the skull cap on your head and cast a spell.
There are no minds inside the hut to probe.
But you find the fire master's thoughts easily enough.
Will this traveler fall into my trial?
He is thinking.
Seems he's hoping you will try to enter the flames.
The chest is closed.
So you cannot see what is inside, but it's clearly not
burning despite being made of wood.
I just leave.
Don't fall for it.
Well, maybe I can do it.
I'm going for it.
You reach out for the chest testing the flames of your finger.
They're really cool.
But still to reach the chest, you will need to step inside
the flame itself.
But I want it.
I want, I want it.
I want it.
I'm leaving fine.
You step outside and nod to the fire master.
Very impressive fire master nods and smiles clearly hoping
you will buy one of his lesser wares by a small flame.
Ask him about the fire in the abandoned house.
Oh, that's interesting.
How much is okay.
How much for a small flame is eight gold pieces.
From the look of you.
I'd say you want a flame that burns on pure danger.
Pulls a little box from a bag by his feet in a light when
you open it and catch on anything dangerous nearby.
If danger there be if it can it will burn whatever is
threatening you clean away.
What is it eight gold?
I have a lot of money.
Is it worth buying?
Yeah, I can't trust this guy at all.
Use it on this guy.
That's too expensive.
Yeah, a nice toy, but I'll save my goal for something more
impressive.
Okay, as you will.
I don't know about this.
I visited a house here in Kare where fire burned in a hearth
without heat one of yours the man shrugs perhaps.
I'm not the only fire master in Kare, but I am the best
grand house was it?
Yeah, it was a grand house if abandoned now.
Ah, the house of Lord Theta.
I would imagine you trespassed if you went in there.
You went blind, you know so much for the seventh noble of
Kare.
He lives as a beggar now.
Interesting.
What about the North Gate?
Tell me something.
I need to pass through the North Gate of the city.
Can you help the fire master shrugs?
Not me.
That's me.
Not bad.
Not many who do none as I haven't heard of.
Sorry.
I was I was no mute.
I had to fucking do that.
I know about the spell lines.
Fuck I can say I'm the mute for a minute.
Okay.
I know about the spell lines.
I was told by an innkeeper.
Good.
Well, you'll need no help from the likes of me.
Unless you'll be wanting to know what the spell lines are.
That might be harder.
Nobles are all but disbanded.
There's no council anymore.
It's an empty building with some guards.
Are they all dead?
No, not all of them.
I've heard tell but now they've all gone to
the ground hidden.
I told you of blind theta already for instance.
Is there no other way to find the spell lines?
Probably.
Kare is full of gods.
Ask the god of malice.
He has a priest near here.
Ask the other one the fat one the god of whatever he's
a god of.
He was much chancer getting something from them powers
that be as he would get a noble to talk seeing as most
nobles have had their tongues cut out already and at least
God stay in one place.
Now get on with you.
There's real customers.
I've got to talk to Goku.
You nod and stride back into the crowds of the market.
One voice Andy one voice Andy.
I've got one and it's a good one passing creatures
jostle and elbow you.
All right, it's time to leave the market.
You move back to the center of the market.
You've been waiting and walking in circles for some time.
Now you smell of blood and straw.
I think that's all I can do here.
Leave the market.
You turn around intending to leave the market when you
realize that you have lost sight of the entrance in the
crush of people and creatures.
You wander for a few minutes from one carpet seller to
the next but you quickly utterly lost because like a
stink cloud fog someone darkness.
How I'm going to do how you cast the spell in a voice
enters your mind with clear instructions how to leave
the market over there complicated and you won't be
able to remember them unless you go now mad mad do
something funny.
I have 10 health riding quickly.
You follow the twists and turns as guided by the voice
in your mind until you see daylight emerging blinking
into the sunshine.
You find yourself near a tall statue beyond which is a
wider Plaza at the foot of the statue is a drinking
fountain drink.
You drink a deep draught of cool crisp water and feel
quite refreshed.
This is a paved clearing perhaps intended for visitors
to the market to tie up their horses, but if any have
and it would seem their horses have been stolen.
We know all about that all around the slum houses rise
tall squats piled on squats emanating a thick and
terrible smell.
There are not many creatures about the main road continues
between the slums heading up a low rise and a side alley
leads left.
Sorry, I didn't mute.
Okay.
Look left to the left a narrow road leads deep into a
slum district, but it's lanes are slung with decoration
and ragged bunting the main road turns to the right here
and continues up the rise towards a run of slightly
grander buildings Ivy and gripweed hang from the bent
metal railings the whole place seems empty deserted and
dark suddenly out of an almost invisible narrow alleyway
a figure no higher than your knee dashes out and collides
with you sending you sprawling they cry about an apology
as they hair away down the street run after it check
myself over.
Yep.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
You charge off quickly down the road, you know, a
pickpocket when you feel one slip their hand into your
purse you catch sight of them just slipping into a
narrow alley further up the road.
It will take you off the main track and into the maze
like backstreets of Carrie if you follow the slum
districts of lower Carrie are unlikely to house the
secret of the North Gate, but you might be able to
learn where to find out more.
All right.
I'm we're about to run into the fall of a thief
that's going to get us kind of lost here.
Oh, we do we go down Mansion Row here.
Do we go up go get the thief into the slums run
after the thief or take the main road down here.
This is one, two, three, all will be up shortly one
two or three main road going up on a main road down
all the thief or up into the slums to give you a
better indicator of where we could end up.
Thief is to one, two, three, one, two, three.
Oh my God.
You guys really want that gold.
Holy wow.
Damn.
All right.
You guys are off of blood.
Go follow the thief.
You race into a side alley after the figure twisting
and turning between tall buildings.
The thief is a small child who freezes for a moment
and begins to run twice as fast straight towards a
high boarded fence kill kill this person right guys.
Kill this person go get him right really.
Oh interesting.
Your choice is very interesting.
The child looks spry and sprightfully and terrified.
You wouldn't put it past them to try and climb their
way out.
Gack is fear gum is glue.
I don't have glue August darkness.
That's all we can do with that.
We can do dumb which is clumsiness which will make
them drop something probably slowness does.
There's also wall which is making invisible wall walk
is create a shield slowness.
Just boom.
Castle.
That seems like a good idea.
You cast the spell in the child's movement slow to a
crawl one foot is placed on the fence.
They try to leap higher, but they misjudge and fall
slowly to the floor.
You grab the child by the scruff of the neck.
It's a young girl.
She squirms and wriggles clumsily as she tries to
escape.
I think you robbed me.
What are you running from?
I think you robbed me declare me.
No, I wouldn't.
I never would.
I'm being chased by the guard.
Are you a guard?
Yes.
Yes, I am and you're in big trouble.
Yes, you lie and you're in big trouble, right?
The girl begins to panic.
Suddenly you hear footsteps behind you and before you
can react a figure has grabbed you by the scruff of
your neck and hauled you backwards into a building.
Scram this new figure growls to the child who needs
no further warning and is quickly out of sight.
What what the fuck?
Don't be afraid murmurs of voice.
You turn to see who it is a dark-skinned man with a
beard of short stubble as you look at him.
He releases you holding up his hand to show he means
you no harm apologies to give you a fight.
He says I thought you were attacking that child.
Please sit with me and talk for a while that
child stole from me.
He nods.
I'm sure she did.
That's how they eat around here, but you can take it.
I'm sure you don't need to take revenge on children.
Surely you look around the building and realize you're
in his house.
You're in his home is well furnished with rich woven
tapestries on the walls.
Look him over.
You look the man over.
He's a noble looking sort wears fine fur is in a cloak.
He seems friendly enough, but he can't be a noble.
You do not recognize him from any of your pictures
or of the nobles of Kare.
You take a seat.
Tell me about Kare you begin.
I'm new here.
This is a treacherous place.
You can't trust anyone or anything in this town.
He winks at you.
But before I go into all that, would you like some ale?
I'll drink with you.
I must be leaving.
I don't drink.
How many times do people have to tell you this place
sucks?
Oh, yes.
Oh, tell me about Kare.
Yeah, sit down.
Well, first of all, this place sucks.
Oh, yes.
Welcome to Kare.
Yeah, please.
Oh, take a look at my wares.
This place sucks.
Kare, of course, one of the most dastardly cities, full
of traps, full of horrible things.
This place sucks.
They really do all do that.
They always do that.
That's true.
Uh, no, I'm going to drink with them.
The man returns with two mugs of ale and he places one
deliberately in front of you.
So let me tell you about my city.
It begins conversationally.
The center of Kare is built around the port and it can
be a dangerous place at night.
Hey, do you know the spell lines?
Like I've already drank five of these apparently.
Why is that?
Well, they say that those wandering the streets get
waylaid and captured onto slaving shifts.
So be sure to be sure to be settled down in an inn
before sundown.
To your health.
Uh, oh shit.
You waste no time summoning the force of zap in your
hands and then casually flinging into the chest of
the man opposite.
He gasps in surprise, but he is not killed only wounded.
Unsurprisingly, he reaches for his sword and you draw
your own.
Kill him in one hit.
Van Gorn raises his sword and stares at you along
the length of the blade.
You grip your sword firmly, then bring it up fast to
deliver a heavy blow.
He is off balance and moving slowly and the blade goes
deep.
He stumbles forward eyes opening wide with surprise.
You have finished me after so long undefeated with
Van Gorn dead.
You were free to search his small house.
Open the cover.
It's open the hangings.
Look behind the hangings searches by get through
everything.
I'm just like opening each curtain.
What the fuck are you doing?
I don't know.
Hey, you know what?
You know what?
You know what the fuck I'm doing?
People just gave me so much shit over the last like
30 or 40 minutes.
Oh, he's going to do how he's going to do sus.
He's going to be so safe.
Oh, yes.
Greetings.
Oh, greetings creature.
How are you?
I come in peace.
I've been getting shit for that for the last hour.
Okay.
Oh, greetings.
I come in peace.
Oh, can I see your wares?
No, I will not touch that fire.
Look, I went full on fucking chaos mode right there
and we get to loot this guy's whole house.
I don't even remember this guy from the last game.
This guy could be a really good guy.
I don't know.
I don't know what this could be.
Dude, you almost killed that kid.
Excuse me.
I want to back up here.
I left that up to you and everyone said thief thief
go kill the thief kill the thief.
And when everybody saw oh it was like the you know,
they turn around and it's a it's a little kid.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, I was just kidding.
I was kidding.
I'm not no, no, no, no.
I didn't mean that actually.
No, I was kidding.
It was a joke.
I would like you to go back and and watch the chat.
I want you to see how many times if you go no go do it
when the vaude is there.
It's not there right now, but I want you to go back.
I want to see how many times the word kill in all capitals
was put in the chat room, right?
Okay.
I want you to see.
Yeah, but but I zap a guy in his house and slash him.
It's shocked.
Whatever to our health unlimited power.
Oh, that's really shitty.
That's shitty.
But you know what?
Let's go.
You open the cupboards in one you find a jar marked poison
and in another a jar labeled essence of bark.
This guy was poisoning me.
I think take him will take everything you clear out the
cupboard and take the bark to take everything you take a
care.
No, wait, what what what happened you take it?
I didn't know I wanted to take it.
I don't want to eat it.
You take a careful sip of the essence of bark.
It tastes like freshly cut grass, but seems harmless
enough.
Then you look down to see your skin turning green.
What I have green.
I'm have green skin.
Okay, hangings look like rich treasures from a much grander
household made of thick cloth.
They're exquisitely decorated with images of orcs and trolls
being hacked to pieces by a hero with two blades in a silver
crown.
One of the hangings has a specific this guy's like a hero.
I one of the hangings has a suspiciously large bulge
underneath it.
And as you watch the bulge move, you lift one of the
hangings uncovering a gigantic spider.
The arachnid jumps at you bearing its fangs and landing
on your chest.
Oh my God.
The giant giant could help me horsefield jig.
You cast the spell and cautiously draw the pipe out of
your pack and begin to play at first.
The spider seems unaffected and its legs begin to twitch
one after the other a moment later.
It is performing a horrific jumping dance across your
chest and arms and racing up and down your legs in excitement.
Finally, it darts to the top of your head and attempts a
backflip falls off and lands on the floor.
You stop playing and it hurries away into a crack in the
floor.
You let out an enormous sigh of relief.
I was hoping it was going to die.
I was hoping that it was attempts a backflip and like
lands on its head.
So stupid.
You're embarrassed that it's a all right search the body.
You search Van Gorn's pockets find eight gold pieces and
you take it.
You found all you will find here time to be moving on.
What did I pick up though?
Sun jewel band.
I got like bark essence, right?
Essence of bark poison.
I'm gonna be able to poison somebody.
You're bald and green.
I can't wait to poison somebody is gonna be so dumb.
I'm so looking forward to that.
All right.
We only one way we can go just this way.
You continue along the street which grows narrower the more
winding it becomes on either side.
Slum dwellings arise high faces appear and disappear behind
drapes.
Someone throws out a bucket of slop narrowly missing you very
chained up animals screech from balconies.
The Sun disappears from view a bucket of slop.
Okay.
I asked for directions.
Did you kill the protagonist?
Good.
Oh right.
It said I could get lost in here.
That's right.
Keep going.
You push forward climbing a gentle slope.
I'm not stopping.
I'm not getting lost here.
The lane gets narrower muck and foul water runs downhill
forming a sheen over the flagstone the walls either side
are now so close together that someone on the top floor has
laid planks across the alley to steal from the house opposite
or perhaps to steal their own things back.
It's hard to be sure.
What why big I could just get huge and walk around for fun.
I'm doing big.
You cast the spell quickly inflating to three times your
normal size.
You hear shutters and doorways slam closed on all sides or
take the plank off remove the plank you pluck the plank from
its place and shake free the robber who is clinging on to
the middle of it.
He cries out as he lands you toss the plank aside at him
and move away the road narrows further until you can barely
squeeze your giant form between the door frames on either
side and fight suddenly you reach a small Plaza.
There's a small open square with a dried up well at center.
This is a crossroads and side roads lead off to the left
and right.
Oh shit.
Look at the alleys you pause to look around the edge of
the square is nothing to distinguish one alleyway from
the other although you do see a line of what look like
blood drops heading right the giant spell fades and you
slowly shrink back to your normal size.
Okay, so I could look over all that the only thing the
alleys have in common is that they converge here once
presumably this well served all the people in this district
but perhaps there were too many people because now the
well seems dusty and dry toss a coin down the well look
down the well look down the well leading over the edge you
peer down into the depths of the well strange this well
seems to have handholds cut into its stones.
If you're good enough to climb down climb down the well
choose a road or toss a coin.
I'm down.
Let's do a coin.
You toss a coin down the well it falls and falls and
falls eventually.
There is a very tiny splash.
All right chat option one or option to my climbing into
the well.
Are we going to pick up a road?
What do you think?
I can't believe I zapped that guy in his own house.
We'll get the coin back.
We were just drinking ale.
The way it was written to he gasps.
Oh my I killed him in one slash undefeated Omega Lull.
All right, that's that's a majority climb in the well.
There's still daylight left in the lore of the unknown is
overpowering you swing yourself over the edge of the
well teetering for a unnerving moment above the long long
drop and you find the first of the hold with your feet and
begin to make your way down into the dark into the well.
I was that you just you just got Elden Ringed by the way.
Oh was that you just got Elden Ringed just making sure
you understand that it is you just got Elden Ringed the
climb is slow and cautious.
You cannot see the holds below you.
So you have to feel your way down after about 10 minutes
your arms are tiring suddenly you realize the position
you're in if your strength gives out you will fall which
you may not have the energy to climb back up either.
It is impossible to see how much further down there is
to go climb out get out keep going down stealing your
courage you continue to climb down a ledge after perhaps
a minute more your foot finds a ledge below that is
nothing but space.
You have reached the roof of whatever chamber is below
a metal bar sticks from the wall here presumably used
to tie a rope to to continue the rest of the way down.
What can we do?
I don't have whatever that whatever that is fall float
in the air fog creative force field something.
Why would I someone darkness here?
Is also sus is there also sun?
No, just us.
I mean floating in the air seems or force field.
That's a good move.
Is it expensive?
Not really, but I'm kind of I'm running out of stamina.
You cast a spell and feel yourself become as light as
a feather and you release hold of the wall and float
gently down in the sewers.
I do have potions you're floating an inch or so above
thick water in one of the city sewers smell is indescribable
terrible.
You're at a dead end of sorts the water disappears into
a grating in one direction while the tunnel disappears
into darkness in the other.
I don't think we're going back up you step out from the
dim light of the well shaft and into the black tunnel
beyond I don't think there's any going back up drinks
and blimberry is the ape here.
Okay.
The ape is finally here one more.
No, that's fine.
Hold up a drink from the sewers.
Ella Mayo.
I think that that's like them.
What do you why is it?
That's not that's like the tunnel is filled with the
worst dent.
You can imagine things splash and scurry through the
darkness pass a heap of black cloth a huddled creature
investigate you creep over to the huddled rags the shape
of a man leaned over clutching his knees, but it does
not seem to be moving run it through touch it collapses
at just the slightest touch and you breathe a sigh of
relief just a piled up cloak.
Discarded by some previous unfortunate.
We traveled this way you sift through the heavy cloth.
This was a fine cloak once before it was left to rot
down here stitched on the back is a number one in a
circle waterlogged the cloak is too heavy to carry
away and has no pockets.
However, and no hidden gold, but it proves that others
have come this way before said that kind of wrong,
but whatever cloak with pockets that seems actually
pretty helpful.
I don't know why they didn't make them.
All right moving on.
I keep pausing to cough.
That's why you don't hear me for like a minute or
so to time sewer turns a corner here with the other
tunnels blocked by filth strewn wreckage you steal
yourself and dig through the foul filth in the wreckage
trying not to vomit from the stench you come across
a small glass bottle on Cork it and breathe it in.
It's blimbrary you stash it into your pack.
Oh hell.
Yeah, let's take it right now.
You walk onwards through the dark sewer and suddenly
the tunnel opens into a low chamber.
There's a chamber you stand ankle deep in filth in a
square chamber icy droplets fall from the ceiling.
The smell is terrible.
But this is not just any sewer in the corner of the
room is a pile of rags someone or something lives
down here search the rags look around the room or
leave search the rag you dig into the rags and clothing.
They must have formed someone's bedding as they
could never have been clothing strips and odd squares
of cloth of all different kinds.
They've probably been scavenged from what people
threw down the drains into the sewers.
Dig through them carefully digging into some old
pockets you find a few gold pieces.
Suddenly you find yourself itching and scratching the
rags are covered in fleas and now they are biting you
as well.
The thought occurs to you.
Perhaps this is not the hiding place of a beggar but
the nest of some terrible beast a sudden rush of
water floods the chamber soaking you up to the
waist a moment later.
It is washed away once more, but there might be more
coming.
What are we doing here one or two you pick some dude
just flush the toilet one or two look around the room
or walk on one or two one or two one or two one or
two.
What am I doing?
Okay, we're looking around the room.
Apparently never one to they get them.
Yeah one is running away with it 60% I just got here
this stream sucks.
No doesn't bud.
All right one wins one wins one wins by a lot.
I just got you just like you just open the stream
and type that you don't have any video for five
seconds.
Despite your concerns.
You stop to look around the walls of the chamber side
from the pile of rags.
There's nothing else here.
No stash of food or weapons and no sign of the
inhabitant.
Then you notice on the far wall some scratches in
the stone a mark of time.
Perhaps suddenly something growls in the darkness in
the tunnel behind you.
You look up to see a dark stooped shape approaching
fast.
It is a rat bear Gack.
God I wish we had a jewel.
There's also law.
Did it work last time?
I don't remember.
Oh kid create an illusion.
I could make an illusion.
Yeah, we can't talk.
We don't have the wig.
I'll do an illusion.
Let's do illusion.
You slip the bracelet around your wrist and cast
the spell summoning the force of illusion create a
fire a wall of water or an army.
Army I feel like wouldn't fire it'd be like like
run fire you create the illusion of a raging fire
as though the whole sewer was suddenly a crucible
the rat bear screams and terror and charges away
down the tunnel.
Okay, we have time now we can look at the marks you
make your way carefully around the cesspool in the
middle of the room the far side where the marks are
faintly visible in the gloom.
They're not just notches but letters and perhaps
once they were full words but have been worn away
by the floating water or else filled with slime and
dirt looks as though it might have been a poem read
the poem still shaking from your encounter with a
rat bear you steady your heartbeat and peer at the
markings on the wall.
You can make out the following through the muck
corgas grace one lock the deep inside the I bid
you there's nothing more to be done here.
If you ever wish to see daylight again, you got to
move on now you walk onwards through the sewer
shadowy shapes loom out of the darkness and disappear
as you move close you walk for what seems like an
hour maybe more tunnel tilts lower and lower.
Perhaps you are going underneath the river the
sound of fast rushing water fills the tunnel.
Zip oh we don't we can't zip.
Horsefield there is huff wind is how does a suss
to see the sunlight horsefield.
I'm going to put up I'm going to force field is
expensive though.
I'll try it nervously.
You cast your spell binding a tight horsefield
around yourself.
It will not last for long, but should anything happen
soon the force field should protect you from the
worst of it that done.
You keep walking the sound of rushing water is
growing louder around a corner.
Suddenly you realize the sound is not coming from
close by the tunnel or through the walls.
The sound is coming towards you somewhere a wall
of water is approaching an old dam must have given
way and the river water is now flooding the tunnel
ready for aid sell shelter.
I have I have a force field.
Take a deep breath run for it.
Pray for aid.
We have the ape right now.
Wait, we have to read this strong beast intelligent
and prudent who takes great pride in acting faithfully
to be depended upon.
Okay, that's actually pretty good to have here.
I think or do we just eat it and I can still have
the ape if I need it.
I did just do three stamina worth of horsefield.
I'm just going to eat it take a deep breath.
There's nothing else for it.
You take a deep breath exhale take a deeper breath
exhale and then fill your lungs as best as you can
as the great wave strikes the water.
Wretches you from the floor and throws you into a
swirling spiral.
You can see nothing but the murk and the filth for
the moment.
At least you are calm and can focus focus even in
the roaring torrent from with the currents from
against the currents from down to escape the flow
swim up or a ceiling duct duct.
It's probably with the current.
Somebody said this is a rerun stream.
Yeah million followers man.
Come on good swim up for a ceiling duct.
The current is whipping you this way in the like
like a fetal bug in a thunderstorm.
It is all you can do to work out which way is up
and which way is down you fight and struggle to get
your body under control losing valuable seconds
of air.
Your force field has trapped some but it will soon
run out.
It's still on.
All right.
We got to get the right call here.
We got to get the right call.
So I'm still in the force field with his air in
here.
So I'm okay swim up or should I just let the
current go go with it go with it swim with the
current you swim with the current which tears you
along the length of the sewer the force field
protects you against bashes and knocks the ground
level is rising below at some point.
Perhaps you will break the surface of the water
but it has not happened yet.
Your lungs are bursting for air with the current
you swim with the current moving at breakneck
speed you cannot last much longer with the current
again you swim with the current moving at
breakneck speed only the air trapped inside your
force field is keeping you alive.
I don't know you swim up towards the roof of the
sewer hoping to find an air pocket to refresh your
breath but you're out of luck your force field
bashes the arched sewn ceiling which is fully
submerged.
Even the ducks running up are filled with water
there is no air to be had.
I'm like a fucking pinball with the current again
swim down from down you turn and fin down towards
the bottom of the sewer hoping to escape the
worst of the current near the ground the water
is slower and you are thrown about less violently
but despite the force field bubble around yourself
just still running out of air the air inside your
force fields running low in the spell itself won't
last much longer up up a duck against bro against
against against I got a force field on that you
pick this is the force field gave us like an
extra like three or four choices here one two or
three I really actually don't know I forgot I
don't remember one two or three.
This is probably the last shot here the force
field gave us extra time.
I think but this is this is a decision that needs
to be made one two three ducks are probably full
of water fray to the ape I could have what Chad
is going to choose the one that rose.
All right.
It's it's three swim up a duck lungs bursting you
reach a duck in the ceiling once inside it wrenches
you upwards with powerful force the stone work
either side is a blur and you crash scrape and
bang into the sides but harmlessly thanks to the
force field and suddenly you are spat up into a
wider colder water lit from above by silvery light
you are outside not dead you come up gasping for
air about a quarter of the way across the river
that flows through the middle of Kari night has
fallen while you were underground and all around
you is pitch darkness you struggle and flail for
a moment to get your head above water and then
turn about to swim for the far bank.
Of course all your water damageable possessions
have been ruined including your pictures of the
nobles of Kari thankfully.
However, the pages of your spellbook are protected
and your fleas are washed away.
What what got ruined what I need those clues.
What happened walking?
What did I lose?
Did I lose anything?
I'm okay, right?
I'm okay about the treasure.
I think I still have everything.
I didn't lose anything ever good swim forward.
Am I going to dive back under a swim forward you
swim along the surface of the river keeping your
mouth clear on the filth as best you can and aiming
for distant lights of the far bank is a figure
moving there a night watchman of some kind you
keep on swimming carving your way across quickly
keen to be out of the jibaji as soon as possible.
Suddenly a voice rings out across the river is
someone in the water man's voice calls.
What are the slaves is escaping one by one more
lanterns appear lighting up like stars as they
emerge from around the sides of the buildings
and down the narrow alleys to the waterfront shit
dive under you dive quickly under the water for
a moment.
You're alone isolated in the brown water and
something hisses past your face an arrow.
They're firing into the water.
I mean where where do I where do I go from here
rewind you lost the pictures.
I don't need those pictures.
Fuck them swim in circles to keep going from
Ford you keep swimming forward but no more arrows
strike.
Perhaps they have lost track of you in the water
since you're not swimming back as they might have
expected but forwards you move slowly and silently
coming up for air when you need to but breathing
only softly and gently after several minutes of
this you arrive at the far bank.
I mean check that it's safe you wait shivering in
the freezing cold water of the river.
But the men and their lanterns are a little
further along the bank.
You should be safe to climb out here.
You haul yourself up and pant gratefully in the
dark on the far bank look around in the darkness
the far bank is less populated than the near
bank.
There are no ins no market stalls just a single
path disappearing off into the darkness between
large stone buildings.
You're too tired from your swimming to walk on.
So you crawl under a bush and make camp you are
exhausted and could do with something to eat but
there is nothing you can do all of your food has
been ruined by the water time to get some rest you
close your eyes and are quickly asleep.
Your dreams are cluttered and crazy face after
face laughs as you ask about the spells for says
one there are 11 spells 1349 River water fills
your mouth and makes you choke but the water is
arriving with fishes each of which wants to tell
you its life story vangorn strides over and shakes
you by the hand.
Thank you for helping me realize the error of my
ways.
He says a moment later he sticks a dagger into
your lung a monk with the hooded eyes of a bat
throws a size a dice the size of a boulder towards
you.
Finally a black well mouth approaches and swallows
you whole.
Oh wow.
We just really cool.
Okay, that's one way that's yeah.
Okay, cool.
Next morning dawn comes and you are woken by the
shimmering light across the surface of the Jibaji
River by the idyllic morning is quickly broken as
the first of the boats begin to sail down the
river sailors cursing and singing filthy songs that
echo between the buildings are on either side.
You almost become accustomed to the terrible smell
here.
You follow the road away from the river towards a
fork in the road.
We're almost at the North Gate.
We're almost there right here.
Oh really?
We'll see what happens.
Who knows what happens in car the early morning
sun is beginning to wake the streets of Kare a few
creatures roam this way and that in one corner a
spring bubbles with fresh water drink cup your hand
to the water and drink a mouthful.
It is fresh and invigorating always drink the
water always drink from the water.
Are there any porta potties in this game?
Yeah, you missed it.
There was like there's like a 10 to 15 minute
ordeal where we shit in a porta potty and we had to
keep doing a way to find toilet paper and shit.
It was it's pretty cool.
It's a wild part of the adventure was disgusting.
Okay, look around looking left the road heads
through a into a residential area that seems well
cared for a short way off to the right is an open
Plaza.
We asked for directions you stop a passing creature.
Excuse me.
I need to ask you the creatures head is bowed doesn't
look up but it pulls itself free and hurries away.
It is too miserable to speak.
There's nothing for it.
You'll have to explore yourself or down where we
going to go you have a really distinct.
I'm making shit up on the spot voice.
What I'm reading it.
I'm reading it.
What do you mean making shit up on the spot?
What are you talking about?
What does that mean?
I'm reading it from a this is a book.
He's talking about the porta potties.
What no, I don't I have a tell.
Do I actually have a tell?
Yes, you have a making shit up on the spot voice.
Fuck this dude is reading you like a book.
Yeah, whatever.
That's fine.
Yeah, you go into quote performance mode.
It's an obvious tell.
Well, maybe I'm doing it on purpose in a way in my
mind because I'm I want you to make I want to make
sure you know, I'm full of shit right subconsciously.
It's like it's a way for you to know that I'm completely
and totally fabricating this 50 come on vote only
500 of you have clicked it.
It's 5050.
It could be two of you in chat right now could decide
it.
This could come down to one person deciding where to
go up.
Okay.
You got it going up.
You follow a narrow winding Street past shops and
stalls.
It's still early and there are not yet open but there
are stirrings from within the houses as the day's
activities begin a face appears at a window and seems
to watch you pass.
Although the creatures eyes are closed and you're not
sure that it actually notices you wave at the creature
you wave to the creature, but it does not react.
Its eyes are still closed.
Another similar creature stands in a doorway across
the street washing themselves from a bucket.
This one is thin and spinely with a long face not
exactly a human and not an elven either something in
between the art in this game is so good.
It's just so I can't even describe it.
Something just so off-putting about it, right?
It's so good.
It's so strange.
Okay.
It almost feels like a person didn't draw this right.
It almost feels like an otherworldly creature an
otherworldly being drew this not a person.
It's really cool.
All right.
Am I going to greet this?
Aliens are people, but I'm not like a human.
It looks almost AI generated.
Yeah, it's just so interesting and unique.
I mean, I love it.
It's Ian Livingston, right?
Let's see did all the artwork.
That's fantastic.
All right.
Oh, let's um, we're going to greet it.
You try to greet the washing creature, but it too has
its eyes closed.
Perhaps it is soaping its hair and doesn't want to
sting its eyes at the end of the road under a low arch
a group of youths are loitering talking and kicking
stones into the gutter.
They notice you and begin to point and talk amongst
themselves approach take a side street to avoid them
or look them over.
Let's look them over first.
You pause to look at them.
They too have their eyes closed.
Although somehow they have seen you or perhaps they
have only heard you one or two approach them or take
a side street and avoid them one or two this side of
the river is creepy.
Yeah, so far.
We're going to get jumped maybe everyone and everything
wants to kill you here.
Yeah, this place sucks.
We're going to approach 70% there's no way you're
going to hold that back approach a group of children
doesn't scare you.
You continue down the street towards them.
They fan out a little until they fill the width of
the narrow Road above you shutters are closing and
people move away from windows as though despite
their eyes.
They've seen a fight coming breathe them elbow my
way through close my eyes.
Hold on or cast a spell.
Let's see what we have available.
Okay, we have Goblin we can summon a Goblin is also
float.
There is hot of course mud which you don't have
access to anymore.
Dud which is treasure hot gigachad hot gigachad
Bob them sure cast the spell throwing down a Goblin
tooth as you do is a puff of smoke and then a moment
later a Goblin warrior stands before you saluting
order him to attack the youths order him to wait
go attack like the kids go attack the use or slip
past the youth what he's going to go what they
okay.
Wait above you despite their eyes.
They see a fight coming slip past what would he do
be like yeah, it's safe.
What is slipping past do I think he I think we're
going to send the Goblin.
And the Goblin will sneak by them and then wave and
say yeah, you can just do that.
They can't they're not going to be able to see you
or something right put a pole up one or two.
I'm not going to make this choice because they
either one.
I'm not sure I'm not going to make this decision.
We need stealth gameplay.
Yes, you do.
It's very it's as close remember one is attacked
to is slipped by this is a guy going to keep keep
this one open.
I don't know why fight.
I don't know.
It's going to be close.
This is too close to call.
It's going to come down to one person.
It's going to come down to one psychotic person
that is going to make it push over isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
You order the Goblin to attack and he marches off
towards the youth swinging his short stubby sword
the blade catches one of the men in the side who
gasps in pain and he does something from here.
You can't see what but a moment later your
Goblin has evaporated into a sudden burst of flame.
The youths laugh among themselves barbecued Goblin
me one asks no.
Thanks replies another he caught one of these kids
in the side and then they fucking grilled him.
What?
Well, I'm going to go talk to them.
They don't know where the Goblin came from.
But all they know some crazy guy just ran down
the street with a sword.
They don't know what came from me.
You approach the group boldly.
Good morning.
Get out of my way children.
You own this Street.
I see you own this Street.
I see you remark.
I see you are very powerful.
I wonder if you have any idea how powerful the youth
replies quietly.
Would you like to find out?
Yeah, my pleasure.
The youth opens his eyes and suddenly a streak of
burning fire shoots from under his eyelids scorching
your side you gasp in pain and he laughs then the
other creatures grab your arms from either side.
Don't struggle or we'll look at you all over.
You are marched away through the alleyways to a
building surrounded by a high wall.
It is a prison.
You're dragged across the yard and into an underground
corridor cell doors opened and you're thrown inside
landing squarely on top of another creature.
Should have drawn the sword.
I don't I think they would have got me.
You're throwing dude.
What do you mean throwing?
Who is this?
Hold on.
You pick yourself to your feet and dust yourself down.
Apologies friend you say to your cellmate.
It's an Elven he seems worn out and exhausted creature
nods to you.
Welcome to my little world.
He replies you ready your mind for a spell but
nothing happens.
The Elven laughs bitterly.
The walls are infused with minimite blood to stop
people getting out that way.
I would have used my own magic if it worked from the
sounds coming through the walls.
This is one of several cells all side by side.
You hear snores shouts and screams coming through
the stonework.
Pray to the ape.
Should I pray now or should I wait?
I kind of want to wait.
Who are you?
My name on the outside hardly seems to matter.
My name in here is number six and that'll be your
name too.
He points a bony finger.
It's written on the door.
See the cell is empty except for a bucket murmuring
an apology.
The Elven uses it for what it is for.
You're an Elven you say I've not met your kind before
but I know of you.
He shrugs.
Elvens are pretty annoying creatures, but that's not
what they locked me up here for.
What is this place?
This is the jail of the red eyes.
There's one outside.
He points at the guard whose face with eyes closed
fills the tiny porthole.
The smell from the bucket in the corner of the room
is quite terrible.
Why would you why do you need to tell me that?
What does that add to the story?
Like hey he's shit in this bucket by the way.
Just want to make sure you know this and you're
aware of it.
Why are you here?
You know, the Elven replies with a sigh of some
passion.
I've asked myself that every night since I was arrested
months ago and I still can't figure it out.
I didn't do anything to upset these people.
My only idea is that the red eyes aren't happy
unless they've got someone locked away.
Maybe now you're here.
They'll let me go or they'll let me go.
Yeah, that would be a good joke on their part.
You can see the creature's spirit has been quite
broken.
I'm gonna pray to the ape.
Come on ape help us.
Help us spirit of the ape.
You raise a prayer to the ape and as you finish
there's a tiny click.
The sound of a lock tumbler falling over.
The Elven's narrow eyes open wide as portholes.
You wait until the guard outside has turned his
back and then slide the door open.
He will not be looking the other way for long.
Don't put shit up.
Don't shit all over moving silently.
You pick up the bucket from the floor of the cell.
The Elven looks at you curiously but says nothing
but the bucket on his head.
You raise the bucket nice and high creeping forward
on tiptoes and then at the last possible moment
you bring it down quickly on the guard's head.
Unmentionable substances trickle down on his face
but for a moment he cannot see.
Drag him backwards into the cell.
Run him through.
Drawing your sword you slice quickly through his
neck.
This is such a terrible way to die.
The Elven looks shocked but only for a moment then
he nods seriously when the others find him.
Be sure they will come for us unless we're gone.
You nod.
He is quite right.
Time to run for it.
You race up a set of stairs heading towards a patch
of sunlight and emerge in an alleyway on the other
side of the prison wall.
The Elven at your back.
I didn't even I didn't have to dump shit on the guy.
Why did I do that?
I dumped, by the way, this was a fresh bucket of
shit.
This guy, the Elven just did it.
This wasn't oh, you know, it's been like a few days.
He just dropped a fucking huge log in this thing
and it was probably hot.
It was a hot new shit that I dumped on his head and
then I slit his throat.
That added extra steps.
We didn't have to do the extra steps, right?
Just kill him.
Run him through.
That was disgusting.
300 people left the stream because of that.
You emerge onto a quiet side street and begin to
weave and duck through the alleyways.
The Elven weak from his long stay in the tiny cell
can barely keep pace with you but is filled with
such joy to be free that he laughs even as he trips
and stumbles.
We got a new friend.
One or two.
Time to decide.
I am imagining it's going to be right or left here,
right?
So I'm not sure.
One or two.
One is right.
Two is left.
One or two.
I don't think that was solid, man.
Yeah, the ape came through.
I wonder, I don't remember if you don't, if you've
already prayed because you can just pray to get
healed or pray in a few other scenarios.
I wonder what happens.
Yeah, to be depended upon.
The ape is probably one of the better ones to have.
You idiots are going to go back to the same place
where people, where we got caught.
We just go right back to the people with the eyes.
We just get put back in jail again and there's no
more ape.
We're doing the comedy route.
Yeah.
We're going left.
At the first junction, you turn left.
Do you know where you're going?
Ask the Elven, but there isn't time to reply.
Shit.
Again, again, again, again.
Where are we going?
One or two.
Do you know where you're going?
All right, I'm going to go left and then we're going
to go left.
We're going to go left again.
And then we're going to get burnt by the eye people.
Going to go into a circle.
Yeah, you're legit going to end up at the entrance.
Wait, right.
Okay, we're going right.
At the next junction, you go right.
The Elven is flagging.
He cannot keep running like this anymore.
Go on.
I'll hide here.
Leave him or help him.
You got to help the bro.
Help him.
Help, help, help him.
You're nearly free.
You reply, grabbing the Elven under his arm.
I mean it.
I'll hide you idiot.
While you distract any more guards with your running,
now go.
Good plan.
Leave him.
It would have been.
The Elven replies and you turn to see he's quite right.
Another guard has entered the alley behind you.
He opens his eyes and a moment later, the staggering Elven
is no more.
The stench of burning flesh fills your nostrils.
You race out of the alley.
Quite suddenly you emerge out of the side street into a
wide square filled with more red eyes, but these ones seem
like citizens rather than guards.
We killed him.
Save him.
So dumb.
LOL.
We got him killed.
I don't think I should I use a rewind on this?
I only got two more.
This one would be legit by the way.
We'll try.
We'll try again.
Let's try again.
I'm using my second rewind.
All right.
It was turn.
Wait, should we do this differently?
Turn left and then turn right, right?
And then right.
Okay, so I'm just going to leave him.
He gaps several.
I'll hide here.
Leave, leave, leave, leave.
You do not need to be asked twice.
You wish him luck and then hurry away.
The Elven crawls into a pile of junk and beds down.
Perhaps you will see him again.
Saved.
Now what?
We're not out of this.
One or two.
One is right.
Two is left.
Choose quickly.
Can you hide with him?
I don't.
I don't know.
This shit is tight.
This is sorcery.
I tell you it's fun.
All right, we're going left.
You keep running taking a left.
Quite suddenly you emerge out from the alleyway into a
wider busier street.
You slow yourself to a nonchalant walk.
We made it.
Made it.
We're out.
Wait, are we?
The road turns and heads roughly southeast once more.
But you have been stopped.
Spotted by a group of young orklings and they're scurrying
towards you.
Okay, hurry to avoid them or wait for them to reach me.
One or two quick again.
I mean, I don't know what to do here.
What do I want to do?
Dude, hold on.
I just had this insane urge for a one steak sauce.
I don't know why.
Just it just popped in my brain.
That sour kind of flavor.
I want it so bad.
I don't know why.
Oh my God.
I want it so bad right now.
I want it so badly.
Just the sauce.
I just yeah, I just want to dig tap tap tap tap tap with
my pinky and dab dab dab dab dab on the top of my tongue.
That's it.
It's our turn.
Silence.
I'm you're going all right.
What one hurry and avoid them.
I think that's what's going to happen.
Let's go hurry and avoid them.
You increase your stride hoping to breeze straight past but
the gang is a big enough for them to easily block the road.
You're soon right in their midst.
Their hands poke at you and push outwards hoping for a
donation.
Look at someone a goblin.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What else is there?
Create a force field.
They can't like touch me.
Oh treasure would be huge here.
That I would absolutely work.
Why would I read their minds?
I know that they're trying to get okay.
Another goblin or should we do the treasure?
Is there also s?
Ooh, I can clone myself.
I have six of me.
The goblins gonna get wrecked.
Yeah, they're gonna just swarm the goblin and kill him.
All right.
Treasure makes the most sense here.
It just does.
Why would you do treasure?
Because they're there.
It says they want a donation.
It's like they're trying to like poke me and prod me.
It says so.
I mean if I put like a million dollars on the ground that
it's gonna be fine.
Or how wait how much is it?
What are they looking for?
Throw a gold piece.
Give throw a gold piece away with throw the gold that okay.
That would work too.
I have money.
They're not gonna like that.
Throw it.
This is so...
Dud?
How much is Dud three stamina or one?
Let's see what happens.
You cast the spell and piles of gold and treasure spill from
the sleeves of your jacket and all over the road.
The orklings go instantly into a frenzy of collection running
over each other and beating each other up stuffing handfuls
of gems in their tunics.
You take the opportunity to slip away.
I okay.
I feel like they were gonna attack me.
All right.
It says they were beating each other up.
They were children.
What?
We were some of the goblin and the goblin would have
the goblin would have swung at him.
I'm sorry.
The goblin would have just you saw what happened when I sent
the goblin to a group of children.
Okay.
Last time a goblin was sent to a group of children.
A sword went into one of the kids sides.
Okay, you continue up the road leaving the chattering
orklings behind after a short distance.
You come across a large building made of stones and
mortar.
Look at the building.
It stands alone inside its own patch of grounds and
unusually it seems to be in a state of good repair.
A large L is carved on one gate post made road and
continue straight past the house.
I think I remember this part.
We going in.
Oh, it's good.
We're going in right.
I think I know this part and what I remember you enter
the gate and follow the path to the front of the house
between tall well-attended trees.
This place unlike the mansion in lower care seems quite
lived in.
All right, we got creep around the side or right in the
front door creep around the side is going to be one front
door will be to 30 seconds on the clock.
Let's get a pole going.
Oh German imagine having an opinion on that on a goblins
because one Goblin stabbed a kid.
Hold on.
I get a sneeze again.
You told him to do that.
I didn't tell him to do that.
You did.
So don't put that on me.
I didn't tell him to do anything actually.
All right, we're going to the front door the door to
the house is solid oak wood.
Decorated with elaborate carvings of vines and trees
and serpents in the middle is a great brass knocker.
You firmly knock on the door, but no one answers how seems
empty dark and quiet.
Zip is teleport.
I don't have the item.
I mean, I could just literally burn it down like we do
every fucking door in the game could blow it down, but
I don't have wind.
We could try to open it with Dopp.
Dopp might just work.
It's one stamina.
Let's try Dopp.
Cast a spell on the door swings open smoothly to reveal
a hallway.
Be decked in finery and well-kept.
This is the house of a nobleman, perhaps even a noble.
Okay inside the house.
Yeah, sometimes the easiest answer is the right one,
right?
The inside of the house is well-kept and clean.
There are fresh flowers and vases and the surfaces are
dust free.
It is as though whoever lived here has just slipped out
for a few minutes and will return at any moment except
for the paper strewn everywhere across the hallway.
The floor is almost a foot deep in books torn pages and
folders with charred edges.
It is as though a lightning storm has passed through the
study on the left.
Under the door lies opposite by the smell of it.
It's a kitchen.
You browse through the papers.
Some are complex and you cannot understand the words.
Others are calculations.
There are also maps and charts and plans of Kaare, the
hills and the backlands to the north.
Other documents look almost like charts for spellmaking
such as the chief mage used back in the outpost settlement
to prepare for your spellbook.
Whoever lived here was clearly a scholar of some great
wisdom and most likely a wizard as well.
Exploring doesn't seem like a good idea somehow.
Try the kitchen, try the study or leave.
You're going to die.
Chieftain of the Badlands.
Explore anyway, gigachad.
All right, let's go to the kitchen.
You open the door to the kitchen and go inside.
It is laid out as though the owner of the house was in
the middle of preparing a meal.
Bread is sliced, cheese is on a plate, and a glass of
wine sits beside the open bottle.
Nothing here has had time to go moldy.
Something is rattling in one of the cupboards.
I'm going to eat some of this shit.
You eat the bread and drink the wine and finish off with
the cheese, which is full flavored and ripe.
There is enough left over for you to add one more
portion to your pack as well.
This is Goldilocks.
Yeah, let's open the cupboard.
You open the cupboard out of curiosity.
And they're immediately bowled over as a thing erupts
with angry force.
You crawl backwards into the hallway to get away from
this gnashing fangs and get to your feet to see what
it is.
A bristle beast and it's furious.
No, opening the cupboards into these, they're always
such a bad idea.
I mean goblin, sap, hot might burn the house down.
Okay, but here's the thing.
Am I running out of goblin teeth?
We're using it so much.
Eight.
It's a lot, but let's kill it.
Yeah, let's just kill it.
You have just enough time to draw your sword.
Let's kill it.
Eight is a lot.
I know, but I let's go with a 6.0.
Dang.
All right.
Good.
The bristle beast bears its teeth.
Beast lashes out with its claws, but it cannot defend
itself from your force.
Do it again.
All right.
Now we get a free kill essentially.
No stamina lost.
We're good.
It twists on the metal then curls up like an overheated
beetle and dies, but the creature dead you pause to
catch your breath.
Where now?
Study.
Pet?
You open the door to the study pushing hard against a
deeper pile of paper.
This room looks like a tornado has traveled through it
and perhaps one has.
In the very center of the room is a blackened circle
burnt into the carpet.
There's a smell of iron and ammonia in the air.
It is hard to escape the sense that some great and
terrible magic was performed here not long ago, but
there's no sign of the magician who crafted such a
powerful spell.
On all fours you dig through the piles of paper books torn
up, almanacs, historical files and sheets of scrawl and
scribble.
There's nothing here with any meaning.
On one sheet you find an intriguing series of symbols.
N, Q, then a series of other marks written and then crossed
out.
Only one is still readable and it has been circled.
T.
Okay, keep searching.
You keep rustling through the paper finding little
doubts of value then underneath a heap of tomes about
the early founders of the city with several passages
underlined and marked with comments you cannot read.
You unearth a green-haired wig which you put into your
pack.
We can finally talk to fucking animals.
You return to the hallway.
You explored enough you leave the house and return to
the street outside.
Finally we can talk to the horse baldness cured.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You return to the main road.
Follow the road.
The road continues on between dense houses on either side
when suddenly begin to smell a sharp acrid smell burning
looking up ahead.
Do you see a column of smoke is the district on fire?
I'll handle this.
Sus.
Where's water fog some in darkness magic protection?
Fuck.
I don't know what that is.
Maybe I'll put on a force field or magic.
Wait, is fire technically magic?
Not really.
Would darkness put the fire out?
It's just fire.
Make it worse hot.
You sus.
You cast the spell in a calm voice enters your mind telling
you not to fear.
There's no danger up ahead.
You're reassured in the spell fades.
Okay, feeling safe with the warming warning from your
spell you stride forward towards the smoke rounding a
corner in the road until you see the source.
It is a fire but not a blazing house instead.
It comes from an enormous Forge set into a large
blacksmith shop.
The blacksmith himself is at work hammering away at a
flat bladed sword.
Oh, okay.
Almost created a force field for that.
Yeah.
You approach the blacksmith and try to attract his
attention by knocking a few of his display items off
their shelves.
What an asshole, but it seems the blacksmith is quite
deaf years of hammering on sparking metal has left him
quite oblivious to everything around him.
Steal something.
Why would I do that?
Is this a Mr.
Bean movie?
What would the point of that be?
Let's let's tap his arm.
You walk over and tap his arm the blacksmith jumps.
I didn't see you here.
Man is clearly not that bright.
I didn't mean to scare you not scared of me of you.
Nah, the blacksmith polishes his blade lovingly.
Tell me about your swords.
This one is my hardest.
He replies proudly indicating the blade.
He is currently polishing up a blade of a large hand.
I try it large hand large hand is large handry.
What try the blade you reach out to try the blade,
but the blacksmith catches your arm.
I warn you once you're tried it.
You won't want any other and it's not a cheap lard.
I'll risk it.
The last Smith shrugs and releases your arm.
They're on them.
You pick up the blade and swing it through the air.
It sings the weight is perfect.
The metal sharpened the balance so delicate.
It becomes almost an extension of your arm.
This is the finest blade you have ever held how much the
blacksmith grins.
I tell you ready for it fighting old pieces party blacksmith
nods.
That's right party.
Uh Haggle, I'll give you half that you begin but the blacksmith
only laughs are talking to your child party or solid to the
next one.
That's too much.
I don't have that much.
I don't have that much blacksmith nods and takes the
blade back with loving care.
I'll find each owner sooner enough.
I'm sure fuck fuck fuck shit shoot shit 40 gold though.
Holy crap.
How would you have?
You might you have to save everything.
Um, do you make wolf armor you ask thinking about the
strange werewolf you saw blacksmith looks at you with
fierce cold eyes Vic for first noble.
He replies but says nothing more.
Who's Vic?
He's the boss has been for a long time.
Just make it an official blacksmith quickly hammers
something.
The noise makes your head spin.
I'm interested in the North Gate spell.
I make sards not magic.
You want a side baby?
The blacksmith goes over to the rack in the back of his
shop and downs a quick mug of ale.
I'd best do your work be guard and begins to hammer so
loudly.
You fear for your hearing you cook you run you run to
the god damn it.
I wanted that fucking sword.
I wanted the sword 40 gold though.
Come on shard.
We will allow you to rewind.
I don't have the money you walk between the narrow
buildings until you reach a fork to the left the road
continues towards some kind of bustling market while
to the right it leads down a shorter Street in the
center of the fork is a great bronze statue with some
kind of pot at its feet.
Interesting down the short Street looking down the
short Street to the right.
You see a sign above a door reading the gambling halls
of Vlada several seedy looking creatures mill about
on the steps cheerful creatures go in and miserable
looking ones come out the statue the statue is of a
giant brute wielding a club and at its feet is a large
pot filled with gold pieces.
This must be one of car as many gods with the pot
intended for worshippers making offerings.
Although none of the passing creatures seem to be
throwing any in interesting make a move time to move
whoa through the arch the statue the left fork.
I mean there's a lot here.
I want to check out the statue you go over to the
statue and look into the pot seems to contain almost
20 gold pieces.
Look at the statue tilting your head you look upwards
at the statue.
He is an imposing figure at least four times your
height and solidly armed.
You do not recognize the God depicted but his presence
so close to the gambling halls suggest he's either
God of prosperity or God devoted to punishing those
who do not pay their debts.
I ain't taking this shit seems most suspicious so
much gold out in the open.
It must be a trap.
The day is dry.
I'm not touching that.
That's a bad idea bad idea.
And with that ladies and gentlemen, we're going to
call it a day.
That's it much more to explore in Kari.
I think that six hours is good.
My voice is getting a little shot.
I also still have sort of a lingering cough and
congestion.
I don't want to overdo it but you will see this return
where at least going to get through Kari.
So here's the question that I have to ask.
I'm going to put the question here.
Let's see how I'm going to ask the mod something
really quick because I want to see if we're going
to be doing the like God and train going by my head.
Okay.
How are we on the videos?
Do we need any more time?
How are we doing?
We need some more time dork.
You need to look up.
Oh, oh whoops.
All right guys tomorrow night tomorrow evening
green screen movie night is tomorrow Sunday evening,
but we'll see you tomorrow.
The time we will be starting.
I want to do it in the evening hours.
So we're going to start probably around not too too
late maybe four o'clock Pacific.
I think that's a good I don't want to do it at like
seven eight nine ten or anything.
We'll start at four.
I am going to try to make sure this internet doesn't
have a problem and I will tell you right now.
This is very very important.
It's planned for tomorrow.
But if if we have a bunch of drop frames, I don't
want to ruin that stream with drop frames because
this one is fine.
If I have an ingest twitch server problem with this
game, it's literally it's a you were reading.
So if if I have to move it I'm going to so just be
aware that it's planned for tomorrow at four, but
I don't want to get that stream fucked up or ruined
by shitty internet problems.
So let me just make sure that we're going to be
okay before we actually do that stream.
So yeah, we'll start at four tomorrow.
If not, if I'm like, I'm not confident.
I want to see if I can get this spell fixed or
solved before the next stream and we will do it on
probably maybe Monday or Monday or Tuesday, maybe
Monday or we'll hold it to the next weekend.
I'm not in a rush, right?
I'm not in a rush or p.m.
Pacific.
Yeah, that's sorcery.
I hope you guys enjoy it.
I if you guys have been having fun cherish it
because this is and when I say cherish it, I mean
really do because when it's over, I'm not going
to be playing this ever again on stream.
I'm cherishing it right now.
If you think that this is a big game and there's a
lot to do which obviously we didn't do a ton of
stuff over here and there's things that you'll see
later.
This is part two part three is potentially even a
little bit bigger than this is more to it.
Essentially.
This is a huge game part three is a whole nother
map.
That's about maybe one and a half times the size part
four is probably the size of car and look if I
don't play through part three, maybe you'll get it
and jump in and have fun with it because seriously
it's one of the best it's just fun to fuck around
and all the spells do different things.
There's so many different routes.
You can take so many items to collect.
It's just a fun time.
It just really is genuinely a fun experience.
But yeah, we'll see what we're going to at least
at the very least complete car and see how people
feel.
Why wouldn't you play three and four?
There's no reason not to but obviously I don't want
people to get bored of it, which it doesn't seem
like that's happened so far.
So let's go.
All right.
I'll see you guys tomorrow tentatively keep an eye
on the sus when I get up tomorrow morning.
I'm going to do some more tests and you will buy
buy like one or two o'clock in the afternoon Pacific
tomorrow.
You will know if we're going to move the green
screen stream or not.
All right guys.
See you later.
Thank you again.
I got to figure out why this keeps happening.
I'm going to talk to twitch about it.
I think and just be like, hey, how come my internet
is perfectly fine?
But sometimes I maybe once every week or two I have
to like jump.
I have to server hop to find the right one.
That's not going to drop like 10,000 frames over
the course of an evening because this is a new
thing.
This keeps happening and it's weird because I will
run speed test and I will run a whole dedicated
test stream to these exact same servers and still
run into problems.
It's weird.
It's not it's not a net.
I don't think it's a network card problem or a
network problem considering I had a broadcast on
OBS to these same servers on Twitch.
I don't get it.
I might try what I'm going to try to stream to an
East Coast server and see how it happens.
But yeah, well figure it out tentatively.
See you tomorrow.
At least we know that the green screen stuff is
ready and I'm I can't wait check the sauce tomorrow
around like one or two o'clock in the afternoon
Pacific because I want to make sure it's ready.
We will see it soon.
No VOD.
I'm going to do that literally right now.
Here we go.
Publish.
All right, when this when this stream turns off in
probably 60 to 70 seconds, they will be a VOD will
be there because I have the ability to publish it.
All right.
Good night guys.
Take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching.
See you soon.