Uh oh. Already? I just... I just started. Why would I be doing this?
Let's hope that was just a little bump. Weird, but anyways, hi guys.
It's a clay... ooh. Uh oh. Classic Jerma stream, yeah. Well, hi everybody.
I'm back. Just waiting to see if this is... I might have to change
Twitch servers again. Am I gonna have to do that? I probably will.
Oh, this is really bad. What a good comeback after
a week of not streaming. And we got a lot to talk about too.
But anyways, hi. Uh, I have returned from about eight days of being absent.
Got a lot to talk about. There's a lot to do.
And hopefully we can straighten out the internet here for a minute.
Any news on the work that blored out? There's a lot of news. We got...
This stream is not even gonna be a stream. This is gonna be like a
news broadcast. So welcome back to the non-stream.
And I want to play this game Space Engine because it's kind of one of those
experiences where you just can travel the universe.
So we can talk, travel the universe. I'm ready. What's wrong with Space Engine?
Is it bad? I heard it was pretty good. This was
highly requested. It was in the Jerma985 Discord
recommended channel. So I mean, come on. You don't think
that I'd look at that? Anyways, before we really get started,
there's a few things that need to be said.
First of all, God, I love you. Can we just say that?
I gotta like, I gotta soften the blow here. You know,
you're just fantastic. Hold on, did you do something with
your hair? It looks different today. I like it. It looks good.
Wait, did you get an A plus? Good. Good. If you got a B, that's fine
too. I don't care. As long as you try.
All right, now that I softened the blow, I softened you a little bit.
All right, here we go. Over the next two months or so,
I am going to be dialing back streams. Instead of four days a week,
probably going to be more like two or three days a week
for the next couple of months. And I'll tell you why.
The carnival stream, if you don't know what that is,
is pretty much getting into full motion here.
And this stream is going to be the biggest thing I've ever done.
And it's going to happen before the end of September.
We are trying our hardest. This is not going to be just a little
dunk tank stream. This is going to be an incredibly elaborate experience.
So I gotta put the time in necessary to get it done.
And there's a lot of potential travel back and forth from a few places
that I may or may not have to do over the next couple of months.
But streams are going to be, essentially I'm going to be splitting
time between live streaming and working on this project.
Because I'm going full speed ahead. As of like this next week,
I'm going to try to go full speed ahead, whatever it takes.
Also, also the green screen encore night is Saturday.
For those of you that don't know, we've been talking about it for a few weeks.
If you have something ready, there is a form
that you have to submit your video to. This is happening on Saturday, so if
you got something, you got to submit it here.
Please use this form to submit your green screen
encore video. It is not, oh video, I swallowed my tongue there.
That was like video it. I was just like fucking puked.
That was weird. Anyways, so when you submit your
green screen, I haven't been on stream for like a week, come on.
When you submit your green screen video, keep in mind it has to be
under three minutes. Try to get it under three minutes.
We are making exceptions for some pieces of content.
But for the main part, don't like just throw up like a 30 minute video.
It's not going to be shown. Also, not every video is going to be
shown. Instead of this being a six to seven
hour, almost every submission is accepted,
we're going to take like the top submissions, ones that the mod team
and me, I'll be involved in this process as well, we'll be picking them.
So we really want this to be just like an encore presentation with some
of the really good ones and not like a 400 video,
seven hour live stream. So I'm, when I say I'm involved too,
I'm not going to watch every single video before the stream, but we're
talking like if there's a case where I need to come in and take a look,
the mods are going to do a really good job of sifting through
whatever is submitted. Get your submission in
before tomorrow night. Try. If you don't get it done and it's like
Saturday morning and you're like just finishing something,
then you can still submit it. I think we don't really have
a hard, hard limit, but if you don't get your submission in by like Friday night,
Saturday morning, it's not going to happen. You know
what I'm saying? It just isn't. There's just no way we're going to be able to
get it in there that quickly. And this is not designed to be like
a scenario where, oh, hurry up and make something crazy. This is just for
if you had something already, if something was already done, or if
you were working on something and you didn't finish it, or you had a
couple videos, or one video. That's what this is for. This is
not another full-on movie night. It's an extra
night, if you know what I'm saying. And that's Saturday at the regular time.
So today, tomorrow, and into Saturday, we're going to do some other stuff.
Mario Maker comes out tomorrow. Mario Maker 2, right?
Maybe we'll play that. But tonight we're going to just play Space Engine
and talk about this stuff. Because there's a lot to talk about.
Wasn't there a third thing? What was the third thing?
What was the third thing? Anybody know what the third thing was? There was a
third thing. Shit. What was the third thing? There
was a third important thing. The carnival fucking twitch place
carnival stream. The fact that streams are going to be
pulled back a little bit over the next couple months.
Encore movie night. No, I'm not pregnant. It'll come to me.
Don't worry. Let's get this on here. And this is a tad loud, so we're
going to turn it down. He's trying. I'm not pregnant. If I'm
pregnant, then I get Disney World. I think that's good. Maybe a little
more. Should we do it at one? I think that's all right. That sounds
okay. We can turn it up. I have no idea what's going to happen in this game. All
I know is we're going to just browse around.
How did you not use... Oh, I was going to read that out loud.
All right. I haven't played it yet, so I don't know what I'm
continuing. I'm going to take you guys to my
house. This is like Google Earth. What planet is this? So this is
Earth? What the fuck happened? What year is this? This is like 2845?
This is all fucking like toxic. Oh, I don't even want to know what the
fuck happened here. Let me look at some of the... How do I
play this game? Is there like a tutorial? Tools? Video capture? Planet
editor? I can make my own planet? I can make like a Minecraft skin?
Wait, I can just go anywhere? I don't need any instructions.
Oh yeah! Interface. Hey, I'll see you in like fucking four hours.
Welcome to Space Engine. This tutorial will introduce you to Space Engine's
interface. There's Earth. What's all the whipped cream,
though? What is that? This is our planet Earth. The table in the upper left
corner of the screen displays various information about the planet, like
radius, length of day, gravity, and so on. Don't minus two me on that. Come
on. That was like kind of funny. It was like a latte.
All right. It was kind of a bad joke, but whatever. Up in the corner of the
screen displays radius, life, organic, multicellular,
marine and terrestrial life, mass, one me, ESI-1, apparent mag, 21
phase, apparent size, 21 degrees by 40, 54 degrees by 47 inches by 62 feet.
Okay. One year is the orbital period. Rotation period is 23 hours 56 minutes.
Age. How old is the Earth? This is 4.5 years.
The Earth is 4.5 years old times 10 times 9. 10 times 9, 10 times.
I don't know. That's like a square root. Gravity, one gram.
The sea's composition of Earth is hydrogen
and salt. The atmosphere is nitrogen, oxygen, and air. The atmospheric pressure
is one atom. The temperature is 15 degrees Celsius.
The greenhouse effect is 33. The number of moons is one. Cool. Okay.
Interesting. If you left click on any visible object on the screen, Space
Engine will select it and displays information about it. Click any star.
Any star. Choose any star. I could choose any car.
Okay. This one. Beetlejuice. Beetlejuice.
Uh-oh. Don't say it a third time. Now you can read info about the newly
selected object. Tiny rotating arrows indicate which object
is selected. It is called selection pointer.
Yeah. Select the Earth again by left clicking on it. All right. So can we go
there? Look at all these toolbars. They have
plenty of useful options, some of which have hotkeys.
Hover the mouse to cursor over any icon to see the hint about its function.
There's a lot of shit going on. Universe map. Solar system browser.
Chart. Star browser. Find object. Is there a star named after me?
You guys remember that scam where you could like name a star
after somebody? Oh, it's called name a star after your
loved one for like an anniversary present. Remember that scam?
Anybody have that done? Like, does anybody have that done so we can find
you? No, I'm not. I'm not a boomer. I remember
hearing those on the radio. When your wife knows that you named
a star after her, she will be so happy when your
husband comes in after a long day of work and you tell him that you
named him after what is effectively a fucking crumb
in the sky out of trillions of them. He's gonna be so
happy with you. Alright, spacecraft manager. I don't have one.
Journey. Log. Locations. Display. I don't want to do that. What if it shows
where I am? Settings. Is that gonna do like a
google flag at like my house? I'm scared to press this.
This is like a video player. Spacecraft mode.
Aircraft mode. Okay, this is like kind of cool. Alright,
so there's a lot of functions here. High dynamic range. The left toolbar,
also called the main toolbar, gives you access to all basic functions of
space. Clicking on any icon opens a special dialogue window. Click, for
example, this blinking icon. Is that gonna show my location? So you
can see everything about earth. Physical. This is cool.
You don't flash me. You may rotate the planet preview in the wiki
windows by holding the left or right mouse button and dragging your mouse.
Try this now. What happened to the back of the
earth? It's like this is like torched. What
happened? Wiki also informs you if the
selected object is real or not. Space engine has thousands of real
objects and billions of billions of procedurally generated by programs.
Objects in the uncharted regions of the universe.
This line can help you identify the object,
the type of object. So this is a real earth.
Does that mean there's a fake earth? Click the gear icon. It opens the
settings menu. Yeah, almost everything you can
configure. The settings menu has multiple tabs, each of which groups
settings by their uses. Graphics. Yeah, graphics. You can
tweak anything else. Simulations such as visual style,
depending on your taste using other tabs. Bottom left toolbar also called
navigation toolbar shows movement anytime.
As useful options such as flying automatically to a selected object.
Sick. Change in free flight speed and setting date. All icons on this
toolbar act immediately, i.e. don't open any dialogue
windows. All right. Sick. So this is like traveling and
speed and sound. The bottom right toolbar is also called the camera
toolbar. Has an options to change the overall
scene brightness. Exposure. Sick. And the limiting stellar magnitude of
galaxies, stars, and planets. It also controls the current field of
view. Oh, that's kind of cool. What's this one?
What do these fireworks do? Increase magnitude.
Magnitude. Wait, is this gonna like this? Is this gravity? Am I gonna like
fucking implode the earth? What does that mean? What does that do?
Is this gonna start like morphing, breaking, and ripping apart?
I don't want to do it. Filters has an option to hide and show some types of
objects. And okay, this is the filtering objects.
For example, you may hide stars to observe the Milky Way or hide clouds
on a planet to observe its surface. Hide galaxies. Hide stars. Oh.
Hide clusters. Hide nebula. Planets. This is so cool. Hide water. What
happened? Oh, what happened? Where did the
water go? Okay, I'm just realizing that was like as if you guys were
like three. You guys, I've been hanging, let me tell you
something, I've been hanging out with a lot of children
over the last week. So I saw my family, nieces and nephews, and like that's
funny to them. Like if I were to get rid of the water,
well where'd the water go? Like so there's gonna be some like kid humor
today. So I've been, I think my nieces and nephews like thought that
just think that kind of shit is funny.
So sorry. That's not gonna happen though. Let's get the clouds back here.
Well, without the clouds, this really looks like dumb.
Oh clouds. Without the clouds, the atmosphere,
any comet trails, any uh auras or yeah this looks like stupid without
like all this cool stuff on it. Wow what a boring shit planet. I want
to move. You know what I'm saying? All right, that's cool. For example, this
icon toggles the displaying of constellations. Click it now, although you
can also press x. Constellations. Oh I gotta find me. I gotta
find me. Where am I? What are these constellations?
Octans? Mensa? Chameleon? This is a chameleon constellation, is there?
There's a puppy? Where's me? I don't, I want to find me.
Phoenix? Arizona? I don't think Phoenix is that way.
Capricorn? Sagittarius? Where is my character? Hercules?
There's a, I don't, there's no, is a Hercules constellation?
Is it booty? Ursa Minor? Where's Ursa Major?
Okay, this is freaking me out. Where is my character? Dude,
I saw a fucking pretty sick game. Make a fighting game
with all the constellations. I said it first so if anybody does it I get 10%
of all the revenue. All right, I have no idea what my,
what my character is. So we're just gonna move on.
Constellation Battle Royale. Now I don't know where it is.
Oh well. Wait. Where's the Earth? What happened to the Earth?
Oh there it is. Oh thank god. Imagine being in like a spaceship
and you go up there you're an astronaut and just spinning around with like a
camera looking around. Where the fuck did it go?
I don't know where it is. Hopefully we just turn us around a little.
Okay you can unlock the main toolbar by ticking the small
pin in the bottom corner. It is blinking red to help you spot it.
So these little pins here. Now if you move the mouse it will go away.
That's cool. So they come back when you get close enough. Cool.
Let's do it to all of them. All right, this is pretty cool. You can
click the pin icon and keeps it there. Two bottom toolbars have a half hide or
half lock option. Tick the pin icon on the navigation
toolbar and see what will happen. Isn't that what I just did? Navigation
is down here. Now if you move mouse away from the
toolbar it'll hide only the bottom half,
leaving only essential information such as the current time visible. Okay what
so what time is it? 12? 18? 17? I want 12 hour.
I can't read that. I don't know what that means. Now hide it completely
by ticking the pin again. Cool. All right now we're going to
learn how to navigate space. Are you guys ready for like
look at this shit? Yeah you won't be here all day.
Streamer can't read a clock. I just don't do 24 hour time.
This tutorial will teach you basic controls and navigation. Okay I'm
going to do this real quick. Here we go.
You may look around using the mouse by left drag. Okay.
Look around by left drag. Hold that button and move the mouse.
It's kind of takes some. So that'd be being. So that'd take that long.
I guess I am in space right? What about right click?
DPI? No look at this. Okay is it my FOV? Go to my. I'm gonna take
you guys to my house. I promise once I get an opportunity.
You have aircraft movement on. It's dull.
What? Are you sure? Oh Jesus. Um how do I turn them off? Spacecraft
mode? I mean I clearly know how to move the left
mouse. I know how to do this. Can I get another tutorial here?
I have to stay in free flight mode. Free mode.
This is free mode. What the hell is going on?
Did you notice the sun? Turn around to see it. The sun is highlighted with
the selection pointer which we viewed in the previous
tutorial. If an object is outside the screen's edge the indicator arrows
will move in that direction of the object. Move your view towards the
arrow to get that. Wow I don't look right at the sun.
Did somebody give a hundred dollars? Holy shit somebody gave a hundred bucks like
five minutes ago. First let me look at the sun and
hurt myself. How long can you do it for? How long
can you do it for? One. Two. Three. Four. Ow! I did it for
four seconds. But our Tingy. Thank you Tingy for the
hundred bucks. Child humor. It's doing more kid humor.
Hey you want to know how to do kid humor? Here you go.
Here's the foolproof way to make any kid laugh. Did you get hurt? That's it.
That's pretty much all you need to do. Did you get hurt or did you surprise
them? That's it. Like if I walk and like
and like oh I bumped my knee. Oh ow! It's like
that was not a kid. That was I don't know what that was.
I don't know what that was supposed to be. That was not a kid.
Anyways Tingy. That was an imp. That was a fucking goblin. Thank you for the
hundred dollars Tingy. But thank you. Hundred bucks came in.
May sound like a broken record by now but your streams are such an escape
from reality. For a while I've been struggling with
anxiety and these past two weeks have been unfortunately hell.
Currently on antidepressants but I have to be honest your streams are
the most effective antidepressants there is.
Even when you're not live it's just a vaude and it's just a vaude.
I can't donate enough to show you how much I appreciate you and everything
that you do. I'm really sorry that you're going
through that shit. Sorry the last couple weeks have not been good
but you say broken record. No I say this too all the time and I
mean it. If you enjoy yourself here and this
can make you feel better and this can make you take you
a load off then that's great. I'm happy that you're able to have a
place here where this is fun. So thank you so
much for the hundred bucks. Let's learn how to fucking drive a
car. Now this is the uh yeah I got this one.
Don't don't step in the poison. Okay you can do that at any time to explore an
object from all sides. By dragging mouse vertically while
holding you can left and right. Uh wait a minute wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait by dragging mouse vertically while holding both
the mouse buttons you go okay got it. More kid humor today. Okay try to
zoom and that was a noise right? That was just a noise.
Stop the kid humor. I can't help it. This is all I've been doing for
eight days. That's not true. Like the last three or four days were like
working on this project but like five days before
that it was all kid humor. This is the same every stream. Is it?
No it's not. Do I do kid humor on the stream? Okay that's cool.
Try to zoom out from the earth. Good now we'll learn other basic
navigation. Uh okay did you spot the moon? I
did not see the moon. Where is it? There it is. So I press C or the
blinking and so this is center object. Okay cool. Use it anytime
when you want to find a selected object that you have lost.
Try to select any star and center on it. Uh this is the
y seti. Set no center. And I can just go there too. Now it's
time to go to the moon. Select the moon and hit the G key
for go. G. We are flying to the moon
in real time. Every time I press G I go slow down slow I'm gonna crash
into it. This is the most useful command in space engine. It's called the go to
and you'll use it a lot. You may notice that it works only for selected
objects just like the center command. Okay cool.
Orbit the moon with the right mouse button and drag until you see the earth.
Wow look at that. Notice that orbiting as well as zooming
works relative to the moon. This is because the go to command binds your
controls to the new object. The moon. The name of the currently
bound object displayed on the navigation tool with the following moon.
That's really cool. Sick. You may bind to a different object manually by selecting
it and pressing shift f. So bind to here is shift f. I'm now
bound to the earth. Now you may orbit the earth with the
right drag. Wow. I'm gonna this is gonna be I'll puke
if I keep doing this. Let's return back to earth. Click the
blinking icon on the navigation toolbar. It works like a double press of G.
The fast go to. This is go to object. Nice. Hit
f2 or click the moon the main menu solar system browser.
It shows all the stars planets and moons in the current planetary system.
Left click on a planet to select it. Well we gotta go to jupiter.
Okay so I have jupiter selected. Somebody's asked can I destroy the
earth in this game. Not everything has to be about
destruction and conflict. Okay now I can center that so we're
centered on jupiter. Try this. Select Venus and go to
it. So I want to I want to but I want to go to
jupiter. Venus center on Venus and then go to Venus. This is really
what it's like. That's not what Venus looks like. This
is not Venus. That's not what Venus looks like. I know
what Venus looks like because it's in my chat right now.
Venus is for some reason in this game
it's when you get the defect gumball from the gumball machine that
didn't get any coloring put on it. That's not true. Venus looks like
it's in the chat. Okay you can navigate the solar system browser like folders in
your computer. Double click on any planet which has
moons. What? Does Venus not have a moon?
What? Yeah doesn't. Okay you can also click the satellites icon which
appears on the planet's cell when you hover a mouse over it.
Satellites. Oh wait what about jupiter? Oh isn't it? Okay I
I'm not even looking at the screen. I know the jupiter moons. It's
Callisto, Ganymede, Europa, and Yo right? Yep I got it. You've entered this list of
satellites. You can select any by left clicking to go back double click on the
parent object. That's so cool. All right let's like
center on that. It's easy. Now select Yo the moon of
Jupiter. Double click on Jupiter enter its moons and left click on
Yo. Now that the select is pointing to now fly there using the go to
command. We're going to Yo. Here it comes. Whoa what?
Nice close the solar system browser by hitting F2 or prison the eye. Yeah F2
you can close the solar system browser. Let's go to Saturn. You can find it by
using the solar system browser or by the search tool.
Saturn. There it is center. Just take a look where it is.
Go to Saturn. By the way you think this is the the whole game?
I've got an extreme news for you. No you can land on any planet you
want and explore it. This is not just like look at the
planet simulator. Any of these planets can be it's like
what's that game? Once again that guy was on all the late
night tv shows talking about how it was like the greatest thing ever
and it wasn't the greatest thing ever at all and then like three years
later they like made it really good. No man's sky that's what it is okay.
Show us your house. I've got to learn how to play.
All right I'm on Saturn. Click the lens icon. Yeah it wants me to
search. Parents, son, asteroid. All right hold on.
Damn it. Nobody named a star after me? All right dude how many of these
are actually oh is it like a you have to think there's gonna be
because they had that like star registry thing.
Big Bits just came in right now. Big Bits, Big Bits, Big Bits. I got it. I
got it. I got it. The Diabeetles just gave 100 bucks. 200
dollars back to back here. Thanks guys.
Thank you Diabeetles for the 100 bucks and they say hey Jerma things have been
pretty rough lately. I recently separated from my fiance and
it just seems like things were getting worse from there.
I'm fucking sorry to hear that but even at my lowest I could go back to
your videos or watch your streams and you've always given me a reason to
laugh. Going back to therapy and I'm making
changes to make my life better. Just wanted to thank you. I've been
watching since 2012 and I always could come to you for a
laugh. I'm happy that you're taking some necessary steps here to
take care of yourself. Making some changes. Going to therapy.
I wish you the best of luck. I'm really sorry to fucking hear that. That's
that sucks. But keep your head up because
I'm not sure how old you are but I really do truly wish you the best
because that's tough. Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for watching the
videos and the streams for that long. Glad you have a good time.
Look at all these. Look at all these Jerma hearts in the chat. That
makes me feel good. It does. All right. How about just
like John? Yeah. Johnson. This is absolutely
somebody's star registry name. How about like I don't know somebody has to have
some like like I don't know like Gandalf right?
No. I don't know like Da Vinci? Did like did Leonardo Da Vinci have a
star named after him? No. Was that just a scam? I don't think
it even did anything. All right well we have to find Saturn.
There it is. Saturn 1. Saturn 2. Saturn 3.
Saturn 4. Saturn 9. Saturn L.
What does that mean? Saturn L3? How many Saturns are there?
Okay let's go to Saturn. Saturn. No Saturn.
I'm gonna click okay. Perfect. To consolidate the knowledge go to Mars.
Find it using the solar system browser. Yeah we can just go Mars.
There it is. Hey how many Marses are there?
Oh yeah I want to go. Go to. There it is. That's not even what Mars looks like.
Somebody put Mars here please. Actually yeah it is. All right now we're gonna
learn how to fly. We're almost done. All right I'm not
gonna make any more jokes. I'm just gonna blow through the
tutorial so just put on like your favorite song
and I mean I recommend. I don't know. Put on like church music or something. Who cares?
All right I'm gonna go. Just don't pay attention to me anymore.
I'm just gonna do the tutorial and we're gonna go.
Advanced movement control space. Basic controls. Yeah yeah moving around like this and that.
Clicking outside the solar system. Okay find the planet.
Go find the planet Trappist. Okay let's get that open.
Trappist. Trappist 1G. F E F G. Okay then let's get out. Let's get
over there. Go to. Oh this is cool. Wait what? Did I go too fast?
Oh boy. Alien ice icy planet almost 40 light years away from Earth.
Now we will learn the free movement. The go-to command allows you to quickly
reach the desired object but exploring it is much more
enjoyable using a game like free movement. Press the W key.
Press the W key. It's the funnest word to say in broadcasting.
Once you learn how to say W it becomes so much fun for you to do.
W W W W W W W W W W W. It's so. Once you go to
broadcasting school you'll learn it. It's fun.
You did this joke before. No I didn't. No I didn't. No I didn't.
All right I gotta fucking calm down. You may move in multiple directions.
R and F is up and down. Okay cool. A D W S R F.
Yep. W and then S to fly forward and backward. Yep.
A and D left and right. Yep. R and F to go
rup and then found. You may change the flight direction with the mouse.
Press W to fly forward and then. Remember these two key keys. Q and E.
They change your roll. Whoa. All right. What kid joke.
Now try to reach the waypoint. Come on like Superman 64.
Adjust your velocity with the mouse wheel with the plus and minus keys.
Now depending on how funny you are this stream you will go faster or
slower. Scroll the wheel up. Press the
plus key to increase to 1000 kilometers a second. Perfect. Now you
can reach the waypoint quicker. This is another indicator that shows your
current velocity. It is zero while standing and equal to
the assigned velocity while moving. Reach the waypoint.
Okay. Good. Proceed to the next waypoint. The selection pointer will help you
locate it. Try this. Whoa. Slowly descend on the
planet surface. This is Superman 64 and then we're
going to land on the planet. Remember Q R E. Two waypoints left.
This is the surface of the universe. One less
surface. Here it is. Look at this shit. Are they aliens?
All right. I made it. We are on the surface now. Note
that if you hit the ground your velocity will be flat.
Fly to the green waypoint ahead and explore the terrain. Explore the
planet. Depending on your computer speed
terrain may take a while to load. I got a pretty fast computer speed.
Cool. Free flight is easy isn't it? Now let's return to space. Just fly
into the sky away from the planet or use the R key to fly straight up.
Increase your speed to 100 to 200 kilometers a second with the mouse
wheel to do that faster. Whoa. I'll never dig straight up.
That's pretty cool. Great. We're in space again. You also may use the go
to command to fly to a default distance from the planet.
Go to object. Ah okay. You can land on a planet automatically
shift G on any planet to do that. How fast? But that's fast. Wow. Another
way to land on a planet or exit to space is using the zoom.
Hold both the left and right buttons and drag the mouse vertically.
Note that this works with the current bound object.
Oh interesting. Yep. It works. Okay. Now you know the basics of the free
flight in space engine. You can explore anything with it. Not only
planets. Simply increase your velocity to some unimaginable value and fly to
interstellar space. Not yet. Not yet. Okay. Let's just get back out.
So is that it? Do I now know how to play? All right. Let's go.
Where should I go? Where am I? Whoa. 10. Set the velocity of 10 light years
a second. That's too fast. C's? How many C's?
What's the C mean? A U is a second. That's a that is
you go over the course of Australia in a second. That's how much terrain that is.
This is a thousand Australias a second. One. Okay. Now one light year a second.
10 light years a second. Is this gonna hurt? I feel like this is gonna be
scary. You may approach any star and enter its planetary system.
Fly to Betelgeuse. It is highlighted with the selection pointer. Aim the
camera towards it and press W to fly forward. Heading towards Betelgeuse.
Now that's the third time? No. It's okay. It's okay.
Betelgeuse is dead. So it's okay. I didn't have I didn't have it cued up.
But he's like a demon. He's gone. He was like purged
fucking a million years ago. Okay. Hold on.
Slow down. What is this? Hey no. Too fast.
Get over there. 778 Australias a second. That sounds good.
Center on you. You're now entering the planetary system. Small dots near
the star are its planets. Approach the star so you can see its
surface. Oh. Oh it's gold. It means gold. AU is gold. It's gold.
That's what it is. Wow. That was fun. Okay this is Betelgeuse.
One of the brightest stars in the constellation of Orion.
A red supergiant. It looks lumpy because of very weak gravity on its
surface which is barely maintaining the gas in its place.
Now look at the filters toolbar. Click the blinking icon to show orbital
paths of planets. Oh that's cool. You can see like
where the rotations are for oops. Where did I go? Shit.
Where? Hold on. Where was it? Oh shit it's it's it's lost in the crumbs.
Oh fuck. Hold on. There it is. Oh okay now I'm orbiting this. I get it.
Okay all right. Orbits of planets will help you with
visual navigation in the planetary system. Planets are shining dots at the
bright ends of lines. Try to reach any planet. Oh I didn't
turn color. Now try to reach any planet manually
What's going on? What's going on? What's happening? What?
Okay I have to slow down. So I need to fly into a planet that's orbiting.
Let's go down here. There it is. We got to go faster than
this. 285 Celsius. Right here. This one. What is this one?
Betelgeuse 2. Let's fly to it. This one looks cool. Wait a minute. Hold on.
There's more in here? Betelgeuse 2 has its own life system.
Its own solar system. Orbits of planets.
Perfect. Now that you know how to explore the universe in free flight mode, next
tutorial will teach you how to manipulate time flow.
Wait a minute. Where'd I just go? I just like sucked into it.
Shit. Get up. Up. Go up. Okay I want to turn off like the gas.
I'm on the surface. Whoa no I'm not. Holy shit.
All right I'm out. Okay now we can do time.
Look we're getting close. There it is. All right.
The navigation toolbar has all the options for time control. Some of which
have their own hotkey. The blinking element is the date bar.
It displays the current simulation date and time. I can't wait to see what
Las Vegas looks like when it was like two million years ago.
It may differ from the real date because in space engine you're free
in space and time. Cool. Right. Whatever. The buttons below the
date bar control time flow. You can speed up and slow down the
time, reverse it, and reset it to the current date based on the system
clock. Speed up the time to see space bodies in movement. Press the L key
to speed up the flow to times 10. Selection pointer. Disabled. What?
Planet Shine. Disabled. What? What are you talking about? L key.
Am I missing something here? Press the L key or this button
twice. What's going on here? Did I mess something up?
Shift L. Planet Shine. L. Something's going on here.
Now sometimes the game bugs regarding time. Might have to reset it. Hold on.
Let's try this. Oh there we go. Times 10. I lost my
tutorial though. This is just times 10 speed but I don't
have my tutorial anymore. I'm lost. Times 100 speed. Times a
thousand. Times 10,000. Times 30,000. Times 5
million. At some point this is going to turn into
like a pottery. It's going to be... Is it burning up on the top?
Stop. Set normal time speed. Okay. I want to get off the ride.
All right. I think I need to see if we can get that back. Okay.
Date and time. Yeah. We can do... We can reverse it.
Times 10 speed. There we go. I'll get it. Times 10.
Continue increasing the time till you get to 3,000.
3,000. Okay. Now press the O key to see the orbits.
You can put on labels. What is that? What does it want me to do?
Oh. You can observe the orbit of motion of the
Galilean moons. O, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto. To make it more
convenient zoom out from Jupiter to 5 million kilometers left plus right
and drag to see now the whole thing. So the
moon's orbits will be seen from the top. Look at the Jupiter info table
for the distance readout. This is cool. Look at how educational
this is. Imagine if you were... Who's sniping Jupiter right now?
Is there something... Is that bad? Okay. Jupiter info table.
The distance readout. Distance readout. What is the orbit here?
Should I have gone out further? 5 million kilometers.
I mean this is 5 million kilometers. Right here is 5 million.
And orbit to its northern pole. I was already there. Now accelerate
time by times 30,000. Oops. Back. This is insane.
Now we will learn all the buttons which it controls the speed of time.
Press the space bar to pause the simulation.
Again, to resume. Kids jokes are costing him this time.
It's all right. It's all right. These kids jokes really. They do very, very
well. These kids jokes do very, very well
during a paused bathroom break of Zootopia. So
I mean come on. All right. Jakey reverses the time
flow. So we're now going in reverse. Reverse time.
That's ridiculous. Note that the simulation date and time displayed in
the date bar are counting backwards. It's 2016 already.
Restore the normal direction. Accelerate time to 3000
by pressing the K key several times. You can put it back to real time
like this. Control slash sets the simulation time
to the current system time. I'll just press it. Okay.
Great. We have now learned time speed controls. Remember the reverse
decelerate, accelerate, set normal, set current. Got it.
You can easily change the simulation date time by clicking the date bar and
typing the desired date. Okay. 2016, period 11,
period 15, 21. Okay. And then hour and minute. Or that's
just fine. And then hit enter. Whoa. Now we will
use your knowledge to catch up to the solar eclipse on Europa. Look at
Europa and accelerate up to 10,000. Pause time with the
space bar when Europa enters the shadow. What shadow? Like over here?
Yeah, like right here. Now slowly accelerate the time
until Europa starts moving. 1000 times is a good value. Once Europa exits
the shadow, reverse the time flow. The moon will start moving back. Wait
until Europa enters the shadow and exits from the opposite side. Then
decrease the speed to minus 100. Almost. Restore the normal time
flow by pressing J. When Europa enters the shadow again, set the time speed to
real time. What? Can I just see it? Can I just like
look at it? Now go to Europa. Europa. Wow, it's
completely black. Reverse the time flow and accelerate it a bit until
Europa exits the shadow. Reverse time flow. And accelerate. No!
Go back. Can I go back? No, no, no. Other way. Other way. Reverse the
flow. Now land to this green point and
watch the sun getting eclipsed by Jupiter. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, stop. Pause it right there. This is as good as it. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop time. Oh, whoa. Oh, cool. Here we go.
Wow. The next tutorial. Guys, I know what we're going to do.
I need people to find events that happen to the solar system.
You know what I mean? When did like an asteroid like explode?
We have to go find the exact day and time of where it was and go
watch it. All right. The next tutorial will
teach you how to use the telescope. We're getting there. Well, we're done.
This is like photo modes. Did you notice the thin lines near Jupiter's
crescent? These are its very faint dusty rings
that are only visible under certain lighting conditions. You may make them
more visible by switching space engine to the realistic photographic mode.
Press the V key. Oh, okay. This is the auto exposure
mode. In this mode space engine renders celestial objects with
physical accurate brightness in attempts to adjust
camera sensitivity or exposure automatically. When you look at a dark
sky it sets it to a human eye sensitivity.
Who cares? You know what I mean? Exposure one.
We'll just display it as exposure one. Yeah, I mean we can make this look cool.
We can take photos. We can zoom in. Yeah, I get it.
I get it. I do. You know what I mean? I get it.
All right, we got it. I don't think the camera mode is something that's
interesting. We can do... I know how to work it.
Photo camera. We got... Notice the value of the exposure display.
Roughly corresponds to the photo camera shutter speed. Oh yeah, something's wrong
here. There we go. Press and hold this, this
to change the exposure value. Yep. You can make it look really, really
blown up and nice and cool. Yeah, this is cool.
All right, I'm ready. I don't think there's anything else I need to do.
Universe map maybe. I kind of want to just browse around for a little
bit. You know what I mean? I'm just going
to go. I want to browse around. So this is
where we are. Where are we? We're at the cold,
airless... Turn up object quality. Where would that be? Visual style?
Lens flare? We'll look at object quality. Filter objects? No, we got
that. That looks good. Graphics? Go to custom.
I'm scared. Should I do... I mean black hole... I feel like this is going to
break my computer. Max the shit out? I can't do that. My
computer's not good enough. I don't got AMD. Maximum graphics. I'm
not going to be able to stream this. High. I'm keeping it on high. No, this is
all right. All right, let's just go. So I want to...
Where's earth? I want to first see how detailed this is.
Where's earth? And where's my search? There it is. Okay,
earth. Right there. Go to earth. Is that the sun?
There we go. All right, so I want to do the current date.
This is what it looks like right now outside your house. Outside your
window when you look. This is what it looks like. Well,
you know what I mean? Like when you're looking down... When you're looking down
out your window if you're in a spacecraft above the earth. This is
what it looked like. So let's go to the United States.
Australia. There's... Is that Africa? No, that's South America. I mean,
that's Brazil. I know what it is. God. Give me a
break guys. You think I'm crazy? All right, let's... I want to make it so
we're like in the... Let's spin it around. I need some light. I want the
sun. I don't want it to be dark. Come to Brazil. I will. I'll go to
Brazil. So we're gonna go see. Okay, maybe a little bit more. Okay,
that looks good. I need to set this as like the object in
rotating the earth. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, shit! I used one of my wishes. Hold on. Should I try to find Las Vegas
from here? All right, I'm gonna try to. Let's
see if I can find my house from the middle of the ocean.
There's no way I'm gonna fucking do this. It's ocean in every direction.
This is 200 miles per hour. I'm essentially a plane.
But hide everything. I don't want any tips. I'm a plane right now.
All right, hold on. The sun... The sun sets in the east and rises in the
west. No, the sun sets and rises in the east,
sets in the west. This is the right way. The home of the rising sun
is east. You can just fly a plane. I'm in the plane right now. Can I do
a different view? Do planes go 2,000 miles per hour?
I don't think planes go fucking 5,000 miles per hour.
No, they don't. They go like 600. Ooh. Acceleration. All right, I need to
find land. Left toolbar for vehicles.
Spacecraft manager? Drunk superman. It's actually kind of
fun to control this because it's really delayed. I just
need to get to land. I think I see land. The sun is
setting in my face. Good luck finding anything. I think I can see land right
here. Is this California? All right, slow down, slow down, slow down.
Wait, no, that's not California. Where's California? I gotta find
California. I'm going so fast. I would have already crossed land by
now, wouldn't I? I'm going east? Wait, did the sun just
rise? Is this rising or is the sun setting? What day is it?
It's setting. All right, so that's fine. Should I put time up a little just
to make sure? Hold on. I'm gonna increase time. Is
that going down? That shit's going up. That's going up. I'm going the
wrong way. Hold on, folks. Am I just in the Pacific
Ocean? Can I see what ocean this is? I'm sorry. I'm trying to get to
Vegas. I went a different route this time.
I decided to go across the whole Pacific Ocean twice.
Normal time. Normal time. Time scale. Use the balloon option. There is no
balloon. Should I swim? What's going on?
Okay, get me in the normal...
Okay. No, that's too fast. How fast can you swim?
I could probably go like, I don't know, 15 miles per hour? 20 miles per hour
swimming? All right, where am I? Can I see like
longitude, latitude? All right, I'm in 35. No, that's time.
Where's longitude, latitude? I need info. I can't even use
wiki. Where's the sun? I have to stare at the sun for a second.
I need to know how... I need... Where's it going? We gotta go that way.
The sun rises in the east, sets in the west. We gotta go... What's going on?
Oh, we gotta go that way. All right, stop.
Okay, normal time scale. Let's go. All right, just imagine that I was in like
a... I don't know, like a sailboat. They
go how fast? Like 60? Okay, now we're in the plane again. Here we go. Let's
go. I'm gonna go faster. This is going
to take you days. No, if you go 2,000 miles per hour,
it's not gonna do that. I'm going so fast right now, like
I'm just gonna get across the ocean. This is 20 fucking thousand, 50,000 miles
per hour. Where's the sun? There it is. 100,000 miles per hour.
Where the fuck is land? I'm almost going a million miles per
hour. Where is land? What the fuck is going on? Is there
no land on earth? I'm going 5 million miles per hour.
Then the oceans are not this big. Wait, wait!
Those clouds? Earth is 75% water. What is that? What's this? What is
this? Found it. But what land? Planet Earth. What continent is
this? I made it. My computer's not good enough
though. All right, let me see. Let me guess where I am.
Yes, I know. I'm aware that this looks like a Minecraft skin. I know.
This is a Minecraft seed. I think, I think I'm in
China. China. I don't know where, where am I?
I was right! I was right! It was pretty close.
I was pretty close. Okay, now I just have to go to Vegas without
guessing. That's Russia? No, it's not. It's China. Okay, here we go.
Let's go to Las Vegas. There ain't nothing here. There's nothing here.
Oh shit. Oh well. It's just the same bitmap image. I wonder, can I like
actually search for Vegas? I don't think they would have like that
kind of shit on here. Why would they have that on here?
Vegas. All right, let's see if I can find... Whoa, easy.
All right, can I... I mean this is like the desert connecting California
to Vegas. Are there any cities? Why would there
be cities? This is a space exploration game. Why
do I care about if there are cities or not?
We can go anywhere in the world. We would just be doing Google Earth. Yeah.
Why would I be doing this? I'm only exploring
Earth. Oh yeah, I have to explore the universe. All right.
What's that? The Andromeda. But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I want to see
something. Hold on. Let's do a once and for all. Once
and for all. Let's see if it's true. So according... I want to see if Pangea
exists. You know what I'm saying? Let's see if it's real. Okay, so we're
gonna go back here. We're gonna reverse time. We're gonna
go back to... How many years?
How many years was Pangea? It's like one?
One. One, one. Yeah, one, one, one. Just one. Let's see what it looks
like. And then we'll do it like, I don't know,
two o'clock. All right, so what we got here?
Ah, fucking Pangea debunked. Why are there
lights? Why are there so much city lights? Okay, so
one ad. Can I do negative time? This is minus ten thousand. Oh, hold on.
There's hundreds of millions. That's not enough. There's no rotation on the
Earth. Why? No, still not connected. The
Earth hasn't spun yet. Oh, there we go. Okay. No, it looks
pretty normal to me. Sorry, guys. All right, give me an event.
How about a comet? What's like a cool comet?
What's a comet that's gone through? Somebody just dumped coordinates into the
chat. And oh yeah, the Andromeda. I want to
check out the Andromeda. Andromeda. It's a galaxy. Let's go to it.
Normal time. Look at this place. All right, let's get it. So there's...
Let's get in the galaxy. Now, what's in here? What's this?
M-110. Oh, fuck. I'm still in 10 minus 10 million BC.
Current time. There we go. And we're on
times one scale. That's fine. You guys ready?
I'm flying at insane speeds. What's in here?
Go right into the center. Hold on, wait. The Andromeda is gonna collide.
Whoa, hold on. Slow down a little. Who the fuck are you?
RS-1235. Let's get some more info on you, please.
This is the one. Found it. Watch the collision. Let's get in there.
All right, let's take a look. White luminous supergiant.
Go find a black hole. I'm gonna try, but let me... I want to get onto this
planet. I want to see what it's like on here.
Increase the mag limit. What does that do?
I didn't do the tutorial for this. What does this mean? Why? What's... Why? What's
going on with all the things in the background here?
That's all stars. All right, let's get onto the surface.
It can't be this bright on the surface, right? Holy shit, this is cool.
Imagine being able to stand here. How much did you pay to do this?
Press V. What's all these, like, divots and grooves and shit?
I want to get off of this. How do I let go?
V. Oh, photo mode was on the whole time. All right, let's get closer.
Can I take samples? Why can I take a sample? And why can't I
leave? How do I, like, deselect this planet? G? Shift?
F? I want to just fly around. Free mode here. Come on.
Free mode. F. I can't leave. What, is this place just huge?
Oh, fuck. It's that big. Oh, I get it. I feel like I'm crawling across
somebody's skin. It's a supergiant. Well, that's...
Who cares? I'm gonna go this way. What do you guys want to see?
The explosion between... Ooh, that's cool. Is that what they look like?
All right. And the Andromeda and... When did it happen?
When did the Andromeda crash? It's not in the game. Oh.
But look at that. Okay, what is this? This is a moon?
Oh, this is a planet. This is a star. This is a planet.
Go look at a black hole. I gotta find one. Hold on. I just got, like...
I just got, like, a shotgun blasted in, like, Overwatch
in the face. Slow down. I'm playing Overwatch.
That was... That wasn't... I wasn't making a kid joke. I was making, like, a...
That's what it felt like. I felt like I just got shot by, like, a
video game shotgun. What is this? This is called
Torrid Arid Super Terra. Whoa. That's a photo right there. Hold on.
That's a photo mode. The giant egg. The giant, like,
golden egg. I gotta get in a good spot for this.
Over here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Hurry. Go, go, go, go, go. Right
here. On the ground. Photo mode. Let's go.
Oh, Jesus. Slow down. Why is it so bright?
That's kind of ominous. All right, here we go. No. No, no, no. Go back.
No! Oh, what have I done? That's fine. Right there.
Drop the magnitude a little bit. Right there. All right. Take it.
Got it. You want to see it orbit. Okay, fine. I can do that.
There it goes. I feel like I'm watching slow-mo a basketball go into
a hoop. I'm gonna pull out. There you go.
You can see its path here. This is cool. This is awesome.
Just get, like, eyes on this. It's kind of cool. All right, back to normal.
All right, let's go. I want to go somewhere else. I want to find a black hole.
They're both 3,500 degrees. Look for 55
cankri. A super earth made out of diamonds.
Wait, what? A super earth made out of diamonds.
What do you say it was called? Cankri? I don't think it's here.
Diana. 55 can... 55 cankri. No, it's not here.
Wait, there it is! 55 cankri right here. All right, did you tell me this is
made out of diamonds? That would be pretty crazy if it was.
Hold on. Orange dwarf. It is 5... 5,200 degrees.
Kelvin. This thing's millions of years old. That's the star. So where's the...
So this is 55 cankri Janssen. This is a planet. Is this it?
55 cankri E. This thing isn't made out of diamonds.
I mean, it looks like it's made out of wood. Let's land on it. Let's go.
I can't see shit. Am I on the planet? Oh, it's a photo!
It's because there's toxic fumes everywhere. All right, let me turn off the toxic
fumes. Atmospheres, nebula, clusters,
stars. Turn them all off. Turn off water. Turn off aurora.
Turn off planets. No, turn off comet tails. Turn off galaxies. Turn off
spacecraft. Turn on spacecraft. I mean, it looks pretty cool.
This one's cool. I need to turn this shit back on.
Comet tails, clouds, water, aurora. Any orbits there? There are. Okay, cool.
This thing's purple. This thing's nice. Turn on the HD. Look at that.
Is that happening right now? Is it happening right now? Hold on. Pause. Is
it happening right now? I'm gonna have a dozen desktop
backgrounds by the time this is done. Sell them. Sell them on like a
royalty-free website. That would mean they were free. All right, hold on. What
about... Check. I want to see the blue one. The
atmospheres are off. They shouldn't be. Oh, they are. You're right. But now we
can't see like the cool blue. What's this up here? Why is there a
ring up here? What is that for? That's magnetic field. That's kind of scary.
Kitchen. How is that a kitchen? Right there. Bingo.
Get one. Earth has one of those? That's interesting. All right, I want to
look... Where is... Let me go over here. Hold on. I want to find a
comet. What's like a popular one? What's like a cool one?
Haley's comet? Black hole. The Black Widow?
We gotta go see where the Black Widow is. Holy, this is a million... Jesus.
What is that? This is bright. I can't even get away from it.
It's peering into my soul. Is this temperature like
20-50 million degrees or something? Wow.
That's really cool looking. Turn all that shit off. Hold on. I can't even
turn it off. It's too bright. This is a neutron star. This is a black hole.
But what is it doing? Can I land on it? This is freaking me out.
The time is changing around it. Can I land on here? I'm gonna do this
gentle. Close your eyes. What happens if I go through this?
Well, I'm on it. This is it. Turn the mag down?
Should be reset, right? It's just ice. Ow.
All right. Hold on. Two million degrees. Don't you guys know when something's
so cold it becomes so hot? If something is like
negative 50 million degrees, it's gonna burn you. It's hot.
That's true. Hold on. I want to go to... Let's go to a nebula.
What about like, Warcraft names? There's gotta be like a thrall, right?
Damn it. Thrall? How about like, Zul'jin?
No. Jaraxxus? We're gonna find one. Come on. Come on.
How would I know these Warcraft names? Sagittarius.
All right, let's go. Holy shit. Should I go into that?
I got a good photo of this. That's so insane that this shit exists.
Oh, no. That's ingrown. That's ingrown. You're gonna have to just get tweezers to
get that one out. Nah, I can't help you there. You're
gonna have to go to a doctor, man. Negative 566. Give me a break.
Oh, give me a fucking break. What? I've made like three jokes. Oh, that's
bright. I gotta get the fuck away from
this. Whoa. Okay, that's cool. It's like a
lightning bolt going through this thing. That's crazy.
Land? Is this shit gonna start absorbing planets
and stars and stuff? That's crazy. All right, this actually is a perfect
home run. Right here. That looks great. I think that's the background
right there. I'm gonna land in it. I'm gonna turn
the exposure down. I'm going in. Let's see what happens. Wish me luck. I
think it actually is like sucking me in.
It just sucked me in. Where do I go? Can I leave?
Where the hell am I? What? This is Sagittarius A?
I'm following Sagittarius A. Oh, no. I clicked. I must have. I clicked
something else. No. Well, I got the photo. Yeah, go to.
What the hell? Go back out. Go back. No, no. Back out. Go back out. I want to see
that again. Go back out. That was potentially even
cooler than when I came in. What's this one?
Any of these have names? What? What do you mean the Milky Way?
That's a Milky Way? Oh, is it not? Is this the Milky Way?
This is the Milky Way? This is our galaxy.
I thought we were in a different galaxy. Blue main sequence star.
There it is. How far can I go out? I'll turn down the magnitude a little bit.
How much can I go? There's the Milky Way right there.
What happens when you go to the end? There can't be this many things, right?
No, there's no way. There's no way. How?
These are all galaxies. No, there's no way. If this is true,
no, if this is true, then we're actually like bugs in a petri dish.
All this shit? No, somebody sneezed and they scooped it up and put it under
a microscope and we just happened to be one of these.
Look at this shit. Let's go to this one. Look at this red one.
We're going to go to this red one. This is right here. What is this one?
Infinite galaxies. Somewhere on some computer is somebody else
playing this same game and he came across. No, he's not. He's not going
to come across Earth ever. That's not possible. Aliens? How come
aliens haven't found us yet? Oh, I don't know. Why do you think?
It's the equivalent of getting rained on outside. You know, if aliens existed,
they would have already found us. Oh, really? Wouldn't they have?
This is a blizzard. Can you pick me out one individual snowflake that's going
by right now? You know, they would have had some
means of communication. You think that some aliens would
have some means of communication? You think so.
You know the telephone was invented like fucking like 70 years ago, right?
And we can only talk to like other assholes on this planet.
You know how long this shit would take? Well, some of them have been around.
I guarantee you some of them don't even have a damn telephone. They still
scream at each other out their windows in alien space.
Why do we have this weird fantasy world that aliens have technology that
can make a cell phone call like 500 trillion light years away?
You lose cell phone coverage when you go through a tunnel.
And we are literally seen as like the most advanced fucking species on our
planet. You think somebody else is going
to have better technology? No fucking way. He knows too much.
What is this? All right, this is the one. This is Galaxy RG 06229807.
Well, let's get in there. Let me in there. I can't get in here?
Increase the brightness? Are there no planets in this galaxy?
There's nothing even here. It's just gas and hairspray.
I wonder why we haven't had a fucking phone call from Dave the Alien.
There's no gas out here. There's nobody out here. Wait, hold on.
This is a star. Cut his mic. Cut his mic. Imagine being on one of these planets
though. That would suck. Look at how shitty this
fucking planet is. Imagine you lived here. This is the
equivalent of living like in the middle of Nebraska.
There ain't nothing cool here. Come on, fly there. I'm pressing G.
Can I not go to this one? Oh, it's because I'm not going fast enough.
Oh, this one's pretty. Okay, why can't I move? Dude, look at this thing.
This thing sucks. How hot is it here? Caramel popcorn. These are parts of space
that are so far away that everything looks like a single star.
I can't wait for the fucking alien to get here because it's not going to be
like, here they come on their spaceships
and they have they have space rifles. No, it's going to be one alien is
going to accidentally fucking press the wrong button and he's going to
have like a Tom Hanks beard and he's going to fall out of his
space boat. And he's not going to be able to talk to him.
And guys, this already probably happened.
The government like vacuumed out his brain and just like looked at it under a
fucking computer screen. This already happened. Cut his mic.
That is a kind of cool looking planet though. It's not even that's a
star on a planet. All right, hold on. Let's get the gas
back here. All right, where's like the New
York City of this galaxy? Because that ain't it. Where is it?
Let's turn on the little thing here to show us. Detail. Let's see.
Give us some detail. It's a star. I know I'm looking for a planet.
All right, get this off. The government has made
video games about aliens. We also have this weird
picture of what is that? I'm going there. We have this like strange
picture of what aliens look like. They probably,
for there to be aliens that exist too. I think I just found the fucking New
York City. What the? Look at that. Is this a star?
That is a star and this is a star. Boring. Oh, nice galaxy you got here.
You got two street lamps. Where's the cool shit? What's that?
Warm super Jupiter. Wait, you get a super Jupiter here? Hold on.
They have a super Jupiter. I'll be the judge of that.
All right, that's pretty. Whoa. Quick, quick, quick, quick. Take it.
Take it like right now. Take it right now. Take it right now. Go, go, go, go, go.
That looks awesome. I can't wait. We're gonna go over these at the end of the
stream. Oh, oh, oh, oh. Check this shit out. Come on,
give me control. Hold on. Oh, yeah, we got it.
Oh, here are there. Here we go. Orange super giant.
Dwarf moon. What does that mean? Look at. Wow, I was wrong.
I had my GPS wasn't on right. It's an asteroid. So what does that do?
A bit of a trail. Get there faster. This is a rock.
This is a stone. What was I expecting? Oh, that's right. It's an asteroid.
How are there even rocks out here? That's something I really don't understand.
Does this move? What is a rock doing out here? What the hell is this here for?
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What just happened? Go back.
Rewind. Do you see that? What the hell was that?
Something just reversed time. There was a shooting star back here.
Wait for it. What's that fucking thing? No, just pull out.
No, no, no. I want to go to that thing. This is another rock.
That's cool. Wait a minute. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Get another photo here. Looks pretty cool. That is a nice looking rock.
You're right. Although I want that like in the back.
Hold on. That's fine. This is good. It's like an ice rock.
No, I didn't get the whole thing. Take it again. I want a good close-up
of the ice rock. Ooh, this is like a peak. That looks
cool. Save it. It looks like shit. How does it?
What do you mean looks like shit? You think this looks like shit?
I want to get it good. There we go. Like that. This alien life form here.
Hold on. Give me something cool here like that. Up a little.
Drop the exposure. No, no, no. Put it back. Man.
Drop the exposure a little bit more. Hold on. Right there. Got it.
That's beautiful. This is beautiful. All right. Viewer's choice. Where are we
going? And what year? So basically, just
delete that. Go to Earth's Moon 2018.
That sounds... Why 2018? Oh, shit. I'm reversing time.
What did that... That was fucking cool. I just broke the fucking... I crashed the
game. God damn it. Come on. Did I... Where is it? What's the matter? What was
that an error for? I don't have an error. Okay, that's weird.
All right. You want me to go to the moon, right? Earth Moon.
Go to the Earth Moon. Why 2018? What happens on 2018?
Where did they land? What a waste of viewer's choice. Go to the Earth Moon.
Well, hold on a minute here. Hold on. How fast can you walk? Like 20 miles per
hour? Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. This is cool.
We get to actually see the surface of the moon. Right here.
But what do you want me to do? Find the footsteps. I don't think they're
gonna have that. Why 2018? Find the flag. Make a damn
spaceship already. I didn't... Spacecraft manager? I don't
have one. Can I... How do I... Can I make one?
How do I make one? You can spawn in a spacecraft.
Go to the menu. Do I have to save this? Why would I have to save it? I can just
type in moon. Flight simulator? Build. Space engine.
Aliens. Fire. Fire Dragonfly Starship. Build it.
Okay, so take control of it. What? Main engine. I didn't... I don't have
this tutorial. There's a lot going on here. Flight
assist. How fast am I going? Main engines. Okay, main engines are on.
Thrusters. On. I'm going 2,000 miles per hour. How do I move?
Orp. Warp. Orp. Net 32. What is this ball of yarn over here?
What is this? Saturn's moon? I want to go that way.
Saturn's moon. Land on Saturn's moon. Main engines. On.
Dock. No docking ports available. Where are you going?
Is it like flying itself? Select star and then click warp to.
Normal up. Rotate to target. Kill rotation.
Switch view. Here we go. View ship trajectory.
Oh, all right. Switch view. Okay, and then warp.
I'm warping here. All right, here we go. Main engines at 100.
Thrusters. Engaged. Go for it. Do I have to do anything else?
Or will it just do it on its own? Is it going to crash?
Am I going to crash into this planet? Yeah, I'm fine.
That's what it looks like on the inside, huh? Shredded tax documents.
Wow. So this is like the shredder planet. Cool. All right, let's push it.
Push the planet. I can't push the planet. How about orb? Oh, that's orbit.
What about H-O-R? What does that mean?
Whore. What is whore? What is whore? All right, go that way.
Well, all right. Well, I can right click and land.
Am I still on the spaceship? Oh, is that my spaceship's out here.
Okay. Well, that was fun. I jumped out of the spaceship into the space.
What is the planetarium? Why does the moon look like this now?
Oh, it's just there. All right, I want to go to two more places.
And then I'm going to do something else. This is fun, though.
No, like five more places. Go to the year 2077.
Earth. There's a Sauron? Where is it?
Well, that's a lot stupider than I thought it was going to be.
Stupid's the wrong word. Listen, what is that down there?
All right. Wait, wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We've got red blood land cluster and then big orange.
Let's go red. Type diffuse. California nebula.
Let's go. What's this one? G1. Yellow giant. Star Capella.
All right, we're going to go much faster than this.
I'm missing so many planets. All right, hold on.
This is it right here. California nebula.
One of these days, one of these just giant red toxic poison clouds
is just going to cross Earth's path. Shift F3.
Search for star browsers. Go to search.
Oh, you can see how many stars and how many planets.
Life. Hold on, there's life on some of these planets?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What do you mean life?
Wait, wait, wait. This for planet A3.
All right, hold on. We'll close this for a second.
I want to check out the red fumes. What's in the red fumes?
Something in here. Star. I'm not going to say that.
I was going to say Final Fantasy, but I'm already just barely
breaking even right now on the joke meter,
and I don't want to cause a problem on that.
I didn't do anything. You can't just write minus two.
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything.
No, I didn't. Oh, that's unfair. That was unfair minus twos.
All right, I want to see what this is.
Percy. Let's see what Percy is.
Percy is actually pretty cool looking.
Whoa. I want it right on the left side there.
I want that in the background too, like this.
Like over here maybe. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I know I want that.
Like this. I don't know.
What the hell is going on here?
All right, this just looks like when you used to have
a disposable camera and like six of the photos
when you got them developed would look like this
because you had to shake your fucking hand on it and shit.
So, all right, turn it off auto.
That's even worse.
I almost want to like go.
Hold on. This is super duper.
Just take it. Take the photo.
I can't wait until we go over these at the end
and you just go, holy shit, he's talented.
All right, what was that going?
Oh, the planet with a life on it.
Let's go get a sample.
Let's go have one of like the space cows peeing in a jar.
Where was that? Shift F3.
All right, this one right here is a this system here.
So there's life here.
Where the hell am I?
Life on these planets?
Let me open that back up.
There's life on one of these planets.
RS8 and within one light year.
Filted like there's 18 planets here.
But what do you mean life?
251. Like that's where I am.
But like which one of these has life on it?
Barrie Center?
What the hell is this?
Well, get there.
Let's go.
Gee, take me to the Barrie Center.
What the hell is going on here?
Here we go.
Does it say if there's life on it?
All right, there's life on this planet.
Oh, life on this one.
The timing.
Wait, did it?
Oh, I want to see.
Clip it.
I want to see it.
I want to see that.
That's so stupid.
It's like I had a button queued up
and pressed it at the perfect time.
All right.
I need to find the life on this damn planet.
No, not the main menu yet, dummy.
F2.
Let me check this one.
Green text in Barrie Center.
All right, there's apparently life here.
Let's take this down to like 10 times
and let's go explore the planet.
There's life on this planet.
How do I find it?
Is it just water?
I swear to God if an alien shows up.
Found it.
Look at that.
It's like a snow snow.
It's a crack.
I thought it was a snake.
Is it like a life-o-meter?
Can I pull up a thing to see if I can find it somewhere?
The moons have life, but you won't see it.
No life on this planet.
Go to the moons.
Go to moon.
All right.
Wait, I think those are those life orbs.
How could there be life on this planet?
Shit can't live on this.
How on earth are you supposed to live
on top of Nickelodeon Floam?
I don't understand.
Does it make any sense to me?
That was funny.
It was.
You just don't get it.
You didn't have Floam when you were a kid.
It hasn't existed in like 15 years.
I feel like this is a conspiracy against me today.
There's a joke conspiracy against me
ever since we started talking about it.
It's actually kind of cool looking.
You think we're under 15?
No.
Nobody had Floam and I didn't even have Floam.
I had it for like an hour.
I've liked that one.
I'm keeping that one.
All right.
Let me turn off the...
That actually looks kind of good.
No, but I didn't have it though.
Somebody brought it over.
Somebody brought it over
and they took it out of the package
and we were playing it
and I stole some.
When they went to the bathroom
I pulled off like a little corner of it
and then spread the rest of it out
inside the container
so it looked like there was nothing missing.
Then I put it into a little shoe box
and then I had my own Nickelodeon Floam.
All right.
Let me go ahead and tell you something here.
Me telling you about a bad thing I did
when I was younger
is not a minus two scenario.
Oh, I can't believe you did that bad thing
when you were a kid.
That wasn't a funny joke.
Oh, am I dead?
Is Dream dead?
Yeah, guys.
One time I ate a bowl of fucking cereal.
Yeah.
Minus two.
Theft isn't funny.
It's not a...
Yeah.
It's not a joke.
Theft is not a joke.
Therefore, there's no reason for it to be a joke
and I'm stuck in the quicksand.
I'm climbing back by the end of this stream.
I ain't going to let this...
Oh, this looks good.
How about right here?
Everyone's working against me now
because they know, oh, he wants to try to break even
on the Joko meter.
Oh, I'm not going to let that happen
every time he says something I can say minus two.
Let me go...
Let me go where...
Let's go here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What was the...
Let me look at this.
Oh, there's an egg.
There's an egg nebula.
Let's go.
Holy shit, you ate a bowl of cereal.
Fucking plus two.
Hey, guys.
Do you like Coca-Cola?
Me too.
Give me a fucking break.
I'm definitely going to get a picture of this.
This is fucking so stupid.
So fucking funny.
Minus two Pepsi is better,
but that's like...
Opinions aren't jokes either.
You know, I thought Endgame was like a really good movie.
Minus two.
No, no, what?
That's not a joke.
No, stop doing...
No, no, no, no, no.
He's got opinions.
All right, let's get in the egg nebula.
I wonder if we can find some spies inside the egg nebula.
I wonder if that's possible.
That's guaranteed.
I will game...
You want to game...
You want to game me?
I'm going to game you.
I will get that to positive by the end of the stream.
You're already falling for it.
I already got you.
Washed up streamer gives into nostalgia.
What are we at?
What's the total?
Let me see your total.
I'm deleting that, by the way.
That's like...
That is like the self-conscious mode active.
I got to look over here and just like, wait a minute.
Where am I?
Am I at my funny score?
I don't want to have to have that climbing up my ass.
Or I only want that available at the end of the stream.
That's going to put too much pressure on me.
I'm going to look over and it's going to be like, oh, total.
Wow, he sucks.
No, no, I don't.
I don't suck, do I?
Let's go on this one.
That's worse.
Look, I know this looks like the gravel circle in Garden Flipper.
That's just an observation.
I'm not making a joke.
That's an observation.
Come on, I want to get like a...
Can I take the atmosphere on?
Let me see what happens when I do this.
No, it doesn't help.
Doesn't help.
Go to the sun and see if it's super nervous.
I don't think any actual things happen in the game.
I think it just is interesting to do.
I think there's certain events that you can see.
Maybe there's no like physics simulation.
Yeah, nothing currently aware of.
This is a cool planet.
I get this one like a D minus, like a C plus, maybe.
Turn back on the magnitude.
I'm like very far away.
Hold on.
What am I?
I'm like lost here.
There we go.
What am I going to go?
I should play universe sandbox.
I could check that out eventually.
That star took billions of years to form and you gave it a D minus.
Yeah, and what's the problem?
I don't see a problem.
That's rude.
Planets don't have feelings.
They have bottles of gas, water, and vapor.
They don't get sad about not being cool.
I'll tell you what is cool.
This.
Let's get a good view of this.
It looks like a double star here.
I got to drop.
Oh, hold on.
I like this.
Slow it down a little.
Get up.
Maybe.
Nah.
What am I going to go?
Right in here.
And let's zoom it out a little bit.
And then I want to turn on.
I mean like that's again from your disposable camera.
You took a picture of the sun.
I've got I got an idea for a stream.
Oh yeah.
This is going to happen.
Oh, this is going to happen real soon.
I'm not even doing anything.
Everyone's this is you guys a game in the system here.
I'm going to buy like five disposable cameras and like go on a trip.
And I'm not going to I'm going to develop them.
And then I'm going to show you I'm going to show up to you on stream.
I'm going to go like this.
No more magnitude.
What is that?
No, I want that looks all right.
Fire watch.
Yeah, but the difference with fire watch is those are taken in the game.
Like I'm going to really go on like a trip.
Oh, shit.
All right.
What do you say?
Like about five minutes of this and I'm going to just go to the bathroom.
We'll come back and do something else.
All right.
I'm going to we're going to type in random letters here because the just
I'm going to just whatever you have in chat here.
I see J.
I see Q.
J.
Q.
Damn it.
J.
S.
S one eight three B.
And then I'm going to go as fast as I possibly can and try to get to the end of the world.
Now, that's a cool looking fucking zone.
I can't wait to level up here.
What's the level limit?
10 to 25.
Nice.
You want to go here?
I do too.
Bullshit.
You guys are liars.
Liars.
All of you.
I don't care about some arbitrary rating system.
I want to get like in here though.
Now, that's an awesome view.
Let's go in here.
It does look like Neptune.
Go see Messier 82.
I'll check it out.
I haven't even gone to see like Jupiter and Mars and stuff.
Messier 82.
Let's try it.
I don't know.
Where is it?
It's not here.
There's nothing here.
M82.
That's a pretty good chat's choice.
This looks good.
Pick at that.
Okay.
What about anything in here that's interesting to see?
It's cool.
A crab nebula?
I think I feel like I've seen this before.
It's cool looking I guess.
What's the one back here?
If you call something a crab nebula, don't you expect it to have claws
or look kind of like a crab?
Why would it be crab nebula?
What is this thing in here?
Can't even click it.
Not even clickable.
There it is.
I want to check this one out.
And I'm going to fly to this one.
Oh, this is cool.
This one is nice.
I want to fly like hordes of right there.
Right there.
Hold on.
I'll get out of here.
That's perfect.
What is that?
This feels like it doesn't belong.
I feel like this is an error in the game.
This is chewed up bubble gum that the developer accidentally left here.
I mean, it's cool looking.
Wait, I can get a pretty good picture here I think.
Looks pretty nice.
All right, cool.
All right.
What's the last place I'm going?
Somebody said the spirit of creation.
Whatever.
Something of creation.
Pillars of creation.
This is huge.
What the hell?
Is this a giant E?
E.
I'm still loading in shit.
What the hell is that?
How big is this?
That's huge.
Yeah, this is the Milky Way.
Wow.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah, I know.
I know it's our galaxy.
I just didn't know that like the crab nebula or I don't know.
I haven't taken like fucking ninth grade geography since the ninth grade.
I don't know that.
Why would I know that?
I haven't opened up like a ninth grade science book since I was in the ninth grade.
I don't remember that the pillars of creation are in our galaxy.
Why would I have that information right now?
Why would I remember this?
Click the flag.
I'm scared to click the flag.
Okay.
I can click the flag.
Wait, is that my address?
I saw my location.
I saw my location and I fucking freaked out.
Okay.
Spare me.
All right.
Look at the pillars of creation.
We saw that one.
Sunrise in hell.
Holy shit.
Good photo op coming up here I think in a fast forward time frame.
Watch this.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, hold on.
I don't even care where I am.
Who cares?
I would laugh so hard if I had a face on it.
I'll come back.
Come on and hurry up.
Come on.
Where is it?
Where did it go?
Here we go.
Ready?
Find me a better picture from anyone that's ever played this game.
That's going to be featured in a magazine.
Go to the Great Wall?
Hold on.
Let me see what this is even first.
This is like a lava gallery.
No, this is a crab galaxy.
Okay.
If it were me making the rules, this would be the crab nebula.
Take a look.
This is a crab.
Just for everyone to make sure they understand this.
This is crab nebula to me.
Why?
I just did like a loop-de-loop.
I'm going to fucking throw up here.
What's going on?
Where am I going?
I don't understand.
Oh, this is Beetlejuice 3 is the name of this planet.
Oh, god damn it.
No, no, no.
Not Beetlejuice 3.
Just wait for it any minute now.
It's not how many times you say it.
It's the planet number.
Hold on.
Where is he?
I don't...
I'm dying this music.
Is he here?
Where the fuck is he?
What the fuck?
Somebody at the door.
Hold on.
Weirdly enough.
Weirdly enough, he drives for FedEx now.
I actually got a couple things on Amazon.
So put them over here.
I got to do water filter.
So that's cool.
Because the water in Vegas can be kind of not so good.
What was going on?
Oh, right, right, right.
We're going here.
Reused joke.
Come on.
That happened.
I got three.
Come on.
That actually happened.
He actually drove here.
Actually had an actual filter from the actual Beetlejuice
that actually showed up at my actual house.
Recycled water.
What is this thing?
An actual Beetlejuice.
Oh, is there a great wall?
What do you want me to do?
Should I go into locations?
One of the biggest stars known.
What is this one?
How big is it?
How many pounds is that?
Type in fuck and see if it gets any results.
Why would they ever do that?
No scientist is going to make.
Fuck.
I don't believe that for a second.
No, of course not.
I don't want to type it in.
I'm turning the game off so you can't see what I type next.
No, none of those exist.
None of these exist.
What is this thing?
This is the biggest object in the universe?
Something like that.
This is Starwo G64.
Go to the Pinwheel Galaxy.
Well, that was a...
I think you lied to me.
Pinwheel?
The Sloan Wall.
There's nothing...
There's nothing showing up.
This...
The wall?
What would it be called?
M1...
M101?
This M29?
Who keeps track of this shit?
If to be like an astronaut scientist person,
do you have to memorize all this shit?
Imagine needing to know all this.
So this is the biggest thing in the universe.
This here.
The M101.
It's called the computer.
Yeah, what about like 40 years ago?
30 to 40 years ago?
How did they keep track of...
They wrote it on notepads?
They had a book.
That's a big book.
They had computers.
Not powerful enough.
They had like fucking 100k worth of data.
That's not enough to store 500 trillion stars.
That's kind of cool looking.
Text is not heavy at all.
Yeah, but 500 trillion lines of text
is more than a computer in the 70s can handle.
This is actually called the pinwheel galaxy.
Well, maybe I should die in there.
So many things in here though.
Let's just pick a random one.
It looks super giant.
Do I feel like the guy that names stars
is the same guy that's so sick
of naming different colors of crayons or paints?
Yeah, we just found another 500 planets over here, Bill.
Shit.
Yeah, we really need names for them all.
That's cool though.
Where do we go?
What was it called?
I...
I see what?
I see 1001?
This is it?
I wouldn't be surprised, man, if this was an eyeball.
This was an eye.
What even is existence, by the way?
What the fuck is existence?
101...
1101.
I just wanted to laugh.
So this is it.
It's like foggy over here.
I see 1101.
Let's get in a little closer.
What's like right at the heart?
Is it weird that I think that if you get to the center of this,
you're gonna get superpowers.
That's how this works.
If you touch in the middle here, you turn into Superman.
How would that be?
It would be...
That's how that would work.
All you need to do is just breathe into your nostrils, the air here,
and you'll get the power of invisibility.
This is huge.
Hold on, what just zoomed by?
Star.
Radiation.
Yeah, but what if it's not radiation?
What if it's something else that we don't know?
What if everyone's just like,
ah, there's radiation in there, you're dead.
What if it's not?
What if it's like radiation?
I don't know.
What if it's something else?
What if it's like the other...
I don't know.
Nobody knows what's in here.
You don't know what the hell is in here.
Nobody knows what the fuck is in here.
What?
No, I'm serious.
Like, you don't know what's in the middle here.
Quick, say, Shmee.
I'm in the middle.
I'm in the center.
I have made it to the center.
I'm gonna try it.
Okay, here we go.
Fuck, it was muted.
Why was it muted?
Why would you be muted?
Why does every...
Why is YouTube permanently mute itself?
What feature is that?
What kind of dumb feature is that?
Hey, you know that website you just clicked on to want to watch a video?
We're gonna make sure it's muted when you click on it.
Why does YouTube always assume that I'm in like a dorm room
surrounded by like 10 people at like 4 o'clock in the morning
with speakers as loud as they can go?
What?
YouTube, I promise I'm not like in a fucking nursery
with the volume at max
with like a new Bose speaker system.
Why does every video have to be muted?
It doesn't have to be like this.
Everything is either muted or at maximum volume.
Just what is...
Why?
Bose is garbage?
What?
What do you mean, Bose is garbage?
What do you mean it is?
Where are you getting that information from?
Who told you that?
Holy shit, you guys.
You guys have strong opinions about Bose sound.
Whoa, where am I?
I made it.
I'm in the fucking center of all creation.
Let me try it.
I think that may have worked.
Oh, hold on.
Come in.
Just wait.
Wait a second.
Yeah, I'm running up the stairs.
Hey.
Sorry, I had another package.
I got a lot of deliveries.
Me and Beetlejuice, I like this.
This is a joke.
I was thinking about going and getting a package
and bringing it up here
because there's a package actually down there right now
but it has like all information on it
and I couldn't like...
I couldn't do it.
I would have to like have ripped off all the labels and shit
couldn't do it.
He had to drive back for another package.
Okay, so where are we?
Oh, ding dong.
Oh, that's funny.
Here we go.
iCar.
Wasn't I supposed to leave
till I go to the bathroom and come back
and do something else?
iCarly.
This is not an iCarly.
Wait, i...
Wait, hold on.
One, one, one.
There's a black hole in here.
So, shit.
Control G will take me to...
What's the name of the...
Okay, so I did Control G.
Go find Drake and Josh.
So I'm back in here.
But so, so what?
Am I inside of the damn thing?
Zoom out.
I'm trying to zoom out.
Holy shit.
Whoa, this is insanity.
That's awesome.
Holy shit.
I gotta get a good pic of this one right here.
That's insane.
Remember all of this existed.
Yeah, that's wild.
That's what I'm saying.
Like how the fuck does this exist?
What the hell even is light?
Where does it come from?
You understand what I'm saying?
Where the hell does light even come from?
Photons.
What the fuck is a photon?
Like, I know it's energy,
but what even is energy?
What does that even mean?
Right now somebody's laughing at us.
Somebody's laughing at us right now.
Somebody has this on a computer screen,
like up fucking seven trillion light years away somewhere.
They're like, oh my god, they're laughing.
They're trying to figure out what light is over there
on that stupid shitty stream.
That guy's such a boomer.
Like they even use that terminology too.
I want to get a better picture right there.
It's going to hurt, but it's all right.
Drop this a little bit.
I'm going in.
Why am I going backwards?
I'm going backwards.
Am I going backwards?
What the fuck is that?
Turn up the brightness.
Oh shit, I know how this movie ends.
For the rest of my existence,
I climb out of TVs and fucking call people,
collect from the bottom of the well.
How do I get out of here?
Head towards the light.
The light doesn't exist anymore.
What even is light?
What is, there's something else here.
I'm going.
Quick.
Someday somebody will develop these.
Did I make it out?
I made it out.
So what's on the other side?
Go again.
There's a Windows update error here.
Okay, hold on.
Black hole.
Go in.
Do it again.
Let's get the fuck in there.
Turn off the, turn that off.
And then I want to make this fast.
Oh fuck, I'm reversing time.
I just went through it.
All right.
I'm now in, I'm in no man's land now.
Now, this is important.
This is important.
I'm going to go down.
I want to go turn up the brightness.
Turn up the magnitude.
We're going to find out what's down here.
Okay.
I'm looking down and I'm going to go 500 trillion light years away until we hit.
What the fuck was that?
Wait, that's right.
Time doesn't exist in here.
I forgot about that.
There is no time.
There is only now.
I'm very comfortable right now.
Whoa.
Wow.
Literally fucking nothing could change.
My attention right now.
Holy shit.
This is fucking incredible.
Actually fucking one of the most amazing things I've ever seen.
I'm all right right now.
I don't need anything else.
Nothing else.
Oh, hold on.
Sometimes you got to go get a package.
Fuck it.
They'll leave it at the door.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need this right there.
No, no, no.
Do it again.
I want to get that again right when they, right here.
Ready?
Did I get it?
Need to sign for it?
No, they'll just like, they'll whip it as hard as they can at the front door.
Oh, I made it through.
I think.
Stop.
I just want to take a fucking picture.
Wait, wait, wait.
What was that?
No one's going to get one of these.
No one's going to get one.
I did.
It's the Borg.
Come on.
Let me get this.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Right here.
It's a toilet.
Wow.
What a wonderful, beautiful black hole.
Really cool stuff.
I wonder what this actually is.
There's so much science as to what the heck is this even?
Is it energy?
Is it a time paradox?
Is it aliens?
Did aliens make this?
I don't know.
It's so many questions that I have.
We'll never know the answers to.
Now I'm stuck down here.
Great.
I've got to, I'm stuck down here.
Can anybody help me?
Is there anybody that can help me?
Oh, hold on.
Somebody.
Somebody got to somebody's bearing a plumber.
No, almost.
You got to do more than that.
A little more.
We're still stuck down here, man.
Help us.
Preview, preview, preview, preview.
That wasn't even a plunger.
What the fuck was that?
We're still stuck down here and we need help.
What do you recommend is the quickest and easiest way
to unclog a drain?
I don't know.
If your sink is clogged like this,
you're definitely looking for the quickest
and easiest way to get it unclogged
and the over-the-counter drain cleaners work most
of the time, but they can be a little damaging
to your pipes.
Before you try that.
Yeah.
This is a drain snake and it has a brush
or sometimes several hooks on the end.
Well, be careful.
We're down here.
To reach down and grab.
Easy, easy.
To be clogging up your sink, particularly in a bathroom.
But if you have a lot of grease and food,
you need a little pressure
and everybody has one of these very, very effective.
What is it?
Oh, is that a plunger?
I can't see.
But if you have a double sink like this,
you want to make sure you take your stopper
on the open side of the sink.
Where is he?
He's coming this way.
That'll put more pressure on the side of the plunger
and then that'll be very successful
in blowing through.
That wasn't enough.
Follow that up.
Plenty of hot water.
Sorry, Dave.
That wasn't enough.
God damn it.
You're going to need something more powerful than that.
Come on, almost there.
You got it.
Thanks.
All it took is a vacuum to stuff it down the drain.
By the way, if you ever have a drain,
if you have a clogged toilet or something,
just get the vacuum attachment.
Stuff it down into the toilet bowl,
into the drain,
turn it on and suck up whatever it is in the vacuum.
Now, one of you psychos is going to do that
and I have to make sure I say
that that is not a joke.
I hope you do that
because it works.
Do not do that.
I'm not going to be responsible
for your fucking YouTube prank video
that you put up online and say,
hey, Jeremy said this.
This is so crazy.
All right.
I think we saw all we need to see in this game.
Is there anything else?
Any other cool, any cool other nucleuses?
Zoom out all the way.
Oh, yeah, right, right, right, right, right.
I was going to do that.
I was going to run away.
Where am I?
There we go.
Okay, let's turn down the magnitude here.
It's a little much for me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Put black hole quality on low.
Black hole quality on low.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, where, where, where?
G, control G.
What was it called?
What was it?
Black hole quality on low.
Look up IC dash.
Shut up.
All right, hold on.
I'm going to go pee.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to pee.
Are you guys fucking kidding me?
Really?
All right, nice.
I come back and people are just putting minuses into the chat.
Is this tug of war or is this a barometer for how the jokes are?
It's because I left.
I'm coming back.
All right, what do you guys want me to turn on?
A quality low, right?
A black hole quality on low.
Why is it two mediums?
Oh, never mind.
Black hole quality on low and then go to a black hole.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
Yeah, I changed it.
I know.
Come on.
I live in one part of the earth that cares about this and this.
All right, so where's the black hole?
What's a cool black hole that you know of?
Because after this, we're going to move on to something else.
Go inside a black hole.
For a second, I really almost
like typed that in.
Not because somebody just wrote it.
I was like, oh, wait, no, that's a song.
Which one of these?
X1.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What what's going on here?
Why is this?
Why is it on?
Okay, all right.
This is...
Why did that happen?
Oh, this thing has like flames on it.
Is this a black hole?
This is not a black hole though.
I'm looking for a black hole.
Right, is the other one is a black hole.
This is a black hole.
Don't look like a black hole
Hold on slow down slow down. What are you thinking here times 30?
Slow down the speed. Let's get a closer look here. It looks like a butane torch
All right. Why do I feel like this is going like a million miles per hour? This is a regular speed
Slow down. I mean I where do you well abstract now do normal speed
I'm gonna warn you this is probably gonna hurt. This is not gonna be pretty to look at here
Just be aware of this despite this this could be a little over stimulating
Just want to make sure everyone's aware of that because this is gonna be a time is one speed
Yeah, just be this is gonna be super stimulating
Shit, what did I what the fuck? I'm trying to just go in backwards, but it's hard to line up. I slow down slow down
That's it. I get I'm zoomed out as far as I can in theory. You would see the back of your head
Let's go the other way. What happens if you go the other way in a black hole? No wrong same thing
Yeah, same thing happens. Well, that was cool. You get out. Do you though you're dead by the radiation?
We don't know this radiation there 3c 58
I just took I just took like an actual screenshot. I think 3c
58 3c
66 B. Let's see what this one's like. Yeah, it's a run-of-the-mill galaxy. No, yeah
FoV down. I mean, this is like the normal fov the bubble nebula now
Hold on. We'll do something else. Just relax. Just relax. I see why. Yep. Okay, do Sagittarius a didn't we already do?
Sagittarius a yeah, we already did Sagittarius a I was here before I mean we didn't see the ion cannon that was coming
Out of it. I don't think it wasn't this pronounced was it this is insane
Do a time-lapse doesn't have an orb. What is this an orbit of now you get tangled in that
You'd get tangled up in there. Oh, that's cuz of the black hole. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Wow, that's so cool. They all just ran the fuck into each other. What is the trajectory of this?
I want to see what is that trajectory? What's going up there?
What's that and why is that doing that if there's a black hole down here and it's all the gravity is getting like
What's this guy flying around for?
S111 that's so strange. What that's such a weird pattern
It goes up here and then just rides the rollercoaster down and does the same thing again. No, no, no, wait
Hey, hey, hey, wait, wait, come back. Come back. Come back. Wait. Wait, what it's what come back come back
We reversed it just don't give a fuck come back here. What year is it?
8400 the year 8400 where'd it go? Where'd it go? Where the fuck did it go? I did okay
I did this stick this it disappeared on me. Let's go. Take a look. Oh, this is like
Quatrillion light years away
Really what I'm on it, right G. Yeah G double G tap G go to object G
I'm I press G like five times. Are you like I'm not pressing G. They're like won't let me go over here
This is freaking me out. Hold on. See I can't go any faster. I have to like go there
What is happening? Yeah, look at this. It won't let me go over here
It stops me right here and spins me around. All right, I'm gonna have it come backwards then
Did we find a new planet? I think we found a new planet. I know nobody knows about this only we do reverse time
Pull it back. What I want to go to s1 1 1 1 is that the
Let me move out of the way. I think they might be broken. It might be broken. Yeah, I might come on
Is that it? I'm so confused right now. What is this line?
The line is even bending. I'm just gonna get right in the way. Okay, so
Let's go. Where is it? Get over here. Is it the black hole is fucking it up. The hell is this doing?
Well, oh well, I tried it's insane. Oh
Come on make a milkshake. It's pulling me back. Stop pulling me back. Just center G
It's going so fast that they all froze. All right, normal normal. It's time
You guys ready? I'm going this way for 10 straight seconds. Go to ID 10 T for black hole
Did you just spell out idiot? I think you did. Yeah, you did. That's idiot. That's that's pretty good
I'll give you that one. That was pretty good. All right, you ready? So we are distance 12
The gala the universe cannot be infinite. There's definitely like a brick wall that you walk into there has to be an end
Nothing is infinite. There's an end. I made it. I did I'm here. I made it
I told you I told you there's gonna be like a fucking wall here. That's the end
But what does it look like from far away all the way back? I'm gonna laugh my ass off if it's a gnome
Gly now we're in darkness. Wait one here. What is that?
Let's find the I need the one red dot here and then I'm gonna move on. This is galaxy RG
wall 0 1 6
1 8 8
8 up the magnitude. I mean I'm at I'm at like almost a magnitude limit
No, I'm not how far can this go? I mean am I gonna try to break the computer?
Let's pull back and see what it is
What's the image? Come on my computer hurts
Pull it back and have it say something like the treasure's buried at this precise location. So that's what it looks like
This is this is somebody with like a sunburn. We're just a goddamn skin cell all of us
Pull it down pull it down pull it down pull it universe Sandbox universe. I'll do universe Sandbox
All right, let's play a fun game
So let's spin it around and wherever I land with my face and my finger is where I'm gonna go on vacation
Let's see. Oh my god. I hope it's Hawaii
I just choked on my water. What the fuck?
There it is it's this galaxy double G Oh
Oh
Shit the the limit. I just blew a firework up in my face
What a great disposable camera picture by the way got the firework exploding again. It's over. Yeah, that's it
We got we got the wheel of death space engine has stopped responding close the program. Okay, that was interesting
Imagine being a science teacher and unloading that up during class
We didn't get that shit. The guy had a chalkboard and drew
Shitty planets in this like crusty white paste and his handwriting sucked
Imagine we had that shit god. That would have been awesome. I would have been so much more into school
Think about how much more fun and cool school would have been. I was so disinterested in high school
All right, so we have like
a couple hours hour or two I
Bought and I have downloaded. There's a couple of things that I thought would be might be fun. I have received various
Recommendations and we're gonna do a poll. We'll do a poll on the screen here in a minute
I don't know I know about one of these but I do not know about the other one
So I'm gonna mispronounce this
Very very poorly because I don't know how to pronounce. I don't it's this one is called
Recetteer and item shops tail and the other one is cook serve delicious of the two that were
Requested that I thought might have been interesting. I also have cook serve delicious, too
Now I don't know there might be some internal debates here by the chatters
Both are so good. I have played cook serve delicious before I don't know if I should just open cook serve delicious, too
Is this a scenario where cook serve delicious to is just a better version of cook serve delicious one do it
We'll do do what cook serve delicious to is worse
Well, I'll put a poll on the screen here because we'll vote on that too. So straw poll
So let me give you an indicator of what's going on over the next few weeks. I
Want to do so obviously tomorrow. I'm probably gonna do Mario maker 2 tomorrow and just played random levels and
Fuck around for like, you know a few hours, however long I can take it
Saturday is the grain screen movie night on core stream and then on top of that
Next week. I want to I think I want to do Dark Souls randomizer
At least try that once or twice
randomized items randomized enemies and stuff looked like it was
Just I can't say words
but
Yeah, I can oh, huh. All right, hold on
I'm gonna just write on a bucket of an item shops tail
Is an item shops tail like its own stream?
Cuz I can kind of just play cook serve delicious for like a couple hours and we can just chill and talk about stuff
Cuz I didn't want to also bring up
we're kind of just
rolling here, so I didn't want to bring up the
Cuz at least two options are needed. There are two options. Oh
Okay, so the first option the cook serve delicious
That's just if you want to see that rather than an item shop still we will pick the first of the second one
I might even just open the first one. You know what I mean vote on that
I'm gonna put the BRB screen up and drop in a shitload of frames to
I don't know why this shit was fixed
But apparently not
Hopefully this is kind of like an outlier today because that's a lot of drop frames. I
Don't have time for reciter. It's its own stream. Is that true?
it's not just like a little
cook serve delicious is
More inclined to what we're doing right now. Does it really take that long? Huh? It's gigantic. Oh geez. All right, um
Well, okay. Hold on riddle me this riddle me this right? Let me ask you this
Would you want me to just do that tomorrow instead of Mario maker 2 and we'll do Mario maker 2 next week
Doesn't take that long. Yeah, but I really only I mean, I'm probably only gonna stream for like another couple hours. So
Absolutely not never play Mario maker. Well, we'll see how it goes. I'm gonna play it. Yeah, I guess I'll strike while the iron saw it
Yeah, all right. All right. Hey, listen, I know you just voted on a poll and I'm going to pretend like that poll never happened
so
Sorry, I will play that item shop game
Next week before we do Dark Souls remastered
randomizer
So you can expect that that can that's kind of what we'll do next week. What a democracy. What a great democracy. We got here
but the streamer just
Reverses everything he just said but let's open up a cook serve delicious and we'll do Mario maker tomorrow
Cuz that's like that's like a hot game. I mean I gotta play the hot game. Hopefully this is not loud
I can't believe you asked us. Well, I I thought that cooks
I thought that that item shop game was like and a good thing I you can probably hear it
I can't even change that you're trying to stay relevant by playing Mario maker
What do you what are you on about here? I gotta turn this way the fuck down. This is so loud