And the word milk. That's gonna be kind of hard considering that there will be a cow on stream
for the next... up to two hours I think. I'm just getting high guys. How you doing? Good afternoon.
I love doing the up to certain amount of time for streams because it could be anything. Yeah,
this one's gonna be up to eight hours. That could be 20 minutes. 20 minutes or eight hours. Pick one.
Yeah, we're gonna do black and white too today. It's running. It's in 1080p and it looks glorious.
I'm also trialing out a new brace. I've got Boomer Brace 2.0. It's a little different. I'm
just... you gotta get used to it. Might need to loosen it a little bit. It's been upgraded
and eventually we're gonna upgrade until I'm Dr. Octopus. But yeah, we're gonna... we can
get started here in a second. Let me just make sure the tweet went through. We can get started
in about a minute, two minutes. You're back. Okay. Are we ready? Are we ready to begin?
Black and white 2. There we go. Now spoilers. No, no, no spoilers. No spoilers. All right. Let's get
out of this. I don't want to know what's possible. I want to get in here blind. This is black and
white 2. I just loaded it to check out to make sure it could get captured well and that it was
in 1080 fucking pretty, dude. And it is. I got all the fan patches to make sure the game runs.
Let's hope we got a good case here. New game. Let's go. Are you guys ready for the Moo Crew?
I'm a meteor that's about to crash into Earth.
I'm coming. I've answered your prayers. We're back on God Island like last game.
We're your conscience. We're part of you. Looks way better than the last one. You'll be the God
you want to be. So we'll guide you as you make your godly way through whatever this world
throws. But before then, you'll want to learn the big. We'll help you with all that. But even more
importantly, you'll need a creature. Yes. Let's go and choose one. Who is it going to be? What do
you guys think? Who's it going to be? I wonder. There they are. Wonderful, aren't they? You have
four to choose from, but the one you choose will be with you throughout your whole time in this
world. So consider carefully. Monkey? No. Make your choice wisely. Absolutely not. We'll tell you
about these amazing beasts. All creatures can be trained to become lovable mischievous
pets. Or they can be the ultimate disciplined weapons of destruction and war. Look at Varian.
He's just so curious. Can become these things. That's the wonder of a god's creature.
Don't stop zooming in on the monkey. I want to see them. I want to see them.
All creatures will grow up to be huge and powerful. They can be cute,
quirky pets, inquisitive and fun. The graphics is so much better. They can be single-minded
war machines. Can I see what the other ones look like when they get older?
All creatures will be as good or evil as you teach them to be.
Now snooze. Boring. Snore. Snore. Yeah, right. I'd rather they spread love in
the form of a massacre or two. By going into battle, creatures can live for war,
domination and destruction. Such a shame if you ask me. No, I don't know. Now this is what I'm
talking about right here. I love them. Oh, he did it. They all have their own lives,
but you need to be a responsible parent and not overfeed them. Oh, he's barfed to the shit. Yep,
gotta be the cow. Cow's the best animal. Now it's time to choose. He did a book of eight. I
thought you'd know he's perfect. That might be a little loud. Let me turn it down. It's a little
too loud, isn't it? All right, so hold on. It's a little loud. Yeah, it's maxed out. Let's go like,
bring it down a tad. Okay. Yes. All right. Let's see. Let's give them all a chance,
but we already know what our vote is. What's wrong with this one? Why was this one just sad?
Oh, look at him. Wait, is he gonna pick me? Remember me from last game? I was so funny.
Oh, he looks unsure. I have never been so sure of anything in my whole life.
That was awesome. Why is everybody so sad?
It's a baby. What? What was that? You know, let's, let's just do it.
Yeah, it's different. There's like, there's different shit here.
Yeah, I'm gonna do it. This is different than last year for manipulating the world.
It's not just drag buttons. Your view around the world like this. And why is your frame rating
when you do it? Hold down. Yes. All right. So it's right. Click this time to the right.
Just carry on dragging. Hold right. Okay. That was gonna say that didn't work.
Great work. Now we must move to our right. To move right, hold down the movement button,
then drag the mouse to the left. Bad PC. Wonderful. Just follow the arrows.
It's a lot better looking than black and white one for sure.
One hop this time. One hop this time. Two hops this time. That's pretty good.
I don't have a bad PC. You have a bad PC. Let's keep going. Click and hold the ground.
Then move the mouse back to pull yourself forwards. Follow the arrows to get back to your
creature. Excuse me. Hold on. It's just taking. Wait, there were a couple of winks that came in.
What do you think about fucking boomer brace 2.0? This has got, this has got fucking titanium in
the middle. There's steel in here. What do you think about boomer brace fucking 2.0 guy?
He's pretty good. Oh yeah. He's bulletproof. He's bulletproof.
Super villain. I know. And whilst keeping the movement button down, drag the mouse back.
Isn't that? That's what I'm doing. Game. Hold. Pull. That's what I'm doing. Hold. Pull. Hold. Pull.
Hold. Right click. Pull. What? Why is this? It's kind of finicky.
Now why is it working now? Weird. My fucking whatever. The creature is moving behind us.
We must pan backwards to find him. All right. Pan. Yep. That's working fine now.
I love that run. Look at his legs. Well done. Evil German. Whatever. I know this looks like
an evil villain origin story. It's going to keep going until I have my whole head is made out of
metal. Now we shall learn to rotate your view. Hold the middle mouse button down and drag from
side to side to rotate your view. Yeah. Last time it wasn't that.
Click and hold in the highlighted area. Who cares? I'm doing it correct.
Now whilst keeping the middle mouse button down, drag the mouse left.
Click and hold the middle mouse button in the highlighted area.
I was in there. Click and hold in the highlighted area.
You didn't even click in the right spot.
Lovely. Keep the middle. This is going very well. Now.
Click the middle mouse button in the highlighted area and hold it down.
Now whilst keeping the middle mouse button down, push the mouse forward.
I just want to hug Murius. What's wrong with Murius?
There is one last thing, Leader. Learning to zoom in and out.
He's doing like a depressed dance. What? What's with the depressed dance?
Holy shit, that was bad.
Now try zooming towards the creature. Excellent work. Wonderful. You showed remarkable skill,
Leader. Way to go, boys. Sorry I couldn't help but you know places to be.
All the controls you just learned can be used to move around the world.
Can you please say it, Leader? Sure.
This is a gold scroll. These lead you through the story.
Silver scrolls lead the closest in the world.
Is this the wink? Fuck.
Bronze scrolls are tutorials which can teach you so much.
Double click the movement button on the ground there to zoom to it quickly.
That's actually a really good feature to know.
I've seen bronze tutorial scroll here, boys.
That's a good feature to know.
Move the hand over the rock and hold down the action button to pick it up.
Once you've got hold of it, release the button.
So let's move all these rocks out of the circle.
Was it in the original game? I don't remember.
Oh, that's it. You picked up the rock like an expert.
This is different though.
Now move it outside the circle and click the action button again to drop it on the ground.
It used to be you had to hold and then let go.
Now I have to let go.
You've fooled it beautifully. Well done.
Reminds me of my cricketing days.
Yeah, this is a little different.
Watch out!
You have received 1,000 tribute and you thoroughly deserve it.
Tribute is good.
Another bronze scroll. So much to learn and so little time.
You know, virgins are wonderfully versatile.
They can do so much in the world.
You can simply pick up a villager and put him or her next to something.
The villager will take this as divine inspiration and become a disciple.
Hype train game.
Hype train game. What's that? A hype train?
Holy shit.
Yeah, you used to have to click and hold.
Now you just click once.
Disciple farmer.
This person is safely working at the farm.
Don't look, leader.
The breeders are doing whatever it is such people do.
What does it look like?
Builder, breeders, farmers.
You see, we got a builder.
Well, you don't need that.
It's fine.
What about you?
Forrester.
Disciple forrester.
And this guy is chopping trees for wood.
You got all that, boss?
I do.
And to prove it, there's a thousand tributes waiting for you.
Why not explore the land?
Click on the silver scrolls when you see them.
Click on the gold scroll on the big mountain to leave.
All right. Tutorial done.
I get it.
Is there any new information that I need to know that's not in this?
Uh, no, that was like a little refresher course.
Oh, this is scrolling my chat.
Oh, that's not good.
That's not good at all.
Actually, uh, might have to, um, I can't see chat now.
Uh-oh, hold on.
Um, might have to open up the third party program here to see you guys.
Might have to open up.
What about another window?
I'm gonna have to open up on a phone.
Let's see.
Okay.
Yeah, I can do it like this.
This is fine.
All right.
We're good.
I got you in a new window.
All right.
So let's do, um, what's the side quest?
If there is a God up there and you can hear me, please help me out.
I mean, my life is in ruins.
A rock has rolled onto my lovely garden.
I've been trying to move it, but it's too big and heavy.
If ever a man needs a God, I'm him.
Please hear my prayer.
Who's he to ask us to move a rock for him?
Let's teach him a lesson.
No, no, that's wrong.
A knockdown is like laundry.
Nothing without them.
There's a lot.
All right.
You, all right.
You, you got lucky today.
I, you'll, I just, you got saved by the laundry.
The rock is gone.
My garden is rockless.
Marvelous.
You moved the rock.
The man is happy and all is well.
Oh, is this how it's going to be, boss?
Win in the hearts of this world's people.
You've just received.
Why is the tree bowing?
Oh, okay.
Nice.
All right.
So we got some tribute there.
Let's just keep, let's keep moving around.
Need some more side quests.
It's a lot smoother than the last game too.
Wait, is this, let me guess.
Is this going to be throw a rock over here?
A silver scroll.
The waterfall is blocked.
What will we do now?
This is awful.
Don't worry.
We'll think of something.
What about the animals that built this dam?
What about the beavers?
Objects can prove very useful in both defense and attack.
Tools through an object.
First, pick it up.
Then, whilst keeping the action.
What if I remove the rock beavers?
In the direction you want to throw.
Release the button when you want to let go of the object.
Same tutorial.
Oh, mega lull.
Rock beavers.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, all right.
It's too much or too little.
What the fuck?
Oh my, okay.
Come on.
Jesus.
What?
I don't even need to die.
That's hard.
That's really hard.
Well done.
Lockage has been cleared.
Try another.
Nice shooting.
Oh, fun.
I'm so excited.
I can't tell you how excited I am.
I can't wait for Murius to grow into a full grown cow.
And point to the point and go.
That's my favorite.
That's all I care about.
We could help their friends by moving them.
So they can be together in the main valley.
Okay.
Isn't that sweet?
A little lost valley of people.
Where do we put them?
You hold the nun.
We're here.
Great.
Welcome home.
The nomad is in the right valley.
Good.
This is unethical.
Oh, is this unethical?
I'm doing like a nice thing.
I'll show you unethical.
Would you like to see unethical?
Next time, walk on your own.
I mean, is that unethical?
Or is it mean?
You rescued everyone.
Look, you received 1,000 tribute.
Why are they punching each other?
You stink.
The land is complete, leader.
Click the gold scroll on top of the mountain to regress.
Here we go.
We're going to the top of the mountain.
It's time for Murius.
This is where Murius has to go do his fucking shaman quest.
To go get chain lightning.
Are you sure you wish to leave the land?
Click again to confirm.
We got a little refresher.
They didn't expect that.
Split one, villager.
Now you've had a taste of your powers.
We're ready to visit our mighty Greek capital.
Yeah.
Full of people that worship us.
What?
Please hear us.
Can you hear them?
Please help us.
That's a pure prayer.
That's weird.
It sounds like something terrible has happened.
Worship.
Mighty one, please heed up.
Our armies are crushed.
What's left of us hides in this city from the brutal Aztecs.
And now they are at our walls.
I implore you, please help us.
Oh, that's a lot of people.
Wait, what?
That's like 5,000 people.
Wait, damn.
Our city is under siege.
Killed nearly all our troops.
What am I supposed to do?
You're all going to die.
Look at the pig.
The pig just sitting there.
Save the villagers.
Save the village from the archers.
What?
Pick up the villagers and place them in the portal over here.
Where they'll be taken to safety.
Okay.
You've got a village report.
Yes, you put them down in the right place.
Am I just seeing that?
Do they have a god?
Oh my Jesus Christ.
Oh, those weren't people.
Okay, it's all right.
Those weren't people.
That was just a bunch of pots.
They were pots.
Okay, those are people.
Those were people at that time.
Those were people.
What's happening?
Watch that rumble.
That creature seems to be performing some strange ritual.
And he's huge.
We just have a baby.
We can't do anything about this.
Go get him, Murius.
Let's save as many villages as we can and get out of here.
I don't think we even...
I think Murius is still like in a crib somewhere.
What are these crazed ass tics doing?
Um...
Crushed down villages with barrels.
Oh my God.
This is horrible.
This huge fire...
There are some more barrels...
Wait, I can do that too.
Pull the god fence away.
Who's invading...
I've learned.
Why the hell...
They do like...
Were those jumps?
We can set these bales of hay on fire and rule them down to deal with the platoons down there.
Pick up the flaming stick and hold it over the hay bales.
Here we go.
Burn.
All right, that was a lot.
Another volcano.
You can make volcanoes in this game?
Before you could just like shoot lightning bolts out of your hands and throw fireballs.
You can make a fucking volcano.
Murius could just like water plants before.
Okay.
So we just...
All right, so the ass tics just destroyed everybody.
Okay.
Let's go.
Now we've got the story.
Once they save Murius, they're gonna instantly say,
You are now our best friend.
Let's go back.
The portal.
Yeah, these guys made it.
But think of how many got toasted.
Anyway, where are we?
This looks like an old Greek settlement.
We can reestablish ourselves here.
It looks so peaceful here with no Aztecs.
It's the perfect place to build up and get more followers.
There is already...
Who's the guy that you followed for two hours?
We don't talk about that.
A field which we can use.
That's deleted from the blog.
He is the extent of your influence.
You can only do things within this ring.
You can extend the green influence ring by placing more buildings and having more people.
Yeah.
When you're ready to learn how to feed your people,
click on the gold scroll over the field leader.
Oh, what's that?
What did it just do?
Let me take a look what we got.
What we got working with here?
Who sleeps like this?
It's just...
He's sleeping with one leg in the air crossed over
because he's farting so much that he has to sleep in this position.
He has to sleep in the constant I'm gonna fart position.
That's unbelievable.
It's still funny.
Your villagers are going to need food very soon, leader.
Move your hand over this field,
then click and hold the action button to pick up the grain.
When you've got 200 food in your hand,
drop all through it into the storehouse.
Enough food in there, boss.
How much do I need?
Can I hold?
And it goes...
We now have enough food.
We need to get our people working.
This is so much better than the last one.
It actually tells me...
Villagers can be turned into disciples who will work at the job you assign them.
Pick up a villager, then put them down on a field.
Yeah, that's so much better.
I can actually see who's working here.
Now place the villager down over the field.
You going for it?
One of the seven, two out of seven.
Okay, good.
Reestablish the village, yes.
Fill it up.
Those farmers can handle that small field with no problem, boss.
They actually knew what this game was supposed to be on the first one.
And our town expand.
Grab and pull a tree out of the ground and drop it into the storehouse.
You can still do that.
That's good.
When it gets desperate.
Owls and tribute.
Got some wood.
Do I have any choppers?
Some disciple foresters to collect wood for us.
Pick up a villager and drop them next to a tree to make them a disciple forester.
Make a total of three foresters.
Make two disciple foresters.
Now place the villager next to a tree.
We got some nifty foresting going on, boss.
No, I didn't.
All right, they're gone.
As of February 20th, 2022, links are gone.
Not links.
Well, that just shows how much, well, that's how I really feel.
What was I saying?
Winks are gone.
I was trying to drop it in here.
There's a wink right there.
It's changing.
It's changing this next week.
Click on the gold scroll.
April?
No, not April.
That's like two months from now.
The statues on your town center represent your town's desires.
This shows what your people would like to build next.
Keeping your people happy is important.
They will let you know if they desire a building type.
See how the statue is carrying grain?
That means you want food.
That represents the people's desires for food.
If they need ore or wood, they will let you know.
Keep an eye on the statue as it will change.
Why is he wearing a backpack?
This place's height represents how good or evil you are.
A fucking backpack.
From the top, a flame or a fountain will spring as you perform your good deeds.
The whole city will shift to show you if you are good or evil.
This statue lets you know your people's desires.
Watch the height of the statue.
The higher it is, the more they need their desire.
Okay.
This scroll shows the impressiveness of your city.
Its population and happiness.
There is plenty of other useful information about your growing metropolis.
Refer to it often.
So that's the need.
That's how evil I am.
Hold your hand over the statues and leave it there to get more detail.
Alright, that's good.
So right now we're doing great.
Ohms.
Oh, this is so much better.
Oh my god.
It's so much better.
Look at that.
If you get, it's wow.
They, what an improvement from the last game.
All right.
Why am I evil?
I didn't even do anything.
I'm 0.1% evil.
How?
I didn't do shit.
All right.
Let's keep going.
Your people desire houses.
Move your hand over the rotating building.
Then click and hold the action button to drag it off.
Wait, what?
We need the right buildings and food if we're going to support a powerful army.
So hold on.
This is how you make buildings now?
Click the action button again to place it down.
All right.
We got to, we got to put, I got to do this right because this is the first like actual mission.
Let's go back here.
That's right.
Keep going.
We can speed it up by picking up a tree and dropping it on the building.
How much wood does it need?
Your villagers will use that to build the house with.
Did I lost the tutorial?
No, this is the real game.
The tutorial, we were on tutorial island.
Now how much do you need?
320 wood, what do I have here?
609 wood, what the fuck?
I need a builder, right?
Come here.
You.
Builder.
Disciple builder.
He's going to corrupt the save again.
What?
Place 11 foundations.
Are you serious?
Oh, I got to place 11 houses?
That's a lot of houses.
Keep going.
How much, how much wood do I need?
Subtitles are riot.
What do you need subtitles for?
How do I rotate?
Is there like an altar?
R?
Middle mouse?
Right mouse?
How do I rotate?
I can't rotate.
Tell me how to rotate.
The house is finished.
And look how delighted the villagers are.
Oh, okay, good.
You can also drag a building blueprint off an existing house.
Really?
Move your hand over the existing house.
Hold down the action button and drag to get the blueprint.
If you want to cancel an action and empty your hand,
simply shake it briskly left and right.
We need to have, these laws have to be good.
Photoshop.
That's not even accurate.
Why did you say that?
I'm, I'm, I can't.
Why?
It can also help to build buildings yourself.
Come on, I want to learn.
This is God building.
Yes, you do it by picking up resources the building needs.
What can sign in the way?
Then hold your hand over the building
and press and hold the action button.
This is very useful,
but you do lose some of the resource in the process.
So wait, I can build?
Make two disciple builders.
We can also create some disciple builders
to help with our city building.
Just drop a villager by house.
Then you drop them down by a house.
It's under construction to create one.
Hold the action button.
Make three disciple builders.
Okay, hold on.
Why am I using ray key to try to build a house?
That's not how this works.
What do I have to do with the tree in my hand?
Keep going.
Or drop the person by a building site.
I need four more foundations.
Wait, this is facing the wrong way.
Okay, well, all right.
We're going to expand this way anyways.
Let's go over here.
We'll have like the one community, one community.
Three more foundations.
You need to create a disciple builder.
This town sucks.
This wasn't even in the last game.
This will be the expensive house that's back here.
You need to create a disciple builder.
I know, hold on.
Excellent.
We've got a nice little troop of builders.
Can I get rid of the sign?
It's blocking me.
Fields within roads.
You may lay out roads.
You can fill inside them with a field by dragging out.
The field will make the road as its boundary.
What?
If you lay out roads, how do I lay out a road?
I didn't do that part yet.
That's not in the tutorial.
Drag from the road.
Oh, shit.
You can make roads in this one.
So we have to...
All right.
Should I go from here and just like this?
No, this is a bad road.
That's not right.
Building snap to the roads.
Oh, fuck.
This is wrong.
Oh, this is really bad because now these will never be on a road
unless I go in the middle here.
All right, here we go.
Ready?
Can I move the houses?
No, no, no, no.
That's making another house.
I didn't know this was possible.
Come on, give me a break.
That's all right.
It's okay.
Whatever.
It's the first level.
Who cares?
This is the problem, though.
All right.
So we need to go from here to here.
I can't go like...
What some roads are like this.
What am I supposed to do?
Delete them all?
Yes.
It was done.
It was done with a crayon by a five-year-old,
but I didn't know you could even do this shit.
That's fine.
It's fine.
It works.
Let's connect these.
But I'm gonna need to construct five villas.
Hold on.
Let's go out to here and then we're gonna...
Oh, fuck.
This is so wrong.
If I had known that roads existed,
I would have done this differently.
All right.
We're just gonna bucket.
This is the first level.
Ooh, it's the first level.
It doesn't matter.
All right.
Now I need to make five villas.
I have enough builders, right?
What do people need?
Free time.
Throw a villager.
No, I'm not throwing a villager right now.
Did you know?
With a villager in hand,
keep the hand still to get detailed information
about the person you're holding.
I need to make villas.
Uh, I was too busy looking at the roads.
What do I have to do for a villa?
Adult population, 34.
We need some...
We have a high brick road.
Good.
You've built enough houses for now.
Oh, that's a house as a villa.
We must get the people to multiply.
Oh, dear.
It's embarrassing talking.
Nowhere it ain't.
Where's the cow?
He's talking about breeding.
Breeding, boss.
You hear me, goody?
Just over here, fart sleeping.
We need three breeder disciples
to satisfy the village's needs.
Drop a man or woman from your hand
next to one of the opposite sex.
Disciple breeders will continue forever.
All right, you and you.
Excellent.
We need two more to satisfy the village's needs.
We need a breeder, breeder, breeder, breeder,
builder, builder, breeder, breed.
Oh, you are a breeder.
Okay.
Oh, we need...
All right, we got a male here.
Uh, you.
And you stop what you're doing?
Marvelous.
Do that instead.
You've now created enough breeders.
Any disciple will carry on doing that one job forever
unless you give them another job.
They want free time?
Do they have...
No, breeding...
No, they want free time.
They want to breed and they want to sleep.
Well, I just built the houses, so...
Forever, forever sex.
Sort of.
All right, now...
I'm gonna get some breeding here.
What we need to do is increase our population.
That's what we're doing.
Now we've got some breeders.
It should be easy to get 75 villages.
Increase population by 41.
All right, hold on.
What is this?
Ore desire?
This is ore right...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We need some...
This is new.
Builder.
Mine worker.
This is a new resource.
Click the gold scroll when you are ready to learn about the toolbar.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
I gotta get some people working in the mines.
Too young to be a...
What?
Who is it?
Karen Segal James.
Happiness.
Minus 0.84.
Depressed.
Health 100.
Breed.
Okay, well...
Whatever.
Right, let's open the toolbar.
See?
There is a flag at the bottom left of the screen.
Toolbar.
All you need to do to open it is click the action button on it once.
Okay, that's kind of in a weird spot.
It's like all the way down here.
Hey, what's that?
That is the toolbar.
There's gotta be a hotkey for this, right?
Good.
Now click again to close it.
There's gotta be a hotbar for this.
F1.
Oh, yeah.
That's much better.
So this is awesome.
So much easier.
These tabs are used to navigate the different menus.
The tab currently selected is the construction tab.
So the menu shown is the construction menu.
Each menu is divided into submenus.
We are going to show you how to access some advanced features.
Advanced, boys and girls.
Bring up the tribute menu.
Tribute menu, F4.
This is the coolest part of the menu.
Torture pit?
The tribute is like a form of currency.
Why is that the first thing there?
You can spend it on whatever you like, including new buildings.
You can improve your godly powers.
And add constructions or features to your town.
You earn tribute by finishing challenges
and doing other impressive things.
We have plenty of tribute at the moment.
Enough to buy a temple.
So the faithful will flock to this edifice erected in your glory.
Their earnest worship will be amplified in this holy place.
And not only will your people be happier,
but your entire town will be much more enhanced and impressiveness.
Okay, let's get it.
There it is.
You can now build a temple.
This is a good thing with a capital G.
Your town's impressiveness will increase.
Select the temple from the construction menu.
Then place it down in your town.
Torture pit.
But why would I?
I'm like afraid to do that.
All right.
Oh, this is huge.
We're going to put this...
That's not a bad spot for it.
Or should we have this for...
This is like our real estate community.
This would be our business section over here.
Right?
Like down here?
No, these are going to be houses over here.
I think like right here.
No, it's going to be connected to a road behind here.
The torture pit is going to go down here.
So it's all right.
I'm thinking like right here.
Select the temple from the construction menu.
Then place it down in your town.
Right here.
Right in the edge.
Some buildings require all to be built.
There are two sources of all.
The first is the ore mine and ore deposit in the ground
that can be mined by your villagers.
There are also all rocks.
The villagers can mine these but at the same time
you can add them to your storehouse yourself.
Oh, I just pick up the ore.
So they can't do this.
I can do this.
Here we go.
Ore is over here.
Boom.
Oh, boom.
I got to be careful I don't hit anybody with this.
I don't want to hit anybody with this.
Let's just pick them all up.
Get it over with and done.
And then conquer whatever we need to conquer.
Oh wait, 22.
All right, temple.
Temple's not built yet.
It's time for the torture pit.
No, I'm not a fucking monster.
That's not the second building I'm going to build.
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I got it.
Builder.
You.
Who are you?
You build.
I'll help.
You coming over here too?
You're going to help build?
No.
Why are you just following this person?
Okay.
Why have I run out of trees?
They need to breed.
My population's doing fine.
15, 14.
We're almost done.
Is that it?
Why am I holding like a dead tree?
Oh, I think I'm outside of the ring.
Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
I'm inside the ring.
Oh, it needs ore.
Oh, okay.
Oh, come here.
1,200 ore.
1,000 ore.
What?
Come on.
Is this ore?
What are you doing?
300 ore.
Almost there.
Where's the cow?
Resting.
Because the cow is not doing...
The cow can't do anything yet.
But we'll check in.
It's still sleeping.
It's been like seven days.
What a lazy bastard.
No, he's a baby.
And plus, wait, it's a cow.
It's a she.
It's a cow.
Cow, it's a cow.
How do people get so many channel points?
If you subscribe, you get double.
All right, we got the temple now.
We're very impressive.
Oops, I just dropped a rock on it.
I just smashed a window accidentally.
It says, is it okay?
All right, impressiveness went up.
I need one more population.
Very impressive city.
Then people will come from far and wide to live in it.
Civic buildings are a good way to increase impressiveness.
Nobody gets hurt and we get more followers making us more powerful.
Why'd you build the temple on an incline?
Look, those people are migrating.
They want to live in our town.
They're bringing all their worldly goods.
Hooray!
People of all tribes will be drawn from far and wide.
Here they come.
To live in a good city.
Come on, it's time to do something.
Here they come.
They're coming because they want to see the impressive city.
Come on over.
Take a look.
Have you seen the cow?
Take a look at the cow.
All right, it's time to do some work.
You got to go.
They'll make people laugh and stuff.
Let's not disturb him.
I can't even wait.
All right, I'm just waiting for them to come in.
All right, who's this?
What are these people doing?
I don't like the look of those fellows.
Why, they have swords?
Where are they going?
I can't grab them.
This is an RTS.
This person has patrols.
Okay.
Look at that town.
It's not dissimilar from ours.
Hi, guys.
All right, are they almost here?
Let's welcome them.
Let's welcome them by immediately grabbing the person with the flag
and throwing them as far as we can.
I don't like that, though.
They're going to come over here and kill us.
All right, anybody who's at the temple?
Anybody?
No worshipers?
Here, use it.
Do you worship at that building?
Oh, here they come.
These people have come to join our town.
Pick up their migration flag and drop it anywhere within our influence ring.
Wait, they have a migration flag?
Okay.
18,000.
Torture pit, torture pit, torture pit.
Oh, God.
All right, hold on.
Look at how many people are here now.
This is Breeder.
This is...
Wait, before anybody does anything.
Let's get some more people.
I need some workers.
All right, let's go.
How many people are in this field?
Zero to 17.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Guys, guys, guys, guys.
I know you just came in, but here.
Let's go.
I need more.
I need more buildings.
Okay, wait.
Breeder.
We want Breeder again.
We want Farmer.
What are the needs?
I'm looking.
I'm a good guy.
4.9% good.
Pick on the gold scroll.
Armories are where you can turn your people into warriors.
Really?
Holy shit.
Warriors who can take other towns and lands by force.
Buying the armory is the first step towards having an army.
Open the toolbar and click the tribute tab.
Armory.
Why build that when you can build an armory?
Why build the temple when you could build an armory?
It's burning.
It's just that every voice is burning, isn't it?
Recruit powerful armies made up of strong brave swordsmen.
Almost scarily eager to do battle in your name against your enemies.
Let's get it.
Select the armory from the construction menu.
Then place it down in your town.
All right, where should I put this?
How about over here?
Where's the nearest town?
Down?
All right, I want it down here.
Somewhere like over here on the edge.
Where's the entrance?
Right there?
Okay, so we're going to go like this.
We're going to have a road eventually connect here.
Right there.
Let's get some roads.
How about like this?
Split around the farm.
That looks nice.
Oh, that looks nice.
Oh, this way over here.
Oh, look, that looks nice.
Then from here, we're going to go this way.
God sucks at design.
Why am I evil for doing this?
Oh, because I'm building an evil building.
I get it.
It's an evil building.
Go.
Evil.
How much does it need?
810 wood, 500 ore.
Uneven.
Doesn't need to be even.
Marius, when are you going to wake up?
I want to play fun games with you.
Like kick the tree.
Do you remember kick the tree?
You love that game, Marius.
All right, let's get some ore.
No, that's not right.
The green ring you see is the extent of your influence.
Oh, shit.
I need miners.
How much ore do I have?
Is it?
Let me go to my stockpile.
I got a lot.
How much do I get ore?
I'm full on wood.
Wait.
Okay, that's good.
Gee, the people can be slow at building, boys.
We should do some god building.
You know, they were speeding up.
That is sweet.
All right, now we can make warriors.
They're recruited via the flags on the top of the armory.
Pick up one of the flags on the armory.
Then place it in the highlighted area.
So I have to make war?
Make platoons?
Number of troops, number of melee.
It's melee.
God, I know how to say that word.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Dropping the flag will make a standard size platoon.
To recruit a larger platoon, hold down the action button.
Then drag away from the flag.
You can make a huge army so you can just drag this gigantic area.
Wait, why are you coming over here?
I didn't tell you to come over here.
Boy, too many people want to be warriors.
Wait, don't I have to tell you to be a warrior?
All right, are you sure you guys don't want to be farmers?
Oh, God.
Okay.
I can't click it.
Where are they going?
These are the best thing ever.
But you're going to need to keep them under control.
So you need to know all about these here flags.
Every platoon has a flag.
You can see it held up high above the army.
And also in the bottom right hand corner of the screen.
This is an armory tab.
Each platoon type has a different color and symbol on their flag.
To make them easy to identify.
This one is a swordsman platoon.
The flags also tell you what rank the platoon is.
Those pips along the top indicate the rank from raw recruits to seasoned veterans.
If you click on the flags in the bottom right with the action button,
you pick up the flag and gain control of the platoon.
Okay.
Click on the flag with the move button and you'll go directly to the platoon.
And there you have it.
The basics of army flags.
Pick up the platoon flag, boys.
Pick up the platoon flag.
Health 120 to 20.
That's kind of in a weird spot for a platoon here.
Let's go.
That's perfect.
Click on the highlighted area to tell them to go there.
If you want to cancel an action and empty your hand,
simply shake his brisket left and right.
So I don't have to have influence over here.
That's kind of a big deal.
I don't have to have influence?
So I can just make a ton of people and just go conquer towns.
They just go where I can't.
That's so awesome.
Actually having control over what they do.
Because remember last time it was if you were outside,
it was like I had to throw people to gain access to be able.
It was that's a much needed change.
I had to throw that one unkillable guy around the map.
Do I want to do this by force?
I guess it's just teaching me how this works.
All right, where are we going?
Didn't these people all just come over willingly?
Everyone just came over here.
This is an empty town.
They're coming?
Raise it to the ground.
There's nothing to raise.
It's just a few houses in a temple.
They eat twice the food?
Oh god, here they come.
How do I put the flag down like that?
All right guys, do what you do.
Diplomacy first, always.
Well, we're already doing this.
Take over town by impressing what?
Impressing the stones?
Impress them with how many soldiers you have.
I mean, that works, I guess.
How are we doing?
Do we need anything?
Homes?
We need some houses.
Okay, we're going to get some houses.
We need some villa.
I know this is terrible.
It sucks, but who cares?
We're going to do two more.
I know it's terrible.
I know, trust me.
I'm the one making it.
You don't think I know it's horrible?
We'll do like three more houses.
That's fine.
Do they get it?
Dermot the bomb.
Dermot, he has earpods in.
Oh shit, I can't hear you.
And so what?
Do I just gain influence?
I can't hear it.
Impressiveness required to capture.
There's 19 people still here.
That's weird.
Oh, and there we go.
We got it.
Hooray.
Now where are they going?
More followers for our glorious war machine.
Yeah, now you own this town.
You can do anything in the great influence ring,
just like in your town.
That's what I need.
Attack is the best form of defense.
Get your armies out there.
I adore it.
A newly created platoon starts at experience level one.
Unless they fight, they gain experience.
When the platoon's experience reaches a certain threshold,
they go up to the next experience level
and with it, their skills such as fighting and speed improve.
Lastly, if you want to disband the platoon,
drop the platoon's flag onto an armory
and let those weaklings off the hook.
Oh, that.
OK, so they can go back to being regular.
OK.
You see, you can win by taking over towns using force
or by impressing the people in those other towns.
Need a builder over here.
War solves everything.
How many of you guys are farmers?
Build.
You can win by a mixture of impressing and war.
They're all breeders.
Alas, the time of innocence draws to a close.
You must take a step down the road of good.
And by the way, war is evil and I'm evil.
You get where I'm coming from.
Time to choose, boys.
Time to choose?
Take over every town on the land.
Oh, shit.
I got to take these two over.
Be good.
Be evil.
Um, well, hold on.
Oh, it's time to awaken.
It's time to, but not yet.
Not yet.
Let's let the fucking hype build a little more.
Another important part of the toolbar is the objectives menu.
Select the objectives tab to open it.
F2?
F1?
It's not F2.
What is it?
Objectives tab?
Right.
Here you can find all the important tasks
that will enable you to complete a land.
And also some less important tasks that are just interesting.
We're almost there.
The tabs at the bottom right control which objectives you are looking at.
Oh, that's cool.
Either all of them or a selection from the total.
The objectives window up in the top left also displays the objectives.
You only need to complete the gold scroll objective to complete the land.
Okay.
But you earn more tribute by undertaking some of the other ones.
Yeah.
Yes.
You earn tribute for every objective you complete.
Oh, the side quest?
They call it the gold scroll.
I'm not clicking on...
No, I don't want to do that yet.
There's like this...
All this stuff.
All right.
That's good to know.
As our city grows, the greater the distance our villagers will have to travel.
To aid their little feet, we can build roads.
To build a road, grab an existing road by holding down the action button.
Then drag out the shape of the road you want.
When you are happy with it, click the action button.
So you got to build roads first.
And then you block out the town.
Yeah.
Okay.
Have a go at building a road.
All right.
Well, I need to have...
We'll just have this connected here because it's tutorial.
Whatever.
Who cares?
Doesn't matter.
I had to do that just to keep...
Oh, that looks really bad.
From a satellite, that looks really bad.
It doesn't matter.
This is level one.
We'll block out the next complete village.
We haven't even woken up the creature yet, so we're good.
All right.
What's this side quest?
What does it do?
Drunk city builder.
Hey, you!
Great God!
If you exist, I know you can hear me.
My daughter's fallen pregnant.
She says no man has touched her.
It's an immaculate conception.
So it must be down to you.
You are responsible for the child.
Pay me a dowry of 1,000 wood.
I have no idea how this happened.
How does she get pregnant?
She's having sex to my left.
Whoever is responsible and clear your good name.
Something is amiss here, lead out.
That was ridiculous.
Maybe you should see where she's going.
Where is she going?
Something is amiss?
What are we doing?
Clean up those ants.
There's bugs everywhere.
Who left out like a can of food?
Come on.
I don't know.
I don't know if that was scripted enough, but that was fucking funny.
Who's playing the automaton?
All right.
How?
Watch out.
The person has an axe.
Click on the gold scroll.
No, I'm busy.
New follow quest.
I don't care if this is two hours.
At least I don't have to be behind her.
Where are you going?
All the way?
Are you walking all the way to one of these houses?
Okay.
Oh my God.
What?
She's going right over here.
Why do I feel like one of these random townspeople is going to just throw something at her?
Or like a attacker or something.
They keep walking over here menacingly.
Where are you going?
I don't know why there's so many bugs.
I don't know.
Here we go.
It's because the houses were so far away.
This is the home of the community.
You had to walk across the whole town pregnant.
This is like scale it back.
This is like probably 10 miles.
This is like at least four to five miles is scaled.
Okay.
So now what?
Is she going to be like you're the dad or something?
Hello handsome.
I know something was going on.
No such thing.
What?
Someone ought to let her father know about this.
I don't understand.
Hold on.
She's like she's pregnant.
How is she?
Okay.
She's having she's having sex while like nine months pregnant?
What?
Wait, what the fuck?
Where's the okay?
Where is this guy?
He was in the other community.
What community was he in?
This one?
Uh hey.
I got something for you.
You?
Hello?
Can I talk to you?
Uh I was gonna bring you over here.
No come here.
It took too long.
What?
No I didn't.
He's already gone.
You have to put him in the chimney.
She's walking away?
Oh shit.
There she is.
All right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
No look.
It's all right.
She'll do it again.
She'll go back.
It's all right.
Oh we need ore.
How many people are in the mine?
Zero.
What?
Disciple mine worker.
Disciple mine.
Oh no, no, no.
You you keep doing your thing.
Disciple mine.
All right.
We'll go back to that quest.
It's gonna happen.
Just remind me that it's happening and I will catch it.
Click on the gold scroll.
It's time to awaken Murius.
Creature's waking up.
And it was a long sleep but here we are.
Ah I'm over here.
He's scared.
He doesn't want to leave the pen.
Why are you scared?
Let's use the leash to get him to move.
Okay.
To grab the leash click on the creature with the action button
or you can just press the L key.
Okay.
Grab the creature's leash.
Here we go.
He's been in the pen for ages.
Make him come outside for a bit.
Move him outside by clicking the action button once on the ground.
Excellent.
With your creature on the leash you can move him or get him to do things.
And more importantly to do what you want him to do.
Oh my god.
Why are you so slow?
He slept like a hundred years?
Well.
Well done.
That's how you get the creature to move.
The creature's hungry.
Let's feed him.
Okay.
What do you want?
Food?
Grain?
With the leash in the hand click on the field.
Don't get grain.
Here it comes.
I'm going to get that grain.
Yes.
Eat it.
It's delicious.
That's better.
He doesn't look as hungry now.
When click the action button on something with the leash the creature will try.
He ate the entire field?
Double click the action button on that rock by the field and he will be leashed to it.
That's right.
Marvelous.
Does the leash actually work in this game?
You should now teach your creature whether what he does is good or bad.
Should I eat a villager?
Oh dear.
He's going to eat a villager.
You should teach him not to do that.
Nonsense.
Eating villagers will make him strong.
Click and hold the action button on him.
Move the mouse quickly from side to side to punish him for eating that person.
He didn't eat anybody yet.
Move the mouse slowly.
Pet him and reward him.
Eating people is fine by me you see.
He didn't eat anybody.
He has not eaten this person.
So he hasn't done anything wrong.
You haven't done anything wrong yet.
Why would I discipline you?
Just pick somebody up.
All right.
You're good.
I'll sometimes choose to eat a villager.
What do you mean sometimes?
It's sensitive.
Wait.
I'll often choose.
No, no, no, no.
Don't often choose to eat a villager.
How do I?
That was horrible.
Oh my god.
I knocked him down.
What is he doing?
Oh my god.
That's so bad.
You're on the road to making a nasty creature.
What a senseless waste of human life.
If you want to cancel an action and empty your hand,
simply shake it briskly left and right.
That is just about everything you need to know right now.
Why don't you try experimenting with your creature?
Okay.
Let's experiment.
What do you think is over here?
Can you pick this up?
Try.
I can't do that.
I'm going to eat snack on that grain.
No, stop eating the grain.
You eat too much grain.
Oh my god.
Can he eat bugs?
Wait.
Come over here.
Eat the bugs.
Can you play with the bugs or eat the bugs or something?
Wait.
Pick up this rock.
I have to teach you.
Pick up rock.
Okay.
Good.
Very good.
Do not eat rock.
He's learning.
He's getting inquisitive.
Okay.
Now you figure out what you want to do with it.
Put it down.
Very good.
All right.
What about the?
I had enough for today.
Okay.
Well, that was a lot for one day.
This is a rock.
That's enough for one day.
Food coma.
All right.
How are we doing?
People want to sleep.
Do I not have enough houses?
So let them sleep.
All right.
What about the daughter?
There he is.
Where is she?
Because look for the pregnant lady going.
Okay.
We missed it.
We got to do it again.
Oh, he's up.
Where are you going?
I want you to learn.
I want you to do things.
I want you to.
Why are you so?
Why is his stomach so big?
Just kind of doing a perimeter.
Look at how fat the stomach is.
Is he blowing a kiss?
He's so wonderful.
I could enter.
I could entertain some villagers.
Yeah.
Do that.
Entertain the villagers.
How is this entertaining a villager?
He's like smelling them.
I am going to play with that villager.
Okay.
Cool.
You good work.
I did.
I had fun.
Bye.
He just wanted to smell him.
Bugs.
Yes.
Very good.
Everybody loves him.
Good job.
Yeah.
Very.
No, I'm trying to pet him.
Good job.
Entertain the villagers.
All right.
Let's do.
Now we have to take.
All right.
He he'll be fine.
He's going to learn.
I need more houses.
Let's see.
Right.
For creature.
I'm starving.
Fuck.
How much grain is here?
All right.
Here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Take some of this.
What are you doing over here?
What are you doing?
What is he?
Is he bringing this?
Where are you bringing this tree?
So pointless.
Wait, what are you going to eat this?
No, no, no, no.
Eat this instead.
Eat that instead.
No, no, no.
Eat this instead.
Hey, hey, leash, leash, leash, leash.
Eat this.
Eat the grain.
Eat that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Eat this.
Why did he pick up the tree?
He picked up the tree and gave the tree as a present
to one of the villagers.
Eat it.
Eat that.
Isn't it good?
Yeah, it is.
I'm going to...
What does it say?
I'm going to play with that villager.
All right.
What do I do with this tree?
Oh, somebody already picked it up.
Okay, good.
ADHD cow.
Yeah.
That's so much fun just to watch him grow.
He wants to play with...
This person's not interested at all.
All right.
The pregnant lady.
There she goes.
All right.
We're ready.
Now I'm going to...
Hold on.
What do I need to do?
I need to build...
I need to build something else.
Where's he going?
Why is he picking up trees?
Why is he doing this?
What's the logic here?
Is he trying to plant trees
or he's giving trees to people?
I'm going...
I'm dead.
What?
What is he doing?
That's the wrong store.
That's not...
That's incorrect.
I know he's trying to help, but...
He's locked himself in here.
That's not correct.
All right.
You tried though.
Good try.
You tried.
Nice work.
Thank you for trying.
He's just a baby.
He doesn't know.
He didn't eat anybody.
Okay.
What was I doing?
I'm too distracted.
ADHD cow and ADHD streamer.
This is a horrible, horrible fucking combination.
All right.
Lady, lady, lady, lady, lady.
Come here.
Is she there?
Here she goes.
Entertain is equals eat.
What?
Here we go.
So now what?
Do I just put him down here
and knock on the door or...
I get 20,000 tribute for this.
Hello, handsome.
Here we go.
This way, that way.
I...
I can't believe it.
I apologize.
I'm so sorry for accusing you wrongly.
I'll make sure the child is raised faithful and true to you.
So what...
That's all I had to do.
Okay.
That works.
That's 20,000 tribute.
What is he doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Shall I poo on that villager?
I don't think so.
Why?
Why would you do that?
Why would you even ask that question?
Should I...
I'm going to eat that villager.
First, you're going to shit on them,
but you decided you're going to eat them instead.
That's so rude.
Okay.
He doesn't know.
He's like fucked up.
Was he drunk?
Where are you going?
Gather from the fields?
Yes.
Get all...
Do that.
Yes.
Gather from the fields and put it in.
He can do it all in one go.
All right.
He's going to put it in the wood pile, isn't he?
Nope.
Good.
What's going on?
What do I hear?
Like a...
We're going to attack?
All right.
Go to bed.
Maybe he'll growl.
All right.
That's good.
I need to...
Wait a minute.
I'm just going to go kill these people.
What are we doing over here?
What do we need?
Sleep.
We need some more buildings.
Is the storeroom built?
The storeroom is built.
Everyone's just like kind of standing around.
Disciple farmer.
Guys, get some shit done.
Oh, there's two more.
Okay.
We need wood.
Disciple forester.
Come here.
Pick this up.
Let's go.
For Valar.
What do we got over here?
We have...
Let me see.
Stay over here.
Because seriously, if they attack,
I want them to be right there.
I need trees.
Hold on.
Let me...
Let's build another house.
Forty...
How many people are here now?
A lot, right?
Yeah.
Let's do...
Just get another house here or whatever.
I have so much food.
You know what?
I'm going to take a bunch of this food.
I'm going to take like fucking 10,000.
They're not even eating it.
I'm bringing it over here.
That's evil?
I own the place.
What is he doing?
I'm going to have a dump on that villager's head.
Why do you keep saying this?
What is wrong with you?
He never does it though.
He always threatens to take a shit on somebody,
but he never does.
Should you poo on somebody?
Wait, we're going to scroll.
Come with me.
We're going to go...
I want you over here.
Can I...
Yeah, I want to take you...
Take a walk.
I want you to go impress these people over here.
You go explore.
Go learn some stuff.
Who needs homes?
My chat's all fucked up.
Hold on a second.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want...
I need to save the goddamn game.
Holy shit.
That would have been a disaster.
Atma Starfish, thanks for the five community subs.
Create a new save.
Can you imagine two hours going by?
Take over the time.
All right, I'm ready.
Let's go.
How you doing?
It's nighttime, but there's no ore over here, though.
I need to get over...
All right.
Is it time to have a fight?
I got to fix my chat.
Hold on a second.
It's like...
It's all fucked up.
I can't see what anybody's saying.
Even in the other window.
Hold on.
Okay.
Yeah, you guys are like...
I'm full two or three minutes behind me.
All right.
How do I just make it so the scroll doesn't happen?
I can't, like, lock this.
Is there a way to remove the ability to scroll on,
like, chat window in Twitch?
Because it doesn't matter what I do.
I have to go get, like, uh...
I have to go get, like, my iPad or something.
Don't tell him.
No, tell me!
Remove the mouse wheel?
I don't think anything...
Can I lock it?
Make it so the program takes exclusive rights to the cursor.
I don't even know how the fuck to even do that.
I'll just deal with it.
I'm just gonna have to do this, like, every, like, few minutes.
Here we go.
Okay.
Full screen the game?
The game is full screen.
There...
I mean, there is no...
This game is, like, 12, 15 years old.
All right, here we go.
Let's fight.
Ready.
Go fight.
Go attack, go kill.
Where are they?
Why don't you guys go the long way?
Jerma, can you explain how you got this game to work?
Do you have the discs?
Yes.
Uh, so this game is currently running on the fan patch.
There is...
You have to get patch 1.1 and 1.2,
and then you have to get the 1.3 fan patch,
which fixes everything in the game.
Wait, actually, you know what?
Can I just...
Should I just attack?
Get it!
Just spy cap this fucking thing.
Who cares?
They're not even coming back.
They're not even paying attention.
They're too busy.
They're too busy fighting on the two-fort bridge
to realize I've taken the briefcase three times already.
We win.
Wait, they're not coming over here, are they?
No, I'm gonna get it.
This is gonna be it.
I got it.
I'm gonna own it.
And then there's only one more town to take.
Where's the creature?
I'm gonna eat that villager.
Why are you doing it so menacingly?
All right.
No, no, don't.
Don't.
Just...
No, no, no, no.
Do not...
It's...
You know what?
It's probably more efficient for him to eat villages
than to eat like 5,000 grain.
I'm gonna be honest.
Is it okay to destroy those trees?
I'm going to turn that tree into wood chippings.
All right, good.
We can take out some of his rage.
Take out some of your frustrations.
Like, do it.
Yeah!
You need this.
I'm going to play with that villager.
Good.
Okay.
Have fun.
We're actually...
We're gonna get it.
I can't believe I just took this village without anything.
No!
I can't.
Ugh, it's fucking scroll wheel bullshit.
I'm actually gonna have to get my iPad.
Like, I can't believe I got the village.
It's iPad time.
Punish him?
Oh, wait, wait.
We got...
Hold on.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight.
We have your land.
Now what the fuck are you gonna do?
We're getting attacked, boys.
Where?
Kill them and drill them.
Oh, fuck.
Whoa, my God, dude.
Uh-oh.
Are we winning?
We're not winning this fight.
We're not winning the fight.
I just got fucking collapsed on...
Oh, my God.
They're here with their whole entire force.
Uh...
Murius!
Stop playing with trees.
I need you over here for a little bit.
I'm out of breath.
Stop running with a tree in your hand.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna gather from the field.
Good job.
Okay.
Excellent work.
I need you over here.
It's time for you to start.
You have to...
It's time for you to have fun.
I need you over here.
Over here, over here, over here.
You're being a bad parent.
Look, I'm just trying to defend the world here.
Coming.
See?
This is what I'm talking about.
Show them your fucking anger.
Show them your might.
Tell them they can't be in here.
You know what to do.
Eat them.
Leash to the army.
I'm going to stomp all over the platoon.
Good.
Do it.
Unleash it.
Is it faster than you?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get him.
There you go, Murius.
Unleash your anger.
I'm out of breath.
It's all right.
Just kick another one.
Eat one.
They have no match.
Start eating people.
Eat them.
There we go.
Good job.
Come on.
I'm starving.
You'll have plenty of food in about five seconds, Murius.
Good fucking thunderclap.
There it is.
Yes.
Dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead.
Murius, I love you.
You've done such a great job.
Unbelievable work.
Unbelievable.
Nice work.
Do you see that rage?
Okay.
Now literally eat as many of these people as you want.
He only eats live meat.
You're very good.
I'll munch on their villagers all the time.
They taste so strange.
He's going to get a dig.
Look what he did.
I'm so happy with him.
Taste for human flesh.
All right.
Time for you to go to bed.
You know what?
We wiped out their whole village.
Good job.
I actually need a...
What do we need here?
Inspect.
You can actually go...
You can go to bed.
You need to rest.
What do you think about that, Murius?
We need that storehouse built quicker.
I'm going to build the storehouse way more effective than he was in the last game.
He's just aiming to please.
He wants to please so much.
That's not the store...
Oh, it is.
So useful.
You deserve a week's rest after this.
Excellent job.
No, I didn't want to...
Very, very good.
You are so...
What a good cow.
Link?
Yeah.
In fact, I probably should bring him back to sleep.
Okay.
We need...
I have one more town to take over.
There's a scroll over here though.
What a beautiful sunset.
Yeah.
You gotta love a big ball of fire.
Let's see it again.
By clicking the action button on the sky, the hand will change to sundial mode.
When the action button is released, the sun will move in the heavens.
I can change the day-night cycle?
The power of the sun.
But with great power comes great responsibility.
Force, show us how it's done.
Change time to day.
But all light needs a shadow.
Change the time to night.
I feel like this is fucking with everybody's head.
Imagine you were outside when this happened.
Well done.
All right.
So you can chat in now.
That's cool.
Oh, rooster.
No, I need help.
This rooster wakes me up every single day.
I can't get enough sleep.
Please help me to silence it.
Maybe we can help him, leader.
Such tasks...
I don't understand.
...really rewards, you know.
Roosters always crow when the sun comes up.
Perhaps if the sun came up a few times in a row,
the rooster would keep crowing until it gets hoarse.
But that's going to fuck up every country on earth.
Silence this rooster by making three days happen instantly.
And fuck up.
All of Wall Street will close and the Dow will drop 25 million points.
Is this smart?
He's still going.
You're rapidly moving the earth.
Everyone will just fly off.
We'd all be like, no!
Everyone would fly into space.
The rotating rooster has lost its voice.
10,000?
We'd be crushed?
Would we get crushed?
I'm thinking of crushed.
No, that's not right.
Come on.
I'm trying to satisfy the bloodlust of the people in chat.
All right.
So, Marius, what are you up to?
Hanging out?
In fact, come back and go to sleep.
I want you to grow.
I want you to go to sleep.
You've learned quite a lot.
I want you to stay in the pen.
And I want you to get some sleep.
How's everybody doing in this town?
We've got more homes.
Okay.
Let's get some new houses.
Population is booming in this town.
That'll be all right for now.
Yep.
I know I fucked it up.
It's okay, dude.
Don't worry.
Another wink?
What do you mean a wink?
That channel.
You guys are going to wake up at some point in the next four days.
And it's going to be like, oh, it's a popsicle stick joke now.
I'm going to tell you what it is.
All right.
How are we doing?
Is this good?
This has been built.
You have a storeroom now.
Good.
Is there any ore over here?
There is.
It's mine right here.
Armory?
Yeah.
Okay.
You guys can be like, we'll have another military here.
Get some roads.
I mean, how did you guys not even have any roads?
How did you not have roads?
That's fine.
Okay.
A little bit more.
I got to pee.
Fuck.
All right.
I got to pee.
And I'm going to figure out how to fix this chat scrolling.
I'm going to pee my pants up your back.
Pause the game.
What's happening?
What is happening?
We're back.
All right.
Let's see if this worked.
Yeah.
I just did the fix you were talking about, Cad.
Thank you, Cad.
Let's see if this works.
And it might.
It may have fixed it.
Okay.
All right.
Looks good.
Here we go.
We need to take off.
What's this?
Should I make something new?
What's this thing?
Ranged armory?
All right.
I can wait.
I can recruit ranks of archers.
Yeah.
Let's get it.
Lumber mill.
Yeah.
Let's get it.
I don't know.
Wait.
Hold on.
I need to close this.
This is done, right?
Ranged archery.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is this?
I'm confused.
Do I have to build a separate building for ranged?
I do.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I need what?
All right.
We got some of you guys.
Let's go.
We need some breeders.
Is there any men?
All right.
Let's go.
Forester.
Disciple forester.
More.
We need more wood.
Disciple forester.
Wood.
And we need miners too.
Subaru forester.
Disciple forester.
This is going to be the base of operations for military.
Can I put you here?
Disciple mine worker.
All right.
That sets that.
Now we have to deal with this one town here.
Where's Murius?
I think something's very funny.
What was so funny?
What are you laughing so hard at?
You like laughing at an old man?
I don't understand.
Why?
What a dick.
Haha, boomer.
I'm going to snack on that grain.
No, don't eat the grain.
You're supposed to eat people.
That's all right.
All right.
I want an army and we're going to take over the last village.
He's either going back to laugh at the fucking old guy again.
No.
Okay.
I don't know what his plan is, but you're rested.
I need you down here.
Come all the way over here because we're going to take over the next town with Murius.
And we're going to have some military here.
So come over here.
Go for it.
Let's...
Is this done?
Not built yet?
I want to build this.
We're doing a whole military.
Once we have enough wood.
How much wood do I need?
A lot.
I'm going to start helping out here.
That's not right.
The green ring you see is the extent of your influence.
I need ore.
All right.
Let's get a fucking army.
More ore.
Come on.
Really?
Ah, okay.
I got it.
Can I just break it?
What?
I thought I had to need more ore to build it.
All right, guys.
It's time to fucking end mission one.
I'm not picking the flag.
Is there...
Not enough men.
Oh, okay.
That's all right.
We only needed a few.
Look at that.
I can't click the link because I have to alt-tab the game.
And it might break.
And I'm scared to break the game unless I hit the pot.
Okay.
What the fuck was that?
All right.
You ready?
Let's go.
The last town.
Does it have military?
I think I already killed all the military.
I did.
Take it over.
Murius.
Get over there.
Just buy another computer.
You know, you mean like buy like an old...
You want me to capture a computer through a capture card?
Have an old computer and capture another with my other computer?
I mean, this game runs fine.
All right.
Murius, inspect it.
Just be a presence.
I'm gonna play with that building.
Yes.
Go for it.
Learn.
Think.
Touch.
Inspect.
Oh, you could eat somebody.
That works too.
Oh, screaming.
Did he step in it?
Oh, no.
Six flags.
He just shit in their food.
You did it.
No, don't pick up a person.
What are you doing?
They're capturing.
Put him down.
Wait, are you putting him into the...
What are you doing?
You're telling him to work in the field?
Sleep next to the building?
No, no, no.
We almost got it.
He's just a baby.
He doesn't really know what he's doing.
All right.
That was such a toddler run.
If I've ever seen one.
It's time for Murius to get a skill tree.
Oh, okay.
If you want to leave this land, click on the gold scroll.
Let's go.
Are you sure you wish to leave the land again to confirm?
Yeah, let's go.
I'm ready to rock and roll.
Don't be evil.
I thought that was a pop-up window talking about the game crashed.
And it was, do you want to force quit?
I thought that's what this was.
Look, I'm only 1% evil, guys.
Number of towns taken by force, three.
One for...
Okay.
Creature.
Creature is only 5% evil.
Fatness.
Fatness, fatness.
What does that even mean?
Fitness.
Height, four.
Final.
Hit points, 100.
Number of bowel movements, 11.
Killed 34 people.
It's eight, six villagers, okay.
World.
Happiness.
Vital.
Yeah, all right.
We're good.
Let's go.
34 people killed, only 4% evil.
Well, those were attacking people.
That was an attacking group.
Horse land.
I'm certain they'll join us against the Aztec hordes.
And they have a creature, too.
We need to build a town here, though.
We need to try to grow.
First, let's look at the Norse.
They seems they have a weak concentrate.
And your godly powers will often let you hear his thoughts.
I was the aggressor?
Greeks on my homeland?
I saw them all die at the hands of the Aztecs!
Who's talking?
Do they have a devil and an angel?
If we build up an impressive enough town,
these Norse will flock to join us.
Or if we build a big army,
we can hunt them down with a sword.
Norse leader?
Yeah, but who is the Norse leader?
Fucking Odin?
All right, here we go.
Where's Murius?
Still growing.
All right, here we go.
We need to start building.
We should start making houses.
Wait, wait, no, block out the town.
Here we go.
Ready?
Let's get a group this like out here.
This is going to be out to here.
This is going to be houses over this way.
We're going to have our temples going to go around here.
Whatever, something like that.
And that looks all right for now.
What is this?
Ah, yes, walls.
Walls.
These are vital to the defense of your city.
We need to build this wall
to ensure the Norse can't invade.
Click the action button on the turret once.
Drag and then click to place it.
Okay, that was so bad.
I do enjoy the safe, warm feeling.
There's no wall here.
It's foundation.
It's an ugly ass wall.
Drag wall from...
Wait, didn't I just...
Did I do this right?
Needs like ore or something?
I feel like this is wrong.
All right, whatever.
Let's get the process going here.
So we need houses.
We need a storeroom, first of all.
Let's get that over here.
Right there in a good spot.
Wait, where's like the most...
No, I want this over here.
Definitely put this over here.
Near all this other shit.
Can I build it like right here?
I can't.
All right, right next to trees and shit.
Look, the people have remembered all about altars.
Altars are where you can focus your godly miracles.
Let's build one as soon as possible.
Oh, as soon as possible.
What do you mean, as soon as possible?
Are you helping?
He's on a tree in your room?
I don't know what his obsession is
with picking up trees and just putting them down.
All right, what is this for?
I'm going to put this up here.
Out of the way.
Like over here or something?
I'm going to put this over here.
Such power can be wielded with an altar.
Oh, it's an altar.
All right, what about a mine?
Are there any mines over here?
This is not really a mine.
It's up here.
Okay, you're enabling him.
No, all right.
How about that was not?
All right, that was bad.
That was bad.
You just stepped on a village's head.
Don't do that.
All right, you just you literally just killed somebody for no reason,
but we don't waste shit around here.
Astonishing one.
We're protected against the Norse.
If you need a reminder of what your objectives are,
go to the objectives part of the menu.
What was I doing?
These crafty Greeks are building walls,
and so they should send a troop.
Did you just do it again?
Oh, well, that was a split.
That was really cool.
I'm going to play.
All right, clay.
Don't hurt anybody.
Don't stomp on people.
Okay, I need to build this.
Okay, we need to be foresters and builders.
Forrester, forrester.
For work, we need some breeders and houses.
All right, we're getting houses, houses, houses.
Let's go.
This is house.
You're not helping.
You're not doing anything.
Fucking idiot.
Like, you're actually being stupid now.
Get this out of the way.
He's trying.
He's not, oh, he's not.
He's just throwing stuff around.
He is still a baby.
Need a farm.
I need to poo fairly badly.
What do you mean?
What is fairly bad?
All right, wait, wait, wait.
I need fields.
Fields are going to go near the storeroom over here.
Because this is where all the forests are.
And then mine is right there too.
The fields are all going over here.
Right here.
I want another one.
I'm going to construct that building.
Good.
Please do.
Oh, you can make it bigger.
Oh, I wish I knew that.
Okay, nice job.
Should I gather rocks?
Yeah, absolutely.
Definitely, go get some rocks.
Very helpful.
Any more buildings?
What's the current need?
Ore, we need ore.
Let me get like another...
Put this over here.
I'm going to put one more of one for the influence.
All right, let's go, let's go.
How's this looking?
I need some more wood.
Give us a cow emote.
Actually, it wouldn't really be that bad, would it?
We're going to do a whole line of houses.
That house is a little ugly, but it's all right.
We need food too.
I know, I'm working on it.
I'm working on it.
All right, that's it, that's it.
That's it, that's it.
Enough houses.
Come over here, I'll help you build this.
I mean, he's not constructing the building.
He's just putting wood next to it.
Your village is starving.
Well, I have to get the necessities ready.
Most of them.
The whole town is a one road.
It's all right.
Okay, now we're going to...
I need farmers.
So some of you foresters come over here.
Let's get this shit rolling.
Can the Aztecs through?
This is Norse land.
No intruders must be allowed.
Eat this.
Stop shitting bull.
Like, is it fertilizer?
I mean, it could be.
I need breeders too.
I'm starving.
Eat. No, eat it.
Eat it.
You just had an opportunity to eat.
Breeders.
Disciple breeder.
I need a couple more breeders.
Good.
Disciple breeder.
What's my population look like?
All right, good.
You actually did something.
Holy shit.
You have built an altar.
He actually did something.
He actually put it in the right spot too.
Nice work.
Sorry, you can have a snack.
Altars work on a power called man.
You can generate manna by creating worshipers.
Is he going to learn how to do the water spell again?
Create a worshiper.
Show us you can do it.
Okay, create a worshiper.
Create disciple worshiper to assist manna.
Nah, I gotta keep doing this.
You're not doing anything.
Come here.
Worship her.
Now I can start casting spells.
Of course, more worshipers mean more manna.
Of course, costs manna.
And you need worshipers to generate manna.
Simple.
And get this.
You can drop people straight into the altar to create manna too.
You won't ever see him again though.
I gotta harvest this shit myself.
Look at this.
I need more farmers.
Look at this shit.
It's not enough.
Still, give it a try, boss.
Miracle.
Okay.
I have a water miracle.
And drop it on the field.
Oh, fuck.
What field does he want me to drop it on?
Drop it on the field over there?
Like my field?
Does it matter?
I didn't know if there was one for the tutorial or something.
I had to do it in a specific place.
All right, lots of food.
There's also something new over here.
If you want your town to grow quickly, it'll need lots of food.
Our creature can help with this by gathering crops.
All you have to do is assign him the role of gatherer near a field.
To assign the creature a role, open the creature roles interface.
Select the green gatherer role button.
This changes the creature's role and puts the leash in your hand.
Okay, creature role.
Gatherer.
Excellent.
Now just double click the action button
where you want the creature to perform the role.
He's asleep.
I mean, over here.
That means the big one is probably the best one to do.
See the radius around the flag?
The creature will gather resources from within.
That's actually really cool.
Always carry out roles inside the radius.
Wake his ass up.
Hey, relax.
At the moment, your creature isn't a very good collector.
He's not gathering much grain each time.
This is because he's a level one gatherer.
You could improve his performance in roles by spending triple.
Free will.
Should we just give him free will?
Clever, hey?
Let's give him complete free will.
A builder or an entertainer to keep the people amused.
The creatures help with the construction.
Of anything in the town.
You're supposed to be gathering food.
We'll make him serve as an army.
He loves trees.
Our creature is still small and he's not a skilled warrior.
You can use tribute to upgrade his warrior role
and he'll get way more lethal.
Yes, or you can simply leave him in free will mode.
He'll do whatever he wants and whatever you've taught him.
He's a free spirit.
The last thing you need to know about roles
is that they affect your creature's free will.
Yes, the longer he remains in a role,
the less free will he'll have.
Oh, no.
Leave him in a role for too long.
Become more like a machine than a pet.
Oh, no.
Using him in roles for a while is fine.
I don't like that.
And you can see how much free will he has
by looking at this bar on the creature interface.
Okay, interesting.
To remove your creature from a role,
click on the free will button.
Now play around with roles and stuff, boss.
And see if you can get a bigger town out of it.
And remember, if you get attacked, make him a warrior.
We share the hatred.
Who do these creeps think they are?
All right, well, back to free will.
Free will.
You can do whatever you want.
You don't have to gather anymore.
Free will.
You are free.
I don't want you just gathering food all day.
All right, let me build.
I got to build a warrior's area.
We need a armory because, I mean, we have to have one.
Put it at the gate.
Right here.
I thought these Greeks were a peaceful race.
What?
You saw me build that.
I must watch closely.
Oh, shit.
Well, he's been, what?
He's been threatening me the whole fucking level.
Oh, these Greeks.
I thought they were destroyed.
And I'm going to kill them and destroy them.
I thought the Aztecs wiped them out.
Oh, I thought they were a peaceful people.
What the fuck?
How dare they encroach on my land?
Murius.
Might need you.
No, don't eat this one.
Don't eat this one.
This one's important.
Put down.
Okay.
I'm not going to kill anybody yet.
Not yet.
Okay, let's see.
Let's water the mountain.
Here we go.
Ready?
Murius, take a look at this.
He's kicked a rock.
Come here, Murius.
Look.
Look what I have.
Isn't that interesting?
Don't you think that was interesting?
Wonderful.
Cool, huh?
Why are you so sad?
What's wrong?
You go do whatever you want.
It's all about the trees.
And that's fine.
As long as you gather it and put it in the right spot.
All right.
I need, how's the armory looking?
Not even close.
The Aztecs want to rule.
They need the Greeks destroyed.
I'm just preparing in case I get attacked.
What the hell was I doing here?
All right.
What do we need?
What are our needs?
Food, more food.
We have plenty of wood.
More food.
How can we?
We need more farmers.
How many people are actually farming right now?
Zero out of seven.
One out of five.
One out of eight.
How the fuck?
We need more farms.
Get over here.
Your cow is eating them.
No, he's fine.
He's just dancing.
Look, they're having a good time.
Is he growing?
All right.
Let this guy hang out and be happy.
Yeah.
This split.
I'm glad this splits back.
More farmers.
All right.
Now we got a lot of workers in the field.
We have at least 10 people doing this.
The Greeks mock us with their very existence.
You're going to deposit?
Deposit rock.
That was whatever.
Should I turn these rocks around with some poo?
Sure.
Poo on the rocks if that's really what you want to do.
In fact, it's better if you poo on the rocks and not on people
because people will be very upset by that.
So if you have to go to the bathroom, go to the bathroom behind a tree.
Should I poo on that villager?
No, don't poo on a villager.
You just asked it to poo on a rock.
Why are you asking this question now?
I just told you to poo on a rock.
I can't.
All right.
This curiosity is killing me right now.
What does this even mean?
He doesn't actually poop on them, right?
He's lying.
He can't get it.
Clean up the poo.
Oh, he just hit his head.
Are you all right?
All right.
Let's keep going.
I'm going to gather food.
Good work.
Yes.
Excellent.
How are we doing on food?
Doing okay?
My military is almost ready.
I need more food.
I need another farm.
I need more farms.
Like more people.
How are we doing on population?
Sleep.
Where's my?
Let's see.
Birth rate low.
All right.
We need more fucking.
They wish to wage war against me.
So be it.
The pitiful survivors of the Aztec attack will not last long here.
Stop eating people.
All right.
We got more breeders.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop.
No, I'm trying to.
Don't eat a villager.
Don't.
Okay.
No villagers.
I need a new temple.
What about water?
That's what you guys doing over here.
This is doing whole lot of nothing.
All right.
Farms?
Disciple farmer.
Let's get a military.
How many people can I make here though?
I don't want to destroy the whole economy.
to build an army click and drag the army flag
available men 5
available men 25
alright I'm gonna do
10?
I need more breeders
breeder breeder breeder
are they waiting to go into the house to breed?
I don't understand what they're doing
the greeks have recruited a platoon
let's see how it
fares against
norse ire
you can make fields any size you like
yeah we learned that a few minutes ago we're good
what are we missing?
let's put this wood in the store where it belongs
stray wood everywhere
food going good
how about miners
alright I got an army I should be okay
what is this grain?
watch it
I'm going to stomp all over that platoon
is that what you want?
is that what you want to do?
you're okay
no no no that's not worth it
don't start a war yet I'm not ready
need a little more food
how do I open the door?
can I open the gate?
there's no gate here
can I make a gate?
gate house
they just stuck back here
what the hell are they gonna do over here?
if they waste all that money they're not gonna get in
can't do anything
let me do this one more time
I think it's time to leave
we're gonna go together what do you have?
nothing really
there's one army running around that's it
what about over here?
I think I can take this
I'm going for it
I can take this with the cow and a couple of the troops
I must stop these persistent Greeks
let's go
Nereus I need you
we gotta do soldier
soldier
come with me
open this door you guys too let's go
ready
here we go
going under the guise of night time
what?
a Greek army is coming?
get ready men
there's not time for a snooze
no no no don't play with anybody
it's not time to play
you're supposed to be on war
open the door
here we go it's time for our first battle
our first real battle
capture it
Nereus get in here
Nereus where are you?
under the guise of nightfall take the first town let's go
eat this person
come here go over here
inspect the building
I'm going to play with that building
go play with it
go kick something go punch something
go
go over there and attack it
do something
you look a little thin
oh he docked it over good
he looks a little thin
he's really thin
yeah
take a perimeter
put these intruders to death
every last
one of them
this kick building
kick it
yeah
these guys
it's kind of funny
eat this food
eat
there's nobody to kill they're all hiding
you need to eat there you go
eat again you're looking
too thin
now go back over here
we're good we're going to get this building
you know what to do
can't really do much right now I can't even
it's just like screaming in the house
I'm soaking what is he in the water?
he's focusing on this house
he has no abilities
he's just scaring
everybody inside
it's like a bear in it going after a tent
I'm tired
what was that?
no defense
what's going on?
why is he puking?
why did he just puke on this guy?
oh my god
he's not stopping
what the fuck
what was that for?
he just came
that was like six times screamed, puked
and then fucking went to bed
oh I love it
okay we'll just sleep
we're going to get it soon
don't worry
free will
you can go back to free will
do whatever you want
you did a good job
you tried I told you to make a mess
and you did
good work
alright well that's still happening
let's do some more stuff over here
still need food
too many people
too many breeding
how many people are working in these fields?
zero out of eight
zero out of seven
they're all farming
they're moving, they're depositing
yeah okay
let's get another field
I just heard
were you eating?
is he doing something?
he killed somebody
he killed my own guy and ate him
that's fucking
that's diarrhea
is it wrong?
no I'm going to help them build
yes do, do so
very good
let's build this
I'll sometimes lend a hand, yeah you should
absolutely
go ahead, hack an opponent's storehouse
no
no no no no
because it's ours now
I need more troops
serious
food farms
holy shit
freddy dread
freddy dread dropping
a hundred more subs
a hundred community subs
there's an animal in here
this is an outrage
take the nearest settlement
we must stop this greek invasion
farmer
but freddy
holy fuck dude
another one hundred subs from freddy dread
the dude just comes and drops
subs all the fucking time
one of those
you're not going to eat this person are you?
put him down
it's a breeder
yes gather from the field
excellent work
is this your town?
it's not mine
okay here we go
freddy my gif sub is about to run out
extreme generosity freddy
that's fucking
thousands and thousands of dollars
that you've given this stream, seriously thanks man
where's their store room?
do they even have one?
speaking of people that give
a ton of money to the stream
sixty nine subs
from phylactery lich
sixty nine fucking subs
a hundred and sixty nine subs in
less than five minutes, less than two minutes
insanity
thank you both of you
that shit's insane
and look I don't even have to do anything, he's doing all the work for me
when are you going to do the casino stream?
not doing a casino stream
these are all farmers
I need, I got a, what are you doing?
store room? he's going to get that town
it don't matter, alright I need to start expanding
we need houses
we need more, I need houses
wood, let's get a temple in here
let's get some more houses in here
I'm going to use this villager
for free weight?
this curling villager
relax dude
let's build a temple, I got plenty of wood over here
let's help build it
how much ore do you need?
I need a shit load of wood
the ticking, the ticking, the ticking, I know
it'll all stop soon, don't worry
I don't even need to build it for this, I'm just going to get it done
what do we got?
I'm going to play with that villager, good, what's not taken over here?
should I go, should I wrap around all the way?
alright
the next plan is to go get this villager
I'm going to try to get this villager on influence
I'm not going to try to kill anybody
how you guys doing on wood?
they got a shit load of wood, let's do the same thing over here
let's build some houses over here
do I build a wall?
alright I'm going to do a wall
wall gate house
okay they come from right here
alright I'm going to go
let's just put this whole
alright, it's going to be weird
oh okay I can just do the whole thing
how much do I need ore? I need a ton of ore for this
I need too much ore for this
no, this is a waste of time
it's not worth it
I'll just build some more houses
where's the houses?
scream redeemed
construct a building? I would hope you would
please help me
what? I didn't catch this one too?
stop building
what did I think of the animal crossing direct? I didn't watch it
I have no idea
I don't know, how is it?
does it look good?
can I pick this up and fix it?
alright, pregnant, put that down
Murius, please construct the buildings
the animal crossing is amazing
I've played the animal crossing before
I didn't watch the direct
Murius, wrong building
the ones that need construction over here
I appreciate his attempt
but not really
what we were looking for
they sure aren't changing or improving anything
really? I don't know
what's the general consensus on it?
alright, where's Murius? He's doing alright
keep hanging out over here, how many builders do we have? How many farmers?
what are you up to?
you're just clapping, alright, no clapping
do that
we need some more breeders
let's go back to my original town over here
how are we doing?
more houses
these people are sleeping outside
let's do this
nice
this is going to be nice
I want every other spot
like that
and one, no, two more
see, now we have a neighborhood
redeemed to Wink
sweat check for 75,000 points
let's water
give me this water
over here
give everybody a shower, more food
we're looking good over here
I'm going to build all this shit
you have good taste in hats
do I? that's good to know
what do you mean?
I haven't worn a hat on stream
on camera in probably like
a couple years
what hat are you referring to?
a fedora? I've never put a fedora
on my head, once
ever, I don't think so
I really don't think it's ever happened
green screen stream?
I don't remember
where is
are you coming home? he's coming home
he's like, I'm sick of this bullshit
I want to go to sleep
maybe
for like a second or two
this is out of my influence? fuck it is
he's going back to bed
I wonder when he's going to grow
on the slime stream?
did? did I?
I guess I did, yeah
was that really a fedora though?
alright, let's go back to here
alright, let's move
I'm going to build a building down here
what do they want? temple? sure thing
let's get it, let's get it down here
this guy talks a lot of shit
his army is stuck on the right side of my game
he's all talk
he just wants me to walk away
he wants me to get scared and leave
he doesn't have shit, he's a liar
there's a little bit of ore
where are they getting the ore?
more influence
good, good, good, good, good
keep going
more buildings over here
you already have a store room
oh, save the game
woah
yeah
yeah, this is
two full hours have gone by
alright, let's build
some fucked up stuff
altar, field, armoury
creature pen, I'm going to pull the creature pen up here
so he has another place to sleep
that he likes, you know?
boom
torture people
oh, was it fuck it Thursday?
what is today, Thursday?
yeah, I have some sun chips
would you like any?
no, I would not, I would not
I do not find those to be delicious at all
alright, Marius, follow me
come up to here
and here, look, a new house
take a look, inspect it, check it out
let me know what you think
let's move the army
the army is going to
I'm going to try to get these people on the left to like me
I'm going to put these guys over here
because that's where their army is going to be attacking from
alright, now, it's just as simple as
building more buildings
what do I want, torture pit?
Dilla, destruction tool
can I even make a
torture pit?
poo? I'll poo on the rocks
I'll spend some time playing
oh, this is his brain
one man?
cost five thousand to make somebody?
teddy bear? a ball?
a voodoo doll?
a lamp? punishment spike?
a good creature toy
playing with this as an effect on alignment
shifting towards good
let's get it, how do you like it?
check it out, do you like it?
give it a look, I'm going to play with that toy
he loves it
hey, don't be so rough
did you break it?
he broke it
did he? where is it?
the response, okay
why did he destroy it? whatever, he was just playing with it
what in punishment spikes?
no, that's fucked up, I don't want to do that
alright, what do I want to do?
do I not have access to
how come I don't have access to the
torture pit?
do I need like an altar or something?
I have all this stuff, don't I?
I guess I'll put an altar in here
they don't have one
you gotta buy it
and just getting some influence
they have wood in the store room
so I should probably use the wood in the store room
I'm going to have some fun
playing with that tree
good, you have to be evil to
get it
that makes sense
let me get some worshippers in here
I'm going to influence these two and I'm not going to have to do anything
I'm not going to have to fight anybody
who's available?
you are
you are available
ready?
are there any side quests that I missed?
I haven't seen any
should I work out using trees?
yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm going to, yeah, weight lift the tree
that's way better than a person
it weighs like 5,000 times more than a person
maybe he'll get big
muscles, alright, let's do another
more houses, put them down here
start our influence campaign this way
and then that way
get a shit load of wood, put it over here
why is this evil?
is he going to lift it?
do some exercises, you need to get bigger and stronger
he doesn't get it
should I eat rocks
or are they bad for my teeth?
no, no, no, don't eat rocks
I'm going to eat that rock, don't eat a rock
no
no, I'm trying to
I'm trying to tell you
don't eat rocks
oh my god
don't eat
rocks
don't eat rocks
I'm trying to be gentle
eat food
I wonder if I could fit that toy in my mouth
I wonder if I could fit the toy
in my mouth
sentences said before disaster
he lost track
of what he was doing
let him learn
we're going to be at the doctor
he's going to end up with a marble in his nose
even more
let's keep going
I don't know
armory, put it back a little
oh yes
armory's turned weedy men into
warriors
I need the wood
I need 500 ore
how's eat rocks
good for their digestion, I don't think that's real
I think what you're saying is inaccurate
keep it going
I'm slowly going to encroach
I'm just building power plants up into their base
do the quests
I was trying to look and see if there are any on the
oh you're talking about just like little tasks
at the top left
let's check it out, let's see what they are
what do they got for us
how do I see the tasks
dwellings
civic buildings
how do I see the
tasks
they pop up sometimes
oh shit
eat some food, you can have food
don't feel like you're stealing
you can have as much as you want
I need ore, is this ore
there's no ore over there
I have to take some from here
wait 500
that's enough
where's my mouse
keep that influence going
what do you guys think about me now
that's what you think
where's my army
I'm going to have two armies
do I not have enough men
I don't have enough men
shit
we need to do some breeding
peace through power
peace with power
I'm going to try
but
is it going to really do much
what are you doing
get out of there
eat some food, I'll give it to you
eat that
eat it
you know you want to, here
it's delicious
it smells good
eat it
should I beat up those animals
what animals
there are no animals here
beat up an animal, where's an animal
oh the rabbit
what a dick
if you're hungry eat
where are you putting wood over here
there's no reason for him to do this
I'm going to gather wood
good work
I'm going to play with the villager
he's just taking wood from the storehouse
I'm putting it outside the storehouse
he's alive
let's keep going
I was doing breeding
do I have enough
available men
let's go with
platoon size
they're right here
I don't think he even has a creature
does he have a creature
10 in here
he does, where is it
I haven't seen it once
curious I need you over here
what do you have, put it down
rabbit, wait what are you doing with this
I'm kind of curious actually
bringing it back to the house
there's just trees
there's just trees in here
I'm going to keep him in there
because he keeps putting them in
I'm just going to let him
I'm going to let him keep doing
what did he just do
he just screamed at him
he's so fucked up
okay watch
he's just
I'm going to let him keep fucking doing this
he's going to keep putting trees in his house
until it's impossible to walk
I'm going to just let him be a weirdo
but more importantly
come here
I need you to be a soldier
at level 2 now, good
alright
let's make a move
level 2, attach him to the arm, he's not going to attack them right
the morale has been increased
oh that was a
battle cry, let's get in there
are they going to retreat
attack, I'm going to have a dump on that villagers head
okay go do it in here
go do it in here
on these guys
do it on these villagers
get in there
attack
fight
we're level 2, they're level 1
aren't they, Murius let's go
get in there
Murius, Murius go
get in, out, in, in, in, in
attack
pick up
where's he going
I'm going to
what are you doing
put him down
he's petting him
you're fucking crazy
alright let's take it over
he just smashed everybody
alright take the city over
how many people, is it one person
let's capture this
capture the building
take it over Murius
help take it over, I need to make another
he's blowing a kiss
to the building
alright is he going to capture
I don't think he can
I don't even know what to say
I'm going to build that structure
wait he's going to go over here
and help build this
arm
wait
what
should I be entertaining
these folks
yes, yes you should entertain them
entertain them while we
conquer them
entertain them, this doesn't seem very
entertaining
who's he playing with
I'm going to go and gather that free
I can't fucking take it
anymore, it's too
he's so all over the place
I hope he brings it all the way back to his house
please do that
no he's just an idiot
just putting it into a pile over here
why is there a fun song playing
okay
he's looking right in the camera with these sinister
fucking, what is he doing
where are you going
oh okay
just putting him down in your house
go back to free will
we almost got this town
in the meantime I'm going to start building out this way
Murius can sleep for a little bit
let's continue building out here
and let's do a water spill
how's this town look
good, I think we're good
you go worship here
everyone worship here, that's not doing anything
alright, Murius is awake
nice trees, okay
I do need
I'm going to need some more
men, what do I have
I have how many men available
zero available men
okay, well
apparently
no there's available men
what's he doing
I'm going to play with that villager
I want you to eat too
let me see your stats
come here for a second
come here
well fine, just do whatever you want then
alright, here we go
let's get a, I'm going to play with that villager
well then get over there and play
alright, is that it
entertain them
you want to play, well then do something
how many more towns are there
there's one, two, three, four
this is the main town here
what is this creature
you know how to do that
he's sending an army
got it
okay
no no don't
don't don't don't don't
it's too late, but don't
don't put that villager down
drop
drop drop drop drop
drop it drop it
drop it drop it drop it drop it drop it
drop it, okay
drop it
it's okay, just drop it
level three, nice
let's go
let's move this army, can I combine armies
there's only one guy over here
start a temple over here, keep the influence
going, I'm going to do the influence, yeah this way
do I knock down people
I'm going to let Otto
outside, hold on one second
I'll tell you what, go outside, alright I'll be right back
give me two seconds, pause again
can I go out, alright
I'll be back, the BRB
alright let's go, alrighty
what were we doing, just taking over a village
actually I'll take this opportunity to save the game
alright I got a huge
ass army right here
I want you
to, can I combine you
can you go into this group
can I, you now
in that, you now part of them
I think, kind of, let's see, can you
join them
not really, alright
I'm going to go for it, down
where do I want to go
person or is that food
person or food, I know it's
weird that I have to ask that question, person or fucking
food, does he have a knife
oh, alright no no, come here
come here, we got shit
to do over here, this is fucking full
who needs food
alright I have too many towns
I have too many towns, too many towns
too many towns, I don't know who
needs any, here we go, this is the one who needs food
what the fuck is going on
what is going on, why are they all doing this
why are they all doing this, what are they doing
why is every single person walking
into town, what's going on
farmer, farmer, farmer
what's at the, you hear the bell
this fucking bell is ding ding ding ding
ding ding, where are they going
wait, oh I thought this was a
battle going on, wait the gate
is open, has the gate been open
the whole time, oh fuck me
hold on, oh shit
who's taking this over
what's going on, hey, hey
come here, all of you
defend, defend, defend, furious
no
come here, I need you, I need you over here
come here, soldier
defend the city
defend, defend, defend, get in here
they're not taking this shit
I actually think they have this under control
maybe not, how fast can you get
here Mirus, is this alive
no, I think this is
ok, they're not going to get it
no, you show them
you show them
your fucking anger, fight
just be careful of the other people
great, he stepped on
a kid, ok
we've removed them
no, you killed everybody
great
creature collects 3000 food
alright, alright
this is ours, Mirus, calm down
this is our stuff
relax
relax, relax, relax, cool down
cool down
raise the morale
yes
hooray, good, good, good
stay down here
I want to play, you've earned it
you can do free will for a little while, let me go back up here
what does this mean
does this have an armory, why can I not build an armory here
I can build it
is this already being built, what is this
it's not a people
I don't understand
it's too steep, oh ok
I gotta go down and I gotta get this
town here, how is this town looking
I'd like to influence this
town, but do I have to keep, ok not a question
do I have to build
all the way down here
to get them to care
or, no I don't, ok
I just have to be impressive, alright that makes sense
so now, let's take a look
let's see the actual stats, I have to zoom in and just sit here
impressive is required to capture
gamhaven
ah ok, I need more
impressiveness, where is gamhaven
what is that, you know
make it daytime, I can't see anything
these guys are still just walking around
it's
maybe daytime, let's go
everybody out, they've been there the whole game
to invent fortnite
to gain followers
I'm gonna keep working up over here, wait
there's a little town right here
there's a humdigger of a fight going on
what, where
oh, right here, here he is
soldier mode, come on
you can take him on by yourself, we gotta get
I have to get rid of this villager
why would you ever do this without your creature, knowing that I have one down here
start eating people
a huge soccer kick
watch out for the buildings, watch out for the other people
now he just scratches his ass
why is he so itchy
back to free will
I wonder, what should I do with this guy
bathe him, he'll be alright
I'm gonna go
I gotta get this right now, ok I just destroyed
all this shit
I'm gonna capture it with mirror, I'm just gonna take this one guy
I don't think the speed
capture speed goes anything
are they all clapping and happy about the shit all over the ground
probably, it's weird
alright we're gonna go in and
capture this
hang out right here, I'm curious, go kill everybody
let's take this, we're gonna take this by force too
he's got one more group
and then I got one guy
I can just capture the whole thing, don't matter
this thing's growing too
he looks bigger than he does before
you go in there and take care of that
you
capture it
evil
alright, now just stay here
watch the punch
jump on him
stay here
take it over, no other armies
there's an army coming right here, but we should be able to defend this
in the meantime, hold on, I'm gonna send
some support
do I have any support? I have these guys
what the fuck was that
it was like a gunshot
okay, it's kicking a building
are they coming down here?
do the scroll quest? I haven't seen any
I don't see any scrolls
on the map, have you guys seen any?
I haven't seen one, oh there's one right here, okay
help us
we need to finish our special brew
throw this barrel to my
brother over there so he can add his ingredient
then throw it to my other brother
on the next island
it needs to go to them all in turn
until our brew is finished
barrel throwing quest?
sure
throw it to my
brother on the other land
kind of, okay, what
is, I don't understand
why can I pick up the
this one has a weird thought
throw, well, I
I did it, did I do it?
I mean
did you get it?
throw it back
no, throw it over here
okay, it's the game, come on
pick up
pick, pick
pick, click
click
click, click
oh, I got it, hooray, great
oh, this is so fucking finicky
holy shit, come on
I
I did it, hold on
not again, right?
I'm just waiting for Murius
to come over and just fucking eat this guy
in the middle of a cutscene
I just want something to happen
all right, so now we're going from
oh my goodness, we're going from here
we have to throw it across the whole thing
oh, this is gonna actually
suck, okay, so
I hear
Murius is kicking shit
okay, so now let's go from
this is
what's up with the ticking?
I'm ticking over a town
currently ticking over a town
Murius is kicking shit
sweet
praise be, the brew is finished
let's drink it, lads
but first, a tribute
to our benefactor
hooray
yeah, I got one guy taking a town over
currently, wrong button
I was trying to press this button
I thought that was the camera button
to the same spot
where the camera button usually is
is this where I guess it was?
20,000 points
all right, now, Murius, where are you?
I'm soaking
good, and you need to take this place open, you need to hang out
oh, he's wrecking this place
all right, you don't need to wreck this place
just be an entertainer for a little while
entertain this person
that's the last person that you haven't killed
I'm so happy
evil, evil, evil
this is still working
boy, are they rebuilding the town as he destroys it?
that's kind of fucked up
well, he's on happy mode
so
yes, hi, I see you, hello
wait, what is that?
is that the pot?
I guess not, I almost have it
I think peekaboo
first thing that's getting built here is a creature town
well, it's a pot market
how come I can't build a pot market?
all right, you can hang, I need a creature
city, second, this is ready
no, no, don't, no
Murius, no, no, no, no, put him down, put him down
I need this guy, no, put him down, no, no, no
put him down, put him down, put him down
I got it, okay, I got it
put him down
put him down, put him down, put him down
I got the town, right? Okay
I was gonna say, that's the only guy capturing the city
no, you don't have to play with the villager, just relax
I need a creature den
put you anywhere
help me build this building, Murius
they don't have shit though, they have nothing
they have a little bit of wood
actually, they got quite a bit
good, gather
fields
good job, Murius, we need to maybe rebuild some of this stuff
how are the townspeople doing? breed
any forests around here?
I need a mine
you can get this
I'm kind of evil
only that? 7% is not bad
they're pooing on the rocks?
there are no rocks
uh, forester
disciple forester
forester
I need a farm, let's do a big
just one huge ass farm over here
this, just one, who cares
just one big ass farm
disciple farmer
all people standing around, get in there
all right, now we should start to get some good shit
breeders are over there
there is, okay, there's ore over here, good
oh, you think you're gonna come in here, don't you?
well, I got a fix for that
you're quite happy?
good, you're about to be even more
happy, attack
what do you have in your hand?
what is that? he has
grain in his hands?
not much, but
you're doing fine
get him
all right, pick up tree, throw tree
are they hiding in the trees?
all right, throw, throw at them
crush them
can he reach from here?
attack, attack with your new melee weapon
tree
get him, attack
holy shit, he does use it
he uses it as a fucking weapon
run him out of town
holy shit, that's so dangerous
that's so dangerous, get him out of here
get him out, get him out
he's gonna kill everybody
go after them
what?
where?
where, what, I don't understand, where am I getting attacked?
all right, just throw it
here we go
oh my god, just fucking throw it
throw it, throw the, yes, good
smart
where was this other attack going on?
I think it's only just right here
throw downhill, he wouldn't throw it
there was nothing to throw
they're just running away from it
Murius, Murius, Murius
Murius, Murius, please
all right, pick up a fucking tree
I'm gonna throw it
how do you throw something, throw
all right, throw it, throw
get it again
get it
all right, we're gonna throw it downhill
no, he's got a fucking piece of grain
kill them
oh my god
Murius, what the fuck are you doing?
they're like dragging him
finally
you stepped on somebody
he'll kill them eventually
what was I doing?
the town is coming under attack
the Aztecs want to rule
they need the Greeks destroyed
how do I throw?
I can't change the throw
throw, this hurt somebody
do something Murius
you're fucking killing me
you gotta do something
don't I have an army?
do I have to make a new army?
attack, attack, attack
he killed somebody
he's just wrecking this town too
just defend this area
there's no reason for you to run around in circles
just defend, defend
I'm gonna go get my actual army
there's a home digger of a fight going on
no there's not
give me my actual fucking army and just defend over here
ready to go
just, don't get them please
defend the town
being a soldier, do something
they just run in and run out
Murius, get them
get them
alright, my actual team is here
this is like the stupidest army ever
they're just running in circles
absolutely decimated
just decimated
time for a counter attack
every time we do
Greeks are a strong force
I cannot tolerate these Greeks any longer
let's go
I will have to act
Murius
this is North's land
no intruders must be allowed
free will, he's alright
instead of wink it's turning into just like
stay together
it's time to go kill this motherfucker
he's streaming in a cave
yes, yes
you know what, sleep for now
you guys hang out here for a little bit
this should be enough to take the other city
what else do we got?
take a little rest
let's get some food for Murius
and then we're gonna go in
this is his stronghold here
he does have
look at how much of a little baby this is though
Murius is going to
karate chop this guy in the head
and instantly knock him out
this is gonna be awesome
he doesn't stand a chance
I got like 5 towns
get some rest
health 58
can I heal these guys?
can they like rest?
is there a way to like heal them
or feed them or something
maybe feed them
food? alright Murius
it's time for you to eat
why don't you not like me, what?
I'm depressed
what is that weird movement
alright here we go
Murius I want you to eat
eat this guy
just eat the food that's right here
alright need it?
alright we need to get, here
eat this
try that
is this a pig?
no that's a cow, this is cannibalism
so don't do that
I can't get there
alright whatever
he's eating
he's full
it's time to begin
Murius go in
we might get a creature fight here
which I have to be prepared for
let's get a morale boost
Murius morale
let's see what happens, do it
war cry
look at all these people
war cry, do it
give them some, there we go
pretty good war cry
let's go
let's go after them
hey Murius
hey
don't go in, stay behind
raise morale, don't attack
raise morale, you need to help
yes
there's a fight
raise morale
there we go, good
no
you're supposed to raise morale not start fighting
take it
capture
alright Murius, it's time for you to get in there because we've got
we've got a creature up here
should I try to be friends with the creature
should I distract the creature, what do you think
entertain the creature
kill the other creature
get a rock, another fight right here
you can't do that, pick up the small one
get it, pick it up
alright just get in
prepare
go in there
oh my god
what are you doing, fight
stomp
good work
don't run too far in
nice
we'll get this last town
I'm going to do another war factory
it's not command and conquer but whatever
stomp
Murius, you can eat the second
attack
there you go, go ahead, eat
you're good, eat Skye
I know you're hungry, I know, trust me
eat
ow
ow ow Murius, go go go go go
oh my god there's a million people here
oh my god there's a lot of people
I'm angry
take it out
oh shit, how much health does he have
get in there, are you okay
62 health, he's okay
good, get in here
these are the ones you have to worry about
there's so many
well okay
Murius
how does he get up
fuck, I thought I wasn't going to be able to get it
what are they doing, don't get your hands off him
don't touch him, he's dead
no he's not dead
he's dead
where's that army, he just made a huge one
good, come on
how do I bring him back
he used to just kind of respawn in the last one
he's not respawning
wait, he's back
he's fatter than ever
perfect, come with me
take out your anger up here
shorter, I think he may have grown up
he looks a little older
do they have a creature down here, no they don't
no, I got free will, he's fine
his free will is disappearing
he's fine, he's fine
free will
you can just kind of walk around and look at stuff
I'm going to stomp all over that
platoon
that's his free will
he's angry
that's his free will, I didn't tell him to do this
I'm going to
break down those walls
Murius, wait
Murius, Murius
Murius
he's lost control
I'm going to
what town, what town is under attack
do you see a town under attack
alright, are we ready to break in
I got a lot of troops here
alright, what do you got, you got food
you got food, you got people, we got
let's get some
what do I think of, what do I want here
there's an army, oh there's an army outside the town, right
alright, let Murius take a little bit of a rest
free will
oh fuck
Murius, time to get up
why are you going to come at this
what a mistake that was, that was an instant kill
the entire troop, every single person
instead, I instantly killed every single one
alright, counter attack time
let's go
let's get this fucking door open
get this wall down
save the game
how do I get in
people are getting shot with arrows
I can't attack the door
there's no attack door
I can't do it
I think only he can
into the door
oh my god
I didn't, I thought they could attack the fucking door
I didn't think only he could
everyone's dead
load the game, load the game
I thought that they could attack the door, they can't
load game, okay, Murius come here
get that door open
what the fuck is this range, oh my god
you can shoot across the whole game
open this door
how much health does a door have
Murius is going to die
he's fatter than ever
alright, alright
oh good, punch
alright, everybody in
there's a fight already going on
alright, retreat, retreat, retreat
no, no, retreat, retreat
don't rip the walls down, Murius
alright, you're free, turn the free will off
it's too dangerous, I need more
I need more men, oh god
now's not the time to laugh
wait, where the fuck are these going
where the fuck are they, there's too many
okay, this is a shitload of people
it's time to run, Murius, out
get out, out, out, out, out, this is a lost cause
lost cause, lost cause, they're recapturing
whatever, just go back, back, back, back
we gotta make up, we gotta make up army three
times this big, we got the door down
that's all that matters
no, no, don't stomp the platoon, just get out
get out, get out, get out, get out, in fact, you know what
we're gonna save scum, just a little bit here
we're just gonna save scum the game
we're just gonna be scumbags
everybody out, out, out, out, everybody go
we are not even here right now
we don't, we're not here
everybody get
okay, no one's even here
we're gonna build some, let's defend
good, okay
defend
Murius
now we're gonna build up the town here
we're getting
trashed
you know what to do
free will
go ahead and do whatever you want
for the time being, while I decide what
I'm gonna do here
there needs to be
prepare a force to destroy these
okay, I need a, we need
we need
war
no, don't attack the building
it's not gonna end
he's just, he's out for blood and I can't stop him
I may have come up
a little, a little too soon
um
we need, how much do I have
I need another armor
right here, okay, you're good
what's he doing
Murius, do something, do anything
what the fuck is going on
what?
where are you going, stop
sell, sell, sell
everything
I have no idea what he's doing
but it's, I came up here way too
I need to have like a hundred troops
what do they got in the store room
okay, who's available
five people
good enough
wait, don't take all the men
don't take all the men
Murius and earn my reward
from the Aztecs
throwing their soldiers
back over their walls
Murius is dead
Murius went too hard
I shall put these intruders
come on, get them over the gate
get them over the gate
the Greek warriors have
spirits
shit
the Greek town
cannot be allowed to grow
ranged armory
I need houses and shit
he's gonna come back angrier
and fatter
probably, but I need
I need more houses
what do I have for roads here, okay
I need a ton more
men
it's gonna be sloppy but I don't care, it just needs to work
everybody breed
my other towns are fine
I know it's ugly as hell
we need a lot of soldiers
even back here
it doesn't matter if it's ugly
it just has to work, this has to exist
I'll get a road back here eventually
I need a bigger army
I need range too
breeders
who old to be a disciple?
what?
breed, breed, breed, we need more breeding
more breeding
no wood, breed
are they gonna be kids?
wait, this is not gonna work
I'll let this play out for a little bit
I just tried to breed this guy with a pig
okay, that's not gonna work
okay, good
let's make some kids
Murius?
actually fatter
that's not even a joke, actually fatter
I need you up here
actually, go rest up in here
for a little bit
do I have any more military capabilities
I know that there's like a million people
down here
what about over here? how many men can I make here?
okay, 20
good
how about this?
this is probably gonna be huge
oh, yeah, I'll take 60 people
thank you
no, just breed
how are we doing over here?
breeding?
are we looking on breeding?
is that going well?
more breeding
oh, this lady's already pregnant
who's not pregnant?
everybody not pregnant?
I think the whole village is pregnant
so fat
will you at least learn water spell?
here, look
get leashed
look what I'm about to do
isn't that interesting?
alright, let's take off your free will for a little bit
come here, will you do what I want you to do
and get up here, go up there
you can have your free will back, but like, just get up here
here we go, what do we got? 60?
let's go
ton of people, good
this should be enough to break through the front door
prepare a force to destroy these Greek troops
no action
what do you mean no action?
open?
open the door
get up here
fortify up here
out of the range of the snipers
I gotta get my own snipers
get out of the fucking forest
you freaking me out
buy spells?
you buy spells?
mana cost 750
tribute menu?
old man
hand gestures?
wait, I have to unlock all this?
pot market, heal miracle, hand forcing
okay, I have to buy all this shit
torture pits, this is how you
okay, you unlock this shit
okay, I get it
let's do
hold on, hold on
I don't have time to do this right now
get out of this fucking menu
did they kill everybody?
where's the group that's coming up here?
alright, give me the tribute menu
wait, did they kill everybody?
no, did they make it all the way up here yet?
hold on a second
I had 60 fucking people, where are they?
how do I select them?
where are they?
okay, where the fuck is everybody?
oh, here they come
that's fine
alright, I have to unlock some of this shit
I didn't even realize what was happening here
okay, hand gestures
what do I have to tribute?
256,000?
no, I was doing this
heal miracle
let's buy it
fertility statue, hand gestures
let's get it
they're not going to get through this, there's 60 fucking people here
okay, just stay defending here, don't go anywhere else
hand forcing?
I don't know what that means
plant market, hovel, naming stuff
statue market, tavern
prison, torture pit
should we just start picking people up and torturing them?
granary
this will process the crops your farmers produce
increases the amount of food
I mean, I have a lot
granary, where are there so many dead bodies?
graveyard
what about fireball or something?
advanced soldier
the next level of warrior skills for the creature
will be more effective and dangerous in combat
it'll be harder to hurt
fire miracle
burn things, enemies are a good start
get it
nice, alright, let's take a look now
let's get this going
Murius now is way better
so is this advanced soldier already?
let's get everybody up here
it's time to move in and fight
let's get you guys
alright, come with me
I want you all up in the general area
once they're all up in this general area
I'll open the front door
this door is open
this fucking door is open
let's go in the front door
why are we going in the door that's closed?
going in the door that's open
we're going in the door that's open
okay, there's tons of people up here now
let me make a torture pit
so we can literally just
when they come in, just pick them up and put them in here
and just torture them
I don't even need that much
I need ore
alright, so this is done
how does this work?
just pick somebody and put them in
so do I have to train this
or is Murius already leveled up
like the advanced soldier, or do I have to do something about that
do I have to put it somewhere
already upgraded, nice, okay, good
no, no, no, no, no
you can snack on the grain
snack on the grain, but don't run in
this door is open, we're going to go in the open door
army is here
now, do I
don't tear down those walls
stay here, let's get some archers
don't eat a villager
are they hitting them?
alright, do not eat a villager
here, eat this instead
eat that
yum
yummy
eat
what's going on, what are you guys doing
what the hell are you guys doing
alright, sick
cool
this sucks
I have so many people being bred
alright, I need, I need wood
we gotta get going, I need archers
once that's done, I'm just going
in the fucking back door
what, I just throw that
is that going to be seen as an attack, because I was not ready to attack
is that an attack
we share the hatred
for the Greeks that our Aztec
masters have
what in the name of fucking god are you guys
doing in this chat
what the hell are you doing
this is like, this is just
nonsense
it's just absolute fucking nonsense
the town is getting
mashed up
you guys lost your damn minds
wait, wait, wait
is there a creature coming in
stopping, what are you stopping, stop, stop, what are you doing
okay, there's so many soldiers
up here
alright, well fucking settle down
you guys are making me anxious
what the hell is going on over here
this is not even like typical crack chat night
this is just like, writing random
words
what the fuck are you doing
alright, I need
I can't pick up the archer flag, why not
is that not enough men
not enough ore, what the fuck are you talking about
how do I not have ore for this
something is currently being taken
okay
what are you guys doing
alright, quell it
quell it, slow mode
two minute slow mode at least
quell it, quell it, quell it, quell it, quell it
and keep it on, and keep that shit on
see you in two minutes loser
good use of your two
minute sentence
slow mode doesn't work
what the fuck
you guys are fucking nuts
alright, I do a video game
to play
I don't have
any soldiers here
is it any soldiers at all
how far away is that from Urius
I don't care about that town anymore
I have fucking a thousand people, let's go
I need archers, but I don't know what I need
or a number of troops
you can create fourteen troops
okay, let's go, I can do fourteen
fourteen archers
I need, we need to go, we gotta go in the front door over here
we gotta go in and take the whole thing
save the game here
what about the archers on the walls
there's only like three right there
can I leash you to like a tree or something
alright, stay over here
I'm gonna leash you to a big rock
come over here, I have to walk the other direction
they're gonna take that town, but I can take
I can literally take over the whole capital
this is a long fucking walk
god damn it, that's a long walk
that's a long walk
this door's closed now, shit
reload the game
no, it's too late
we have to put it on five minutes slow-mo
we actually have to do this
recruit an army to send against their puny forces
break this down
someone's isolated tribe
break the door down, get everybody in
the door's gonna go down, I got fucking like a thousand people right now
break it down, get in there
shoot those guys up here
archers
get in the door
look at the range, they can't even shoot
alright, good, good, good, good
kill these ones too
alright, alright, he's in, he's in
he's in, he's in, he's in, get the
no, no, no, no, no, no, no
oh my god, why'd I have to pick up flags to have to go fight
what the hell
pick up flag, drop flag
oh fuck, come on
he's picking up a weapon
alright, the door is open, whatever, we're gonna win
actually, you stay away
get in
rage, attack
move, move, move, move, move, keep moving, new target
we have to capture, capture, capture
oh, here we go, this is it
fight him, fight him
Murius, get
Murius, get over there
throw it free
Kevin, he's killing everyone
everyone is dead
attack him
attack him, what are you doing
what are you doing
you're leashed
to him
oh, now you wanna fight
and now you decide it's time to attack
he's kicking
the shit out of me
fight him
his archers shoot me in the back too
god damn it man
I'm not even hitting the right direction
what the fuck
get up
and fight
oh my god
it was a disaster
reload the game, reload the game
reload the game
okay, so I
walked in
and he killed everyone
so
we're gonna have to rethink this strategy
so let's go back to where we were
come back here
Murius, come back over here
so
I'm still being shot with arrows
oh my god
why is it so hard
okay, get over here
so, the plan here
the pitiful survivors of the Aztec
I need to
stop whippin' fireballs and shit
we need spells
so
I need to build a
first of all, first of all, first of all, Murius, come with me
there's currently
they're taking over a city
we need you to go over here
on your soldier
come over here
and come
it's, it's, it's
one person, I'm kidding
is it actually just one god damn person
I don't even know
where are they
are they still, who is taking it
okay, good, okay, very good
let's go ahead and do that again on the other one
wherever, okay, good, right
um
okay, you know where this got all
fucked up is where I didn't realize that I had to buy
the new stuff with tribute
and it's been like, I did it the whole
game
why is chat so slow? uh, because they were
unruly
and they had to be quelled
they had to be stopped
alright, so
uh
what do I wanna do?
how do I wanna do this? I'm gonna have to
I pulled all the troops up here, fuck
alright, I want to
what are they doing?
oh, they're putting the fires out
these people still, you know what?
I have to, oh, yeah, yeah, I should have made like
three or four saves
I'm so far done at this point, like I'm
fucked
I need to have rewound like an hour and a half
and like build other buildings
I have to just hurt myself, I have to
and then just go back from
scratch and build buildings
I gotta take out a whole city, we gotta torch the city
it's gotta be done
alright, we're through from scratch
are we still getting attacked somewhere?
that top city is gonna be under attack
is he alive?
alright
so this is how to do fire
heal
and now can I just do them in the air like this?
do I have to press a certain button?
is there like an activation
thing that I need to do?
I was gonna say, can we get rid of the guy that just did all caps
for like the whole paragraph
like what the fuck are you doing?
like what the fuck
I gotta kill this guy, I gotta take this guy out
there has to be like an activation right?
as long as I keep those people up there
I'm going to
let's get some archers
but first let me build
I took all the able bodied men from
every community
oh I royally fucked this
all up
let's start some breeding
this game is a bit hard?
I mean from it's very nature
I think it probably is
what's going on in there?
can we pull all these people out?
there's a shit little people in there
what are you guys all doing in here?
20 worshipers?
no no get out, get out of here
how do I get them out?
guys guys guys you gotta
we got shit to do
it's all women
oh no
I fucked up the whole earth's population
I sent every man to war
there's no men
I fucked up all of earth
wait a man
that's a man right?
okay we're good
how do I do those gestures though?
okay ranged armory
his shit is so much more advanced
than mine is right now
is chat really this bored?
I have no idea apparently
apparently
but whatever
that's just the way it is apparently
chat loves
slow mo they like to talk about how much
is their favorite thing
Dermot please turn up and ban that person
I'm not even kidding for like at least 10 minutes
where are they all going?
oh
I put all my eggs
in one basket and that basket was
wrong
and he's so much stronger
than me
how much do I have for one man?
wait I can spawn a man
give me like two
chat is very problematic
yeah what's going on today?
what is going on today?
are you guys all collectively like
huffing fucking glue?
like what are you guys doing?
you wouldn't understand
oh my god
what the fuck
anyways
I'm going to continue to pay attention to the video game
because that's what I'm doing
throwing rocks
did it work? alright we're gonna start throwing fireballs
that's the plan
Murius get up here
I need to build a
we're gonna close this out here
we're gonna close this one out good
I need a one of these things
an altar up here
with an altar I can just I'm gonna just whip bombs
across the gate and then we're going in
make it emote only
actually you know what
actually no don't do that
that's just when they come out of it
they're gonna be even worse
you know how that works?
it's like you're putting like a muzzle on somebody
and then they just go
I scream for when this muzzle comes up
and then the muzzle
yeah it's just not gonna work
just never take it off
that's so bad
we went better than this
we shouldn't have to do that
we shouldn't have to do that we're better than this
oh man
aw
no no no no
don't go in
recruit an army to send
against their puny forces
stay right here
stop stop stop stop
you're gonna get shot with arrows
first things first
get everyone ready
let's torch their whole city
I know you're angry
hungry? go eat something first
let's burn it down
burn their city to the ground
torch
destroy it
fire into the
watch this one
I'm just gonna drop this fireball right on the door
right here, boom
killed everybody
slow mode on twitch has an upper limit
I think it's like 30 minutes, I really think it is
shit, why hit the wall
alright, is it time to go in?
they don't have any fighters
um
Murius what the fuck are you doing?
Murius what are you doing?
no stop stop why are you fucking fighting
yourself?
is it the leash?
he's just so angry
stay stay stay stop stop what are you thinking?
alright he's just going in
I can't stop him
the embodiment of chat right now he's just going in
can I break the door down with this?
I wonder
it might be time to go in
it's an allegory for your power in black and white
what happened to all my friends?
perfect shot
nope
alright let's drop a bomb right here and let's try to get in the front door
I'm going in with
let's see if I can hit it come on
alright time to go in
this is the opportunity
Murius I need you
to be on soldier mode
they don't have any more archers so that's good
break the fucking door down let's go
you're supposed to bring balance to the force
not destroy it
don't care lester
where do I land these guys?
where do I capture?
where's the thing to capture?
attack? where is it?
right there
Murius why have you stopped hitting the door?
Murius
Murius the door
yeah the door
Murius
the door
excellent work
My son
Torch it
capture it Murius you have to deal with the other
god you can do it you're supposed to be
super strong
alright alright
no no no no everybody run
everybody in
in in in in
In. In. Capture. Get it?
What? This is how he's destroying him.
Holy shit.
Take the town over. That was pure fucking rage.
That was rage. Total fucking rage.
Get it. Get it. Fight. Fight. Fight.
Mirrius, be careful in here. Mirrius. Mirrius, be careful in here.
Okay. All right. Mirrius, attack the archers. You're gonna be the block.
Can we get it? Fire.
The town is getting destroyed.
Where? Oh my fucking God. Where is the stupid building?
What are the gestures? For the love of God.
Where's the... We need you guys to stay alive.
Start killing. You can take it in a second.
You punched that guy to dust.
Take the town.
Oh God. How am I gonna capture this shit? They keep pouring people out.
All right. We're doing 55 fucking men.
Let's hope I can get them out there in time.
Mirrius, what are you doing?
Mirrius, stop fucking hitting that shit and go over and help them.
Oh fuck. Why are you hitting the wall, Mirrius, of all the things to hit?
Why would you do the wall?
There's a guy sitting right here.
Do it again. Get on top of him and beat his head into the ground.
Do it. Kick his ass. Kick his ass.
Get on top of him. Do it.
Good. Good. Good.
Good. Capture.
No, stop going to the wall, man.
He wants to destroy the wall so bad.
We're so close to winning.
Who's left? I don't see anybody.
Just get everybody on here and take it over.
Handing out some pocket signs.
Rats, stand up for the wrong.
German chat has proved unfair.
Now we infiltrate his lairs.
I think I win.
They're taking this, but that's not going to be enough.
I got their capital right here.
All right, Mirrius, go ahead and take the walls down if you really want to.
Maybe he should just go.
No, because he's going to wake up.
And I have to get back on top of him and punch his face until he's dead again.
Let's give morale.
Who's clipping their nails in the background?
Does kind of sound like that, right?
Raise morale.
Take this shit over.
I'm a little out of breath.
Here he comes.
All right, when he respawns, just do it again instantly.
Here he is.
No, you're getting stuck on a building.
You fucking idiot.
He's getting stuck on a building.
Get him.
Yep, got him.
Yep, yep, yep.
All right, he got a couple of shots and that's okay.
More than one.
All right, you're good.
Just, Mirrius, Mirrius, Mirrius, Mirrius.
Get on top of him.
Get on top of him and beat his fucking head in.
Elbow drop.
I win.
I thought he was going to elbow drop him.
Eat him.
That's fine.
Being a new viewer is a weird experience.
I was just like spam for like 30 minutes.
All right, my lights are on.
We already went over this.
My lights are turned on.
My exposure is lower because I start streaming during the day.
Eat this.
Kick it.
I'm going to use my two minutes on an omega low.
Now that's a good use.
That's a good use.
Pick this person up and just throw him.
Aztecs.
I wonder if the old prophecy is true.
If the Greeks are the weak race brought to strength by a god.
If so, will they fulfill the next chapter and go to Honshai
where their separated Greek brethren wait for them?
Did Mirrius get buff?
No.
We've done it.
Victory.
He got fat.
Your evilness knows no bounds.
He died.
Well, he got incapacitated twice and apparently had a bunch of food in his stomach.
Do I just have him build a few houses?
But I got to get the free.
We got to go back to free will.
I'm going to lose free will here.
Look at how bad that looks.
It's like a zipper.
All right.
Hell yeah, I did it.
Are you sure you wish to leave the land?
Click again to confirm.
Leader, I've been hearing rumors that some more of our people survived the Aztec volcanoes.
Some elite archers managed to fight their way clear after we left.
We need to find them.
We need all the elite troops we can get.
We need everyone we can get.
Archers or not, they're on another land.
We must go and find them.
Yeah, archers.
What are we waiting for?
All right.
Twenty.
Yeah, that was a little bit of an evil level.
Preacher, 32% evil.
Age three.
He's now seven feet tall.
Fatness.
The lightest he was today was 592 pounds and now he's 2400 pounds.
That's like a car.
Fitness is actually not bad.
Hit points.
Final 45 because the number of bowel movements, 54.
167 kills.
Grain and villagers.
All right, we can do some miracles next time.
A little evil.
It's okay.
It's not full-blown evil.
Water field, water forest, build a wall, use creature rolls.
Undead legion, nut oil.
What is nut oil?
Undead legion and win the land.
What's undead legion?
Impressiveness was okay.
My vitals.
All right, we're good.
We saved the game.
Real Link, you got it.
No.
Opposite.
There's a lot of people right here.
Mega Man 2 is better than Black and White King.
There's some juicy towns to ransack.
I'm gonna like this place.
What?
Watch this.
You're wearing a cast.
No, no, no.
This is...
The rumors of the Greeks return are true.
My brother has sent me to make this island safe.
This I will do.
Oh, sounds like a tribal commander, boys.
We'd better start building now.
These Japanese seem to be formidable builders themselves.
And get some armies, boys.
They look pretty handy at fighting as well.
That's a pretty sick Nerf combat vest.
That's probably the best boy I've seen described.
50 warriors.
Now that's nice, boys, real nice.
What?
What is it?
I'm going to play with that toy.
This will be full of them.
What do you think about the toy?
So, you like your armies, do you?
Bow to the might of my armies.
It's got a lot of armies.
You love me.
Leader, you must start building a wall inside your influence.
I have to build a wall?
You finish outside it, but not in an enemy's influence.
I don't even have a creature den.
All right, we gotta start with the most important part.
And these guys will eat twice the normal rate.
So, keep an eye out on your stores by forcing from the tribute menu.
Okay.
All right, let me do the test.
Hey!
Oh, I can't.
I need to unlock forcing.
Get some sleep by the trees.
Yeah, I gotta build some shit first.
Let's build...
Let's get a storeroom back here.
Let's put it...
There's a bunch of trees over here.
Let's put it right here.
They're planning to store for the future.
This conflict will not have a speedy resolution.
Clear this out.
He just threw somebody.
Nation needs resources, and this storehouse will be full of them.
You're a little late, Murius, but you used a good try.
They will store enough to keep the form of this conflict alive for years to come.
Okay, let's get tons of...
Huge.
I mean, like, just a stupid amount.
Their land will soon yield them all they require.
Oops.
Okay, now let's get a...
71 people can work on there.
I taught him that.
I didn't mean to.
Let's drop this in here because it's ore.
Just re-ore.
Go play with your toy.
Stop.
Don't...
Stop doing, like, the...
Just stepping on people.
Stop!
He's doing it on purpose!
Get up!
What's up?
You can play with the toys, yes.
You can play with your toys, but just please move out of the way.
So I can pick up this boulder.
There we go.
So now we got...
Let's put some people in the woods.
People just doing their thing.
Let's get, like, 10, 20 people on the farm.
Disciple farmer.
10 people in the woods?
How many are here now?
Disciple farmer.
Work isn't filled.
5, 10.
Let's do, like, another 5.
Disciple farmer.
Hey.
We need to build some roads and some houses.
We're gonna do the houses back here.
Let me get your toys out of the way.
There's gonna be a street this way.
Two streets.
Two streets that meet into the main road here.
Sure.
Oh, here?
What?
What the hell was that?
Why is it...
Oh, he threw that over here.
Thank you, Mary.
I appreciate it.
Okay, now I got a big farm.
I need to build some houses.
Actually, how much tribute do I have?
All right, I want...
Don't I...
I already did that.
What do I want to research?
Okay, armory.
Our advanced soldier.
One man, one ball.
Voodoo doll.
Lamp.
Meadow?
What does a meadow do?
Animals can graze and flourish here.
It's an enhancement to the town.
Well?
Positive effects on the...
The town ham...
All right, I got to do the force pickup, right?
And forcing.
20,000.
What do I have?
150.
Yeah, I do it.
All right, I can now do that.
Plant market.
Okay, let's do...
Let's get a plant market.
House.
Maybe a...
I don't want to hovel.
Tavern?
People need somewhere to relax and unwind.
A prison.
Draggs have sighted the corrupting criminal
that kept away from the populace
within these diank walls.
Maybe a nursery.
I need this so bad.
All right, let's settle down here.
Yeah, settle down, settle down.
Now I got a lot of opportunity.
We got a real link.
Cool.
Save it here.
All right, have we settled down?
Have we settled down, everybody?
Did you get it out of your system?
Did you like scream into the bag long enough?
Are we functioning again?
Get this.
Oh, I need a creature den.
Oh, look.
A town right here.
Let's influence this town.
I'm not going to destroy this one.
Magical shrine of some sort?
I'm just a creature.
You're okay.
Influencer.
E-clown influencer.
No, not really.
Considering I've said,
can you guys settle down?
Settle down, please.
I'm the fucking substitute teacher in the class
of all like the bad kids.
You know what I mean?
Like, guys, can we just like tone it down a little?
And they're like, shut the fuck up, loser.
Okay, can, okay.
Said everybody, I'm Mr. Elbertson,
and I'm here to teach you math.
I'm not going to teach that math.
I'm not going to teach that class math.
They're going to fucking be mean to you.
You're going to try to connect.
Hey, teach.
Shut the fuck up and play the game.
You're a loser.
You suck.
I ain't doing shit today.
Nobody does that.
Hey, that doesn't happen in classrooms.
I haven't been in a classroom in 25 years.
I have no idea what kids do these days.
He always hit that lady.
All right.
Keep going.
No more distractions.
Wait, he did hit that lady.
He's playing peek-a-boo?
Why is he scared?
I'm going to play with that toy.
Good.
All right.
Let's focus, focus, focus, focus.
I need A.
Let's do a nursery for the new kids.
I'm going to go right over here.
That's fine.
Children are the future and need to be looked after.
So there are city builders.
They're not much my size.
Absolutely.
Please pull on the toy.
Yes.
Right.
Absolutely.
It was a false alarm.
I've been in that position before.
No, he didn't.
No, it's this.
I don't like to take spells.
Well, maybe you shouldn't shit on it.
Okay.
I need wood.
Yes.
Please help me construct the wood.
All right.
Yes.
Get out of the way.
You picked up like three twigs, dude.
Wait, what happened?
Did I get killed?
We good?
Are we good?
What happened?
All right.
Let's get some houses built.
We need some real houses.
Future generations of Greeks arrive in this land.
House, house, house, house.
Just a regular house.
Here we go.
Boom.
Are we good?
All right.
I want to do houses like this on either side.
Like that.
The Greeks wish to house their people.
This shows foresight.
We can now house our people.
Excellent.
Okay.
Same thing on the other side.
Jeremy, never leave us again.
I'm sorry.
I didn't.
I don't know what happened.
He's helping.
We're going to have a lot of kids.
One more.
All right.
We got a lot of houses here.
We need wood and lots of it.
Who's not?
Is anybody?
We need some foresters.
They're all foresters.
Shit.
Run out of wood here.
Let them settle in their houses.
Soon.
Wink.
I'm changing Wink to just like angry.
It's demonic.
Who was that?
Was that even you, dude?
We're going to run out of trees.
Greek holds seem uneasy for.
Stop hurting people.
You're hurting people.
Stop.
What if I just don't build any?
If I don't build any like war machines or factories,
won't that mean I'm not a threat?
We can be friends and stuff, right?
But it doesn't have to be violence like last time.
What if we?
We have homes for our warriors.
Although they choose to be on the battlefield.
Still need to build that wall.
I got a lot of houses.
Time to make some breeding.
Not being very helpful right now.
I estimated them.
Their tongue grows quickly.
Yeah, I got to start doing.
People have to start breeding.
How far into webcam?
I mean, it's going to start.
You're just going to start to make me fucking laugh out loud.
Water miracle.
Okay, let's do water miracle.
I can't.
I need to have a little worship.
You hate me.
That was depressing.
Look, see?
Breathe.
Let's go.
Breeding.
Start that population.
Breed, breed, breed, breed, breed.
Breeding.
More.
We need plenty.
We need people to live in these houses.
All right, that looks good for now.
Dancing?
All right, they all dropped it.
Okay, looking good.
We got a lot.
Let's do the.
Let's get some worshipers here.
At least this is how it merits is happy.
That's good.
All right, what else do I want?
I don't want to make an armory right now.
I need to make a temple.
I'm just going to go back here behind the altar.
Yep.
Praise all the gods you wish, Greeks.
They will not aid you now.
Are we going to get a cringy mode?
Never.
That's never going to happen.
We need to influence over here.
Actually, I can do this now, right?
Yeah.
Let's do this little side quest.
Student one, it has time for your test.
Destroy the blocks using your chi.
I don't want to do that.
Focus, boy.
What do I have to do?
It's got to hurt.
Poor fellow.
Perhaps you could help by destroying the blocks for him, leader.
I could do that.
Usually, I wouldn't agree with being a thief.
But when it comes to destruction, I just can't say no.
All right.
I'll destroy it.
What do you want me to do?
Like, grab it?
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Bash it?
How do I bash it?
I can't, like, move around?
No, no, no.
Focus your chi, student.
Uh, forcing brings your hand to the physics room.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Press and hold the action button in a clear area to engage forcing.
Gently, gentle movement will nudge things.
Wait.
Hold.
Okay, I'm holding the button down.
Nudge.
Is this what I'm supposed to be doing?
And then hit it when he...
Okay, well, let's try it again.
Okay, here we go.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Okay, he did that on his own.
I didn't do that.
He actually just did that.
I didn't do anything.
Excellent.
You must work harder, student.
I don't understand.
I don't, I don't get it.
Like, I hold the button down and then I'm trying to, like, nudge it.
The quantum moon.
Yeah, leave it.
I was trying to stay on the rock.
Let's try it one more time.
I don't really...
I was doing it right.
Okay, I'm just holding the button down here.
You need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Just hold it down.
I'm just holding it down.
I'm getting lucky three times in a row.
There's got to be some...
There was a weird ring that came up from the bottom of it.
Focus your chi, student.
Just wiggle it.
Press and hold the action button in a clear area to engage forcing.
Gentle movement will nudge thing.
Good work.
Um, why is it not working now?
You must work harder, student.
Gentle?
How is this not gentle?
Like, how is this not gentle?
Stay away from the rock, then move the hand close.
You were following me.
You need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
No, no, no.
Focus your chi, student.
Pull up the YouTube video.
Try stroking the rock while holding...
All right, I'm going to do this one more time before I have to go back and build buildings.
It's been like three days.
I'm not affecting anything right now.
Like, I have a fist right now and I'm not touching anything.
You need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
What is happening?
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
I have no idea what's happening.
You must work harder, student.
You may build cities, but nothing you can erect can match my cities.
Keep praying to your false gods.
Wait for him to strike and then do that.
A nursery to nurture the honorable warriors of tomorrow.
All right, it doesn't matter.
A magnificent temple.
Like my temple?
Respect from all outsiders.
Okay, I got some respect.
Let's do some worship.
Worship her.
Let's...
You, what are you up to?
Come over here.
Let's get you in the temple.
Okay, we got plenty of...
How's the nursery doing?
Good.
Plenty of room.
What do we need?
What do people need?
Food, desire, and homes are okay.
We need more food.
Water miracle.
Let's get this water like this.
Check this shit out.
Ready?
Are you sick?
There's more people on the farm.
Disciple farmer.
All right, all he's doing is throwing the bear back and forth.
What the hell is he doing?
Disband the army?
Can I?
I don't have a...
I think I need one of those war factories.
We'll do it.
Do some more watering.
More people in...
Oh, he's got a tree.
He's gotten big.
Disciple farmer.
Are these people foresting?
We almost have enough of them.
We're gonna take like two towns.
They're all going to bed?
We need a fucking road to go from here.
All right, what am I doing?
I need roads.
We get roads that come...
Okay, here we go.
Yeah, they might need roads.
I think they can actually walk.
We're going to gather that ore.
What is this?
Hey, will you fucking relax?
What is he doing?
Was the creature done?
Creature, creature, creature, creature pen.
There it is.
Let's put this one...
Let's put it up here.
Right on the edge.
They build a home for their creature.
I have never seen such a thing.
You don't have a creature?
How?
How is that possible?
Greeks have a formidable city.
My people must work harder.
Nah, I don't want to fight.
You've taken over the town.
We have?
Why would my people forfeit their honor and join the enemy?
How many people?
These people join us and take up our culture.
We will benefit from their strength.
It's five people.
There's five people there, man.
Thanks.
That's cool, I guess.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Good to see you.
Wait, hold on.
Their town is gone.
They're dismantling their entire town
and bringing five people over here.
I wanted to keep those buildings.
I would have kept those buildings.
Okay.
That's sure.
Whatever.
Come on in.
I see you taking the road.
Smart.
These Greeks are like any people I have met before.
Give me a flag.
Nah, I'm trying to accept you.
Give me the flag.
Our migration is waiting at our borders for you to accept.
Come on in.
Six people.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Where are you going?
Come on in.
We've got plenty of room.
Now we build down here.
And then there's another place right here.
Look at this.
There's nine people in this town.
Let's influence this way.
We have a nursery.
The children grow and love us.
Great cities.
Where are you guys off to?
Let's get some water.
All right, Murius.
Can I give you a task or something?
He's just been whipping his...
Let's put you on gathering.
Here, gather.
Gather food.
You're so preoccupied with the toy.
All right.
Now, what do we need now?
Let's build...
What are we doing on population?
On houses?
Food.
Everything's doing fine.
No, why are people so unhappy?
Child population zero.
What?
What are you...
How?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
What are the kids?
Where are all the children?
A magnificent temple.
We'll learn respect from all outsiders.
They need beer.
Okay.
Tavern.
Let's put the tavern.
I want influence.
So let's put it down here.
Can I get it over here?
Come on.
There's a road right there too.
Murius, get your toys out of the way.
Right here.
What's this?
The population will be grateful.
Now you've built them a tavern.
I have to get rid of this shit.
Look at how annoying this is.
Allow our hardworking people to wax
and praise our culture through drink.
You'll need to work harder
to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
What, the smoke?
I mean, did the shit on the ring underneath it happen before?
No, no, no.
Hold the button and shake left and right until smoking.
Is this mission?
What is this thing?
Hold button down and shake left and right.
I saw the smoke.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Focus your chi, student.
I don't even know what this game is wanting me to do.
Like, oh, you can interact with the world,
but shake until there's smoke.
It doesn't say that.
Okay, I'm in it.
Touch.
Really shake it.
Really shake that thing.
Just do it at the same time.
Forwards and back.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Wrong at the same time.
Punch at the same time.
Just go up and down.
No, no, no.
In the name of god.
Focus your chi, student.
Tap?
Shake?
What the fuck?
No, put this down.
Read the other signs.
These other signs have nothing to do with this.
Dearly departed.
Dead people in the streets.
Empty towns.
Yeah, this has nothing to do with this.
Slide between all three rocks.
When I was sitting here going up and down like this,
there was a ring that was appearing underneath it.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
When I was doing this last time, it actually worked.
Good work.
I haven't changed anything.
You must work harder, student.
Do it in a circle.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
What?
I- why is it working sometimes?
I saw the smoke.
No, no, no.
Focus your chi, student.
Up and down.
Shake harder.
Good work.
You must work harder, student.
Is there a YouTube video of somebody doing this?
This doesn't make any sense.
You basically can't stop shaking for a second or you fail.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
I'm not letting go.
The fist is closed.
What are you talking about?
Slightly larger- why would they make this like this?
This is the strangest video game mechanic I've ever seen.
You must work harder, student.
Just repeatedly punch.
You'll need to work harder to harness the awesome power of chi.
You may try again when you feel ready, student.
Yes, Grand Master Kai.
Good work.
This is- going in a circle?
No, this is- shake, punch the thing.
This one's not working.
All these people are like, dude, get in a circle and go up and down.
Move it in a circle.
Shake it as violently as you can.
Received tribute.
Well, I don't care about the tribute.
I'm just glad that I've got real estate now.
Imagine trusting me like that.
The tunnel will allow our hard-working people to relax and-
Save again.
Hold on, I need to-
Praise our culture through drink.
Okay, tavern.
More follower.
Is the game loud for you guys?
It's loud for me.
What happened?
Why is it loud?
We gain strength in such-
All right, temple is almost done.
We cannot fail.
Water the plants?
All right, how's he doing over here?
Are you still gathering?
All right, he's gonna hate me for this.
He doesn't want to gather forever.
Drinking weakens the senses of both builders and strategists.
How much-
Okay, we're good.
What do we need?
Do we have food?
More food.
I got-
Okay, am I gonna just fucking pull it up?
I'll do it myself.
That's fine.
Water.
What did I just do?
I got-
All right, food is now not an issue anymore.
Water again?
Buy myriads of spells.
Yeah, let's go.
It's time to buy some spells.
Advanced builder.
Heal miracle.
Lightning miracle.
75,000?
Should I give him lightning again?
Like he used to.
He loved lightning before.
He's getting it.
All right, what else can I do?
Rest home?
Lumber mill.
That's what I want.
Are we doing on crops?
More.
We need houses?
Are we actually having children born now?
Happiness bonus.
How are there no kids in the town?
There's 12 breeders.
How are there no kids?
177 adults.
Is it-
Are we foe?
Do we need more homes?
All right, I'm doing it, though.
I'm-
Okay, I'm gonna do them over here.
I'm gonna have another street over here.
You're in the boring suburbs?
Oh, we gotta make sure we hit all these.
All right, let's go.
These Greeks are expanding their territory.
We must remain vigilant.
This game's so much fun.
How are we doing on-
I want to take this mission very, very, very slow.
You know?
I want to make sure we're prepared.
And I'm gonna use diplomacy first.
Not fireballs.
Not mounting somebody and punching them in the face until they're dead.
Diplomacy.
All right, we need a-
We're here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Better, better, better.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ah!
Start the construction of the Siren Wonder.
Oh, this is bad.
What?
Noooo!
Okay, connected.
A migration is waiting at our borders for you to accept them.
Who?
Oh.
Hi, guys.
Pretty cool area you got here.
I'll be taking it.
All right, finally, there's children playing.
All right, Murius is gonna get bored.
Uh, look at all this food.
Murius, you're done?
Please, just cease what you're doing.
Be an entertainer.
Just hang out in the middle of the town.
We entertain our new friends.
entertain the new friend look at new friends yes there they are yes it is
haircut why does Mary's have this haircut we need we wear everything's
doing great that leads us to over here a lot of space we unite against the Greek
menace our honor and power shall drive them from this land what do we do the
storehouse down here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah storehouse down here no I
can't I don't own this yet I'm gonna put something up here
doorhouse up here and then a farm or house up no I want a little under
armory armory yep I got some space down here too okay armory is going down here
and then a ranged armory we'll train the finest swordsman with this armory good
is there even a mine I don't see a mine anywhere doing diplomacy I am but just
in case I also need more borders just in case it should take me pretty high up so
the Greeks are most warriors we must be ready for the inevitable us hold here it
is very good mine got a mine mine right here okay I gotta build up this way keep
entertaining we need it right now look at all these kids that are coming in we
need more time or more houses because we're gonna have a ton of kids coming
in people my grades to the Japanese way of life get rid of this don't throw that
all the way all right so I have it this is I get a eventually build this more
houses mansions I'm gonna invest in mansions at 15,000 maybe a well yeah
yeah yeah he bought a plant market what I don't even know this does but I'm
putting it in town like you sell plants people are happier when the town has a
market we now have a market we Japanese are traders and builders at heart need
armies combining forces leash platoons of swordsmen to platoons of archers as
one would protect the other good to know platoons at rest will automatically
regen health good okay we need more houses we need them or he's getting huge
yeah he is cool we're starting to continue development over here let's
start running out of trees houses more houses house keep it going I want an
insane population because I want to be able to train like 5,000 troops if I need
to that's good for now we'll do the other side okay I can get a road there
it's okay because you know I know you don't want to be on the same street as
everybody what ignoring horrible city planning why this is two different this
town is ugly is that this takes place in like 6 BC why they also pissed watch out
oh gate houses stundas warnings to all we now have a market we Japanese are
traders we now have a market why they have to say it hey just want to let you
know we've got a market now no so do I this should be good on population for a
while finally I got like a good starting point here it's too much grass in this
village I have cement they have taken another settlement those that expand
too fast expose their flanks oh shit they're company here they come see we
don't even need violence we just have this bustling city see I told you we're
gonna use diplomacy this time I told you I have fun with even plant trees I know
that is fun all right what's wrong we need food what's the population oh man
what's the population okay adult population 243 oh fuck okay I need we
need food all right go back to gathering we did together actually free will do
whatever you want I need more farms we're gonna put some I'm gonna do a
second farms over here put it on one I don't know all right I need to write in
our culture brings we need two more farmers farmers farmers you all right
what's wrong with you person has had a kid okay I will watch me the interest
while the siren does her work does that mean we need some more we need more
farmers come on in put your toy down make another farm back here actually I'm
gonna put it over here yeah good idea good idea Jeremy right here that's fine
I'll get it in a second hold on I know the doorbells ringing but hold on okay
yes welcome now all of you go work at a farm why does Marius have an utter and
some of you breathe too we want more breeding is that my party in here okay
water that place but I'm gonna do some self don't harvest it on our own okay
do I need more farms another one shit we need something up here so I can go
start going this way have I taken all the towns over here yes I have there's
only one that's over here that exists and I think I can build a little bit
more shit over here let's put a wall up right with the gate smart that's pretty
smart protect you from the magnificence of our city what is this wall to keep me
out or to keep their slaves in that's gonna build right am I chats being
degenerate Chats been on drugs all night
I have no idea what's going on get more people in the field all right
Marius I know you love it I know you do but like you've just told you play with
the toy too much you're too old for that toy okay just okay you can play with the
toy once in a while you can but you're too old for that toy you're like you're
like 30 policy I'm going to beat on those animals what hey what are you
doing I sometimes attack wild animals no you don't stop that don't do that
again anymore farmers I'm gonna start to get overrun by people in a second here
we need more food fuck how much food we need yes Trump hair all right more
farmers I'm doing what I can on my own here the teachings say walls which keep
the full route also keep the strength in I fucked up this wall I don't even know
how I did it what's he doing of course he's doing man and he just art just
farting let me check on how we're doing as a town everyone's so unhappy why
productivity birth rate why is everyone so unhappy need more bars and markets
I'm gonna build another bar right here I'll put another bar over here look see
bar their warriors will become bliss if they spend their time drinking in such
places because they're forced to breed and farm right but let's make another
market let's make a plant market yeah another plant market see we'll have
another one right here right next to it hang out at the plant market it's a
little skewed but it's okay breed fart farm water the trees a little bit all
right now we need breed farm fight drink play with toy sad face okay we have or
I don't have very much I don't have very much at all we need people to be over
here okay we need miners now who wants to go mine over there I need
influence over here I can't even send anybody there they're different mine I
don't have access to a mine don't I the town chooses the honorable path of
Japanese enlightenment it's not a mine oh no I did build it this bell they're
eating all the food they're eating all the food oh they're eating all the food
what I tell you about playing with that toy all of you go oh they just sitting
around eating fuck it's okay here they all come I need some of you guys be oh
they're all just going in random direction they have a place to live I
put you in the mine I'm quick enough I just threw him I was trying to get him
into the mine is this a mine no I have to build something right here how about
a another storehouse up here good to me then we'll have the farm here more trees
and I'm I you cowards don't even smoke crack nobody should smoke crack not even
you Trump hair I can't even get over it
hey the creature collected 5,000 we get some tribute nice job okay let's get
some people over here God's sake you mine I throw you again I need another
building I need something else over here how about what are you how are you on
houses population 432 for oh we gave me the road to go over here which road one
of these ones come up from here we've got away please I'm working we've got
the way I'm working I'm working all right here we go we're gonna wrap
around here like this all right how is a keen to be part of a civilization we
welcome them we need another nursery all right nursery 2 is gonna go over here
and then this graveyard this shows me to go back here I know we gotta get the
way from the town right teachings right back to be up here or over here
graveyard is gonna go over here there's like a fine place for it back here okay
good oh you're wicked funny fucking stupid fucking goddamn fucking idiot
fucking stupid fucking idiot a nursery for more kids I think this look at this
town's looking pretty good look at this little town look at this place look at
this place we've got we're secure on the left side look at we've got our own
happy little town but nobody's happy but you know what I mean all right let's do
some more houses I was sure I want mansions I have a hundred and two
thousand tribute we need bigger houses about a statue market these will make
them happier yeah yeah yeah that's fine a manner manner rat home no okay that's
fine we're good let's build some this is okay this is where like they're all like
the rich people are gonna live next to the gold mine that makes like a little
sense of lore the statue market over here right next to the right after the
people you get out of the temple yes they tempt our towns send our just to
fortify the walls how you doing Murius you having fun all right we need to
wood I need or two can't build this without or what do I have fucking none
700 is something I have to finish building over here right did they build
it already oh wow you guys are so smart statue market you need what it or desire
and homes oh fuck okay all right right right mansions mansions mansions where
is it mansion manner here we go Greek architecture is sturdy what does this
take to build all right that's enough because I'm gonna now okay let's put
some out here too he's gonna be like in the little another little corner here of
them it'll be a road that'll connect to I don't know I'm something I don't know I
don't know how do I do how to delete I didn't think this one through all right
I get in that mine whoa I took this city I didn't do anything
by the way I think coming to take no they're coming this one right up here
yeah I'm doing pretty well how can mine oh shit go get yeah go mine
food I'm working on it working on it okay working on it
integration is waiting at our borders for you to accept them working on it
working on it that's a lot of people I don't have houses for you
is he doing it is he actually picking these up oh yes good all right 200 3200
save the game holy fuck you're right you couldn't be more right all right now I
need to finish what was I finishing this oh yeah houses these manners honey wood
in here manner what's ticking he's taking the town over there but that's
not that doesn't concern me I'm just tacking until the end game and then
Murius is gonna go over there and just electrocute the fuck out of every single
person and we're gonna win that's what that's what's going to happen
I need wood is this done it's done okay take that and sure whatever finish that
house finish the house no Murius Murius Murius Murius Murius finish the house
finish the house where you putting this no you just put it in the hole that
shit gone thank you thank you son we're done right we just need I need some more
wood this is done this is done this needs a little more this one's done done
done done done they all done done done all right we need a road I need a road
going up here I know ugly sucks terrible shitty I know I know I know but just
bear with it I figured out what to do later okay
that's food looking we're actually weird perfect right now 10,000 tribute and
people are just barely starting to be happy or 94 I got lots of space we got
this place in front of us is almost ours we're gonna build up with that wall
built make some houses to the road from the second set of houses we gotta go we
gotta build some shit down there ready it's gonna blow I got tons of I got
tons of everything now I just gotta get people into that mine he just put this
up holy shit Murius look at this all right you can take a break take a break
you can take have some rest you can take some rest that was a huge rock nice
we've got another oh shit they're dead have a place in which they may rest
honorably miracles sacrifice for a quick burst of mana you can sacrifice people
into the bowl on the altar keep in mind yeah this is a big mine all right I gotta
get some influence up to this way we're gonna go straight up I'm going to eat
that villager okay sure well I don't know who well who that even was all
right it sounds good we need more houses oh my god we do need okay we're gonna
try to connect up this way I'm going straight up here you go ready we'll have
something from here maybe a little housing development no wait this way
I'm gonna go this way housing development connecting to this road
here and I don't know I'm talking like Dan Aykroyd why that was a perfect Dan
Aykroyd I didn't even try what are you trying to tell me sign important to
build and protective walls as soon as possible yeah I've got one they're going
up Maria is Marissa sleep here is he's got free will so you can do whatever
okay so water some shit it's over here graveyard right okay so now this is
where I make 700 people in the military and just walk in a straight line and kill
everybody get their base that's nothing this is nothing these creeks should not
be our enemies but we must oppose them the Aztecs command us to where's your
creature you're gonna have one lame Wow fucking lame you don't even have a
creature this will be easy so how we doing let's check all right let's do
check up what can angry there are 300 males to 160 females I make 160 soldiers
there why they what I mean why should I make like a hundred soldiers and just
put them up no no no no no no I have keep keep them but they keep going with
the plan plan is let's put some more houses up this way building out I want
to how much trippy do I have a lot of rest home all these crumblies yeah we
need for all people yep we're gonna put a rest home up here actually we're gonna
do like two this is gonna be where the old folks go like back here no I want to
get some yeah right here this is fine this would be like the the old zone yeah
this is where they all want to hang out is with a 55 plus communities should be
good I'm fucking addicted to this game respect for the elderly and infirm is a
true sign of strength well the second one so are we able now we capable where
these where's everybody going over here lumber I do the lumber mill lumber mill
lumber mill granary yeah yeah yeah all right granary over here what do you
think right in the middle this is like a back here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
think so back here right like over here right here
granary not do the houses back here it's gonna sit right here I'll get the ready
here we go check it feeding the people just got easier with this granary all
right now we need a lumber mill did I upgrade the lumber mill I don't think I
bought that yeah did one of the mills going over here by the houses I mean I
have to put it over here don't I know they like get that out of here was like
having a fucking cell tower in your backyard come on guys relax it's a
lumber mill like it's really loud I'll do it down here there's nothing over
here it is precious and this lumber mill is so efficient just meant to do some
adjustments to the boomer brace here they're okay over there all right I need
1500 shit butter or did I build something else down here I'm losing
track when there's something else I constructed I guess not not yet I just
put it back or so they begin to stockpile their food supplies granary
complete lumber mill complete more material for their constructions how's
this evil I haven't done anything evil yet go get your toy all right it's time
to expand outward oh I said it and now he's playing with it he's jacked look
how huge he is okay now the wall gate there that looks pretty fucking good
hide behind no matter I can tempt their people out no you won't I got great
benefits here they're like fucking immaculate you can't even compete I
can't do anything over there yet all right how we build out how we doing on
offspring birth rate is normal low productivity normal pressiveness why is
everybody hate everything well is he so why is everybody so angry I have like a
statue market I've got looking at this right more taverns what I got like three
taverns taverns near the houses in their tavern right here alcohol you fool oh I
near the houses okay hold on they hate it I got tribute to spend 14,000 no I
don't let's go I got to get to this front door output level plus 75% that's
insane look at the food now city planning city planning I didn't know I
had to put the current parade there's 14 people in here what else increases
happiness well I'm gonna put this right right okay well look where this is going
look right here it's right in the middle of the right there okay so there's a
well here what live laugh drink muscle milk okay now you go to well you can use
it whoever wants to use it use it are you happy look they're like I guess all
right another one another well right here for you guys this is for you you
know we need the wood all right I got a shit little another well see there you
go hey still unhappy all right replace the house with the market everybody up
how do I delete this I don't really like rip this out of the ground too much
breeding all right we'll slow down on the breed find breeders and we'll make
them I don't know miners torture pit no I'm not torturing anybody I got a build
out here so I can get to the mine put a tavern right here no fuck a market we'll
put a just a little plant market right here you guys look cool I know let's do
another one plants and shit right here I mean like that what about right over
here check it out there's another plant market right here no more fucking get to
the mine they want to like it but they're saying I don't like it but they
do like it they're saying nah I don't know about that but yes look at their
faces it's like it's green which means yes right they're saying like green is
it neutral what is I don't understand good are we good okay are we happy hey
nobody no children in this nursery because it's not connected to any roads
there's no kids here why is it no kids in nursery we need homes no no one's
fucking cuz no oh right cuz they don't have any homes all right let's go
houses manors up this way we're going up I spent so much time making houses I'm
gonna have a thousand people all right I may have built too many houses what do
you think too many all right we're gonna do house house plant factory and then
another house fuck outside no no no no no all right here we go they're all
waiting for the house to be built this like this is a lot of people all right
now I'm gonna put a well and a statue trading Murius you're helping and I
appreciate it look up here with the tree good you know it's your favorite thing
you love trees right so now we are going to what statue market right here and then
well and then maybe a trading post just trying to make people happy adequate
housing all right we're still going now we can make the road go up a little more
all right so from here I'm gonna build another the men are horny how much how
many men do I have 370 okay it's time it's time it's time to have like a
hundred people in New York this is more than two to one male to female I we got
up but no they're gonna eat all the food no not yet they're gonna eat all the
food are we still in slow-mo I don't think so I think Chad is like stops
like drinking crack beer so these are all done if you believe in them almost
happiness no 197 hey I see some happy faces I see some happy faces now let's
get a statue market over here and then let's put a well
one of the towns full of rage all right I think it's time to what do I need how
much trivia do I have 17,000 I'm with my objectives anyone know how to get that
period I'm going too much I'm going to go don't eat no no I'm going to munch on
that rock oh now he's now he's walking weird move rocks I need to teach we need
to get tribute what was it how do I get to the the objective so I can get some
trip you sure people are starting to move up it's a sign scrubbing scrub the
ground by forcing it repeatedly by any scrubbing motion okay you're talking
about I can't do it over here because I'm not sad for I'm a bit hungry we'll
maybe you didn't eat rocks what is this hey okay no don't eat anybody oh wait
wait wait wait um where's the destruction tool okay now you've been a
bad boy you've been a bad bad boy go think about what you've done you just
right when I get everybody happy excuse me you've been a very very bad
Murius that's right get I'm sorry but you don't stomp on people and throw
rocks at people that's not what we do here go think about it
he's hairy gonna get my haircut you find I think a nap I gotta go fix you a
mess which yeah which house was it they rebuilt it all right they've already
rebuilt it we're good now that pissed off yeah maybe you shouldn't throw
fucking rocks at people the Greeks spread like blooms on the blood-soaked
battlefield it what are you doing okay nice thank you did I what I'll sometimes
sleep by a player's storehouse whatever that's fine you want to he's so hairy
drop a heel please all right I need to take a look 558 people in the
population all the people over here are pissed okay I get it demolish one of
these it's my demolish tool okay one two three four five six seven one two
three four five six seven one two three four five six seven one two three four
sorry you guys a random lottery to get your house destroyed sorry put in a
market here I just raised your house to put in a store I know that's very very
it's not good I know that's not good but you gotta do you gotta do everyone's
unhappy over there because of that and I'm gonna put a well somewhere over
there too finally they like no we don't have to drive to the grocery store
17 miles away there you go how's everybody doing let's take a look now
give me a bigger picture please still unhappy over here on the left why I'm my
unhappy me well there are no strip clubs come on there's not enough space to do
this ah right there you build it we do want food all the desires are fine this
is hustling it's pretty good better let's put this in here I need miners okay
we gotta build we have to put something here what can I put here that's fine or
another pen no I'm well I don't know what should I put up here to torture
pit no make another temple he's had it sit right up here there we go right here
people are gonna like look at how happy they are that this is gonna be here you
have a hat I thought he had a hat on where did he get a hat so now we could
make some miners finally long enough there's a happiness factor in here all
right well I are not unhappy like not past they're like not thrilled but
they're not red all right let's make let's put some people into the mines
disciple mine worker I'm gonna say probably like 10 people in the mines
disciple mine worker oh I asked a long time ago to anybody you're gonna play
with the building be gentle with it please I was actually pretty sick that
was pretty awesome when'd you learn that I'm gonna pick breeders I think who was
a breeder yeah I think just killed somebody mine mine mine there's so many
people I just gotta start grabbing them maxed out zero to 20 what are you
talking about that's a lot of wood mine worker reader
it's in a weird slope it's hard to put people there all right now oh I keep
asking this question and turn it around I keep not even looking and paying
attention what what's the button to look at the objectives yeah why would that
many people say f disciple mine worker I'm gonna chomp on those trees wait he's
gonna eat a tree now we're gonna talk about your diet man I'm going to snack
on that grain he's pretty big what grain can you pick this up are you strong
enough to lift this up can't do that you can't pick it up not strong enough okay
well go do whatever you want free will have fun David sounds like plan yeah let
me see let me see input action left mouse button quick save is ctrl s quick
load show text window function tooltips is it tab splay fertility map oh that's
what it is instruction tool objective window oh there it is when the land
build a wonder create a hundred soldiers creature collects resources isn't he
doing that already we need soldiers okay it's time making a hundred soldiers we're
doing 60 60 melee so and then you like your armies do you 40 archers might of
my armies here we go population control we need 40 archers so we have just
deleted out of the city and now I should put people into breeding so now
we've I've got food it's important I'll get 10,000 favor for doing this or
whatever it's called they're gonna be eating a shitload of food we have to
make sure I got food stores I don't like really at all but that's okay and I'm
we're going to capture this no no no no no capturing no capture right no
capturing no no no no seize it who's gonna shit a little hearing built a
platoon they plumb war he's getting like thousand years was there a rate oh shit
well welcome who raided I didn't see it is it time to go just I don't want to
take anything by take over three towns by force oh come on you're gonna give me
that let's go how do you make a can you make them like defend each other and
stuff all right let's go capture it wasn't their way I could make the the
arches support the group thousand came in a thousand left oh that's weird they
got snapped out it's captured by force I don't want Murius to see this I don't
want him to see what is this minus minus 500 food so there's this town here
there's a I'm gonna wrap around this town here I want to get this town first
so we're gonna go we're gonna come back actually we should have gone this way
first damn it ah that's all right build a wonder
mysterious we're actually probably gonna be calling it a night here soon and
resuming tomorrow afternoon I'm still into this game I still want to play it
close the gate now yeah it's not that I do you really bring over he brought over
he brought over like 20 food into the stream voice yeah yeah we've been go for
like seven hours probably time to wind it down a little bit I gotta get some
food and only two lands after this one and then the expansion yeah I'm just
it's just fun to play I'm just having a good time and tomorrow we'll maybe we'll
just play for a little bit see if I'm still into it and move on something
else so after I take this over that's probably what we're gonna call it seven
exact hours Mega Man confirmed Mega Man not confirmed all right we got this
town I'm gonna okay here we go this is a good place to start tomorrow yeah oh
yeah all right yeah we'll call here I will see you guys tomorrow we're gonna
start with this and then after this depending on how much I'm still into it
after three four plus hours we'll see what we want to do thanks for watching
see you tomorrow have a wonderful day it's gonna play rain world I don't know
what that's not that's not determined yet we'll see you tomorrow though let's
get to the bits let me make sure I can get out of this game it's not gonna
crash on me hey we're good all right the game crashed let's hope that's not a
bad time I saved it okay thank you for joining me in the
MOOC room let's go back seven hours ago at the beginning of the stream we had
potion dweller for 250 thank you potion dweller with the tragic news of Winx
going away we will activate a day of retaliation spending all our wing points
on the very last day I forgot what day that is so please restate as of let's
see streaming tomorrow as of Thursday the 27th of February we're gonna change
links to something else we're gonna change we're gonna freshen it up a
little bit there's your official date dude are you fucking serious oh fuck oh
god oh no no fuck I didn't even get to use one that's the problem is gonna be
this never-ending cycle of people trying to build enough and people that have
built enough so we want it we'll do something more more interesting than a
wink a wink it's just like a wink turn off because I can go back to being
naked it is that's a great that's good for me that's good for me there you go
there's the last day for Winx hopefully the next thing I do is something do a
foot cam I don't think I'm gonna do a foot cam hey will got thanks for the two
dollars and 69 cents thanks for streaming both these games you're missing
my favorites as a kid I remember when you load up black and white too you can
actually play with a lion head logo as a physics toy this blew me away yep yes
you can black and white one you do that too you can scoop up the pixelated it's
really cool never before half-life or half-life 2 did it make do it five
minutes of bugleberry you know that would be so bad I can't do that
ex-war 2 thanks for the 250 germa don't let the fact that you can't figure out
the controls of a strategy game meant for baby children distract from the fact
that you instantly killed and mercilessly destroyed Chad Rack the kind
man who became a tree who helped you on your journey in sorcery book 3 at the
first chance you were given this game was this game was not meant for children
this game was meant for gods and everything has to be a children okay what
is it what is a non children's game I've come curious it seems like oh man you
can't even play this children's game look at this children's what's a not
children's game what would be in that category dark souls okay what about
besides dark souls Nancy Drew Nancy Drew is a kid the children's game I'm sorry
porn games okay well that's a Sam freelance police thanks to the 250 high
germa I made a lo-fi song using using your my father was a wealthy man
monologue I dedicated it to my dad for his 50th birthday it's a bit long but I
hope you can share it during a community night also it's my birthday on the 24th
do something fun and I'll bring a cake well what a perfect opportunity to have
us announce the next community night the next community night is going to be you
ready let me make sure I get this right because I have a things plan let's see
going boing boing then the next community night is going to be Sunday
March 1st March 1st Sunday we're gonna do community night before it'd be pretty
fun that quick this yeah there's a ton of submissions is a lot of so but you
guys have been putting in so much stuff community crack night now that was that
wasn't even today and by the way let me what the hell was going on today what
was going on today I look over at the chat room and people just going crazy
people were going nuts it was just like just spam for like 30 minutes I understand
spam is fun spam can be fun but I'm not sure there was one comment but anything
that we were doing it was just like copy pastas and people screaming at each other
and we got we got a we got a hit way omega low cringe community who cares
game sucks the game what how could you say that some of you guys were fucking
seeing red it was a wink I'll get it don't worry don't it's just it was
messy and it was going so fast too that's the thing it's not even about oh
wow there's some spam oh it was a hundred miles per it was just crazy this
is what it's like for you now it's not a community it's chat it's alright though
I just we're stream 2020 what are you talking about I like had a ton of fun
playing but they were non subs I don't believe that for a second I saw some
subscribers in there throwing mud at each other this game's fucking hilarious
and fun and interesting we talked about oh where's chat experience I see well
put it on the list put on the list put on six months up mode as the channel
grows and this is I know this is a road that I have to figure out what I want to
do about it and I don't think we've really talked about it but when when
there are there's really two ways you can really moderate a community I know a
chat room it's like either just let it fly and fucking it's whatever and just
anything it's just people just writing anything besides obviously the pain of
shit that you don't want your chat room or you have to really really moderate
and have very strict rules and potentially even have it on permanent
like sub only mode it's it's really difficult to balance in the middle and I
really don't know which one of them I would rather have because it's it's
tough because on one hand I want there to be people just engaging and having
fun and you know just talking shit and having a good time and being able to
write whatever they want as long as it's you know relevant to what the fuck we're
doing and like in the community or whatever but then you know you get to
the point where is it just like people writing just spam that has nothing to do
with anything it's just I'm just gonna write this because I decided to and which
one of those roads do you want to take and as this channel gets to a point
with is but sometimes it's you know five plus thousand six thousand plus people
at the same time I figure out how I want to do I want to have a more strictly
moderated chat that's you know very very strict and people we can actually read
the chat and communicate or do I want like a let's get a fuck who fucking
cares it's hard to do something in the middle 30 minutes slow mode 12 month
only mode that would be so bad I don't think it's even about more mods it's
just how I want the community and the chat to be enforced but you you get to
that the end of the road where there's the cliff there and like there's two
where there's two ways to jump they increase the moderation and maybe have
sub only on sometimes because this is like a shitload of potential this shit
lot of people here or just whatever it just take out like the bad stuff but
just kind of let it ride and have people say kind of whatever they want it's it's
tricky I don't mind chaos I mind people posting in bad faith just to cause
trouble but that what that but that's what I'm saying this with a highly
moderated chat that is almost it's hard for that to happen moderate the off
topic stuff and I and I can be sort of guilty of this myself because I like to
just say shit that people you know you guys will look over be like oh hey
something about this what about that and then I know people are gonna fucking
just start spamming and you know I'm saying that's fun so how do you manage
that too it's a lot it's I'm thinking about I'm thinking about it and I know I
thought this this is not I don't like having these conversations because but
you kind of have to have them because it's I'm not gonna pretend like oh yeah
there's people are fucking like screaming in the chat and there's the
same copypasta thousand times and the same link has been posted a hundred
times and there I saw one guy say something about the cow and it is kind
of there beater only mode I actually brought it well it's not that I haven't
brought up we talked about this last week about I'm gonna put a separate
place for links for images and I like having a fun chat and don't get me
wrong I fucking love the chaos but we might have to do some controlled chaos
chaos control as Shadow the Hedgehog once said and he was on to something and
this is I'm not like mad I'm not upset about anything which is it's just
something we need to talk about we got to talk about it I'm not mad as obviously
if I was you would probably know it's just as we go forward you got to think
about some ways to control the chaos but also let the chaos through let's see
he's disappointed no no no no not at all I'm not disappointed I'm not angry now
if you excuse me I have to mute my mic for a minute
I swear fuck go fucking every single fucking time I'm not I there's nothing
wrong all right we'll move on that's all I want to say hey seven layer Wario
thanks for the 1,400 bits thanks Wario 14 dollars you're I got back from a
really good job interview now I'm back home to watch you torture a village with
a giant cow that's come on that's like that sounds like a pretty great Saturday
afternoon what's today Thursday that sounds like a great Thursday afternoon
thank you and good luck on the job hope you get it
silent serenity thanks for 250 hey Jeremy I made a big money at the boomer
casino stock market recently so here's 250 bits don't spend it all in one place
kiddo I won't I will use it in with something else thank you I have visit
like two weeks got the third one Freddy's red and phylacter lich both gave
but Freddy gave a hundred community subs and phylactery get 69 so together
they had 169 subs in 30 seconds so thanks both of you guys it's fucking
ridiculous actually fucking crazy and the phylactery as I'm saying this gave
5,000 bits right now thanks by like during they say hey German to set up a
24-hour slow-mo everyone gets one message per stream actually 30 minutes
I think is the long or as long as you can do well I don't want to do that
though like that I don't want to do that I don't want to like you can only write
one message every fucking 15 minutes every 5-10 minutes just like I don't
want to do that I like when people have fun if you're sitting in the chat and
you can only write like once every 10 minutes no that's not you're not
chatting you're posting your post there are people that tweet more than once
every 10 minutes and that's how long that's what I'm allowing you to fucking
chat in my stream Sam and Max 30-minute slow-mo was a fun joke yeah it was but
I don't really want like when you control it too much people just start to
it's not a chat anymore it's not a community it's like I know no no no you
don't speak you get one message well anyway well and the King's going to read
that one message and what does it say ah see you another 12 minutes when you're
allowed to speak I'll get it right we'll figure it out
randomized two-minute ban what happens when you get to 10k viewers I don't know
man I don't know you know it's a constant reevaluation of the channel
you'd have to have more it would have to be I don't know I have I cross that
bridge if that bridge ever needs to be crossed but son of Genova thanks for the
250 German you're a bad person why what I do I was waiting for black and white
2 since way before you played black and white 1 it keeps getting delayed and the
one day you played is the day I haven't examined another city I kindly demand an
apology because the expectations of your only important subscriber aka me have
not been fulfilled thanks oh I had technical problems with the game last
week sorry I that fan patch I wanted to make sure I get it installed I screwed
something up sorry you didn't get to watch black and white 2 but it's okay
because Murius will be back tomorrow that should be happening actually this
should be happening ancient Sasquatch thanks for the 250 I had an evil
German dream last night you hacked into my phone and forced me to play your
twitch game show you destroy other people's phones if they don't answer a
few random questions right I got about three out of seven but then it came down
to a troll choice between the right one and picked the green one I answered
wrong and you destroyed it saying I just don't understand why there's so much
nihilism in the chat chat spammed the German nihilism emote and that's when I
woke up German nihilism invaders thanks invaders for the 250 hey German want to
say thanks you're the reason that I know my best friend and my partner Henry I
love you Henry thank you for bringing us together because without you I would
never met him thank you from both of us well thank you that's good enough it's
really good to know thank you invaders glad to bring you together thank you
Timothy laughing my ass off that's a pretty great name ten bucks from Timothy
he just added an underscore LMAO that's a great name I feel like I would I would
have that name I want that name I feel like that would be my name if I wasn't
German I need five and I would just say I would just write a bunch of bullshit in
people's chats and like that I get it I get it trust me when I tell you I get it
I really do I do I mean that right I know I get it I do but when this is a
lot of people here I get it thanks for the ten bucks Timothy
abomination there abomination zero thanks to 340 three dollars and 40 cents
this is all I got but I want to thank you again German I'm gonna overshare but
my shitty parents are kicking me out in a month just want to thank you for all
the good times and help you've given me just by being you keep it up I'm really
sorry to hear that hopefully you can crash with a friend for a while maybe
some relatives or something might be able to help you out that's not fun I'm
really sorry to hear that I have no idea how old you are what your situation
is but I really hope it gets better I'm sure you have already but some
potential relatives like cousins aunts maybe could help you uncles friends
hopefully you can get on the right path here thanks for the 340 take care
yourself wish you the best Hank cheesecake thanks for the 400 bits
honestly the Moo crew has literally no power when compared to the Drew crew
please bring back the Drew crew I must return to my comrades I don't know about
that I I think I'm a Moo crew guy if I had to pick the car I just love the
cows like all right hold on let's let's go over let's go over the evidence here
Nancy Drew brilliant detective can solve children's slider puzzles with ease
mystery okay danger excitement all right cool right new crew Murius pros rocks
at people all right eats trees and rocks too eats people okay does a really cute
dance and can do a split and points and says oh has shipped 54 times on camera
oh this is tough I'm gonna have to go book group it's tough it's hard to pick
it really is all right let's get the let's get the credits to roll here that
doesn't mean the drew crew is never gonna show up again I have I still own a
bunch of those games it's not like it's not gonna happen anymore he does get us
people don't think I do we're way more similar than you think I mean that
becomes all the subs shitload of community subs tonight as well as just
people subbing in general thank you guys you still have some bits to do about six
or so let's see just about I also want to touch upon the fact that after Hank
cheesecakes four dollars here people were just giving 25 cents and saying
free us free us free us this person's poop this person says egg this person
says free us I had I had to like quell it I had to chaos lizard amiibo thanks
to the 300 bits lizard amiibo actually had a dream a couple months ago that I
was back in high school and you were one of my teachers he taught a class about
streaming or something but you refused to talk to any of us you kind of just
sat there and none of us said anything the whole time you kept tripping people
as they left the room at the end of the period worst class I've ever been and I
hope you were fired it was great to see Murius again I missed him and his antics
stripping kids as they leave in class what is wrong with me in your dreams I'm
such a psycho peaceful Haley thanks to the 250 hey when I was streaming the
other day some reason AI dungeon wanted to call you jerk ma and generated this I
heard you like listening to farting and screaming you look down at jerk ma who
has been silent for a while he suddenly gasps as you suddenly begin farting into
his ear it smells terrible but it tastes worse they stopped doing that he says
with disgusted stinks holy shit that's insane you didn't feed it that info oh
I should be way more disgusted than I am that's fucked up that's messed up I'm
gonna do New Year's resolution I'm gonna stop saying the upward as much as I do
that's hard for me all right but thank you Haley that's insane boy key thanks
for the five dollars hey Jeremy I've been doing some backlogging through the
Vaude and found myself screaming at you through the screen especially during
Nancy Drew that being said fuck the mood crew when's the next Drew crew stream so
I can yell at you and chat I'm captain of the mood crew and I don't appreciate
that at all Nancy Drew doesn't fucking eat rocks so what
Nancy Drew let me okay I'm gonna say this one more time Nancy Drew does not
eat rocks and throw up and kick houses the choice is obvious soon though
whenever this whenever I have no what no it's not it's not gonna be soon there's
a plan for every single day that I turn the stream on we're going to GameCube
soon I got chibi-robo gotcha force Mario sunshine we gotta do this like but I
have Wii games no more heroes to Mega Man Legends I got the Riddick games
cooking mama all of them this all the raving all the Rabbids games did guys
it's never gonna end yeah gotcha force is one of my most look forward to games
to stream since I started streaming that's a bold statement I know holy fuck
what did you just say yeah gotcha force you guys you guys don't know what this
is this is gonna be the most pog stream in the last probably two years it's
yep it's one of those games I doubt that yeah me too but I can hype up a stream
can I what about the carnival stream no no video like purely video game stream
purely video gaming like I stream a video game there's a way to see you
collect these little robots and you make a team of robots you fight other robot
teams and they you could they come out of boxes you guys gonna love it there's
boxes you open you have to pay any money you guys gonna love it hey Esquilo
thanks for the 250 hey jerk mom why is every call me jerk mom sometimes I make
edits of your face and I'd like to send your germ mom edit let's see what it is
it's very this is very scary let's put it on screen to scare everybody else it's
pretty scary also I lost there it is I was big thanks for being such a good
person and reminding me of my brother you have this aura and for supporting the
LGBTQ plus community please visit subs discord chat once in a while shout out
to Haley stream and subs yeah I've made that clear before that I have my full
support I'm open to everybody I don't give a shit who the fuck you are I don't
care at all I care about people hanging out here and getting along and having a
good fucking time that's it I don't give a shit about anything else I really did
that is my priority is whoever you are whatever walk of life whoever you are we
can just hang out and fucking watch a cow throw rocks at people that's it you
don't have a barrier here I what barrier would I make or what I don't want to tell
if somebody but what why would I have a barrier what do I want certain people to
not watch my twitch channel doesn't make any sense I want anybody to enjoy this
channel no that's not what I said oh they say it wrong what if we don't have
internet just no I'm not gonna that was a bad would've been weird if I just said
that but no we just have to be careful guys because and let's let's address it
now I've seen some of the fighting that happens in the chat it seems some of
this shit you know somebody will do like a trans pride emote for instance and all
of a sudden it's like okay well let's have a gigantic fight in the chat and
we're just let's just derail everything we're not even talking about the game
and people are just fucking screaming at each other that this this is this
stream is for us to have fun and hang out and have a good time people will do
that don't care about trans pride no I'm well aware I'm well aware of all look
there are people that see a trans pride emote and they just fucking say
something horrible and then that gets a reaction of people that are just like
it's an emote and then that starts a fight and then that starts a fight it's
like fuck you fuck you it's like whoa whoa whoa whoa that's this is not what
we're doing here this is not what we're doing here we are not gonna have fights
about people's identities and people's fucking preferences and and and gay
straight trans that doesn't matter to me it shouldn't matter to you but again I
would like I said previously we got to talk about spam we have to talk about
people just writing shit and writing whatever they want and then going forward
how I want to moderate the channel German nihilism no more messages and you
say this during a live stream as I'm doing it now can't ask for feet cam
anymore I just want everybody to fucking have a good time I don't like looking
over and seeing that this just people fighting in this community about this
shit and it's not even why is it people even fighting over this I think everybody
needs to fucking kind of internalize this in maybe pump the brakes a little you
should block trans pride if it's bothering you no no that that's not I
don't why would I I'm not gonna ban emotes that's just that's absurd I mean
no that's not feel like I joined at a bad time no what this we're just going
over and I've seen it I've seen it and I've tried to kind of change the
conversation a little bit try to get away from people arguing and chat about
this stuff but I do want to make it really clear that I would like us to
fucking be able to get along I don't want people to be down to each other's
throats when I'm like I'm like fucking throw like I said I'm gonna use this as
a perfect example because it's a great example if I'm throwing rocks at people
and like eating people on screen if I'm like surfing on a way I don't want to
it's it sucks to look over and see people fucking hate each other it's just
not it's it sucks it's not cool I don't like it that's not what this community
is for it's not why that's not what this community should stand for we're here to
have fun and enjoy each other's company full stop end of story now we're here to
make fun of you and there's a difference between banter and people
actually getting truly upset at each other us walking around back and forth
we do it all the time people that have problem with the emotes should be banned
because they bring negativity well also I mean there's I talked to some of the
mods about it and there's potential of people writing like for instance like
the trance pride emote a bunch of times specifically maybe to try to bait
somebody to be angry with them I think we've gotten there and that's what
that's what happens and then real people then start to get angry with each other
we do yeah we did discuss that yeah internet doesn't change that's what I'm
just saying we have to be careful because you don't you don't want to start
fucking screaming at somebody and the mods are we we haven't had we're
supposed to be doing another kind of state of the channel mod meeting I'm
sure if it's something guys the discord have seen us in the Archmages tower
sometimes you just see a bunch of names and I'm in there too we go over stuff we
talk about this stuff and we want to find out ways to make it so it's
enjoyable for everybody it's it is still called the Archmages tower I love how
much we still talk about so it's such a huge part of my entire life but
hopefully hopefully we can start to move on from that because I've made my stance
clear that I'm in full support I think over the years you guys have heard me
say it plenty of times don't want to see you guys fucking hating each other not
here not at all and not ever we got to get over this shit anyways kind of pack
that on to the conversation we had like 20 minutes ago acting like what movements
were a political well I'm not even talking about like it politics versus
not politics versus socially I'm just saying in general my main problem is
looking over here and see people actually really upset with each other
because this is new this is only within the last probably six months or so I've
been around for ten years this is new I've never really talked about this like
this in this kind of candid way so why I'm spending a little extra time on it
anyways we will continue the conversation that needed to happen yeah
it did it did and I'm actually glad that we could I could bring it up moving on
moving on goo berry juice thanks for the 300 bits bro that was a lot of fun I
just want to tell you how much I appreciate the work you put into your
streams you're constantly innovating and bringing your best effort to every
stream I just want to say that I love you as a person Jerma now wait this is
the wrong stream sorry pal I'm sure you're okay too maybe even if you are a
total himbo just kidding I was talking about you don't read this part he didn't
say my name but I put it in there anyways I have the power I read the
messages I can change it to whatever I want I can have it say anything I want
thank you for the gov three dollars goo berry juice gnarly thanks in 250 turn on
your fucking lights you look like a darkest dungeon highway man that's
pretty pog actually thanks Kiki Morris Sunday thanks for the I said your name
wrong you said that you were never gonna give money ever again if I said it wrong
again I'm sorry you sure did you keep him Morris Sunday fuck soiled it thanks
to the five dollars oh I'm doing the finger bite anyways read my red my
imagine I've been trying to make you read this on stream for like a month it's
okay you can't pronounce my username okay bye and this says German will never
move to Philadelphia and just happen to be not only in the same apartment
complex as mine but right next to door and I introduced myself by giving him
cookies and he's like the fuck are these I don't eat sugar all the time like you
do fatty and he slaps a plate out of my hands what what what was this so
important why do they need to read that well I don't know why that's so
important it just is all right well thank you for the five dollars it Kiko
second part of your name thank you though seriously sorry for fucking up
your name every time all the swag thanks for this five dollars if you
thought about doing a test stream with stricter rules to see how it feels it's
so tough for me I just want it's hard yes I have absolutely sure do a test
stream on master of comedy people are gonna be worse I think that initially
something like that would be bad for a while but then people would just get
used to it and that's just that's just your chat after a while but the problem
is and here's the real problem I've been doing this for so long with the same
kind of rules for six straight years that that's a big change because I've
been doing it for so long if I just started streaming six months ago that's
different but we've had the same kind of rules for a long time so has it been six
years I started streaming on twitch my channel got partnered in like 2014 or
2015 I've been streaming on twitch since like 2014 or so 2015 he's like
that's when I got partnered we need more mods maybe we'll do like a fucking big
mod maybe I was gonna do a lot of apocalypse before maybe we need to do a
mod knighting ceremony mod lottery thermostyle is to have mods snipe out
the trolls but it's hard with such a big audience yeah I do not take this lightly
at all and I know people going well man you stand you've been a real long
fucking time on this it means a lot to me because I want people to enjoy this
stream I want you to be able to shitpost I want you to be able to fucking say the
things you want to say and have fun but you know I got a fucking reel it in
that's just that's it but we have one more here well no two more actually
Avery drop dead thanks to the 250 German if you could read this privately it
appreciated okay we'll do thank you for the 250 thank you everything is being
looked at and talked about so don't worry thank you finally uber morph point
thanks for the $15 1500 bits I sincerely appreciate your will to stomp out
negativity in your community so many content creators let those parts fester
and become worse I think I think the word like stomp out negativity is I mean not
necessarily correct because I don't want look if you tell somebody that they're
stupid and they're wrong and they're an idiot you bet you that you'd make that
person fucking even more angry and hateful you know I'm saying it's hard
trying to you know push people in a more positive direction but without
telling them like wow you are sure are a fucking idiot like oh yeah I'm a
fucking idiot huh you're a fucking idiot it's tricky nice political debate some
people just some some people and some people are just playing out to cause
chaos yeah I know that's why it's so tricky because like stomping out
negativity is like what if the negativity is coming from a place of
somebody just trying to make a problem because they haven't but that's what
they're doing for fun then you have like two potential negativity sources that
are coming at each other it's just just riling shit up yeah haha who would do
that you can't act like both sides are equally at fault no absolutely not like
if you're like a bigot or like a racist and shit like like yeah you shouldn't
fucking be like that like don't you don't be like that that's not that's
not good that's really not fucking good but it's sometimes not that easy to
simply just say those things because the person listening might not give a shit
about anything you're saying it's actually really tricky you ended racism
CEO of racism oh my god I was here all right all right you did it all right we
did it god but this stuff is hard to talk about because when I turn my streams
on I don't I don't turn my stream on with the idea of well you know I'm gonna
talk about a bunch of issues today let me talk about all the bad shit in the
world I mean that's not what I'm doing here that's not the point of this stream
it never has and it never will be but sometimes we can you know somewhere when
I feel comfortable doing it you know we talk about it like we're doing right
now stop to talk about it I've lost somebody wink points trying to get him
to read please say it again when there isn't what's not the end of the stream
most people who need to hear this message already left he's bullying me
what I didn't what I just read it it really bothers me that no matter how
long this ending sequence is popcorns never cleaned I just want to watch funny
man play video game and not have to see you deal with spam we're working on it
and we're it's it's a hard to it's hard to do that's not don't think I don't
think about this all the time I do and I'm gonna be completely upfront and
this this is not something that has been really in the back of my mind it's this
is not like a we got a fucking talk chat it's just recently there's been some
fighting and I'd like to see it stop I turn on my stream and I just let's go
have some fun make more t-shirts you got it you're gonna lower wink prices in the
final day thank you for thank you for spoiling is all the people that are
saving up for links you'll get to use them it's gonna be wild all right I'll
see you guys later see you guys tomorrow take care of yourselves see you tomorrow
goodbye good night it's been fun it's been real you're gonna break his eye no
I'm gonna I'm gonna have eye drops that's the joke shh don't tell anybody
I'm gonna put eye drops in like every fucking 20 minutes don't tell anybody
that's a funny joke I want I don't want you to say that to anybody why did I
just try to go to facebook.com I that was weird I did I took an FACE I oh
okay who are we raiding we're raiding who's he's screaming Raid Jonah Hill
he's though all right we got Vinnie and Joel Vinnie and Joel Vinnie Joel Vinnie
Joel mmm Vinnie Joel Vinnie Joel fuck which button which button do I press
um I like them both they both fucking awesome they're both hilarious great
people who do I you did Joel last time oh oh Joel ruined halo that's right no
but he's a great guy oh of a coin all right I have a bottle cap if the bottle
cap lands ridge side up we're going to Vinnie we're going to Vinnie I mean rigged
oh you can't see the coin all right fine here here hey come on if we got I know
you hey hey hey your webcam is a little full your webcams a little dark it's I
have to turn up the exposure hold on all right here we go ready if the bottle cap
is facing up like this like ridges pointing up going to Vinnie cap up cap
side up going to Joel you ready I fucked hold on do it again not hold on that
wasn't in your eye what is it no oh my god dude what what what what rigged I
do I don't have a coin all right whatever it whatever it is in my hand
right now you saw it go in there Joel was that Joel was that Joel of any Vinnie
all right we're going to Vinnie what you guys just like split in half nothing
changes all right good night guys see you guys tomorrow for more various and
friends I mean I didn't miss the wink I did it I'll say hello good night guys
see you tomorrow 2 p.m. Pacific good night bye have fun
was burped really loud bye