Hello. Let me quit this game. I need to change the title to Last Hero of Nostalgia.
So I do nostalgia and then like comma bat chest. Is that good? Is that, is that, nah.
Last Hero of Nostalgia. How about, no, I don't want to encourage bat chests unless I say it.
How about nostalgia? Let's game. Whatever, I don't care. Nostalgia. Let's game. Who gives a shit.
That's arguably worse than the bat chest title. Okay, just give me two seconds. Yeah, sponsor's
over. I'm probably going to keep playing that game. That was really fun. All right. What was
the last thing I did here? Hold on. Hold on. Okay. Okay. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
There it is. There you go. You can have it for a little longer. Just for a little bit longer.
All right. Now I have to do the fun thing called it. The buttons are completely different in this
game. So it's not X, Y. It's R1, R2. This is going to mess me up. If I lose in the first 10 minutes,
it doesn't count. Yeah, you can take the timer off for the sponsor. Oh, I should probably take
up though. Let me do this real quick too. Hold on. Let me just take the panel out. Give me one
second. I'm glad I'm doing this now because the last time I did a sponsor, I believe, I wonder,
I think it was Gotham Knights. I left the panel there I think for like three weeks. It was kind
of ridiculous. All right. There we go. It should be good to go. Yep. Let's begin. Base came in the
bottom right. Probably a good idea. All right. Let's keep going. If you don't know what this
game is, this game is Last Hero Nostalgia. It's like a parody Dark Souls game. It's very good.
It's very good. Almost surprisingly so. We're all really into it. Watch this. All right. What
was the last thing? I was going to go up, right? There's like two ways to go. I forget where I was
going. And remember, I know it was literally yesterday, but you know what I mean? Like it's
processing info can be difficult sometimes. Wasn't it? Was it a big theater room? I feel
like it's this way. I think this is right. Oh my God. Oh my God. Yeah. I got to get used to
the controls. I told you that one didn't count. I pressed it. I pressed X. That one doesn't count.
That one doesn't count. I have to read. I'm not throwing for content. I've got to learn.
It's R1, R2. You understand? Tell that to the judge. I'm documented here. I'm documented.
Okay. Let me just run around for a sec. I think it's this. Yep. Okay. This is where I want to go,
I think. Is it? I genuinely don't remember. No. Like in my brain right now is Wild Hearts. And
I'm like, oh, that area with the coral. It's like, this is a, this is a, this is, this game
is not in my brain right now. Like where the hell am I? Never happened to you guys when you just
play a game and you just like leave it and you leave it in a spot. You know, here's the problem.
I left it in a spot that wasn't like right at a boss door. So like I'm still in this area,
but I like to have no idea where I am. Anybody else happen to happen to you? Like if I was in
front of a boss door, it's like, oh, okay. Right. Here we are. Once I get it, I'll get it. So many
things to burn into memory because it's down here. I remember this because this is where the
wizard guy was. And then through here and then through here, I remember finding the pot head
person. And I think that was where it ended. I think because then this leads, I don't know.
No, this guy, this goes back down to that other area. What about over here? I don't think I've
gone. No, I have not gone this way. All right. Perfect. Let's go. Welcome to the stream. Oh,
this is, this really is like the whole game is connected. Okay. So now I can be here. Any
memories? All right. So that's a shortcut to get back here. I swear to God, there was a place I
could go up. Stivity row. There's a boss here and I need help in there. Like, should I go up all the
way? Cause that's the, let me go up. You look mad. No, it's a little confused. I don't want to say
I'm angry. I just don't remember this one door that I, I remember I walked by it like five times
before here. No, does anybody like remember? No, no. Top of the tower. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
It's here. It's right here. It's right here. All right. So I go down here. Yep. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Cause then I go down here and I can walk
up another side. Don't even please. I'll never get back here again. Please do not kill me.
All right. Here it is. Right. And then it was right out the fucking door. All right. Everybody
relax. Everybody just chill. It was literally right next to us. It was right next to us the
whole time. I come, I forgot I opened this door. Everybody just chill out. Everything's good.
Now we just sit down. I'm doing a luck build. If you didn't know. All right. There we go. Right,
right, right, right. And then this goes down here. We don't touch this. We come out this way.
And we look over here and then we turn around and we go back down and then we go up and then
we go up. No, I didn't press it again. Whatever. Give me some fucking water. And then we go down
and then we go up. Here it is. It just took a few minutes to get back into the swing of things.
Yeah. And then we go down the elevator. Evil. What do you want? You want, get away from me.
Get away from me. Get away from me. Big hit. Me crit. Dude, you healed this BM. Don't you know?
Okay. What did that do? This dude's spamming projectiles. Hey, I'm playing to win. And now
we go down the elevator. I actually think we don't. Where do I actually go? I thought that
was the progress route. It's not maybe this way. I don't know. Yeah. Cause this is back here.
I've been here before. Watch the VOD. I mean, I thought going up there was progress. It's not
through the bucket headway. You went into the staff rooms last time. Um, so that was,
wasn't that behind the wizard room with the old man? I was just in there though. I gotta go back
into the... I just wish I wasn't so fucking confused right now. I could go down here.
I don't think that helps though. It is a very big map. It actually is. Where is game progress
though? And how do I get there quickly? Just jump it. Now that, that's like the two zones ago.
Cause going down past the wizard guy was where that pothead was. And I went through there and
that just is a shortcut back to one of the first areas. I have no idea where I'm supposed to go.
There was a flickering door in the very first area. I don't know. I would imagine it would have
been here. Maybe back in the... God, I don't know. It was the boss that you said you'd save later.
Yeah. That's what I thought we were doing. I thought, oh, I'm going to go up these stairs.
There's the boss. And then we keep going. But that was not what happened. Now I don't know
what to do. It's going to start over. Cause like, this is the shortcut to go down here,
which I was already here. Maybe, maybe it is this way. I don't know. That's where I came in.
Say please and I'll tell you please. In here, I went down there. That's just a shortcut. Can
I go anywhere else behind? I know I'm just monologuing the entire thing I'm doing,
but I'm trying to process where the hell I am. Okay. This is where the wizard was. This just
goes back to the second area. Where the hell am I? That left door? The left door is a shortcut.
This goes back down to that, isn't it? Cause this comes up here. We were up here before.
This is the quest reward place. I don't think this is right. I remember this. This is it. How
did I get so turned around then? Didn't I leave, didn't I leave this area that goes down to the
depths? Oh, hello. Wow. These vaults once held rewards for our heroes. Having restored our good
king, a hero returned to a procession and, uh, and play honoring their deeds. We would give them our
most beautiful crafts, not for fighting, just tokens of our adoration, our veneration. Of course,
their story wasn't yet over then. There was still the kidnapping during the festivities. Oh,
good times. Still don't master Smith. Right there. Hit him. But I might be able to try some more
complex enhancements. More complex enhancements. All right. Am I, am I doing the cane? Yes or no?
Cane? Yes or no? Is that stupid? I don't have any other weapons to really try.
I'm all right for now. Whoa. What does this do? Two, one, 99 to plus 182.
648. What is this doing? This is fucking crazy. Is it scaling with decks more? I mean, I feel like
I'm just going to have to do this. I'm doing it. I can't see anything. Thank you for giving me a
purpose. Is it worse? I don't know. I think that's better. 281. It was not 281 before. All right.
Cool. Thank you. I remember this. Let's fight this. Let's see how much more damage. That's
fucking ridiculous. That is ridiculous. That's like, I just cut him for almost this entire health
pool. That was epic. Goodbye. Clean it up. Yep. There's the fridge. Oh, no. Attack him from behind.
Hurry up. That's a lot of fucking people. My computer just almost crashed. I killed them
so bad that my computer almost broke. Yeah. Oh, yep. Yep. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. I remember this then through here. This is where I stopped streaming. Okay.
All right. Nice. Yes. Everything is good to go. This is exactly. I remember stopping. I'm going to
stop right here. Always stop before a boss. Don't ever stop in the middle of a fight. Pull it up.
Oh my God. I got stuck. You guys are on the same team. Oh, fuck. This is bad. Hello? Coward strat.
It just has to work. It just has to work. Look, if you and I did the same thing and you died there
and I won, I continue to play. You have to start over. I hope it's worth it. Crucible.
And I can remember it. I just want to look at it. Strength, unfortunately. So that's not going to
work. But I am going to. Should I just remember everything? Why not? Right. It's 3000. That's 3k.
It's not worth it. No, it's not worth it. I'm not going to use it. So this thing is really cool,
though. Finally, progress. NPC city. Leisure Lake. Can't get in there. Stivity row. No. Kitchen.
Who's your favorite Ice Age character? I'm personally quite partial to Scrat. Um,
what's the tiger's name? Not that one. What's the mammoth's name? Manny. This is kind of creepy.
The kitchen. Wait. OK, there we go. Uh, I can level up. Am I just, am I actually just going
full on just luck build? Is that stupid? Well, definitely get that. What's the new ability?
Stamina recovery when low. Keep memory on death is kind of hysterical. Not bad. Oh,
it is worth remembering because you, the more that you remember, the more shit you unlock. Yeah,
that's worth doing. No matter. Yeah, it is actually. Yeah, you get, uh, the upgrades.
It's cool. You can unlock the lore. Yeah. The one guy in chat that said it's worth doing.
We need to listen to that person more often. Irrelevant appendage. Another strength weapon.
Just an arm. OK, continue. So just a TLDR. Those that weren't here last night. The game has a
feature where you have to go to the place that the weapon remembers somewhere in the world or the
armor armor too. And you need to be aware of it. You should be checking it pretty frequently. Um,
the way the game is on, uh, PC is on Steam. The narrator had taken to scathing others in his
duress. Sudden forget it. What? Don't poop a pixel. I think that's kind of a bad thing.
Player housing. Approach the banquet table. Surely there was no hope. That's a crazy looking
castle. Curiosity, but void. Wow. Interesting. Damn, bro. That's crazy. Oh, it's our friend.
We've been doing this person's quest since we started, so I'm very curious. Hello. Together,
my friend, we shall mean that thing. What if he dies? Wait, um, yes, let's do it. Yes. Yes.
Let me get this item first and then we'll go. That's another trinket. All right. This is
definitely a boss. How many heels do I have? I got four. Four. Are you coming? Come and help me.
Wait, follow. Let's go. What's this deal? Statue this guy out in the first area.
Nom. Oh my goodness. That's a big combo. Give me a crit. All right. Back it up. Back it up. Back
it up. Don't be stupid. Oh, that. Ow. Oh my God. This guy is goofy. I'm dead. That was goofy. That
was really goofy. Just like them. I like this boss. What's your opinion on tums? Uh, don't
overdo it. Tums are a temporary solution to a potential deeper problem. And why am I? What am
I doing? Yeah, don't, don't abuse it. If you're having acid reflux, if you're having lots of like
GERD problems, uh, you definitely should probably look into it and not just like pop tums, tums,
tums, tums, tums every day. There's some medication that can help that stuff. There's also
lifestyle changes. Like it might be some food that you're eating. I'm not a doctor. I'm not a
doctor. So I don't know. If we talked to a doctor, they would probably be better than me. All right.
Let's go together. My friend has, I thought he was a doctor. Oh shit. That's why I'm here.
All right. This, this guy's hard. Oh, all right. He's going to go dance. Free hits, free hits,
dance, dancing, dancing. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Oh, is a clone.
This music is fucking crazy. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
bro. I ain't even looking anymore. See you later. Nice fight. Tom's dancing pole. And what else?
That was something else. You're wicked lame. I completed the encounter. Did you see that?
Did you see that? I went swoosh slash stab at a stab at a stab.
Echo.
I am the greatest. We are.
Nice job.
We're awesome. We're awesome.
Thanks for the help. Okay. I got a couple of things I want to look at. Oh, strength. I forgot
to blink. Decreases stamina usage. What did I pick up? It was like a red annoying enemy ahead,
but try quick attacks. I went the wrong way. That was the boss room. Warning. Classic David.
Oh, David. Come on, David. Get it together.
The narrator felt nostalgia cascaded over the narrator.
Oh, that was kind of funny. Oh, it's a I can another blast. Any memories?
Path of the Good Monarch. You carry one relic that can be remembered ahead.
I like this zone. This lady just attacked me. What's your deal?
Put down my art, please.
R1, R1, R1, R1.
You might have taken this as an opportunity to dispatch me.
True.
Perhaps I misjudged you originally. I am. Well, you may call me.
My name has no meaning. Call me Vengeance.
I watched you approach the consumer's banquet. You read Nostalgair of his gluttony.
By chance, our paths are aligned.
Across this canyon lies the keep of the stolen crown.
A great one has usurped its throne.
I will purge this kingdom of all that strangle it.
Can I have your weapon?
Though I do not recognize your story, I do know your make.
You were one of them, yet also somehow less than them.
And I suspect in some way even less than me.
You all thought I was going to do it?
I mean, none of this is an insult.
Your peculiarity may be the thing that saves you from their fate.
Hey, dude. Little Caesar's pretzel crust is back.
Are you kidding me, dude?
I wish you well on your quest, so long as it is true.
Should you falter?
I will kill you.
Not before I kill you first.
We already had an encounter, and I distinctly remember winning that one.
I will kill you while you stand,
except you kicked the ever-living shit out of me 10 minutes ago.
It wasn't even a contest.
You kicked the shit out of me.
But I will kill you if you screw this up at all.
I'm watching you.
Is there anything else I can do over there?
Nope.
All right, goodbye.
Why did he add, hey, dude, to that random pizza crust message?
I don't know, because I...
All right.
I read it, and then I process it, and then the chat is moving so fast sometimes.
That I have to repurpose it, and it's kind of...
It's like, hey, it's gone.
Okay, let me repurpose it and get the gist of what that person was saying.
Suddenly, and for no reason at all, and without implying any third-party emotional investment,
hope bridged the divide.
Wait, that was a clue.
It was a clue.
The blue shell.
A carapace from a road-crossing beast that could knock a carriage off its course.
The narrator was the most exuberant cheerleader in all of Nastal Gaia.
His belief in the institution of heroism was unwavering.
To conduct the hero's journey and articulate its wonder,
the narrator wielded his immense power over Source.
Nobody thought much about Source back then, where it came from or what it was.
Magic was simply accepted as part of the code of existence.
After the degradation began,
some who were never meant to access Source began harnessing it through unconventional means.
At first, the narrator tried to believe that this was...
This too was part of a greater plan.
This forbidden use...
Everything is fucked up, and it was called a glitch.
But how good is it?
I'm about to just put that in my main hand.
No, I can't.
70%?
32?
Oh, it's a magic defense shield.
Might need it later.
You look like Freddy Fazbear.
What are you gonna say now?
Warlock's Wilds.
I need a bonfire.
Nope.
It's this guy.
I don't think I want to unburden anything.
I could unburden the...
That's not worth it.
I don't care.
Stop.
Stop, Jerma.
Right?
There it is.
Yep.
I...
There it is.
Stop, stop, stop.
Keep the non an NPC.
Smile while they hit you.
All right.
Hold on.
Was it her?
It's probably another shortcut.
Oh, it's...
No.
Okay.
I thought I pulled it.
I looked over at chat.
God.
I don't want to die down here.
I was in another area.
Blade the Bold's withered icon.
Oh, shit.
That's another flask.
Somebody asked a long time ago if I recommend this game.
The answer is absolutely yes.
Good game design ahead.
Let's find out.
Okay.
So it's through this gate.
Nice.
This game seems way more fleshed out than it needs to be.
It's really surprising.
I thought this...
I honestly thought this was going to split it like a joke.
I mean, the game is a parody kind of gaming and Dark Souls and whatever, right?
But on its own, it's very, very fun.
20 health, probably?
Yeah.
I have a lot of crunchies that I have not used, don't I?
I do.
I don't think this is going to get me there.
What do I need?
8,000?
9,000?
Six.
Okay.
Yeah.
Get health to 20 and then I'm going to move on.
But are you made of breadsticks?
Have I got any new gear?
I think it's time for some change of clothes.
This is 1710.
I like that bat roll.
Never mind.
Bat roll.
The shiny is fine.
I'd like to upgrade it.
I'd like to find the remembrance, whatever it is.
All right.
Let's move.
Somebody said, what was more painful, Jump King or Millennia?
I...
Jump King was sustained horror.
Millennia was bursts of horror.
I don't know.
Because one is extreme, vast, awful horror.
And the other one is just like a slow drip of just pain and suffering.
One happens really quickly and the other one is...
I don't know.
They're both bad.
But goddamn, they're fun.
I will never play the Jump King DLC.
No.
Never.
Ever.
That is one thing I can guarantee you I would never do.
It's never going to happen.
I watched the pain and suffering of people playing through the DLC.
Just like, no.
New tether.
Nothing glowing.
Stick to the path.
Danger ahead.
Step carefully.
Tell me what the fuck to do.
Tale of Luck.
What's that?
It's a different weapon upgrade.
There's a lot of weapon upgrade material.
I feel like there's only three types of weapons.
And we've seen like more than three upgrade materials.
Oh shit.
Why did that...
I...
I scared the shit out of me.
I guess I wasn't expecting the light to light his face up.
What had come over the sensible narrator?
Rather than chronicle the protagonist, more and more he talked of himself.
It's a little secret.
Britney Clarkson.
Britney Clarkson?
Who is Britney Clarkson?
Am I fat rolling?
What happened?
Britney Clarkson.
Anti-hero finger wagglers?
These are oven mitts.
All right, the drip is getting kind of good.
The narrator's fate was tied to Nostalgia's.
Or perhaps, even were he himself unstrung,
his affection for Nostalgia could never be severed.
Why am I here in footsteps?
Running away.
Shut up.
All right, well that was annoying.
You know, I didn't know if they were going to put a poison swamp in the game,
but of course they would.
It has to be authentic.
You just fucking...
You just...
You just snuck up on me.
You're just running away?
Bro, they're in the cardboard.
I don't have any healing.
That rabbit is going to jump out.
You little fucker.
Are you real?
What is that?
I hate this.
I'm...
This is fucking scary as hell.
It's 1030 Pacific.
I can't be screaming like this.
It's way too late to be screaming like this.
So I went a weird way though.
Maybe I'm going to go right down.
All right, let me check.
This whole area is a Zelda reference.
Yeah, it is, isn't it?
I wonder what being a caster like is in the game.
I wonder what being a caster is like in this game.
I said that's weird.
So what if service?
This is Dex Source.
This is the...
That's the Zelda sword, right?
It probably goes...
It probably has a projectile.
Well, it's not the character I'm making.
Broken of a youthful operation.
I think I just have to use it.
Okay.
But will you get...
Get out of here.
What did you all...
Oh my god.
Stop.
Oh, that's lucky.
Full stamina.
Will you stop this?
Will you just fight me?
Get over here.
So what did that do for me?
Okay, so it's lit up.
Do I have to light three of them probably?
I bet you I have to light three.
Although this is lit up a little better.
Is it gonna hurt?
Checking.
Just checking.
A lot of money.
My first stream in a long time,
I usually watch VODs.
Welcome to the stream.
Hey, what's up?
We have a lot of respect for the VOD watchers here.
The YouTube video watchers.
I know that not everybody can watch every stream,
which you never expected to either.
Whenever you catch one, you catch one.
That's it.
All right, this time I went over there and it was bad,
but I have to get the aggro.
Which one is it?
It's you.
All right, yeah.
So you got to turn on the beacon
and that gets rid of the poison.
It's a good mechanic.
Don't you even...
Did you turn to the tree?
Thank you.
No.
This weapon stinks.
Although it isn't upgraded at all, is it?
Save me mask?
All right, that's creepy, but whatever.
Keep it.
I don't...
There's no memory on this.
So I don't think I can unburden the memory.
Nothing.
This is where I died.
I forgot about you.
Honestly, the luck actually is working out pretty well.
Those crits are awesome.
There's the Zelda shield.
Oh, it's a hold.
Oh, I can just walk through it.
I feel like this would have a memory here.
Don't you think so?
Let's see.
Memory's location is known by a relic
whose memory lingers in Warlock's wild.
So that's where we are.
Nothing yet.
Maybe where you get the sword.
This is where I started.
What's the point of going all the way back?
Shortcut for what, though?
I guess...
No, that's not...
Really not that far.
Very close.
I guess I could sit down and level up
and get some flasks.
Can you please explain why you hit the pink guy every time?
I don't know.
Can you please address the Botox allegations?
I don't...
No, I refuse.
All right.
I've got enough.
Why do you hit the pink guy every time?
Why do you do that?
I don't...
Stop hitting the pink guy.
Here we go.
All right.
So where the heck am I supposed to go?
Oh, fuck.
I forgot you were respawned.
Oh, up here.
Two.
Oh, my goodness.
All right.
Is that all coming up here?
I think there's one more.
Ooh, not up here.
You know, I would deal with it,
but I don't give a rat's behind.
I don't give a rat's behind about that.
About fighting that person.
Oh, no, Chris.
Game is broken.
I got a lot.
Wait, another upgrade material?
I don't give a rat's behind.
And I know people are going to be like,
I can't believe you're saying this right now.
But I don't give a gosh darn.
OK?
Everybody knows me as the...
I don't say anything bad or anything.
But you know, I don't give a rat's behind.
Calm down.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Let me let loose.
Let me let loose sometimes.
Low state.
I actually like this area.
It's fun.
I have the other coin.
Ooh, what's that?
Another shortcut?
OK, wait, let me unlock this first.
You make pigeon noises in your sleep.
Oh.
What are you talking about?
Like, oh, look at that.
Level up.
There's the 20 vitality.
Now I'm going to go dex and luck and nothing else.
Get luck to 40.
My mom said my friend on the screen has to apologize.
I don't really know you.
Don't lie to your mother.
Don't lie to your mother like that.
You need to tell your mother the truth.
You're watching a television show and it shouldn't be.
Did he get up tomorrow?
He said you have to.
Yeah, it's Saturday tomorrow.
Wait, is it like 4 AM for you?
I tried to double it.
Ooh.
All right, I want to go this way.
Are we going to get poisoned?
Fire.
Oh, yeah.
I am on fire.
I look forward.
Hold on.
We can't talk yet.
Stop it.
Ooh, that thing looks cool.
What is that thing?
Because I want it.
I hope it's not a strength.
It's a cake pop.
And I can't use it.
I can't use the cake pop.
That makes me sad.
The TF2 update thing.
That was kind of out of nowhere, wasn't it?
I wonder if they're actually going to go through
with making an actual update.
Are you a doubter?
I don't know if the word is doubter.
It's just the game's been out for so long.
It would actually be really surprising if they were like,
you know, let's start the dev engine back up again
and make a bunch of new stuff.
It would be kind of...
They edited the post,
and it's now a holiday-sized update.
They had to clarify it.
It's a holiday size.
It's over, man.
Well, I don't know.
Hold on, though.
Just we'll see.
The reason why I didn't bring it up
is I didn't want to get excited about it.
We don't know.
It might be good.
It might be crap.
It's got to let them cook.
Oh, fuck.
I did this.
This is bad.
I'm dead.
I thought I could make it up or something.
Quit trying to fit in.
I don't even care.
We all die at some point.
Where's the elevator?
They go 6,000 souls.
Bring back the cool Jerma.
Bring back cool Jerma.
Fall asleep on stream.
No, I don't think so.
What was your favorite arc?
Somebody said.
You know, I thought about this recently.
The amount of time that I've been kind of on
like YouTube and Twitch and everything.
I don't think I could tell you.
I think I have fond memories of the whole time I've been here.
So I don't think I could really tell you.
I don't have a favorite arc.
So many shortcuts.
What is going on here?
What the hell is this?
My face.
How did I hit my mouth on that wood?
I hit like my two front teeth on that.
Avoid down.
Yeah, but you never know when people are just talking shit.
Could be made up.
Is game actually good?
It is actually good.
I'm promising you it is.
All right, so let's keep going the right way.
Somebody relics here that I can identify.
Nothing.
Wait, this is new.
Oh, I want to put that on.
Oh, scarecrow.
All right, keep going.
Please.
I'm just getting greedy now.
Are you real?
Yes.
Don't even.
I actually need more stamina.
I'm running out a lot more frequently now.
Yep.
Bullshit.
Girl, why do you look like that?
You know, you're the probably 700 millionth person to say that.
How dare you?
Man, but you answer all those times.
How dare you say that?
Bringing up how I answer that question.
How dare you ban that person?
How dare they?
How dare you step into a conversation that I was just having with somebody
and say how dare you for me?
How dare you ban that person for five to ten minutes?
I think this is a maze.
It's a maze.
Is it a maze or am I just dumb?
I think I'm just going backwards.
Yep.
I probably have to drop the coins right and know where I've been.
All right.
Yeah, we're doing that right now.
I'm using these coins.
I got 34 of them.
Here we go.
Let's go.
I'm making sure I don't get lost.
For instance, I've been here.
I've been here.
This is not the right way.
I came up like a tunnel.
Where the hell did I even go?
Is this way?
I've been here.
Oh, you little dorks.
Who's doing this weird shit?
Stop.
I thought I had these.
Okay.
It's hard.
Keep going.
Blood.
All right.
I've been here.
This is where I've been here.
I'm not going down there again.
In there.
I've now been up here.
I've been right here.
I haven't been here.
I've been here.
Kind of cool.
Anything else scale with decks?
No, that's the only one I have.
You made my little brother cry
when you said rats behind.
Yeah, this is the new Jerma.
It's the new me.
Problem.
Dark Jerma.
Oh, look, it's our friend.
Hello.
I thought that was him still talking.
What?
No.
Well, yes.
I mean, it's yet to be proven.
Come now.
I thought that was you.
How dare you say how dare you in this game?
I'm fucking quitting this game
and uninstalling it.
They know each other.
My friend's heart to love a thing so much
to hold responsibility for that thing
and it'd be twisted beyond the tenderness
of your stewardship.
That's the goodness.
How dare you in due course,
you will confront the greatest of the great ones.
Someone has to.
Yes.
Well, I suppose I do like riddles.
A well spun riddle positions its maker
in the perfect position for what may come
obtuse enough to not be held liable
for the ensuing shenanigans,
but cryptic enough to suggest unquestionable wisdom.
More importantly, a riddle does not violate
the listener's own discovery.
Back to your quest.
Friends are rare in nostalgia.
I actually did not really mean to do that.
Whoops.
Okay.
So that's that.
I've been here.
And I've been here.
That thing is going to be,
you know what I mean?
I love this weapon.
The offhand sword just hits so hard.
Tale of luck.
Nothing is vibrating.
Oh, new bonfire.
How do I get over there?
Oh, nice.
Memory of a valiant hero.
Home of source, blank parchment.
I hear a anvil.
What's your taco bell order?
I need to know as soon as possible
or I'm fucked.
You're in the drive-through right now?
Shit, come on, man.
Can I help you?
Oh, um, hurry up.
Can I get two cheese or gordita crunches
and a large Baja blast
and one Doritos Locos taco?
There you go.
Saved.
Can I not open this door?
We have the same fucking order.
I think that's the only order at Taco Bell.
I don't, I think everything else is not worth ordering.
We're all going to have a very similar order
because that's the order.
Such a ridiculous gate.
Was there a humility implicit in its frame?
A humility so long ago forsaken.
Here it is.
I don't have a coin.
What?
What about a crunch wrap?
The issue with Taco Bell is...
All right, let's go over this.
During my tier list, I brought this up.
Taco Bell has 20 items on the menu.
They're all B minus.
They have one thing on the menu that is an S plus.
I don't...
If you have something on the menu that is S plus,
it's so hard for me to order the B minus items.
Even though they're okay, they're good.
They're not bad.
I enjoy them.
But the cheesy gordita crunch is...
If I'm going to go to Taco Bell,
I'm going to get cheesy gordita crunches.
Everything else is like two or three rungs down for me.
So it's like, oh man, I'm going to go to Taco Bell.
Oh, you know what?
Let me try one of the...
No, fuck that.
Cheesy gordita crunch, S plus.
No, what else?
It's hard to do that.
Because I don't go to Taco Bell.
Holly and I don't go to Taco Bell that often.
So when we do, it's like...
Should I get the chalupa?
No, no, no, of course not.
All right, let's go.
No dialogue?
You just did almost 400 plus damage.
I'm going to be a cheese ball.
I like the other stuff at Taco Bell.
It's just I didn't sit down at the bonfire.
Oh my God, help me.
God, maybe I should do stamina.
No, let's keep dex.
Let's get to like 25 dex.
What's the worst fast food restaurant?
I don't know.
I'm trying to think.
What is the worst fast food restaurant?
Huh?
There ain't supposed to be an anvil in the wilds.
Disguarded amidst so many tools of field and forge.
Who would do this?
My fingernails.
My fingernails are long.
Even those who hate your kind still got to work.
This wasn't just discarding some traditions.
It was a discarding of tradition itself.
BK.
I wonder what this anvil has helped forge.
Maybe I can replicate the feats.
Oops.
Yeah, I mean, I kind of gauge how much I like a restaurant based on how many.
Look, everyone goes, oh man, that fast food restaurant sucks.
But I gauge how high up on the list it is for me based on how often I go.
And I have not been to a Burger King in I think the last time I actually went to.
But before doing that Whopper thing that everybody seems to like,
um, before doing that, it was all the time that I ate two cheeseburgers.
Because I was getting a blood test and I was freaking out because I didn't eat all day.
And I ate two fucking, did I tell this story before?
I've told this story before.
No, I think I have.
I definitely have.
I haven't, I swear I have.
Whatever, I'll tell it real quick.
So, um, one time, this is, I mean, probably five years ago,
at least at least three or four years ago, something like that.
I had a doctor's appointment to go get blood work.
And I didn't eat all day.
And you know when you get your blood taken?
It's, I don't, I'm not afraid of needles or anything.
I'm not afraid of going to the doctor and like, oh, no, no, no, don't like, don't do that.
But if I haven't eaten at all, I like to be well fed because you can get a little,
I don't know, you can get kind of lightheaded sometimes if you don't for some reason.
Um, yeah, fasting before blood work and yeah, I'm not, I don't know.
But still, I get a little lightheaded sometimes.
But so I'm, I didn't eat all day.
And I was like, fuck, I, I gotta go, I'm going to the doctor's appointment.
I need to eat something.
I don't want to get like, they're taking all my blood out.
And then I'm like, oh, I'm like, I feel woozy or whatever.
You know, I feel a little weird.
So how long did you fast?
I just hadn't eaten.
I didn't, I don't think I had to fast for this blood work.
You don't have to, you don't have to fast for all of your blood work.
Only certain blood work you do.
So I didn't have to fast, but I was like, okay, I want to eat something.
So I went to Burger King was the only thing I could think of.
I was like, fuck what's like here right now.
And I just driving, driving, driving like, I, there's a Burger King right here.
Burger King.
It's like, I don't want Burger King, but whatever, I have to do this.
But my appointment was in like 20 minutes.
It was in like 15 minutes.
So I'm just like, fuck, all right, go to the drive-through.
I'm just going to get something small, nothing big.
And I want to like, overdo it.
I got two regular cheeseburgers, just two plain cheeseburgers from Burger King.
And I just ate them really fast.
And then I kept going to the doctor.
I got my blood taken.
I know I didn't eat that much.
So I got my blood taken.
I was like, everything's fine.
I feel good.
I feel all right.
And I hear back from the doctor, you know, like a week later.
Hey, I just want to talk to you really quickly about your cholesterol is a little high.
And I was like, oh shit.
And I'm sitting there thinking, is it the cheeseburgers?
Because I ate two cheeseburgers like 15 minutes before getting my blood taken.
So I said that.
I was like, oh, I had like two cheeseburgers like right before the blood test.
That's probably what it was, right?
And the doctor was just like, no, that's not what happened.
I thought that I had like cheeseburger blood before I went to get that blood test.
And I'm sitting there going, no fucking way.
I'm telling you, if I went to go take that test again, and I ate like spinach,
salmon, and a bunch of broccoli, it would have been lower.
That's what I really felt.
And there's the story.
I thought I had cheeseburger blood.
Oh, your cholesterol is a little bit high.
It's not too bad.
But you know, we really should probably try to get that brought down.
Oh, well, see, I ate two cheeseburgers.
So it's like, you fucking idiot.
I want to upgrade.
Ah, I need one more.
Shoot.
I got to find another weapon I like.
Now address the grilled cheese off the floor.
That's not real.
I made that up like 10 minutes before the stream.
I don't even remember the context of what we're talking about.
I don't even remember.
I was in pre-stream chat today and I said, oh, yeah, I ate a grilled cheese off the floor.
I don't know.
I thought it was funny for five seconds.
Guys, I'm almost 40.
As an almost 40-year-old man, you don't eat grilled cheese off the floor.
That just doesn't happen anymore.
I mean, maybe when I was like 10, maybe I dropped a grilled cheese on the ground.
He's almost 40.
Yeah, bro.
All right.
I need to play my video game now, please.
What age are you allowed to eat grilled cheese?
There's no, I'm just saying like if you're like a 10-year-old and you're like, oops,
I dropped my thing.
I don't care.
As a 40-year-old man, somebody has the log.
It's me and hey, dude, I heard you ate a grilled cheese once that fell on the floor.
Is this true?
And then I said, bro, fucking leave me alone.
That's what I said.
I feel like I should have an FAQ, but it would be 30 pages long.
There are too many questions, some not even based in reality.
Hey, dude, I heard you ate a grilled cheese once off the floor.
Is this true?
Bro, fucking leave me alone.
Of course it is true.
But I don't want to say it all the time.
But that was a joke reference or whatever.
You get it.
Somebody said, dude, you keep pretending that you're some normal
40-year-old, but you just talked about a story how you thought you had cheeseburger blood.
But that's like a funny story.
By the way, that was also like years ago.
That was not like yesterday.
I promise I am a functioning adult.
It was like three years.
It's years ago.
I didn't think.
I just like was a thought that crossed my mind.
You're concerned about cheeseburger blood as a 37-year-old.
Oh, we just have fun conversations sometimes.
It's not that deep.
I've been here.
You also told a story about drinking espresso on the toilet.
Yeah, but so what?
So what?
I'm living life a little, all right?
I'm living life a little.
We can't do that, apparently.
No, you can't drink an espresso on the toilet.
I'm living my life, all right?
You can live yours however you want.
I'm living my life.
Where am I going?
Why is this over here?
It's a dead end for no reason.
Yeah, I'm just I'm living my life.
Okay, this is this is progress here.
Yeah, I just I felt I sometimes I just feel like doing stuff.
I saw that you prop hunt mother butthead.
Where are you?
Yeah, I got hey, we got a motto on this channel called you do you.
If I want to drink an espresso on the toilet, I'm doing it.
And you know what?
I'm doing it tomorrow morning.
That sounds like a great idea.
You poured orange juice into a purse.
Yeah, I fuck around a lot.
I remember that.
Oh, demonic.
Look at this demonic shit.
And let me correct the record on this.
It was banana milk.
What are they sacrificing this?
Is that a kid?
Why am I killing this?
Why did I just kill that kid?
Oh, wait.
Interesting.
Hold on.
Really?
Come on.
Damn.
What I figured it would have been here.
You ever had vanilla ice cream with soy sauce?
No, I don't think I probably ever would probably.
I don't really like soy sauce that much.
I'm not a soy sauce fan.
I like soy sauce very, very rarely with sushi.
And that's pretty much it.
I like to dip the sushi into the soy sauce.
Take a tiny little bit of wasabi right on top.
Done.
Easy.
Spicy tuna roll like salmon roll or even like a good.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's probably the only way I eat sushi.
I love wasabi.
I love nasal heat, nasal heat.
It's what I like more than mouth heat.
I find mouth heat to be.
Did I get a coin?
I didn't get a coin yet.
Shit.
No, no, I did.
No, I did.
Do you miss Boston area Chinese food?
I miss a lot of Boston area food.
I guess not with Vinny.
Vegas food is phenomenal.
Some of the best sit down restaurants I've ever been to.
But a lot of those East Coast delis, sub shops, pizza places, Chinese food.
There's a lot of really, really, really good ones.
I miss the snow too.
I love Vegas.
It's kind of like both sort of completely different climates.
I love the sun shining.
It's super nice.
It's just it's always sunny outside.
Always.
It's just every time you wake up in Las Vegas, especially from.
I want to say it gets cold here.
It does get cold.
It gets to be somewhere in the mid 30s Fahrenheit.
But besides like a month or two of the winter, it is beautiful every single day.
Every day.
Because that's one of the things that I had an issue with in on the East Coast.
It felt like there were more rainy days.
There were more kind of just dreary days than there were sunny days.
And I felt like I really wanted to get in a different environment like that.
That was more sunshine.
And a lot of people don't like the heat out here because it can get to be in the Fahrenheit.
It does get to be somewhere in the 110 to 115, 120 Fahrenheit sometimes.
But I kind of like it.
I don't know why.
It's just so it's so ridiculous.
It's just so it's like an oven outside.
It's it's so something about it.
I don't know.
I like it.
It's just so much more different than anything I've ever experienced.
And it's not sweaty because it's a dry heat.
You got to be careful though because it's dry heat.
There is not very much humidity in Vegas or the whole state of Nevada.
So you don't sweat.
It's just hot.
I have been in really hot days in the Boston area.
85, 90, 95 degrees in the Boston area is awful.
I'm like soaking wet.
It's it's just humidity.
85 in Boston is not as bad.
That's not true.
90 in Boston is not as bad as 115 in Vegas.
I'm telling you this isn't.
Oh, stay with them.
Are we talking about humidity right now?
Now I humidity is Boston was kind of really got everything.
It got a bunch of snow.
It got a bunch of heat.
It got a bunch of fall weather.
Actually fall in Boston is like my favorite thing.
I think fall in Massachusetts is almost not comparable.
What's with this thing?
Is it weird?
Are you doing that?
I isn't going to poison me, isn't it?
I can't wait.
I'm out of coins.
Actual lizard.
You're the type to spend your day laying on a rock.
Hey, do not dog wizards.
I'm not wizards.
Don't talk about wizards like that.
Should I just tank it and run?
Or is that stupid?
Dude, is it stupid?
Should I tank it and just run?
How much further do I have to possibly go?
Dude, get off of.
No, I want to say yes.
Again, I bring the camera back.
Somebody.
Wait, somebody said they had a chicken sandwich because of me and they're pissed or something.
What happened?
How could I serve?
Why are you mad at me?
Let's go again.
Plus three.
This thing is deadly now.
It's deadly.
All right.
This is tower number three.
I need to find another coin.
I think the kids have the coin.
Oh, I'm still mad.
I got an original chicken sandwich because of you and it wasn't very good.
You have one from Burger King?
Long chicken sandwich.
Oh, I mean, it's that really my fault.
I don't the last time I really went to Burger King for real, real, for real.
I don't know.
It's probably 10, 15, I don't know, 10 years ago.
And I got a long chicken sandwich and I was like, yeah, that was all right.
A lot of here.
You know, Burger King could probably be really, really good.
And I would never know.
What is that?
Has anybody been there recently?
Okay.
Yeah.
How is it?
Is it fine?
Is it all right?
It's mid.
They have good French toast.
I don't know if I read that wrong, but that kind of makes me want to go.
Is that real?
French toast.
Burger King has French toast.
What dimension am I in?
How have I never heard of this?
I'm eating a double whopper right now and give us a rating out of 10.
How is it?
Two?
I don't think that's the same person.
That's dead space.
Hold on.
I need to look at that.
Seven out of 10.
I can put on the dead space gear.
That's funny.
It's fat rolling.
Unfortunately, this is strength.
But I feel like something is vibrating.
No, I could probably keep the helmet.
Chesapeake's probably too much.
Still fat rolling.
70% right?
71.
That works.
Oh, yep.
Token.
Okay.
Now where's tower four?
They gave it an eight out of 10.
The bacon double cheese XL is a 10 out of 10 is what they said.
Delicious.
We got a delicious.
Okay.
Bacon double cheese burger?
XL though.
That's a big ass burger.
How much bigger is the...
Why does it have like t-shirt sizes?
When did...
Is there like a small, medium, large XL, triple XL?
Why is it like a shirt?
That's a man-sized viewer.
All right.
Time to try to find where that fourth tower is.
I used to get the rodeo burger in mod chat.
VR Josh.
Yeah.
The rodeo burger was actually fantastic.
If you don't know, the rodeo burger at BK was a tie-in with small soldiers.
It was a movie.
That movie came out.
And that burger was attached to it.
It was probably the single best item they ever came up with.
It never left?
Why do I feel like it did?
It definitely did for a while.
I know it did because I remember it wasn't there.
Is this tower four?
No, it's tower three.
Well, I'm going to...
All right.
Pause this conversation for five seconds.
I need to find the right route.
I need to look and not look at chat.
Give me a minute.
I don't think it's this one.
Shit, I went down here already.
Where's my coins?
Game did that thing again where it minimized.
That was weird.
All right.
He's not looking.
Tell him he sucks.
I used them all.
Rodeo burger is definitely still around and it smacks.
I like it.
The reason the rodeo burger is great
kind of reminds me of my five guys order, which is...
Let me see if I get this right.
Rodeo burger is barbecue sauce, onion rings, and something else.
Barbecue sauce, onion rings, single patty.
What else is on it?
Is it bacon on it too?
No way.
It was tower three that you need to activate.
Oh, thank you.
I thought it was four.
Wait, the coins are numbered.
That's right.
I thought...
Yeah, I thought it didn't matter.
There's no cheese on it, right?
Please try the spicy honey chicken sandwich
with fried pickle chips from Wendy's.
Sounds like a lot, but I promise it's amazing.
I haven't been to Wendy's in a very long time.
Our meaning is gone.
Time arrived when you confront the final great one.
Could help you.
Oh, let's kill this person.
If first you could restore what has been lost.
Perhaps the spindles could prove a hero.
The narrator watched.
There's probably a remembrance thing here.
You hit so hard.
It's unbelievable how strong that was.
I'll get crit.
What do you got?
Translucent map.
Yeah.
Okay, there's...
Is it the...
No, not the shield.
Just the sword.
I want to put it on.
Damn it.
You're going to address the KFC mashed potato.
What are you talking about?
I love KFC, but I never go.
I have 21,000 souls.
Hold on.
KFC is good.
KFC falls into that same category for me, though,
of I never choose to go there,
but I will eat it and love it if you present it to me.
Like raisins.
Yeah, that's also pretty true.
Yeah.
I would eat a whole box of raisins right now
if it appeared in front of me.
Just boop.
They're right there.
I would eat the whole box,
but I'm never going to buy them.
I'll never purchase them.
All right, let's see what the boss is here.
Raisins are nice.
They're fine.
How do I get back down?
Let's drop.
I had some famous Elbertson egg salad for lunch.
Ooh, that's a good choice.
How do I get where I need to go?
This way?
Whoa.
I've only been able to use this one spell.
I wonder how the other ones are.
Oh, but I didn't even answer the question.
Somebody said, what's the worst fast food restaurant?
I don't, I don't think,
honestly, every bad fast food place in quotes,
there's a reason to eat there.
I know a lot of people,
oh, what about Jack in the Box?
Jack in the Box has these little tacos
and they are crack.
So it's probably, no,
but Sonic, the food is awful.
The food at Sonic is awful,
but all their drinks are so good
that I can't say that it sucks.
That would be not right.
I've eaten at Jack in the Box and gone,
that was pretty good with their little tacos.
I don't, I thought this was going to be
much simpler than I thought.
How do I get out of here?
What about White Castle?
I have never eaten at White Castle, truly.
I don't know if I've ever truly eaten that one.
Arby's, I've only eaten at Arby's
I think once in my life
and I didn't really like it.
So I haven't really given it that much of a chance.
I'm lost.
Ronald McDonald or the King?
Be honest, please.
It's not about the food.
Who's the better, oh, Ronald McDonald all day.
Ronald McDonald all day.
I don't even need to see who Ronald McDonald is fighting.
He wins every time.
Ronald McDonald versus God.
Aren't they the same thing?
Amen.
All right, where am I going?
I don't know how to get to this place.
I saw it from a distance,
but I don't know how to get over there.
Dude, how do I get the fuck out of here?
I need to go look from above again.
Why do I feel like this is a different area?
I feel like I'm stuck here.
How do I get out of here?
This is why I dropped the coins
and the coins are gone
because I reloaded the area.
I found it.
I think I got it.
Yeah, Grimace was cool, too.
They were all cool.
All right, is it that way?
It's that way.
All right, so I got to go down that way.
Grimace was the man.
You know what I mean?
Grimace was awesome.
One of my favorite Grimace lines.
I'll never forget it.
God, remember what you remember?
Hey, Ronald.
Fucking legendary saying.
Just sends chills up and down my spine.
I'm just like, God, Grimace is a fucking man.
Remember what he used to say?
Ronald, I love classic shakes.
Just God damn, man.
He's such a cool motherfucker.
Where am I going?
I'm sorry.
I need to go that way.
Don't kill me.
Down here.
Okay, I need to get there.
How do I even get over?
Down here, down there, straight through there.
And up there.
Let's go.
No one, and I mean, no one knows what you're talking about.
Somebody does.
You don't remember the classic Grimace lines?
Is this right?
No, I already lost.
Yeah, it's the fucking Zelda forest.
What are you linking me?
What is this?
Hold on.
Bony fingers.
What is this?
I don't know how you do it.
I put together some really impressive deals.
But this thing you've pulled off, it's amazing.
A big and tasty for just a dollar.
How do you do it?
What's your secret?
He didn't even say anything.
No, that's not the classic Grimace line.
We could own this town.
Of course we will.
He didn't even say anything in this commercial.
He doesn't even talk.
Why did you link this to me?
You know Grimace.
What the fuck?
He never spoke?
Yes, he did.
Grimace had a voice.
And I know it.
Did Grimace walk this way?
No, he walked this way.
There it is.
I knew you liked happy endings.
What the hell?
I got to get out of here.
Barney rubble.
All right.
Where is this place?
I hate getting lost.
I was too busy laughing at Grimace.
And I don't remember where I am.
Am I going the right way?
I'm out of stamina.
Get off me, Donnie.
If I die right now, I'm going to do a huge Grimace.
It's going to be the biggest Grimace you've ever heard.
Oh my god.
I don't want to.
I actually don't want to do it.
I just said that to be an idiot.
It was just me making a dumb joke.
I actually don't want to do a Grimace voice.
Just get away from me.
Get away from me.
Hey, boys and girls.
Everybody loves a McDonald's.
Free me shakes.
I don't know where to go now.
I got chills from that, dude.
Get the hell away from me.
Fuck, I forgot where to go.
Oh no, I hate this place.
I was right there.
It's I have to go.
No, no, no, no.
I know.
I got to go to where I fought the lady with the wings.
Where?
Fuck if I remember where that is.
Where is somewhere like in the midsection here, right?
It's above.
It's like over.
Where is it?
I don't remember.
Everything's green and foggy.
I can't see anything.
Everything is green and foggy.
I where's my visibility?
I have no visibility.
I don't know where I'm going.
Where is that place where I fought that lady?
You've played this game for like 10 hours.
I haven't played in the Zelda forest for 10 hours.
Everything's foggy and everything's disconnected.
I know I have to go down.
Where is that?
Where do I fight that lady?
That way.
Has there ever been a rogue's gallery like McDonald's?
No.
Who comes?
Nobody even comes close.
Those of you that are wondering what happened,
I was reading chat and walked in a complete circle.
All right, let's try this shit again.
No more messing around.
No more grimace bullshit.
Just get me over there.
Is grimace in hell?
I think grimace is still alive.
So no.
And then it's this way, right?
Oh my god.
I have to do this.
Didn't even get hit.
Do a poll.
All right, do a poll.
Is grimace in hell?
Don't.
Seriously, dude.
I just want to get out of here.
Grimace is not.
And the fact that you would say that grimace is,
it just saddens me.
It just disappoints me.
Like just it just it you saying that grimace is in hell
is disappointing to me.
Yeah, what did he even do?
What did why is grimace in hell?
What did grimace do?
He's a capitalist mascot.
Grimace is a nice is a nice character.
Grimace is not in hell.
I this is a long poll.
Okay, here we go.
Who is grimace?
The big purple guy from McDonald's.
If you're curious, he sounds like this.
Gotcha.
I know a lot of you just muted the stream.
Well, did it for no reason.
Watch out for bad game design.
Avoid curiosity.
Is the squirrel?
All right.
What is it?
What's the verdict?
63% of you think that you know what?
At least I'm happy that there's like almost 40% of you
have not lost your minds.
Something amazing has spawned.
No, you silly.
Though you sure are swell.
When your cycle started,
an innocent, uncorrupted NPC also appeared.
That hasn't happened for ages.
Hey, I have a fun idea.
How about you find them
and bring them a little gift from me?
This guy's weird.
An innocent wouldn't be able to stay
innocent long in this messed up world.
What the hell is that?
Is this Dex?
No.
What is this?
Give it to an innocent?
What so many cycles had crumbled.
Might it yet be restored?
Dare the narrator hope.
Oh, shit.
Keep of the Stolen Crown.
Very interesting.
So interesting, in fact,
that we're gonna have to finish this another time.
I like this area.
Good fast food stream.
They're all fast food streams.
I just hide the fact that they're not.
But yeah, thanks for watching.
That was a really, really fun day.
Wild Hearts seems pretty fun.
I might play some more of it.
I don't know if I'll play it on stream,
but it's definitely something I think I'm interested enough
to get through some of it.
Not that it matters, but thanks again to EA
and the developers of that game
and for sponsoring that part of the stream a few hours ago.
And thanks for watching
and thanks for sticking around during that.
Thank you.
And then this was fun, too.
A lot of nice time tonight.
I had a great time.
So the next time you see me is going to be...
I want to finish this game.
We probably only have like a couple hours left.
Let's say Monday.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I got that wrong.
Sunday is technically...
Wait, no, no, no.
Tomorrow would technically be Sunday, right?
Technically.
So yeah, we'll finish it up Sunday.
And after we finish this, we'll pivot to something else.
We'll see.
Have a great evening.
See you all soon.
Let me just make sure I save the game.
I think it saves automatically.
Yes, it does.
Same time.
Big huge shout out to Vinny.
Vinny made that way, way, way more fun and way more interesting for me.
So thanks, Vinny.
Take care of yourselves.
Get some sleep or good morning, whatever one it is.
I'm going to go get some food.
Call your mother?
Well, I mean, maybe not right now.
Might be late.
We'll see you Sunday.
Goodbye.
See you later.
Take care.
Yeah, that was a little late.
Whoops.
See you tomorrow.
Tomorrow as in Sunday.
It's technically Saturday night right now.
So like in a day and a half, a day, a day and a half, two days.
See you later.