Hi everybody, this is Jerma here. We're gonna be playing this early Steam access game called Snow. Looks pretty fun. Let's try. Okay, play.
Where's the audio? Why is there no audio in this game?
Wait a second. Hold on. This could be the best game ever made.
I must have messed up something with the uh, with the audio settings because there are no audio. I'll figure that out. There are no audio. Good job with like talking.
Alright, I need to slow down here. I don't want to get like run into a tree.
So this game is like touted as the first ever like free to play open world simulator, but it's not free to play yet. That's like the funny thing. What?
I need to like reload this game. This could be so good.
Ah, oh my game crashed. Alright, I want to spawn at like the summit. We're going, we're going right to the summit.
And we're, yeah, I still don't have any audio. Alright, whatever. Let's try to get down to summit.
I'm going to destroy myself so bad. Oh God. Oh my God. I'm going too fast.
So I was wondering what the most important thing is. In fact, when you're developing a game like this, when you're putting these things together, I want to see what the community had to say.
And I came across this. Can you at least bust your balls on a railing? It's not a true snowboarding game if you can't bust your balls on the railing.
Busting your balls is one of the experiences of being a freelance snowboarder. Moving further down the discussion, this person says it's an alpha.
So things will get implemented over time. You don't know if it's possible or not, but we'll see what happens in a few months.
And this guy says alpha state is already almost finished. The basics are there. They either have ball busting on railing action or they don't. Case closed.
I'll tell you, the game looks pretty good. Look at the snow and the mountains. It's pretty cool looking, but I mean, there's no audio. I don't have any. Oh, look at that trick. Oh, shit.
Oh, wow. Okay. Alright. I got some points for that. That's how you get points. But maybe it's just something going on with my audio settings or something.
Anybody else that has this game? Is it my settings? Do you have audio or do I not have audio?
What? Alright, that's fine. Look at the music. I'm going to do a backflip. Alright, here we go. And the next thing I go off of, I'm doing a backflip.
Doing a legitimate full backflip on the next jump. When I first started playing this, I was falling all over the place. Now I'm not.
Here we go. You ready for a full backflip? Full backflip. Here we go. The game crashed. So I've crashed. Like, I can't even get down the mountain.
I literally have crashed every single time I've tried to get down the mountain. Let's try this again. I'm going to go the scenic route.
Hopefully I can get to the bottom of the mountain before the game crashes. That would be a good thing. This is like the this is a crash. Let's go down here.
Let's go down here. I'm going. I'm going to do a backflip. I promise you guys I'll do a backflip. There it is. Oh, can you get the double backflip?
Yes. Oh, that was pretty sick. Double backflip. Can we do another double backflip? Nope, we can do one backflip though. I'll take the points.
Front flip and no, it crashed again. Fuck. No, no. Why? Why?
Dear developers, I want to play your fun little ski game, but I can't. The game seems to crash every two minutes or so, taking any fun away I could be having at all.
I understand this is an early access game and it's ongoing in its development, but I think we can all agree that the number one thing you need to work on is implementing busting your balls.
Busting your balls on rails action is the quintessential part of any snowboarder's life and ball busting takes precedence over everything else.
Signed, Yerba.