Can you please just tell the stars apartment is a jungle story?
The stars apartment is a jungle story for your video. Yeah
Dude, this game the center is getting so many. No, he's back
God damn it. I was too busy like paying attention to you a fucking stupid jungle bathroom
And I don't know why I brought up the jungle bathroom. I just told I just told the story all the steam is gone for the story
Dude, this center was getting so many kills and I was just like oh tell that story and I wasn't even paying any attention
I was paying attention to the story there. Well, I wasn't telling it
Yeah, but I was like paying attention to the nut to the notion that you were going to tell the story
That's it. I was sitting there whacking the gun. All right
Everybody wants to know this I want to know I'm sure the viewers wants to know star how where did it all begin?
I was born in New Jersey, New Jersey
Yeah, no fucking Jersey
Somebody please good. I have a medic now. I got a medic you think your unusual is gonna save you
You think you're like stall see your unusual didn't save you didn't save you
Sorry, that's a bad idea to be taunting bad idea
Bad, hold on. Wait a second. I can't mess this up
I
Did don't you dare taunt don't like taunting then get chased for like 30 seconds and have the guy with a guaranteed kill
Where did this time all begin? Where did this taunt begin?
Jersey you should see
Plymouth Rock
No rocks in Massachusetts you fucking idiot, I've never been to Massachusetts
How did I get back here? By the way? I don't know. I'm not even playing the game. How did I get back here guys?
I've been sitting here. Just laughing and me and star but just been being wicked stupid. How did I even get back here?
Look what the card is. What did I do?
What did I do? I'm at their spawn on upward all the way at the back and they're at the second point
Um
Star I know exactly what I want to do. So get your ass in the game like right now
Okay, there's three spies on this team. Okay, that's fine. I'm the fourth. That's great. Just letting you know so you don't like
Your job is to get back to red spawn like the all the way back. Oh like back to the future
I wonder who that medic is
This engineer is paying so much attention to like what I'm doing. He's like, what the hell is this guy doing? Wait, wait
No, he doesn't he doesn't know your spot
Just come over here
Yeah, all right now take your disguise off. No one's gonna spawn. Damn it dude. This is no
Kill it. I kill him
Why are we doing this why is this the thing we're doing?
Oh, all right. He's
This is that same engineer dude
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Is there another spy? Is that another spy? I'm so confused right now. Hold on. Let me I gotta go look
Yeah, that's a spy. Yeah, wait, there's a cloak spy behind you behind you behind you
I thought this was a dumb idea, but I forgot like the germa factor
Well, you're not gonna like hit it as soon as I show. No, I didn't I that was
Unnecessarily. I did not mean to do that. Oh look who it is
Okay, you need to get to no, I don't trust you. I'm look I promise you. Okay. Okay. That was a little bit scary with it
Oh, you're like whole team spawning here now. Yeah
So go hide and like a place like just do
No, just disguise as an engineer and just walk over to that guy
Just get in front of him. I want to try to box
Okay, do you see this engineer which one down to the down down spawn down at the their spawn?
He we can literally lock him in. I
Don't think he'll know what's going on. You get up you get on that side. I'm gonna get on this side
So he can't move. Yeah, he's stuck. He doesn't care
Completely locked in he's confused. He's like what's going on here? What can I not move?
This is this is confusing me
Get out of the way he's saying get out of the way in chat, this is awesome
That was amazing