Hope that music pumped you up because I'm uh, get pumped up pumped up for that starting stream soon music
I'm gonna sit here and play monster ranger. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry
Never mind. Hey, uh get sad anybody ever done that before
I know a lot of like streamers and youtubers really like pump up and they pump the fuck up their streams. Has anybody made it like
A sad music start. We're just like a somber beginning to the stream like
Just like hanging out instead of every stream of being like pumping up music
every stream starts really really like slow and
They like air the grievances in the beginning of every stream
Uh, you know, let's let's pump
But in all actuality, let me turn this down. Yeah, we're gonna do monster rancher again
monster rancher 4 we're gonna close
The series here probably with monster rancher 4
Unless I decide i'm gonna play the ds ones because the ds ones apparently are really good, too
It's just a question of capping
The ds which I know you need to mod it
So this will probably be the last monster rancher 4 stream
I'm really close to a and s rank
With one of the monsters and we have a dream team now
So we're gonna probably close it up today
Tomorrow we're gonna do risk of rain
uh taleks
wanted to uh
Swap the days we were talking about it
Downstairs we were saying yeah, we'll just do it on friday. So we'll do that tomorrow
And then the day after that is the sakiro gambling stream
But welcome though. I didn't even say hello
I didn't even introduce the stream at all
I just kind of turned on the music and forgot
Online game. No, no, no, no, no, no
There's a just preface to this there's a reason for this I painted your crying face
It's something else. That's for sure
I'm gonna skip the music. I'm sorry
It's kind of it's speech jamming me
But uh, let's turn this off so you can see the screen
Push this forward
But i'm ready to go
Exactly what we left off. We had the five monsters
And I don't really know what to do with them
I know that four of them are gonna be useless
Hold on. Let me see this before we get started
Oh my god
Look at this
I gotta put this like on screen. This is fucking insane
No, the music I don't want to hear the music for this
This is what i'm talking about
It's not supposed to be like this
Look at this happy music
Thank you. Yeah, man, that's fucking amazing
If you're just joining us. Yes, that is on the screen
There's a lot of emotions going on right now that I can't really describe to you
All right, let's go
Another amazing piece of artwork from yenwen. Yeah one at least one or two
Probably like three of those are gonna be emotes
I mean just have like three different versions of like the crying face
One of them really zoomed in
That'll be like Jerma Cry
Jerma Cry 2, Jerma Cry 3 or Jerma Cry Z for like zoom in
Hello everyone. I did several chores today. Hope your rooms are clean
Thanks for reminding me. I probably should do that
Next time on Jerma Cry Z
Jerma my boy. Yeah, that's it. That could be another one
but so
If you haven't seen the last few or last two monster rancher 4 streams
We've ended up with this team of five
the unprover
the spyroid
Roberto who's our main
These are just fucking smurfs. The rest are just alts
blossom
and add rock plus
Those are
You can tell yeah, you can tell who the main character is here. It actually is kind of funny
Because even if I didn't say anything
This is just the cast of an anime it is
Okay, so you've got main character who's on a mission. This is the one that matters. This is the character that matters
menacing
Little bit has a kind of a dark past
Really powerful really strong. This is the huge guy. There's always a huge guy in anime that has a deep booming voice
It's pretty arbitrary to the story but ends up jumping in and hitting somebody with a big punch every couple episodes
Here's comic relief
Comic relief goofy weird guy. Yeah, he has a voice like this
Has sage like advice but is strange beyond measure
Uh cute weird stuffed animal that pops up out of somebody's pocket or out of their purse or something
Makes a couple of noises is what is the main selling point at hot topic make the noise
I'll try
I think i'm pretty close, uh, then you got
rival
You've got best friend rival, but not really as intimidating or cool
As main character and ends up getting shown up all the time
In almost every other episode and can't stand it and eventually it turns evil because of it. We got the whole team here
We've got the whole anime show. You don't even need to watch the show. I just described the whole thing to you
He has to die at some point. Yeah, this character is gonna die. I like it. It's a pretty good team
It'll take eight seasons. Yeah, I like huge guy. Let's take a look at a schedule
I haven't read the manga you're reading it right now huge guy is best guy and huge guy
Also, here's the thing about huge guy that maybe about some of you guys that don't know about animated shows
huge guy
And little funny cute thing somehow become best friends and that you did not think that was gonna happen
And in fact eventually through the story little cute thing stuffed animal toy
Will be in the pocket of this character after about four or five seasons
In fact
Some people said well, okay, well and japanese anime. No, no, no, no. No, this happens in shrek
This exact character is in shrek, which is an american animated movie. So
That happens in american television animated movies as well. All right, let's go
Enough of this bullshit donkey and no the dragon. Have you not seen shrek the giant dragon?
All right. Let me look at their stats again. I forget everything
But I hope we're having a good day. That's the that's the intro. Okay adrock power. What is what adrox moves?
all power
Okay, probably build power and
life
This character is terrible. No wonder you're like the second right anime character
All right. This is 140 147 is actually pretty good base
Because that's not terrible
Not terrible base accuracy either
You can't nobody can step up to Roberto though. All right spiroid
Huge intelligence, right? We've been building it for a while
That speed is so bad though
All right, so we need
life
accuracy
Speed I was going full power here
And then maybe defense life for now
defense
So I don't want to there's never a manager for the anime team. That's the thing that sucks about monster rancher 4
There's not somebody standing there with a notepad while they all go off on their fucking quests and missions and shit
No
They all do their own thing. I'm just gonna auto do it for two of them. Here we go. Let's get Roberto done. I want sandbag
Yeah, what do we got? Yeah sandbag
He's he can rest the next day
Who are the two or three characters that I actually care about probably spiroid?
Look
And we're gonna do speed
I really don't care about anybody else. I really don't like i'm sorry. I don't maybe uh, I like the weird little
dancing plush toy thing
These two actually really don't matter. I'm gonna be honest. So you add rock plus and unprover do not matter
How do they ever expect you to manage five fucking monsters? We're gonna end up combining them eventually
It's the book trampoline. All right, let's start working on you
What did you need? The other two can just be automatic
They're just dna bait anyways
So intelligence speed let's go with life defense for now and then you can rest and we'll take a look after that
No, fuck ad rock didn't do anything
Hey, wait, was that was I supposed to do something?
Yeah. Yeah, sorry. I'm just managing fucking everybody. This is just a circus
Fuck doing tournaments. I should start charging people admission to come in here
We've got a dragon that reads books
We've got the funny dancing, uh weight lifter
We got the juggling act
and then
We've got the guy that kicks the sandbag
Great and then somebody's sleeping over here. Where is he?
That's kind of depressing
This is so depressing that i'm gonna have to fuse you
All right, you know what? He looks like
He looks like somebody looks like
frozen dog poop
Well, like dog shit that's on the sidewalk that nobody picked up after like six months
You don't I don't know if you belong here man
Okay, let's just go to the weekend
I'm being so mean to him
Yeah, well that's part of his character arc. He has to prove to the group
That he's stronger than the main character and he gets close
Not quite there. Oh
Roberto has become very mature
Got to adjust our raising to keep up with it
This is not good. Um
Roberto is signed up for this tournament. I gotta get Roberto to a rank
Before he dies
So if I win this one this one
Shit, I still have to find the stupid rock for that guy
All right new plan
I'm sending in the troop of morons to go find the thing that the guy wants
Roberto's not going he's just gonna rest
And this is perfect for the anime storyline because in every anime whenever the main character is not involved
They all fumble all over each other
They're sent on a mission and they can't fucking do it. They're all useless
And eventually they accidentally complete the mission. I can't wait to see what happens
uh
What was it exactly that I needed?
Did I already get it? Or I need like I need to go explore the jungle because somebody's lost, right?
That's what happened last time
Yeah, so we've got to explore the jungle with everybody but Roberto and hope that they can come up with a victory
So let's rest
And then we got trampoline everyone needs to be fed too
How do you feed five people?
rest tub
You don't know just automatic who cares you're gonna die anyways
Okay
Pretty terrible gains, but that's okay
Oh, we gotta see the cutest thing in the world. Where is it?
Where is it?
There you are
You're really hungry
food
Uh, do we have we got squid? Do you beef?
Okay, have a squid beef is for very special occasions. Nah, sorry. Sorry beef is only for main characters
all right, yeah, have a uh
Have a banana
What you don't think that's a pretty good rule that beef is should be only for main characters
You want me to give the side storyline our character the
$300 piece of food. What do you like? Have a mango. I'm keeping you around
I'm kidding. This this is this is this character's gonna stay around for a long time. I'm not getting rid of this one
We can replace the character with this can be comic relief and cute thing that pops out of somebody's purse
and every time it shows up the screen goes different like colors behind them and
Bubbles are on the screen and shit. Oh, you're good. It makes a weird squishy noise. You've already heard me do it
I don't have to do it twice. All right, everyone's fine. Let's go
Keeps getting hit in the head
All right jungle
Select the troop. Let's go. No Roberto. I don't want
Should I
Feel like i'm gonna run into a boss and it's gonna be a waste of time. I mean no
Can only I can only take three
Okay, well then we're gonna
Try to leave spiroid here, but I need to level up
Now unprover blossom and spiroid. No, this is a good one
We'll get like the two or three frames of animation of unprover
Scary going in from behind spiroid out from behind and like looking and peeking with the sweat coming off his head would be perfect
Okay, so we need to find the people that are here. Somebody's lost here
It even makes the right noise too
That's the same noise it makes. Oh, I can't it's it's too scary for me. I'm not sure
Watch out
Why do I know all these tropes?
I don't know because i've seen
It doesn't take more than seeing like one or two episodes of an anime to know these tropes
You don't have to be like a seasoned anime veteran to know these things
This happens in like
85 of every episode. All right, come on do something here
machine gun
All right, you know bring in the real character, please
Not bad. All right
All right, so now I have the ability to do like a team up, right?
What was it square?
Was a circle. What was the button to have somebody jump in from the other side?
Oh, there it is. Okay, it's x
That was just the anime that was the uh, that's perfect
Yeah, I don't need to do I need to explain that. Oh, you know what happened?
Big character did all the work
Little funny plush toy character jumps out at the end gets the last hit and goes like yeah, you take that
Oh, it's perfect
Maybe we'll flex
And when they flex there's a goofy boom big explosion of like muscles, but they're not real
It's just a cute thing with muscles like big muscles that show when they inflate for a second
And then after holding that pose for more than a couple seconds
It's like the air comes out of them
And a big sweat mark comes on the head. How the fuck is he level eight?
I feel like he hasn't done anything. We get it. Yes, we get it. You watch anime
I really don't though. I do not that often but I do
Maybe like twice. I've seen at least two of them. I work at an animation studio. I'd like to hire you
Me you'd like to hire me
I'm not so sure about that
But what if I don't do my job? Well, I
Guess I could try
and fired
That's right. You are in charge of everybody on the team
Oh
Okay, everybody. Oh finally everybody has to listen to me
Line up everyone
And then they just like they just like fucking stampede over him. He just still doesn't have any power. He thought he did
Now, let's try
What's this?
Do it. Come on
So I love somebody's rights. Can you stop this? I don't know if I haven't I don't know if I can turn it off
Well, that's amazing
Was it a cake?
Okay, blossom. What do you got?
hyper beam
head attack
We'll see you overrun. I love it. Nobody can do oh wait. What was it? Let me take a look head attack
Exactly what that image should look like
very high accuracy rating
Not very much life, but good crit and good accuracy and it doesn't take very much guts
This thing is amazing. If you start off with this every time
You could just drain them. Oh wait, wait, that wasn't I got something else too, didn't I?
hyper beam
beams
Apparently eventually they're gonna get a beam
B's no beam
B E A M
M as in Michael
You guys ever get on the phone with somebody that does that for every other word and you kind of just like you don't need to do that
Yeah, you coming to the party? Yeah. Yeah, i'm coming to the party. You got you got the address, right?
Yeah, I think so. I think I got it. What was it? One? Uh, what was it? Just tell me one more time
What was uh, it was uh, 484. Yeah, 44. Okay
West uh w as in as in as in west
E as an egg
A as an apple. It's like I know like dude, I know you said west. I know what you said
Come on. What?
Come on, don't get knocked out here. All right. I had to had to pull it back
nice
Hey
Why was it w e a guy was even spelling it wrong
West
Yeah, if you're gonna do that, you at least give me the right
spelling
a as an i i ya
What?
Nobody can help me do that
Why did you say that? What did I say? I said somebody wrote. I don't know what that is. Oh, that's the okay
Never mind. I don't know if that is
I know what that is
Sure you I prove it. I'm not gonna prove that
I know what it is
What is it then? It's the
It's the emote it's like an emote on twitch hit it. All right, I gotta play out. We see in the classroom
There is uh, the the girl's name is ayayo, right? And then uh, what happens is she doesn't understand her
She thought she's saying ayaya. So she ends up screaming ayaya like that's your name
She's going around the room pointing at people's names and giving them
Their names when they tell her but she's confused with ayayo because she doesn't understand that one
She's thinking and they keep going back and forth about ayayo or ayaya and then um,
You end up watching like a 15 hour version of it on youtube. I know what it fucking is
He looked it up like right now you like yeah like while i'm doing inputs and sitting here right now
Did you hear a keyboard press? No, it's called it's called like a few months ago
I had no idea what the fuck that was
And I was and saw it everywhere and I saw references to it. I'm like, I don't know what this is
So I searched it and I read about it
And now I know the whole entire story
It's called informing yourself and then seeing the facts presented in front of you and knowing what it is
Oh funny glasses
Can I can give those to me? I like those bro. They're facts facts
Funny glasses distract me. What was that? What did I just pick up? I can't go into data on my data
I did get distracted. You're right
It worked
Although somebody wrote I didn't even know what that meant and he does why?
It's because I typed it in and I looked up what it meant because I didn't know because I saw it everywhere
Guys, i've done the same thing with other emotes on twitch that I didn't understand
Like sour, please. I kept seeing it. I didn't know what it was and i'm like what the fuck is this
It's a guy like dancing in wal-mart
And I looked it up. It was from a video of a guy dancing in wal-mart
Oh, come on. How much gust damage is how much does do
That does 29 guts damage. That's pretty good damage. Actually. What about let's try that. No bring come back out here
Let's try the headbutt
I mean, that's that's the cutest thing ever
Not bad damage either for it being a shitty move
With no power levels up
Nice counter stupid
It's the eye from monster rancher one
Dude, what?
What a fucking easter egg
hard head
and mastered kiddie punch
Look at this
Kiddie punch
Apparently it does a lot of damage
10 it's only 10 guts to do this
Oh, it's a terrible accurate
The accuracy is awful
I don't know man
you build
accuracy
With this character and just spam this move over and over again
And hard head is moves that use your head. What is the most useless body part?
um
I mean, that's kind of a weird question
Okay, I was I didn't you just said body part and I just I see lungs on the screen here
Lungs are very important, but I mean that's that's a pair of lungs. You just said body part
And that's my brain just turned that into a pair of lungs
um
What's the most useless body part? Okay, let's think about this
uh
I mean, yeah, like your appendix doesn't do anything
battle cards
Your appendix doesn't do anything
Your your nails. Yeah, like your toenails your nail like
You know that there's a theory that we're gonna evolve off our fingernails and toenails, right?
Over a million years if humans are still around we're you're gonna evolve off no fingernails
Oh this again, i've talked about this before
No, look it up. Look i'm serious. Look it up. Hey, you know the thing that I did called this
facts and knowledge and data from like the institute of technology
Which institute of technology
That's easy
The reblog from my grandmother's facebook
It says it on the bottom right
Institute of technology
It has to be real
Which institute of technology the institute of technology?
flight ride
grave throw
All right flight ride
Let's you ride your monster and fly over ops. Oh, okay. I can finally do that now
I can cross the gaps there
And what is this?
d by grave throw
Look at that
s life damage
Not bad accuracy either
All right, which one of these sucks?
So this is a short range so fire is good
Flutter is mid. So this is d bite life a life s
Guts 23 30 not a big difference in guts
Hey, this is just a better move. It takes more guts, but it's just a better move. It'll land more often in general. So
There's no uh, yeah, let's replace this one
He's an intelligence monster
Yeah, but some of those moves are good to have
If you run up to somebody that has
um
You run into somebody that has high intelligence those moves are not going to work
Can I fly over that?
Hold on
Can you fly this?
I can't like just fly over that, huh?
Holy my god
That did a lot of damage. That was a nice crit though. All right, bring it up
fire in the middle
blast him
nice
Jeremy I bite my own fingers. Do you was that cannibalism?
um
I don't know. That's that's a different that's a topic that I don't know if we can even touch on right now because that's
Depends on who you ask
Is it auto cannibalism if I bite my fingernails?
No, because you're not you're not biting your fingernails and eating your fingernails for sustenance
It's just it's a habit. I'm asking you. Okay. No, I don't think that's cannibal. That's not auto cannibalism
You're not eating your fingernails for nutrients
What if I am though? Well, then i'm I really hate to tell you this but you've been doing that really wrong because there's no nutritional value
In your fingernail
I don't I don't think it's even calories in your fingernail
It's like chew. It's like biting. It's like eating wood. Damn it. Holy shit that hurt
All right, pull them out pull them out. I don't want them to get hurt here
Nice blossom
Try it again
Come on, hit it. Just try to get it. Just try to hit it. Oh my goodness. Not good
Damn, I always got this stupid thing
16 chance to hit this
No
Oh, come on
What the fuck? What is this guy? Seriously?
He's blocking every attack
They're gonna all die
Because nobody will do a fucking move. Look at this and he blocks every attack
Oh my god, give me a break
Hey
He's dead
This guy's unstoppable. I cannot fight this guy
Okay. Well, uh, he didn't he he now he comes back again. Of course it is great. This is fantastic
And now he's bullish. He's gonna die here
Wow, what a what a fun game this is
What a great mechanic we have here. This is fantastic
Are you serious?
Like I blocked almost every attack
60 to 70 percent of every move I tried to do they wouldn't do and he got final guts
I got fucking party wiped right? Yeah. What the hell was that?
Genuinely angry. What the fuck was that?
I got literally wiped
They're all one that I just took the lifespan out of everybody here down because one alligator
Decided to block every single move
That's such a horse shit
Is that even uh, what like come? Oh, i'm so annoyed by that like that's how it's all
Combined them. No, that was things were going fine
Ding block ding block ding block ding block ding block. Oh, you're bullish. You're bullish. You're bullish. You're timid
You're timid. You're timid. You're timid. You're timid ouch ouch ouch ding block ding block ding block ouch ouch
Oh, you killed me. No, i'm back
final guts
This game is for children imagine being a child and having that happen to you and crying
And like going into your parents room with the disc and the case and being like
I can we go back to store. What is it? What is it? What happened?
Yeah, this game's not fair
Of course get in the car
Which one do you want instead?
That one
And you point really hard at the box and it's super mario party for n64 and that's the game you should have bought
He points at sakiro
That's so funny
Are you sure? Yeah
And he beats everything first try he fucking perfect deflects every single enemy
He's the one on reddit that's telling you that you quit crying about how hard the game is. It's not hard. It's easy. I beat him
anyways
jack's origin story
Yeah, like man, this is so fucking hard. I haven't got any tips like i've died like a hundred times to the ogre
This is like fucking really hard
just dodge right
slash
You're not intelligent
Not intelligent
I'm so fucking mad right now. I can't believe I don't want to do that again
I don't want to bring i'm gonna have to bring roberto in there. Can I save scum? No, no, no, that's not necessary
Go put your ass handed to you again. And I was reading stuff about um
There are people saying that to add like an easy mode to
Sekiro
That's like a current that's a current topic right now
Was did this happen when like bloodborne came out or dark souls 3 when dark souls 3 came out was there like a no
But nobody there wasn't a reason for it because you could just over level
That's true. This is like the first time really this has probably ever happened
Cuphead yeah, but cuphead had like a casual mode didn't it where you could play like on easy
It did still happen. I'm of the opinion that like
Okay, if I go into an art gallery and there's a picture like with like this the scream right and I look at the scream
And i'm like, huh?
The scream that's who made that?
Oh, uh leonardo da vinci
Oh, okay
Do you mind you pull up you grip a fucking sharpie off and you like do you mind if I uh go in here for a second?
What are you doing? What are you doing? You like and you add like a row of teeth on the screen
It's a church. What the fuck are you doing? And like everyone's gonna like tackle you and like rip you out of there
I must have what the screen is by edward. I know I know I got it wrong. I just said any painter
How are teeth in easy mode?
No, i'm just saying it's like
Making like an easy mode after the fact I think is not it wouldn't work
If from the very beginning they decided to do something like that, then I think that would make some sense, right?
But if the game's already out
And they retroactively go back and have to change everything
You know what I mean?
There are a lot of games that are made from the ground up with like that in mind and that's that's great
If securo had in like an easy mode at launch
It's like okay. They said they wanted to do this. They wanted to have it like that. That's fine
But if it's already done and it wasn't like part of the plan then somebody's give 20 fucking community subs
Uh great lord wall and thanks for the 20 community subs. Holy shit. Thank you for the 20 fucking subs. That's uh,
A lot, thank you
but yeah, I mean I I totally understand the the aspect of
Like I want to enjoy the game too, right and I don't want to grind
Ishin for 17 hours, right? I completely understand it, but I think something like that should be like tied into
How the game is developed in the first place because that shit is fucking hard
That game is hard hard hard like very fucking hard you've heard you those either watch those streams. Holy shit
That's one of the hardest things i've ever done. Okay life
All right, everybody needs to rest because of that shit
Only reverto can do anything
You fought the headless guy and had a psychotic breakdown. Yeah, I know that's what i'm saying
Like it's I understand like what people are talking about when they say like holy shit
This game is fucking next level
But in my opinion, I think decisions like that need to be made
Right at the beginning. All right, everyone needs to eat
How about uh, you like bananas?
Uh, wait, wait, are we talking about a germa opinion here?
But also like look think about this too and I know that some people are gonna like I've given my opinion in my stance
on that right how I think like
retroactively adding modes to games that are not
Baked into the vow the artistic vision of the creator, right?
I think should be done differently
But the person that wants to enjoy sakiro they still paid for the product, right? They still paid for it
and sometimes it can be difficult for
You think about that like oh like imagine you get like I yeah, I got like two kids
I gotta go to work and come back. I got like 45 minutes today to play sakiro and you you just add the ogre for four days straight
You know what I mean?
Some people just want to like enjoy the experience and that's like a whole nother
That's a whole nother opinion there. You could just play another game. Yeah, but they still bought it and they still want to like it, right?
Somebody says having one difficulty means you can balance the game specifically for it
Yeah
But but if you have modes like I mean like devil may cry right has like a bunch of hard and easy mode
The cuphead is one of the hardest games that came out like last year and that that had modes too
And it wasn't like holy shit. Why are these in here? But it was
Baked into the game. They like planned for that. They were making that that way
Yeah, there's no need to be rude to each other. This is this is we can have a very
Decent conversation with each other
Sometimes we talk about these things. You don't have to be angry or mean with each other. Come on guys
I mean, I just beat sakiro
Last week and I see a lot of people talking about it. So I figured hey
Why don't we talk about it for a sec? It's interesting. He's flexing on it. I mean, I did just beat sakiro last week
Okay, everyone's okay
All right, let's do some training. Wait, no, no, no, when's the tournament?
It's today. All right, don't train. No, actually you can train today
You'll be fine. All right. What about everybody else? You need to do no everybody. Look at how fucked up they all still are just rest
You're the only one that can even do anything
Okay, let's give you some good food
Uh, that's not good food
I was just gonna give you a potato
All right. Roberto is somebody said Roberto's gonna die
He's not gonna die yet. He'll be okay
for like another couple tournaments
How much time does he have left? What do rocks like to eat?
You can even have a potato who cares?
Yeah, but I I didn't want to like open up like a can of worms with that topic
I just figured it's very very much relevant right now and we talk about relevant things on this channel
We don't you're good
so you can now
Train tomorrow. Let's do we need you to do like life
No, no, no, you need you had high speed high intelligence. You know, just fucking burn
Intelligence just do it. We got a tournament
All right, Roberto. Let's see what you got. You're in b rank now
All right, Roberto versus lean. This is a dragon. I think
Look at that 296 intelligence high defense high power. This thing is not to be fucked around with
Nice and nice lean meat
Right at the bat. Perfect
It's a giant sonic the hedgehog. They're always going to be sonic the hedgehog no matter what
Every one of these will be sonic. I want a statue of beanbag sonic
All right. Well lean beat
sunday
On sunday won the last match
high power high defense
All right, it's got a land move that's it at that i'm just i'm stacking power on Roberto
We're just going for one hit kills
Uh-oh
Thank god
It's so hard to counter that it's so quick
It was energized. It was energized
Eden looks like you're not that threatening
No, not at all. It should be easy
Sponsored by energizer not quite
Perfect. Come on. I have to get to give me to a rank. Nice countered it
All I want is a rank. I don't even need to do s rank. I just want to get to a rank
Roberto has six months to a year left to live. Okay
I'll save every month
I'm gonna drink this five-year-old pac-man energy drink. That's been on my shelf
Don't do that
You're gonna insta puke
Yeah, you will insta puke. I watched somebody do stuff like that
And then I can't recommend you do that
paron
High power, but not that bad shouldn't be that much of an issue
Huge dog
Uh-oh, let's go for a power slash
Oh almost back it up
You missed it
Just going for a little tap damage. That's all I wanted
Somebody said that was a cursed
inkling
Uh
What a what like a very specific reference. All right, this is the guy to beat life 284
So it looks like he's gonna try to outlast
No, even if I lose here, it's sunday and I already beat sunday
Just has really high health
Why am I not using more?
midair
Um, I don't know. It takes too much damage
Takes too much, uh guts
pretty good
I am the victor of this championship tournament
Roberto wins
B rank two more tournaments and I win and I can get to A
A rank
I got a salmon too. Am I the most popular I can be? This is as popular as you are physically allowed to be
In a fresh salmon
He doesn't get to eat it though because he's gonna die
We're gonna give that to the baby
All right. We need I need a friend
Who's friends?
I need to look at this because if I get six more months
Who likes each other?
Roberto and spyroid are good friends
How do I make them great friends?
so we need to level up and get spyroid up
and then
Combine spyroid and roberto and then have the ultimate being but how do I make them better friends?
By taking them on adventures together. What if I just bring two of them?
Blossom does not have any good friends
That's kind of sad
Send adrock to the slaughterhouse
Not yet
All right. I'm gonna bring spyroid blossom and roberto
And roberto's gonna steamroll while they all become friends
Let's save it here. All right. What do we got for tournaments?
Where is spyroid spyroid I need to win I'm gonna
I have to I have to stop ranking spyroid up. He's the only other one I really care about besides blossom
but
Can I just can they both rank up if they win this one together?
A fifty dollars just came in
shala
shalasha
Thank you shalasha
For the fifty dollars five thousand bits and they say your streams are always so unique compared to other streamers
And that's something that I that I draw a lot of joy from
This money's chump change compared to what others to what you deserve
Hope you can continue to bring laughs to your viewers for years to come. Thank you again. You're pretty good
Thank you for the extremely extremely generous amount of money shalasha shala shal's shala shal's
the bostonian accent
Shala shashka shala sha that's the shala shashka got it. What did I say shalashka?
shalashka
You ever been to shalashka before?
It's the most it's the most northwestern state in the entire united states
But thank you so much, man. Really appreciate it. That's a ton of money and
Don't don't compare yourself to what other people have given any amount of money is appreciated on this channel
No matter what what every denomination it is. Let's get uh, let's get spyroid in this tournament
And then this one we got to start ranking them up because if we're gonna fuse spyroid
Yeah, if we're gonna we have to just do it. We just have to blow through it
I don't like that feature
You know what I mean?
I don't like the three star feature if he's ready. He's ready. I don't i'm having to do three tournaments. No matter what
Am I drinking right now? No, i'm not
No, i'm drinking coffee. I have a cup of coffee in front of me right now
rest rest
Rest today because you have a tournament
You can actually
just automatic
for technique
You can do the book
and you
Who cares?
Okay, let's go for it decent gain
You're good
I need food though. I gotta get go to town and get some food. Does this take the whole no it doesn't
Oh fuck
I'll do it tomorrow
Hope we get acting lessons today
step one
Imagine the situation you're currently in I really should do an acting lesson stream an acting workshop
Damn it. I should just bring in
actors into the studio
And do an acting workshop on stream
We'll take maybe we'll get the discord or the chat to vote on
Slides like scripts teach from movies to do
Huh? I like this idea actually a lot
and then at the end
This takes a little more planning, but at the end maybe chat holds up like a sign of like between zero and ten
Like the olympics, but it's like the acting olympics
Why don't they do that?
How come there's no acting olympics?
I guess that it's just the academy awards, but
Because that's mean
The acting olympics
You give them different scenarios that they have to do on the fly. They have like an hour to prepare for the scene
Because it's so subjective
We see why I think they shouldn't add an easy mode two huge
animals versus each other
Look at this one
Holy shit
Best character ever best character ever
Now we have to do that two more times before you can get to d
fries
a potato
Jeremy have you ever heard that some animals can see colors that humans can't you ever wonder what those colors could be?
No, I have no concept of what that could be
You know, there's no concept of what that possibly is
like infrared maybe or
Anytime I think of a color that I don't know why this is
Well, whenever I can't think of a color that humans can perceive I always just think of
The prism the prism color, you know what I mean?
It's because movies have done that
It's a color that humans can't see
And there it is on the screen and it's just like a reflecting prism color
Okay, you got another one tomorrow life blade. How are you? You're okay rest today and eat I gotta eat bingo right here
Another competition is scheduled for that. Just yes, we're doing this one instead. God damn it
Why can't I do more than one?
sloppy sloppy game design sloppy game
Sloppy can only do one tournament. How am I supposed to manage five fucking monsters if I can only do one tournament?
I can't I gotta hire somebody to do the other one. All right schedule. We've got
Tomorrow we've got a rest. We've got what do you know what my power right? Yeah power and health
power and accuracy
Straight up power
Everybody else you can you can go fuck off. I'm just kidding
rest
sandbag
You can do something and you're on automatic anyways
Plus 14 power almost a little 20 power. All right, you're good. Let's praise and give I gotta get food
floppy game design
Yeah
No, that salmon is for whoever comes out when I fuse the two of you
Um, I don't have anything else to give you
Uh-oh
Huh? You're gonna have to wait till tomorrow to eat
Wait, do you have a tournament today?
Everyone people are hungry
Uh, who do I give this food to?
Lee
I'm so glad you took care of my kids lee my son
Not so easy. Is it well actually we want you to be okay. Here we go
You get the beef
We want you to stick around for a little while because you gotta get it like at least c or b
He loved it. All right, proceed to the weekend. Give me some town go here. Let's get some more food
Welcome fain. I would like
to buy
A lot of this let's get fuck it. Come on, man
Get five of them
Let's get a bunch of bananas
and
I need more mangoes
Uh a couple of squids maybe a couple of squids
And that's good
I have so much dumb shit. Look at this
raises spirit a little during adventures
Toughens toughness and accuracy a little bit during battle
I feel like I should just liquidate my inventory but money it doesn't seem to have
Too much of a purpose yet
I think it will very soon though
You sound like orson wells
What?
Orson well, it sounds like this. This is kind of the way that he used to talk
I don't think that I have that kind of inflection
The beginning and end of most of his words were pulled in a little. Why do I sound like that?
Young orson. No, I don't
I don't think young orson wells
What that's I've I've never heard that before. Okay, we got
Trampoline that's fine
Target that's good
Rest and food and then your tournament
uh
you need to
Rest because you're gonna be very angry and you
Or something who cares I could go for a mimosa
Do it up. Look at how bad adrock actually is
You sound like my cousin orson wells
All right. Here we go. Let me give you a nice delicious scrumptious
Mango, you got to be nice and nutrient nutrious eyes for your tournament today
and you
You're good. You
uh have a
Have a
Banana there's also the stream the guys there's so many streams that I want to do this summer
I just need to get in touch with the right people somebody's like bartender
I want to just like throw a party where i'm the bartender and the stream is just
I have a party in the studio
When I just invite a bunch of people and I have to make their drinks for them
And see if I can do it
Go get my bartender's license
And do it it's that you can get a bartender's license in like I think a weekend
Just for the stream
Just like invite a bunch of people
Like streamers youtubers like friends just get them all here
All right. What do you let me what do you like?
Okay likes
trokaten and like just doesn't like to play
Spyro likes to fight doesn't like to play
Likes reference doesn't like to sleep, right?
So blossom likes roses and doesn't like to fight
He likes fossils and doesn't like to battle
What do you like for food though?
high pride cool
cheerful
Have a banana
Imagine having like a room with like 40 50 people in it and i'm making drinks everybody
And everyone would try. Yeah. Hey, do you think you can fucking make this one?
And I do and I can
And i'll be wicked fucking lively and i'll be chatting up everybody
It'd be so fun
Rent out a hibachi and try to cook there
It's like, okay, you know how people do first impression
For games and stuff what if I did it now hear me out on this
What have I started doing first impressions?
on other
occupations
like occupations
chef
teacher
detective
Show like just how difficult these jobs are
Be go be a pool boy
Just do like this be a pool boy for a stream
And give like my first impressions on like being a pool boy
This is just dirty jobs, but
Not dirty jobs, not like dirty jobs. This is just
jobs
Jobs with jerry b elbertson
Uh, this is why I like dude, I just
Some of these things just have to happen
I'm gonna tell you something right now. I'm gonna i'm gonna I think i'm gonna blow the lid off of one of these things
That is coming up soon
Because I need to tell you what it is. I have to talk about it
Because you have to be ready for it
This is not like you need to know what this is
And i've already started talking with people and trying to get the ball rolling on it
So it's gonna if it's gonna happen it's gonna happen soon
This like if this just pops up one day
No one's gonna know what to do. It's gonna be fucking confusing
It's gonna be really confusing if this stream just turns on it's gonna be like I don't even know what the fuck's happening
Remember how we talked about the detective stream before it happened for like a week or so a couple weeks
And I mean this is not gonna happen in like a week or two
But like i've already started the process of trying to figure out how this is actually gonna work. Here you go
You ready?
An upcoming stream that i'm trying to and i've been i've been trying to do this for a long time because it's just hard to do
It's not like a big deal
It's just something fun that i've wanted to do and it's gonna happen probably if it's going to happen
It's gonna happen soon. Here it is
i'm going to set up a stream
where
I sit in a dunk tank
And twitch controls a robot pitching machine
To try to dunk me while I talk shit
I think I may have talked about it once before
At the very end of a stream
But I never not like in the middle of a stream. I think I talked about it maybe once a little bit
I've been and that was probably a while ago and i've been trying to figure out how to do this and i've got somebody now
That has knowledge in this area that can help so
That idea is actually probably going to happen. How does that relate to detective? Well, it relates like this
There's going to be like chat bots and stuff that are in the stream a day or two before people are going to be like
What the fuck is this?
So you kind of need to know that that's a possibility
Is chat going to aim it by saying left right? Yes
It's going to be total chaos
And you gotta dunk me
And then and I know people saying well, hold on a second. What if we just aim it like backwards?
No, there's going to be like safety
There's going to be a safety person there that's job is to make sure that you guys don't like
aim it all the way to the left and like
Blow out a window. There'll be a safety individual there whose job is to make sure that it's safe
Do you guys know how it don't tank works
There's a cage and like a little button fill the tank with maple syrup. No
I'm filling up with hot sauce
That's not happening either
But there was a major development on that very recently
So there is a very high possibility that you're just gonna see that it's just gonna happen
You'll see the fucking okay when you start to see like the chat bot come into the channel
And I we might do some testing too on it to make sure it works
That's how you know, it's coming
Fill it with ecto cooler
Uh, not this this guy's a pushover
Is it's gonna be a pitching machine the chat moves? Yes
the original idea was
To have it be
a stream that you kind of got like it lined up for and
Okay, that was insane
Like it was somebody's turn, right?
But it logistically it would be very difficult to set that up and maybe it depends on if I can get some
The people that I have involved if they can give me guidance on it
So, you know essentially maybe you like you pay like five dollars in bits or something you get three balls
That was like the original idea that this would all be for charity, by the way
Um, but then I thought about that would be very very difficult to do
because
It would just there could be a ton
Of people in that line and it went we might never end
There was ideas maybe to have like certain people maybe get a you know white listed to do it
Like another streamer is something to get a chance or make it an event
But i'm not sure yet, but I don't think that I don't I don't want people to pay to do it though
Bidding war for five minutes highest bid after five minutes gets the ball
Yeah, or like random draw is another thing maybe like random draw give somebody a chance to do it
But the thing with random draw is
If what if that person's like afk
It'd be like, oh, all right. Well, we need to have a code set up where if they didn't move
For x amount of seconds, they would just go on to another person
Have a quiz at the first but yeah, I think these are all interesting things to try
But I didn't want to kind of just start opening up a conversation about it
Because it's something that I really really want to do soon
Because it's I once the weather started to get better
It was going to be these things I want to try to do and this is one of them the asmr stream is another one
That's still happening
I can't let that one go because of a couple of very specific things. I want to do in it
Well 260 accuracy, yeah, I would break twitch. I don't know
If it was done, right?
I mean when like twitch plays pokemon was a thing there was
Tens of thousands of people there
Just needs to be done, right?
Isn't asmr banned from twitch? Uh, I
That would be very new development if that was the case
They're people that based their entire channels on that, right?
prga2c
Okay
uh
What the fuck is this? It's an actual robot thing
This is like a true bot
a terrible defense apparently
That thing's cool
Breeding robots. Yeah, don't you just build a robot?
yeah, the reason why the the dunk tank thing is something that was going to take a while was just because
programming and
Robotics and stuff that takes people to know what the fuck they're doing with that certain
field
And i've been throwing the line out a bunch of times actually
over the course of the last like five months to see if I could find somebody that was like really knowledgeable in like the
chatbot area and
Very the reason only reason why i'm talking about it is because there was a very very recent development
On getting it actually started. Let's back it up and just end this. Let's let's make this like flashy
Would I be paying? Oh, absolutely. Yeah
I just like burnt all my guts
Uh-oh
Uh-oh. All right. Come on 52 percent. All right, we're good
hubris was taking over
Have you saved a single time? Yeah, I have
$5,000 in a melon. Good job. Roberto
You're too famous already
The people here that uh, how do I contact you?
Cyber junkie helps kibo with a lot of chatbot stuff
Talk to william osman. He's great with electronics and probably be happy to do it. Yeah, these are all great resources things to obviously absolutely consider
$5,000 a resident sleeper a melon pogchamp
Okay, so that's two
Can I get another one of these done before you die?
Can I get up to a rank before you die? So why is this so spread out here? Okay, so we're gonna do
Spyroid is already signed up for this one and then spyroid and blossom
We're gonna do this team battle one and then spyroid from here
We'll be able to do you're gonna do three tournaments in a row
We'll get you rested up. Don't worry
but I at the moment I do have somebody that is
very knowledgeable that is putting me on a very good path at the moment, but
If that doesn't pan out or if I need more resources, I absolutely will ask about it again
After the monsters reach a certain age, they cannot be raised any further and they cannot participate in any battles
Well, it's all right. We're just gonna say we're gonna save scum every week
You should ask steve urkel
Yeah, let me ask steve urkel
To help with the twitch bot dunk tank string
Yeah
Okay
Why what?
All right, you should ask norman osborne any more fictional characters. I should be aware of that will help me with this
All right, let's get some training here
All right. We got big tournaments coming up for you. So you can just
rest here
just do the
Target you need better
Okay, target trampoline target rest trampoline
And we got this one
you
Sandbag sandbag sandbag rest probably
Tar no, someone's already using it do
Do intelligence again just stack it
And then maybe rest we'll see
You who cares
Somebody's already doing that. What about life?
Big gains by roberto
Let's feed
Hey, good job
food
squid
You should ask my good friend
Elon musk
He's got like a fucking trillion dollars, right?
That's a pretty interesting melon. That's I feel like i'm that melon
You pull that up and push that down and you're gonna blow up like the road runners
uh
Like bridge that he's gonna cross or something. What in sam hell are you saying?
I'm saying like the wily coyote
That's the thing he uses when he lifts up and pushes down and the roadrunner he misses
Have you ever watched an anime before?
What if I want to feed you?
I have too many expensive items
Here have a squid
You didn't even like that for a second. I thought he was punching
The rock guy ad rock
Where even is ad rock?
Oh, we're here
It's really really nice to see
That you brought your son to comic con
And dressed him up in a decepticon outfit and you're in an optimus prime outfit as the adult dad
Here don't be frustrated
That looks like it's stuck to his hand. He's trying to get it off
Yeah, it kind of does
That was actually pretty funny. We got that moment
All right competition. We don't have anything right? We never got the three-minute ad you promised us. Yes, I did
I did that at the very end
Sandbag book target nothing new
I have to bring you like tablets or something, right?
Where the fuck am I gonna find these?
More ads i'm not running the three-minute ad break right now. I don't have anything to do here
How am I gonna fund your dunk tank?
Don't worry. No, you're not getting an ad break
Okay
You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good
Let's look at the schedule. All right, two back-to-back tournaments to get you out of this dumb e-rank
Rest and then no trampoline
No, actually, this is fine. No trampoline then rest
Trampoline that's a fun word to say
trampoline
You can rest
And then I want you doing sandbag
All right
light blade and then rest
And then you want to do?
I don't know who k is
like no
sandbag
Hmm
pretty bad gains
I subscribed and donated for ads. This is outrageous
tired
You're hungry too
banana
wants vitamins
Please I need vitamins. Oh, you've been feeding me as bananas
That's just too much potassium and starch. You're killing me
Can I please get anything else?
He doesn't want fruits
He just wants to be nutritious. He wants a balanced meal
Please vitamins
Who's frustrated? Well, you'll be fine
Give him vitamins. I don't have vitamins
Okay, spyroid
It's time for you to rank up
You're not getting any ads. I'm not gonna do ads
For like the 40 people in chat that think this is funny 2 000 if you don't
Three minutes of ads
This is just like no contest here
94 85 chance to hit this
He didn't even belong here. That's why why can I just skip this league?
I'm not gonna run a straw poll
Hey, look you want an ad you really want an ad that bad just reload the page
You'll probably get one
That doesn't count
It's only 30 seconds. What the fuck
Why are you guys so accepting of like advertisements? Usually that's a thing that people don't want to see at all
Give us ads give us ads
Because your chat is fucking mental
They want the other 2 000 people to suffer
What a strange what a strange little figure he he doesn't know what?
He doesn't know
You guys don't you guys don't know shit. What are you talking about here? I know everything everything there is to know
If there's something to be known, I know it
Try me
sandbag
Uh, you actually no just rest
Now who gives a shit train?
The spyro is gonna just steamroll the whole thing anyways
How many houses are in the world?
Uh
That is uh, 642 941
in
The united states and they're what you gotta specify what country in the whole world
there's
742 million houses in the world not even close
Look it up one
One house for every 2 000 americans
Americans
One house for 2 000 people
90 don't have oh my god
That's a very big house
Hey, eat a fucking potato
That means this one house for most of the people in this chat
What did I say?
Don't be frustrated here. Well, you really are not focused at all
This is like the worst i've ever seen anybody not be focused
We're all watching you from the living room
All right, you want a cake?
All right. How about a cake?
No, you no cake
What about no, you know what fine you're gonna have to kick
Take the cake
There we go. What's this clip? I can't even hear it. Never mind. What's your dream house?
We've talked about my dream house. I think on stream before everybody's so frustrated. What the hell's going on here?
Yeah, we already talked about it. I want
A I want a huge bowling alley in my house and I want the bed
Like let's say there's 10 lanes
I want a like septuple king size california king bed in the middle
That takes up like four lanes. I want a bowling alley size bed
Yeah, and I want to cover the bed with like silk and grease
and I want to just do the
What was that thing that you just put in the backyard?
the
slip and slide
I want to have a slip and slide bed so I can run as fast as I can and slip and slide on the bed
And then just let me just keep going slide and then stop and fall asleep there
Yeah, we already talked about this
All right. You guys have seen the movie richie rich
What about the movie blank check?
You can see blank check
Let me go over the beginning of blank check and how insane and stupid of a movie that is
Blank check is a movie about a kid
that
Gets his bicycle run over by some criminal and like hits like runs the kid over
Guy gets out of the car and the kid's like what the heck my new bicycle and he's like
Quiet kid be quiet. Let me take care of this
Is it a bike? What's it gonna take and the kid's like freaking out about his bike and shit and the guy writes him a check
a blank check
And just signs it and gives it to him and the kid
Puts like a million dollars on the check and cashes it and gets the money
In a sense, apparently the banking system would just allow that
That's already I mean, I know it's i'm like i'm describing the movie
This is blank check is the name of the movie and he buys a bunch of fucked up shit
He buys like a bunch of crazy weird like richie rich style
Mansion weird stuff and then the criminals come after him now what a weird movie
So it's richie rich and home alone together kind of yeah
it's
i'm yeah somebody said i'm not even describing how insane the movie actually is yeah, but
Oh god, this is bad
You actually countered that shit
Yeah, it's called blank check
Highly recommended. Let's swap out here
Take them down. There it is. All right, bring it in the next one
head attack
Nope
Shit, this is bad
Come on
Thank you
All right now get him
He buys a house for hundreds of thousands in cash
Yeah, imagine that imagine like a fucking 11 year old
Buying a house in cash
Buying in cash
You know not that long ago. I wanted to buy a car
Like this is a while ago and I wanted to buy like just a cheap kind of used car from a dealership or something
And it felt really weird because I just wanted to buy the car like let's say it was like three or four grand for like
a shitty used car
Just I want to just give me like I want a different car
And like like talking to people about buying a car in cash
Is weird because they have like why
Um, because I just I can I think I want to I can do that. I think
Why are you doing that?
Because I don't want I don't want the bank to know why
But I don't care. I mean if the bank knows it's fine
Well, I can set you up with a good like interest rate like no
Just the word like buying x in cash always just sounds like wait a minute. Hold on. What do you mean buying this in cash?
Blank check has nine percent on rotten tomatoes
This
Everybody wants to like sign you up for like fucking credit
I get you good 16 like eight percent interest apr. That's good. So now robert spiro can now do this
Spire. Yeah, he's he needs to rest though
Take a rest today and then get ranked up
jerma put roberto in the femur breaker 9 000 or fuse him with
The corrupted spiral
What the fuck is the femur breaker 9 000?
What are you talking about that's so fucked up buy a car with bits
briefcase full of like
Cryptocurrency. Yeah, and how are you gonna pay him? We can sit with some finance. No, I've got this
You lift open the briefcase
It's like a bunch of those
novelty bitcoin gold plated bitcoins
It's like 41 dollars. All right, you're good
You have a dream car. You're thinking about tesla
No, I don't have a dream car I I just want a car that works and is easy to drive
No, I don't I don't drive manuals. No
I'm the type of person that gets behind the wheel of a manual
And would this would exactly what would happen? It would be fine. Everything would be going perfectly. Normally I would be good
Everything would be fine. Pull up to that red light slow it down a little
Okay
Now let's start up. I've done this like a hundred times. Let's keep going get it out of neutral clutch up
Put in first gear
Get into second gear and then accidentally put it in fourth gear
To that'll be 2,500 dollars, please i'm so stupid with that kind of shit man. I would fuck it up at some point I would
Nobody wants to hear your life story
I don't know why i'm thinking about this going to like a convenience store
Like oh, yeah, I want to pay uh put up like a fucking
Tootsie roll with a monster energy drink i'm gonna be paying in cash and you think it's like scary
What am I gonna feed him have a banana
Why why are you paying for this energy drink in cash?
What the fuck is this? Huh? Why would you get this buddy?
That's so fucking funny. It's not really but it just like is
All right, let's go to the
This dude's got like 20 in cash on him
Would that come from where'd you get that?
How did you get that much?
All right, let's get
Spyroid out of this like fucking wood rank already
Before I say other things that make no fucking sense
What are we gonna get rid of like the penny?
That's another one. Aren't we the only country on earth that still has like a one cent denomination in physical currency?
No, you know canada's the only country that got rid of it. Is that true?
Why are you still alive? Don't ruin this for me
Oh my god, I hate this game
He's gonna win. He's gonna win right here because of this don't do it again
I let you know, you know, I really would love somebody said i'd love like a 20 dollar coin
That'd be what kind of cool wouldn't it be to have like a hundred dollar coin?
You'd lose it. Well, you could lose a hundred dollar bill too and they still make those
It's heavier too
And plus if hey if that that hundred dollar bill gets stuck in your in your pockets or something and it gets in the laundry
That shit's all fucked up and it could be ripped up and destroyed
That coin is going to be fine
And yeah, why does it have to be?
You got why are you guys talking about like a quarter?
Why wouldn't if it was a hundred dollar coin, it would be the size of like a small like teacup
It would be like a rock
It'd be like a tea saucer. It would weigh like four pounds to make sure you couldn't lose it
a twenty dollar rock
Why not just have a hundred dollar rock? Yeah, that's what i'm saying. Like have a half a rock that's priced at a hundred dollars
Well, like i'll look at nostalgia like this is what they used to trade when they were cavemen
So like there's a nostalgia factor there
I didn't block that come on. So a diamond a diamond is a okay a four pound diamond
that was as big as a teacup would be like
a hundred and fifty million dollars
That's not a twenty dollar what?
Four pounds of gold would be very expensive too. No, just there's no material like cubric zirconium or something that could be like
100 bucks
and you just bring that to the grocery store and they pay for your
Pay for your sunny delight
Just replace
Replace the dollar with a full can of arizona iced tea
That's fucking awesome
Yeah, we got rid of the dollar. It's now the one dollar denomination is a can of arizona
What a pain in the ass imagine getting back like six dollar bills you get six cans of arizona iced tea
What a miserable experience
How the fuck are they able to still do that?
But it can't like think about that, but we've had this conversation. I'm having like deja vu
Why is arizona iced tea a dollar?
That's just like it's like a gallon of iced tea in there. Is it just water and then like syrup?
How come arizona iced tea is 99 cents and like the one next to it on the shelf is a dollar 80
for less iced tea
The strip club
It would be a bunch of fucking weirdos like like drinking their iced teas and like putting them on the table
You just look around the guys like counting their strip club money they got like fucking 40 arizonas in a backpack
That would be a mess
People would be accidentally dropping them and like they would be exploding and fizz would be going everywhere
A casino was just like you had to just open it and pour it in the machine
Those things are so heavy too
Going through the the turn the kiosk for like the toll
You just like whip out the window like fucking four arizona iced teas
out of the car
Oh, that's so fucking funny
Shit like that is just like yeah, I I love that shit
fucking absurd
Wishing wells. Yeah, there's just floating hundreds of floating arizona cans
arizona
Okay, I gotta take a break
Atm arizona tea machine. I gotta pee. I'm gonna grab an arizona iced tea. I'll be right back
Shall we? Oh, hey, yeah, I get grabbing tea beer back. But yeah, honestly, I don't I don't know how the arizona iced tea just must
I don't know how maybe they sell a lot which arizona did I get the watermelon one?
Green tea and honey. Oh
They have so many flavors too. How do you have that many flavors? You don't actually know what it is
Hey, this is for real. You know what? I've been doing lately. I've been
Like soda. No get out of here
Juice. No, no, no, no, no juice. Get it out of here. You want to like a little secret cut down on your sugar intake
Check it out. Ready? Listen to me. Take a glass of water
Right filtered water probably if you have it
So just water and put a little bit of ice in it take a buy lemon
Just get like a bag of lemons. It's like three or four dollars take one out roll it on the counter cut that shit in half
Get a little lemon squeezer a little like a little juicer
You know things like with the upside down cone and you go
The juice of a half lemon put that into the ice water, you know straight out if you want to and then add to that
Just one teaspoon of sugar
One teaspoon no more
Spin it around with a straw. Enjoy it one teaspoon and make your own easy
It's like it tastes much better than the lemonade you can buy at the store. Even the ones that are organic
They still load those things with shit
That's like that and if you don't want the sugar you don't have to add it
But I like having a little bit of sweetness to my lemonade
It is just lemonade. I know that what do you think this is a rocket scientific thing that i'm describing
Just squeeze half a lemon of juice
Into a glass of water with a little teaspoon of sugar stir it up. That's a healthy alternative
to like
Monster or even like a orange juice. It's light. It's refreshing. It gets the bowels moving
I'm serious now. That's a good thing
Everything is a healthy replacement to monster. You know, that's probably true
I you know, probably smoking cigarettes is probably a healthy alternative to drinking monster
All right, who's got a tournament you are in d now, right? Good. Let me see the schedule
All right, so you are here now. We can do one two three and bring you up
Three of these in a row
And then the official tournament is here
I can't sign up for it yet. All right, what about you?
Roberto has one more tournament
in s
Already signed up for it and then the official cup is here. Hopefully we can no it's not it's a group battle
Don't die before this
Fuck I have to go find the stupid explorers
Blood is a healthy drink. I've been feeling a lot better since I started replacing soda with blood
Is that some kind of new like energy drink or something?
That's got to be some
Really interesting marketing campaign, right? I'm surprised no one's done that yet if that's not true
Have it be like thick and red and like have a weird sugary flavor to it with a bunch of like b vitamins
Monster blood. Why have they not done that? Okay, that's fine. You should rest here
rest and then
I gotta look at stats here
Terrible life. I gotta work on life right now life and speed
That just they're just awful or life and defense i'm gonna get speed at least that's abysmal
There's speed here
Get on that trampoline
Then you can rest
You doing why then you can chill
You can rest
You can do sandbag you can
do
uh accuracy
Well, that was a huge gain for improver. I miss being back sonic. I think we all do
but
His legacy lives on
I think you deserve the salmon. Yeah, you do. We gotta get you up
Frustrated why you don't like fish? Oh, no that wrong person is Roberto alive. Yeah, Roberto still alive tired though
What a character but that's Roberto salmon
He used them before he expires
I will
I'm saving before every week in case he dies
Then i'm just gonna reload and then put him on ice
Get the dragon up. Are they friends?
What how I gotta get them to be good friends
That's breeder info. I mean they're good friends, but I want to be great friends
I gotta take them on an adventure
All right
You're who cares?
wisdom
Where the hell's the doll there is?
Very lively today
Okay, let's see
dead
All right, we got
Uh more tournaments here in a row
Rest and then let's get you on speed
Two speed that's two speeds in a row
And then let's get you on
health
You need it bad. You just it's like a guy this big
Rest trampoline life blade life blade
Maybe even rest here. Yeah, just rest here
And you are gonna rest
sandbag rest
Book book rest good
Rest rest rest
i'm tired
Now i'll put you under
Target, okay
Bad
Arizona iced tea. Okay, you're doing good. You are okay
Let's praise you
You got a big tourney coming up before you die
That's so sad, but it's true. All right spiroid clean it up
My toilet water tastes like I can't drink sweet tea
Sweet tea hurts
If I drink sweet tea, I feel bad. My body hurts
I'm wearing the pumpkin goggles
pumpkin vr
But you you see sometimes I understand I like having things sweet. I like sugary stuff, right?
I like drinking soda. Sometimes I like
Uh, I like sweetened things. I like sugary things cakes ice cream, right?
But you really get to know somebody you get to see who they are who they truly are
when they order a tea from a restaurant
And watch how much sugar they put into their iced tea
You really they can tell you anything they want about themselves. You'll know exactly who they are. I see some people
For like an unsweetened tea that they get from ice from the restaurant
They put in
like 10 sugar packets
What's going on there? Why what's what's going on there? Why you what's going on? Why are you doing that?
too much
10 that's rookie numbers
They're okay. Uh, like the coffee is another uh situation here, right?
there were the order like I
And if you're one of these people then it's uh, that's it's all right to be one of these people
but just be careful
i'm not telling you how to drink coffee, but
a double double
double cream double sugar
Be careful
You end up it's like you're drinking
Ice cream. It's milk and sugar
double double double cream double sugar in a regular coffee
And when I say regular i'm talking if you go to like dunkin donuts
They're regular already like a regular iced coffee from dunkin. I believe has four or five teaspoons. I think tablespoons of sugar
easy
You work with someone who drinks four times four
Just be careful
That's so much
That's an insane amount of sugar
unprover
Well, I don't care if you drink coffee black or if you drink coffee with double double
But if you're gonna order like a ultra quad
Just order an ice cream
It's probably better
Do you tell people that when you have coffee with them be careful
Yeah, i'll take a a quad quad 15 sugar, uh
half cream
Be careful
You're you can rest and then life play tomorrow. You can sandbag and then rest
You read a book and then rest you doing target practice. That's fine. You are gonna do the life thing
22 hell, holy shit
Oh, there goes jeremy again
Telling me how to eat things and how to live my life. There he goes again
Just have a mango classic jeremy
Fish is bad. What did they say?
Fish is bad. What the he's so okay. Let me help you
Here have a melon. No
Not a melon a mango
Those things like a thousand dollars, aren't they?
God damn it. I wanted to give him a fucking mango. They both had the same
starting letter
He loved it. Yeah, and i've been completely not caring about anything he's doing
Just go buy more. I know but it was like two it was like a that's an expensive piece of food for somebody
I don't care about
Yeah, that was a pretty that's a major overreaction. That was like I just rolled off the cliff in fucking demon souls
And yes, I said demon souls. That's my favorite one
Oh shit a thousand iced teas down the drain
Bloodborne is my favorite from software game demon souls is my favorite souls game
Hmm thinking face
Bloodborne is a souls game though
I'm, sorry, uh demon souls dark souls dark souls two dark souls three
bloodborne
souls
Counter
Oh fuck he's gonna lose
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I pay attention here
Got it
Almost blew that one. I almost blew that one. I almost lost to the sheep. All right corn gold
We were just talking about corn syrup and then here he is
Terrible worthless shitty opponent one hit kill, but yeah, my favorite souls
Sekiro born is bloodborne. No, why don't we just say what do you at this point? It's not gonna happen
Okay. Okay. I get souls born. I get dark souls souls like
But at this point, it's just a from software game
Like just what's your favorite from software game?
His his health is so bad that it's gonna make me lose this tournament
Real i'm dead get it. Oh
Yes
I swear to god man. Why is that in this game?
Fucking final guts. What's the point of that? It's all it does is just it that's just not why
All right. Well, that's a wake-up call there. I get to just spam health and intelligence tons of help
I countered with circle on that one
No spyroid victory
Reaction reactions
Let me take a look at his
bullshit
107 health
212 intelligence. Okay
His accuracy is fine. It's just the life defense and speed are abysmal. I'm gonna get health to over
800 now we do get to 200 health
Before anything else because that's just gonna that's killing me
He does have up a 200 iq
So you can use that funny
video on demand live broadcasting meme here
so
life blade rest life blade
Take it. Yeah, I want you to be good
You have a tournament here. Can you do it?
There's a tournament now with you
Go somebody you live from germa's basement
Here we are live
Here take a carrot
You like these?
Thank you
Don't tell me how to live my life
I'm not telling you how to live your life
I'm just telling you to be careful
Never once did I say you should not
Do don't put that much sugar in your coffee. Did I say that? I never said that
I said to be careful
That's different than
Don't do not right?
It's a threat. What is not what are you talking about? What?
What are you saying here?
Who why can I not select you?
No my god
The person on the trampoline
You aggressively told us to make lemonade for 10 straight minutes
I did I did I did not aggressively tell you to make lemonade
I was aggressively describing my lemonade procedure
It's a shitty lemonade. Um, all right. I didn't even tell you the next part would add a little bit of basil in it
I was cut off by the screams
You guys like you
That makes it sound basil
Basil, it's fine. What's wrong with lemon and basil?
You guys are angry at one of the best combos
Basil and lemon
Have you ever had basil lemon ice cream before? What do you mean? Oh my goodness. Now I am gonna get angry
Lemon and basil is an incredible combination
What is happening to my character right now? Why they suck now?
Why do you suck?
That's bad. Got it. All right, I see one swing. What's what's the swing at?
63 no
Don't count on this. Thank god
I am the victory
They they disagree with your beverage preferences. It's basil and lemon
They go together
Like two peas in a pod
early
That's a pretty good german 985 name
mint idiot
Okay, next you'll be asking me to squeeze toothpaste in it
disgusting
disgusting next
Ha ha ha
They go together like peanut butter and mayonnaise. All right, you know what i'm i'm gonna put this to bed right now
lemons and basil
lemon and basil lemonade
Put the lemon basil sugar and zest in a bowl
Muddle this mixture until the basil is well bruised and the sugar is mixed in transfer to a pitcher add the lemon juice and water
And stir refrigerate allowing the basil and zest to infuse more flavor at least an hour
Basil lemonade basil lemonade recipe fresh basil lemonade basil lemonade recipe all these five stars lemon basil lemonade
Five stars bayman bayman loves to resonate
Five stars basil lemon recipe five stars all of them have five stars
Every single one of them you find me. Oh my goodness. We're done with that. I don't need to talk about it anymore
What do you mean fake? What's with all the deleted messages because they disagree with the streamer
What about lemon and basil ice cream? It's fantastic. I'm serious. You have to just try it. That was 426 damage
Oh my god
I super killed that guy
It's not disgusting. I'll tell you what's disgusting. Oh lemon basil ice cream is disgusting. I'll tell you what's disgusting
Would you like to know? Yeah. Hey, let's talk about it
what do you put yeah stuff like a bunch of chocolate chunks and fudge brownies and
And Reese's in my ice cream
Hey, you know what? I want to put a bunch of cookie dough in it lemon basil
Excuse me
What is this a bird?
What the fuck was that?
That was a hand puppet. That was a bird hand puppet
What the fuck was that thing?
What about vanilla ice cream with honey and marshmallows i'll allow that
Okay, no i'll allow that lol that
Lemon basil is a boomer flavor until you try it
And then you're gonna secretly you'll be you'll come back in the chat. You'll be like
But secretly gonna be that was fucking really good i'm just maiming in the chat now
Holy shit, he turned into an airplane. Oh god. Okay. Thank god. It didn't hurt that much
What do you get lemon basil ice cream?
You you organic you grow it yourself
Got it. All right bongo
Flour and heen
Just grow the lemons and grow the basil
Churn your own ice cream buying ice cream from the store
Next you'll tell me that you go to the freezer aisle and you buy ice cream from there
Fuck you fuck off driving by here jerma makes ice cream from his own breast milk
That's so fucked up, uh, I can't even
I mean
Why does he read the gross comments, I don't know because they stick out because that's really absurd
You had the option to stop mint sentences. No, I don't
I have
forward
Or backward. I don't have stop
Let's hear backwards
Um
I told you guys to lay off with the whole lemon basil thing. I mean, come on
I'm trying to make lemon basil lemonade basil lemonade from scratch, but I can't figure out how to invent the universe
We just put you just that's what a joke
What a jokey thing?
blank
So we have okay, so okay, so we have
A few things to do here. Okay, so we got a few things
All right guys, so we can all right what we're gonna do here. Let's think about okay so we can do
Yeah, you can rest. Yeah book target tub
Rest and you have the tournament today. Don't fuck it up
good increase
Good increase
I made up the whole thing of lemon basil ice cream. I did not
I'm running out of food
Here have a banana
Never had a lemon lemon's probably my favorite fruit
I just like lemon juice
I like lemon zest
Lemon can is is an incredibly versatile thing
Mario and zelda are gonna work with labo vr. Oh, that's gonna be fun
Need a lemon on stream. No lemons the best fruit that you don't eat
It's used in so many things, but you don't actually eat lemons
It's kind of weird how that works
What do you mean you do?
You guys like cut a lemon in half and like eat the fruit out like a grapefruit or like an orange
I don't believe anybody that's saying that none of you. I just really don't believe that at all
You're gonna fuck up like your stomach acid. Yep. Be careful
All right, we got a single battle with spyroid. Just can you do it this time and actually win?
That's like saying eating a pickle fucks you up. What?
Lemon lemon juice straight is insanely acidic
Pickles are pickled. I don't believe it. What's my opinion on limes?
Yeah, they're like the jokey side character next to a lemon
Lemon's the main character plus lime also kind of tastes like throw up. So this guy this character sucks
What's wrong with this guy
He can't land anything and his moves don't hurt. I just gotta keep him away from tournaments
No, I actually I love lemons and I love limes not I don't like limes as much limes are good on food
More than lemons for me like a squeeze of lime
Adds a lot more. I lost four fans. Well, that's what happens. You lose two tournaments in a row
And there's the backtrack. No, I said, okay, but fine. I'm not gonna backtrack it. I don't like limes
They're only good when you squeeze it on like a piece of meat or something
That's 90 of their use. Yeah, but i'm talking about i'm talking pure just flavor eating a lime versus eating
lemon, but I would rather you fill a
like a tub of
No, I don't think I would no, I can't I wouldn't do that either way. So
I never had limeade. Yeah, I have it just it tastes it's too sour for me
limeade versus lemonade limeade has that weird
super
Like puckery aftertaste
Lemonade does not
All right, please just do life in defense. Just don't do anything else
Just life over and over again
Strawberry lemon, I love strawberry lemonade
It's really good
Cherry limeade i've never had that before that sounds pretty good
Maybe one day i'll find it
All right, you need to rest you're frustrated
rest
target saying ah rest you're all like
You're all fucked up
Cherry limeade is good
I'll have to try it. I've never had cherry limeade. Do I live under a rock?
I don't think i've ever had cherry limeade before
If I have I didn't really
I didn't go holy shit and remember it
Favorite flavor of red bull none of them I drank one
I drank like two of them three weeks ago and had the worst migraine i've ever had in probably the last five years
So I I stopped
Is there in none of the above?
Just drink one
Yeah, I didn't drink like three
I had one and then I had one the next day
I didn't just slam them
Be careful
Okay, you're lively you're fine. You don't need to eat anything you could
Everyone's doing just fine
You're fine
You're fine. Everyone's good to go. Keep going
There's a way to make lemonade sweet without sugar just add it. That's not that's disgusting
I love mayonnaise, but I think it only belongs in certain things for me
Did you wait? Did you say he loves mayonnaise?
Right
He puts mayo on like a turkey sandwich
Yeah, it's fantastic actually and don't even throw this nonsense at me for miracle whip that stuff
is
Unedible it's unedible
It tastes like poison miracle whip tastes to me like what poison tastes like if I've ever had it
And this is in my personal opinion. I'm not i'm just saying I don't really like okay. I gotta be careful here
Just be careful
No to be completely fair though miracle whip actually is pretty good
In certain recipes where it replaces mayonnaise and it tastes better but on a sandwich though
That's a yuck
He's wrong
That's not a backtrack. I just still I just said yuck
He's spineless. No, I just said it was I think it's yucky
Guy don't ever have an opinion on the internet. Someone will throw a drink in your face
Sorry, the only way i'm allowed to have an opinion on miracle whip
Is if I go to like a mayonnaise reddit and we like talk about how bad it is
Is there no, that can't be what am I saying? There probably has to be all right. I like everyone's
schedules here
sandbag book tub
target lightweight
I'm honestly surprised that there's an active batman arkham reddit than a mayonnaise one
What japanese mayo is that japanese mayo is fucking amazing
it is
Unbelievable
If you've never had japanese mayo before
You gotta get it
Isn't mayonnaise just
whipped oil and eggs
Don't tell anybody that
I said you just I don't know where you got that secret recipe from but what the fuck man
I'm gonna have to delete this pod
Fuck, I I can't believe somebody actually just said that
Aioli is next level. Yeah, like a garlic aioli
You guys are gonna make me want a sandwich
Oh, you know, I don't know why but for right now, I don't know what it was
I somebody said the word like garlic and then mayonnaise and then sauerkraut came in my mind
And then like swiss cheese popped up and then pastrami showed up
And then thousand island dressing just showed up too with toasted rye bread and now I want that
I want I want a pastrami sandwich right now
I want a ruben
Or it could be just pastrami doesn't matter with mustard. Maybe
hmm
Damn swiss cheese is bad. Come on. That's not true
Thousand island is shit
Guys food is more subjective than like art or comedy. You know that right?
Think about how many stand-up comics you've seen that you were like, oh those jokes weren't funny multiply that by 500 million types of food
All right, everyone's good. I think it's the tournament right now, right? There are so many kinds of food
Group battle. This is not
I don't have anybody up here. I need to do the stupid find the
guy in the forest
Yeah, the amount of food combinations you can make
There's
So many of them
There's as many types of foods as there are houses
at least
Do you like uh gyros? I do
I do love gyros. They're amazing
chicken gyro
No competitions just train and send people to the dungeon whatever the hell it is
I look I like we talked about this already
I've
There's a bunch of i've had a ton of delicious
gyros
Gyros every time I order one I get corrected on the phone
I've ordered a gyro from probably 15 different establishments and I say it I say
Yeah, can I get a chicken gyro, please?
Uh chicken gyro. Yeah. Yeah, that's the one I then call another place
Hey, can I get a chicken gyro, please?
a chicken
Gyro
Yeah. Yeah, that's the one. Yes, of course. What's happening every time so it doesn't
What am I supposed to do
From my understanding it's like euro, right like euro
Like gyro are they just fucking with me on the phone?
So I am saying it correctly, but but how come I get corrected on the phone?
Like I like hey, I'll take one. I'll take one chicken gyro, please
Okay, one chicken gyro like almost like they're underhandedly correcting me and I'm like, yeah
All right. What we got for you. Let's do more life blade life blade life blade
You are going to do power
I forget about adrock
I don't care about this guy at all. I I don't want to even put him on the ranch anymore
But i'm gonna level him up a little so he has friends
All right, you rest and then we'll get you on the
Book again
Tons of power. That's a good life increase. I'm just gonna keep i'm gonna spam life on spirid
Uh, yeah, I could I could go for like a corned beef sandwich right now
You're good
Who's not having who's having a rough time here? Oh you okay?
What about avocado toast?
Yeah, I mean I
Avocado toast is man. I'd put an egg on it. That's just for me. You know, I don't order it but sometimes it's available
Like a poached egg or a nice like cooked egg on top
That's vegan. Well, that's not what I mean a vegan food. What do you mean?
I just told you I put an egg on it
I need to win
All right, he's dead
He'll be dead real soon. I gotta be
Uh
How do I pronounce caramel?
It depends on the day
Caramel caramel caramel caramel
I don't know. It just depends
You're all good
continue
Save it. Did I save it? Just do it again
Caramel
Okay. Well, I need to look at stats because unprover has seriously gained 20 in
A couple of categories more than four or five times. Let me see this. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What are you doing?
What are you doing? Stop shaking around. What the fuck is this? Hey
Hey
What is this doing this for?
What are you doing?
Uh, why are you doing this? This is weird. My shit's like getting all fucked up
Uh, this might be like a bug in the game. Not necessarily the hardware I have
Okay, that was weird
Now that was a game. That was a bug in the game
Strange. Anyways, what was I doing? I was looking at it over here
Joke incoming? No. No, I just
I
It's just that screen
Don't ask me why the hell that happens on
This own why are you doing? It's probably the winter. Um, I'd really love to look at the stats
Apparently not though
Well, I was gonna have to try tomorrow
I'm out of food. Fuck. I'm out of food
I thought the disc was fucking up at first. Yeah
Uh, I need I gotta feed you something beef
You're not gonna want that beef though. I don't think
I have five beef. Why am I playing this?
This is I like this game
Will you eat, uh
chocolate
Here have a chocolate you liked it good
All right, you're gonna have to wait
You're gonna have to eat something here, too
You can have a beef too
What's a food combo you like that nobody else likes?
I like cut up cucumber and cold hot dogs with hot sauce and lemon juice
well
I'll tell you one of my favorite things in the world
I'm, not sure I ever talked about this before but let's talk about it now
I love
nice firm crispy french fries
I dip them
in tuna
Like tuna fish
If I have fries in a tuna sandwich or something
I'm talking about the mayo whipped up tuna fish sandwich type tuna
And dip fries in it
And it's it's really good. It tastes great. It's got a lot going on there
Yeah, like tuna salad like a tuna fish that's mixed in like a the kind of tuna fish you order in a sub or you put on a sandwich
Also on top of that pretzel
uh, if you do
One of the my favorite snacks was just make a bunch of tuna take like a one or two cans of tuna
Whip it up with the mayonnaise add a little sprinkle a little bit of fucking basil in there
Don't do that. But you know, i'm making a joke reference to the last like four or five hours of talking
And just dip pretzels like hard pretzels into the tuna fish and eat it
I'm serious like that's it's fantastic
another thing
Weirdly enough this and this isn't a staple. I know but not this way
if you take a hard pretzel, like if you go get a bag of pretzels from the grocery store, whatever
and
uh american cheese
Just slices of american cheese
Take one slice of american cheese take a bite of the pretzel
And then take a little bit of the american cheese and put it in your mouth and eat it
At the same time the combination of those two things
Is godlike
It is absolutely godlike
You have to try it
Normal cheese. No, it's it's it's got to just be like
american cheese
Don't melt it
To see that the flavor doesn't make any sense. It's a perfect flavor combination
You could do you could do it with cheddar too. You could but i'm just giving you my recommendation
You could do that with pretty much any cold sliced cheese
I wouldn't do it with swiss
cheddar american
Provolone provolone is amazing with this exact technique
In fact, I'd probably recommend provolone and the hard pretzel over american cheese and hard pretzel
And that's fine. Everybody can say what they want. I'm just telling you that's it tastes so good together
It is a secret technique
Pretzels and cheese together. Yeah, but people when people eating pretzels and cheese
They typically it's not just like a sliced deli cheese
And biting hard pretzel pretzels and cheese is a big baked pretzel with a cheese dipping sauce not the same
It does not taste the same. It's incredibly different. Trust me
I'm gonna open up my own fucking restaurant tuna and french fries
Sliced provolone cheese and hard pretzels that I bought from the grocery store
Basil lemonade ice cream. Let's get some mangoes
You'd be out of business in minutes. I disagree
Oh
Yeah, like 300 bucks for a uh watermelon
I have to replace it
It's a you unless but wait what I got plenty of beef still. Let's just get a couple more of them
Grab a few bananas
And be on our way
I wouldn't be able to even beat diner dash
Why would I play diner dash?
Diner dash is the type of game that your mom accidentally downloaded in a virus facebook website and she's still playing it for some reason
But that's fine
Because it's good
But that's I can't backtrack that one, but you know, that's fine
Fuck oh
Hey somebody needs to give a lot of money
50 bucks from kxc 5000 bits. Thank you
Thank you for the 50 dollars 5000 bits loving the monster rancher streams germa
These games are comfy as fuck. No lie
Yeah, I love playing games like this
because we could just sit here and just
Talk shit about whatever we want and just have anything we want any topic can be rifled out here
It doesn't matter. We just talk about anything
Half the things we're saying aren't even real but still fun
It's just comfy game
But thank you for the 50 dollars 5000 bits kxc
insane contributions
Play animal crossing when the new one comes out i'll play it
I'm gonna but by the way that stream title is gonna be
trying not to rage
At animal crossing like and then like in parentheses like death counter
Okay, you're gonna rest and then we'll do life training
stack health
You can do
Target
You can rest
You're he's probably so close to death and I didn't even get to a rank
Because i'm supposed to take
Uh, I think i'm gonna bring him in to the jungle and try to get that next rank to unlock the new monsters. I have to try
Yeah, everybody rest up. We're taking the strong. We're gonna take Roberto
spiroid and blossom
into the
Forest not the forest the jungle has to be done
And then we have to combine
I need at least to get to a rank before I move on from this game
You know like I have to at least unlock a rank
What an accomplishment that would be
Okay jungle
Let's bring Roberto
And spiroid and blossom
These are the ones that are doing well here. Let's just say this is a good place to look at stats
Pretty balanced across the board life intelligence and accuracy
Actually really balanced across the board
You are like better than
spiroid
64 to 12
I don't balanced
Look at the power on Roberto
He's at almost 500 power. I have to get him in the next tournament before he dies
All right, let's go
I should start a lunchables restaurant. How long do you think it would take?
So if I opened up a restaurant called like germa's food or welcome to the restaurant
What doesn't matter whatever the fucking placeholder name can be
How long would it take if I were to buy a bunch of frozen dinners and shit
Like stuff from the grocery store unpackage it like heat it up and like pretend and put it on the menu and all that
How long would it take for someone to figure out that I wasn't making this food a few hours? I don't think so
If I went to the frozen section
And picked out like like like hungry man
And plated it so it looked really nice
It would probably take a little while
Oh, I have a burger on the menu and it's just the frozen patty from the grocery store and I just I put like
Kale on it and shit. I put like a nice little garlic sauce on it and I don't think people would know
That's literally what they do
Microwaving a tv dinner and then putting it and presenting it a different way on a plate
and calling it like
chicken a la carte
and it's like the
kid cuisine
Fried chicken
I really think would take a couple months before somebody figured it out. I worked at a restaurant for three years. We did that
people actually doing that
With blue pudding
Yeah, like the shitty little
Square brownie thing that they have
That's on there too
The brownie that is the whole it's like a well
And it's supposed to be a brownie, but it's just a well of chocolate cake mix
Corn that's half frozen eating it uncooked is the best
I've never done that
Like the you go, okay
You would be able to figure it out really really quickly if it was a kid. Okay. Remember the Lunchables pizzas
Imagine ordering a pizza from a restaurant and the Lunchables pizza comes out
That would be a bad business move. It would have to be stuff that would be easily hideable
For see
Yeah, you wouldn't be able to get away with the
Lunchables deli meat stack circle things
It would have to be
the chicken nuggets
Kid cuisine lean cuisine type stuff
the turkey dinner
They put the three or four slabs of turkey in the gravy. You could get away with that if you presented it correctly
a jack in the chow
Is this a fight? I think this is like a minute like a hidden. Okay
I can't counter. He missed it kill him in one hit
All right. What is it? What do I get?
What's the point of that? Did you get anything?
nothing
All right
It's just a mimic. I don't remember the last time I had
one of those
like thanksgiving dinner
microwaved lean cuisine esque
tv dinners
Was it good? I don't remember
All I have in my mind anytime. I think of one of these tv dinners
Is the taste
of low quality gravy
That's it. No other flavor comes to mind just
kind of watery low quality gravy
And i'm talking not even for the thanksgiving one. I'm talking even for the fried chicken one
Who can dig?
Which one of them can dig?
Of plant plants aren't even here
Stouffer's
Yeah stouffer's stouffer's does have
Sort of just one flavor doesn't it?
All I think of is stuffing gravy taste
I'm thinking of the macaroni and cheese and I all I think of is gravy stuffing
Stouffer's is just oven flavor
Why do I know what that means?
I know what you mean by that. I understand what you're saying
It's oven flavored
macaroni and gravy
Would you guys like to know what the best macaroni and cheese is?
I can tell you the best store macaroni and cheese
No, and it is not the yellow earwax mac and cheese. It's not that one. I'm not gonna say the name
king's fist
The best macaroni and cheese from the store that you can possibly buy this cracker bread
If you don't believe me try the cracker barrel challenge
It is the best
That you can possibly buy
I do not take that lightly
Is this stream sponsored? No, this stream tells you real things that the stream believes
None of this is paid for if you don't if you never had it before just try it next time
Next time you're at the store or the grocery store if it carries it
Just try it
Make it on the stove. You have to make it on the stove
Try it come back
And tell me that that was not in your top three
grocery store mac and cheese
If it was not in your top three grocery store mac and cheeses
Then I will remove you from the channel I will get you ip banned from my channel I will remove your
Name, I will make sure that the name never pops up again
Now I will respect your opinion
but
grunt
Cracker barrel is my favorite. It's number one. It's my favorite. It's in my pantry right now. Please don't ban me
We don't have crappy us mac and cheeses over here mac and cheese is like as
Us american as you could possibly get
mac and cheese is
American. Whoa
When am I gonna go on hot ones?
I'm not fucking cool enough to go on hot ones guys
I don't have enough clout to go on hot ones. What are you talking about?
I can't go on hot ones guys. I don't have an instagram
I would have to make an instagram and take a picture today and just post it there
I can't fly over that
So today we're going to be talking about what it's called what's happened in that pic and it seems that you have this instagram
Picture here. We're going to go back to 2018 2019. What is this? What happened here?
I made that account like four days ago
And I took the picture because I knew that you were going to ask me a question about an instagram picture and I
That's the only one I got. It's me smiling
uh
With a like a just like a gray backdrop behind it
All right, man. Well, thanks for coming out here for hot ones
I actually like that show. It's not bad
How well would I do? I would do very well in that show. I wouldn't have any milk wouldn't have any water
I would be completely fine
I would be perfectly fine
It says the guy with digestive problems. So no, I mean I later I wouldn't be but I wouldn't I wouldn't be like
I'd be fine
Where's the milk?
That wouldn't happen. I'd be okay. What's going on with the internet here? Oh no
Are we good? They have a hot ones. How come they don't have a cold ones?
It starts off you drink like a room temperature water
And eventually it gets to like ice cream popsicles and then you get to like
nitrogen
They do have that
Everybody okay
I know everyone's really obsessed with hot hot sauce on their food, right? Hot hot hot
Yeah, yeah, but let me get some hot sauce on that sandwich. Let me get some hot
Franks red hot whatever right? Is there a reason why people aren't like nitrogen infusing their green beans?
Why does it not go the other way? Why is it only hot because you can get hurt with nitrogen
You can get hurt with hot sauce too. You eat like a hot
California whatever it is a reaper
People have like gone to the hospital because of that shit
Spicy is a flavor cold is not that's true. But how come somebody hasn't invented?
Like in a lab somewhere like cold as like a condiment. I can't keep that up. I'm sorry. There's only so far I can go
Menthol
Why are you not putting menthol on your french fries?
Yeah, mint is cold spice that's true
menthol mac and cheese
I
You might be onto something there. Oh a spicy italian sausage. No menthol italian sausage
That would be actually gross
That's some real hipster shit
No, I even I can't continue to talk about that shit white pot
I have to draw the line at like
We're just talking shit at menthol sausages
Can I please find this so I can level up my characters and do another?
Come on
Before the stream ends we need to see
wind lore
Spyroid can't obtain any more traits
Abandoned wind lore. Uh-oh. What how do I remove a trait?
Remove wind lore
Inferno
Okay, good thing. I just did that
Because I use fire on that character all the time
I just want to do
The next tournament, but I have to find the lost people here
So Roberto can one shot the boss and we can go and move on with our lives
Come on. Why is everybody freaking out?
Why are you freaking out?
I got Roberto here. He's got just 500 attack power
And he's level 13
Earth lore. He doesn't know
He doesn't know
Neither do you
What's the percentage of the people that have even played this game before that are here?
Don't ever get rid of lore
Bingo
I'm doing 250 to 500 damage a swing
And that's not even with my big move
And that's just pressing x
Okay, blossom. What do you got?
Ruby, that's it. How much longer till Roberto dies of old age? Very soon
So i'm saving the game
at every point that i'm pretty much allowed to save
and
When he dies, we're going to rewind time
And we're going to freeze him and fuse him probably with dragon
Maybe you can call it. Yeah, you can call me scum if you want. That's fine. You can call me scum
Can you speak like courage the cowardly dog courage? Does doesn't courage not talk?
Doesn't he only just go like
That's pretty much all he does right
Oh, he talked to the camera. That's true
I don't even kind of
I can't really place where his voice sounds like
I got cute and it's gonna be bad
Sorry, I just wanted to do 300 plus damage
We'll do it again. I'm gonna do as hard as I can
48 guts watch this
That's it
courage the cowardly dog
on courage
the cowardly dog show
Stop
Stop. I just want to get to the end
stop
Stop this
Don't stop 290. It's not enough
Everybody gets final guts with me
Nice good follow-up
Did I see the episode of dexter's lab when they swear?
I don't think so
I don't think i've seen that
Did somebody search this?
Somebody can here, right?
Lawson can search, right?
Investigate what's in there?
Okay, I don't want anyone to panic but
I just took a sip out of my coffee
And there was something solid that I just swallowed
That was weird
I think I just I think I swallowed chicken bone. Look there's a chicken bone in my coffee
Don't you hate it when you have chicken bones in your coffee?
This sucks. I don't want to look around here anymore
You just drank up a spider
My brother told me this the only reason why I think about this and my brother told me a story
About how he did that. Oh, I can't even think about it
Oh god, okay. I'm gonna I can I even tell the story. It's so fucked up. It's just horrible
Well, it's making me like shiver
So, all right, if you're queasy about spiders and shit mute the stream for like five minutes
All right. Here we go. Three two one. Hey, what's going on guys? Welcome to the video. My name's jim. I got a story for you here
Uh in the background is gonna be some monster rancher four
And it got me thinking at this one time
That my brother told me the story
About how when he sucked up a spider through his straw
and
I'll tell it for you. Here we go
so, uh
my brother
Made coffee. It's like the similar situation. Oh my god. Did I do that?
Yeah, he made coffee in his coffee maker, which I did
And he had a glass and ice and coffee
And he was drinking his coffee
and he slurped up a
Super big solid object
And he like spit it out
And it was a huge spider
And he freaked out but I may have swallowed it. I don't even want to think about that. I hate the unknown
Stuff like that
Anytime something like that happens. You just don't know
Well, what the hell was that? What could that have been?
Don't worry tomorrow. You'll have powers
Ooh, this is a tobita c
Okay
Okay, this is the building chat was talking about they said he doesn't know
God i've got the all-powerful roberto with his one hit kill moves
I can't wait to get a pastrami sandwich
thunder lore
Abandoned thunder lore
Zap I got a tablet. Hold on. What how can I remove?
Lore or something what's going on here? I have to keep all these
seriously, why
Do I have to have all these?
I can't remove them 4c
What's the point of having all these traits if you just it fills a list and then you you're stuck
Local boomer can't read. No, I know I can I can remove them or not remove them
But let me can I just take the ones I don't want off?
Not at the menu where I learned them. You can remove them at the ranch then god
Uh-oh
Thank god, this is the thing that fucked it up last time
Didn't have roberto though
All right. Come on internet. Stop it. You're starting to make me angry
I think this is the last place
This is a jaguar
Thank god. I've got roberto. He's
unstoppable
Get to a rank
How long is this game? It's kind of never ending
I don't think the game ends
It's the seventh floor of this jungle
If you finish s rank it ends
I'm, not sure i'm going to be able to do that because roberto is going to die
And then i'm going to have a new monster to try to play around with
Okay. Yeah, you can unmute. Yeah unmute
Lifestyle, okay cool tablets more tablets
Beat the game dump ass
To get s rank you need to fuse two a ranks
So I have to get hold on so I need to fuse two a rank. So I have to get roberto to a rank
fuse him
with
the dragon get the dragon to a
Fuse two people together and get those two a fuse them together and then bring those two
to s
Oh god, kraikin just came in with a raid. Hello everybody
kraikin raid
Thanks a lot kraikin. Hope you had a good stream
Not sure what you planned, but I hope it was fun
Welcome everybody
Oh god, i'm gonna die. Don't die. It'll actually kill him if he dies
No, don't counter it. Oh, this is bad
No
Three hp bring out somebody else anybody anyone. I don't care who it is
This will kill him. He'll die
Come on not they not a new audience coming in just kill them
Oh, this is fucking horrible
All of a sudden everybody doesn't want to do any moves
You see this?
Thank god. We're playing monster rancher 4. This is a game where you breed monsters
You put cds in
And it pulls a random seed
And you can fuse them together. You can mess around with dna. It's pretty interesting
And we can't go that way. I do not want you in the front now
Oh my god, why are we getting so many of these random encounters?
They're increased exponentially
Sorry, this thing sucks
No, it doesn't I gotta do a different move
Where's my bite?
bullish
Bullish come on grave throw bullish again. Come on
Just hit it
Just let me end this encounter. I need to find these people here
God my god
Please
Uh, this is really bad
There's a group of people on an expedition that I have to find down here and for some reason
This won't let me leave this area
This is bad. Don't counter it. Thank god
Kill him on 97 damage. That's it
All right, that's a double team move. You should die from this. Yeah
Unless you knew he has a clip explaining who he is
out of context
This looks way harder than it was last time
I can't even go this way
Uh, it's
I don't know if it's harder than it was last time. There's a lot of new mechanics
That the game has thrown in
these counters
can sometimes be pretty
Uh bullshit, but
Why are you looking all these?
Are you trying to scare everybody away? All right, i'm gonna pull Roberto back. No, i'm not
Like
Now I might have to
This dragon's defense is so bad. His health is so bad
That was the luigi side running move from smash brothers
Your whole team is shit
All we need is one character to do anything good
Somebody just has to get to a rank
And then we fuse them
With somebody else that's their friend
This has taken a long time. I'm on the seventh floor. How long have I been in here for?
30 40 straight minutes
Can't go this way
100 years
Switch back to Roberto. I mean if I can get the damage here
Uh, maybe not
I'd like to have you level up
Come on grab him. All right
Fine switch it up
Don't want him to kill
All right, bring in Roberto
You want to play that game?
Don't let the spider bite your stomach. I added that somebody just said bite you
I miss wall-e
Everybody misses wall-e
But the problem is wall-e unfortunately was not very good
So we had to freeze wall-e
I just went in a circle
Where am I supposed to go?
Oh, I could get up
Up here
All right. I made it
Thank god
Well, here's your beanbag sonic
Just be huge this time with an eye patch
Is he the one who kidnapped the folks around here?
Wait, he's trying to tell me something
I know what you're up to you're going to use that machine to alter us monsters
I know what evil you're up to my altered arm is proof
Alter the monsters. No, we would never do such a thing
Silence I can see through your plan. I've experienced far too much agony to stand by idly
I won't allow a single other monster to go through what I did
Please listen to us. We admit we use machines. We just we use gadgets but altering our monster friends
We would never ever do that. Please believe me
Your words tell me nothing
We shall fight and I shall gaze into your soul
No fain he refuses to listen
It's okay. We'll prove to him that rio's telling the truth of fighting
Why would that yeah, let's fight him. Let's prove let's prove him right
again
Chain it
Kill him not even fucking hard. Come on
Last hit get I need last hit fire last hit
You can do it
Come on fire last hit so you get the level up
You can't look please don't no don't die
It's okay. We're gonna be fine
It's okay the dragon died, but we're gonna get this last hit got it game over hard one
The dragon is uh
earth lore
mastered 10 out of 10
Please understand. We just want you to return the people you've kidnapped
We never meant to harm you
No matter let these wounds be a sign of the trust you earned
You need only to promise to me you will never alter monsters and I will return all the people
We could never let a monster suffer
Rio you have great promise the rest is up to you now. I take my leave
Don't he looks so sad altering monsters. It's just wrong
Whoever did this won't get away with it
You beat me you have my trust you hurt me
Fuck this garfield voice spy rod was injured. I'll send it to the hospital
I think we may have our priorities wrong here
I think spyroids death
Spyroid hasn't gotten better. I hope I hope it comes back soon
Excuse me. Hello
Oh cynthia. Hello. I'm here with a delivery. It's a letter from mr. Carnab
Let's see
Congratulations for saving the investigative team as a thanks. I wish to offer you a gift. It's
monster association office
That's what it says. Let's go
slowly
somehow
I slowly somehow
unprover without doing anything
Turned into the second best monster I have
Uh spliceable spleen five community subs. Thank you spliceable spleen
Thanks for dropping some subs here
Five from spliceable spleen. Thank you. What would you do to work on with you?
What are your moves?
lot of intellect
tons of intellect
Intellect defense is actually really good
Just do a bunch more intellect and intellect. Yeah, read some books
Very balanced
Sandbag, yeah
Today you can do probably life
Who cares what you do?
Look at the look at the stat gains on unprover. That's ridiculous
All right. I think there's a change of plan here
Unprover has that's a that's the third or fourth in a row more than 20 stat points
You deserve this
Quills
Oh boy, you're like starving
um
Here have a have a banana
Is dragon gone?
Dragon actually is gone
Tired all right proceed
Uh, we're gonna go to town
The association let's finally get out of this rank
Ah to you I have something for you and it's this a breeder's rank b certificate
Now you can proudly enter the ima competition in tourable
and the ima competition is as much as I
Hate to admit it a tougher than our fimba competition
Everybody fucking hates this
What's wrong with you? What's that thing up?
Mr. Carnab, I have you heard of altered monsters. They're monsters with machines grafted to them
No, I can't say that I have
I like to fiddle with machines, but I could never imagine meddling machine with monster
Goodness gracious. I'm so busy. I've got to get going now. Ta ta
He's gone
That seems strange
Goodbye. Oh, where's mr. Carnab?
Oh philia glad to have run into you. There's something I wanted to ask you so that guy's evil. He's he's definitely manipulating monsters
Grafting hooks on them and stuff like a fucking psycho. Well, that's the situation. Do you know anything about it monster alterations?
I've never heard of such a thing. How cruel how awful like
not awful at all is
Breeding monsters and forcing them to fight each other for your own personal gain, but that's okay. That's that's fine
How cruel?
freezing them in canisters
And stuffing their dna into each other until you get what you want so it can fight in a tournament for you
Nendoro's arm was altered. I don't know who did it, but somebody surely did
Hmm. Why don't you try torbal?
That town is on the forefront of technology. You might be able to find some clues there
torpola
box off locked
uh-oh
Shit for those of you guys that came over from kraken stream if you don't save every fucking
single time
You get a softlock scenario which we're in right now
God damn it
Well, I mean, I don't know what the last time I saved it. Let me try something here
I'm gonna try to like blow into the microphone and see if it helps
It's a long shot, but we'll see
one
two three
Spyroid hasn't gotten better. That's not good. This is actually it's I think spyrode might actually die
I mean you did you did get one hit KO'd
He got the hook dug into his skull
so
We've got a new favorite best friend
unprover
Intelligence again
I'm gonna do i'm gonna try to get intelligence to like 300
Everything else is perfect. The health is fine
What about uh blossom?
Tired, do you have rest?
Sandbag
Adrock is so bad has adrock ever had a stat increase that was more than eight. I don't think it's ever happened
Come on, stop stop kinking my hose
Internet somebody's like going to my internet and just like kinking the hose
I love when this thing rests
It just lies on its back
Come here. Let's give you a
Some hot chocolate what the hell what the fuck
Stop this nonsense
Uh, I I apparently i'm still live
Weird. I don't know why this fucking happens, man
It really is almost like somebody steps on the wire
I should be live still
It doesn't say it's off
I think I am should still be live
Well, i'm gonna have to send another message
Because this has been happening the last like four or five streams, right? We just hit like this
patch
for like an hour
it just
Dumps on itself
Well, yeah, it's all over the place
Lively good
Uh, what about you frustrated, but you're gonna be fine
I'm not me. Wait, is it is it is it twitch servers?
Is twitch having problems today?
No, I I don't think so
Torbjorn
Yeah, you may have to refresh
Because it's kind of
This is just weird
It's as like a surge because i'm getting
I have a my cap my bitrate cap
Is that six thousand?
It's like electrically surging through my internet because like okay, so six thousand is my cap for upload
And this shit is going to like twelve fifteen thousand up like twelve thousand up
And then dumping down to like five hundred
That's weird
And like obs shouldn't even be allowing this to go past like ten thousand
Why is it a twelve thousand?
Like right now right right now. It says i'm streaming at like nine thousand up, which is
What I have a cap at six thousand here
What the hell is this doing?
That's very odd
You know, sorry, this is happening
Really is something else and all the people what's this?
Is that wit?
Huh fain?
I never thought i'd see you here. How are you doing?
Just fine and you
Me well a day hasn't passed that I didn't recall the events of that day
It won't help anything, but let me say i'm sorry
Oh, it's all right. Don't worry about it. I've eaten i've even managed to become an official breeder
Really? Congratulations. You did it
No, if you have to ask something come to the university. I work there. I'm willing to help you out if you need it
Well, I must be going bye
See a friend of yours
Something happened between you guys you're acting different than you did when you met graham and philia
Yeah, I guess although something did happen, but it's all in the past now rio. Let's go to the university later
All right. I need to
What's the end what are you gonna do?
New store
watermelon peach
beef chocolate canned fuel
solid fuel in a can
honey toast
Uh get a couple of carrots
That's such a weird number to stop at for drop frames
I'm at ten thousand even drop frames. That's very odd
Peaches mangoes watermelon, uh, how much is beef is five hundred dollars here. That's kind of a rip-off
What does the fuel do
is the fuel like the
energy drinks or energy bars
Where if I feed it to them and pumps them up, but it takes their lifespan away
Or is it better?
Hey, isn't it horrible amazing the bustle of town the incredible technology and the monsters. There's nothing like the other times
Yes, it certainly isn't like the other time so definitely in this town is anything other than the budget
Altering no, that's not something i've heard but it's certainly possible
Here improve battle ability is everything
Monsters are raised to be strong and i'll be i'm trying to do this like a times five speed apparently
It's entirely feasible that somebody has already done some experimentation in monster alteration
But that's too cruel that may be but that's the reality of this town
You'll see once you enter the competition
It's no walk in the daisies, but I don't expect a fimb of reader will have much of a chance
Thanks for the advice, but I have no choice. I've got to enter the competition and find out
Well, then first you've got to go to the association and register for the competition. Yeah
Go to the torval monster association next week
I'll mention you
Oh, don't even tell me we're gonna have to do a thing where
Titi you called master wit. Do you have visitors?
oh
It's always been celebrated what the heck are you doing in that getup?
And since when did you talk so politely?
Why you iota?
I mean shoot how very unkind of you. I happen to be very proud of master wits abilities
And that's why I became his assistant
If you're done, please get the heck
I mean kindly to cleave. Hmm
You're talking funny
Please mention us at the association don't tell me I have to go like on another one of these missions
What is this guy?
What brings you here today?
Command
He sees a very promising boy
But he's just a bit too serious if he lightened up a bit new worlds would open up for him
Come back anytime. Okay
So come back next week. What if
I'm gonna have to go to
Another one of these adventure things and do a mission
It's gonna be such a pain
Spyroid has come home from the hospital
Not dead not dead, but we got this other good shit going on here
I'll just we'll see if you can catch up
Sandbag
You can do can you do?
Life no, you can do defense
You can do target. Okay, that looks good
If we got another 20 plus increase from unprover then
I mean, nah, fuck everybody else
The intelligence stat increase I can get that to like 500
So we're probably gonna end up fusing these two together then because the stats are gonna be so much better
i'm, sorry, you're cool and all but you just
You haven't been improving as much as the unprover has
It's a weird sentence
Frustrated you'll be all right
Okay, what's coming up?
town, right
Go to the get our association
You're a femba breeder. I'm sorry, but I think it may be too difficult for you to at your level
All right, but of course you're welcome to enter
It was a pain to get into the Ruin competition, but it's easy here in Torval
Yes, you know, there's been a spike in the stray monster population in Torval
Since we have that problem on our hands. There's a hardly a time to test competition applicants
Sorry
It's not a problem. But why are all the stray monsters here?
It's a side effect of over
bearing training and machine based methods
Many monsters run away and injured monsters are often abandoned
Oh, I shouldn't talk about such gloomy matters before the competition. I'm so sorry
Uh, nothing gloomy about it. It's a fabulous story. I must say here's the asshole
Is that fain I see here?
Oh, you live in Torval. Don't you your father is a top ranking. I'm a official, right?
An elite. I'm a official. Thank you very much. Let's get it right pal
You can't be serious about entering the I'm a competition. Have you lost your marbles?
What
Oh, so sorry. Didn't mean to say that out loud to make it up to you
Why not stop by and see my fabulous ranch just look at these the latest training gadgets more than 60 monsters
If you can't take the training regimen, well, then poof you get axed
Maximum efficiency only made possible by my maximum wealth
The best ranch in ima no make that the world
axed
What do you think monsters are they're not replaceable cogs in some machine?
The best ranch you've got to be kidding
Oh for heaven's sake I know you're jealous fain, but don't get mad at me just because you lack the means to run things like me
Besides you're really only wasting your time you evil stragglers. They're not back. He got real angry real quick
They're not worth a grain of salt fain. I'm sorry
Oh you
She punched me. She punched me right in the face
Not even daddy punches me. What?
This girl is your responsibility make her say she's sorry nobody needs to apologize to you
I feel exactly the way rio does
I'll defeat you in battle and prove to you that your monsters method monsters methods. Don't make a good monster
All right, let's go sign up and one hit ko all his monsters
The guy looked like you no didn't february week one
Hello, is anybody home?
More of this like exposition. Oh, hi tt. You're still wearing that getup, aren't you?
I'm disguised. I'm trying to get more info and intel. Oh you hush. This is what master likes
I wear it to show master my affections. I don't give me the third degree
I didn't say anything bad about it. So what?
You're here for a reason. Of course. I am master wants you to come to the university
Shoot, why do I have to come to your ranch on an errand?
Well, you got the message. So i'm out of here. Hmm
Okay. Okay. Geez, guess i'll pay visit to the horrible university soon
Hello, how are things need anything today? Go ahead take a look around. Yes
praise
Which would you appraise the life tablet?
It's the first time i've appraised this training gadget. Apparently this training gadget is called a rodeo
I'll add this to your training gadget list
I also have an old tablet
this
It's the first time i've appraised this training gadget. Apparently this training gadget is called a cannon
I'll add this to your training gadget list
cannon
Sandbag book target trampoline
So you shoot yourself with a cannon to pick
improve defense
Okay
Let's get it on there
Oh, damn, that's good. That's a long way. Okay
And what was the other one?
rodeo level three
Is life
I
Rodeo
Okay, is that all I that's all I got right anything else I think that's it wait, hold on
Uh by effect
You don't have any praise to now. Okay
I think that's it
Spyroid and roberto will make the better fusion you don't want your fusion inheriting that it hates to battle which unprover does
This is true. So i'll just keep you around and maybe level you up
All right, are they friends yet like really good friends?
They're just good friends not great friends
Okay, let me see the calendar
No, come on, where's the official tournament
You're killing me with this. I have to go back to town or something and talk to the university again
Again
Well, stay with the book you do not the life blade this time you're gonna do
the rodeo
This is gonna be really funny looking
and you
Do the sandbag
You can do the target. That's fine
Do the book, okay
One t intelligence minus three intelligence
Uh, it has a drawback
That's so stupid. I need a better view
You're doing fine
You're you need to eat
Have some beef
He loves it. He's having so much fun
Okay, you can yeah, i'll just feed you
Give me something quick
like a carrot
What the hell are you guys linking that that my face doesn't even fit
That's not even my hair
My ears aren't that big
and I go to town
Torval University, please let me before Roberto dies get him to a rank
Things got out of hand
Yeah a little he had it coming though
Yeah, I know what you mean, but he's strong. You can't beat him with standard training gadgets
We must beat him with normal raising techniques
In that case at the very least you'll have to upgrade the training gadgets at your ranch
I'll teach you how to assign effects to gadgets use this metal
What are you thinking? There's no need to extend your hand to him here use this cannon
Doping
You can make gadgets with the magic effect. The name doesn't sound too nice, but it works fabulously. Give it a try
Thanks gadgets with effects. I'll see how it works
Just what is the deal?
Have you gone out of your skull wit?
I mean, are you sure this is a good idea master? I told you
Oh, I wouldn't bring you here today
But I can say yes to you that what you see is a very promising boy
But it's just a bit too serious if he liked that a bit new words, you know what for him?
Give me the fuck out of here. You know, that was as close to a donald duck as I probably could possibly do
That's very close to donald duck. That would be an interesting take on donald
If I go so overboard with that it turns into donald duck
Torval competition
Hello there, my name is swift. I sell special training gadgets. I look forward to doing business with you. What will you do?
Effects you don't seem to have any of gadgets what buy training what would you like to buy? What the hell is this?
It's skins from my sandbag
Uh, so this is fire
Sure
Intensive gadget training that increases focus don't let your monster train too much or it'll get hungry
Makes magic training more effective. You get money with every punch
uh
lucky book
magic book intense book
All right, don't let your monster skip a word battles are not won by muscles alone intense reading magic book lucky book
This is just another layer
i'm gonna pee
All right. I'm gonna last pee in the night. I'll pee everywhere back
See you guys in like two or three minutes
Okay, I got some food. I got some rice
some pita
excellent, uh
So I think lemon is lemon on here. Mm. Nice and lemony exactly what I was looking for
So don't mind my like eating noises
Yeah, that I've had a good amount of lemon today
um that this
recommended daily value of lemon is
Reached almost turn on the camera. I don't I don't have to close it. I don't have any clothes. I'm out of clothes
I'm not fully nude my god
All right, i'm out of room here. Okay, that's better and i'm gonna make sure I take my probiotic. Have a good boy
All right, we need a book
Lucky book magic book magic book increases focus now this one increases the effectiveness
what
What are you talking about? I can only do this once with one item
seriously
Oh, man
I think i'm gonna go for it magic book
Will it still be okay? Yes, you'd like to purchase this gadget. I'd like to purchase the magic book. It's too late. I did it
Magic book cannot place any more gadgets on the wrench. Well, then give her the regular book
Where's the regular book?
No, I want
I want the regular
No, get get rid of the get rid of that remove. All right got invaded
Behind you kim just came in
She uh, there was other things
That to go with the rice and the peanut. I heard the door. I heard the door
Yeah, she kind of just walked in and placed it
Oh that makes it so much better
Oh my god
All right magic book is in I don't think I I can't
Purchase anything else, right?
No, I can't do anything else that's so
Hope I did the right thing
Should I sell the other one 500? Uh, I think i'm just gonna sell the book
No, i'm gonna hold on to it I might need to do double time
All right, that's fine. Let's see how good this thing is. All right. Can I please enter the competition now?
Finally jesus
Are you gonna even live that long?
Just rest only just put grandpa in bed until he has to come up and do the tournament to get up here
So, let's see
uh rest today because
No, yeah rest today do the book tomorrow
Magic book, uh, you can no you need life. That's more important than that right now
Get on the rodeo again. Who cares about your defense or intelligence?
Here we go 14 16
That's not even a good increase
Really?
You look exhausted
Okay here
Come here
Uh, have a banana I don't want bananas. I want vitamins
Okay, good
How are you? Everybody's good
When was the last time I shit my pants on stream?
uh
I've not ever done that
And I fucking read it i'm some oh my god
I don't know why I do that. I'm sorry. I keep just reading the gross comments
I seriously don't know what's wrong with me
truly
Like am I reading that is it? Oh, yeah, that's like weird and strange. Maybe that might be funny or something
I don't know why I keep just instinctively reading these
That's a long way away how does a floating wolf armor go to the bathroom, holy shit that was 27 intellect
That's insane
You deserve food for that one
You deserve not only do you deserve fool you just
You deserve a salmon you deserve a salmon for that one
nice work
He didn't like it an asshole
That shit's like fucking 40 dollars a pound
having fun
It's dead. Everything this character does looks dead
There we go
Who gave blossom lsd?
Uh
jake book
Spam that intellect
rodeo
No life blade
I don't want to drop you that much
Sandbag, that's good
Uh, you can rest today
You can get in the tub
See what we get this time
another 27
I need to really just start putting in tournaments. What is it almost three or four hundred intelligence?
Uh
299 intelligence
It's pretty great
hungry
Just get reverto to the tournament. That's all I care about
How you doing over here? You okay?
Not really how many carrots?
I don't have any carrots left hydrate. Oh, I got a water right here
I don't think we've even seen that character do a move. All right, i'm gonna save it here
First week of spring saved the game
We're very close to reverto's death
Hit the book again
Then you can rest
You hit the life blade again
You hit the snow you rest
you
Hit the
Cannon
You rest
Making quesadillas
Quesadillas are amazing. Oh that plus nine defense of minus three accuracy
You just let the
Cannon hit you in the ass
I don't understand how this builds defense
I mean maybe
Hey good work getting shot at by a cannon. You're so good at that
All right. I didn't want to like just do gross mouth noises
Stray streamer, what's up? Can you do your famous thanos impression? Yeah, sure reality is often disappointing very frustrated here
Gross mouth thanos
Did I were there gross mouth noises there?
I i'm sorry if there were were there mouth noises
hungry still
how about a
a mango
Tired. All right, let's keep going
Don't die yet
Only a couple of two or three more weeks, I think
No
Oh, this rank is getting too easy for this monster. It needs new challenges. It could be a good time for a fresh start
Roberto hates resting. Why am I doing this to him because you have to sleep when you're tired. You don't just stand in the corner
Okay, rest
rest
sandbag
Here it is up here. This is the this is the one that matters as long as you live for the next one
One, two, three, four five six weeks
We'll be good to go and we'll finally get to a rank and that will have beat the game
But not really that's a lie. It would just you know close enough as they say
Why have I not put anybody else in tournaments for eight months?
well because
monster rancher four
Is hard to uh manage
Because I have five monsters
each monster has to do three
tournaments
each to rank up
So that's three six nine twelve fifteen tournaments to be able to be allowed to rank up to just to get to d rank
So I kind of have to pick a couple that I care about
And the other ones are just dna bait for a while while they sit on the ranch
There's a lot of it's a lot of management
And i've been told by an expert monster rancher player
Told me that uh, usually you want to have focus on one or two and the rest are just adventure bait
Somebody also told me I got one guide. It's not that hard to get to s rank
I thought somebody said somebody lied to me. Okay
You're just doing okay
Here have some food
Have a mango
How are you you're you doing? All right?
S rank is actually easier to get to than a and b rank war really
Well, i'll be at a rank
Very very soon. Hopefully he can live long enough
Is there a way that I can prolong his life?
To make it so he can do s rank
Or is he just gonna die?
Yeah freeze him
What if I just feed him nice beef every day will he live
But hold on. Wait, wait, wait
Is it true? Tell me if this is a false thing or not
If I freeze him and combine him with somebody else, he will stay at a rank. Is that true?
Was that why?
Is that for real?
The thing that comes out will be a rank. That's a half truth. Well, how does it what does that mean?
You have to combine it with another a rank
Okay
All right schedule again
You're going to what are you at? Yeah
Get that magic book
Just become unstoppable
Uh, let's do life blade
Rest. No, you don't need to rest training
What are you at? No tired fullness
um, maybe
Get on the rodeo
Let's see a little bit of a health increase
Rest and then sandbag. Okay, let's go
23 life minus three intelligence. I don't really use it at all. So it's not a big deal
I might need to buy some more food here in a minute. Thanks for the stream. Hey, thanks for coming up
Glad you like the string
Thank you
Uh, you're okay
You're okay. You can eat though
Okay, let's also praise you you're doing a great job sleepy over here you're fine
It's inevitable it's gonna happen real soon
I'm paranoid at bad death
Two things Roberto can live another year if you're lucky it should only require
It should only require only one monster to keep rank, but in four i'm not so sure
I think it's still ho it's true. I suggest not taking Roberto into the dungeon again
As he could die as soon as the dungeon ends
Definitely do we noted here
Do the book again
Then you can rest here
like blade
You're doing well. Okay tub
Yeah, I don't like the defense thing didn't really work out for you last time rest
The final dungeon is an hour long and it sucks. My monster died of old age as soon as the dungeon ended
That kind of sucks
Anybody who was hungry somebody else was hungry weren't they you're kind of hungry. What about you?
Uh, I have another beef. That's the last one I got that wasn't enough. How was I not enough food?
That was a piece of meat
Okay
Let me check their stats here
That screen is killing me. It's like being underwater and opening your eyes
He's almost at 400 intelligence
Hates mangoes
Well, that's all we got stop feeding unprover mangoes. He hates them
Well, what does he like
squid
Rest and then magic book
What no, no, no, no, no
God damn it. You have a tournament in like two days
the menus
Just click click, click, click, click, click. Sometimes you just accidentally hit the wrong button
Okay, thank god it's not today two days two weeks
Yes
Everything requires a confirmation
Feel like i'm using windows
Yes, run as administrator, please. Can I run this game as administrator and not have to do this?
All right, here we go
sleep
Rest do not do anything today at all
You can do
something how about
How about accuracy?
And you can go in front of the cannon
Whoa, what what happened? What happened plus three? What what was wrong?
mango
He doesn't hate him. Okay. Did I just give him something he doesn't like even more than a mango?
He doesn't like he likes but uh, he
He hates fucking bananas
It's ranked from top to bottom, isn't it? The stats are way too high for his rank
Well, let me just take him into the tournament
I don't want to do three garbage can tournaments to be able to prove that he's ready to go
All right, you go to tournament. Why did you buy so many mangoes? I don't know
They looked cool
All right
No, it's tomorrow not this week next week
Is the official b cup?
to move on to a
And then freeze them
Yeah, no
Some more food and high spirits
That wouldn't set up less
By the way, are you raising any mochi at the ranch?
No, no mochi at the ranch
Hmm really well then forget it
Why do you ask?
Well something is up
Recently, we've experienced these odd incidents mochi are disappearing
Okay, they walk off in the night
As if something is beckoning them a number of the customers here have lost their mochi recently
Mochi are so affectionate to humans why on earth would they run away?
Yeah, that's just it and mochi are the only kind disappearing
Have you had any problems at your ranch rio?
Hmm
No, but we don't have any mochi. So that may be why we're doing. Okay
Well, okay in that case, don't worry about it. I'll be sure to tell you if there are any updates
Yes, please do
All right. Give me give me like five give me 10 carrots
give me
three watermelons
Give me
Five beefs
And that's it
What's what is a mochi?
Week three spring cool
Uh, hello
Oh philia. Hello
Oh, who is that with you?
Oh, hey, I have regenerated ariel a new friend a mochi
It's so soft and nice to touch
Won't you try petting it?
No, thanks
When it comes to mochi fan acts strange
Just like at the restaurant
Why do you avoid mochi?
Are we eating these animals?
Am I allergic to mochi? I don't get it. You could tell, huh?
A long time ago. I had a mochi. I had no parents. So it was my only friend
I took my mochi around acting like a real breeder showing it off to everybody
And I didn't even notice how exhausted my mochi was
One time I was out with my mochi who didn't want to be out at all when we were attacked by a stray monster
My mochi weak from exhaustion
Lunged at the monster and they both fell into the sea
My mochi protected me despite my selfishness. I can't raise a mochi again. Sorry. I want to be alone for a while
I never saw him raising a mochi at school
Even though they are so popular because they are so easy to raise
Rio, I can't always be with fain to help him. Please support him as much as you can
Bye then me me support fain. Okay
So that's uh, I got more backstory now apparently let me see the stats
376 intellect he's eve rank
I don't want to uh, I really don't want to do this. I don't want to gap him
You want to see what's gonna happen with this?
They're gonna everyone's gonna forfeit every single match. It's gonna be a waste of menu pressing
Well, there's a fight tonight. This is the big one for Roberto. Do I even have to show up?
Can I just send like a piece of paper?
That says he's who's gonna come today
No, my god, man. I don't want I'm trying to press down and hit no
Uh, whatever here
Have a carrot
Why is digimon still around but monster rancher isn't um
I think it has something to do with the fact that the gimmick of this game
Really could only live a certain amount of time
The whole cd thing. What would you do now?
It'd be kind of hard to do now. You could still do discs, but I think I
Somebody mentioned I don't know where I read it, but like maybe like urls or something
For this would be like interesting maybe
QR codes. Yeah
Bar codes. Yeah, that'd be cool
But you'd also need a way to scan them
And you're talking about another game peripheral
That's probably why there was a monster rancher announcement, right on their twitter
This game really can only exist on mobile if that's the case
QR scan with your phone, right?
All right, Roberto, let's go
But yeah, there was a recent announcement from the monster rancher twitter that was like hey here we come soon
Yo, all you monster battling freaks. This is the day you've been waiting for
Win and you get a ticket to glory. You'll be rank a
Lose and you get nothing
Who will a goddess look fondly upon only one of you?
Now show us a good fight official grade rank b in trouble
Roberto
Versus depart 320 intelligence 240 defense pretty across the board. I have almost 500 power
Let's bite the floor with them to get to rank a
Bill out of the cannon
This was a skull skull doll thing see if I can get it quickly here
Good start. Oh, wow. You're nothing. This is rank b, man. You can't be fucking around now
Back to the miners. I'm keeping you from writing your lab report. I'm sorry
Go get go get that done
There's a vod though. You can watch the vod if you want if you're into it
All right, daras versus roberto
Oh high speed
Shouldn't be that concerned about it
You're putting this is b rank man. You don't quit to get to a rank
That's unbelievable
All right, uh colorn
327 health
Just high hp
It's weird. I mean hot dog things
Let's get in here and just try to get it. Let's just try to get it right now
That was risky, but it was worth it. Oh do it again
See you later. That was square
power move
It was risky
Uh bal boa
Is three, you know looks like that's the competition
Uh radicon
Pretty balanced across the board. Nothing too scary. I don't think
It's one of these robots
All right, let's see how we're gonna do this here
got it
Follow it up with just a swing check this ready power swing
Again don't counter that. Uh, oh
It's all right back it up
It's two counters. Is it god that sucks to just guess
All right
If I beat balboa, I it's a little bit stung
Even if I lose to balboa. No, he's fighting. No, this is bad
We're both four and oh
Really has to come down to this
All right
322 defense 350 power and a ton of health
slow speed
I have a lot more power, but I don't have that much defense
Let's go for it
Well, well, so you really come to fight in the competition
Oh, don't worry. I'm not interested in getting revenge for that time. You punched me. I didn't punch you my friend
Watch yourself my balboa sword fighting skills are top tip top and sharp as a knife
Who knows he might even accidentally injure your poor monster
I have the same thing. Don't I except you we have like this you guys is it made out of cakes
You this is like the candy land version of my character
Don't do that
Got it. That's a big one
Oh
You got nothing what was about what was that balboa mixed with it but like the it was almost like a
One of the slugs like the one little cake people
The goddess showed her love to roberto
He was a fairy in a robot. Okay
Congratulations. What's going on? Hope you come to your senses deal and can see that your methods were wrong
Hi, you cheated
You met with wit didn't you what did wit do for you?
Like like steroids. Yeah, you use steroids to strengthen your monsters. How awful. How could you dare say such a thing?
Shut up. So I can't accept this. I won't
What do you mean? I did
I never did steroids
And one of the other ones is on steroids. Not this one
How can we save the poor monsters on your ranch?
Darn it. What will it take to convince stale?
How about a teacher?
Maybe a teacher from the school that everybody went to
Hmm, I see but I was expelled and I don't know
No
You must not close your heart out of fear
That's the same mistake I made
You must overcome it
You're right rio
Maybe we should go to the town of visually and elvis
I can't do that. That's not gonna happen. That was really like
That was phoned in like crazy
Don't ever try to do a goofy
Because only one guy can do goofy
Roberto's two fans
What a hack performance
It was I I kind of figured I figured halfway through that that wasn't turning out of what I held the way that I thought
And I just kept going tall. Hello
Oh tall
Hi
How are your monsters doing? Shall I give feins monsters a checkup?
Well, thank you. That would be great
Let's see
How's everybody doing?
All done. None of them had any problems at all
They love you tallt you understand monster language
What made you decide to become a monster vet?
A long time ago. I had a mochi her name was mochina and she died from an injury
What's with these mochis? Everybody has a mochi apparently that tragically died
I was so sad. I couldn't do anything to help
I guess that's how it started
But isn't it hard for you?
It's your job to protect life, but you have that sad memory
I had a similar experience
Really what happened to you?
Did you write that down? That is a sad story
But I think of that experience as inspiration. I always think i've got to try hard for mochina
I figure if I don't keep working with monsters that mochina would keep would weep in heaven
She'd probably think it was her fault
I bet your mochi was happy because it cared about you enough to risk its life to protect you
Thanks tallt not at all. I'll come to do a checkup again. Bye
Okay, we now have
585 power
That is such an unbelievable number
I want it to be 600
And then we're gonna stack health a rank reverto can still he's still living
Let's do it. Let's see what the what it looks like. This is like the real league
This is the actual league
So what about the other ones? We've got
five
206 275 health you can you can slow down on the health now. He's got plenty
Maybe uh
Intellect and accuracy for a little bit
You on the other hand, let's get you to 400 intellect. No, you have to do a tournament
Everyone's just gonna quit. We just have to do a menu spam for like 10 minutes
Do this shit
tournament here
here
No here
All right
Book I have a tournament now
But I can do the book again, no, don't even just just let somebody else do it
You just rest
You do the light blade again
Sandbag. Yeah
and then rest
You can rest and you can tub
Roberto almost at almost at 600
How much more do we need?
At 602 you made it now just work on living life
a little bit extra accuracy
Okay, how's everybody doing food?
You could eat
Have a beef
Roberto can easily get s rank. I would suggest now icing two monsters and making some new ones
Some of the rank a rank fusions can be really good
Okay
So who we ice in here? I'm gonna say
I don't know what to do about this
Unprover is just I feel like he's gonna be insane
Maybe these two blossom and um ad rock
I'm gonna try to do ad rock and blossom
I forgot ad rock was a monster to be honest
Are they friends and make sure that they're friends blossom and ad rock are not really that close
We can just do it. Who cares
We're almost we're at s rank. Anyways, pretty much we just gotta beat a rank with you. You'll do it easily
Roberto's friends everybody but Roberto's still
Good
And I really don't want to have to go through every single tournament again
You can stick around
Let's do it. Let's let's head to the uh, let's head to the shrine
Spyrode and Roberto the only friendships that matter. Okay
Let's head to the shrine that was a competition today who oh right i'm prover
Visily
Uh, no, fuck that let's just go back and association and ice people
So let's see what we get it's time to retire ad rock
Goodbye what retire one of them? What do you mean frozen? Oh
Prover
Vroomer energize shroomer get rid of shroomer
What do you mean wait, wait what
If you use them, don't retire them
Don't they have to be frozen to they have to be retired to freeze them
Breeze instead of retiring
How do you freeze?
Don't you have to be retired? What are we talking about? Wait, what?
Don't you don't you have to freeze them?
You have to retire them to freeze them
You can fuse the retired ones to open up space. Yeah, but those ones don't do anything
We already tried this before we we already did this
And these combinations are don't do anything. They're terrible retiring is deleting. Yeah, I know
Yeah, I don't
I'm gonna delete shroomer. He was one of the eight
Willy Wonka mushrooms that we had I I know I know that
if I combine like
Prover and like energize i'm just gonna get another dumb useless energize bunny. Okay, like prover
and energize
Are you ready? Like it's gonna show me right? Let's see what it does. Don't use a combination item
Yeah, like mush mush tan and then gun bit
Look at these terrible stats
We've already seen mush tan it's a gun bit let's go
Just energize
That's why I was just retiring them like let's do mouse and uh rumor
No item. Yeah, we've already seen these skunk roller. Remember?
Yeah, i'm just retiring them
So we're gonna do blossom and add rock right these two are gonna be combined when he's eventually about to die
Goodbye
You also need to rank up too
That's weird. There should be more fusions unlocked, but there's not more options. It's weird
All right blossom
Goodbye. Yes
Retire who the next mouse you did mouse was the monster I got for free in the beginning of the game. Goodbye
That's the start of pokemon. Yeah
All right
Now we've got some real combos here
so blossom
And add rock
Uh, no item. Yeah, let me see what happens mum mew
Rage rock and aunt mew
Rage rock
Those stats are awful
artificial
sprite
They were both e here. Yeah
I mean, this is a rock monster
We don't have one of these
You think a rock monster would have way more like base defense. Oh, no, that's the secondary. Okay
Rage rock just is add rock
Aunt mew let's do it. The stats aren't even that good. Let's go. Fuck it. Let's see it. What the hell kill it
That's that's blueberry
All right, uh, um
I'm gonna go see if I can get a new disc in here
Let's go back to town. Let's go to the shrine
Let's put a cd in see if I can get anything
from saucer
Uh, what do I have for a disc that's still just hanging out here? Let me see. I gotta grab one
Now i'm gonna freeze blueberry I will
Don't worry
How about um, what do you guys think about?
um
The sopranos
I think that works
Ed and eddie
All right, we got ed and eddie
the sopranos
And uh psyops the mind game conspiracy
Let's do ed and eddie first
Put it in upside down. I'm trying to get me to break my playstation 2
Put in the disc contain containing a single jpg of beanbag sonic
Uh
All right ed ed and eddie something we've not seen yet
Thanks for waiting create the monster. That's a weirdo
It is the three eds. There's ed ed and eddie. It's the first time we've seen it. All right, let me add a page
Take it home. Should I take away ed ed and eddie?
It even has the bright colors. I can't fit it all
Yeah, the three eds like three ed
Ed and eddie
Three ed
Or three three d
freed
Oh, it could be ed boys. All right fine ed boys
Come on, I need to go forward. I can't go forward
Ed boys
Is it two
Well, I mean it's ed with two d's eddie with two d's and ed with one d should it be two d's
No, i'm not gonna make a b o i s
This is the ed boys
2d or 3d
two b's and boys
No, no, no, no, no, it's just ed boys
Can I do any more? All right, let's freeze uh blueberry
old english
That's a let me get a sip of my water. Let me get a sip of my water. Let's see the stats
Of the ed boys
It's just terrible 115 127 125
garbage
What about you?
Well, definitely gonna freeze blueberry
No, no, not the shrine
No, no, no back back back back back back
I'm putting the sopranos
blueberry
Freeze blueberry
Here's the thing though. I do have a lot of the second and third level
Uh training devices
So there is that
So it's gonna take a lot less time to get that much
stat points
Let's put in the surprise. I do want new types though
I see some people saying hey, well, those were what you froze the that one the blueberry was good
Yeah, but it was still just one of those
Little toy sack puppet things
I want something new
All right. Sopranos is gonna go in
Uh done that's it. That was quick soprano something we have not seen before
Faked it
No
No, I don't want to duck
Psyops Psyops the mind gate conspiracy use monster rancher 3. I actually don't even know what that disc is
I'm, not sure. I brought that with me to vegas
No, I didn't like it. I didn't like that game monster rancher
Going back in it was bbs the boston era. Yeah, that is back when I was in massachusetts. You're right. I've unlocked
Like eight to twelve new species
Can we get something else besides?
The sack people the ducks and the plants and the shrooms
What's the process here? All right, so this game
Any cd that has data on it has a seed what i'm doing is pulling
the seed
From the disc
And then swapping the cds because you have to and I think the game may have locked up here
It'd have to be ps2. It does not
Uh ps2 is making a lot of noise. It's trying to read. Did I like burn out my reader? Come on
Come on. What is this?
It's it's getting stuck. It's repeating itself the ps2 got
Fucking whacked. I'm gonna try something drastic here. I just opened it and closed it
Come on. Hold on
Ha ha ha ha ha
What is this an nes cartridge?
This better be good the plant. It's a windmill robot plant
Steam punk i'm not gonna get another disc
I don't want another plant guys. I've had like three of them
Hold on
How about what's this one?
You got it. No, I don't even want to I don't even put that in the tray. That's the stupid without warning game
this this is
freedom fighters
A clock tower, of course
clock tower three
Seem it. I did see him in a couple days ago
Let's get clock tower in here and whatever we get from one of these. Uh, that's it
We got freedom fighters as well
Space channel five dreamcast does not work for some reason good something about the discs
And the data and how they're coded on the cd or something because we kept getting the same monster over and over again
Okay, let's go
It's another plant
I'm just gonna win the game with s rank and just feed
Roberto
Like energy fuel every day and make sure I can get to s rank and win
No softlock this time. That's good
cats
Freedom fighters, this is it. I am making a commitment to this creature
Put in the disc for the office season two
I didn't bring very many dvds or anything with me here. All right, pray for something cool
This is pretty much our last shot. All right, close it up
aka the good season
Don't people love that show except for like the last two seasons or something
Go buy a bunch of one dollar dvds. I did do that for monster ranger 2
Well, there it is. Mr. Jello
Oh, just wuss Thanos
Looks like snow. Does somebody say it looks like snow white?
Squisher rubber cement man
Then
Slop that's it
This monster doesn't matter
Let's take a look at stats
How sad that monster looks? Okay. Here we go
slop
I'd like to wuss Thanos
But that's too like me me. I get it
Not bad base stats
That's we we put this guy on the magic book
We'll have like 800 intelligence
Here's the eds. Okay
Okay
Let's get a save
magic book no breaks
Well, we still yeah. Okay, let's get you on the book
You still have to do tournaments. We're speaking of tournaments
We've got a tournament here a rank signed up for it. This will be the first time seeing it
a rank a rank
today
You are
Let me see the schedule again rest it up
Uh, let's do training on the magic book
I want to see how what the second one on day one what your stats are like
Wait, what does it say? Oh somebody doesn't who doesn't have a schedule? Oh you okay?
Plus six on the magic book. Come on you can do better than that. You don't need anything
He puts on glasses that's so stupid
Young monsters gain less from the machines
Yeah, I probably should just have them not do any machines, right?
All right rank a seven grand salmon
Let's see what the competition is like in the second highest rank in the game
the galaxy tuck
Roberto and slim
Not that scary
Everybody's gonna die in one hit anyways, you're cool looking this power is out of control
That's just what happens
When you stack it, he's have 600 fucking power
Just keep him alive to the end of the game
300 almost 400 health
That's nothing i'll tear through you
Bomber, okay, that's fine
You don't stand a chance
kill everyone
What's championship will helm it's another one of uh, it's a sword user
350 power
You can't match my strength. I'm sorry. Oh fuck. It's the same
You're just me from another dimension
And they can only be one of us. I'm sorry
Put on
Congratulations seven thousand dollars. I mean, it's just raisin
This is raising somebody the right way
complete mid-maxing steps
Can't wait till he dies. Well, hey
easy
Okay
So let me like let me ask a question if I fuse Roberto
With somebody that's e rank
Is it just going to come out as like a shitty e rank monster?
Do not just saves come and find out
They always come out as e
Because I mean it just it just seems so counterproductive to just get three people at the same time to rank a
Let's see. I want to see what happens. I'm curious
We got to save
I'm just curious what happens. It's either they come out at the current rank or two ranks lower
Let's see combine
combine Roberto
with
Um, I don't like rumor
Prover just i'm just curious. Let's see
Who's d this is uh, somebody that's e let's see somebody that's e
no combo item
What comes out?
e two e's and they're both just awful base stats
So that's not gonna happen
Not even any stat increases at all
So what if it's d? Let's see
uh, so Roberto
and rumors d
Do I get a d monster?
No
These definitely look like they have better stats though
Better step but like okay. Here's the thing. I don't understand about this game
If it gives you a rank e monster
With stats that are that good base the higher. Okay, if you have two people at a higher rank, right?
Won't I just
One hit kill every single monster in rank e
What's the point of even doing e tournaments?
You just climb faster, but I mean that
Seems kind of redundant to do all the tournaments again at the bottom when all the monsters are gonna have like 100 stats
It's just a smurf account. That's really what it is
um, okay, well
I'm gonna bring the dra I'm gonna bring the dragon over here just to see what happens. We have it saved. So don't worry
Uh, can I retire from here? Oh fuck. Whoops
Might be able to beat the game with Roberto. Yeah, that's true. I don't I mean I could but i'm just curious what I could get
Yeah, let's retire
Spyroid and just see what happens. I want to see what it would be
He's ranked d. Uh, yeah retire somebody just i'm doing this for the sake of just checking
Uh, I get rid of like prover who cares
Okay, they're friends Roberto and
Spyroid are friends
So this should be more favorable
And no combo item just yet glacier zag
I mean this that's
191 power base. It's pretty great. But
Vesuvius
fire flutter
Detail d bite and this is swing charge kick and cut in two
Is this a
dragon with a sword
Let's see
Or is this a there's a dragon coated
Knight
All right. That's pretty cool
So that's a dragon knight
he's really cool, but
I have to start over again. Okay. I mean can I
let
Just wait, just wait. Wait, wait. No, no, no, no. I'm gonna get let's wait till
Let's wait till roberts is gonna die. I'm gonna bring spyroid up to like rank c or b
Let's see what the other one looks like
I'm gonna try to get to let's just wait till he's dead
I'm gonna keep leveling them both and then event we're gonna pick whichever one is the best here
No combo and I can do a combo item too. Okay, let's see what this one is
Freeze roberto now so he doesn't die. Well, the theory is that i'm gonna be saving so frequently. It's just the same thing
No, the other thing's way cooler by far
This is just a better base version of the one that I already have. All right, let's load it
That second the dragon knight was awesome. That's what we're gonna do. Let's see what combo items can I do?
No
Combo item speed stone
Defense stone int stone. All right, that's kind of cool
higher defense
Look at that defense
I'm warning i'll never have to level that up once
This is glacier
Stats aren't as nearly as good as this one though. This is like really really good to start off with
especially if they
If I get him to rank s and spyroid to rank like c or b
Glacier is the same. Yeah, it's the same one
Yeah, that's the plan. We're gonna do defense stone
And get these both to rank like c and s
Let's load the game
Can also swap the order. Yeah, you could swap the order too. Let me see that
Just in case you know, just in case let's get our bases covered
Hello fain
spyroid
And then roberto
Uh use an item just to see what it looks like
Like and we can get
Say same stuff
Same deal
All right, oh i'm just gonna turn the playstation off
I don't think can I load game from here? Probably no
All right. See you in a second
Data corrupt
That would be awful, but we're good. So for the remainder of the stream
We're gonna try to get
Roberto as high as we can before he dies
And then when he's dead
Just right before he dies
Freeze him
Make sure he was friends that he's friends enough with spyroid get spyroid to like rank c
Or b or whatever and just see how far I can get that and then fuse them together
So the question I have the people that have played this game before if I get to s rank
And he's still alive
I pretty much have beaten the game. I just have to do you win. Is there a credit sequence?
Should I not do that? Should I just fuse and just have our last child be the dragon knight and just that's cool
I'm just getting late too, isn't it?
Yes, okay. There is a final dungeon and final boss
I feel like i'm gonna need three people to be high for that though
So we got spyroid. All right. Let's just keep going. What does the calendar look like?
Roberto, uh, let's yeah, let's do this
Try to get to s rank as fast as possible
Okay
That's good
and then
Any official turn do I have to do something here to get another fresh official tournament?
Uh, you don't and I didn't as a kid. There is a credit credit sequence
Okay
The map generation could be really annoying
Well
How about that? I'm not gonna stop yet, but
We'll see how far we are in the next like 45 minutes or so
And if i'm not like close
Because let's put it this way
I'm gonna be I have mr. Mosquito
So mr. Mosquito is a game that i'm gonna be playing
and I also have um
What's shadow of rome? Let me see what we got here
Yeah, I have shadow of rome and mr. Mosquito
So maybe what we'd end up doing is just if I don't if i'm like another hour or two out
I would probably just
Cap the stream next week
After all the other stuff I want to do
With start with mr. Mosquito play through that do like shadow of rome or
And finish this
At some point during that stream or start with it and then move on to mr
Mosquito and then do shadow of rome because if i'm this close to the end then the next time I turn the playstation 2 on
I probably should finish it. So but for now, let's uh, let's just keep doing this for a little bit longer
because tomorrow
Uh, think me and italics are gonna try risk of rain 2 co-op
Seems like it's really fun
And then saturday is the secura scratch off germa slots day
So that's kind of the plan for the next few days
but
calendar
Let's see if I can win some more of these
And get to s tonight. I wonder we'll try
Uh sandbag tonight. No, you know what? You're you're so powerful already
I probably should do something else like
life
And then rest
You are the only two that really really actually matter
Did I decide on the charity yet?
No, i'm trying to have a cup narrowed down
I will tell you what the charity is
Because i'm trying to get it to like a good charity, you know
Trying to do my research
So you are fine. You can actually switch these
Do this one
No, no, no, no
Get on the rodeo. Why not and then rest?
All right, let's go it's pretty good gain
Have some more meat
He's pretty tired. That's all right. You you're fine. I can feed you. There we go
Uh
Is he sitting in a tub of himself?
He just pissed in this tub. He just made a tub around himself and peed in it weirdo. Oh, this is this tomorrow
There's a drink in there too
That is this probably still also piss
All right, rest rest
You uh, you the goofy fuck. I don't know what the hell you're gonna be doing. Um life blade maybe
Not like any of these guys really matter. It's too much to have to deal with
Take take too long. Everyone lives only a certain amount of time
I can't say I was a huge fan
of the
Three plus monsters to have on your ranch. Yeah, save it
target
Uh, you don't it's just like that. You're just not any i'm not gonna be using you anymore
And do what you need to do
Plus the re he just needs to rank up but for him to rank up I have to do three full tournaments
And then do the official tournament just to get him to rank d
I don't have time for that. I got like so many other things to have to deal with
Like Roberto's almost dead. So I got to get him as far up as I can before he dies
Okay, paz. Let's see what you got
Not even quick do a tag tournament. Yeah, I mean, okay if you got this whole thing with you have five monsters
That can be on the ranch at the same time. Why on earth would you have most of the tournaments be single tournaments?
Is that kind of counterintuitive to the how the very base of the game is supposed to be played?
Is I mean instead of it being the single tournaments of half of the tournaments that you could select were t for team
It seems like there's one tag tournament every like two or three months
They should be every other week
Because as it stands right now, it's almost like you have to focus on one or two and the other ones just kind of get left behind
Because there's not enough opportunity to rank them up when you have to do it five separate times
By the rights to monster rancher
Uh, I don't I don't have that kind of money
Counter miss that you did
Have you considered how many people in this game must fucking hate the two of you?
Because we're unbeatable
All right. Well, hold on here. He's got 420 power and 400 defense
If anybody was going to stop me it would be this kind of character right here. It's a dragon with dodge
Uh-oh
You got high defense, but I can
You scared me a little bit not very much though. Just a tiny bit
Congratulations
So for those who get played what?
How do I get the official cup to rank up to s?
Is this something else I have to do?
Is there a storyline thing that I have to progress to do it?
Another town I have to go to stop stop stop
Go to the new town. Well, let me just get
Uh, I wish like okay, so this is what i'm talking about. So you look ready
Solo solo solo solo solo solo solo solo solo solo solo team
Why wouldn't yeah if you're gonna have a game with more than one two three four five monsters that need to be raised at the same time
Why aren't half of these t?
T solo t t t why are they so far in between look at like rank e
may ready
april
April may june july august september. How many have you seen down here?
one
In six months not enough t's
Wait, so you tell me okay, but this is a group battle
Like so I can't pull anybody up here
Well, it's all good
I'm close to the end anyways
Oh, man, the devs really got to release an update for this game
Well, there's the patch
Let's let's win one more which is down here
I just have to wait till
Let's see
Look at this shit. Come on
Did you just forget to fill in the slots?
one two
Three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven like where are the tournaments?
Can I just do this by myself? I can just pull you up here. Okay, like you're gonna get destroyed. No, why can I
Roberto has to kill. Okay, Roberto has to win
This is gonna be horrible
Does it have to be three?
It's all five
It's we're gonna have to kill all five people. Do you think he can do it? I don't think he can do it
Oh my god, this is gonna be so stupid. He's not gonna build it. He's gonna run out of guts
There's no way he's gonna run out of guts not gonna be possible. I wish I could just do it alone
I can't no that's not gonna work either
Use the others as meat shields
I'm just gonna have to i'm just gonna spam the rest of this was gonna rest everyone's gonna go to sleep for like a month
Let me go here
Fuck it. Let's go
I also wish I could set up like an auto feeder
Having to hit a okay open menu open menu
Select item. I can't just like set this up like you have a schedule system
All right, let's go
Let me see that new town visily go to visily see if I can open up anything already scheduled to competition
Do you yeah what i've just I need to open up the next story thing
Uh, let's go to the school
We're gonna find out why he got expelled
Nice to see you. What brings you here?
Mrs casa, I want to talk to you about dale
You see it's very sad indeed
This is casa, please tell him what he needs to hear
That I cannot do to teach us to guide with language and to encourage learning. It's not about forcing ideas upon others
but
The only thing we can do is consult with ima about creating official rules to regulate this
But even if that is done, there will be those who break the rules like you once did. Oh
What what happened?
the ancient book the tomb of black arts that sleeps in our school library
And is rumored to contain ancient arts of monsters strengthening
Our school forbids anybody from opening the pages of this dangerous book
He broke that rule
Arts of monster strengthening. Is that true?
Why would you do that?
Exactly. We were all surprised that one the one who cared for the monsters most would do such a thing
That's why when it happened, I asked you are you covering for somebody but you insisted it was your own doing
Yes, it was
Yes, of course. I see
I shall wait then wait for the day that you have grown strong enough to tell me the whole truth of this matter
Here we go
out of the way
What's your problem get lost? I tell you
oh
teacher
Giuliano is
Hey, what's going on?
Stop it lambda
Don't you have respect for your seniors?
What the heck are you doing?
I mean, uh
Uh, i'm so sorry something has gotten into their heads
Huh chris why you there? What are you up to? Uh, oh, it's mr. Richter
You bet. It's mr. Richter. Are you little punks?
We're sorry
Hey, you two got what you deserved chris. I'm talking to you, too
Yes. Yes, mr. Richter. Well, i'm sorry things are crazy around here. Here's your class s license
Thanks for listening to our dumb shitty story for the last 47 straight minutes get lost
Oh boy, finally they're out of my hair to think it's just a while back. I was scolding you and your friends
Well, you seem to be doing well fain
You gotta be worried there for a while if we can learn from all of this
In any case, i'm glad I had the chance to see you again
Hope we can learn from all this in any case. I'm glad I had the chance to see you again
Hope we can learn from all this.
In any case, I'm glad I had the chance to see you again.
Hello, what brings you here?
Oh, that's it.
You want me to do it?
Should I do it?
You want me to do this?
Should you want me to do it?
I'm putting everything on.
All right, give me my stupid quest.
What's the title of this stream?
What is the title of this stream?
The Five Horses of the Apocalypse.
That was the last second title, wasn't it?
Today's another nice day.
Oh, we have a visitor.
Hello, like always, delivery.
Oh, rank A Breeders Certificate, awesome.
Maybe it's from the battle with Deal?
Although Deal didn't admit your victory.
Rank A, that's amazing.
I didn't know you were doing so well.
Shoot, I'm a big fan.
So don't leave me out of the loop on your progress.
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
Don't worry about it.
Well, keep up the good work.
Can I do it now?
Fane, now you can enter the Vizli competition.
Yep.
How are things?
Anything today?
Go ahead and take a look around.
What will you do?
Do you have anything that I can do?
Anything I can praise?
Come on.
S-rank, give me those tournaments.
Team tournament, you can't do it.
All right, bingo.
Done.
And then that is gonna be the rank A competition.
Get them prepared, get them ready.
And then bingo, S-rank.
Also, let me hold on a second here.
Spyroid, and then this one.
Spyroid will be ready.
Let's go.
I don't think you're gonna beat the game
until you win the S-rank tournament,
which I don't think Roberto will live to.
Well, I at least wanna see the S-rank tournaments.
Even if I don't do it and I'm gonna end the stream.
Like I said, I will probably clean it up
on the next PlayStation 2 stream I do next week.
So this is not the end.
We will do it again.
We will clean it up.
Roberto can definitely live as long to do it
as long as you don't give him drugs
and send him in a dungeon.
Okay, let's see.
Let's go back here.
Everyone has a thing to do, right?
Sandbag, no, don't do sandbag.
You already have so much power.
I'd rather you do like life or something
just to get some more defense.
Magic book.
And you just stand on your tippy toes for a minute.
Pretty good increase for a Spyroid.
All right, you're hungry.
You love chocolate?
I got one left for you.
That's very odd.
Okay.
You're good on food.
You are all right.
You are all hungry.
What do you eat?
Let's see.
Canned fuel, yeah, of course you love canned fuel.
You're not gonna get it though.
You turned yourself into a basil lemonade.
Where, there you are.
How are you doing?
Tired?
All right, Spyroid.
I'm gonna spam X.
You think it'll work?
What the hell is this?
Yeah, I was gonna hit X.
She's speaking into a chalice.
She's talking into a cup.
All right, Spyroid, spam X the game.
Final guts.
Oh my fucking God.
Please stay the fuck down.
God, it's hard when you don't have
an overpowered character, huh?
This game would piss me off to no end.
All right, shill, burning.
Pretty good start.
And then we're gonna do counter it.
What was it?
Power?
He's been paid to throw.
Ladies and gentlemen, Spyroid wins.
A lot of health, just realizing that now.
Gambit, flip him up.
Let's go with a slowed now, that's good.
Counter, and he missed it.
Those eyes.
A ton of health, no accuracy.
Look, it doesn't matter.
We just have to get him to a higher rank
so he can be melded together.
Gotcha.
That's the eyes of somebody that didn't know
there was a math test.
That face win.
Pop quiz.
That face win, my boy.
All right, we're close.
We're so close.
We're almost there.
Not much longer.
We just have to do this one here.
Right, he's already signed up for it.
And then you have to go this way.
That official one after beating this one.
Relax, train, and we'll be fine.
Rest.
Don't rest, you don't like resting,
so what you should do instead is get on the rodeo.
Who cares what you two do?
Take some beef.
Crunchy.
Don't feed him a bone.
And who else wants to eat food?
You, what do you want, a tomato?
Whatever it is, what is it?
Vitamin.
Take a vitamin.
Let's load you up with drugs.
You can have a nice fresh salmon.
Is Unproved doing good or is he still lame?
I mean, he's good, but I just don't have the time
to really care about it.
Roberto's dying, so we need to focus on Roberto completely.
Save it, this is gonna get risky.
Okay, we have two tournaments here, coming up.
You, rest, you.
It don't matter.
Rest, you hit the book, and you punch a sandbag
for a little while.
I remember to save, yeah.
You got a tournament.
You, everyone's fine.
All right, Spyroid.
The fresh green cup.
Sounds tasty.
Sounds healthy.
Don't put Spyro on the rodeo, it lowers his intelligence.
Well, we're not gonna even get him close to rank B.
If I can get him to C, I'll be happy,
because then I can fuse him.
This is all just to get a better stat
when I combine the both of them eventually here.
Whip.
Rank A or bust, baby, speed run.
I don't even, I don't know if that's gonna get there tonight.
Next time I play it, I will.
You, D.
Why does she have a disc floating in front of her?
Final guts, yeah, sure, I'll do it again.
Fuck that, can't break.
How does that hurt you?
What?
You just jump around in a circle,
and it did more damage than punching me.
All right.
Jesus Christ, what the hell was that?
Oh my God.
No, stop, go closer in.
Hit this.
Oh my God, don't even make me jump.
I gotta stay back.
I can't, I couldn't counter it in time.
Seriously, why?
It's over, I have one HP.
I have to block whatever it is.
We both have one health, except you unfairly got yours.
Do it.
Give me a fucking break.
It's just a load of absolute bullshit.
It's just bullshit, that's really all it is.
It's just total bullshit.
It's just so many of the games mechanics fighting against me.
Oh, I killed you in one hit.
Oh my God.
I think I lose.
No, I win.
I still won the tournament.
Does UD accidentally beat me with,
she rolled a one five to 10 times in a row.
No, by the way, this is like a 40 sided die.
I accidentally lost to that character.
Let's go to the calendar.
There it is.
Rank up.
And then this is almost time to rank up.
I'm so sick of it, I'm so sick of that.
Okay, rest, you actually rest here.
No more, no, no sandbag.
I want life blade, more life, more.
Did I get bit by a bug?
I feel like an itchy arm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm,
hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
No, sorry.
Mosquitoes out today?
That means you're gonna get money soon.
Are you sure I didn't just get bit by a fly?
Oh, I absolutely loved it.
You haven't been singing in your guay voice lately
and it makes me sad.
Guay, guay, what is guay?
I haven't been singing in my guay voice?
All right, spiroid, no one's got anything.
This is tomorrow.
And then we're close.
We're close, we're close, we're close, we're close,
we're really close.
The throat noise?
Bleh, bleh.
That, like what?
Guay, guay, guay, guay.
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
Like, guay, guay, guay, guay, guay, guay, guay, guay,
I know what you mean.
Guay, okay, let's see.
Stream saved, he did it.
What sort of genetic lottery did Roberto win
to be born such a killing machine?
It's scientifically proven that Skrillex's song
Scary Ghosts and Sprites causes mosquitoes
to stay away and stop having sex.
Just like blast it.
We should have a day.
Where's the legislature?
If that's true, seriously, if that's true,
then have a day dedicated to everywhere on earth.
You put, you have to legally put a pair of speakers
out your window and blast that song as loud as it can go.
If that's true, then no mosquitoes
will ever come back ever again.
Why don't we blast it everywhere?
And then they'll never have any offspring
and mosquitoes will go extinct.
It confuses them.
Light blade, fresh.
This looks good to me.
Where's the rock version of this song?
The metal one.
There's a rock music song in this one.
All right, this is the last tournament here before
I can do the official one.
And then I'm probably gonna have to call it after this
because it gets getting late.
I'm going for more than seven hours now.
Streaming tomorrow too.
So I do need to kind of get some rest.
It really is a goblet, isn't it?
South Thirl versus Roberto.
Do I have a new, that's high, 468 health.
Get out of here.
When's the stream gonna start?
Um, I don't know.
Essentially, probably in the same time
between like it always is, between three and four.
Good start.
Then go.
Yeah, I mean, I don't see why it wouldn't.
This'll be quick though.
I like when they just get it over with.
It looks better this way.
Blue versus Lily.
Moody.
This is versus Jinx.
High 300s.
Roberto is not dead yet.
No, Roberto's still alive.
Whoa.
Robo Bird?
Sit down.
It's so much easier when you have a Roberto.
All right, Moody.
You know, nothing special.
Just getting lucky I think.
Just one of these little bird things.
Take me to Asteroid.
Just let me see.
Get me there.
It's pretty much done deal at this point.
Is this even fun anymore?
Yeah.
Yes, because I'm gonna get to see S rank.
Highest we got in Monster Rancher 2
was I think B is the highest I got to.
And that was hard.
I'm just steamrolling people.
Monster Rancher 2 was hard.
Jerma's spending hours and hours here
just to see the letter S.
Well, that's not wrong.
Okay, so then this is, oh, come on, really?
This is what I'm talking about.
Now you tell me, I got another monster
that needs to do a ranking and I have to wait.
Just look at this.
I want you to just pay attention here
because this is why, what the fuck, right?
What the hell?
Official tournament.
August, September, October is the next official tournament
to rank one of these monsters up.
I don't like that.
What's going on with that?
What the hell?
Might as well just burn it up and just get there.
And I wanna do one match in S to see what it's like.
You did put it all on Roberto.
I did, but that seems so spread out
for having this many monsters on the ranch.
You can't have more than one official tournament
in six months, four months.
I know I don't have to have more than one monster,
but that's like fun.
It's a cool mechanic and I would like to enjoy it.
All right.
Rest is the last thing I'll be able to do
before this official tournament.
Let's do, let's do accuracy.
We haven't done it in a while.
Might as well just get it up a little bit more.
All right, let's go.
Let's see it.
They don't wanna do official tournaments
when they know you're just gonna come in and win anyways.
I've just been giving him pills.
Just freeze, slough already.
Where's the Roberto will win coffee pasta?
It's funny how that was like a little meme two days ago,
but it's actually true.
I mean, that's true.
It is, almost there.
He doesn't even need a coffee pasta.
Coffee pasta.
Target practice, and there's the tournament.
Life blade, rest, you need to be fed.
You don't even have anything.
It's just automatic for like technique.
People are gonna start to get banned.
Here comes a R9K.
You did this.
Why would you want a potato?
Fair enough, just eat it.
Roberto's gonna die in 30 minutes.
Might as well spam it while we can.
I don't think he will.
I think he's gonna be around for a lot longer
than you think.
I think he's gonna be just fine.
All right, tournament time.
Beautiful life increase by Spyroid.
Official rank A tournament.
Give me some food.
Carrot, please stop.
My laptop is heating up and it's burning my legs.
This is it.
Official league grade A.
The final barrier to rank S.
Nash versus Roberto.
Let's see, who at the top?
What's the cream of the crop here?
Easy.
I feel like Roberto is,
I feel like Roberto's not supposed to be still alive.
There's no reason for,
I think Roberto's supposed to be dead.
He's just one hit killing everybody still.
He's not supposed to be alive still.
He's unkillable.
He could live another year.
Am I just gonna steamroll S and just beat the game tonight?
Is that, that might happen.
Who cares about the other monsters?
Let's just win.
I'm just gonna kill everybody.
This is view.
Like 300s.
All right, all right, go cocky.
Uh-oh, all right, don't get cocky.
Still very possible to lose.
Very possible now.
I'm gonna hold back.
No.
Uh-oh.
All right, easy.
That was so many guts damages.
Whoa, boy.
I gotta counter this.
Oh, you motherfucker gave me a break.
He's gonna lose.
No, he's not.
Hit it.
Oh, not good.
Yes.
I fucking hate this game.
Are you gonna die?
God, why?
I almost got killed by the troll doll.
All right, sunset.
Look at those stats.
And then I was down.
Look at how bad the speed and intelligence is.
Wow, I really am.
Like the last cannon.
Sunset.
Wow, that was fast.
Get in there.
Like that.
Back it up.
Don't blow the guts here.
Three no.
All right, Sun Louise.
There are, I'm still undefeated.
Three people here are undefeated.
Let's see what happens here.
All right, this is gonna be tricky
because three and oh, the top three.
I'm gonna get RNG'd somehow.
I know it.
Sun Louise.
Why are you so good?
You aren't.
It's probably your move set.
Tail sting, smoke bomb.
Whole lot of bullshit.
Let the AI control it?
No.
The AI is so dumb.
That's cool looking though.
Clean it up right now.
That's a good combo.
Just gotta connect, that's it.
Okay, Spartacus or Spartix.
Spartax.
Spartax versus, okay, Spartax loses here
and that's a good game.
Ooh, who won?
No.
All right, Spartax is really the only thing in the way.
Four and oh versus four and oh.
Comes down to this.
Huge accuracy.
But I just gotta land, just gotta land the attacks.
Oh, you two came to Visley too.
I had some important business here so I dropped by.
Picked a stop at a C to enjoy the competition
near the old school.
With rank A opponents, my Spartax should get
some good exercise.
What, you just came and joined the tournament?
You would just go into the grocery store
and you just have to stop and join mid-tournament
at the end?
What are you talking about?
What a humble brag.
Oh, you know, I was just like on the way to the store
and I would enter the highest capable quality tournament
in the world.
Lock it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bad.
Come on, come on, one more, one more.
Do it right now.
Double tap him right here.
No!
Fuck, this stupid game mechanic.
Where you just have to guess what move they're gonna do.
Like, what the hell?
I have to do this whole tournament again.
Like, why would that be in the game?
Just a one out of three chance to not get hit by a move.
Oh, come on, it really is rock, paper, scissors
at the highest competitive level.
This is rock, paper, scissors at the Olympics.
Did I save before?
I don't wanna do that again.
Did I save right before that?
Was it right before that happened?
God damn it, I don't, I hate that.
God.
I don't know.
No, but I need to get to S rank and then I'm gonna.
Ugh.
Yeah, it is today.
All right, what can I do differently?
How about this?
What if I just go, come on, just.
Here comes choke two.
No, I'm not gonna choke again.
It's not even choke.
It's just fucking whipping dice in the air.
All right, I'm gonna give the best food I can.
Why do they all want potatoes?
Get a watermelon.
Nutrients, focus.
Lively, completely focused and not tired at all.
Let's go.
Where's a good place to start the franchise?
What do you think is the best?
Monster Rancher 2 is absolutely the best start
and it's probably the best game.
You could probably just do Monster Rancher 2
and not any of the others, if I'm completely honest.
Or maybe the DS one.
I have not tried the DS one.
This one's all right.
No, this one's good.
I like two more than four.
Yeah, I do.
I do like, I mean, I wouldn't play this one
for like 30 hours if I didn't like it.
I do think two is a better game though.
I like two's mechanics a little more.
All right, stay down.
Let's go.
You draw to make monsters in Monster Rancher DS?
That's cool.
So we're in the same timeline though, right?
Does that mean that he'll do the same exact moves?
I can't lose right now.
Block it.
Oh my God.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha.
I can still do it.
I just can't lose another one.
I didn't even try.
Okay, fine.
I'm fine.
Spartacus is the only one that's not,
that doesn't have a loss.
I just gotta get there.
Oh my God, I almost lost.
Ha ha ha.
How did I almost lose?
I thought the past was already written.
The ink is dry.
I thought that's what the case was.
Things are looking up.
I mean, the past is already written.
The ink is dry, but I can do it.
All right, Spartacus versus Roberto, go.
Win this match and I win the tournament
and I don't have to do this bullshit again.
Oh, yeah, all right, out of the way of the store.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
Let's go.
99 fucking percent.
99 percent chance to hit.
What the hell?
Go for it again.
Get it.
You missed.
Fuck you, I win.
Because I have 100 speed.
I know, but I won.
That has pulled a muscle in the front of my left shoulder.
How did that happen?
That hurt.
The young breeders from Toggle, Fane and Rio.
These new champions will have a new trophy
sent to them, congratulations.
Thank you very much.
The trophy boasts an exotic gem unearthed
at the ancient ruins of Prometheus.
It's been a while.
What the voice of the Gaia stone.
What is it, Rio?
The flow of darkness strengthens hurry, you must remember.
You must protect humans from the very fate
that they are headed for by their own mistaken actions.
This is the human monster war that's incoming, right?
20, 40, 80.
I was thinking about it.
What is it, Rio?
Rio!
Oh my, quick, bring a stretcher.
Where am I?
Rio.
You fainted on stage, that was a real scare.
This is the school nurse station.
But what in the world happened to you?
Could you tell me?
Yes, well, you see, a voice from a stone
and a frightful sight, that's all very strange.
The Prometheus ruins, where the stone was dug up,
contains many unsolved mysteries.
Perhaps if you checked into it,
we may get to the bottom of things.
Prometheus ruins, huh?
Let's go.
But Rio, have you recovered okay?
I'm fine now.
It was just a little shock.
And I can't just lie around here, let's go.
Okay, then it's off to the ruins of Prometheus.
I was gonna do one match in rank S to see what it looks like
and then turn the stream off.
I just wanna smell the air in the rank S tournament.
Look at this shit, here we go.
Sign up for it, it's today, let's go.
I didn't save.
I don't think I can.
I can smell the game.
It doesn't matter, this is one and done.
Whatever, you're fine.
You're fine, where's Roberto?
Roberto, why are you doing this?
You should be resting.
I'm supposed to see.
If he dies, I die, what is that?
Whatever.
Rank S, I just wanna see it.
Don't knock over everything.
Arcadia.
Ladies and gentlemen, presenting the Arcadia Cup.
Who will arise victorious?
There can only be one.
Now let tournament begin.
Goldy.
Holy shit.
Well, that was a big increase in difficulty.
What the hell?
Their circle encompasses my circle.
This is bad, look at these hit chances.
Zero percent, zero, zero.
Well, that's one way to do it.
Okay, Rudolph versus Maxi Mill.
We don't even need to see this shit.
Goldy, look at how, Goldy's impossible.
What is this nonsense?
Okay, Ogre versus Goldy.
Look, it's not even fair.
I lost 11 fans.
11% of my fame is gone.
What a bunch of fucking assholes.
Not even true fans.
I one hit KO'd 99 out of 100 monsters.
And then 11 people are like,
yeah, I don't like this guy anymore, he didn't win.
You're really gonna hang up the towel there that quickly?
He's still alive.
Just in case something horrible happens.
All right, I need to get you where you can go, Cali.
This is nonsense.
Let me wait four months for another, no.
I'm gonna call it here.
I'm gonna call it tonight.
I'm going for just about eight hours.
I did not expect,
that was a huge ramp up in difficulty there.
So I had one stat that was really good.
It's like 89 intellect, 106 speed.
Dude, you gotta use, rank S is the actual video game.
But I'll call it here, that's it.
Before it gets too late.
So Monster Rancher 4, we will probably do, like I said,
tomorrow is Risk of Rain 2 with Taleks.
Saturday is the Sekiro scratch-off and German slots.
And then next week, like a Tuesday or something,
whenever I, Tuesday, Wednesday,
whenever I come back next week,
we're probably gonna do, what are we gonna do next week?
Should we start with this?
Yeah, it's still, it's in everybody's mind now.
After this next couple of days,
after I take a couple of like two, three days off
after the weekend, we will come back
and we will play this a little more.
Mr. Mosquito and Shadow of Rome.
After that, I don't think there's gonna be
more than a couple of days.
Those three games combined might even be one stream.
VR is gonna come back after that.
We'll do a whole week or two of more VR.
I wanna do some more multiplayer VR.
I'm gonna do Mind Show, actually do Mind Show.
There's still a ton of content in VR that I have not done.
But for the immediate future,
Risk of Rain 2 tomorrow co-op,
looks like a really fun game.
Everyone seems to love it.
Alex brought it up and it's like,
yeah, let's just try it.
Let's see how good it is.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching.
Take care.
Monster Ranger 4 will return for at least some,
what if it will do, there will be a conclusion.
Roberto's still alive.
There's still a fuse potential here.
There will be a conclusion to Monster Ranger 4.
But that's gonna be the time.
We'll see you guys tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
We're gonna do the bits.
If you're taking off, see you soon.
Labo VR is another thing.
There's a lot of stuff going on.
Other stings, other projects.
There's plenty to do.
Let's head back to earlier today,
about just about eight hours ago.
Mandem Requiem, thanks for the $12.
No message is 12 bucks.
Thank you so much.
Dork Cube, thanks for the 250.
Wait a second, guys.
What if Jerma doesn't know all this stuff about anime
because he's a huge weeb,
but rather it's because Jerma himself is an anime?
Well, that's a debate that you guys can have
without me involved, because that's about me.
I don't know.
I have no comment there.
Master of Ceremonies, thanks for the $5.
They say Hyper Beam.
I don't know if that is, but thank you for the $10 here.
$5 again for Master of Ceremonies.
Is there a way to refund bits?
I didn't think my hard-earned money
was going to a weeb streamer.
Well, you gave five more.
You gave $5 on top of that.
Also, before everybody goes,
I wanna say thanks to Kraiken for the raid.
If you were still sticking around from Kraiken stream,
thank you.
Maybe we'll see you again soon.
But thank you to Master of Ceremonies for the $10.
Manboy, thank you, Manboy, for the 250.
Jerma, you can't hide your weeb ways now.
I found your MyAnime list.
AnimeLover985.
Well, I mean, you clearly just made that account
and did that.
Appreciate the 250, though.
Thank you, Manboy777.
Jess, you got it, thanks for the 250.
So there is a species of shrimp
that has 16 cones in its eyes.
We have three, red, blue, and green.
With 16 cones, that's about 500 primary
and secondary tertiary colors.
How fucked is that?
That's weird.
You just can't, there's no way to know what that looks like.
So why hasn't science come up with a way to clone that?
There's no way we can, no.
Okay, a shrimp is a shrimp, right?
We don't have a way to find out
with their genetic DNA and their code
how that happens and how we can't, you know,
get eyes, cover our brain with eyes.
Why can't we do that?
Our eyes have yet to open.
I don't know how we can figure that out.
Thank you, Jess, you got it.
Sad, Vega, thanks for the 250.
Jerma, another good stream, but really,
you as a bartender, that may be your weirdest skit.
Are you gonna dress up in a fancy bartender tuxedo, too?
Also, you should take a look at a game called Outward.
It's kind of an older style RPG, RPG,
with modern game mechanics that seems really good
and has co-op you can do with a friend, maybe.
I don't know, I don't think so.
That's how Alex played that game,
and he told me that it was kind of a brutal game
that was kind of, maybe would be fun with two people,
but maybe not, I don't think.
It's not in the cards right now.
Would you beat Dark Souls?
I mean, isn't that game like you start,
like it says Kenshi with a dodge roll?
We'll see.
One of the plans does look interesting, though.
Talk about Outward.
Holy shit, he didn't say, I'll look into it.
I'll check it out, but thank you, though.
Also, thank you to Void01 for the $2.50, the 250.
Jerma, update on that TF2 item based on your hair.
It's getting close to being done,
and we're having some troubles figuring out
the side and back views.
Can we get a face cam reference?
I don't have clothes on,
so I cannot turn the face cam on.
I'll give you some references on Saturday,
because I'll be on face cam the whole time.
You'll see me Saturday, on camera.
Ass slap incoming, nope, those are pants.
But thank you, Void.
Zalaski, thank you for the 10 bucks.
Thank you, Zalaski.
And it is a Giazio, is it linked to a rock?
Oh, there's a giant Spongebob coin rock thing, okay.
We were talking about, I've got some weird tangents.
Sometimes we just go, just start talking about random
nonsense, but thank you, Zalaski, for the 10 bucks.
Appreciate it.
Honey Chain, thanks for the 250.
Don't you hate it when you buy an ice cold Arizona,
open it up, take a sip, and it's actually PVR?
I hate when that happens.
Thank you for the 250.
Thank you, Frody and Weapon for the 250.
Enjoy your two and a half Arizona green teas.
I will.
Who drinks their money?
It was an elaborate conversation.
I wouldn't even, I can't even describe how that
conversation even happened.
Just did.
Something or other, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, bank just called and apparently
everything is wrong.
I'm gonna start paying for bits in cash.
They'll get the first envelope in two to three weeks.
Cash, paying with cash.
Where'd you get that cash from?
You carry that cash, like you're paying in cash.
Interesting.
Why, that was weird.
Hey, Meef, playable, thanks for the 250.
Monster energy, blood and basil, five stars.
Mithril bong, thanks for the five dollars.
Hey, Jerma, just wanted to say go fuck your hat.
Fuck my hat.
I'm not wearing a hat, but thanks for the five dollars.
Hatless today, hatless yesterday.
But thank you, Mithril bong, for the five bucks.
Snoozing copter, thanks for the 250.
Your story reminded me of something.
One day my mom was doing garden work outside,
and when she came back in and told me,
she was hearing scratching sounds in her ear,
and asked me to take one of those ear magnifying glasses
to take a look, so I did, and I didn't see anything
until a spider came crawling at me.
Imagine looking at a spider through a magnifying glass.
It's huge, and you could see the eyes and the hairs.
It was like a jump scare.
That's, that's un-fucking-believable.
Your mother had a spider in her ear canal.
What?
That, that's what happens in the first hour of a horror movie
when the main character thinks that something's wrong,
they got like cursed or grabbed by like the witch
or something, and then she goes to the,
or they go to the doctor, or he goes to the doctor,
and the witch doesn't go to the doctor.
Well, I'm sure the witch can go to the doctor too,
that's fine.
You know, I grabbed somebody, I think I gave him something.
But the doctor does that.
That's the part of the horror movie
where it starts to really turn for the worse.
What a scary movie.
That's fucked up though.
If that's true, that's fucking insane.
Jerma lied about 5K subs thanks to the 250.
You did change your name though, I will give you credit.
Hey Jerma, have you heard of a game called
Digimon World Championship?
I had it as a kid and it's like this game,
but you can't control your monsters in battle.
You might want to check it out if you like these games.
We talked about it a couple of days ago.
He did lie, but it was April Fools.
It's not a lie if it's April Fools.
It's an April Fools gag.
Wait, wait, wait, there's this two Jerma lied now.
That's not the person changing their name?
How many of these are there?
That's funny.
Hey smelly boy, thanks for the 250.
Please do an orc impression.
No, I can't, I can't, it's too late.
I'm too tired.
Me, me orc.
There, that's one of the workers.
Hey pin, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jerma, been having some serious heart issues
due to my ADHD medication.
Despite the fact that I took the lowest dose.
I made the decision to taper off of it.
It's hard to live with ADHD,
especially because I got a taste of what it was like
to just think clearly and for the most part, be normal.
I'm frustrated that nothing in my life seems to go well
and every time I try to do something to improve my life,
it ends up making things worse.
It's been rough.
I had a similar scenario.
When I was younger, I was prescribed Ritalin and Adderall
when I was like 16, 15.
And I didn't like, I didn't like the way it made me feel.
So I tapered off it and I stopped taking it.
But yeah, that's probably when I was,
that was when I was probably like in high school,
like junior high maybe, like 14, 15.
I would know, I wasn't on both at the same time.
I was on one and then transitioned to the other one.
But I didn't really like it.
My appetite dropped.
It was, I wasn't eating a lot when I was taking Adderall.
So I tapered off it and stopped doing it.
But hopefully, in my case at least,
I just kind of tried to work around it,
figure out what I was good at doing
in the time that my brain would focus on it.
And so far, I mean, I'm in my 30s now, I'm doing all right.
I'm doing okay with it.
I mean, you guys know me pretty well at this point.
Sometimes like it's just, it'll crop up that like,
holy shit, just all over the place.
But you know, it is what it is.
But hopefully you can figure it out
because it does take time to figure that out.
And sometimes, sometimes it would mean,
like you said, low dosages, low dosage of medicines.
You know, sometimes you do have to get on something
to kind of start to get better or feel better.
And that's fine.
I really hope you get it sorted out soon though.
Because it can be difficult to work with.
CBD helps my bad anxiety issues.
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of research and data
going into like CBD, things that it can do, the benefits.
That's a conversation for your doctor though.
And a lot of doctors are really warming up
to the fact that that's a possibility.
But I wish you the best of luck.
We also had 283, $2.83 from Errolis.
There's a Jex wallpaper here on Reddit.
I told you that that was the screenshot, right?
Why do you have to always use the picture?
Why do you guys always have to use this fucking picture?
We're making the face with the crazy eyes.
There's so many different images you could use.
It has to be the one with my crazy bug eyes.
It's a classic.
Thank you, Errolis, for the 283 and the image.
Krosk, you know, I have 370 images of you.
I've got a folder of you.
If that's what you look like, I know, but still.
Peek-A-Banana, thanks for the 250.
They just said Germa Hart, thank you so much.
Felix Phillips, thanks for the three bucks.
You're great.
Thank you, Felix, for the three dollars
and the incredibly nice message.
You're great too, thank you.
Let's get the credits rolling here.
Thank you so much, everybody.
All the community subs given tonight.
All the resubs, all the new subs.
All of you, thank you.
Finally, we had Tyler Mike came in with 250.
Hey, Germa, just wanted to let you know,
Ace Attorney for PC releases on Tuesday.
Obviously, you have a lot of stuff planned at this point.
Just making sure it's on the list.
It is.
Those are gonna be some just relaxing streams.
Kind of like the Monster Rancher streams,
where we just kind of hang out, talk a lot of shit.
Have a good time.
Those will just be fun little chill streams.
That's gonna have to be after the VR,
because I do want to get through some more
that I've had the itch for VR.
And that's it, thank you everybody for the bits.
See you all tomorrow.
More puking.
When did I puke?
I mean, I almost puked on the Sekiro stream.
Hey, should Sekiro have an easy mode?
I don't know, maybe, I don't think so,
but ask the guy that almost threw up
because it was too hard.
I mean, it almost happened.
Yeah, the Jaws game too,
but that was because of motion sickness.
I was also sick too.
Try not to use a walkthrough on Ace Attorney.
No, I got plenty of walkthroughs here.
They chat in the chat room.
You guys can help me.
I'll put like a timer on the screen,
for if I can't figure the case out,
then you guys will just tell me the answer.
I'll make a game out of it.
I'll give myself like 20 minutes per case.
And if I just can't do it, then like,
okay guys, what, help me.
20 minutes.
Watch the anime instead.
That might be better.
I, what do I got here?
I gotta clean up this desk.
My desk is covered in PlayStation 2 games
and cases and discs and everything.
Each case is an entire stream after the tutorial, really?
Am I gonna, am I getting myself into something
that's gonna be over my head here?
Yeah, nah, nah, okay.
All right, well, that's gonna be it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for Risk of Rain 2.
Gonna check it out.
And after that, see you on Saturday.
That's all.
Take care.
We went a little late tonight, but that's good.
I mean, it's not good, but it's all good.
That's what I meant to say.
It's all good.
And I'm gonna sit here,
because it's almost eight hours.
And you know me.
It's 7.59.19 right now.
So I gotta sit here for 40 seconds.
Wait till it's eight hours so I can turn it off.
Good night.
Awkward goodbye streamer.
Okay, see ya.
Yeah, see ya, okay.
Run ads.
No, I'm not running ads.
I'll run ads tomorrow.
I'll run ads tomorrow at the end of tomorrow's stream.
30 minute ad.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Fine, fine, fine.
All right, here you go.
I'm giving you 30 seconds.
His one 30 second ad, that's it.
I'm out.
I promised.
All right, here's 30 seconds.
Why do you guys have to beg me for ads?
This feels wrong on every level.
All right, see you in 30 seconds.
Those of you that don't wanna see this, see you tomorrow.
Here we go.
It's running.
Ads.
I can't see the ads, JermaPluto.
Okay, if a marketing person saw this chat,
you know how many emails I would receive
from various companies if they saw the timestamps
for these chat messages?
Holy shit.
You see that audience of people that are all begging
for advertisements and to be marketed to?
Hey, Jerma985, what's going on, man?
I work for XYZ company,
and we really wanna do a thing with you.
Maybe play some ads at the end of your stream.
All right, people should be coming back now.
All right, welcome back.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Take care, guys.
Hey, thanks for watching the ad.