I was not late. I was on time. Yeah. I'm here at the appropriate hour today.
You were one minute late. That's all right. All right. What's your favorite word?
Uh, truck. I don't know. I don't know about it. I just thought of the first thing I could think of.
I don't know. I thought of the first word I could think of. I was just like, okay, I guess
whatever. It's pretty fine. Or what are you saying? What did you say? Let me see. What did you say?
What should I get a Taco Bell? I'm in the, I'm in the line. Please hurry.
Cheesy goody to crunch. That's it. Big two of them. That's it. And maybe a drink.
Does he even know he's live? I just clicked the button. I know I'm live. He doesn't have enough
fiber. Oh, quantum. Yeah. No, quantum is a good word. Quantum. Quantum just sounds elaborate.
It sounds interesting. Something's going on with that word. You know what I mean? It's very
interesting. Lots to break down with that word. Quantum. Fulcrum. That's pretty good.
Package is a good word. A lot of good words. Anyways, he doesn't even remember saying that.
No, I don't. My hard drive is being filled with new information and I'm cleaning out the shit
from before. I have a full hard drive. Just wait. Just wait. I want you all to wait until you turn
over 35. When you get to be 35 plus, shit just starts getting front filled. You only have a 512
kilobyte hard drive? Bro, upgrade. I know. Stir just cleared Q remastered. It's time to pack it up.
You know, I talked to Stir about this and I was like, oh yeah, that game Q remastered. Yeah.
Like, what a fucking ridiculous, hard fucking game. Like, you played it for like 20 minutes,
right? He's, he loves this game and apparently he plays it all the time and he's almost 100%
of the whole experience. Really? He's like, yeah, yeah, actually, like I watched you do it and I
kind of felt that way too. Just kind of do it and I got to know what the hell was going on and when
I finally got it, it became like, like it was an amazing experience. Like, wow. I was like,
Stir's got a pretty high IQ. Caveman brain versus genius brain. Which one is which though?
Which one is which? Genius caveman. Dude, you've got a rat brain. Yeah, whatever.
All right. I, my brain is very good at very specific things, but I think we're all like that.
Aren't, aren't you good at a few things that you can really go like, you know, I'm really good at
this. I'm not really good at these things too though. You can't be good at everything and you're
not bad at everything either. Get it? You can't be good at everything, but you're not bad at
everything either. Write it down. That's a quote. I made that quote. Write it down and you attribute
that to me when you say that. Is that fair? I wrote it down. I wrote it down. That's not how
quotes work. All right. We're going to play Katamari. I didn't even know this came out last week. I was
unaware. Uh, we love Katamari. The remake came out, played the first remake. Obviously, I love
this franchise. I think this is a great franchise. Really cool to see that they ordered and recalibrated
another one too. This is apparent. This is the second game. This is Katamari 2. I saw one bat
chest, which is a really good sign that usually, okay, if one person is bat-chesting something
and it's not a wave of them, then all right. Then that just means,
all right, come on. That means that that person's just, it's Katamari. You don't bat-chest Katamari
nowadays. No, we don't. Who does? You probably don't even know what the game is. You probably
don't even know what the game is. You just, you just saw that I was playing it and I was excited
about it. So you wanted to bat-chest to make me feel bad. You can quote that one too. Exactly.
Yeah. All right. Let's, I don't, I'm probably not going to stream for too, too long tonight.
I, I don't want to be excuse Andy, but I do have kind of a bad headache and it's going
to affect me. You can already tell like four or five hours from now. So not that short.
I just probably not like over six or seven hours. All right. You guys ready?
It's going to chill. It's going to be a chill stream. Oh, here it is.
Drink more water. I, I am. I don't just get up in the morning and go through my whole day and
afternoon just like, ah, ah, ah, ah, something's wrong today. I just, I just wish I, maybe if I
had one sip of water, who'd fix it? I drink a lot of water. I'll prove it. See? All right. Let's go.
Is the controller work? Oh, that's kind of loud. It's kind of loud for me.
No, I'm not a milk guy. Why do people ask that every week? Hey dude, are you, do you like,
are you like drink, do you like to drink milk and shit? It's like, why are you asking this question?
You ask it all the time. Hey dude, talk about milk for 20 minutes. Why do you want me to continue
to do this? All right. Let's watch. This is good. This game is so good too. I think this is probably
the best one, isn't it? Wasn't two, was two or three the best one? Yeah, two is the best one,
isn't it? We talked about video game soundtracks and how, what is actually the best video game
soundtrack? Katamari is probably up there in the top five. It is. It actually might be one or two.
It's possible. These games always had unbelievable soundtracks. Every single track was amazing. Every
single one. There wasn't a single bad song. It's definitely in the top five, top 10. We're not
skipping any songs. All right. Let's go. This is, I opened this. Making a new save. Yeah. I opened
the game just to capture it. So don't worry. I didn't play already. I'm going to be very upset
about that. Are you bald? No. I'm getting there though. I got another like at least five good
years. Bold yet sensitive and rugged to boot. Tolerant and compassionate with a heart deeper
than the oceans. Such is the great cosmos and the king that rules over it is marvelous to behold.
Except for the one time that he destroyed all the stars in the universe. No big deal really.
That was a good laugh. Having come to and realized the folly of his ways, the wisest of kings sent
to the planet earth, his beloved son, the prince, and commanded him to make a cotton
groove. You're not bald by eating an entire cantaloupe on screen.
That was an AI generated comment.
All up. Rolled and rolled until the Katamari was big enough to be lifted up to space to
replace the shiny stars that were so grievously lost. And that dear friends was the plot and
purpose of the fabulous game called. Katamari Daversley.
And it rolled right out of the game to bundle away the many and sundry ills that blight the
modern world. Overnight, the king found himself a superstar. The adulation of the crowd knew
no limits. Every audio book you've ever heard, by the way, every audio book you've ever listened to
is that oh dear such a chorus fans crying out from all and I love it by the way
to kill not enough stars. Oh, sweet memories. Yes, it was that time.
Time we smashed all the stars in the sky. It's like something out of a dream. We have totally
forgotten. What made us remember? The only place with stars is around earth.
Looks like Katamari Daversley was being lazy. Looks like Katamari Daversley had everyone fooled.
What impresses us all over is the scale of destruction we were. We were on a roll. Yes,
we were. Fierce and fabulous. We certainly were. We were really something. Yes, yes.
Oh, speaking of something, there is a tidbit. Not what we get. Not that we get it, but it seems
we're quite a hit. Go on. A big hit with earth. The stars are full of stuff. The star now apparently
full of our fans. Prince, prince, what do you think they love about us? Our looks, our tights,
our mustache. Oh, Eureka, we've got it. It's our chin. Yes, that must be it. Yes, must be.
Our chin is so magnificent. Earth is full of dedicated followers of our chin.
I want to hold your chin. Let me feel your goatee. They ask so nicely, so passionately. How can we
say no? So now, our prince, we must go to earth and grant our fans their wishes. Their wishes are
our chin's commands. Our chin's commands are our wishes. And so on. A succulent meal. Oh, that's
right. They did this overworld thing. Looks like the fans in the select plaza want to ask the prince
something. Talk to them. An icon will be displayed at the bottom of the screen when new fans arrive.
Make their dreams come true. I love this part. I'm going to turn it up a little.
Okay. Hi. Oh, I forgot. How do I do this? Nice to meet you, your highness. Boy, it was fun. I
think it must have been fun. I'm sorry. I've forgotten. I've completely forgotten how to roll
the Katamari. I know I'm a goof, but I love Katamari Devasi. Help me remember, please, Vittorio.
All right. Let's leave our fans on earth to the prince. Now, where shall we go and play?
Oh, it's the prince. What do you want with it? What? Oh, you forgot. Forgot how to roll the
Katamari? How to enjoy the Katamari? The meaning of life? Of course you forgot. The things you can't
forget that make you hurt. We think it may be better not to dredge things up. Your highness is
cool. Cool? No, it's important to remember. No, it's crucial to remember. Yes. Just try and think
back. Yes. Yes. Bugleberry. Bugleberry voice. Lots of different applications. Friends that forgot all
about Katamari Devasi. Poor friends. Playing the very first game of Katamari Devasi. Would you guys
buy an audiobook? Just like a horror story read by Bugleberry? Was that something that you would
want? All right. So what is a Katamari? What could a Katamari be? What does Katamari taste like?
Does it have a point? Why roll? Why make it bigger? So many opinions and schools of thought,
but let's just try it out first. Hear ye, hear ye. We present to you an all and sundry the Katamari.
Only if it's at least eight hours. It would have to be a book that I got permission to read and
kind of have it licensed out to me or something. It would have to be a really obscure horror book
and it has to be less than 200 pages. Take the standard Katamari and roll it firmly.
Okay, it's a left and right stick. I kind of remember. All right, let's go.
Yeah, you go backwards. You can go side to side. Just spin around. There we go. Throw up some stuff.
The best part of the game. This is okay. This whole game is just oddly satisfying the entire
game. If you actually never played this before, even seen this be played, get it. Go get it right
now. Get it now. If there's one thing you do this week, this game, this game is not expensive,
right? I think it's like 20 bucks, 30 bucks. It wasn't that bad, right? 30 bucks.
What the heck am I looking at? You're looking at a very, very good video game.
All right, we have to overcome the wall. Not big enough yet.
Soundtrack is so good too. Just wait till you hear some of these classic beats.
Oh, I can go down. All right. Wowies, you got up there. Prince turn. Oh, that's huge. Yep.
That's a big, that's a big freaking deal. Quick turn. You can also do the Katamari view. You can
just kind of take a look. These things get ready. I'm not going to spoil it for anybody that doesn't
know. This game is just really fucking good. That's all you need to know. Okay. Prince view.
Ah, miracle eye. How are this? That's just zoom. Miracle eye. All right, then we're going to do the
dash. The dash is just going to go. When you're just a little bigger, you could maybe roll ace up
here. This is ace, a cousin to the prince or a cousin once removed. We forgot. Cousin, kin,
something like that. Alrighty. Time for you to challenge ace head on. If you go like this, you
can go fast. Somebody put a different soundtrack on. What? I'm not going to put a different
soundtrack on one of the greatest soundtracks of all time in all video games. Can we get a
poll up to see this is Katamari Damacy soundtrack. One of the most important pieces of media in
history. Yes or no. Can we get a vote? All right, let's get them. Ah, fabulous. You're pretty good.
Anyway, let's go back. Royal rainbow. Is Katamari soundtrack a big deal? That's a good vague way
of word it. I like it. Is it a big deal? Hmm. Was it like this? Katamari Damacy? Honestly,
this is not what we were thinking. But looks kind of fun. A kind of sort of fun game. 18 centimeters,
seven millimeters. We see we are a little tough. So big. It's just a training run. An unbelievable
size. Astonishing really. Very and truly fabulous. Oh, it's cousin ace. What were you doing on earth?
You at the tutorial stage? We have no idea what you're talking about. Hmm, this feels kind of,
this feels strange-ish. Not that we understand if that's a good thing or not. Oh, wow. I remembered
everything. Really everything this time. It's totally the best. Katamari Damacy. Your highness,
thank you so much. This Katamari is just a token of my thanks. I'd like to offer it to you. Oh,
really? You're giving it to us? Seriously, fabulous. Thank you. We are so pleased.
What should we do with it? Oh, we can pop it up into the cosmos. Yes, that's what we do.
Oh, all right. So you guys agree. Look, it's a star now. Wow. It's so beautiful.
Are you going to play the Jump King DLC? No. We totally forgot to tell you, but this is the
select plaza. Talk to fans. Chat with cousins. Do a little saving. Look at your collection.
Move around a little maybe while pressing X or right bumper. When you get tired of rolling,
just hang out here. Okay. Cool. I think we can. Yep. We can change. Should I be ace or should
I be the prince? I'll be ace. Collection 0.4%. Options. I think we're good with audio and
everything. I mean, I put the graphics in a good spot. All right. Let's do the next one.
I want to see the Royal Rainbow. Hello, your highness. I just love you. That beard, that nose,
that chin, that style. I love it all. But I love the Royal Rainbow the best of all.
My dream is to see a real live one. Please show me. Oh, but of course I'll show you. We are hungry.
Our tummy is empty. What shall we eat? Oh, it's ace. Hmm. What? What kind of food? Huh? Royal
Rainbow. Why, when our tummy is so empty? No way. Boring. Your highness, you're so striking.
Striking. Oh, we so like rainbows. You must simply must, you simply must see it.
Should we go ahead and make a Katamari too? Yes. Yes. Yes. Let's go. All right. Yes. I'm so ready
for this. We're hungry. Oh, let's roll here. This is an earth home, so unbelievably small.
Plenty spacious for ace, but not so much for us. Oh, we forgot about the Katamari. How about this
much time to make this big Katamari? Three minutes or 15 centimeters. If you can manage,
that would be nice. All righty, ace. It's all yours now. Let's go. Oh, your first ever roll-up.
It's six out of 10 today. It's six, 10. Congratulations. What did I even get? All
right. I gotta go. Only three minutes. Yep. Nice. All right. The food. I don't want to leave until I
get everything. What was it? 15 centimeters. All right. Yeah. All right. I gotta go this way.
Too small to get anything else. I can't get the cat. Not yet. I want to get the cereal box too.
Remind me of the cereal box up there. Oh, shit. That's bad. Maybe not. No, it's okay. Oh, cousin.
Come here, cousin. Yes. You just rolled up some weird buffness. Wait. Second cousin macho. Oh,
stop kidding in the way. Second cousin macho. Can't get these. All right. I'm almost there.
I got plenty of time. 15, right? Not big enough for the tennis balls.
Oh, look at all this. Look at how juicy this is. One minute left. We got it.
All right. I'm big enough to. I don't think I'm big enough for the cat.
15 centimeters already. We asked for a 15. Wait, what? This would be exact? Does it have to be
exact? No, I don't think so. Make it bigger. Oh, your first ever crash. Wait, what? It's six,
10. Today is six, 10. The birthday of your first crash. Congratulations. I want to get all this
stuff, but it's all right. Yup. Come on. Oh, sorry. I love this game. Our tummy is empty. You're done.
Shall we go home and get something to eat? Yes. Turn the music up. I'll go in the options and
turn it up a little. I'm looking at my tags again. Tournament art, dislike boat cheese,
not the sus guy. Stop asking. This is we're going to find this stream and look at those tags and be
like, I fucking hate this guy. I would read those tags and go, I hate this streamer. I don't like
this guy. Like this cream puff that looks so good. Oh, it's Katamari. That was a surprise, but what
a word. I don't know. 18 centimeters. Yes. Well, so undistinguished. You can go bigger. You know,
do us a favor and roll a bigger one. Oh, it's second cousin Macho. What were you doing on Earth?
Making friends with the crayfish. I have no idea what you're talking about.
This feels, uh, snacks-ish. I had mostly snacks. That's better. Do we understand what snacks mean?
I got to see the Royal Rainbow, but it wasn't exactly lively. I think it's because the Katamari
was so small. I'll give your highness this stale old Katamari. Oh no. Okay. Into the cosmos. Oh,
it's a star now. Wow. It's so beautiful. Wrong voice. Biscuit Uranus. That storyboard was quite
interesting. It's a storyboard, but the pictures move. There's music. Extreme storyboard. That's
what it is. It's called a movie. A fascinating movie. So that storyboard movie, what it showed
is a glimpse into our youthful days. A pretty tumultuous tale of daring do. We can't wait for
episode two, but if we keep rolling, we'll eventually get to see it. All righty. We're
going to roll on ahead. See you later. Battle mode has been unlocked. Talk with the one player and
two player characters together. Where's Macho? Probably should save the game. There is an auto
save, but I don't trust it. Okay. Usual stuff? Controls usual stuff. Yeah. All right. Rumble.
It's fine. All right. Here we go. Background music. We want the sound effects a little bit lower,
but we want the music a little higher. That's correct, right? All right. We got a lot of new
things going on. All right. What are you doing? I'm really sleepy, but first I want to see a big
Katamari. The songs you can set to background music increase as you play the game. Set your
favorite song to the BGM using Y. Hey King dude, you're so cool and relaxed lounging around as
usual. I love Katamari Damacy. I love how mellow it is. I'm copying Katamari Damacy and lounging
around. Oh, now I'm falling asleep before I do. I want to see a real Katamari. Come on, dude.
Show me. Oof. We were asleep. Our eyes opened. Oh, Macho. What? What? He wants to see a Katamari
before he goes to bed? What? Are you serious? Oh, this is Katamari Damacy. We are not that easy.
We work hard at rolling, you know. No, no, not possible. Cannot be done. No. Your highness is
the best. The best? No, not impossible. Not at all. Yes, you are very and absolutely right. If anything,
we should play except just before bed. Yes. All aboard. Let's make a Katamari. It's the best.
So sleepy after all. Let's roll here. It's a room again, but let's just work on getting it big.
You make it bigger, you can roll it in lots of other places. Um, let's see. How about this much
time to make this big? A Katamari. If you can manage, that would be nice. All righty, Macho.
It's all yours now. All right. Got to be, got to be big. Start with the basics. Shit. I'm losing
time here. I got to get bigger. All right. Sorry, we fell. No, this is perfect. Actually, perfect.
Oh, I'm not big enough for the nail polish or whatever it is. I have to come back here.
Something is coming. What do you mean something is coming? All right. I get the batteries. Here
we go. Nice. I think I can get all these batteries. Yep. And the locks, too. Yeah, I'm going to get
all this stuff. Where's the prince? I changed character. I went to Macho. All right. A few more
things. Something's coming. Nice. All right. I'm big enough for the toothbrushes. Can I go outside?
No, I have to be 20 centimeters. All right. I'll probably upgrade here in a sec. You should speed
run this game. Um, no, it's all right. I like just playing this game. All right. It's about,
we're about to snowball here in about 10 seconds, I want to say. Oh, all right. I'm going to go
through the middle. All right. Loading cans. Ah, finally, we can talk. We have a little trouble
with loading. You can't talk during loading. You know, we finally have our voice back, but we can't
talk when it first starts loading. Goodness gracious. We're sleepy. We're just such a sleepyhead.
You can get to more places if you roll on from here. We're very drowsy, but we'll keep it together.
All right. We can. I'm not going to leave yet though. Like this stuff in here that I don't want
to. How much time do I have? Four minutes. These are big. All these tuna cans. Oh yeah. All right.
I'll go now. Oh, I got a crayfish. Can I go out out? Oh my goodness. I think I can. All right. I
gotta hurry up. Everything's a little too big. There we go. Oh my gosh. I can't get the little
elephants. Oh shit. That hurt. Give me all this food. Shit. I'm not big enough. Oh well. I need
to be 40 or 50. I gotta go speed this way. Get it. It's 40. I'll get it. I need to upgrade one more
time and I'll be able to get all this other stuff. There we go. Give me the bottles. All right. I'm
good. Look at this over here. Look at all this shit to get. I think I get 50 or 60. This dude
is never playing Zelda. You're probably right. You're probably right, man. I'll be happy with
50. Oh I got somebody. A present. Oh no. I didn't get. I got a present. Did I get the lizard? Oh
give me all this. I could get so much bigger if I just pick up some more of this. Cousin was in the
house. Your Katamari is as big as 17 of these toolboxes. That's cool. I missed a cousin.
That's okay. But I don't know. I might play it. I had a lot of fun but I don't know. I don't have a
plan. You know what I mean? We fell asleep with our eyes open. Oh there's a Katamari here.
Came out of nowhere. 63 centimeters. Makes us sort of sleepy. It's not small but it's a
stale Katamari. So average. We think you can make it much bigger. Wow. We got a camera as a present.
Fabulous. We love cameras but it's far too small for us. Macho. You can have it from a fan so make
sure you appreciate it. This feels like this Katamari feels necessities-ish. Like what was
that mean? Doesn't sound very nice. What do you call this feeling? I'm awake but not alert.
Hungry too. I mean this is just a regular old Katamari. You can have this one dude. Oh really?
You're giving it to us? Seriously. Fabulous. Thank you. We're so pleased. What should we do with it?
Into the cosmos. Oh it's a planet now. Awesome dude. I want to travel the universe in my dreams.
Play Breath of the Wild off stream. Yes. I don't know. By the way, are you using all those presents
from our fans? Do you know how to use them? You know the birthday cake in the select plaza? Yes.
Go there to put on your presents. They'll give you a snazzy new look. Little costume pieces.
You get a camera as a present. You can take pictures with the Prince camera
in Prince view. Take a picture of any stickers you find with the camera. Collect a lot to get a
picture frame. Oh okay. You can take a selfie using Selfie from Prince camera. Really? Okay well
we're going to put the camera on. Cool. Alright let's get on. Put a video of Zelda being played
in the corner. I need Zelda sensory videos going on for you guys to want to watch the stream.
Alright this one's like a beach level but what else we got? Your Majesty 8%. Alright let's do
this one. A new approach to Ikebana? What is Novell Ikebana? What does it mean to be new is
newness? What is new Ikebana? What is Novell Ikebana? Am I saying this wrong? I'd like to ask
your dynamic highness. We like red roses. The divine flowers. The deadly thorns. Oh shivers. Oh
macho. What? It's pronounced. How do you pronounce it? Ikebana. Ikebana? We like roses so we're all
about gardening. No interest in Ikebana though. Not at all. Your highness is so sensual. Sensual?
Ikebana is too fabulous. We think this is the time for Ikebana. Off we go to create a new style.
Oh wonderful. This is the land of dreams. It's so beautiful. We are awestruck by the power of mother
nature. Oh completely slipped our mind. How about this much time to roll up as many flowers as you
can and make a beautiful herbaceous katamari. Alrighty macho. It's all yours now. Pick up flowers.
I don't know how many you need. I think it's just as many as you can get. Anything? Like I want to
get that big one in the middle. I don't want to neglect any certain area. Really easy to do that
in this game. How? You'll miss everything that moves. Oh wonderful. It ran off. Macho you silly
goose. What wait talking about the getting hit by the what was it an animal? Ow. That's good enough.
Can I get everybody yet? Let me see can I get this person? Yep. Can I pick up the grass?
Yep all right I'm gonna go up. Whoa that was that was a bird okay.
Sunflowers yep. I'm gonna go all the way down on the other side.
All right I'm gonna go the other side now. This is a whole entire what is over there all right
I'm gonna go this way. 600 I wonder how many I need to be good. I'm going down here.
Can I pick up the actual? Yeah I can. How big am I? One meter. You have to roll up moving things
before they run off. So romantic. Two minutes? All right what about the all right in here.
What's that? A flower. It's rather large isn't it? All right let's see if I'm big enough to pick
up more bigger things. Not yet. Am I really not big enough to pick that up? No. 700 oh a lot over
here. 800. Shit. Oh oh I gotta get over a thousand. Oh cousin. This is gonna be close.
Oh come on. There we go a thousand nice. Right when I get big enough to actually start picking
up everything. Oh it's all right I got to a thousand. Go. Okie dokie mokey all done with
the flower power katamari. Your katamari is as big as four thousand three hundred of these.
Well that's pretty flowered up already. Want to go home now? Yes. Passionate love. Passionate
amore. The international message of the red rose. So fabulous. Too fabulous. This katamari
is fabulous too. Wait when did you make this? One thousand flowers. Oh it sort of has that never
before seen vibe. It's a katamari but kind of soft. A katamari that dares to wear perfume.
But fairly certain there are far more beautiful katamaris out there.
Oh it's cousin Ichigo. What were you doing on earth? Traveling on the back of a baby deer.
We have no idea what you're talking about. This feels kind of flowers-ish. That was mostly what
was there. Of course it's probably because you paid nothing but flowers. I'm starting to see
something now. There's a clue in this katamari. From here on I have to find it for myself.
Yes thank you so much your highness. Please keep this katamari as token of my thanks.
Okay let's make it a planet. I wish you were named Luigi. Why? The sunflower planet. Oh
probably gonna have some major sunflower updates. In the next week or two I would say
it'll be a major sunflower update. Are you growing a sunflower out of your ass? Um yeah let's just go
with yeah. I'm gonna make this person really excited. The answer is no but whatever. Cool okay.
Let's play with Ichigo. Hello please can you clean this up? Music list. Hold on. Should I
pick a song? Register your favorite songs. Once you've registered more than two songs you can
set a favorite. I don't know if we can do this yet. Not yet. The real thing is something else.
Anyway nice to meet you your highness. You're as stylish as ever. I'm a parent with a son in
elementary school. He loves katamari too. He likes the rolling up part. He rolls up everything so
there's nothing left. But his room is a huge mess. Seems he can tidy up things in the game but
your highness please do something. I feel this. When a game asks me to clean, like my favorite
part of the whole game but cleaning up my own desk is like nah nah I fuck that. I don't want
to do that. Why is that? Why? I will spend six hours making sure the desk in the game is pristine
but not my own real desk. We tidied it all up in the last Katamari Damacy. Ichigo do you even get
that part? Huh? What the kids room? What happened to our story about cleaning up the universe?
Did we finish talking? We don't care about kids rooms. Actually I love Katamari. Love it.
You say kids room we say miniature universe. Did you know that? We're very good at cleaning up
miniature universe. Anyway let's go tidy. Rarely compared to the universe this isn't cluttered at
all but still bothers us. It bothers our love of order. Is this many things cluttering this room?
So let's clean them all up as quickly as possible. We know you can do it Ichigo. Alrighty
good luck. All right I gotta get everything. Oh present. Shit okay I gotta get everything.
I'll have to come back up here. Shit I'm really not big enough besides I can only pick up gum.
There's no time limit so this one this is fine. Oh doesn't some weird caterpillar.
Wait it's second cousin Lamor. Oh stop. I don't know what he said.
Ow all right there we go now I can really start to move.
This one's this one's banging. Yeah this is a good one.
32 remaining. If I do this in under four and five minutes I'll be happy.
Come on. Come on hurry up. Back up for the gift now. I'll make sure to get that before I'm done.
Let's head back up. All right this is the start. Give me that present. All right got a gift.
I think that's just the stuff over here now. I got the character right. Yeah I'm good. It's
the last item right here. Two. Shit what did I miss? I don't know what I missed.
Oh something up here. Yep one more item. Find blind. Am I? What do you mean? Where is it?
Ah under three minutes I'm happy with it. I'm happy with under three.
There's a lot of gwa in this franchise.
So stylish and connected but it's far too small for us.
Ichigo you can have it. For the fans I'll make sure you appreciate it.
Oh it's second cousin Lamor. What were you doing on earth?
Nothing much. Well that was unexpectedly honest. Oh great the end of day sale is over. I could
have gone if the cleanup were done faster and better. Oh no what am I going to do about dinner?
You can have this thing your highness. Why does everybody hate me? You're giving it to us? Okay.
Untidy planet. It's so pretty once it's a planet because you are so fucking slow. Do you ever think
that you're going too fast? Do you know what I mean? Do you ever think that you should slow down a
little? Do you know what I'm saying? Am I going too slow or are you going too fast? Looks like it
would be shocking to touch. It brings us back but we don't want to remember this how to say it. We
forgot. Are you curious? So then try out the shock. It looks dirty so we won't touch it.
Okay bamboo sword of memory. What does it do? Enough playtime prince. The king of all cosmos
needs knowledge and strength. The road to the throne is long and hard. If you have time to play
then roll a katamari. Experience the king's memories. You'll gain access to more memories
as you make fans dreams come true in the select plaza. Oh do I have anything to do yet?
Study time. This is new content. Oh okay well I'll wait to do this later. This is what kind of like
new DLC. Oh no it's part of the remake then because this game did have DLC didn't it?
Old old Xbox live DLC or was that the third one? Oh my god that scared the shit out of me.
Yeah I have I'm I'm just thinking of the explosion from like three weeks ago.
I want to roll up the brightness. Wait I want to be the new character.
Where's the new character? There you are. La Amor and I want to put on some new clothes.
Here's the cake. Cool all right let's do it. I'm a dog but I love Katamari Damacy. I play it
constantly when I'm in the dog house. I play against other dogs too. I was just thinking can't
you roll up the sun? I'm sure you can. You can roll it up. Katamari Damacy is cool don't you
think La Amor? Really there's even a dog in our fan base. Doggy play too? How cute.
What about the dog? What what did she say? She said why don't we roll up the sun. Really? We want
to hear her too. Woof the sun. Woof woof. She said sun almost maybe maybe almost nearly. But we are
so moved by our canine fan that we will roll it up. The sun anyway. Wowies you're finally here
it's space. Outer space. Okie dokie. Want to go for the sun? Want to roll the earth and roll up
the sun? We know you can do it. All righty good luck. Oh I don't think I'm gonna be able to do
this. Oh it's Cassiopeia. We made that you know. I think I can't do this until the that sun. Wait
not yet. But this is the planets that I have now. Yep yeah so okay there you go ready. I definitely
don't have enough. Oh too bad too bad. It's because the Katamari is still too small.
Which means that there's not enough stars in the cosmos. Not enough not enough so not enough.
Okay uh let's go to the beach. Sounds fun. Nice to meet you your majesty. I don't look
it but I'm a complete brick. Sure I can swim but my dream is to be a gold medalist. I'm thinking
the 100 meter butterfly since I need to practice anyway let's try rolling underwater. We couldn't
go underwater in the first Katamari Demasi. What do you think? You want to roll? Yeah. Have you
never played this game before or something? I'm getting tired of your decision making. What?
You roll over objects with a ball. It's not like I have to choose who lives or dies. I'm literally
rolling objects over with a big ball. We prefer the mountains to the beach. What about you? I mean
yeah I played this game 20 years ago when it came out for PlayStation 2. It's been been almost two
decades since I've played this game. What do you want about underwater not the mountains or the
beach? Well there goes our vacation buzz. You streamed the game. This is a different video game.
This is do you not wait hold on a minute. Do some of you think this is the same remake from two
years ago? What are you guys on about? You already did this. This is a different game. Is it? I mean
the concept of rolling up objects is the same but I don't I don't understand what the what the
concern is. All right let's go. Six minutes. We need 80 centimeters poisonous. Oh there we go.
You're a lot slower underwater too. Am I too small to pick up anything down here?
Oh the ocean floor. There we go. We'll get a little bigger this way. Go this way.
Oh shit. All right. Real didn't. What a quirky laundry. Okay I didn't even see that one.
Oh my god. I just fucking got like magnetized to it.
It's like I couldn't even move. Oh my god. I have no control of the character right now.
There we go. Oh can I not switch? Yeah I can. There we go. Go fast. Am I big enough to pick
the crabs up yet? No. How big does it need to be? 60? 180. I got plenty of time. What? They're too
big. I thought I was going to get all of them. Excuse me. I named one of my koi after you. Like
the fish? That's pretty cool. You got a koi? Damn. Now let's try to snowball this. Go fast.
Oh give me the present. I want that present so bad. Give it to me. Give me the present.
Come on. Wasting time. Yeah I got plenty of time. Well I can get the big crabs now. Now
is the time to go get it. Okay. Can I get these yet? No. I might. I'll probably get 100. I don't
like how floaty you are underwater. Spit around. I didn't get the present but whatever. It's all
right. Give me 100. Well I got a. All right that's a fine number. I got a glug. Nice glug glug go home.
Same number as my IQ. That's right. Brilliant. A lot of crabs. Bob float and roll up.
Oh we did get a new cousin. He's riding the manta ray. Okay cool. Cool. No underwater skills. I get
it. I shouldn't have suggested rolling underwater. I don't need this brick katamari. You can have it
already. They're never happy with what we do. Shhh cutscene. Stop laughing. I'm laughing at
mod chat because they posted 985 new record. You weren't paying attention. Yes I was. We want to
eat something sweet. Oh okay. Hansel and Gretel. We love Katamari Damacy but we love sweets too.
Okay let's do it. Should we make an album? Like a music album? What do you want me to do? Like
have some of the tracks just be poetry. Okay we actually it's not easy for us either. It's not
easy to just sit and watch. No. Huh? What? Sweets? You want to eat sweets? Well we want to eat them
too. Really and honestly a good idea. Now let's go eat. Rock opera concert. I don't know if I'm
capable of doing that. The gingerbread house. It smells like buttercream. So yummy. No we must
control ourselves. Already you have this much time to roll up the gingerbread house. Then once the
sweets. Did I play this game like six years ago? Seven years ago? Like the original version on like
PlayStation 2 for like an hour or something. Maybe not this one. It's all yours now. Let's go.
Wait I'm gonna get all these. These hamburger buns? Holy shit. It's a good game. I don't think I played
the original one if I did. It was probably during like a PlayStation 2 fuckface night.
Probably only played for like an hour or so. From like almost half a decade, decade ago.
Let's go. I don't think it was this one though.
Oh you're gonna. Give me that. Give me that present. I gotta get big enough to get that.
Remind me of that later. No. I'll go back and get the rest of those later.
Oh shit I just picked them both. No I didn't. I got one. Okay all. Wait what? All done. Oh shit.
No no I don't want to go home. The goal was to roll them up at the end. Oh I'm sorry.
All right we got it. Oh sorry I didn't read that part. We're good. I was reading chat. Sorry we'll
make it better. I'm gonna stay in the house. I'm not gonna leave this till it's all gone.
All right I'm already much bigger now. Okay once it's big enough. Okay so it is big enough.
Am I big enough for the fork? No shit.
Come on. I got two minutes. I gotta get to a thousand. Come here. Give me that treasure.
What? Am I seriously not big enough? Get over here. All right we're good. One minute. I got time.
30. At 20 seconds I'm gonna go for it. All right we're good.
That's good enough. 1300. 1400. German streams. Katamari Damacy reroll from four years ago.
Yeah that's the that's the first one. This is the second one. This is the second remake.
You did beautiful Katamari at the end of 2019. That's true. This isn't Damacy because we love
Katamari. That's right. All right they had to have been happy about this right? So here we are. This
is the sweet Katamari. The Katamari that even we could only dream of. It's full of sugary goodness.
Unbelievable. Okay. I think they're happy about it. Wow. We got a long nose as a present. Fabulous.
Oh cool. You wanted to eat cookies? Do you save any cookies for us? Snacks-ish. We're covered in
cream and crumbs after getting rolled up in the sweets Katamari. Oof we're full now. You can have
the rest your highness. Oh they're very happy. Good. As long as they're happy. 2.9? That's not bad.
Hmm new. All right let's pick a new character. Now where's the uh the ball?
There's a big ball character. Where are they? Oops. Where's the ball? There you are. Marnie.
All right Marnie. I'll get you some some different clothes. Perfect. Oh I can only have ah well I'll
keep it. What do you got? So you're the king. My what a fine chin and a fine beard. Anyway my
grandson's been at me. He's asking for Katamari Damacy. He's the apple of my eyes so I'd like
to buy it for him but video games can be bad for you. Right? So I thought I'd play it first to see
for myself. What do you think? Sure. Video games are bad for you. Marnie you're so tiny as uh tiny
as ever. Are you working out? Are you boxing? Oh we used to box. We just remember. We did uh
beat a rabbit once. What? The grandchild? Like we know what that means. Don't interrupt. Can't we
wallow sometimes? Magnificent figure just like I imagined. Magnificent. Yes grandchildren are sweet.
Very precious grandchildren. Ah yes yes. All right let's try little rolling with the grandchildren
too. All right let's roll here another earth house. It's about time to start somewhere new.
Roll in the fresh air to roll with the wind in your hair. Oh we forgot about the Katamari.
How about this much time to make this big a Katamari? That's a long time for three meters.
You can manage that would be nice. All right Marnie it's all yours now.
Shit I fell off already. I'm gonna restart. What? You're going to roll again? Oh really? How nice.
You know the rules. Yes all right good luck. I fell off too and you got it. The early game is
really important. What is going on in this song? It's a bunch of like car traffic.
Go outside at 20. Get out of the way. Get out of the way.
I think I'm just gonna speed across the whole bottom here.
Oh I can't get up there yet. Come on. Keep launching over those. It's not bad pace.
Loading. We can finally talk. When we were little we used to box. Well not just boxing.
We used to study every kind of material art. Ballet, karate, wrestling. That was very tough.
We were always crying. Oh the memories. Material art. It's hard to read today.
Material art. I can go outside but I'm not gonna go out there yet. Hang on for a minute.
Let me get all the change your papers. Let me get all the remote controls. Yes.
Get everything. Get the plate too. Get the frog. Get the plate. Everything. I'm going to the fridge
now. Couldn't get in there before and now I can. Nice. All right good. I'll go outside now. Oh
I got another prince. I want to get up on the table actually. I got plenty of time to go outside.
I want to get on the table. Shit. I was in Johnson. Stop getting in the way.
All right I'm going outside now. I'm getting 100 percent. Oh I got the cat.
I love when cats just watch tv. All right squid. All right I have seven minutes to get huge.
This little snowball is in this corner. Go. Not big enough. Once I get to one meter it'll be good.
I've got to get through everything. Close. Oh we can finally talk. Anyway one day we're in a real
boat. Boxing boat of course. Our semi-final appointment was a rabbit. Appointment? We just
missed it. Oh listen. It's because this music playing in my ears. Both ears at the same time.
And it's kind of it's like louder than me hearing myself talk. I also don't like to hear myself in
my headphones. So it's kind of a it's just all around. I'm like speech jamming myself.
Didn't beat the rabbit by the way. You can get to more places if you roll on from here.
Everyone have a good time. Show that grandson what it's all about. This dude is faded.
Fine.
Dude this dude is fucking faded right now. Yeah gosh I can't take this. The sounds in my ears
right now. I can't talk. I forget how to speak English. I just rolled up a fucking fat joint.
I don't even know what English is. Why do we have language? Why language is a thing? Who made up
the first language? Is there a reason why we don't all just talk the same? Why was there more than
one language ever made? How? What happened? How come we don't just how come we don't communicate
with each other better? Who made the first sauce? All right I actually gotta I gotta get a little
bit better here. Gotta be 50 to get over this. Let's go. Move out of the way. Stop. All right five
minutes. Shit everything's too big. All these TVs are gonna get scooped up here. Oh uh oh.
I may have come here too early. Go back to the smaller area. That's probably a good idea because
I'm gonna be in trouble if I don't. Although I might get over here. It's really easy to go from
two meters to three meters so I think I'm all right. Go go go go go. All right there we are.
We'll snowball now. Shit. Shit. All right I'm gonna turn down because there's way too many
people on the road. All right where's the best way for me to go now? This way. TVs. I got it all in
one go. Come on. Get everybody. Train tracks. Oh okay. The flower beds. I'm getting hit by the
train over and over again. I can pick the fences up that means we're gonna get through. All right
I got one minute. Come on get the houses too. Oh what the fuck is all this? Oh my god the screams.
Did I not get anybody? These things are huge. Get them all. Get me to four. Get to four.
It's all right. I love this game. 3.6. Do you do aromatherapy? Sometimes I don't know. Sometimes
you want to smell something like eucalyptus for like five minutes. What's this in our right hand?
It's a Katamari. Oh 3.6. Isn't that kind of small? No it's not. It's huge.
It's barely a Katamari. You should make a Katamari big enough to make his grandson sit up.
3.6 is big. This feels schooly too. It's a complicated Katamari. Average Andy.
What are you talking about? What should we do with it? Let's put it into the cosmos of course.
The shopping Pluto. Jesus I'm so fucking noises that are quick and loud to me.
You've got me fucked up forever. Oh somebody's quests have opened. What are you? I wish we could
roll together. Just a copycat isn't it? When you make a snowman you roll a snowball to make it bigger.
The game just copies that. Am I right? It must be. I mean it's the same thing. So let's get back to
the roots and make a simple snowman. Oh it's snowing. When it snows we think of snowmen.
Snowmen are cool. Yes they are. Oh it's miney. What do you want?
What? Copycat? A Katamari Damacy? A copycat? A copycat of the snowman?
No no that is so wrong. Not a copycat. We respect the snowman. The snowman is the best. The best.
Roll roll roll that snowman. Let's go hand in hand to winter wonderland. Democracy manifest.
Let's get started on a snowman. Alrighty how do we do this? See the snowman body here. Marnie is
going to roll up a head and then roll it onto the body. Very simple. Yes. Yes. That's all it takes
to make a snowman. Wowee is amazing. Katamari Damacy is so amazing. Let's get back to the basics
and enjoy ourselves. Joy to the Katamari. We just got to make a snowman. Okay. Do I just have to
roll up snow? Or do I have to pick anything up? Oh okay. There's no time limit. And this is a great
song. Can I turn the volume up? Are there any little things I can grab? Or should I just roll
the snow? Oh can I get the penguins? I'm too afraid to do it right now. Everyone's having so much fun
over here. Get up here. What did I just pick up? Now I should be able to get. Oh you just rolled up
something. It was weird and naked. That's la la la.
I'm gonna get all these because I feel like they're good. I think we're pretty much ready
right? That's the size of a snowman's head. I think I'm done. If I was making a snowman that's
what the head would look to see like. Bigger than this? A snowman's head is not that much
bigger than the body. It's smaller. Make it huge? That wouldn't be accurate.
But it'd be funny if it's huge. Well all right.
This is the kind of song. This song just makes me think that everything's gonna be all right.
You know what I mean? Present. Give me that present Santa. I got it. Present for us? A
present from a fan? This head is way too big. I think you guys got this wrong. I think it's
supposed to be normal. It's supposed to be a regular snowman head. I think I can almost
get this whole thing. Roll up everything dude. They're gonna be pissed off. We're gonna really
piss them off. We don't care. That was so like quick. We don't care if they're mad.
What's this penguin selling? Wait I want to take a picture. What are you doing over here?
I'm just making some delicious food. You want some? No thank you. I've eaten today. Okay come back
when you're hungry. The sleigh is just moving on its own. That's kind of sad. It's okay you can
have that. Oh shit it's vaulting me. No go down. Too big. Too big. Too big. No I'm sorry. You have
to live with this guys. You don't demand I make it as big as possible and then start chanting too
big. What is going on up here? Can I get up here yet? Come on get up there. What are they eating?
Are they eating something? Where is that? I get the trees yet? More. More? There's not much left
to get here. I'm almost at maximum. Bro just create a mass extinction event. Yeah do it. Yeah
do it. What the hell are you guys doing? I'm too big to get any of that stuff. All right I've gotten
everybody. I'm not sure I can pick up anything else to get bigger than this. This is it. I can't get
the igloo yet. I can't climb this either. Use the house as a ramp? The snow is making you bigger.
Oh I see the one you're talking about. This one here. No not quite. I want to get the igloo but
oh no still can't climb it. I'm happy with this. This is all right.
I'm happy with this. I'm happy with it. How's the snowman? It looks awful. Oh yes looks good.
Good. It's terrible. The snowman's so fun. So much fun isn't it? We just can't win. It's 200
more fun than a Katamari. What makes this so much fun? What is it? Is it that it's fun or that it
lets you forget yourself? Well we know the answer but it'll build a character for you to figure it
out. Wow we got a present. Looks kind of familiar. Oh it's papa. Oh we want you to have it morning.
Oh it's cousin Lala. What were you doing on earth? Working on a tan in the snow.
We have no idea what you're talking about. Wow that was so fun. Building a snowman is the best.
The best fun. I don't know much about games but as long as it's fun who cares.
It may be a copycat but Katamari Damacy is still fun. Please put the snowman up in the cosmos.
That's something only Katamari Damacy can do. Yes of course. Of course we're going to do that.
Star will it be? We wonder. We can't wait to see it. Snowman planet. Wait can't you?
Do I have this weird memory where you can dance? Can't you dance? There it is. My god what the
fuck? I can't do it. Why? I am I'm all right. I'm all right. I have I have a very very hard limiter
on the audio now so don't worry. Nice to meet you your highness. I think Katamari Damacy is fun. I
play it a lot alone. I've never played the versus mode since I'm alone. Your highness will you be my
friend? I'm sorry. The answer is yes. My students are all big fans of Katamari Damacy. The king of
Katamari Damacy around. They're too excited to work. Your highness can I ask you to come see the
student? Like Carl Jacobs gave subs earlier. When did that happen? Was Carl Jacobs here?
Wait Carl Jacobs was here? Really? Holy shit. Oh hey what's up? It's like two hours ago? Well
thanks dude. Students at earth schools? No they're studying Esperanto. We are tri-pupata. We love
your highness. Love. Hooray done with studying. Perfect time. All righty off to see Bugleberry.
But this is a school. Very lively. Looks fun. What school is for studying? What kind of studying?
Rolling? Oh we forgot about the Katamari. You can only play with the students for this long.
If you can make a Katamari this big they'll have a great time. We know you can do it Marnie. All
righty. No! I want to restart. I'm good. Get all this shit off the desk. I think I'm... Yep we're
good. A lot of buckets. Go in a circle. Looks like you can get out onto the hallway. Not yet.
Not yet. Get everything. Whoa not big enough for any of this. Okay then. I have to go back
the other way. Yep there we go. Carrot. All right I gotta turn around. What? Stop bouncing me around.
I'm going back in here. Come on. Oh I got something. Get me on the table. I'm kind of
glitching through this. Cousin Miso. Get on the desk. Yeah. All right get all that shit.
Okay. A little too big. There we go. Oh grab the camera. Shit that's a sticker. I can't do it.
Can I go outside? I can pick the chairs up now. Wait in here. Look at all this shit in here.
Can I get the desks yet? Get out of the way. Oh shit I'm stuck.
Can I go in here? What is all this? Oh this is all toilet paper. Shit I have no time.
No I don't want to go outside. All right go. Get everybody quick. I got 30 seconds. I need to go
in a different room. Hurry. Get in there. Get in there. Get in there. It's too... I'm too big. I
can't get in here. I can't move. All right. I did okay. Did you make friends with the kids?
Want to go home now? They are suffering. Is that good enough? Okay. Yes. We counted. We counted
for the first time. Okay. Okay. To the Katamari in our right hand too. Oh Katamari came out of
nowhere. Go. Go. Go. Bigger. Make it bigger. Bigger. 2.5. Hey that's small. Nobody can have fun
like this. Make it bigger and let the good times roll. I'm doing this one again. Oh me so. You were
wandering around a school. I was going to eat you if you're not careful. Is this the TF2 guy?
I mean I kind of. Years ago that was correct. Is this the TF2 guy? You know what? That's pretty
rare nowadays that you're not asking me if I'm the sus guy. You know. All right. Cool. Welcome
to the stream. What is that I'm feeling? Kind of ripped off is how I feel. All right. All right.
All right. All right. I'm doing it again. I'm going for five meters. I'm going to get it this time.
Aren't you the put cigarettes out on my dick guy? Yeah. Oh man. All right. School is great.
Playing with friends. Confessing your love. Yeah that's me. How did you read that? I don't know.
Culture Fest. Sports Fest. Graduation. Ah youth. We went to school too of course.
It was night school. We feel youth was bittersweet. We'd remember from the shock of the bamboo
sword but the king never looks to the path. I'm going to put on. Hold on. I want the camera. All
right. You can only have two things on. Camera. Camera and mask. Camera and nose. I think nose.
Don't you eat bugs? No. No. What? Wait. What? Good day. I'm kind of bored. Oh wait. No. I
want to do this one. I want to do the school one again. What is the school one over here?
I have some kids refusing to come back to school because the Katamari was too small.
I'll. All right. I'm going to do this one again. I think you'd like Tears of the Kingdom if you
played on stream. Would I like it? What are you going to do the next smite tutorial? I'm working
on one now. Smite's still going strong and are there more cartoon characters than gods in the
game now? Wait. I just remember there was there was like a Ninja Turtles crossover and I was like,
oh okay. The Ninja Turtles are in Smite now. They added a lot of just random shit. Whatever.
I'm going to play as like Donatello. That's pretty cool. All right. So I have to pick up.
This is a different mission. What is going on in here? This is kind of loud in here. Oh I got a
new cousin. Huey. Not yet. One person in here? Somebody said, dude, open up multiple streams to
get sound echo? Why? That probably would be annoying to listen to. Only one more person.
Where are they? One more? This is two minutes, man. Come on. Where's the last person?
Shit. Oh there you are. Time to get out of school. Bye now. Under 220? That's probably better.
I have this open on five tabs. This sounds insane. Okay. Uh huh. It's hard to judge.
You can get the students home from school much faster. Yeah. 229. That's really good. Hey it's
Huey. What were you doing on earth? You were playing with kids. That's a good thing. Oh it
feels seeding-ish or rather children-y. Here we go. Okay. None of the students would leave the
school for a while. I think they wanted to play with your highness a little longer. So it's not
as though you were just slow. It's fine to have a dawdling Katamari now and again. I'd like you to
have this cut. Was it bad still? Two minutes and 29 seconds? Hey look it's a backpack. I used to
have one like that. Cool. Watch your blinds. I'd like to win. Okay. Nice to meet you. As you can see
I'm pretty small but I'm a sumo wrestler. I'm so small that I can't win very often. I thought
playing Katamari Damacy would make me bigger but it didn't. My oyakata got mad and told me to stop
playing video games. Anyway I thought it through and I want to study with your highness. I want
to be stronger. Please say yes. What are you guys doing? I just looked over at the dashboard for
the first time in like an hour or two. The stream went up like 2,000 viewers because you guys are
opening a fucking shitload of tabs. Just in the last 20 minutes I think the stream has gone up by
like a thousand or two thousand viewers. How many of you are actually doing this? Inflating the
numbers yeah. All right so what are we gonna do? You want to be strong for what? Here's the thing
about strength. You have to work. Don't ask for it. I want to be like you. We see now. Yes we absolutely
get it. We get it. All righty let's get stronger. I keep forgetting to turn the music up and the
sounds down. We're getting fired up. The battle is starting. Today's opponent is ready and standing by.
Okay. He seems pretty strong but still. Give it your best shot. Give it all you got. How about
this much time to decide the bout? Viso make sure you roll our fan firm and steady. As for you our
fan eat everything inside and grow nice and big. All righty we wish you a good fight. Okay I need
to eat food. Is he saying? I just lost everything I just picked up. All right let's get some cabbage.
I didn't get it yet. Oh cookies.
I love delicious cookies. A lot right here. Give me the fish.
I missed every single object but honestly every single one. That was impressive how bad that was.
There we go. Can't get the chicken and the turkey.
I want that cart.
Oh my god look at those raining mushrooms. Not big enough.
Keep going in here. All right I don't want to get up there yet. Not quite ready.
How big should I be before I try it?
Shit can't get watermelons in either. I think I can get yep.
A fig mom. Dude your view count is fucked up now.
Hurry up. Lot of stuff over here.
All right with one one minute I'm gonna go back.
All right where's this? Where is it? Right here. Not yet.
Oh my god look at all this.
Let's go. You ate well and rolled well and now you're pretty strong.
Yes all righty let's go. That wasn't bad 234.
I'm gonna go to sleep. Where is it in the world for you right now?
We're starting to figure it out. What the most powerful thing in the world is.
Not missiles or guns. It's the heart in all of us we think. Of course Subo is important too.
Supari Moridashi it's the best. Oh did you happen to win? Microwe wrestler man did you
finally get to win? And did you happen to win by roll up? Super rolling up his school.
You ate hard and rolled hard? Yes we think you worked very hard. Congratulations on your victory.
How's it Nick? What were you doing on earth? An eating contest? I was food as usual.
Much obliged your highness I finally won. I was up against someone fairly strong but I managed to
win by roll up. I'll apply myself and become stronger. Work harder so I can beat an poseki.
Oh it's almost time for practice. I'll leave. All right we got a happy customer.
Welcome to the cosmos. Good Yokozuna win planet. Remember this game is freaking goofy.
Yeah I mean it's what you might say this game is wonderful. A very wonderful game.
Candy pop presents freaking goofy.
What am I going to do about dinner? His room is sort of cleaned I guess.
But it took a while didn't it? He'll be in college before you finish.
You know parents are busy people you have to clean up this bastard. All right we'll try this
bastard. You want to order a pizza tonight? Um if you want a pizza get one.
All right I'm gonna try doing this one again. Okay a hundred things in the room. Go.
Two okay I get under three minutes.
How's my pace so far? Better? He said eh. Damn it too small.
I got plenty of time. I'm big enough to get this.
Not yet.
Seven items left. I'm too big to fit through here. Two one zero up. Where is it?
Where is it? Where's the last item? Where's the last item? Get it. It's right here roll over it.
All right that was almost a full minute quicker. I can do definitely better than that. I could
probably do better than that. We'll see if it's good though. It's a miniature universe of my
kid's room sparkling with cosmic order. Took two minutes and 12 seconds. Are you sure you can't be
more efficient? Shit okay it's sort of cleaned up. Of course it's cleaned up but it's not so
different from what I usually do myself. I guess this is about it. It's only Katamari Demasi after
all. This Katamari is kind of in the way. It's gotta be under two minutes. Planet or planet dust?
Well let's replace this one. Better. The mission is hard. This game is just as challenging as it
needs to be because you can just roll around and have fun or you can try to do the very very
intricate challenges. What do you got? So you're the king. It's nice to meet you. I'm almost 89
years old. I'm still young at heart. My perspective is still fresh but I can't seem to find anything
fun. A friend told me that Katamari Demasi was fun. Is it true? Yes it is. Miso's hair is boring
so not fun. You know there are options don't you? The afro, mohawk, pompadour. Oh we just remembered
we had a pompadour. We were the sharpest of the sharp. Those were the days. But excitement? You
want excitement? Talking about a pompadour yes? Oh it's far too late now. Your highness's avant-garde.
All righty so starting now let's roll it vanguard style. Okay here we go. Are you winning Jeremy?
I think so. It's so sunny. It's a nice day. It's hiking time. Let's get going. Oh we forgot about
the Katamari. How about this much time to make this big? 12 minutes for 12 meters. I can do that.
Alright this one's gonna be good. What I'm going for. This is gonna be a real one. This song is
phenomenal by the way. And I didn't turn the music up again. Fucking idiot. This is arguably like
one of the better songs in the whole game. No not this one. I lied. No it is this one.
I think I'm making that up. I think it's this one. I think I'm lying.
Fine. Bananas. Pawn. Pigs. This reminds me of like tune music. I feel like I'm gonna I'm walking
around like toon town. Because I'm in an amusement park. I've got them all. 50 not quite. I'm not
going there yet. I can't pick up the bananas? These things are worth picking up.
I still have 11 minutes. I'm good. Alright let's go this way.
I think that was fairly efficient. Give me that upgrade. There it is. Loading. And oh we can talk.
Where were we? Oh yes we used to have a pompadour. It's a very cool look. Sort of sticks out over
your forehead. But that can be a problem yes. If you don't do it well it gets saggy. Well it's
mostly about the attitude. That's what it comes down to. You can get to more places if you roll
from here. Get more rebellious. More glamorous. Not going there yet. Get all this other shit.
I'm going back in here. Alright go.
Oh I'm in line at a ride at a theme park.
I gotta come back down this road. There's so much shit here. 8 minutes.
Shit. Okay time to snowball. I got lots of time to snowball too.
Really? Still can't get the umbrellas. I need the big soups. Get up on there. What?
Get out of here. It's a gun. Flowers. Oh shit. It's not big enough.
You roll like my grandma. That's fine. We can all play Katamari differently. Alright now I'm
gonna go up. I'm gonna get this is gonna be I'm gonna suck up all this right now.
That's this. What's up everybody? All these chairs are gonna be so much space. Nice.
Nice. Three meters? Not quite. Okay I gotta go back out on the street. Oh I can't get that.
Have I got the fence yet? I don't think so.
We can finally talk. We don't like loading. Anyway we can't manage a pompadour anymore. No.
We can't handle a hairstyle that draws so much attention.
Shy and retiring by disposition. Yes. Because we were young, youth can be very embarrassing,
but it's whatever. You can get more places over there. Can I get the horses? Can I get
right? Alright I got a lot of time but it's not gonna fix anything here. I gotta go down every
road. Every street. Yep. I'll get those tables later. I want to once you can start picking fences
up. That's when it's all over. Fences, cars, that's when you can start to really just kind of go
crazy with it. Alright I'm going back this way. Get it all. Get it all. These things are pretty
big. I want to get them all. That too. Alright what about down here? I'll turn around. There it is.
Shit I gotta get bigger. Come on hurry. Hold on to this section I haven't been to. Okay
give me this whole fucking structure. Anymore can I pick all the houses up now?
Let's get her. I gotta roll over here back to where I was. Cars are very good right now.
Trees are good right now. Let's go hurry. Alright I gotta get to a different spot.
I gotta go back up to the town and up this way. Hurry. Hurry. I'm not gonna make it. Let's go.
More houses. More houses. 18. These are all so big. Just get these.
Okay I'm good. I'm good. Could have been 20 but it's alright. Did I get a present?
No it's right there. Shit. Imagine your house gets sucked up by a meatball.
So many memories. Oh what's this? It's a tatamari. Once we took a good look it seems kind of half
big. Besides the appearance 18.8 is just mediocre. Katamari that breaks on through.
That's what we want to see. This feels plant-ish. That was a little boring. It's over. That's the
end. Don't you have to make the thing bigger for the game to be fun? I don't need a boring
katamari here your highness. You can have it. Broke Jupiter. That's kind of exciting. It's
gonna be in space. My grandma took an edible and is tripping watching your screen. She's freaking
out. That's a fake story but alright. What the hell? What happens to the people you roll up? Do
they die when they go to space? No. No they don't. There we go. I'm gonna play as as Lala.
Alright what are the new quests? Is this a versus or what is this actually?
Is this actually like a two-player thing? We so want a pet. Something to soothe our weary heart.
Dearest. What kind of pet should it be? What a friend? What are we talking about pets here?
An adorable pet to play adorable games with. Everything about you is amazing.
Everything. Friends are so very important. We are everyone's beloved superstar so we can't be a
friend to just one person. Let's get rolling and find some friends. What are you doing the shock
college screen? I'm not doing. Alright why did I even read that out loud? Okay. Mother nature's
very own zoo. Too long. It barely fits. Since our fan probably wants friends fast. How about this
much time to roll as many friends into a Katamari as you can. We know you can do it. Lala. Alrighty
it doesn't sound right if I say it that way. Alright friends. What counts as a friend? Oh this
is the woofing and the meowing one. I love this one. I love this song. That's animals?
More friends. Is it people too? A lot over here. Can you get the rabbit? Bunny? Okay I'm stuck.
I definitely can't get the tigers right now. Can you get the pigs? Prime that please.
Oh look at all this. Get me in here. Shit. Can you get all those flamingos? Good. I'll come back
here later. What's considered a good amount of friends here? 100? 200? Alright I think I
can get the tigers now. A lot here. Let's go. That. I hear that everywhere. I think I can go for 200.
Oh I got a present. These don't count as friends but they make me bigger.
Can't pick these up yet. Oh yes I can. Can I get the camels? Yeah let's go.
So many over here. Elephant? Nope. I can't get the giraffes either. Stop walking. What are your
thoughts on Tom Brady? Oh Tom Brady? Who's fucking football? I fucking love that. Oh you mean fucking
Hall of Fame Tom Brady? Most passing yards of any fucking quarterback ever? You don't know
shit about football. Oh cousin. This is getting kind of out of hand here. I have not watched a
full game of the Patriots since I was probably 20? Maybe like 25? I don't know. Alright anything
else I'm missing here? Climb this. We're going all the way up. We're going all the way up. Can I get
the big? Can I get them? Yes. I got 200 plus. I got quite a lot. Okay am I missing anything?
There's a bunch over here still. Getting caught on shit. I need 250. Come on. Come on 247. I need 250.
250. Oh you piece of shit. Come here. Yes we're good. Brady. Come on Brady. Why did you plus two
that? I didn't even do anything. Why are you plus twoing this? I just said Brady. Tom Brady.
Is it? I didn't do anything else. I put like the funny accent on right? That's right.
Alright fabulous 250 friends. That's good. We could have rolled up more friends.
Oh with second cousin beyond. What were you doing on earth? Slumming it somewhere up high.
We have no idea what we're talking about. You think the subtle touch of a Chinese zodiac is
the signature here? Oh wow so many. This is amazing. Katamari Damacy is amazing. So many.
I'm really grateful. Now all that's left is your highness to persuade. Will you be my best friend
in exchange for this Katamari? Oh really? You're giving it to us? Fabulous. We are so pleased.
The evolution planet. Now that you mention it there weren't any. Hmm swans. You know swans?
We think we remember seeing swans at the zoo. Wait was it swans? We're not sure. We'd remember
from the shock of the bamboo sword. There is no need. Hey where are you? You're a lot bigger in
person. I used to watch Katamari Damacy when I was still in my mom's. What did that say? I used to
float in there and think you roll up stuff and get bigger, crash and get smaller. Kind of like
life. That's what I thought. But sometimes there's not a lot to roll up right? There are times like
that. So how about trying to get as big as possible with just a few things? I thought you
were reading chat for a second? No. We're bored of Katamari Damacy. So boring just to roll.
Monsters, dungeons, la la la. Are we there yet? Huh? What? Going to use a new rule to roll?
Are you sure this is fun? You're my role model your highness.
Roll model? Yes it must be fun then. Fun as a hundred of the usual Katamari's put together.
Probably more fun than fighting monsters. Hurry up let's get rolling.
Roll according to a rule. The rule here is make as big a Katamari as possible using a limited
number of objects. A thoughtful kind of rolling. Yes we can't possibly do it. We would break this
rule left and right. But we're sure that you can do it la la la. All right so what do I need to get?
What am I picking up here? What am I picking up? Remaining just 50 objects. That's it.
No it needs to be big objects. I'm not big enough to pick up the big stuff.
You can't read. Wait what? I don't understand. Your Katamari is already huge.
I don't want to pick up the fucking buoy. Get as big as possible with only 50 objects. These things
are pretty big. Let's go look around. One more. These things are kind of big. That boat's pretty
big. These are kind of big. Can't get the alligators. Okay the statue's big. All right now
don't touch anything. Get huge stuff now. This is big. Yep. Alligator. Oh no I didn't want to pick
up an anteater. Don't pick those up either. Fence. All right fences are huge. These boats are big.
No. Damn it. Get off me. All right let me get to five and I'll be happy. Shit. It's all right.
It's all right. Could have been better. Can you please play reader rabbit learn to read with
phonics first and second grade? Yeah. Um yeah. Is that good enough? Is that small or big? We don't
get that part. Is this a Katamari or something else? That's another thing we're not sure about.
Now we have to hold fast. Make it much bigger. Something's not right. This sort of thing
is sort of different from what I was thinking. Roll it right please. I was born to do this you
know. Your highness can have this thing. Oh it's amazing. You really are amazing. Your voice is
extra crispy today. Thank you. It means a lot. I really appreciate it. I'm not going to resub to
you because you're not playing Zelda. Here's what I want you to do. Find a streamer that you like
that's playing Zelda and I want you to give your sub to that streamer. If you're doing the thing
that you want to see them do and you can be like holy shit this person's playing. This person is
playing Zelda and it gives me such joy. Okay let's go. Good day help the paper cranes. I don't know
how Katamari demires it but my friend loves it. See this friend she's sick now and not in school.
I want her to get better soon so we're making a thousand something but the cranes got scattered
by the wind and it's a mess. Your highness can you help us collect the cranes for my friend?
Absolutely. Can you do a Daxter impression from Jack and Jack and Daxter? Don't tell me which one.
Okay Jack and Dexter is don't tell me if I'm wrong or not because there's a couple games with this
this plays out. Jack and Dexter is the one where it's like a it's like a weasel and a
young man with like big hair right? So Jack and Dexter are but I don't know who is who.
Is Dexter the weasel character or is Dexter the character you play with? Dexter is the
Daxter. Daxter is the weasel. Okay you want me to do an impression of this character.
I don't know what this character sounds like but I'm gonna give it a shot. Can you give me a line
to read? I feel like I know what this person sounds like but I don't give me a line. A line
from the game. Oh that that's a good one.
All right give me another one. How about this line? I'm Daxter from Jack and Daxter. That's
not what happens. Give me a line if you want me to do an impression. Give me a line. Give me a line.
You guys want it so bad. Give me a line. Whoa Morty I turned myself into a Daxter Morty.
Okay give me a give me a real line. He goes ah I'm Daxter but no he doesn't. None of these lines.
Okay this one's real. So there I was toe to toe with five of the nastiest metal heads you ever
saw. Slime oozing from monstrous jaws. Feet sharper than the daggers. Slowly all ten of them
surrounded me Jerry. Do I surrender? No. I summon my highly trained killer instincts and pounce.
Ha yeah and when the dust is cleared there were 20 less metal heads in the world. Is it close?
That was Bernie Sanders. You just put it why do you put Bernie inflection on everything?
All right wait wait this actually quotes here. Hold on let me hear some of these.
Let me turn this down for one second. See I don't I have no idea what this person sounds like. Hold
on. Okay. Rocks when turned over reveal their dark underbelly in the great struggle of good
versus okay. I swear that's the last time I ever ever touch any stupid precursor crap.
I mean that was pretty close. It will be your downfall these. That was excuse me that was
really fucking close. I did that was actually pretty close. Freaks will not save us. Oh yeah
the road map to Jack. Nice going little buddy. Yes it was. Especially when he was screaming.
Let's see what's on the tube tonight. Seen it. Rerun. Boring. Sorry ladies. Whoa sorry Jerry.
Right I had it right. For somebody that has no idea what this character sounded like it was
actually pretty close. And you know what? F you if you don't think so. Okay let's keep playing.
Bully. He's a bully. He's a bully. I think it was pretty good. Okay can you? There we are.
All right just love peace and a few other guys. Oh we forgot about the Katamari. You have this
much time to roll up lots and lots of paper cranes. Thousand cranes to grant a wish. Okay so I
gotta get to a thousand. Easy enough. We know you can do it. La la la. Let's go. All right I turned
it up. I turned it up everybody. I know a lot of people are asking me to turn it up so it's turned
up. It's not a whole lot of time. The chicken just fucking destroyed me. What was your favorite
subject in math? Uh logic. I'm not kidding. The redditor comment. No it's not. That's not math.
That's logic. How do I? There's not a thousand paper cranes in here. Is there another? Is there an exit?
Okay there is. Okay there's quite a lot in here actually.
Crispy voice today. Crispy. It had to be crispy. All right. Crispy onions.
You happy you had the onions? Are you glad you glad you had the onions?
You happy you had the onions? Don't blame this on me. It had to be crispy. Crispy onions. They have to
be crispy. What's that from? Mods. Oh shit I fucking forgot. Okay I gotta get like some steam
gift cards. Holy shit I was about to play the game show bullshit again and I forgot that I haven't
even given the first fucking people their things. Oh shit. Wait you scammed him. I just completely
forgot. All right don't worry I'll take care of this. Can you please say it was a bad day?
Hold on I don't want to lose. Oh this is the room to do it in. I'm gonna get so close. It's gonna be so sad.
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Oh I didn't do it. I'm an underachiever. Yeah it's from curvy enthusiasm. They get behind the slow
golfer because Larry's cousin they they really want to get in front of the slow golfer but
Larry's cousin orders crispy onions with his eggs which is gonna take extra time which Larry's like
you fucking idiot. We gotta get in front of the slow golfer. The guy the guy 90% that's not bad.
Won't help get anyone out of the hospital sooner. I need to get a hundred percent.
Opio. Opio. Up to the cosmos. What about Clank from Ratchet and Clank?
Okay Clank. Clank is a robot right so I will probably have a probably have a robotic voice
but are we talking c3po level of like a robot and I talk very eloquently or are we talking
like caveman style robot where I have five words I say.
Hmm hold on this is important. What are you linking me here?
Are you happy on the onions? Oh that's so fucking funny. That show is so good.
I'm sorry I just laughed really loud in your ear but somebody said I sounded like Beavis and
Butt-head. I sounded like Butt-head from Beavis and Butt-head. Clip it I want to hear it. You
sounded like Butt-head. Shut up. Link it. It was a great laugh was it. I need to hear it. It was the
you have an attitude today. Bro somebody just said I sound like Butt-head. That is an attack
all right that's an attack. I'm going on the defensive. That wasn't that
not even that close.
I'll tell you one of my most my favorite episode from Beavis and Butt-head is when
Beavis sits down in one of those automatic blood pressure machines and just fucking freaks out.
You guys remember those things? It's like Butt-head squeezing my arm.
Butt-head get it off me. You look stupid. He's like he's fucking and I think it like he gets like hurt.
He has a fucking meltdown sitting down in that thing.
You did the clank voice perfectly. I did? Oh that's good.
Oh we do honey or no I want to do opio. I need more presents too. I'm really lacking in the present
department. All right let's go here. I want to roll up a car. What I want to roll up is a car.
I tried myself during a race but couldn't roll them up. Give me a chance please.
Do a master shake impression. I think I could probably do a good one and I think I did do a
good one. People said it was a bad one and I was really disappointed. You've got some real
corn holio energy today. He used to like he used to put his shirt oh my god. He would make um okay
corn holio used to sit there and be like
he would make Popeye noises. You know Popeye? Popeye would be like
I need TV. It's so childish but it's fucking funny. I don't even care.
I'm obsessed with yeah uh Holly's been watching King of the Hill. That's a great show too. Mike
Judge does a lot of great work. Everyone including the Katamari will go at the same time.
Roll up cars to your heart's content. Let's see how many. Okay so I get six minutes to roll up
a bunch of cars. Five meters. Cars. Okay let's go. Let's start. Go! Okay got one.
Oh this one that goes oh the Katamari rolls around on its own. Why? It's a racetrack.
Not big enough. Oh look at these Super Mario pipes. Whoa it is moving on its own. It wasn't
kidding. It's actually moving on its own. Are these frogs in the race? I almost have them all almost.
Shit. Come here. All right I'm definitely big enough now. One more and I'll get them all.
Come on. What's happening? Goodness. All right there's like five people left. That one,
that one, that one. Still not big enough for the actual race cars. Three minutes. So close. There
we go. Get the rest of the cars and I'm gonna start picking up everything else. Really? Not
big enough? What'd I get? Go backwards? Kind of moving for me. Oh hurry up. There it is. All
right. Finally. I can get the rest of the cars. Where's that present? Is there a present? There's
a present? On the big boat? Big boat. Where's the big boat? Where's the big boat? Big boat.
Let's see. Big boat. Big, that big boat. Did I get all the cars? I think I got them all. Yeah I got
all the cars. We're good. We get to like 10. These things are huge. No, no bounce. Sorry.
It's pretty fun. It was pretty fun. Everyone won the race. Cars they're pretty fast. Of course
we are faster. If we fly we are even faster. Oh what's this Katamari doing here? What is this
clunker? It's a three cc engine. Seven cc. Let's work on getting it bigger. At least 60,000.
60 million. Sorry. That's the level of Katamari we can expect. Wow. We got a horsey as a present.
Ooh. It's kind of charming but hopefully oh you can have it. I'm a fan. Appreciate it. Hey what the
this isn't as fun as car racing. This sure ain't as exciting as car racing. Katamari Demasi was
more fun before. Let down. You can have this thing your highness. Beat the record. All right
we're gonna go put the music up and the sound down again. Let's swim in the ocean. Right at
the beach we used to uh blue sea, white sand, seagulls, umbrellas, starfish, crabs, seashells,
tires. Tires. I remember from the shock of ambusade that we have no interest in tires.
No I didn't fucking do it. Quiet. I didn't say it. You all thought it was gonna happen. How dare you
think I was gonna say that. Genuinely upsetting. Genuinely upsetting. What do you got? Hello your
highness. Katamari Demasi is a really popular thing all around the world. Anyway I'm on a
camping trip right now. We're having a good time and every camping trip needs a campfire but
can't get the fire lit. I mean we haven't had any luck. Your highness can you help us out?
Of course I can. Long day today. Home in a hot bath. Oh we left a fire burning for the bath.
Oh opio what are we going to do? Huh? Campfire? If more important issue.
You must return to the royal castle and check on the fire for the bath. Katamari is live fantastic.
Think of that. Today is sauna day not bath day. That's why we left the fire burning on purpose.
Okay then to the campground. This is the campground. Wowies we're a little bit excited.
Everyone else looks like they're having fun too. We want to pitch a tent next to them.
Okay this is the small wood pile. Light this by rolling it up and you have a campfire.
Okay if you can manage in this much time that will make everyone happy. Okay I don't get it.
Should I? Because I can? Let's get big. Football. Bucket.
I can't pick up the buckets but I can pick up the cats.
Still going to play source 3 you bet. Dead on it? Oh yeah dead on it. Dead on it. I have a feeling
going in the water will be bad so I'm not going to. I will get the cinder.
Am I big enough to pick the mushrooms up yet? Now I probably am.
What about Hilux too? Oh yeah I'm back log barrier right now.
All right I don't want to touch this yet but I will roll over all this.
I gotta remember where this is up on the hill. Oh my god my eye is so itchy. What happened?
Why does it feel to be known as a liar? I'm like uh-oh. Why did I even look over a chat for no reason?
Fire goes out when you stick it in water. You should be able to understand that simple fact.
Please roll with some common sense.
Fire carrying everyone's trust. Fire that was going into his head went out.
This goes way beyond simple disappointment. Think about it. Hope you extinguish the flames
of their hope. They don't love it at all. They don't love us. No maybe the fire of our spirit.
From our eyes are these laser beams. Usually it's a much more effective form of spanking.
Re-lighting a fire that's gone out. It's not easy. We're going to go home now. Goodbye.
Oh this one is hard. You sound like Giga Chad. Oh I feel like I look like Giga Chad.
Did you even eat today? Yeah I had a little bit of avocado and a tortilla with some chicken
and some tabasco. It was pretty good.
And a gallon of milk. There's the milk guy again. There's Mr. Milk. And a gallon of milk too.
No no what was it the milk guy? There is a milk guy that's in the chat every day.
All right I think this can go out too. We care about your bones. I get plenty of calcium don't
worry about me. I'm going to go back to I need to I need to touch the fire right now or I'm dead.
Thoughts on you being a cultural and developmental figure of my life.
It's a good thing. It's a good thing. All right now that I got you here. Really? Okay.
Brush your teeth every day. Eat a well-balanced diet. Get sleep sleep every day. Make sure you
get some good sleep. Vegetables are not gross. Milk is fine but like don't eat too much. Don't
drink too much milk. Have some milk. I don't care. Sometimes you're gonna have milk.
Um try to be like nice to people if you can. I know it can be a problem sometimes. I get it.
I get it. Try to be like a try to be nice to people if you can. I know some people. I know
I get it. I know some people you just like oh how the fuck am I going to be the nicest person.
Try it. You try it. Try to be a good version of yourself right and we all
just go through ups and downs. I'm not telling you to be the best version of yourself because
you need to be. Let me just roll up a puncher. Thanks a lot dad. Fuck you game. I didn't even
pay attention to this. All right if I get hit once I'm going to delete my twitch channel after
next like six years from now. I'll play this again. And six years when I play this again I'm
going to do this exact thing and if I get hit then whatever. I was just went right into the water.
Is this a baby game. Yes and no. You can make this as difficult as you want or you can just
kind of roll up stuff and have fun. You don't have to take it too seriously.
Which to me that's the best kind of game. A game that's just fun to play.
No pressure on it or anything. But you could really go hard with this game and be very good at it.
I typed that three hours ago dude. This is a reddit game. What does that even mean anymore?
That's losing meaning. That's losing meaning. Everything is a reddit thing.
I think you're replacing that with like all right this thing that I think is kind of stupid.
This is a reddit game.
Reddit chill. Yeah well that one makes sense to me.
I think they mean it's a game for millennials.
I mean this game I mean this came out when I was
19 18 or something 20. I don't know. When did this come out?
How old was I when this came out? 17 or something. I need a fire right now. Hurry up go.
Oh my god I'm not paying any attention. Can you please remind me to take my pizza out of the
oven in 30 minutes. 30 minutes. Bro why are you cooking a pizza for 30 minutes.
I think it's gonna be like charcoal. It's gonna be a slow roast.
It's gonna be a burnt ass pizza. Yeah slow roast pizza. Would that do anything?
Okay let's have a food conversation. That's our favorite thing sir.
If you put a pizza in the oven at like 250 degrees and you cooked it for an hour. What would happen?
But like 200. What what what? It would be awful. It would be terrible. It would just be a bad pizza.
It would be very yeah it would be terrible.
Frozen pizza is gonna be it's gonna be terrible already. There are some good frozen pizzas.
I'm telling you I don't need I don't see them anymore. They probably I don't know
they probably fucking discontinued the whole franchise. I have no idea.
Uh Dr. Roker's pizza doesn't exist anymore. I don't I can't find it anywhere.
That shit was actually phenomenal. All right I'm not confident that I can do this one that well so
I'm gonna end it soon here. I'm gonna just go in there and do it. I'll try for like two or three.
30 minutes for a pizza though. That does feel like a very long time. Uh DiGiorno? If I could do a
pizza tier list frozen pizza tier list I could probably do it. I've had a lot of them. Uh DiGiorno
stuffed crust is pretty high up there. I'd say it's very high up there. It's in fire bro. I know I
got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Fire up there. I only have 27 seconds. I thought
there was no timer. Just hit me. Oh my fucking god. I didn't think there was a timer. Did that
timer disappear out of nowhere or was I just not paying any attention to the game? I was just
talking about pizza. There is a timer. Okay I just I seriously was not even looking. The game was
playing by itself. I was in food mode. You know a game actually has a great food mode that we've
not talked about. Red Dead Redemption 2. It has an unbelievable food mode. You just have to hold down
a button. You can sit there and just watch the conversations that happen within Red Dead
in the cinematic mode because they just stay on the road if you press one button.
So you can sit there and you can at least at least one hand to eat. I got a bag of chips.
TF2 has a food mode. It's called engineer. No no. That's it. Yeah I know. You know how I know that
you get backstabbed every single fucking time you play the game because you AFK standing. First of
all you put you didn't put your dispenser against a wall and you didn't protect your back with the
dispenser. The only way okay the dispenser right behind you and the sentry right in front of you
and the teleporter right to your left. Spy has to jump on top of your shit and then crouch and try
to get you. As long as you're looking around it's not gonna happen. I can tell you get backstabbed
all the time. Food mode is engineer. That was one of the most involved classes in the whole game.
Gotta move that gear up. What are you talking about? You know what I want to play and I'm gonna do it
eventually here because it's like seriously the only time a company has ever made a fucking fun
version of this thing and how infuriating is what I am about to tell you. Team Fortress 2
comes out with this game mode called man versus machine. I was playing man versus machine and
sitting there thinking wow this is going to be a new paradigm for video games. I cannot wait until
more companies make this shit. I can't wait to play this in more first person shooters.
Team Fortress is the only game to make one of those fun. The only one. I feel like it's the only
one I've played that I genuinely fucking loved every second of it. I've played the other ones.
They're okay. They're good but they just say that it doesn't even come close.
Man versus machine is some of the most fun I've had in Team Fortress. So here's what I'm telling
you that I'm gonna do. Listen up. I'm going to set up a man versus machine scream or something
with screamers. See if I can get like five, six people. Sounds like a lot of fun doesn't it?
I actually have been thinking about doing this for a long time just because of how
long it's been since I played it. Just how much fun I remember it being.
I cannot tell you there's something that's going to happen immediately. It's going to take a little
while. Not that it's oh my god it takes so long to get to get into man versus machine but
it's something I do want to do. Because I feel like don't correct me if I'm wrong here everybody.
You can call me a boomer if you want. Call me a boomer. Call me a millennial. Whatever you
want to say. I feel like a lot of people in the kind of gaming world right now or PC gaming at
least didn't really ever experience TF2. Have you noticed that? TF2 is kind of people go oh yeah I've
like heard of that. It sounds like that's fun. Yeah I've heard of that. I mean you heard of it.
You've only heard of it? Have you played it? Oh not for very long. Man really? I feel like it was
kind of its own era. But I'm kind of getting the itch to not necessarily I don't know not to play
Team Fortress again. I really don't think that's going to happen. But man versus machine I've
been itching to play it. Never played it. Never played it. All right you know you know let's do
a real like not no joking around no fucking around right now. Mods aren't full. How many of you here
have played Team Fortress 2 for more than three hours? Like you've played it for more than a few
hours. How many people here have done that? More than a few. Like let's go with five hours
because I feel like that's a good amount of time to be like okay I'm not playing the game then I'm
going to lose. Yeah if you played for over five hours like all right pretty curious. The orange
box. Orange box is I think will go down in history as the single greatest thing to ever be on the
shelf. I don't think people understood back in the day of of everything has to be monetized.
Everything has to be separated and monetized. Everything has to be if they spend tons of money
on it. The orange box was like five fucking full games in one box and they just were like yeah
have it. We don't even give a shit. Have all these have all these genre defining experiences in the
same fucking box. At least three of those things in the orange box were genre defining experiences
and it's all in the same box. So all right so 60% of you so that means 40% of you
have not really played Team Fortress 2 more than a few hours probably. That's pretty remarkable
honestly. Now TF2 is I want to say they they want to do oh we're gonna fix stuff and do updates and
stuff. I don't know I haven't repaid I haven't paid that much attention to it. I just know that
they were doing stuff like oh we are gonna do some updates and try to do some fixing and change
this and get rid of that and I have to imagine at this point it's so it's so old now and I don't
know if the money is there for them to kind of do like a TF2 remaster or something or you don't
even really need to. I feel like that game still holds up. Isn't that weird? That game is so old
but still holds up. Fortress Source 2. We thought they were gonna do that years and years ago.
It just never happened. We got a mushroom as a present. We really hate mushrooms. Opio you can
have it. What if I had? Make sure you appreciate it. Oh it's second cousin Kinoko. What were you
doing on earth? Dancing with the grandpa. Every time TF2 is gonna do I just doesn't feel the same.
Remember when TF2 was gonna do a huge update and they're gonna add a ton of shit and people had no
idea what it was gonna be? I guess maybe Fortnite still kind of does that don't they? Where it's
like hey we here comes something huge. There's a ton of new shit in this. Does it still hit as hard
as it did back then? Tell me the truth. What's your TF2 blunt rotation? Engineer, Spy, Heavy, Pyro.
Engineer, Heavy, Spy, Pyro. What about the demo man? You what you don't I want to go out I want
to go out drinking with the demo man. What are you talking about? No I and by the way my it's yeah
he's definitely already thought about this. What about the scout? No no no no the scout's gonna
take like the scout's gonna take like two like a puff and just start freaking out and yelling
about aliens and stuff like he's gonna be he's gonna talk about the aliens that come through
the walls and shit now it's gonna be like oh man okay that's literally you yeah well you gotta
put up with me all right that's how it works that's just you yeah well nightmare blunt rotation
that's such a funny term it just I know exactly what it means too it's so stupid save the pandas
okay support a good cause today save the red pandas unless we step in red pandas will turn
into regular pandas need to eat yummy strawberries or they turn into regular pandas we need your
support yo you have any idea who came up with the first sauce something else jumped up there
recently and it was a really detailed conversation I forget what it was what was this person say
girma Vinnie Joel northern lion is ideal blunt rotation true true the sauce a solid or a liquid
uh it's it's neither it's a gas why did I skip all that that was like kind of interesting
so good chocolate we want to have some oh the red pandas yes of course this much time to roll up a
bunch of things Katamari should be able to save the red pandas we don't know a thing about earth
money but we're sure you can do it all righty life absolutely priceless so I have to get
chocolates or is it just that was just for fun every time somebody writes this I have to say it
and it's annoying that I have to expensive things I got it there's meat ham is expensive
row tractors are expensive diamonds are expensive blenders are expensive $27 for a blender
where'd you get that kind of deal hey did you take your burnt ass pizza out of the oven yet
I'm reminding you well dude don't I you really you don't do you know you don't do that
what is happening right now oh another diamond expensive well shoes 150 trophy expensive
thousand all right cash register cool would there be any Katamari spoilers this stream
a ton way too many I don't think you should stick around oh they're not happy if you do that okay
oh all right 14 000 euros cap would you please play magic the gathering that would be the worst
stream I've ever done look at that little frog hello Mr toad how expensive is it oh it's a
washing machine roast pork if only 50 bucks all right hold on telephones these should be good
20 grand I can get to 20 right 17 000 guitars are expensive
get me to 10 this is like golden shit here we go 21 000 21 000 dollars
can you please do a Dennis Reynolds impression I'm on my knees I don't I don't think so labor
of love carefully rolled by opio you wonder how many strawberries you could buy with this Katamari
hmm okay whoa 21 000 676 dollars pretending to be all surprised but actually we are totally
clueless so is this a lot oh it's second cousin Odeon what were you doing on earth helping out
at a rummage sale we have no idea what you're talking about okay key there's not a lot there
that's not much we may have to settle for black and white pandas but it's the thought that counts
I appreciate the thought so I'll just take two dollars and 50 cents you can have the rest
21 000 dollars is not a lot of money familiar venus 21 000 dollars worth of strawberries that's
a lot of strawberries a bible stream would be amazing no it wouldn't you think it would be
you have this thing in your head of that being so funny but I'm telling you it's it won't be
I am I assure you it will not be oh I want this mushroom character cool sweet I am a bird that's
right I'm a bird I love Katamari Damacy I played it till my feathers fell out while I play I think
gosh if only I were that big what I have it wrong you can be big inside oh that's true being big
inside it's all about heart please good king won't you let me roll please do a Patrick Bateman
impression what is it okay every morning I put uh stuff on my face and then I peel it off and
it's a nice skin peel makes me feel good makes me feel good about everything and then I go to work
with my suit on I who cares that was Woody Allen I go to work and I put my suit on and I I'm telling
you can you do a cat impression maybe now do Jesse Pinkman Mr. White you wear the three stooges in
fortnight that's what I've been saying for years for years I've been saying that okay anyway 17
minutes to get to 500 meters oh shit there's plenty of time can you apologize for that please
no I'm sorry well I apologize yeah whoops I'm apologizing for not saying I don't know what
that was you know that whatever like sorry I'm not apologizing sorry that's what that context was
sorry I did the sorry not sorry races he didn't one bite who cares we're fucking crazy over here
at Reese's oh whole thing in one bite in the wrapper are you talking about he must have lost
your mind Reese's not sorry at all ever can you do a Vince McMahon impression yeah
there you go he's wicked red there can you do an impression of my dad yeah hey son
poor daughter how are you it's me dad just got back from work checking on you how you doing in
there okay oh checking out some katamari tamasi okay okay well hey Jim Jesse how you doing in your
science project we've done this like a thousand times already I'm cutting it off the next one
is going to be Goku we've done this before we've been here before many times you're going to say
Mr. Satan right now and then I'm going to do Mr. Satan and you're all going to clap we've been
we've done this show before well I mean all right do do what you're good at right do what you know
well all right let's have me to do Mr. Satan over here okay and then it's going to be Dutch
and then we do Dutch and then well I tell you Arthur you need to get out of here
and then of course we do Dutch and then that version of Freddy Krueger we've done this so
many fucking times Bill Murray do Bill Murray okay okay shit hold on I'm gonna do it off stream for
a second okay this is toast who can do Bill Murray somebody just wrote it sucks do it do it do the
same like six impressions you do every stream is it new every time for you can I ask that is it new
every time for you how does it feel is it new each time this is not a bad pace that actually
probably is it was wasted like 15 straight seconds doing that all right where have I not been
I gotta go this way yeah once you start getting fences that's when it all hell breaks loose
okay good pizza's ready all right I hope it's good I hope you actually didn't do that
sounds fucking heinous aren't most pizzas are like 12 minutes or lower but like 15 minutes
total it's been so long since we've had an errand please no I retired that one yeah it's a deep dish
pizza oh maybe that's different all right I got 12 minutes and start getting cars pizza review time
I would love to just do food review stuff I think that'd be fun food review would be fun
remember the tierless stream where I just was I full of shit or not that was I like that a lot
it's fun what the hell is going on in here what is going on super good farm spot right there
all right when's the next upgrade I think I can do nothing else here let's go over here
hurry up well shit
it water what am I doing oh my goodness what have I done I've ruined everything
I've ruined everything where am I going I was why is there a car under here I need to get
okay I need a better view please see where I'm going here okay back that way how do I get back
to the other place I just was here we go there we go okay finally we can talk we have a little
trouble with loading well a touch of boredom is something to do with it we are bored of being us
bored with the king thing for now we could we could shave off our beard maybe what else
you get our hair permed we make over that's kind of important firms are nice yes pretty nice
you can get to more places now not yet okay I have to capitalize on this because I kind of
really screwed up too big all right capitalize capitalize capitalize on it you're not capitalizing
capitalize all these fishes oh come on hurry up I only have eight minutes how did I perfectly
get stuck under here where am I bad time loss oh I know that this is a disaster at this point
why do you keep going in the water because I'm spinning and there's a ton of forward momentum
and I can't stop it's my fault for doing that all right I think I can make all this up
nice yep all right go I'm about to be able I can start picking up the big trees all right I got to
go to the next area how much of this can I pick up yet nothing oh shit and get some of them there we
go all right go that's Stonehenge there are people inside of these buildings the model town all right
I just picked up almost this whole parking lot is this the like the Taj Mahal or something
these are all landmarks I can get most of these buildings now can't I small islands not yet
whoa I need more of this I'm gonna run out of time what was I doing can I get the elephant
yep okay let's go oh I can now go over there all right oh it's London New York Statue of Liberty
what's this I'm so big and I'm just like lumbering around shit I'm going too slow 85
holy shit I just picked it up all right all right we're good we're good I got the ferris wheel I
can't get the bridge yet oh get out of this oh come on don't do this I'm gonna run out of time
no go to that next area I don't even know where the next area is I'm so big where was it it was
next to New York I don't think I'm gonna do it it's gonna be really actually really tight oh I'm so
slow and so heavy I move so slowly two minutes I can start getting the islands now start picking
shit up hurry 500 no way was I was like just was I just dicking around for like 10 minutes
oh my so small what do we do that I paused for eight minutes and talk about like fucking
how much I like pickles like sour or better than dill or whatever all right I'm doing it again
I'm restarting I'm gonna restart this one this is a good one I wanted to make this one right
no this one doesn't count this is a warm-up that's his warm-up because I didn't do it
all right I'm gonna pay attention I'm gonna try as hard as I can I'm gonna actually get to I'm
gonna get to 500 really quickly oh I changed the music I'll put a different track on okay so what
do you want for a song Tamari on the rocks fluffing spirit scorching savannah baby universe
what do you want I'm gonna have to listen to this like five times everlasting love you got it I'm
gonna get locked in now let's go what a great start that was better better
I want to get these fences
snowman the boxer and the matador we're putting essays in chat I don't know what they say
start it up oh sorry now it's turned up right down here okay pigs well that's not good
what happened it's all right this is actually fucking awful
I should not be here right now to try I that was such a bad move
I didn't realize I was gonna get stuck in there I have to restart this is actually the worst
possible thing that could have happened there's a full minute that was just removed it's so
important with the late game
oh this is shit RNG too there's nothing to pick up
what's shit RNG there is no RNG in this game yeah yeah there is it's all procedurally generated
the whole game everything even like the dialogue
all right don't do the same thing twice train screwed me over so bad
get out of the road get out of the fucking road
just stand in there walk in the whole entrance good pace
I think I'm gonna go back to the little town there we go all right start actually picking
up a bunch of shit I'm getting most things up here now all right what's next over here
okay now we head over there near the fence okay now we're over here spin it what the
fuck are you doing there we go I got here at like seven minutes left I definitely had much better
pace how's this next area is all the way over there is the right 12 minutes get as many trees
as you can or none and none works too okay all of them I'll come back
this is a way better pace I'll come back 10 minutes not big enough yet but I can get it
you're gonna play the persona remake on stream I've never really got into persona
15 is what I need all right this is the end here
all right over to New York soon
okay I gotta I don't know where to go I wish I could pitch the camera differently
instead of having to press the right bumper standing still can I get out rush more yep come
on get it Hollywood sign I'm gonna go right over to New York get it eight minutes plenty
of time all the how big these things aren't that big actually not big enough to ease up
yes I am all right out here it's time to scale all right back over here all right give me the
whole wall there it is the mountain present in the mountain I need some more movement I'm so slow
the islands 250 I need to get to 500 not there yet it looks like I have enough time but I don't
think it's still gonna be close okay come on pick the whole thing up I mean the monsters
you can definitely get up there dude what are you doing why could I not find that
it's only islands left pick them up spin can I not spin anymore almost there oh I see a cousin
oh it's la la la how do I not that the band is still playing they're waiting for me to start
singing and I just won't just dance around the stage song has just that we've been playing the
intro for the song for like 15 minutes all right start picking up fucking islands there we go
get it all all of it leave nothing left yeah there it is it's a whole sky world oh I'm not
big enough to get it now I'll be happy with a thousand I am completely stuck all right all
these these are huge get it what is that I only got three minutes three minutes remaining is it
oh oh it's the it's the king all right let's go to sky island you thought you were safe all
the way up in the sky once you get this big it is really hard to move it around
am I actually not big enough to pick these up
they get the volcano at least no we got some of it I'm ascending
till 1500 let's go we don't fret about the future the king is the king we'll see oh we feel so much
better oh we forgot smaller than we thought oh the thing is huge every second of the whole
volcanoes we got a mount Fuji as a present fabulous it's kind of cool but it's far too small
I got a new cousin didn't I beat the big bang you made the beginning serious big bang
cool
I want to put on some new thing I got yes 64% save it and I am gonna call it here I told you I had a
little bit of a headache it's uh starting to creep up a little more it's the last level or two but
I'm glad I streamed for five hours did I say like four I will see you uh we're gonna finish this
we'll finish what did I what did I say I want to do no wait wait wait wait here's the plan
so the plan is on Monday we're gonna do zumbinis I'll probably finish this we're gonna finish this
zumbinis sounds good I want to get the other zumbini games but they're the only one they put
on steam was logical journey which is I think the best one but I've never even played the other
zumbinis games write that down so you don't forget it I'm just typing something real quick
who's he typing to oh I'm going okay when's the blt stream blt stream is gonna be
that scares me every time uh I'll lead a blt on the same time I play sorcery when I play sorcery
I will eat a blt before the stream starts will it be toasted no not at all I actually prefer
blt to be dry as fuck oh it shows you all the stuff no of course it's gonna be bacon lettuce
tomato mayo on a sub roll not a sandwich bread sub roll get it right all right I'll see you guys
later thanks for watching we'll see you guys in a couple days see you on Monday uh definitely
definitely see you Monday Monday is very important uh Monday's a really interesting big day
I'm very excited for Monday Monday it's gonna be an interesting day I'm looking forward to it
we're gonna play some beanies we're gonna play I said five nights at Freddy's we're gonna play
some beanies we're gonna play Katamari we're gonna do some other shit I'm excited for Monday
all right Peggle we're gonna play Peggle tonight guys thanks for sticking around
Katamari is really fun it's a great game you should definitely get it I'll finish it on stream
there's only like probably five or six more missions left so Monday Monday Monday Monday
you're gonna play Street Fighter again I need I want to practice Street Fighter
off stream before I play it on stream again not understand how combos work
but um I haven't completely written it off yet somebody said so no um I don't know it depends
take care of yourselves see you Monday I'm very excited for Monday hope your head heals it's fine
it's just one of those annoyances I actually have not really besides maybe a few days ago
I don't remember I feel like it's been I haven't had that many headaches lately I've been on a
pretty normal sleep schedule though I actually been waking up in the morning going to bed at night
that kind of thing so they're trying to get it back to normal yeah thanks a lot take care see you
Monday how's Otto? Otto's doing good Otto is doing good when are you gonna are you gonna give a hard
day for sorcery I'll give it to you right now we're gonna go back to sorcery we'll do a little
recap and we'll chill out drink some tea on 24th Saturday the 24th mark it on your calendars that
is sorcery day we'll just relax a little bit June 24th sounds like a good time two weeks from now
two weekends as always take care of yourselves goodbye call your mother I'll see you Monday
have a great night see you soon