Hey, what's happening? So uh, I gotta do something real quick. I promised I was gonna do this.
Just make sure that I'm ready to go and I'm gonna do a backflip right now.
Here comes backflip. That was a pretty good landing. I stuck it completely. I'll do uh,
do two in a row. Do two in a row. Okay, okay, I'll try. Damn. All right. I kind of hurt my
back a little bit doing that. I'm all right. Anyways, hi. How are you? Well, the Kinect,
Kinect crap. Welcome to the fucking Kinect crap day two. My name is GermanN85. How are you doing?
Today, we're gonna do some extra, and not extras, we're gonna do some extra. We've got
Kinect Star Wars. That's gonna be a popular one. I can already tell. We've got Into the Nightmare,
whatever this horror movie is. We've got Harry Potter, episodes five, six, and seven.
We've got, what else do we got? Oh, I'm not even gonna say the name of that one or it'll give it
away. Gotta get that out. I did three, I did four backflips in a row, so I had to kind of get that
out of my system. We're gonna start with Kinect Star Wars. By the way, I want to make sure you
understand this because I need to say it a few times. I know what's in this game, and this will
be the only time ever, and I really mean this, ever, that you're going to see me dance on this
string. Ever. We're gonna do one song, I think, and I know it's the one you go like this. And,
oh fuck, not ready. Not ready. Hold on. Not ready. Not ready. Not ready. Not ready. I forgot about
my wireless Bluetooth setup. Hold on, not ready. Not ready. My wireless, like, Bluetooth setup. I
didn't put it, I didn't set it up. God damn it, I had to charge it. It shouldn't take too long.
How could I forget about my fucking wireless capabilities? All right, this is good. That's
it. Where's the, okay, there's the right. Just gotta sync it, and I'm ready to go. Hold on.
God damn it, my god, this is stupid. All right, syncing now. Here we go. Battery fully charged.
I just got confirmation. Sync up. Do it. Sync up, please. Come on. Don't make me look like a fool.
Number one. Bluetooth pairing successful. Bluetooth connected. Oh yeah. Yeah, don't
even tell me. I don't know. Fuck, I don't know. See that image? All right, I gotta test it. I gotta
test it. Hold on. Let's go over here. Just like tie in a tie. On the neck, under, and then over.
Make it a little looser. All right, I got my tie on. Wait, that's not good.
How did I do this last time? How did I do this last time? Did anybody see me do it?
Did anybody actually see me do this last time? No, you didn't. All right, I'm ready. Here we go.
Through the loop. Tighten it. There we go. Through the loop again. Into the shirt. That's what it was.
All right, I'm good. All right. All right. Synced up. Here we go. It's time to play Star Wars.
The Kinect version. Why did they just spit the disc out at me? Why? What's, what are you talking
about? They just like spit it back up. Okay, I think we're good. Welcome everybody to Kinect.
Crap, my pants too. I got water this time. I probably should turn it down. It might be a
little too loud. Just a little bit. That's better. So remember, this is Kinect. If you don't know
what the Kinect is, it is a terminal reality. It's a virtual reality simulation system.
How do I skip all this? This game auto saves automatically. Please do not turn off your
console when you see this symbol. Do be careful. Well, auto. We're most insistent that we not
disturb anything. I walked into Star Wars. This is a very important assignment. I honestly couldn't
Oh, auto. Oh, hello. I am C3PO, human cyborg relations. Auto. Master Luke said we would
meet you here. We're most excited to have you supervise our mission. Very good. Uh, start game.
Start game. Start game. I said the microphone symbol's down there. I'm supposed to assume
it's not going to work. It's like continue to play using this profile or sign in to choose a
different one. This game uses drop in drop. Yeah, it's 10 to Dragoon 74. It's me. Yes, we're running.
This is going to start to get low here over the next few Kinect streams, I think.
And yes, I've got the thing in the hair. Make sure it doesn't get in my face today.
Of course, I qualified R2. How else do you think we got this assignment?
R2.
Jedi Destiny Dark Side Rising. We've also got Podracing? Podracing? Galactic Dance-off.
Translating all these files into Shrevewook? We'd be here for centuries.
Rancor Rampage? When am I going to use my lightsaber? Duel of Fates. I can't use my
lightsaber yet. I'm not doing the dance-off first. Absolutely not. Okay, what about Jedi Destiny?
The history of an entire species. Jedi Destiny Dark Side Rising. Let's do this one.
If I'm interpreting this correctly, I want to use the lightsaber.
I'm not doing the dance-off first. That's like the pinnacle of all online content.
I think I'm going to do that first. It's the only time I'm ever going to get this dance-off
straight. Like the best thing that I will ever do on this channel. Like the most highly rated
thing that I will ever fucking do. Here we go. Get away. Excellent. Now call up the file, R2.
Let's take a better look at the commander selection. Begin the destiny. Am I the Jedi
in Star Wars Connect? No. I have to pick from a random Jedi? The Jedi history really is quite
stirring. Honestly, my compassion algorithms have never seen so much use. I can't be like Darth Me?
I don't know why I want to play it. I think I'm going to be the alien over here.
By my calculations, there is a 63.44% chance that any of these operations will end in failure.
When dealer is showing a six, I know C-3PO. What's good about the singe? Casual or advanced.
That was a fucking funny joke because that actually is the percentage. It's like 63.4%.
I swear to God, that's a funny joke. I don't care if anybody thinks it's funny.
The record begins with Master Zane and her padawans approaching the planet.
The training never stops. What are you doing? I want to select my padawan? That's me, right?
Okay, Darth Singe. Oh, it's flip two. Whatever. Let's go. What did I do?
Let's see if I can get a good spot with the sun beams right into my fucking eyes.
I'll get it. Star Wars. Right. Oh, he's singing. That means he has to go like this.
All right. How do I make it go faster? Go faster. It is a time of uncertainty.
It is a time of uncertainty alarmed by the encounter with the Sith Lord Darth Maul
on Naboo. The Jedi Council has begun strengthening the ranks of the Jedi Order.
By opening training outposts to instruct a new generation of padawan learners.
Meanwhile, events throughout the galaxy suggest that the influence of the dark side is spreading.
A group of padawans are on their way to Kashyyyk, home world of the Wookiees, to learn about the
force in preparation for the difficult times ahead. The narrator doesn't know how to...
All right, let's go. Is that synced up? You should hear the snap of my handcuffs
up there like that. Bored. Let's go.
It's a new guy. It's a new guy. Welcome, padawans. Each one of you is strong in the force. Brave.
Instructed in the teachings of our order. But not all of you will become Jedi. As you know,
the ones must proceed through a series of trials. Trials of skill, courage, insight.
I'm roleplaying. Stop.
Stop. You're gonna blow this for me. Stop.
Blow it for me. I'm gonna pick my lightsaber now.
No, that's not me.
I think this is cutting off circulation of my brain.
It is me.
You got it.
Feel the force flow between you and the pedestal. Take a moment to feel its weight.
Oh, shit. He's insane. Let's start with some simple drills. Swing back and forth until you
feel comfortable. Shouldn't we step back from each other? You're too... I think you're too close.
We're gonna clan. Some of the ancient Jedi forms.
You've been practicing these since you were younglings. Very good, padawan.
Should I clang him? Just ding. Does this block? Oh, I was doing that.
I didn't get to customize my character. All right, that's a really dangerous move
because if you fuck that up, that goes through your back and kills you.
Like, even if you're slightly off, I mean, it looks real cool.
But that literally goes through the back of your skull when you die.
Oh, yeah? I mean, that was kind of cool teach. Check this out.
Dad, I win.
Can I two-hand? I'm a two-handed sword kind of guy.
As Master Yoda can attest, we live in an uncivilized time.
In combat, many of your opponents will use blasters.
If you can't get close enough to strike your enemy, you'll need to deflect their blaster bolts.
So you just gotta go, bing. Now it's your turn.
Audio is decent. I don't care. Some enemies will attack from a distance.
Use your lightsaber for deflection. I'm not doing this shit like yesterday.
Very good. One guy's not going to turn the stream off for like 30 minutes to get beat up.
I know it's safe. I checked it. It's not perfect, but it never will be.
Oh, let's do it.
Padawan, you must deflect these laser blasts.
No Padawan is perfect.
I've done it four times.
No Jedi Knight either, for that matter.
Good work.
I'm sorry, I gotta D.
I gotta D.
There will be times when your opponent won't simply vaporize or be sliced into pieces.
Sometimes you will have a true duel.
You two, come forward.
Let's move on. You'll need some space for this, so spread out.
Of course, these are all training sabers, so no one will lose an arm today.
I want to do the thing that you did.
And it will cost quite a wealth, though. Wouldn't be very instructive.
I can't do it from behind the back?
Engage your opponents. Attempt to block their lightsaber strikes.
Left, right, high, low. Pay close attention to the enemy's attacks.
Move your saber to the correct position, Padawan.
I just what? Okay. I thought I just got my head.
You can do better to defend yourself. Also, a quick dodge or jump at the right moment
allows you to avoid. Why am I dodging?
I shouldn't be dodging. Defend yourself against your enemy,
you have the opportunity to change the momentum of the fight.
To put it on your terms. Why am I dodging?
I shouldn't be dodging. Why is it blocked to dodge?
Once you now have your opening to train and try to defeat your opponent in a duel.
I'm going to clash.
Do I have to hold it? Do I have to kick him? Okay.
There we go. There we go.
Please, whoa, don't do a finishing move. Is that it?
Well done.
Fatality.
A good beginning, Padawan, but there'll be much more to learn on Kashyyyk.
Prepare for arrival.
And now it's time for your next Jedi technique.
The fucking dancing.
All right, this is gonna be real.
All right, let's go.
I think you're ready to block. Block, block.
Slash. Should I skip the cinematic?
Does anybody care about Star Wars?
No, nobody cares about the story in Star Wars.
They just care about the light thing that makes cool sounds.
Master Windu was here too.
I can't believe it. It's Obi-Wan kind of Sith boy.
Danger? Great hope in you. We have.
Tomorrow, your lessons begin.
Here are your new trainees, Master Yoda.
I'll warn you, they're still very rough, but they do have potential.
Say the same for you. We once did, long ago.
No Padawan could ask for a better master than you.
A pleasure you were.
You've done very well, Ma'am. A council sanction.
We know you understand the importance of this undertaking.
My turn yet?
There's something troubling you, Master Yoda.
Something dark I see in these Padawans' future.
We have all sensed it, and yet the council's vision remains clouded.
The events on Naboo, Darth Maul's appearance, these were no aberrations.
There is a darkness rising in the galaxy, and the Sith Master waits in the shadows.
I must return now to Coruscant. May the Force be with you.
No, they did it to wipe the source Lucas, right?
Your training does.
Why is this Wipeout Wookiee edition?
Wait, hold on, do I have to do this?
I don't think I'm going to be able to do this.
I'm standing here, I'm standing right here.
Okay, I have to do Wipeout Wookiee challenge.
Focus, focus into your center, then explode outward with a kick.
And wipe out man.
Source senses, avoid these obstacles quickly. Explode quickly to avoid the logs.
Time has come that this is only a test.
Go! What the fuck are you doing?
I hate this.
What? Am I out of like, Naruto powers?
For most of the end we are.
Help you, I could, but then you would not learn.
Why can't I just walk?
Use your senses to jump at the right time.
Once more, Padawan.
I don't know.
I jumped through it.
I just want to walk.
He's laughing at you?
Use the force to knock over the training dummy.
What? Wrong arm.
Concentrate, focus.
Do not be afraid.
You have the most serious mind.
Guide you, these will.
I'm itching my leg.
He's like, putting his hand.
I can't like, itch my leg.
Oh, get in there! It's like, come on!
And heavy objects will live.
Oh.
Yeah, test your skill.
This will.
Yes.
This is just Jillian Michaels in the jungle workout for James.
Cannot withstand the power of the force.
Now we have to play Angry Birds.
Use the force to select the rocks.
And at the tower, fling them.
Not bad.
Very good.
First hit, first try.
With a simple rock, an explosive.
You manipulate it by holding your hand out and focus your energy on the rock.
To catch it, catch with you can.
And redirect it.
Yes.
What? Catch it? Oh, catch the rock.
Am I trying to hit you on the head?
Imitation.
Precision to your display.
Okay.
No more training.
Not bad.
I don't even need any more training.
I know you. That what you need.
I gotta stop walking forward.
I'm just like, wandering around like an idiot.
Uh-oh, here we go.
Here comes the lip.
Senate Scythe.
That's it, if you've never seen Star Wars before.
Don't.
It's literally like, it's just too much.
That was it.
I took out the whole thing.
Yeah, Star Wars, it's a whole thing.
This is like 30, 40 books.
I love to say, oh, but the Star Wars movies now, it's based on like 50 novels.
And they're all like a thousand pages long.
It's just, it's a lot.
The books, you know, they're all right.
But if you really want to get the whole thing, you gotta read them all.
The movies really condense everything down way too much.
I think the first, so episode four, which is Star Wars, it was for a lost city.
It's like, I think this, it's like the middle 30 books.
Like, there's like 20, book 20 to book 35.
You can really start the books out of one or two, which everyone was like, what the fuck is this?
Like, it was episode, book 20 came out in 1970 or something.
You see how much that doesn't make any sense when you talk about other pieces of media?
George.
This thing's gonna explode.
Oh, I thought we were gonna do it.
I thought we were just gonna blow up.
Is this gonna kill us both?
Quick, Yoda, bail.
Bail out Yoda.
Go find us a motorcycle.
Actually, the control's pretty good.
How do you break?
Thank God there's a shield.
Otherwise, a regenerating shield.
Otherwise, Yoda, we would be in some shit right now.
Break out.
Not bad.
No, there's more.
This is boss.
Boss ship.
Is it telegraphing on the ground?
It makes this a lot easier, I guess.
Don't, thank God.
Oh, I did advanced difficulty too, didn't I?
Now you finally said something.
Look at the trees.
Oh, sorry, Yoda.
I thought that I was gonna drive into them.
Shit.
Am I going the right way?
Stop talking in front of me.
I don't care about the...
Break.
All right, so Yoda's gonna jump off and slash him?
Oh, we just got to get that last little scene.
That's pretty cool.
Break the disk?
I'm not gonna shred every Kinect disk.
Cross the water to the village.
We'll shoot them.
If I'm gonna break, you need to shoot.
All right, I was supposed to go that way.
There's a big wave bracer.
It reminds me of it.
All right, I'm done with the bracing around shooting.
Can we do anything else, Yoda?
I can't see.
This is a blur.
It's blur.
It's a blur.
I swear to God, it's a blur.
That was all the same thing we were saying.
What the fuck?
Can I break?
No, fuck.
Thank God this saves states.
10 seconds to shoot.
Let's do it.
Just like that?
Good job, Yoda.
We make a great team.
They should make a movie about us.
Don't worry, they will.
At last, the village we have reached.
They will.
That wasn't very fun.
I don't think that was very fun at all.
I like the Jedi stuff.
I think I know why the Kinect failed.
Because 75% of every single Kinect game is dodge left or dodge right.
That's if they didn't do anything else.
Go like this or go like that.
That's almost every single one of these.
And sometimes you go like this.
I'm here, right?
You're training.
And may the force be with you.
All right, this is what I wanted to do.
I feel like I played Harry Potter the exact same way.
This is deflecting.
All right, now go in.
You missed one on your right.
Get over here.
Come here.
I had a chance.
Didn't work.
All involved.
All of your friends.
I want to do an actual deflect like that.
Like that.
That was fun.
That was pretty fun.
It's on rails.
I can do that too.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
I can actually play.
This way?
Down?
This is kind of a pathetic Jedi.
If you can't take one droid with a stick,
you probably need to go back to school.
All right, those guys have armor.
I'll handle this.
He's coming in.
That arm looks like it's going to explode.
Not bad.
That was like, just let me walk through.
Like, did you really have to have that?
Yeah.
Here comes boss, I think.
Oh, Chewbacca.
Chewbacca is dead.
Oh, shit.
Chewie.
No.
He got shot like right in the head.
Oh, that was terrible.
That was awful.
That's not canon.
This is one of these expanded universes.
It's like somebody just, like, knocked him up.
Go on, get in there, Chewie.
They're all, they're, all right.
It's by their own movies.
How did you figure eight?
Figure eight.
I, I, my brain can't do it when I hear this sound.
I didn't do anything.
I just stood behind and just, I just looked like I was doing something.
We were all carrying the sofa, like six of us,
and I was just putting my fingertips on him, attending.
Where's my lightsaber?
Oh, right.
He's all right.
He's okay.
He's gonna be fine.
I actually have to do this.
That's actually part of what I have to do.
No, I'm gonna get an ice cream, mom.
This is how actors look, right?
This is, all right, I just, like, kill skull.
The actors just do this shit in front of a green screen.
They just, in action, and they just go like this.
And then, like, six million dollars worth of CG.
And editing goes into that and makes it look, it makes it look awesome.
Go look at any behind the scenes for the many movies
you've ever seen in your whole life that had action in it.
It's like this.
It's, it doesn't even look real.
Like, then all the millions of dollars that make it, like,
fuck, fly everywhere, it's ridiculous.
What do I do?
Now what?
Oh, John just barely made it.
Did I get it?
John, look it.
Look at the actor and look at, look at the action, right?
I told you.
She just, she just killed, like, five people on our team.
Just saying.
I think I missed my opportunity.
I think I missed the opportunity.
Why am I jogging?
Big rates, big rates.
I gotta, I gotta stop thinking about it.
I fuck it up every time I think about it.
Let me get one.
That was on her.
That wasn't even on me.
She missed that one.
I just saved your life.
Turn around.
Are you fucking serious?
I need to get inside the ship to destroy the core.
Hold them off as long as you can.
I'm gonna accept the thermal detonator.
I can't wait till the fucking music goes.
How the fuck do I go over there?
Yeah.
Hey, that's low.
They didn't do anything.
Whew.
Why flip?
Why not just leap?
Why not, like, step over and land safely?
Why flip?
You can't see where the fuck you're landing.
Imagine trusting the fact that you're gonna do a full rotation and land on your feet.
You just don't.
You just miscalculate when you're going forward.
You just land on your back.
That's when, like, baseball players, like, do something stupid
and they end up on the, I mean, like, the disabled list
for, like, 15, 30 days.
That's the type of shit that you do when you're a Jedi.
You end up on the fucking DL.
Yeah.
They have to have a list, guys.
Really?
I can't wait till we transition to dancing.
I was gonna do a Chewie, but it might have been a really, really embarrassing Chewie.
Let's get started then.
Let me test it behind you.
Let me just test it and see.
As long as you don't see my face, I can do it.
As long as you don't look at me.
I know what you said.
I just didn't think it would happen this soon.
See, if it was in front of the camera, I would, I wouldn't, I would back out.
Lock it.
I can't wait till I fight Doc Vader.
How come nobody's ever decided to do the strangle to Doc Vader?
You know?
Why wouldn't Obi-Wan just stick to like this without strangling Doc Vader?
They both just, like, it's, it has a better grip at that point, I think.
Just do that to the Emperor.
What's he gonna do?
I will electrocute you.
Do the Doc Vader.
He'll, you got an old man by the throat.
He's not gonna be able to shoot you with electricity.
Fuck that, dude.
I would just, I would just, I would just stone cold stun people.
Like it was before.
You know, get him, like, round the neck like this and then, like, stun him.
And they would go, boom!
And they would launch you up.
It would be fucking awesome.
Come on, let's go.
Now all of a sudden you don't want to.
Got it.
You and me.
I just hit the lady behind me.
I just, like, right at the lady.
Just do that.
Like, you know, as a Jedi, you don't have mana.
Think about that.
These motherfuckers waste all their time learning how to sword fight, like, from the 1700s.
Just go like this and throw people off a cliff.
What's the, what, what's the point of that?
Just go like this and push a whole army off a fucking bridge.
Why would you even ever get in close for any reason?
This is tiring.
You get tired doing this shit for more than five minutes.
Yeah, I just gotta hold my hand out and just concentrate like I'm doing a fucking crossword puzzle
and I can throw somebody off a bridge?
The only thing I can think of that would be a problem in doing this is just the trope
in every single piece of media.
A slight nosebleed.
Oh no!
I did it too long.
I'll be fine in a second.
Why do they bleed from their eyes?
You really want to give some real gravity to that situation?
A blood out of the eyes.
And it's like blood.
Blink, blink, blink, red.
Blood in the eyes and you can't see.
Then it'll be like, whoa, shit, you don't want to do that.
You definitely want to do that shit for more than a minute.
You won't be able to see.
Oh shit, it's been 57 minutes.
We're supposed to be done in 30.
We're supposed to only give everyone these 30 minutes.
Oops.
It's me, I'm here.
Let me just finish this and then I'll do one dance.
Actually, you know, I can't do a dance.
Sorry, guys.
It's been 57 minutes.
I still don't understand that.
It's like, oh, chewy, chewy, chewy.
Chewy.
I'm way ahead.
Explosion.
An explosion launched me.
I didn't do that.
That was the explosion on my back.
Yeah, fuck that, man.
I would just get a suit of armor.
I would be in like a steel full suit of armor.
I just hold my hands out and throw it.
So that would be a caster.
That was more embarrassing for you than it was cool for me.
I will say.
Chewy, don't do it, Chewy.
What the fuck?
This stupid ass boy, Blaine.
Am I good?
All right, I'm good.
Want a Jar Jar?
I can't do a Jar Jar.
What's that Chewy doing on the left?
This Chewy on the left, I think he has like sand in his eyes.
Let's make him think he did that.
This shit don't fucking do anything.
Signed me up.
Arties.
How's hair?
Controlled.
Although, might need to re-tie it up here.
Next, next.
Hold on.
I can't quit mid-game.
I'm gonna do this and then I'll dance for you guys.
I'll dance.
I need to get the boss.
It's Darth Vader.
He's the boss in every one of the video games.
It's not gonna be anybody else.
It's just gonna show up.
It's gonna be a one-on-one scenario.
Am I driving the...
How about you do something?
I have to do the work for both of us?
I know that you just had your hands lightly on it.
Nice work.
You need to do a Chewy?
Does the lizard people have Chewy sounds?
What's that?
Darth Vader.
It's tricky.
Tricky here.
Grab somebody.
Alright, we're good.
Yeah!
Oh no, they must...
Oh, that went quick.
I don't wanna fucking stop.
I really don't.
Oh, shit.
God.
See you later.
That guy was expendable.
Ah, man.
I'm fine.
This is so stupid.
Did you tell me to duck?
Did it on instinct.
Put the saber down.
Easy.
Got it.
No, I'm fine, Xbox.
I need a full...
Ball...
Oh, I need three servings.
Oh, failed to pull the spring.
I'll be alright.
Oh, my God.
We're good?
Was this supposed to happen?
It's like another part of the scene?
Uh, what do we do now?
Get off!
Come on, get yours, hurry up!
When will it end?
When you hear, off camera...
And he steps in.
And he goes...
Here it comes.
The walk.
Five of his attacks.
And then, there'll be an explosion,
and then the anger and...
I'll take care of you next time.
Non-canon dickhead, and he'll just walk away.
This is a long chapter.
This is the Clone Wars.
That doesn't matter.
Think that matters?
Darth Vader could be eight right now,
and he's still gonna walk out like eight feet tall.
Oh, I get...
Where is the...
Oh, it's the twins!
This is...
Now, this is a fight.
This is the two twins.
Tweedle-dee and Tweedle-dum.
Oh, I got a...
First base.
Down.
What was that?
How did he hit me?
How was he hitting me?
All right, mine's down.
Oh, I have to...
Dance waiting room.
What was that?
I do hope your day has been an enjoyable one.
Your Wookie friend has been very diligent,
and I believe we are almost ready for takeoff.
Are you excited?
I don't know who this is.
I'm excited.
This robot?
I am TC38, and I'm very pleased to meet you.
Welcome aboard the Star Runner.
Oh, I'm very sorry.
The power couplings seem to have failed.
That's enough.
Get out of the way.
Here comes Darth Maul.
They will not escape us.
Were those the twins with the masks?
Oh.
I did it.
Oh, God, no.
Looks like a welcoming party.
It's friends of yours.
Is there a chapter selective,
or am I just playing through the whole game without knowing?
I believe your friends...
I believe Chewbacca would like you to take up the main guns.
We're not friends.
Because he's quite occupied trying to activate the hyperdrive.
I am going through the whole game.
It's been some time since we've been serviced.
Stop, stop, stop.
What, and what...
I'm having a fun time.
I think you should man the ship and hurry.
Everybody wants to see the fucking meme dances so bad.
Abort mission.
You want to dance?
Fine.
I'll give you a dance.
Dance.
The Millennium Falcon's gone, so it doesn't matter.
How do I get this in...
Did I do it?
I can't get out of here.
I can't leave.
Exit game.
I'm stuck here.
I can't leave.
Lift your right arm.
That's to join, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Should I...
I don't think I can get out of here.
Xbox.
Main menu.
Exit.
Connect Star Wars Walkthrough Part 45.
End of walkthrough.
We didn't want to switch.
I'm not switching.
I just did the only thing I knew how to get out of there.
We're going to do the thing.
This thing.
You're going to go...
Don't tell me they never gave you what you want, you know?
I got to give people what they want.
I'm going to go like this.
I'm going to be the first idiot to hurt themselves
playing this stupid Kinect game.
I'm going to like trip trying to be a funny guy
and I'm going to like...
Like run in the wall.
Up to do be careful.
Master Luke has best insisted that we...
Louder!
Did I corrupt my save?
No, please.
This is a very important site.
Did did did did did did did did!
Yes!
Stop!
Care less if you...
Oh, hello AMC 3PO.
Human-Cyborg relations at your surface.
Master Luke said we would meet you here.
You've been recognized.
So I continue to play?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
All right, here we go.
I have both lightsabers and shit and everybody wants to spree you.
There it is.
Slot one.
Oh, yes, R2.
We're all eager to get going.
I think I bit my cheek.
Yeah, I bit my cheek, I think.
I think the stream...
I have to leave.
Oh, oh, stream over, I think.
Dear, this archive appears to have been merged
with a Torgian Entertainment's dispatch.
It's completely corrupted.
Still...
I have a hangnail right here.
...sometimes prove...
Ooh, ow, ow, ooh.
...should we take a little look?
I can't stream today.
I'm sorry, guys, I can't.
Here we are, Commander.
Ready to go.
Song title.
Who am I going to play as?
I guess I'm going to be...
I can't be the stormtrooper?
Of course I know what I'm talking about, R2.
In fact, there are several afterimports of documentation
based entirely on that routine.
And I would have unlocked it.
How do I get a layup?
I would have gotten one of these characters.
Wrong story.
You know, I don't know why you're here, R2.
Isn't there something that needs fixing somewhere?
Well, then, be quiet while the Commander thinks.
Song title.
I'm afraid we can't do anything.
I'm afraid we can't offer any advice.
I've never been fitted with a strategy chip.
And R2's broke a long time ago.
Well, I wouldn't call those good decisions, R2.
It's a miracle we even survive some of your decisions.
There, there, there, there, there, there, that one, there.
Wait, what do you mean, there? Han Solo?
Oh, yeah, this is an app. I know. People love this one.
It's a continual fascination to me
that simple, repetitive audio output
and the varying decibels of...
Enjoy a VOD.
People that are watching the VOD,
have a great rest of your night.
I'll see you next time.
I'm going to go all out for this, though.
If you think for you, I'm just going to be like,
oh, funny. No, I'm fucking going to do this.
Stick it as hard as I can.
Right?
That was a pretty good one.
You looked the part, but let's see some of your moves.
I haven't seen this.
Never done this before.
But I answered to ain't a picture in the palace
No
And since the carbonite's off me
I'm living life now that I'm free
Yeah
Told me get myself together
Now I got myself together
Now I made it through the weather
Better days are going to get better
I'm so happy
The carbonite is gone
Who dances like this?
Solo, solo
Picking up my plants to put in all my
Ow, I hit those. I can't hit a song.
I'm solo
I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, solo
Solo, solo
I'm hunting solo
It feels so good
Stop feeling misunderstood
Back in the game, who knew I would
So flat, time I spread my wings
Loving myself makes me want to sing
No more
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Told me get myself together
Now I got myself together
Now I made it through the weather
Better days are going to get better
I'm so happy
The carbonite is gone
A movie that is over now
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
They look like a star
You can't stop my shine
I'm loving class city, my head is in the sky
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, solo
That's a lot of money, thanks a lot man
So I can do it again?
Advanced? I can't do advanced yet
Alright, I'm getting five stars
Of course I know what I'm talking about R2
In fact, there are several outer rim forms of communication
Based entirely on dance routines
Cloud City is always looking for new talent
You think you have what it takes?
Like a star, you keep my shine
I'm cloud city, my head is in the sky
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
Solo
Yeah, I'm feeling good tonight
Finally feeling free and it feels alright
Oh, time to do the things I like
Gonna see your princess, everything's alright
Oh, no job or to answer to
Ain't a fixture in the palace zoo
No, and since the carbonite's off me
I'm living life now that I'm free
Trying to get myself together
Now I got myself together
Now I made it through the weather
Better days are gonna get better
I'm so happy the carbonite is gone
Happy that it's over now
The pain is gone
I'm ashamed to cover up my eyes
I'm jumping in my ride tonight
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
Solo
I'm picking up my plaster, putting it on my sign
I'm jumping in my falcon, put my sign
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
Solo
Did I get it wrong?
What am I talking about?
Why should you join me in life?
It feels so good
Oh, stop feeling misunderstood
Back in the game, who knew?
I was spraying my wings
Loving myself makes me wanna sing
Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Told me to get my act together
Now I got my act together
Yeah
Now I made it through the weather
Better days are gonna get better
I'm so happy the carbonite is gone
I'm so happy that it's over now
The pain is gone
I'm ashamed to cover up my eyes
I'm jumping in my ride tonight
I'm getting down tonight
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
Solo
I feel like a star, you can't stop my shine
I'm loving plasticity, my head's in the sky
I'm solo, I'm hunting solo
I'm hunting solo, I'm hunting solo
Solo
Shit!
Ripping stuff off the wall
Retro...
Okay, I got advanced difficulty
That's not how I'm gonna be able to do that
Do I get more points?
I can only do this song like one more time
before people start to hear it in their sleep
Alright, this is it
Whatever happens, happens
And I'm moving on
I'm so sorry
That it's gonna be over now
But we gotta move on
I feel like a star
Let's go!
Always knew the general solo was not to be trusted
This final proves it
Was that... did I pick difficulty?
I didn't get the very difficulty
It's kinda casual
What's that?
I have to... I have to do that to fail, right?
I... I don't know how I get out of it
There's no way to get out
You can unlock Darth Vader singing this
Wait, there it is
He's not joking
You can unlock alternate voice tracks
Keep up the good work, commander
We're really getting to the heart of this dictum
I'm not doing this one again
May I respectfully remind you
that you have not yet viewed the advanced musical sequence
for the I'm Han Solo audio track
Thank you
Advanced
This is it, this is the one
Alright, so it's that
the pose, not this
I do it wrong every time
Let's do the spaghetti arms
You gotta, you gotta do, you gotta do
Man, every young hot shot needs a man
Let's go up here
It's being that guy back there
It's different
So far, the night is gone
I'm movin' on, it's over now
The pain is my change to cover up my eyes
I'm the solo, I'm the Han Solo
I'm the Han Solo, I'm the Han Solo, Solo
I'm pickin' up my plaster, puttin' in on my side
I'm chumpin' in my cow, got my side
I'm the Solo, I'm the Han Solo
I'm the Han Solo, I'm the Han Solo, Solo
Am I right?
stood back in the game so flat time i spread my wings loving myself makes me want to sing though
yeah yeah yeah yeah told me get my act together now i got my act together
the days are gonna get better i'm so happy the carbonite is gone i'm so happy that it's over now
the pain is gone
oh
it was fine i got did i get it five stars
what's this another extended musical sequence oh goodness gracious me
might want to consider viewing the extended sequence for the i'm han solo audio track
though i can't say i approve
and it feels all right oh time to do the things i like gonna see your princess everything's all
right oh no job but i answered to ain't a fixture in the palace too no and since the carbonite's off
me i'm living life now that i'm free yeah trying to get myself together now i got myself together
yeah
i'm so happy
that it's over now the pain is gone
i'm
loving myself makes me want to sing
yeah
my act together now i got my act together
the days are gonna get better be the i'm so happy that it's gone
i'm so low i'm so low i'm so low i'm so low solo solo
feel it like a star you can't stop my shine i'm loving cloud city my head
i'm so low
it's like s o l o s o l o s o l o i'm living my life like a stress noble
i'm putting on my shades to cover up my eyes i'm jumping in my ride i'm getting out i'm so low
i'm hiding so low i'm hiding so long i'm hiding so low solo
feel it like a star you can't stop my shine i'm loving cloud city my head's in the sky
yes i was lost halfway through there i'm laughing at that like stupid like pretend pump up
fake hold yourself then pump up do let's go don't ever tell me i'm old again what's that
enemy oh i think i just poke muscle i think i don't ever fucking let you guard down what
am i gonna do now look at that like okay i that i love that makes me look bald i'm not though
i gotta redo this see i just want to prove that i have hair let's go man that's the get pumped up
at 11 30 at night when your parents are sleeping and they have to wake up for work tomorrow
just did it on that another game to go i'm gonna go outside and spray myself with a hose
i think i'm actually gonna i'm gonna spray myself with a fucking garden hose
outside that looks fucking weird what can i do okay all right let's go next on the list
i'll just show you do my i gave you a sneak peek fighters uncaged hold on to your seats
free oatmeal that's what it takes you want to the power of oatmeal look at that fucking look at
that rock look at that fucking egg in there it's a fucking power three oatmeals now down here we've
got a scenario that ain't that ain't no pretty in this area we've got some work to do and in this
area and dad down here and back here calves but it's for three oatmeals a day we'll get you
one of those thanks with 20 community subs chunky baloney i missed it i was too busy five star
why don't you take a picture david me they both made me drain this water
you haven't had to identify me all right i think should we do lesson first figure out how to do this
fighting technique basic punches i think i i think i kind of already know how to do this shit
hey welcome to the ring i'm going to teach you some things ready we got from new york
hold your hands up like this take a few punches that's it now rock them high never mind to raise
your guard stand face the sensor face up in front of your shoulders raise and lower your guard three
times i can't even see the opponent straight punch punch straight your arm must be extended
left it is i don't know how to do this got a hook left hook he looked like he was gonna punch me
he was getting ready to throw is there like bear hug all right so punch kick basic kicks
advanced punches we don't give shit i'm ready how about just training fighting ranges habits
no it's called punch the guy in the face technique i'll give you a technique it's called punch guy as
hard as you can oh we have to do it anyways uh thank you to uh janerino for the five community
subs thanks with five sub thank you and we got chunky baloney for 20 huge amount of subs thank
you guys we have to do this shit anyways i'm gonna breeze through this straight i have to do it
straight kick straight kick i don't skip it i just need to know how to do it once knee strike
skip it knee strike okay you can do knee you can do kick you can do punch round kick got it
skip it train skip it let me find somebody is there a storyline in this game or is it just
beat up the ai oh god all right what your tutorial is between it's like six tutorials
that are five minutes long that have individual cutscenes individual loading screens i would rather
have the guy the new yorker tell me how to do things okay try enough for i fight your trainer
you're in okay medium range long range let's go one let's go i'm not going to give him a chance
come on got you got from new york
jump kick to go to medium range
i was too far away for that strike
so
dodge that strike
at medium range this he dodged my strike show me what you made him he's oh i'm groggy
he's gone we get to my who's that guy who's the guy from final fight
what's his name it's like what the fuck is his name
yeah that guy was awesome he was unbeatable is there a game here
feet keep an eye on my feet yes you should
very well i should make him act stupid i should make him act stupid
watch out for my feet how to straight after dodging all right watch out for my feet watch
out for my feet waiting he was doing so well he just let me beat him up
i'm waiting bang bang bang bang bang bang i guess i lose now thanks thanks for playing
watch my
i could have countered straight after dodging well get in there
can i do something besides the trainer why the fuck are we doing this again why would you
ever in a hundred million years do this watch out for my feet
feet he is getting worse his dodging will be less precise watch out for my
he's exhausted watch out for my watch out for my okay if this guy gets up he's i don't he can't
this guy i'm gonna kill this guy i taught you nervous keep an eye on my feet
region watch out for my feet watch out for my feet i thought i'm about to press the button
to turn this off but i kind of see what happens the rest of the game it can't be like this
right there's no way watch out for my feet if i have to fight the trainer again i will shred this
game watch out for my fists exhausted i can straight kick to the long range
at what point is he like out of bounds keep an eye on my feet watch out for my feet
watch out for my feet touch my fists
keep an eye on my feet all right i've got to put i've got to put them out i've got it because this
is it has to be it just give him everything i should sweep him when he misses this is it
please that would be the end i think i did it
all right all right all right rider first guy if we're standing on the mats down in a gym
it's coming up we'll need a shot of adrenaline one fight this is what i'm talking about
i can't do that one anymore but this one should i give you a sneak peek what do you think
should i sneak peek in just give me a little sneak peek see if i can do this it's wow classic
yeah in fact actually what you don't know is that would have been
a pretty funny joke if i had eight cds in my hand i'll let it be a surprise because i feel
like this one's gonna be awesome awesome awesome awesome just wait for it dark souls connect dark
souls 2 connect you have to have you have to flip around your room to dodge i'm sorry it's the mighty
more than power rangers connect i did i missed it why don't you change this song what why do
they need to change that rangers forever power rangers samurai show now do i get to pick what
ranger i get to be and by the way it's a little dark in here change that shit whoa whoa whoa whoa
what that's all right okay i'm trying to put the lights up a little there we go it's getting a
little dark all right ranger training or collection it's voice actor in new game no ranger select oh
this is a tough choice billy elf i don't know what the red ranger's name is tina and i'm gonna
say i'm gonna be tommy green ranger green ranger green ranger is that what they look like it looks
like a kid's halloween costume you could get that in the spirit of halloween and like the
party store that's what they did they they were like they were like iron mill whoa
samurizer go go samurai this is gonna be a good one do my symbol mastodon pterodactyl toad angel
fish this is the best game i've ever played in my whole life i mean this could be this could be
better than bloodborne this is probably the best game i've ever played let's go mouth guy
it's just don't let it go like this don't let it go like this please get in there
yeah
that's
As in the cereal you eat in the sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
don't get hit,no don't get hit,
wait 25 granger license point. Next double achiever!
what i got it i did it
You actually get to do this.
Don't go Samurai. What is he
doing that? Why is it split
screen? Come on, Jerry. Let's
go. You're keeping us all
If I was 13.
Fire 33. I played.
He thought that each one is an
individual story. I like that.
Oh god. Now, we got a tan guy.
Write your symbol tomorrow.
I don't have to carry my ball.
Which one? No, I'm worried.
What if I jumped and just went
through the ground? Just like
here we go. Here we go. I want
to get I want to get like a
hundred hit combo. Let's go.
Let's go. What's this?
Good.
Right here.
This is done. This arm is done.
I can't I can't I can't do it
anymore with this arm. When you
get this. This is fun. I need
like a like a stick.
Just be like. Next. You know,
I'm like going like this. It's
like just my arm's gonna throw
my arm up. If I go like like
that.
Did I break it?
Now, not so tight this time.
Make sure you do it a little
looser. That's better. What
are you going to say about
that? I think it's time for me
to kick. It's time to kick your
ass. It's **** up the sensor.
It thinks my body's like three
times longer. What? What? Jerry?
You're gonna do it together.
Sorry. Sorry. How did you make
it like this? Why couldn't you
just do the command? Victory is
out. It's like the wrong way.
The way you look at it. Like
remember, I'm mirrored. Flame
badge. Flame badge. Next. I
gotta go refill that water and
right after this one. Go, go,
German Ranger. I'm trying. Why
would I want to get that on
camera? Whatever. Your symbol
tomorrow. Green tongue. Act today.
I have to use my right hand as
a weapon because it's hard for
me to do this now because I
it's my I'm losing circulation
here. I'm gonna pick up my
right hand and use it like this
because I have no strength.
That works. He's weak. Weak.
I've been in the middle of an
exercise for two and a half
hours. I can't do it. I have to
chase him. Oh no. I dodged it.
Why would you step in? It's
gonna double tap. You idiot. A
car. Turn off the power. Alright,
here we go. Lights are off. Oh
**** You saw me, dog. Here we
go. Stop. Activate. Quit
looking at him. Run after him.
Boss. Alright, let's go. Three
three. Fight. I don't have a
uh I don't have power up yet.
Let's do this thing. Oh, he's
snoring.
Don't go in. Now, wait. Don't
get hit. Back up. Back up. Back
up. Back up. Back up. Back up.
I can't get hit by this. This
way is he gonna go? Left or
right? He's doing it again? I
can't. Get over there. Get over
there you **** idiot. That's
good. Thank god it's the
children. I thought that was
another camera pointing at me.
I was like, who put a **** camera
in my room? It was like facing
me this way. I was like, why is
that? Inferno badge. No uh
Megazord? Next. Why would there
be no Megazord? Uh after this
one, we're gonna have to do a
uh I gave up. I don't have any
energy to do that. Let me see
what I do. Uh that's what I do
with me. You know, that doesn't
do anything. That doesn't have
any powers. It's just what they
chose to do for that particular
reason. They chose to go like
this. It doesn't mean that I'm
not as strong. It's just weak.
That doesn't do anything. That's
just for show. Let's get that
clear. Alright, so it's not this
way. It's this way, right? I'm
gonna try to get a first try.
Go, go Samurai.
I don't even know you can dump
with the Megazord. Pink Ranger
screwed that up. Not very good
this time. Victory is ours. What
an awesome show that this was.
Well, that was great. I love
that. I love that. I love this
one. The show was bad. Why do
you say that? Uh I messed up.
BitSlave gave ten community
subs earlier. Thank you BitSlave.
So this. Ooh that was like 30
minutes ago. Whoops. I am a
idiot but thank you for the ten
subs. Dropping ten subs tonight.
Today. Whatever time it is. Let's
do one more. Last one. The
original show was great. I grew
up on that show. They had like
inside that the like the the
Honker Burger, right? They did
that the restaurant they would
eat and hang out and the the
American actors only record us
the inside the restaurant scenes
and like reactions outside. Please
stop hurting me. It's time to
finish this. I dodged it.
Go go samurai. Write your symbol
tomorrow. Do it. Let it go.
That's like on a wedding fucking
photographer. What the fuck are
you doing? You got it when like
drunk Uncle Frank was forward?
Not when he was like juggling
upside down? God damn it. I was
gonna go straight up in the air
but like literally you would
have just like my my fucking
reverse upper body underwear
would have come up. The T-Pose.
The T-Pose. A little blood like
brush to my head. I don't know
how people stay upside down for
that one. Alright, last one and
then I'm gonna get some water
and we're gonna move on to a
relaxing one. Today, you will
fall to my sword with my sword.
They come up. Oh, that's such a
strong right input. Jump.
Excellent. That's kinda cool.
Watch it. Let's dodge it. Yeah,
there we go. Can I get in? No.
There comes a bottom slash,
right? Okay, we're good.
Searching for the project. What?
I can't hear him. Let's do this
please.
Connect is broken. The connect
is broken. It doesn't work.
This guy says yes. I got the
wrong calibration. Get out of
here. I gotta recalibrate the
head. Water. Retie this.
Splash, splash. Moisturize.
Dump like a cup of water down my
pants. See? That's bullshit. I'm
not even getting the points on
my ID. I got fired. I got
recast. Re, uh, casting call.
Interesting. You want some?
I was trying to use last
weekend. Go, go Samurai. Okay.
Write your symbol tomorrow. No,
no, no, no, no. I ain't doing
another one. Q-R-N-T-U-V. Hey,
we're back. He said the line.
He did. Sometimes he does. All
right, here we go. Let me get
the piece of water. I'll be back
in like two minutes, three
minutes. I'm gonna go pee.
Please do Q-R-S again. I can't.
That was a night that will, I
could never do that again, I
don't think. It was just, I
can't replicate that ever
again. I can try to emulate the
thing. Like, oh, it's not, no
way. I can't emulate that.
Sweat check. It's all right. I
mean, I'm a little, I'm a
little, I got some film on me
but it's fine. I'll be right
back. We're gonna do, we're
gonna chill out. We're gonna do
a slow paced one. See you in a
minute. I'm back. Okay. So,
we've done a little, we've done
some intensity. I think it's
time to do something where we
just hang out and get through
one of these more relaxed ones.
Family Feud? No. Far worse.
It's not Disney again. I
promise. I redid the hair.
Splash some water. I dumped a
whole soda down here. Right.
Probably should put this in.
This Bluetooth headset actually
goes pretty far. I can hear
everything you guys are saying.
Some of them are more nice than
other room comments. Speaking
of not being able to hear
things, why can I not hear it
now? Power off. What do you mean
power off? What do you mean
power off? Hold up your arm and
wave at the screen to begin.
Power on. Battery fully charged.
It's talking to me. I have my
own like Iron Man suit in here.
Okay, so Bluetooth connected.
Now, there we are. So, this is
called Fantastic Pets and Where
to Find Them. Hopefully not in
a movie theater if that series
is bad. Okay, welcome to the
game, Tender Dragoon 74. That
was an easy joke. Continue with
this gamer profile. Hey there.
Welcome to the game. I told you
we were going to relax on this
one. This is just for me to
catch my breath for like 12
minutes and then we'll play in
a horror game. This is you make
your own pet like a the one,
the thing in your hand. Visitor
detected. Hi there. I've been
expecting you. This is a
computer? Welcome to Dr.
Menagerie's house. I'm a natural
interface entity but you can
call me Natalie. This house
belongs to Dr. Menagerie. He's
an expert in fantastic pets.
Also, he's like splicing DNA. I
probably should have mentioned
that first. We got you got me
like rolls here. He's in here
right now but he left you a
message. Cats, dogs, animals,
dragons of the same house in
the same room. I imagine it must
stink in here. Hello. I don't
suppose you remember me but it
has been a long time. I'm your
uncle, Dr. Menagerie. I'm a
doctor of zoology. That's the
study of how animals and humans
interact and live with each other.
It's fascinating work and it
takes me all over the world in
search of rare and fantastic
species which is why I'm
sending you this message. There
are loads of rare and exotic
animals living in my house and
I'm even. I'm afraid you're a
little too close. Try moving
back. So, head over to the
house and choose your first pet.
Oh, by the way, you'll meet
Natalie there. She'll help you
along. Can't he tell me that?
Good luck. Just watch her on my
shoulder. Why can't, why can't
he just say, hey, back up? He
stops talking. Hey, hey, hey,
hey. Easy over there. You can
spend as long as you like with
each pet before choosing one to
take home with you. The door is
just open. We have all sorts of
pets here from cats, dogs,
ponies, and lizards to the rare
and secret fantastic pets. These
are animals the rest of the
world doesn't know about like
dragons or unicorns. By the way,
the reason you can't see me is
that I'm a computer. I'm the
house you're in, I suppose. It's
my job to help your uncle look
after all the pets that decide
to come home with him. This is
over there. Dragon like takes a
dump in the corner. There's like
puke in the corner, pee. Okay,
let's go. On to the main event,
the pet. Don't don't act like
that's not what would happen
here. What what a cruel little
grass you got. Look at your
carpets. That's why you got
hardwoods installed. The icons
you can see all over the street
are my movement system. With the
door open. They let me move
around the house with you.
There is probably like a shit
log hidden behind a lamp
somewhere in this house. So we
hold your hand out and a cursor
will appear on the screen. Now,
move that cursor over the
choice you'd like to have. Cat,
dog, unicorn, or lizard? Lizard
pull. To help you choose, your
uncle has left you a file on
each of the pets that you can
choose to adopt. Oh, look at
him. Hello Nomad. Nomad joined
us from the deserts of Africa
where she spent her days sun
bathing. Apparently Nomad
decided to leave the desert
because she was fed up with sand
getting into everything. Oh,
that's so cute. Okay, I don't
know how to choose. Okay, let's
go. I need to get a prop on the
house. This is Sadie. All right,
let's go to Sadie's store. Say
hello to one of our most
mischievous pets, Sadie. Sadie
loves to see what's going on
behind the scenes and to figure
out how things work. So she's
always getting into trouble.
That's on the leg. Okay, always
getting into trouble. Let's get
out of here and out. Ember.
This is Ember, one of our
newest additions. She loves all
types of extreme sports. Have
you ever seen a snowboarding
lizard? Just incredible. I like
the handstand. And the back
flip. I did three of those when
the stream started. I think
that might be the one. We've
got to get them all. Timmy.
Right next to the camera. Funny
star. It's the funny one.
Believe it or not, Timmy is one
of our shyest pets. He's a
little wary of new people, but
if you become friends, then
you'll never see a more loyal,
dedicated pet than Timmy.
Check out Drake. I don't think
it's going to be Timmy. I think
it's going to be Ember. Ah, yes.
This is Drake, one of our
miniature dragons. He may be
small, but he's still pretty
wild. Just watch him fend off a
fearsome squeaky toy. It's
strong. Ember. I chose him.
Handstand, back flips. It's
going to be Ember. Ember's love
of extreme sports has made her
completely fearless. Natalie
says that watching Ember's
stunning. Looks like you know
who's going to take home. It's
too easy. Wait. Yes. No. Hang
on. Nearly there. Hello. My
systems have transferred
perfectly. Ooh, nice place you've
got here. Very chic. Thank you.
Very chic. You like what I'm
doing with here? I won't go.
Yes, I'd love to go. Remember I
told you. Remember I told you.
I told you. What did I fucking
tell you? What did I tell you?
You're too close. Remember I
said about fucking CGI in movies
and how like the guy that boom
boom boom is not like an idiot
and all of a sudden he has these
spells? Check this out. Yes,
they definitely like it here.
Oh yes, I nearly forgot
something, which is ironic
considering I'm a computer.
This is Avatar, one of Dr.
Menagerie's assistants. Avatar
helps out by acting as my hands
because computers don't have
the hands of their own, see?
Try calling your pet over to
you. You can do it just like you
would with a real pet. You see
how Avatar is showing you how
to call your pet over? Whenever
you see perfect. Now you can
call your pet whenever you
like. This is in the room. There
are lots of other commands you
can give to your pet too. So
try plenty of things out. Now
let's try a toy, shall we?
Let's get a toy.
Let's see.
Aha, the bubble bubbler, I
think. The bubble bubbler. Play
with bubbles by popping and
swirling them around. Pop the
bubbles? Three, two, one. Hey!
Help me pop these. The more
bubbles the bubble bubbler
creates. I don't want to. The
faster you move around, the
bubble bubbler creates. You're
going to get me in trouble. I'm
going to fall. Can you get one?
You get one too. These are mine.
I'm destroying it. Did I get
food too? It makes the bubbler
release more bubbles. The bubble
bubbler finished. All of the
activities will finish by
themselves. So you don't need
to tidy them away yourself.
I didn't even get one. It's just
a baby. Hey. Hey there. What is
it? What's up? What's up, girl?
What do you want to do? Hey. No,
you can't go that way. Back over
here. Hey, come here. Come over
here. Come over here. Come over
here! Come over here. Come here.
Hey! Toys? Ball?
As you unlock more toys, they'll
appear here. To let me know what
you'd like to do, simply hold
your hand out and a cursor will
appear on the screen. To select
an icon simply hold your cursor
over it and I'll do the rest.
That's not going to work. Let's
try a game of ball fetch, shall
Now we move the glowing cursor over the icon and hold it nice and still.
Ball fetch.
Right.
Time to give your pets some exercise in the game of ball fetch.
Ball fetch.
Where am I?
How do I take it?
Reach towards the screen to take the ball from your pet.
The markers on the floor display how far your last throw and your longest throw went before
the ball bounced.
Nice.
Alright, I'm going to throw it further.
Here we go.
Where did I go?
I'm currently off.
I was on camera before in game and I'll be back.
How did I throw it further than that?
I'm trying to throw it over the fence.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
I'll try.
I'm afraid you're a little too close.
Try moving back.
Just throw the ball for your pet.
It looks like your pet is enjoying it.
Do it underhand?
How did you know I was not doing it underhand?
All fantastic pets love to play ball fetch.
That's cute.
Ball fetch finished.
Copy the gestures.
I'll try another one.
Ball fetch.
That was cute.
I'm going to try to throw it over the fence.
Is it underhand? How did you know I was not doing it underhand?
All fantastic pets love to play ball fetch.
That is cute.
Ball fetch finished. Copy the gestures avatars performing to get your pet to do different things.
So now you've got to know your pet a little. I guess it's time I told you about trainer's headquarters.
Trainer's headquarters is an organization that looks after the fantastic pets of the world through their trainers, like you.
If you're wondering why you've never heard of trainer's headquarters, it's because they're ultra mega top secret.
The organization isn't interested in fame and glory, only finding and caring for fantastic pets.
Fantastic pet trainers have ten different ranks, and at the moment you're rank one.
That's the lowest rank I'm afraid. But don't worry, I'm sure you won't be there for long.
You can increase your trainer rank by taking part in talent shows with your pet.
I'll explain more about talent shows later.
Clap your arms to make your pet fly.
Fly Ember, fly.
You gonna fly?
Excuse me.
Chaos emerald.
You seeing this?
Look at that.
That's really interesting.
What do you think about that?
Come here.
I'll throw my legs.
What's on the tee?
It's a fancy way of selecting all sorts of other options and things to do in the game.
Your smartphone is in the opposite corner of the display from the toy box, and you open it in exactly the same way.
Just hold your arms straight out to the top left and wait a second.
Get it.
As you know, your uncle, Dr. Minazu, is away on an expedition.
How is this a super game?
But did you know that you get to choose where he visits next?
Where should he go?
Las Vegas.
Right there, Las Vegas.
I'm just trying to see.
Russia?
Australia?
You guys choose.
You guys pick.
Smart click.
Then Dr. Minazuri across the world to that continent.
Whoa, you're getting a little too close.
Try taking a step back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, cancel.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to get on here.
I'm afraid you're a little too close.
Try moving back.
All right.
Where are we going?
Ready?
Where?
All right.
It looks like we're going to.
Oh, you want me to go to the, you want me to go to the frost area.
Frost?
This looks like it's frost to me.
Yeah, that's unanimous.
Thanks for clicking.
Forward.
Whoa.
You're getting a little too close.
Try taking a step back.
All right.
How do we go there?
What are we going to get?
Lost lizard of Antarctica.
Unlock with gems.
It's just another lizard though.
This is, I don't want, I don't want this.
Let it stay lost.
Yes, terrible.
Australian.
Horse.
Yeah.
Hello.
You'll be pleased to hear that my expedition is going well.
I've discovered a very strange and wondrous new species of fantastic animals.
None of which have ever been seen before.
Although, between you and me, I'm beginning to suspect that one of them is just a pony in a funny hat.
Thank you Bitslave for the 10 community subs.
I already said that.
I'm so stupid.
Try moving back.
But thank you though for it.
All right, so did I get that?
Okay, let's go.
The database awaits.
We're going to Australia.
Does that mean we're still going to be in my room?
Welcome to the pet database.
This is where you get to decide how your pet evolves and changes.
You can choose its size and color, whether it has wings or horns, and loads of other things.
Everything your pet uses up a few gems to start the pet database.
But once you're inside the database, you can make as many changes as you like.
Horns.
There are lots of different parts of your pet that you can change.
Red eyes.
Claws.
If you choose this, then all the changes you've made to your pet will be undone, and they won't look any different.
Choose this when you're happy with the changes you've made.
All right.
Let's do horns.
If you choose a pet with horns, it will be more confident and proud than one without.
Okay, I don't like one.
I don't even know what these look like.
Uh, no.
Those are just little leaves.
Those are devil horns.
No.
Actually, I don't hate those.
I don't hate those.
All right.
No, I don't hate them.
Wings.
Does your pet have a pair of wings?
Yes.
Wings make pets more carefree, and of course, they will be able to fly.
Those are like two can wings.
Those are bats.
I should have made Spyro the dragon.
Why did I not make Spyro?
All right, we're going to go with bat wings.
Yeah, that's cool.
Let's do the skin, the coat.
Fantastic pets can be found all over the world.
I can make Spyro.
They have a huge range of skin types, textures, and patterns.
What does Spyro look like?
He's purple.
Purple and orange, right?
Are his legs orange?
Purple and yellow.
Your tooth place.
Are his feet orange?
I don't think so.
All right.
Very cool.
Let's do color.
Is this purple?
All right, nice.
That's Spyro the dragon.
Well, it's got to be a little lighter.
There it is.
Okay, what else can we do?
This is pattern.
This is my favorite part.
You can choose the pet's colors and patterns,
and they will appear on whichever skin type you just picked.
It's just smooth, right?
Does it do anything?
That looks good.
Oh, yes.
Very stylish.
All right, color.
This is where we get it.
It's orange, right?
No, that's correct.
Eyes.
What does Spyro have for eyes?
Okay.
This is where you specify the pet's eyes.
Red.
Do you want them to be adorable or intense?
Awesome or just plain strange?
The yellow?
You're too close.
All right.
Oh, yes.
Very stylish.
Now what?
What is that?
A tail.
What's the emo?
Change the color of your pet's tail for a new look.
No, orange is too darn.
This is where you can change the color of your pet's feet.
That's fine.
Very cool.
Wildness.
Now you can choose whether your pet is cute and cuddly,
or wild and fierce.
Definitely wild.
No!
Wait, actually, that looks more like...
That does look more like...
No, that looks like...
That's more of Spyro.
Yeah, that's Spyro right there.
The cute one.
Build.
This is where you choose your pet's build.
Is it sleek or stocky?
How many can I do?
I think that's as big as I can make Spyro.
Very cool.
All right.
And now fantastic pet.
Earth?
You think I'm a cyborg?
Robot.
All right.
Okay.
Looking good.
I'm afraid you're a little too close.
I think it looks cute.
It's a cool little Spyro...
Ember the Spyro the Dragon.
Copy what you see Avatar doing,
and your pet will do something cool.
Run away?
That's cool.
That's really cool.
You can listen to the emails you've received again later
by using the smartphone.
My systems include a camera,
so I can take photographs of any special moments
and save them for later.
I need to get photos.
Or until you decide to delete them.
You can swap between your pets using the smartphone.
This is a display of every award you've earned during the game.
Pet it.
I will.
Why not check out the encyclopedia?
You can get to it from your smartphone,
and it's full of interesting facts about pets.
She's right here.
You're getting a little too...
Ah, now this is interesting.
All pets have certain things they want.
You know, things like food to eat,
toys to play with,
or needing to sleep.
This is what you'll see when a pet wants something.
Just select that one.
She just frosted her eyes.
Perfect.
Time to give your pet a wash.
To ensure your pet is squeaky clean,
we'll move through several steps in order.
I'll help with each step.
Shower spray.
This is what you'll see when a pet wants something.
Just select that thought.
Getting nice and clean.
Pet soap.
Next is a special pet soap.
Rub it vigorously to get lots of bubbles.
Not in the eyes, but...
Sponge time.
Now rub the sponge nice and fast to get the pet clean.
Time to rinse.
Time to use the shower to wash all the soap away.
Make sure you don't miss any parts of your pet.
Hair dryer.
Finally, blow dry your pet with the hair dryer.
Be sure to move it around so you get all the dirt in the hose.
Pet clean.
Copy the gestures Avatar is performing
to get your pet to do different things.
Don't forget that a second player can join in the game
and you can play with your pet together.
When two of you are playing, you can both have fun with the pet.
Plus, some of the play activities support two players,
so try them out.
Hi, this is Germa985 and you're watching Germa985
on the Disney Channel.
Try all sorts of different gestures
and see which one your pet responds to.
I lost my powers.
Okay, time for your first talent show I think.
What's a talent show?
Well, Trainers Headquarters doesn't just find
and look after their fantastic pets.
They run the talent shows too.
Oh, come on.
A chance for the best trainers and their pets
to show off their skills to the world.
You're gonna do great.
Only one thing, you're too close.
Mom, is that your...
Mom, is that your two-year-old?
...more important than others.
You can score more points at the big shows,
but I'm afraid the competition will be tougher.
If you and your pet do well in an event,
you might win a bronze rosette.
If you do really well,
you might get a silver rosette.
Wait, silver's better than bronze, right?
Yes, of course.
I knew that.
Finally, if you do extremely well in an event,
you might win a gold rosette.
They're the best you can get,
but you have to work hard.
I'm afraid you're a little too close.
Try moving back.
The points that you earn in talent shows
are added to your trainer rank,
so they're absolutely still worth entering,
even if you don't win.
Don't worry if you don't do so well in an event.
You can always practice some more,
so you can do better in an event.
I'm trying to get them.
Remember, talent shows are about having fun with your pet.
There's cameras everywhere!
There's cameras in my walls!
What about the bubble bubbler?
The bubble bubbler.
Play with bubbles by popping and swirling them around.
Three.
Two.
One.
The faster you move around,
the more bubbles the bubble bubbler creates.
It's good!
You're improving!
The faster you move around,
the more bubbles the bubble bubbler creates.
What a talent show!
For me!
Yeah, burst those bubbles!
Come on, get one!
Get one!
Strike a pose.
Pose struck.
Of gold?
I'm impressed.
Keep going.
Ball fetch.
Right.
I'm impressed.
Time to give your pet some exercise with a game of ball fetch.
No, but this one sucks.
Reach.
Try throwing the ball into the screen.
The markers on the floor display how far your last throw
and your longest throw went before the ball bounced.
Whoa, you're getting a little too close.
Try taking a step back.
Just kind of what happens in
just like fetch with a dog for long enough
and they're still so enthusiastic about it,
but you aren't having the 50th time.
Try, Link.
It looks like your pet is enjoying this.
You're like, ah, I'm kind of done.
Are you?
That's enough ball fetch for now.
I'm afraid.
Strike a pose.
Finish.
You're on the way up.
Keep going.
I'm so good at this game.
It's just ridiculous.
Pinata.
What do you risk it?
Sandy scaly ruffles.
You're all done.
Pinata.
Time to give your pet those tasty treats
by pounding the paper pinata.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Bring on.
Be careful you don't swing too hard
and pinata smash.
You're improving.
Bring on the neck.
Yes.
Good work.
Take the picture.
Strike a pose.
Finish.
What silver.
It's supposed to be a breast game.
Nice work.
Keep going.
Brush time.
I know.
Wait.
Whoa.
You're getting a little too close.
Try taking a step back.
All pets need to be brushed from time to time.
Move your brush along your pet in nice, smooth movements.
I'm afraid you're a little too close.
Try moving back.
Perfect brushing speed.
That's it.
You're brushing too quickly.
There you go.
One perfectly brushed pet.
A gem.
Strike a pose.
Finished.
What I always thought silver was much classier than gold.
Power pounce.
Next.
Not yet.
Help your pet run as fast as it can.
Then tell it when to jump for maximum score.
Three.
Two.
How do I do that?
One.
Start running.
Jump.
Wow.
You're fast.
Jump.
Crouch.
Holy shit.
That was the low score you get.
Second jump.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start running.
Keep going.
Crouch down.
Jump.
Yes.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start running.
That's it.
Keep going.
Crouch down.
Jump.
Power pounce.
Finished.
Part of my body that I can't talk about.
I went up and down too hard and it's like, you know what I'm saying?
It's like, that fucking hurt.
Are you going to be beyond sore tomorrow?
I was really sore this morning.
After yesterday.
Six hours of this?
You better believe it.
Because we toddler walking up the stairs.
It's good for me though.
It's good for me.
All right.
We are at the 30 minute mark for this one.
I think it's time to stick around for like another 20 minutes.
Dig in my floor?
What are you talking about?
Don't dig that up.
Go dig over here.
Dig.
Right there.
Okay.
Shutting down tutorial systems.
Enjoy the game.
Dig.
That's it.
Good.
Sit.
Time for some exercise.
Done.
Be careful you don't trip over anything.
That was fun.
Okay.
That's it.
Good.
Let's have a second player.
Please wave at the screen to begin.
Starting two player play.
Whoa.
You're getting a little too close.
What do I do now?
Be careful you don't trip over anything.
You're getting a little too close.
Try taking a step back.
Sit.
Good.
All right.
Time for some exercise.
What?
Exercise?
Organization options ready to use.
Set.
Jump.
Chase time.
Returning to single player control.
Starting co-op play.
Please wave at the screen to begin.
That was a fantastic cut.
Oh, boy.
You can't even see me.
Finally.
All right.
There's so many good ones that are still here.
I don't know.
There's so many that are so good.
What time is it?
It's been about four hours.
All right.
I feel like I want to give that one all day.
I've got too many of these.
All right.
This is going to be a good one.
The price is right.
That's not the horror one.
I know, but I think that's a full game.
I think that Rise of Nightmares is a full experience.
I think I want to give that one.
I don't know.
That didn't sound good.
Uh-oh.
I think it's all right.
Hey, the shuts us off.
It shuts us off.
We're not done.
Price is right.
Connect.
No.
Where's the connect?
Connect party.
You'll have to exit the game if you don't have a sensor.
What do you mean the connect party game?
Let's go.
What do you mean party?
What is that bullshit?
Is this just tacked on horseshit connect mode?
The price is right.
They picked me.
I can't believe it.
Hey, Bob.
Pool table.
The entire family can have our fabulous pool table.
That's like two grand.
It's finished in light English oak and comes with an accessory
package.
2200.
Let's start the bidding.
I thought that's what they did.
What?
That's dumb.
You only get one choice.
It's me.
2195.
It's 2195.
That's 2200 bucks.
Eggs, Bob.
2695.
Now let's play my...
Is that the Xbox?
I thought that was a construction work or something.
Okay.
Basis and glassware.
Shelves.
Bed.
No.
In between the two prices.
Alright, I'm going to say in between the two prices.
to enter a value which you believe is in between the two prices.
All right, I'm going to say in between the two prices, the shelves are probably like
three or four hundred. The bed is probably like six hundred, seven hundred. The shelves
are probably three hundred. I'm going to say five hundred bucks. The shelves are not more
than five hundred. Six hundred? Yeah, no, I'm going to say five fifty. Four seventy, five oh two.
What? A fucking queen size pillow top bed is three thousand dollars? Is it a bar of gold?
I have a king size bed in there right now. We can take up a lot of space. We might not be very big
people. That shit was not more than a thousand dollars. It was like eleven hundred bucks.
Two thousand four beds for fucking cars. I forgot. Continue. That shelf is like a fucking
bed of plastic. That's like two hundred bucks. Plastic shelf with like two glass vases on it.
I still got to go to the showcase?
Ninety five eighty five. I'm going to the showcase. I can't believe it. I'm constantly laughing.
Showcases up for bid. Got to nail this one. It's the closest to the actual retail price.
Without going over, wins their showcase. If your bid is within two hundred and fifty dollars of
the actual retail price of your showcase, you win both showcases. Can you make him dab? Let's see
the first showcase. Our showcase begins with your very own copy of Star Wars. Star Wars. This new
VCR DVD player will force you to work out once you own a new home gym. A Star Wars DVD player
and a home gym. Let's see. That's probably five grand. Four grand. Five grand. More than that
maybe. And a car. 2002 Jeep Grand Cherokee. That's probably seven. Eighteen thousand dollars.
Twenty thousand. Eighteen thousand. Eighteen five. Eighteen thousand five hundred dollars.
Twenty. Maybe twenty four thousand. Twenty four thousand. Plus five thousand to the gym. Twenty
four. Twenty nine. Plus the DVD player. Thirty thousand. I'm going to say thirty one. Thirty
thousand dollars. Thirty. Twenty nine eight six six. Twenty nine eight four four. This game's
dumb. It's either thirty or thirty three. I'm going to say thirty. Thirty four three eight.
Let's go to party mode. Your showcase begins with this fashionable new luggage.
For stylish luggage pieces which are as durable as they are beautiful. Go back to Power Rangers.
Wherever you go. Javiv by Boyd travel in luxury. And now it's time to pack those bags.
Luggage uh twenty two hundred bucks. Two thousand. Three thousand. To exciting Vancouver.
Vancouver. A Vancouver getaway. How long? A round trip coach from Los Angeles to Vancouver
British Columbia. How long? Six nights. Hotel. Three hundred bucks a night. And then Tokyo.
You're talking about three. Twelve. Twenty. Plus Tokyo. This is way cooler. Stop. What the fuck?
Okay you've both bid on your showcases. Let's see what they're worth. The actual retail price
of the first showcase is. A difference of. A difference of. That's right. Your opponent's bid
is closest. This mode is terrible. I won't play the regular mode. I don't care. I've got to use
a controller. I'm doing it. The Kinect mode sucks. No. Get out. All right. Single player.
Welcome to the prices right. We need your help. Just pretend that I'm doing Kinect.
We found a box of unmarked tapes dating back to 1972 that we need your help identifying.
We've sent along the lovely Jessica to help you in your task. Good luck.
Yeah. Why are we playing old tapes from the 70s? Why wouldn't you just make a prices right game?
What is with all this nonsense? 1983. You're too close. Oh fuck. Sorry.
All right. Let's go. You look like that guy. You look like that second guy.
Okay. It's a trampoline. Trampoline. With a unique ground design for outdoor fun and recreation.
Ideal for physical fitness with features such as uniform and larger jumping area from round
trampoline. Let's start the bidding. What's your bid? Yeah. This is much better. All right. I'm
going to say five. I'm going to say. Please give me your bid. 699. I think it's. I'm going to say
699. They're like 700. No. 750. 799. 800. 799. First try by the way. The Plinko machine. Yeah.
This is a good one. This is probably the best one. All right. Let's go. First you need to earn
your Plinko chips. You start out with one free chip, but you can win up to four more Plinkos.
Four different items on display. Each item has a two number price, but only one of those numbers
is correct. Let's take a look at the first item. It's a queen size bed sack. It provides luxury.
Pillow case. That's inaccurate. Box springs and protection for youth from bed sack.
No. Wait a minute. Or the left number, the correct number in the price.
Wait a minute. Okay. So it's the left number. 39. It's probably 30. It's probably like 29.
It's the nine. You can earn another chip with this item. Be everything you can be with Mary Kay
Cosmetics. Skin care and glamour cosmetics presented in your home. Makeup is expensive.
Is the right or the left number. No product has. It's either 79 or it's 84.99. The left one is
correct. 71 fucking dollars. What is the right or the left number, the correct number in the price.
The five. A vacuum cleaner is like a hundred bucks. Here's another Plinko chip. This is your
last chance to earn a Plinko chip. 71? Stainless steel kitchenware. The choice of many fine
restaurants. Prepare, cook, and serve food in your home. Is the right or the left number,
the correct number in the price. Those are three. It's definitely the right number because
that's more expensive for sure. Here's another Plinko chip. I mean, it's cheaper. Those things,
dog shit they shittily made. The bad quality. Drop your chips. I'm just kidding. If that company
still exists 30 years later, I was making a joke. All right. I usually go all the way to the left.
Again, only the left. Only. This is your last chip. No zero. Congratulations. 1500 bucks. No zero.
You're not going for, if you drop it in the middle, you're going to get a zero.
Don't you guys know how to play these? If you go in the middle, this shit balls in the zeros
and you don't have anything. If your spin or your combination of two spins is higher,
that's enough money to go get yourself a shelf. Be careful though. If you go over one dollar,
you'll lose. If your total is exactly one dollar, you'll win one thousand dollars
and you'll spin again. You got 90. I lose. It's your turn to spin.
One dollar, one dollar, one 30 cents. Come on. All right. I give you 70. You have to spin the
wheel again. It's your turn to spin. 70, 60, 60.
Why would I look that happy? I wouldn't be that happy. I'd be very upset about that.
Well, at least you won. I mean, actually walking out of there with free grand.
You don't have access to the archives. You can access them from the single player menu.
New show unlocked. This is fucking stupid. Why would you count? Why can't we just play
defensive right in the gear that it currently is? Is it really that big of a deal?
We have to go different gears every game?
There we go. 2005, the future.
No, I got to get this. I'm going to nail this. You guys in my audience, you got to help me.
You have to help me.
Well, here it comes. A beautiful new area rug. I thought that was a board game.
Area rug.
Not expensive at all. Like 50 bucks? 100, 125.
What? 110? What year is it? $1,000 for an area rug.
No way. No way. 2005. Nice area rug. 400. I'm going to say 400.
$4,400. $1,000. You can get a rug like that for 40 bucks.
Ooh, a stove. $750.
And self-cleaning convection oven with three heavy duty oven racks.
A stainless steel stove is not five grand. $5,000. No, it's like, it's like 800.
They're not this expensive. No, it's cheaper, man. It's like, it's...
$5,000. I think it was fucking $1,300. $1,000.
All right, now these back in the 15 years ago or so, these were like $2,000.
$3,000 at least. It's probably like, it's probably like, it's probably like $7,000. $6,000.
Okay, please give me your bid. How much do you think it's worth? Your bid, please.
Was the first thing I said $2,000? I said like $2,000, $3,000 originally. It's $21,000.
It's going to be like, it's going to be like $21,500. Got it. Oh, right, it went over.
Let me just let you play until you get to go on stage. I've been here for five days.
Big selection of phone... Vtech. Three multi-phone systems from one phone app.
Set up digital mailboxes and staff telemarketing calls with a telezapper.
$60, $65. Vtech technology. You can clearly hear.
Let's start the bid. $69, like 70 bucks. All right, what's your bid?
$80. Okay, please give me your bid. How much do you think it's worth?
For a cordless landline in 2005? Five fucking hundred bucks?
Can you please not do that? It's got to get lucky.
$1,000 for a cordless landline. That was not that $1,000 fucking dollars. That can't be accurate.
More than what? Why would you have like 15 cordless phones in your house?
Is there one in your shower? 20 cordless phones in every fucking room?
A whole scuba set? An entire scuba diving set? I have no idea. I'm going to say $1,800.
I have absolutely no clue. $1,800. $1,700. Sorry, buddy. You were close, but you went over.
Good game time. That's when Bob Barker comes over and he goes,
Oh, hey, Jeremy. It seems like you've been here for a few days. Five days to be exact.
You keep showing up and getting in line. And I'm like, yeah, Bob. I really love the show.
The next prize's first digit is one of the two from the first item.
Uh, silver. Silver. 46 pieces.
I got a shirt that says like, Bob is so cool and sexy, right? Oh, I love Bob.
Get that guy out of here. I don't want to see him in line ever again.
You'll spin the wheel. If you're spin or your fucking weirdo is higher than the current leader,
you'll win the chance to play in the showcase. Be careful though. If you go over $1,
you'll get a shirt that said, I love Bob. And weirdly enough, he had these huge yellow
pit stains underneath his underarms. I don't think he's ever taken that shirt off.
Beat his score to win. It's your turn to spin. 65. Result is lower than the leader.
You have to spin the wheel again. It's your turn to spin.
I got it. I'm looking for low. Low, low, low, low, low. Come on. There it is. I'm in the showcase.
20. Oh, god damn. Yeah, Bob. I can't wait.
The player who bids the closest to the actual retail price without going over
wins their showcase. If your bid is within $250 of the actual retail price of your showcase,
you win both showcases. Let's see the first showcase.
Your showcase begins with a wonderful collection of cookbooks. Cookbooks can be pretty expensive.
Books to help you cook and entertain like a pro. Classic cuisines from around the world
with guides to find food and find wine. Back in 2005, you're talking about probably
two, 300 bucks for something like this. And you can serve it in this lovely new dining room.
Dining room. What kind of wood?
Furniture Saddle Creek collection. This nine-piece dining room group with ladderback chairs and
buffets. And serve your meal on this elegant dinnerware. This 24 karat gold accent dining
collection from Royal Prestige features nocturnal china coordinating lead crystal and flatware for
the ultimate dining experience from Royal Prestige. You know, like this thing I understand about
humans. I have a human complaint, okay? You could go get a 60-piece set of silverware
for probably $25 at Walmart. Why in a million years, even if you had a million dollars,
would you buy like a thousand dollar silverware that you're going to use? It's like, it's like
25 bucks. And nobody cares about that shit. Do you think anybody looks at your silverware
on your house? No. In fact, well, maybe they do, but they're probably, what they're looking for
is they're looking for like the dishwasher stains to rub off on their shirt. They don't care about
if it's gold or not. You know, like those like white spots and they're like, oh, shh. Can they
see me do this? Like, oh, okay. Nobody gives a shit about your gold silverware. Give me that one,
I don't want that one. I'd buy a silverware because if they had a stone and I would say
I wouldn't even care. All right. This exotic styling and intricate embossed detail,
this Paul Meadow Road 30, $3,500 from Ashley can transform the atmosphere of any room
from the Ashley companies. Maybe more, like five grand maybe. And it's carpet too.
Bernier Willam Mills is the ultimate wool carpet manufactured from 100% New Zealand wool fiber.
Enjoy performance, comfort, and elegance with 60 square yards. Probably seven grand, eight grand.
You can also win these authentic German beer steins. All right. That's cool. It's a collection of
limited edition German beer steins. I gotta try to get one of these so I can. With these authentic
German made steins featuring fancy comical or decorative butylins. And take a look at
this fantastic trip to Germany. Going to Germany. A round trip coach from Los Angeles to Munich,
Germany for a six night stay at a luxury hotel. Eat, drink, and be merry in Bavaria's capital city.
All right. I'm going to say. These can be yours if the price is right.
That's probably 10, 12 grand, 10 grand. The steins are probably $1,200, $2,000. The steins
are probably $2,000. The 15, 16. I'm going to say. I'm going to say $16,000. $16,000. $16,492.
Okay. You've both bid on your showcases. Let's see what they're worth. The actual retail price
of the second showcase is a difference of actual retail price of the first showcase is
is over. The actual retail price. I'm going to Germany. Let's go.
Very good. We'll do one more. We'll do one more and then we're going to play. We'll probably be
able to play another one or two. I think I've got a good one. Now don't. Please don't. Please
don't play this one. I love the price is right. It's a little like ice cream.
I'm going to do a heck of a lot. Probably like another potentially like 18 to 20 hours.
So I have to do this again. The contestant with the bid closest to the actual retail price of the
item without going over wins the item and gets to come up on stage to play up. And I have some
digitally downloading the item up for bid. A handsome entertainment cabinet. I think I've
overshot that as well. Furniture designs by Picasso. American made dark oak entertainment center
features retractable doors, curio sides and tee tops from furniture designed by Picasso.
There's about 17 games left. 18 games. Each one of those games will probably take about
30 to you know between 40 minutes and like two hours is what we've done on each one of these.
I didn't. I don't know what this was. So we're going to do one dollar.
Sorry Bob. I wasn't listening to anything you said but I still win.
You just don't want to go over. Cliffhangers. $16,000. What? Are you serious? Get fucking pumped.
There's a mountain climber will take one step on the mountain. If he goes too far up the mountain,
he'll fall off and you'll lose. But if he's still on the path after you bid on the items, you'll win.
Here's the first item you'll be bidding on. The 80s edition of Soap Opera Challenge.
It's your drama by the day. Questions about your favorite soap. So you think is the price of this
item. Enter your bid for this item. It's a soap opera board card game. 19.
Let me say 19 bucks. I have no way that's more than 25 dollars.
Do you have the item? No. Let's see how many steps he'll take.
19. We have Spencer's. Everything children's clothing is meant to be durable easy care
Spencer's. American made will stand the test of time. What do you think is the price of this item?
I just want to clarify. I don't even know what this is. That looks like a trash bag, diapers,
and like a moist towelette case. I don't know what this is. This is clothes.
40? Is it kids clothing? Like is that like a little onesie? Probably 20. 25.
No. Let's see how many steps he'll take.
It's close. All right. Come on. A dog brushing kit.
You think is the price of this item. Enter your bid for this item. 60. 80.
60. It's either like it's between 40 and 60. Do you have the item? No. Let's see how many steps
he'll take.
I'm sorry you don't win anything. Shit. Oh well. Sorry. Sorry. At least I can do the showcase.
What did you get? 75. It's always 75. This game is rigged. The guy has
whoever it is. They have 75 to 90 every time. Price is right. I'll take a dollar.
Anything. And it really doesn't matter what it is. Anything. No. That's.
One more. One more. Last one. Last one. That's it. This is it. Last one. That's it.
I won't do it again. I won't do it one more time. Look over here. Somebody just says
fucking loser. Fucking loser. What the fuck. Hey. Come on. Wearing this together. 1977.
This is going to be probably a bunch of like pink colored carpets. Pink and green wallpapers.
Let's go.
Tea table. Brilliant. Some genuine copper and brass captured in the original collage table.
Coffee table. Eliminated edition designer collection handcrafted by American Furniture Group.
Let's start the bidding. What's your bid? I would. I would say more than that. I'd say a
thousand. This is back in the 70s. Oh wait. This is the 70s. So that means that it's.
Yeah. It's probably like three to. It's probably three eighty. Three. Three eighty. Might be four
hundred. Three ninety. Yeah. Seventies. Three hundred bucks is like thirty thousand dollars
right now. I mean that would be like the seventeen hundred. But you know what I'm saying.
A chest of drawers. You can use it as a bar in the deck. It's a dresser drawer.
All right. How much is like a big dresser drawer? Fire finish. In the 70s. Let's start the bidding.
Five hundred. Six hundred. What's your bid? Those things were so expensive. It might be more.
Please give me your bid. How much do you think it's worth?
Is there a reason why my character is traveling through time? All right. Your bid please.
For retail price is. All right. Let's move on to the next round. I was gonna do three hundred.
Whatever. It's all right. The item up. It's a Chinese chest.
What furniture? Made of mahogany. Mahogany chest. A glass top and Chinese lock
can be used as a cocktail table or as a hope chest. Let's start the bidding. What's your bid?
Four hundred. I'm gonna stick to my guns here. Four hundred. Yeah. Four hundred. It might be
like three fifty. Four hundred. Stick it with it. All right. Your bid please. That's a good zone
to be in. Actual retail price is. I got the whole. I got all the late twos and three hundreds. Let's
move on to the next. No I don't. Because if you go over you lose. I should have went a dollar
over for them. I should go eat some more oatmeal. Country range, country charm,
automatic electric range. What does it range? Full size cast iron reproduction cooks
steaks like it used to. It carries the early American theme into your kitchen
from the house of Webster. Is it a stove? Let's start the bidding. All right. What's your bid?
One thousand dollars. Okay. Please give me your bid. How much do you think it's worth?
All right. Your bid please. Retail price is. Let's move on to the next round. Yeah. What's
with the prices here? They're all the. They're all the same price. Can I get something here that's
not a piece of furniture that's four hundred and fifty dollars? Five hundred dollars? Did they have
any other products in the 70s besides grandfather clocks, chests, and bureaus? And has fine brass
moving? No, they kind of didn't. Your workmanship is in this grandfather clock by biking.
Holy shit. That's true. Let's start the bidding. Stuff made out of wood is the only thing.
This is probably 1100 bucks. These things were ridiculous. Okay. Please give me your bid.
It's going to be five. I'm assuming five hundred. Five fifty. Five. Four ninety. Your
retail price is. Got it. What? No. Oh no. No. Oh my god. No.
I don't know why I'm doing this thing tonight where I'm doing like a pretend.
I'm like pretending to do something to like explain something.
I don't know why I'm doing that. I've done it like five times. Let's start the bidding.
What's your bid? He's being a toot. Please give me your bid. Again.
Don't know what the product was. And how much do you think it's worth? In one sentence,
what was it? What was it? What was it? It was an Xbox. Retail price is.
That was the last round. Oh, I actually just got like enraged timer. I lose.
How much is the last range? 600. You need to get in the bed a decade.
Okay. It's an electric oven. Six hundred forty. I think it's more than that. Six
forty. Six thirty. Six fifty. How much do you think it's worth?
Shit. All right. Your bid, please. I win too. I won.
It's a bumper pool table. All right. This is the seventies. It's a pool table.
It's made out of mahogany. It's probably eight twenty seven. Let's start the bidding.
What's your bid? Oh, and also something you need to realize back in the seventies,
every single product was four hundred and fifty dollars. Every single one was five hundred bucks.
You're wrong. Things like that. It's probably two eighty. Fifty, four hundred.
I had that first time. It's just a thing. Xbox controller. It has four directionals,
but this button is the same button no matter what. It's every button.
No matter if it's left, up, right, down, when you press one of these, every single one is pressed.
It's just a circle in there. All right. So this is a new car. What kind of car?
It has brakes. That's good. Turbo hydromatic transmission, bumper strip, white stripe tires,
sport mirror, rally wheels, vinyl roof, interior decor package, door edge guards,
interior decor package, intermittent windshield light system, and a tilt steering wheel. Five
grand. Four grand. You can win your playing, Professor Price. To successfully answer three
questions, he will show your correct answers on his right hand and your incorrect answers
in his left hand. If you get three incorrect answers, good luck. And these are the last two
numbers and the value of the prize. Here's your first question. How many ounces are in a half pint?
Six. Eight ounces for glass. Eight ounces is a cup. I'm American. I only know as the leaders
jugs and gallons and I only know as gallons and a gallon is I just know what it looks like. It's
just like a big a gallon is a pint, a half pint. A pint is 20, 24 ounces. So a half pint would be
16. No, when you get like when you get a pint, when you get a pint at the bar, that's that's
20. Is it 21 or 20 ounces? 24. A pint is 16. That's what I'm saying. So it's eight. 1.9 GPA
was actually 2.7. Nice try though. What do you mean? No, it's not. The value. That's your second
correct answer. One more and you win. Let's update the score. Here's your next question.
In baseball, how many runs is a Grand Slam home run?
Showdown. You'll spin the wheel. If your spin or your combination of two spins is higher than
the current leader, you'll wonder if you're going to have 75 to 90. Probably 90. If you go,
if your total, if this is the current leader, beat his score to win. Wow. I can't believe I
have to go higher than 75 every single time. Oh great. One day I'll be able to go over that number.
80 please. 15. Your result is lower than, you have to spin the wheel. It's your turn to spin.
Stop on 70. 70. Yes. You win. Showcase. This is this is the big one. This is the big one.
Hoomer yells at a video game. There are two showcases up for bid. I mean I've yelled a few
times. The closest to the actual retail price. You are correct. If your bid is with, let's see
the first showcase. First showcase coming up. Your showcase begins with a game set.
If you want to play the game, do it in style. This is two chairs. This is a dinner table. The table
is a part with solids with an inlaid game surface. The chairs in a screen finish,
velvet upholstery, and brass hardware. And in the next shop we find this. A platform bed. Made by
hand. It's just the thing for a small bedroom and can be taken apart for you. The bed is made by
hand. Accommodates a queen-size mattress. Somebody stuffed it. And there's a range.
And the only other thing that existed in the 70s is the stove. I would really hate to play
the Sims back in the 70s. Your house would just be stoves, beds, and wooden chairs.
That's what it is now.
All right. Do you want to? No, there's other stuff in the Sims.
I don't want this one. You do it. 1446. Wow. That's going to really be great.
Your showcase begins with a new dining room. Table made out of wood. Probably $700 bucks.
A wood buffet server for side chairs and two armchairs made of veneers and solids.
And for a lovelier table, there's stoneware. Gourmet brown rich stoneware by Falscraft.
Handcrafted charm. The ideal in formal settings. Dishwasher safe. Chipper system.
Hey, what was your showcase? Oh, you know, a table just like yours. I don't rug.
I wait. I wonder if I'll get a stove too. Oh, I hope so.
No, mine's way better than yours. Mine is so much cooler than yours.
Have fun with your wooden stove.
All right. I'm thinking that's probably at least $1,500 to $2,000 plus $3,000 or $4,000.
How much do you think your showcase is worth? The table is probably $800.
The RVs with the motorhome thing, the trailer thing is probably $2,000. $1,500.
I'm thinking $20,000. And then the carpet is probably $500. I'm thinking $2,800.
$3,000. $3,000. $3,000. $3,300. $3,000. $3,200. $3,300. $3,200. $3,300. $3,200. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,100. $3,-F explaining.
$3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. $3,500. $3,300. $3,300. $3,300. That's it.
Okay. You've both bid on your showcases. Let's see what they're worth.
The actual retail price of the second showcase is.
Oh boy!
For a difference of. The actual retail price of the first showcase is. Wait. For a difference of. Did I lose?
Your opponent's been his closest. You don't win anything. I'm gonna fall. I don't know why I did this.
I have nothing to support me right now. I'm gonna fall down. I'm gonna fall.
I'm wearing socks. You don't do this in socks. And you don't do this in socks?
Okay, I gotta go for it. I have to fall. I gotta go for it. One, two, three.
I couldn't stand up. There's no way. It's impossible.
You did your best. I did do my best. It's time to do something else.
So. I've probably got. Just about five hours.
Let's go for. This is a fan favorite. If I'm gonna do like one, maybe two more.
This is the fan favorite one we gotta do right now.
It is not Family Feud. Kung Fu High Impact. Remember this?
Star Wars? Yeah, I did Star Wars for like an hour and a half earlier.
Here we go. There's so many more over here.
But I don't want to just blow through because there's a lot of good stuff over here.
There's a lot of good stuff in here. A lot of good stuff that we've played already.
It's time to kick some ass.
They have this shit for Kinect. And it's probably way better than the one that I played.
Get a bat over here. I got one.
Save data must be created. Save it.
The storage device memory unit will be used. That's fine.
So I'm gonna get off camera here because I'm just in the game.
So why would I? There's no reason for me to be on camera.
Here we go. That, okay. That's not what I wanted to do.
Uh, close.
Difficulty normal is fine. Here we go.
Tell me the story.
Things of that magnitude do not end easily.
The stories unfinished tend to carry on when you least expect it.
So it begins.
Ah, what a nice place.
How did they get here?
I didn't think I was supposed to be leaning.
What was there?
I don't know, Jeremy. Who is there?
You gonna do anything else?
Stretch before playing to prevent aching muscles.
Well, why didn't you tell me that like six hours ago?
Oh, Mike, that's where my whole body hurts right now.
Round one. Is that me?
Welcome to Kung Fu High Impact.
Are you ready to kick some serious ass?
Let's go through a few tricks.
That's the clothes I was wearing yesterday.
Enemies are to your left and right.
Fight in your own style. They sure are.
All moves deal damage as long as they're fast enough.
Like this guy over here.
Hey, how are ya?
Sorry about that.
Why am I so tiny?
I really should be taller.
Is it not correct?
It's not correct. The Kinect is in a wrong spot.
Hey, guys. Check this out.
I gotta umbre calibrating this.
I need to be like fucking three feet taller.
See, the Kinect doesn't even have my feet. Look it.
Look it. See?
Look. It's cutting me off.
I don't even have shins.
Look.
Got him.
You got it.
Dodge, jump, punch, double punch.
Get out of here.
Where is he?
No!
Round four.
I'm gonna go this way.
That's so awesome.
I have to get to the options.
So you have to dodge.
Block. Nice.
So I have to ju- I can't dodge red.
Did I get it?
I'm gonna cartwheel into him, motherfucker.
I swear to God.
That's what I do, is this.
Here we go.
Come here.
I saw more. I'm a big fan of the one, two, three.
Alright. I need to take-
I gotta get the Kinect to fix itself.
Gamer picture? Where?
What? What?
What?
Let's look at my headband.
Looks ordinary.
But believe me, I've seen the strange powers these comics have.
Yeah, I guess you could say working for a wizard has its own twists and turns.
What the fuck is the sound of this?
Here we go.
It's time to be a fighter.
Take control of the battlefield and use power punch.
The faster you move from side to side, the more distance you cover in the game.
Kicks and punches also move you forward.
Use somersaults to reach higher platforms or escape danger.
You can even surprise your enemies from behind.
How do I do that?
All at once. Jump, throw your hands up, and bend.
I need new legs.
Why did my parents say that to me?
What happened?
See.
Oh, I gotta go this way.
Power ups?
Where's there- is there-
Why did it not work?
I just stomped him.
Alright, my headphones came off.
Stop boring out.
Use power punch to slam the doors shut.
I gotta block.
I gotta remember to block.
Power punch, shut the doors.
I just taunted when I wasn't supposed to.
You can't taunt.
I'm almost dead.
Check this move out.
These guys just keep boring out.
Use power punch to slam doors shut.
I'm trying to close the door.
Alright, I got it.
Door closed.
They've gotten out of that one.
Which way are they coming?
Is it the guy in the frame?
Oh, my stomach.
Come on over here.
Why don't you-
Hey!
Close the door.
Do a backflip.
I did it.
Jesus.
Ow.
Oh, I gotta close that.
Power punch.
Close.
This.
Fucking.
Door.
See ya.
The Irish stanchion technique.
Close it.
You.
No.
Close it.
Up.
Other way.
Backwards.
Back.
Forward.
Get up there.
Oh, I just caught real-
God damn it.
Get.
Get over there.
Up.
Go.
Go forward.
Get.
Oh, my God.
Don't do it.
I'm fine.
Go drink some water.
What?
It worked.
Stay down.
Whoa.
It was like a Halloween party gone seriously wrong.
Thanks, guys, but I have to skip the party and get back to work.
Same freaks.
Hey, I worked there.
Cut it out.
Bonus items.
These mystic stones contain health or special powers.
Smash them to get to the goodies inside.
Ah.
Great.
Excuse you.
Goodies?
Where are they?
In here?
I'm the best still.
Double up cut.
I gotta utilize the up cut more often.
Double front head.
Adopted feet.
Nice.
Back to sneak into the alley.
What happens if I make myself, like, just tiny?
And they, like, not touch me?
This tank is empty.
I don't have any most...
I'm out of gas.
I don't have to...
Oh.
Kick him.
I can't hear anybody.
I need a...
I need health.
Where's their health?
Did I get it?
Who the fuck is that?
Wait.
Let's talk about this.
You don't know.
On call four.
What?
What are you doing?
What the fuck?
Bonus items.
These mystic stones contain health or special powers.
Smash them to get to the goodies inside.
Thanks for coming to the stream.
I'll see you guys when we're playing Ancestors.
Nice.
Get off me.
I'm trying to talk.
I'm trying to do my outro.
Oh no.
It's a child temper tantrum.
It's working.
Energy.
Rekindle.
You guys have seen...
You guys have seen Kingpin.
When Big Earth McCracken is bowling his ass off.
His, like, wig is just all over the place.
I gotta get this boss.
I'm really fighting.
Okay.
Time for a weapon.
Not helping.
It's too heavy.
Get that obelisk.
They can't hit what they can't see.
You know that guy you see in the gym sometimes
that's there for three and a half hours?
And he's, like, literally waters coming down from his body?
At two and a half hours under that guy.
I am stronger than the fucking huge guy in the gym
that does cardio for three and a half hours.
I'm stronger than that guy.
Hold on.
Where's my mushroom?
There's one.
What?
I tried.
I tried to make the mushroom sound.
It just ate Toad.
Get out of here.
Hey.
Why is that somehow worse?
I heard a crack.
Aim the camera down or push it back so you can get your legs in.
The Kinect has, like, a mind of its own.
I'm doing better.
Do you have to be strong to play this?
Yeah.
Strong enough.
That's a good technique.
The fucking, like, octopus hands.
Or, like, the directing symphony, whichever one you want to call it.
Put me thrash.
What?
Oh.
Get out of here.
I just kicked his ass.
Pee-pee-poo-poo.
Chapter four.
Helmet blunder.
Who are these guys?
They sure don't look like your ordinary comic book fans.
Okay, let's figure this out.
Anyway, warn me about something before she left.
Here's a list of tasks for you to do.
I feel like I shouldn't even be in the scene.
Especially the last one.
See, I'm pretty sure I did everything.
Save the world.
Check.
Clean up.
Destroy Kuang's helmet.
Destroy Kuang's helmet!
Oh, crap.
It's still in the basement.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
Those guys might have nothing to do with the helmet.
Doesn't look like much.
Let's get the job done.
I'll take that.
What?
Who the heck are you?
Kron?
I'm assuming this is a boss fight.
All right, I can take...
I can get...
I can beat this boss.
I have faith.
Backing off?
Don't matter.
Stay down.
I'm not gonna take a fucking hit.
Set the back one!
That's the only one you get!
Back breaker.
Sidekick.
Bingo.
Full health.
We're good.
Fuck out of here.
Oh, I just got combo'd.
Not bad.
I like the bouncing ball technique.
It's pretty good.
Checkpoint.
New pound shaker.
Pound shaker may not do much damage, but it throws your enemies off.
It can also damage particularly sturdy enemies.
All right.
Jump up and slam your hand to the ground as you land.
Even that move don't work.
Shit.
It's shredder.
Ow.
Idiot.
Stupid idiot.
Mom's gonna kill you when she finds out you took my car.
I destroy him.
I bet you think Rob Schneider is funny.
Yeah, I do.
That's a pretty good bet.
I can do this one.
Chapter five.
Eye of the Dragon.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
Oh, man.
You scared the crap out of me.
I have to get rid of the helmet before anything else happens.
I'm going to become the Lich King.
Not a promotion in that one.
Better done better than that.
I feel like I've been in that position like three or four times today.
My body is emanating heat.
We're going to have to go with a new strategy.
Probably lost five pounds today.
No.
I need a new strat.
Oh, right there.
They're not going to be able to hit me because I'm disappearing.
Much easier.
What do you got?
Well, I should have been doing this from the beginning.
It's permanent Liu Kang.
I unlocked the secret.
Woo.
I remember this part.
Did I do the same joke last time?
I think I may have.
This is the best defense if you have like an older brother.
This is the little brother defense against the older brother.
I used to do it all the time.
You just go like this.
And they're going to be able to get you.
I almost just ripped my pants.
Did they rip?
Can you imagine if I went like this and it split right in the middle on camera?
That would be really bad.
Like just just like boom.
Oh my God.
That would be.
You know, I would accept it.
I would accept defeat at that point.
Not wearing underwear yet.
Why?
What are you talking about?
What?
My pants are going to rip in the middle and then like my all my shit is going to come out.
Dude, I'll give it to people that get sick.
I mean, obviously I've been doing this for like six hours or so.
But imagine starting this shit.
This game is just you're constantly moving around.
Forget about like Zumba class.
Just go get this.
Go download it.
Still on the Xbox Store.
Go get it.
You want to work out?
Go sit, sit chair.
Put your legs up.
Rip your pants in half.
I'm up for this one.
There's hair in my mouth still from like an hour and a half ago.
Is the chair fighting?
Come on, get him chair.
You can do it.
It's like Dr. Strain.
Back it up.
Ah, you tried.
You tried.
Chair is doing better than me.
Shred the chair.
No, I'm not going to shred this game.
I'm going to have to go get some water.
And then we're going to we're going to have to just kind of chill.
This is where I tap out at six hours.
I've punched the air probably six to seven thousand times.
This is so fun though.
This is supposed to be a 12 hour stream.
No way.
If I don't get like in the shower in the next like 40 minutes, you will see a guy pass out on stream.
Shred the chair.
Why would I shred my chair?
I love my chair.
It's a great chair.
So here's the here's the plan.
These these games are really, really fun.
And I spent more time in some of them than I thought, which I knew was probably the case.
There are a couple of really, really great ones still.
There's like 10 that are still around.
So we're going to do another.
We're just going to do more Connect.
We're just going to not now.
Not this week.
We're going to put it in the box till next week because Ancestors comes out on Tuesday.
And that's what I want to do next.
That evolution ape game.
It seems really, really just ridiculous.
I'm going to play that for probably a day or so.
We're going to start the next Connect stream with Rise of Nightmares because that is absolutely going to be like a two to three hour experience.
At least it's a full game.
So we'll probably actually do that this coming weekend because let me think about this.
So Tuesday, I'm going to Ancestors.
And then maybe we could do Thursday or Friday.
Maybe because Saturday we're doing upset.
We're finishing Terraria on Saturday.
Star and I were going to do the base game.
We're going to complete it.
So I don't maybe like Sunday.
We'll do like a horror thing on Sunday because this two horror games for the Connect that I'm going to do.
Haunt and then Rise of Nightmares.
They both apparently really interesting.
So but I got some water.
I got a clock out here.
We'll come back.
I'll hang up for a little bit.
We'll do the bits.
We'll talk.
We'll probably be done in about six, six and a half hours or so.
So I will see you guys.
Have you taken off?
I'll see you guys on Tuesday for Ancestors.
That's the day it launches on PC.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to get some water.
All right.
So again, if you're sticking around, I will see you on Tuesday.
Today's Sunday.
So I won't be streaming tomorrow.
I'll see you on Tuesday.
The stream was shorter than I expected.
I drank a battery for no reason.
Why would you ever have a battery for lunch?
I'll do that.
That's a bad idea.
That's that I would advise against ever doing something like that.
So let's do the bits.
Last stream before school starts again for a lot of guys.
Well, good luck.
You still get your weekends and just work hard and make sure you get your schoolwork done.
Did the Ancestors team say how far along the game is for the demo?
Wait, it's not coming out.
You don't stream on weekends.
What's today?
And what was yesterday?
Was yesterday Thursday?
What's what's today?
Saturday and Sunday.
Huh?
What's happening here?
What is this backpack thing?
I see this backpack every day.
So wait, hold on.
Can somebody clarify this with me?
Is Ancestors not releasing on Tuesday for PC?
The one with the apes.
It's at 2020.
But that's a console, though, because it comes out a few months after the PC release.
And I think it's on the Epic Games Store.
I don't think it's a Steam thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, release release date August 27th, 2019.
It's a demo.
The Steam page says 2020.
Well, I think it's because Epic Games Store.
All right.
So I'm going to look into that because hopefully it's not just a demo on the 27th.
Feeling sore or tired?
Take a break.
Connect.
I am.
So it's a full game.
That's wet strength.
That's weird.
So they're releasing exclusively on the Epic Games Store for PC only on the 27th.
And then a couple of months later, it's going to consoles.
And then a month or two later, after that, it's going to steam.
That seems like a very odd release schedule.
I don't know.
That's weird.
But I guess whatever.
But thank you, everybody, for watching.
I'm going to go.
You know what I need to do?
I need to take a bath.
I have this part in the middle of my spine right now.
And you know what I think happened?
It happened when I did the break dancing move.
When I did like in the Power Rangers game, I did the break dancing move.
And like I tweaked my spine.
I'm doing I'm fine though.
I just need to soak for like 20 minutes.
Get some epsom salts.
Yeah, that's a super old person thing, but I'll do it.
But let's go back to earlier today.
Oh, by the way, another important thing for the community nights, the monthly community nights.
We are I just gave a huge list of things to all the mods about the channel and the discord that's going to open up.
So probably somewhere around next weekend or maybe maybe even by the time I stream next in like a few days, there's going to be a new channel in the discord.
In that channel will be kind of like the recommended channel where you put in there a piece of artwork, a song, a video that's related to the channel somehow.
I have a whole huge thing of rules that eventually will get pinned and posted somewhere in that channel.
So in once a month, instead of doing this thing at the end of streams where I put on artwork or video that somebody made, because let's face it, I said this last night, but I'll say it again.
Just because probably a lot of people that weren't here yesterday.
When the stream ends and this screen goes on, most people will just kind of leave the stream.
I mean, not most, but it's usually around like 50 to 60 percent will just kind of be like, all right, see, let us see you next time.
Right. So they don't get to see some of these awesome videos that we show here.
So I mean, I guess that is most. Yeah, I guess it is.
And there's been so many great videos.
Think about the videos. Think about the artwork that has been shown here that a lot of people, maybe they might think it was cool.
I think it was interesting. So I figured we'll do like a little radio show thing where once a month we sit down for a few hours and we just go over all the cool community content that people make in one place at one time.
And everybody knows that's what the function is rather than for the bits.
It's hey, it's the bits. And also, here's a really cool piece of artwork, don't you think?
I think it's better that way. That's what I think. It should be interesting to do.
But let's move on. I just want to make sure I clarify that that is coming probably in the next three to five days.
Keep an eye on the Discord. If you're not part of the Discord, join it.
It's open to the public. Anybody can be a part of it, but it's not just going to be for artwork.
It will be for everything. Everything that is related.
Like one of the things I put in a pin or that I put in the post that I made into the mods was, I mean, if you put like Gordon Ramsay saying fuck off 10 times in a compilation, that is not like a community piece of content.
It's just Gordon Ramsay saying fuck off like 10 times.
If it's somehow related to a game or a stream or a thing or a joke or something like that.
That's very specific. But I'm just saying, I don't want you to link in that Discord like your favorite YouTube video.
That's not the purpose of these nights. Because it's only going to be probably two or three hours.
And I want to keep that reserved for like community content.
I mean, if you edit me into a Gordon Ramsay fucking taste test where he tells me to fuck off, there you go.
What a narcissist I am. I have to be in it.
But thank you. Thank you to Chris Buck365 for the four dollars. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Gnarly thanks to the 250. Have you ever considered representing games you played on a main channel video for a stream? Games like Raven's Cry, Total Distortion, or I Am Alive.
Maybe as a compilation like these Kinect games would be fun. Total Distortion I think would be really cool.
Total Distortion is hard to get to run and to capture though.
All those old games are so difficult because they're barely even DirectX.
You have to capture a whole monitor. The things in like 480 by fucking 160.
It's hell to get those to capture through a capture device.
Oh, there's no music. Sorry.
They're tiny weird resolutions.
I think Total Distortion is actually Flash or Adobe Director or something.
It's not even a 3D engine.
I've used a virtual machine before, but I'd have to really would set that up.
I think I've actually used a virtual machine for recording and video streaming purposes.
I believe I did Windows 95, 98. Just point your webcam at it.
Yeah, that's I could do that too.
But yes, I absolutely have thought about it before.
I mean, Super Mario RPG is going to be done next week.
$50 came in 10 minutes ago. I was not here for it.
But thank you Killer Crocomire for the 5,000 bits.
We all know Sam and Max is coming back, right chat?
Yeah. Yeah, I played the first episode and then a lot of people started to lose interest.
I kind of started to lose interest too.
Something about that third season, the first episode didn't pull me like the first two seasons did.
I'm still going to finish it because I'm not going to start episode one on the final season and not do it.
But it didn't pull. It didn't grab me like the other two seasons did.
Something was something about it. I don't know what it was.
But thank you Killer Crocomire for the 50 bucks, 5,000 bits.
You'll see it again. Maybe to maybe next week will just be we'll do Sam and Max Super Mario RPG and we'll connect.
It makes sense, I think. But yeah, thank you to Elizabeth for the 250.
In honor of playing Star Wars on stream, I'm bringing back this classic. Is this the Han Solo song?
Han Solo? I five-starred that on Expert. Were you here for that?
Jeremy is a Jedi Master? What the hell is this? Why can I not hear it?
Oh, it's good. This is pulled out.
This classic? What is it? This classic?
No, let's see if we can't figure out what you are.
So that was the Han Solo song.
And where you come from.
Oh, it's the hologram video.
Oh, this is from one of the green screen nights.
That is a classic. You're right.
That thumbnail. Yeah, what is it? Shrek?
What is that thumbnail? What does that have to do with the video?
I saw it for two seconds.
Is that the Green Goblin?
Shrek? I don't know. Who is that?
Purple underwear?
Why am I looking at that for so long?
Alright. It's the Hulk. The Hulk. The Hulk. Okay. You're right. You're right. You're right.
The Green Goblin.
Runs around in purple underwear.
I'm tired. I'm sorry.
I need to put this on screen.
This is spot the difference.
This is from C4G.
I have to put this on.
Thank you C4G for the 250.
Thank you.
I don't see any difference.
Thank you Marvash Magali for the 250.
Half of these Kinect games are just fever dreams.
Thanks for the super early stream from Italy.
You're welcome. Absolutely.
Trying to pull the streams back an hour or two.
Slowly.
Over time.
Trying to stick to that.
So you'll be seeing earlier streams in the future as well.
Thank you Elizabeth for the 250.
I will electrocute you is my favorite quote
from the Emperor by the way.
Now we're talking about Ravenous Throat, right?
Oh yeah.
I had a lot of shit to say about Star Wars today, didn't I?
ChunkyBologna gave
$50 and 20 subs
earlier. Thank you.
That is a lot. That's a shitload of money.
Bitslave also gave
a ton of subs and
$50 and 45 cents.
Thank you.
And they say, hey German, not sure if you remember me,
but I used to watch your streams all the time
and donate like 25 cents all the time.
I have not a lot of free time to watch your streams
anymore, but I do keep up with the VODs.
Thanks for all the great content over the years.
PSD still have that picture of my dad and I
on your computer.
I do not. I do not because I have formatted
my hard drive since then.
They're talking about
this plane, right?
I do remember this. Yep, it's airplane
you and dad in front of the airplane.
I do remember that.
So yes, I remember you.
But yeah,
thanks for coming back.
I hope you're doing well.
Thanks for the huge amount of subs
that you dropped in. Thanks for the $50 and 45
cents. Appreciate it.
And then they gave five more dollars. They said five
dollars more for the next BitBadge.
There you go. Thank you, Bitslake.
Welcome back.
Let's get the credits on.
Here they come. These are all the subs.
All the new
old resubs, community subs, everybody.
I think they
should be showing up very shortly.
There they are. Thank you, all of you
again. All
16,500
of you. Just kidding. I don't have that
many subs. But man, it feels like it
sometimes. Thank you guys, for
real. Really appreciate it.
Thank you, Master Chicken for the five dollars.
Probably gonna get tired.
Probably gonna get fired from work because of my prescription
medication. Coming home being able to
watch this stream is making my day more bearable.
I'm not sure what you
mean by that, but
I'm really sorry to hear that. That sucks.
That's not cool. Hopefully
you get that sorted out. I'd probably
figure out if that's, you know,
you got rights as a worker, you know.
But hopefully you can figure out
whatever's going on there. I'm really sorry to hear
that you're having trouble there. But thanks
for sticking around here. Thanks for watching.
Thanks for the five dollars. Appreciate it.
Yeah, good luck. Best of luck to you.
Thank you, Bitslay for the five dollars.
They say, look at this burger I got
from McDonald's. What are you doing?
That looks disgusting.
Why did you
Why did you do
Are you watching this in like a Facebook
browser? This is freaking
me out. This is freaking me
out. Why did you give me this?
Is that a burger?
Hold on. What the hell is this?
You got that from McDonald's?
Why are you giving
this to me?
That looks like a
puppet. It looks like a mouth and a
mustache. That looks like the Pringles
guy without his eyes.
What did you do to the Pringles guy?
I would
still eat that too. That actually looks kind of good.
Except for that weird booger
that's on the left of it. Whatever that is. Like a piece
of onion. Well, thank you.
Thanks for that.
Wasn't that B on your tier list? No, it wasn't.
No way.
McDonald's was on B.
It was like a C-. But thank you for that.
Bitslay, appreciate it.
Thanks for the burger. Silent Serenity, thanks
for the two fifty. Psychopath Stream
alters the DNA of his dog
in his garage. Hello,
Lizard. But I do get the point.
Thank you for the two fifty.
Thank you. Errorless for the two fifty. You should
dastardly make a Jerma plus two emote
and only a Jerma plus two emote.
Not a minus two.
That's not a bad idea.
You really game the system there.
I don't even like Taco Bell thanks to the two dollars and fifty
cents. Jerma, you look like
the over enthusiastic instructor at a
rock climbing summer camp.
Yeah, okay. Yeah. I'll take
that one. Thank you. S10W update
for the two fifty. Hey, Jerma, I want to say I'm happy to support
you. Unfortunately, I live in Canada
and I have to pay double for bits.
Five hundred bits is ten dollars.
That sounds
ridiculous. So I can't do this often,
but I want to let you know that I'll support you no matter what the cost.
Peace and love. Also congrats on
being the number one Kinect streamer.
Happy to hear that this is what you'll be
known for. I was also
the number one house flipper streamer, number one
Labo streamer, number one
birdhouse streamer. I have
quite a few accolades, so
I'll take it.
Thank you, though, and don't worry about ever paying
money if you get
destroyed on
currency change there.
You hanging out and watching is
way more important, so thank you, though.
I appreciate it.
Very good.
Thanks for the, I wasn't supposed to read
this one. This one's
not, this one's below the threshold.
What am I doing reading it?
They actually say whoever reads this is
cute. I did.
It's time for slime thanks to the three dollars. Community nights is
a nice idea. I'm excited for it.
It'll be a lot like this, without
the stream over screen. Probably
on face cam.
Hanging out. Just chilling.
Going over stuff. More
concentrated. What is it
gonna be? Uh, the
channel for
submissions will be up
in the discord probably this coming weekend.
So, like, next weekend. Next, like, Saturday
or Sunday. And then after that
probably maybe get a week of the
submissions. I still also have to talk about the
activity book stream, which I'm gonna do before I play
Ancestors on Tuesday.
That's the plan. We also have
a 250 from Jay Bong.
Hey Jay, haven't been able to catch a stream
in over two months because I was visiting
family in Vietnam.
Glad to be back. Also, has Kim ever taught
you any Vietnamese?
Welcome back. Thanks for the 250.
And yes, I have
been...
She's tried. I'm a very slow learner.
I know how to say... I think I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna say this. I don't know what I'm... I think
Anca Sao Hong.
I believe that means I...
Something Sao Hong
Anca Sao Hong
doesn't that mean...
What's that mean? That means, like, I'm your friend
or I'm your brother, father?
What did I just say?
I am your, like, brother or something.
Are you okay, dear?
Right?
No, I just asked, how are you?
That's what I said. I said, how are you?
Like, are you okay? How are you doing?
I am your
father. How are you?
Wow, how wildly different
that was. At least I said it.
Are you
alright? I am your father.
I played too much Star Wars today.
That's the problem.
But, yes,
we have... She's tried to teach me a few things.
Thank you
Dsoid
KajPDFJA
Thanks for the four dolls. Thanks for the stream, Jerma.
Thanks for the four dolls. Thanks for watching.
You rock.
Thank you for four dolls. At the very end
we had 250 from Future
Gamer. Been watching
since middle school. Now I'm starting college.
Any tips for college?
Good luck at college. Thanks for the 250.
And yeah, I do.
If you can... I mean, this is just
from my personal experience.
You can take
day classes or night classes.
I'm not sure if you signed up for classes already.
But in the future,
I always did so much better
on night classes.
You had your whole day already
signed up. Alright, well for the next semester,
it depends if you're a morning person, that's good.
But for me, night classes
gave me the whole day.
I could sleep in, I wasn't rushing in the morning,
and I could get up, take a shower, get some food,
and was able to go to class
later. That was
really, really helpful for me.
But in regards
to just general advice,
yeah.
Take it easy. You don't gotta be the best.
Do your best.
Fuck. I just said the same thing opposite.
Listen.
Okay. You don't have to
be the best. Just
do what you can as
well as you know how.
Alright.
Slam fucking beer
and scream.
Don't do that either. You'll do the best
in college. You know what? You know what I'll
tell you? The real advice for college, the
real advice, it's not
get a 4.0.
It's try to make some friends.
Because everybody's starting at the same point.
And as much as you
don't think so, everybody else
is thinking the same thing that you are.
This is new.
It's a little nerve wracking.
And making friends is actually a little bit
easier in college.
Because everyone is on that same playing
field. You also
start over essentially in college.
And find people that share the same
interest as you, and try to
make some friends. Makes things a lot
easier, a lot more smooth.
High school is more clicky, but college is
easier to find people with similar interests.
Absolutely, because for the most part, if you're
in a major, let's say you're majoring
in, let's say you're majoring
in engineering or something.
I'm studying, or communications.
I'm learning how to do film, tv,
radio. The people in your
classes also think that stuff is cool.
That's why they're there.
I want to be a business student. I want to be a
teacher.
If you want to be a teacher,
all the people in your classes
all want to be teachers.
You have something in common already.
You went to college 10 years ago, or something.
Yeah. It's been a very
long time. Did you learn anything
from communications related to streaming?
No. It was not a thing.
Live, broadcasted
video from a computer was not
something that we were doing.
We were still using tapes.
But I wish you the best of luck. Just take it
easy, take it slow,
and good luck. Everybody's there doing
the same thing. And with that,
I will
see you
Tuesday.
For Ancestors,
the Evolution game.
See you real soon. Have a wonderful
rest of your night. See you guys
Tuesday. Probably going to start Tuesday
at the normal time. So don't
plan on a 12 to 1
PM start. Somewhere around
3 or 4.
Goodbye. Take care.
Good rest of your night.
Bye. And for those of you that thought that was a little
too creepy, goodbye.
Have a great day. See? I
can do both.