Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here, and Ster, and I don't see Steph. What the hell was that?
Hi.
That was like a Chewbacca growl.
I wanted to announce my presence.
That's a great way to do it. I approve of that.
But we're playing the Wave 666 for the Man vs. Machine thing. Probably going to get stomped right now.
But you know what? It's only good fun. We'll see how far we can get, baby.
So let's ready up. Who are we waiting on?
I'm not ready.
Where are you?
I'm Chewbacca-ing in spawn. I've never played Engineer before. I need to figure out what the Engi do.
What does the Engineer even do? How do you play?
I don't know. I think he builds Sentries and they just shoot at everything.
I've never played this class.
Well we have 20 seconds before. Oh goodness. We lost a player.
Oh yay! That sucks.
Well here we go. Here we go. We lost a guy.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Oh stop. You gotta get over it.
I haven't even made it. Oh this is...
Hold on. I'm wiggling.
The first few are pretty easy. You can kill them while I pretend I'm sitting.
Is this only one wave or are there 600 waves?
No, there's one wave. 600 waves?
Oh my goodness. Why are they holding down the flamethrower? Is there a reason for that?
Hey Star!
Say that you die.
I'm lagging so bad but there's so many crits everywhere.
Oh wow.
Oh are they coming up the stairs?
Look how tall these guys are.
Get out of my face. Beggars bazooka baby.
So how bad did we lose? Oh!
I have a Sentry.
Give me the money. How come I can't see you guys on my screen?
My HUD exploded.
This is super lag.
We're winning.
This round is almost over. Look at the top.
Yeah, the round is almost over.
And there's 600 more.
You better collect all the gold. The monies.
I can't even see these bears.
What do you do when you run out of ammo?
Am I a dispenser?
Oh no, I gotta get... Oh no.
Go, go, go, go. I'm not gonna let go of this until I get some ammo.
There it is.
All these demo men are dead right now.
I don't know what a Wrangler is or what it do.
What it do, what it do.
Look how good we're winning.
We're actually not doing that bad.
But of course, this is the first 30 seconds.
Well, I didn't think we'd get past 30 seconds.
Oh no, they have the bomb.
I got enough money to buy some.
Should I not be doing that?
If you buy anything, it should be crit boosts.
Oh, a Sentry Buster. Cool.
Right here, here we go.
I've never seen a Sentry Buster before.
But what it do, what it do.
Look at these guys.
Oh no, Sentry Buster did it.
Oh, that Sentry Buster has health, doesn't it?
Holy cow. Quite a bit of that health too.
I'm sorry about you, Buster.
Oh, my Sentry's fine.
So many crits.
That hurt so much.
I mean, man, the problem with this thing is you need so much ammo.
I'm not even 10%, not even 5% done with this wave.
Oh dear.
Holy crap.
All right, we're good.
Wait till they drop, wait till they drop.
And look at this, look at this flare gun.
Crits, crits, oh my god.
You should reflect those.
With your gun, your primary action slot item.
This is ridiculous.
Right click on it.
I just respawned and came down the aisle and saw all this.
Oh my god, I'm dead.
We're so dead.
Watch out for those things trying to backstab you.
I'm scared now.
Just god, I need to get back.
Oh no.
Delete this.
I don't even know, let's go.
Come on, crit boost, crit boost.
Wow, they have so much health.
They're never ever ever ever dying.
Oh no.
If you shoot with your gun, maybe they'll die.
Oh no, no, no.
I'm dead.
Spam, spam the crits.
I hope you guys enjoyed the video.
No, we haven't lost yet.
You gotta have a good mindset.
There are so many dudes up there.
This is ridiculous.
I'm not even allowed to walk out of spawn.
I don't think they're dudes.
This is impossible.
They have so much health.
That's basically infinite.
We're alright.
We're okay.
The bomb will reset.
You can see it's in the intelligence in this one.
It's on the ground for a while, it goes back.
Damn.
Why can I not...there we go.
Moving my sentry up.
Did we win yet?
Judging by the wave indicator.
Now, we're getting doodled.
We would kindly protect my sentry for like two seconds.
Oh, I have one dude, Renbender.
He's just hanging out in spawn, just looking around.
Oh, cool.
I don't even know what's happening.
Now he's not.
Yes, he is.
Oh, they're so tall.
That's how they get their power.
Oh, that heavy.
Oh my gosh, he killed me instantly.
So much damage.
Sorry.
I'm so scared.
I love how they're all zombies, it's so funny.
Oh, are they?
Yeah, they are.
I'm too stupid and I didn't pay attention.
If you look at them with your eyes, they actually are zombies.
Oh, you see, that's what I forgot to do.
Dude, it's all about buying those crit canteens and just spamming around the corner.
I don't even care if I die.
What?
That is a really bad mentality.
You gotta care a little bit if you die.
Dude, you just gotta go hard.
Live fast.
So the intelligence reset, right?
Yeah, it's right there.
Yeah, but he's fat.
You can kill him.
Let's just push him over.
We need an equally fat guy to just push him.
Sentry buster, buster coming in.
Oh, star.
Oh, they sent my sentry right as the buster came up.
I'm so sorry.
But it's okay, I got an achievement.
Hey, achievements are good.
They like help you beat the wave better.
Oh wait, no they don't.
Wow, this is long.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what she said.
Yeah.
That is indeed what she said.
Live proof.
Oh, whoops, I accidentally bought ammo refill canteens.
This isn't helping me.
You're an engineer.
Probably the person that's the least useful in the entire game.
I love how this guy's just like taunting in the corner.
I'm gonna go back to the base and be useful.
Get useful things.
Back to the base.
Oh, look at that kill feed.
Here we go.
Who's ever put Mad Milk on is actually a super help right now.
Dude, I'm going up top.
I'm getting bird's eye view of this whole thing.
Oh, we got a tank.
Oh, I'm out of ammo.
There's ammo at the top, right?
You gotta spin something.
Mom's going back.
Does the tank have the normal amount of tank health?
I'm not sure.
Oh, those scouts are so accurate.
Oh no.
Out of ammo.
Oh, there's ammo in here.
This is so intense.
I'm writing like a whole thing in my diary about this afterwards.
Sentry buster.
Get rid of that tank.
Too intense.
Another tank?
Holy crap.
Oh, I got no ammo.
Give me, give me, give me.
Well, this first tank's almost down.
There's a scout on the side with the bomb.
You can't let him bomb it because if he bombs it, I think that's what makes us lose.
Is when people use a bomb.
Oh boy, yeah, he's got it.
Yep, they have scouts about to score him.
No.
Wow.
While I'm happy for that scout, kill him.
Well, that was very close.
I'm glad Star Fidget out that they were about to score it.
Yeah, I always keep track of who's scoring and who's not scoring.
Yeah, that's good.
There again.
These guys got crits.
Wow.
I warn you, you should actually really, really get crit resistance for this wave as soon as you can.
Because it reduces damage on like everything.
By the way, they have two tanks that have zero damage done to them.
Hey, watch it, scout, scout, scout.
I got an ammo scout on the point.
Wow, that was good.
Good pyro.
Oh, that's fine.
Wow.
There's a tank right here that has like almost full health.
I still got time.
I got to go get crit booster to kill this thing.
Bomb him.
Out of ammo again.
We're missing money.
Worry about that instead.
I need the money.
I'm out of ammo.
My children.
Yeah, that money back there.
Yeah, we got this tank stuff.
Got another one literally right around the corner though.
We're doing a lot better than I thought we would.
I did like the outro for the video already.
Wait, what?
I told everyone that I hope they enjoyed the video.
I exploded.
Oh, no.
Damn it.
Oh, you taunting scout.
Oh, wow.
Smoke him.
Yeah, that's not strong.
Nice job.
Give me that ammo.
Okay, bombs going back soon too.
So I'm going to try and move my sentry up as soon as that goes right.
Diddle.
Oh, a lot of these scouts.
Give me the health.
Did you just say these scouts are super good?
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
These bots are just.
Dude, these scouts are good.
They've got probably got a lot of playing time.
All right, we got like a second or two.
All right.
Yeah.
You got a second or two.
Bunch of big demos.
Did I get spies?
No.
Get those crits.
Oh, look at that barrage of death coming towards us.
So much spam, I know.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you should name it Sandy.
Goodness.
Oh, too soon.
Actually, not soon enough.
It hasn't happened yet.
Great damage.
There we go.
I know, but I thought about it ahead of time.
Another tank.
Oh, these these guys are.
Oh, my God.
Danny bots too good.
Oh, that's not good.
That's not good.
Got to get rid of this guy.
Oh, there's another tank in here.
Oh, they're about to like score kind of.
Well, you should kill them.
Oh, we got it.
I'm trying.
They're killing me.
Oh, there's a lot of demos here.
Oh, oh, get up.
Oh, I thought he died.
Well, not your friends anymore.
Oh, dude, he died.
He like exploded.
Oh, well, poop.
It was a good attempt, though.
I mean, we only got to like 30 or 40 percent down, but that's intense.
That is crazy.
So that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And wave 666 is no joke.
So while you have the time, while the event is still going, I'm not sure if they are going to end it or not.
They probably will still have it able to be selected.
But go try it out for yourselves.
If you complete it, congratulations to you because it is pretty difficult.
So, again, thank you so much for watching.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And, of course, take care, everybody.