I got here as soon as I could. I saw the time ticking down. I was like, wait a minute, 3 to 4 p.m. I gotta go.
I did the sprint where both your hands, you know, you do the one hand up, flat, right hand up, flat, over and over again, just straight up, like an old lady on the sidewalk.
That's what I did. Alright, let me tweet it. Give me one second.
Alrighty, so today, my wonderful, wonderful, wonderful audience of mine, we got a bunch of PlayStation 2 stuff to do.
Remember I mentioned a few weeks ago that there was still a ton of stuff that I didn't do, I didn't cover?
Well, it's here. And I don't know the exact process we're gonna do here, because some of these are probably really good.
And I might have to throw away my 45 minute and then bust the way that I do things.
So, we'll have to figure that out. Yes, I'm realizing how not good that just sounded. That's okay.
I'm gonna have to change the way that I do things, maybe, because for instance, some of these are really highly requested.
I got Psy Ops, the Mind Gate Conspiracy, that's one of the most highly requested PlayStation 2 games from people in this community.
And I don't know if I want to give that one like 30 minutes.
Also, I got another Family Feud. This might even be the same game, just on PS2. No, I don't think it is.
That got a bunch. So, I'm gonna go a few days in a row here, and we'll try to go through them.
After this weekend here, I'm gonna go back to some newer games that have come out recently.
So, what we're talking about, well, you did a bunch of VR shit. Here's the PlayStation 2, here's the Dreamcast.
We're gonna go back to some newer releases after this weekend, but I did want to get a lot of this out of the way.
And Vive comes back too. I got too much stuff to do. Why can't humans just be awake for 48 hours?
I wish we had a 48-hour day. If humans could sleep for like 4 hours, be fully rested, you can try.
Alright, so, I mean, the one we're gonna start with here is one that is closest to my heart, I think.
The one that it just sears into my body. It's one of my favorite things I've ever seen in my life.
And of course, I'm talking about, hold on, I'm gonna make sure there's no naked person on the camera.
No, I'm talking about, well, the whole bit kind of got ruined, but what I'm talking about here is Ed Edd n Eddy,
The Misadventures of Ed Edd n Eddy. There it is.
Could have gone smoother with the reveal there. What's up with your hair? What do you mean?
What's wrong with it? What's wrong with my hair? Because I was in the shower.
I'm in Vegas! It's hot here! Why are you in a tank top? I'm in Las Vegas! It's fucking like 150 degrees here every day!
You look like a shitty backup actor for an MTV video. That's your opinion, okay?
And you're allowed to have a wrong one, but that is yours.
Let's get it started. Ed Edd n Eddy, The Misadventures. The Mis-Edventures.
I'm gonna piss a lot of people off, I think, with this one.
Because I'm gonna play this. Here's what's gonna happen. We'll break it down. Hold on, let me just get my controller.
I'm gonna play this for 15 minutes, and I'm gonna be like, okay, so walk over here, grab this box.
Okay, cool. That's funny. What do I do now? Nothing like really interesting is happening.
How do I? I'm streaming, I'm streaming. What do I say?
I'm gonna grab this thing. Oh, I grabbed Edd by the shoulder and I threw him.
Nothing's funny, nothing interesting is happening. What do I do about this?
That's gonna be going on internally in my head.
And then I'm gonna turn it off in like 30 minutes. Go, yeah, it's pretty cool.
I mean, I remember it was like fun. If you liked it, like, that's cool.
Can I even hear anything? Yeah, yeah.
Before we start PlayStation 2 night, can we get some yes?
Checking memory card. Edd n Eddy, The Misadventures.
He's an autosave feature. Cartoon Network. Interactive. Midway. Really?
I didn't know they made this. Think Video.
They patented like one screen 40 years ago.
And now they're in every single video game. A to M.
Oh, I'm not gonna criticize this game.
You don't think I'm aware of the backlash I would receive?
I'm not gonna move yet. Holy shit, this brings back memories.
Yeah, that's why I don't wanna make fun of it.
Not that I was going to.
This needs to be moved though.
Is the color correct? It looks weird.
Where's Ed? What happened to Ed?
How come he didn't say his name?
Wait, hold on a minute. Turn it up.
Listen. Does he say his name?
I heard Ed. Eddy!
Oh god, fuck. Whatever.
Why is turbo on? Why is turbo on?
I don't want turbo.
Okay, new game.
There's no save file. Make one.
If somebody wants to make, like, a video, I'm just gonna give you an idea for a video.
Whoever wants to make it, go for it.
This is not my idea.
This is an idea of somebody that would think this is a good idea.
It's not my idea.
Wait, what? Eddy's game? Ed's game?
Doesn't matter?
Let's do Eddy.
Alright, so remember, this is not my idea.
If you want, you know Venom?
How he calls him Eddy?
Throughout the course of the movie?
You could put, like, Venom in here as, like,
Ed! Ed! Eddy!
That video would get, like, at least 12,000 views.
So, Sockhead, where are we gonna get enough ice to make snow cones?
I'm sure we could locate sufficient frost shavings in the backyard coolers of the neighborhood, kids, Eddy.
I love how much everybody hates this.
Alright, I gotta slow it down, because I got, like,
two or three everybody hates this
things in the first, like, five minutes of this stream.
Haven't I learned, I gotta stop, like,
intentionally hate this?
Collect ice cubes to make snow cones.
Select Ed by pressing R1.
Okay.
Select Ed, so you can cycle through.
When an object glows, it means that you can interact with it
by pressing the triangle button.
Alright, so there's, uh,
Okay, I got the,
I got the potato slicer.
Let's get ice cubes.
Throw shit? Okay.
Good work, Ed's special ability is to lift and throw objects.
And what do we got for, what is his move?
Press the square button to do basic attack.
He has a power-up,
He has a punch, okay.
So the ice cubes are supposed to be,
from my understanding here,
they're like puzzle pieces from Banjo,
or stars from Mario.
Alright, so that's the,
so, don't be mad at me, I don't know who is who.
I'm just gonna say,
I'm gonna say Ed 1,
2, and 3.
Oh, he has an attack too.
And let's go.
Now, he has a slingshot.
Does Ed have a grenade?
Launch a stink bomb,
most enemies are stunned by stink bombs, okay.
They all have their own version of the Naruto run.
He looks like he's trying to do the Naruto run,
but he doesn't have any bones.
Stink bomb.
Okay, so we can push,
launch a stink bomb,
so, how do we launch him?
Press L1 with Ed,
to perform the battered Ed formation.
This move can be used to smash through objects.
Pretty awesome.
Pretty cool game, pretty fun.
If you liked this game back in the day,
that's cool, because it's good.
It's pretty good.
How do I get this off? What's on me?
What is attached to me?
I have an animal on me.
Find a cat to lift and throw at the dog,
to get him away from the cooler.
How do I get this off me?
Ed's gonna die.
No, get off of me!
Alright, he died.
Watch out for the squirrel.
Why are there so many squirrels?
I gotta hit them.
Press L1 with Ed, digging the sand.
Chickens are present in each level.
Catch the chicken by stunning it.
And then grab it with Ed.
Watch out, watch out!
God damn it, which one of these is Ed?
Ed's the big one, right?
Ed is...
Let me try.
Chickens are present in each level.
Catch the chicken by stunning it, and then grab it.
Why do I have a fucking trash can?
Where did I get a trash can?
This one's Eddie, right?
The one with the sock in his head?
No, that's Ed.
Who's the one with the antenna?
This is Ed,
with 1D.
This is Eddie, right?
Also, Ed.
Ed's the big one.
Eddie is the one...
Okay, Eddie's the one with the antenna.
Eddie's the one with the yellow shirt.
Alright, let's go, get that cooler!
Got that cube.
There's a sandbox somewhere that I need to dig in.
Where's the sandbox?
Switch to Eddie.
No, I went all the way back to the part of the hut.
You're horrible at this.
Well, come on, man!
I haven't even seen the show!
I don't know what's going on in this TV show.
How can I be good at the game if I've never seen the show?
Okay, I need a cat.
Cat, cat, cat.
Is there a cat?
Cat the tree?
I'll find a cat.
Alright, hold on.
No cat here, but I can dig in the sand.
Alright, that's Ed.
Ed's the one with 1D.
Costume piece.
I really feel like Eddie would do a great Smash Mouth impression.
Did he ever sing that song?
Any Smash Mouth songs?
I feel like he would be pretty good at it.
Get that cat.
They did that once?
Yeah, I would assume. This is a cat, right?
Alright, well I got another puzzle piece.
Why don't they all jump in the air at the same time when you collect it?
35. Alright, let's keep going.
No Eds allowed.
That's alright, I'm Eddie.
Cutscene.
Violence only begets violence, Eddie.
Do it, man, come on.
Okay, let's go.
What?
R2 button?
You can go into the FPS mode? You kidding me?
Now jump on the picnic table and use Slingshot on Jimmy's dolls.
I can't go over there, though. Wait.
Is this a picnic table? This looks like just a plank of wood.
Alright, let's go.
How do I shoot it? Circle?
This bullet drop.
I did it, right?
How do I get out? Okay, let's go.
This is actually kind of fun.
I was talking a little shit at the beginning about how I was going to skip it.
But, it's not bad.
It's not bad.
I got 4 out of 5.
No, it's not bad. It's fun.
I mean, it could use a little work in the graphical department, but...
Nice!
Throw squirrels into the window of the house.
Why would I do that?
Like this house, right here.
No, yeah, I would have had it.
You got a fucking squirrel problem.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Not the red squirrel! Get the red squirrel off me!
Get away from me!
No more red squirrel.
Dude, these stuff are...
They make cartoons...
Look at how good this cartoon was back in the day.
They had a whole orchestra.
They had a whole jazz orchestra playing these songs to each episode.
They make these goddamn songs on a computer now.
Who's the jazz orchestra?
There's a conductor.
And the special features of the Ed Edd and Eddie DVD.
You can see the whole orchestra play.
Uh, what?
How do you...
Listen, throw squirrels into the window of the house.
Isn't that what... Is this the wrong house?
What the fuck am I doing?
Why are we doing a cheerleading?
I think they'll do like a reunion episode.
When the actors come back, and they're a little too old,
and you can tell they're really trying.
But they don't really... They sound different.
For some reason, the Simpsons...
The Simpsons voice actors sound exactly the same
as they did 30 years ago.
It's insane.
The person that does Lisa...
Still is the exact same voice.
Prepare to major doom!
But Edd and Eddie...
But Edd and Eddie... They were fucking talented people.
It was really cool.
They did great jobs.
Two of them died. Oh god, that's terrible.
Wait, what was I supposed to...
Where am I taking the squirrel?
I forgot what to do already.
Yeah, I missed that cutscene because we were talking.
Well, I was talking.
You were watching me, uh...
Forget where I was going while I was talking.
That's not true.
Wait, what?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
We were talking.
Lift and throw the fridge at the door.
Alright, let's throw it at the fridge.
Hoi!
Okay, use the battering head.
Let's throw it in here.
Okay, so let's do the battering head.
How do I stop doing this?
I got the pot.
What is this thing? A coin?
Ooh, I got two coins.
Three coins, four coins.
Oh, we did it.
That's it.
Let's do speedrun tactics, man.
This is faster.
Meatball machine.
He didn't really translate the 3D very well.
He's got a very strange mouth.
For 3D.
It looks like Bart.
That's like 55-year-old Bart Simpson.
Okay.
He is ugly.
Oh, pigs.
Batter and the pigs gate.
That should change Rolf's mind about the meatball.
Do I get to ride a pig?
Lift and throw the pigs back in the pen.
Okay.
Sounds easy enough.
I can't throw it over.
I do appreciate the default pig sound.
Is it just minigames?
Probably.
Oh, come on.
Will he just walk in?
There we go.
One more? Two more?
This game is worse than I remember.
I think it still holds up.
I mean, I never played it.
Let's use the machine.
Is there another pig?
Can we use the machine?
Is there another pig somewhere?
Oh, the fucking red squirrel got me again.
He said yes.
Well, how do I get on it?
Get the red squirrel away from me.
Does the smart one have to use it?
How do I get back in this house?
No, there's another pig here.
Look, can one of you party members just turn
and just fucking blast that squirrel?
See?
Stop running out.
They just keep running out.
I gotta go in his fucking shed.
Alright, let's activate the meatball machine.
You just completed scam number one.
Cool your head.
10% game completion.
Fully animated?
Kind of.
Stop eating those.
Why did you just turn into Skeeter from Doug?
Col de Sac.
Okay, we got a sewer.
It's open world.
Leave the level and go.
No, not yet.
Let's really examine
the suburbs of Ohio.
I don't even know where the hell they are.
What town were they in?
Anything else I can do?
I can imagine being a big fan of this show
when it was really, really popular.
And walking around
and like going in Jimmy's pool
and being like, wow!
Talking to Ralph.
Picking up paint cans. They love painting, right?
That never said where?
Nah, let's just go to the next one.
This one's in the sewer.
This show fucking sucked. I'm glad it died.
Wow! That's heavy, man.
I know, I know!
We can crawl through the stinky sewers
like the bacteria fusing blob
and I was a teenage sludge hippie!
I don't know. It seems terribly risky
and unsanitary,
to say the least.
It'll be a cinch!
Come on, boys! We got a party to catch!
I like this. This is very fun.
Pin the tail on the ed.
The animation doesn't give
any V-Show animation justice.
Yeah, but it is a PlayStation 2 game.
Find the way into Jimmy's backyard.
Can you watch Ed Ed Nettie
with the whole thing anywhere?
Or do you have to buy the DVDs or Blu-Rays or something?
Is it possible to play this?
Not play this, but watch it?
I don't know.
It seems terribly risky
and unsanitary, to say the least.
Throw toxic waste?
Oh, shit. We're getting attacked by alligators.
The whole show is on YouTube.
What?
Well, I'm talking like a legal way to watch it.
Not like
Edfan2044
that uploads every video.
Oh, my God. Get the fucking out.
How do you kill the alligator?
Just dive through it.
They're not gonna throw you in prison
for watching a YouTube show.
It's elementary, Eddie.
If we move down to the other side,
you two can lift me up to that crack.
I'll lower the bridge, allowing us to cross together.
All right, switch to Ed and press L1
to enter Trampolad.
So we're gonna launch
Ed up there
to turn the dial.
Can we go in this?
Maybe we can.
Is it poison or is it just not an alligator?
All right, do it.
No, I'm gonna die. I'm gonna lose.
You're killing them.
I'm gonna take their souls.
What are they doing? Oh, their pathing is
getting up there.
Where's the most powerful technique?
I can throw the, okay,
the stink bomb. All right, watch out.
I'm gonna collect their souls.
No, no.
It's okay.
I don't think you can kill the alligators.
Maybe you can.
No, you definitely can't.
All right, all right, all right.
Okay, okay, easy, easy, easy.
I'm gonna have to, like,
battering ram that thing. Jesus Christ!
This thing is relentless!
Why is it still swimming on land?
That doesn't make any sense.
This is not fair. This is fucking unfair.
All right, battering ram this.
Battering ram.
Now I need a key.
All right, I have to get a key.
I'm just gonna throw the grenade.
Fuck it.
How do I throw the grenade?
There it is.
Okay.
I need a key to open this door.
I gotta go back.
Find key.
Key.
Why am I standing in?
Kill the alligators.
I don't think I can.
I hit them, like, three or four times.
They swim around like Aquaman,
and then you can't hurt them.
Let's try.
All right.
You can kill them.
All right, well, it's good to know.
I'm gonna find a key.
Oh, that was a coin.
Can I throw these as many times as I want?
I can.
Let's get infinity mode.
Well, he's the best character in the game.
All right. Key.
No key.
No key. In barrel. Boxes.
Toxic waste.
If I was a key, where would I be hiding?
Does anybody have anything to say about this?
That's the Dark Souls shortcut.
Nothing in there.
So they said switch to Ed.
Wait, what?
You can just open locked doors?
When did you possess this skill?
Yeah, Ed knows how to pick locks.
I thought there was a key.
What do you mean?
I thought that was a joke.
I thought there was a key involved.
That's double D.
You charlatan.
All right, well, what's that down there?
What's that down there?
Got it?
This looks like a real Ed level.
What would happen if he didn't have double D?
Would they just die?
This should work.
Why am I calling it double D?
It's Ed.
Edward.
Why would they just stand around?
Watch the show.
I've seen the show. I know the show.
I know about Plank.
Plank is his little friend.
Jimmy.
I know about
the sisters, right?
I've seen the show.
I know that they put jawbreakers
in their mouths.
All they care about is candy.
He's a fake fan.
Name your favorite episode.
I can't do that.
I got like a clam on me now.
I need to do something.
Who can touch these?
Favorite episode.
An episode of Ed, Edd, and Eddie
that I remember.
They got a super jawbreaker
one time, right?
It was a huge one.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
What is an episode
of Ed, Ed, and Eddie that I've ever seen?
But I can't even do that.
I can't do that.
But I can't even do that with the Simpsons.
Right?
Okay, name a Simpsons episode.
Not like Treehouse of Horror.
I can't.
There we go.
We got some doors here.
Mr. Plow? Yeah, but that's
I guess like you just said that.
I didn't.
I'm trying. What is an episode of Ed, Ed, and Eddie
that I've ever seen?
I've seen a bunch of them a long time ago.
Did somebody
steal a plank one time and replace it
with another piece of wood?
No.
You sure?
Alright, I need to do something with the clam.
That didn't do anything.
Fuck!
Alright, hold on.
There's an Ed King back here.
Just who cares?
I'm gonna bring you over here. Just drown the clam.
Do it! Do it!
What's this like Tomb Raider bullshit? Like you gotta be right in front of it? Come on!
Alright, got it.
Chicken!
Chicken! Chicken!
I got it!
Bingo. Two out of six.
Alright, nothing else over here?
I can't name an episode.
An episode.
Even one plot device.
I don't know.
Get off me, please.
I'm just gonna farm HP.
I need a better, like an
attacker. Here we go.
Now you guys have given a lot of good
answers here, but those are not my answers.
Involved
in an episode.
Let me look around here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, you can't say next.
You can't do that yet.
Fuck, it's been forty-one minutes!
I can't
leave this game until I tell
you a Ed, Edd, and Eddie
plot device from one episode that I've ever seen.
I refuse.
I
would be upset at myself if I
didn't do that.
It's like a lever I have to pull.
He says that.
Is there one word like Ed
Is there one word like Ed is not smart?
He doesn't, like he gets like
dumb or something?
He's not that smart and they realize that they need his intelligence
or something?
He gets like dumb? Yes, yes.
No, I'm talking about like Double D.
Double D like loses his brain power or something, right?
Like gets his brain power dumb how
messed up? And they spend the whole episode
trying to get him smart again?
Or is that, was that, so Edd gets
really, no, Eddie, no, Edd,
this one, gets really smart in an
episode, right?
No.
Yes, I'm not stalling. I'm trying to figure
it out. I was right the first
time. Alright, so I can stop playing then.
Thanks for watching. No, I'm kidding.
I can't leave until I open this
door. What about like the Edd Ram?
No, I eBayed. I
eBayed this game. You think I'm just gonna stop playing it?
I had to buy this on eBay.
It took three
weeks to get here. It was
78 bucks total.
I'm kidding. It's a lie. How do I do this?
Am I missing
something here? Am I missing
an episode?
I have to switch to Edd. How do I
get such bad deals? I'm just kidding. This was not
80 bucks. He's blind.
Wait.
Maybe I am. Maybe I am.
What do I have to do with Edd?
Touch this thing? The like elephant trunk?
Grab the elephant trunk and spin it.
Oh, come on.
Look, hold on a minute.
This is like, how many pizzas are there here?
There's at least five
pizza-shaped things here. Look, there's one here.
There's the elephant trunk that I made
before I mentioned.
It's only glowing when
you have Edd selected.
And I had my favorite character, which is
Eddie, selected. So it doesn't
light up. You get it?
It only lights up when you have the person
that can do the reactions selected.
My favorite part about Edd and Eddie is nothing to do
with the show. It's when the guy
goes...
After that happens, I just turn to the channel.
I change the channel. I went in a fucking
circle.
I can't like, talk. Stop talking.
Frankly, I'm disgusted.
You don't know which Edd you are. I know exactly which
Edd I am.
Was there an episode where one of their cousins
like Fred showed up?
Do I get bonus points for that one?
Weren't there three other like
Edd, Edd, and Eddie? Oh, fuck.
No, I'm fine. There are three
other Edd, Edd, and Eddie's that show up in an episode, right?
No, not the girls.
Okay, easy.
Wait, didn't I...
Hold on. Did I...
Where's my map?
I need to press select and see like the coordinates
of where I am.
Where's my dungeon map?
How come you don't have one of those, Edd?
Okay, remember this? Yep, yep, yep.
Alright.
I can't take this laugh anymore.
Alright, then I had the rats here.
And then that door.
Is there... Okay, wait. Is there...
Can I open this?
Is there like another blind moment?
See, what about this one?
I can't use that one.
What about... I'm just checking. I'm just checking to make sure I don't...
Fuck it up. Look at that.
Why does he keep laughing? Because things are funny.
Some things are funny.
Don't lose here.
They're blocking the way.
I feel like I'm really neglecting
the single Edd, right? No, double Edd.
No, the Eddie.
Two syllable Edd.
I'm neglecting him.
That's a tough pole here.
Got it. Nice.
I'm like a fucking lightning rod right now.
That was fucking so hard.
Next. Next. No!
Not until I... Edd Batteringram!
Let's Edd break that, right?
Secret room?
No, alligator.
Connect the names with the right characters or fake fans.
Sure.
Okay. By the way,
I never told you I was a fan of this show.
I told you I've seen the show and that I thought it was okay.
I thought it was great.
Let's start from the beginning.
This is Edd with two Ds. This is double D.
This is
E-D-D-Y. Eddie.
And this is E-D.
Edd.
They're corrected.
Something else in here I can do.
And then
somebody...
Didn't somebody...
DW?
Is it like one of these Edds like...
No, that's Arthur.
Edd-D-W.
No, that's the intro in Arthur.
What happened to that show?
You play for long and you unlock
the secret fourth Edd.
Yeah. Nice fake fan,
by the way.
Remember, like,
name the characters correctly or you're a fake fan.
What about the guy who just said there's a fourth Edd?
What are we going to say about that guy?
Oh, nice. Job record.
Is that a secret?
There's 40 of those.
Judge Dredd.
Ten years, punk.
The fourth Edd. Judge Dredd.
Dredd, Edd, Edd, and Eddie.
Edd, Dredd,
Edd, Edd, Dredd, and Eddie.
I was...
I can't do...
I can't say that.
It's too dumb.
Somebody already did it. I'm not doing it.
Alright. Turn the valves to lower the water level.
Okay!
I need that.
New valves over here.
Oh, Edd's dead.
Edd's dead. Sorry, Edd.
Somebody said loser.
No, no, no. Get off.
Edd fell in the water.
And he was never heard from again.
He fart-joked.
You guys are acting like I made that joke.
I didn't.
What the hell was that? Was that Coraline?
Coraline! Open the door!
Don't tuck them all in there!
Get out of there!
It's not what it seems!
Okay, there's one. The water's going down.
There's one over there.
Okay. Easy.
Edd. Eddie.
Do I throw somebody?
Is that it?
Where's one of the valves?
We gotta get down there.
I can't tell. It's kind of blurry.
Can I throw him?
There's not one.
Please stop this game already.
No, why?
It's fun.
I'm begging you. I'm starving.
Let me at least get to the end of this.
This is a fun game.
Well, I obviously have to go down there.
Is there one over there?
I don't know who that was.
That was just Carrot Top.
I still have a clam on me.
We're starved for good content.
Come on.
You don't like this?
Alright.
This is one of the most requested video games
I've ever had on the channel.
You asked me
to make you scrambled eggs
with like cheese in it.
Pepper, onions. I sit there all day
and I'm at the stove and I'm cooking all these
weird eggs you ordered. You want like
hollandaise on it too. I'm like really?
You want like hollandaise sauce?
Yeah. And then I put this fucking
meal in front of you and you're like
I don't like the way that smells.
Get rid of it. And I'm like I just
I thought you wanted this. You wanted eggs with hollandaise.
And then like the rest of the families
at the table.
Like the 300 family members that I have.
I wanted pancakes.
And I'm just like I don't have
the materials for pancakes right now.
Get them mom.
I can't. The store's closed.
And then you back up and you
walk out. You like go to
your room. No.
Mom made what mom made. If you don't like it
then that's too bad.
You gotta eat it.
It's got broccoli. It's got spinach in it.
Spinach. It's gonna make you grow up big and strong.
Ed Ed and Eddie will make you grow up big and strong.
As long as you don't. Hold on.
I'm gonna die.
I gotta get up there.
I gotta do the Ed spring.
Come on. Get me up there.
This one fucking clam.
No!
How do I like close
the clams mouth?
That's it. Alright.
I beat it.
Alright Jimmy. Let's go.
You don't get killed by a clam but I do.
Alright.
Now what? Drawbreaker.
I'm just kidding man. Don't worry.
Do what you want. Ignore the chat.
I'm just playing around.
I know you guys are too.
Don't worry. I know you guys really do love Ed Ed and Eddie.
I know you do. That's why I'm gonna keep playing.
Jimmy what's wrong with you?
Jimmy. Walk down here.
Oh no.
Please don't come back to do it again.
Okay. We're good.
Jimmy what do you want?
Jimmy. Hello.
Um. Where do I go?
Down here?
Take the valve.
Do you just leave it up there?
Oh.
Your best pal.
So how about that valve Johnny?
Bring it on you.
Just give us the valve and I'll give you a plank.
Plank says you are tricky.
Double D. Let's install that valve
and we're done with it.
No I made that valve. I installed that valve.
I did that.
Why are you guys writing gay band?
Where's the gay band coming from?
The rods are bigger. They're getting thicker.
Oh it's cause of the
valve thing right?
People still making that joke
in like 2019.
Like the gay band.
I'm still getting that reference and joke
in 2019.
We are?
No we're not.
He's here.
Everybody hates valve.
That's not true. They got three VR
games coming up. That's what I heard.
What would you guys do if I just turned on the webcam right now
and just fucking sprinted out of the room
and in the chair like I was
just clicking around and I ran out of the room
and Gabe Newell's in the chair.
Here. And he started talking about his favorite
What would that be worth?
And by the way he's getting the
names wrong. Would you guys still say that shit?
To Gabe Newell?
I really like how Ed
he's the tall one right?
With two D's. Everyone would be like
idiot. No you wouldn't.
I've heard of diversion. So I have to break the trampolines.
I mean break the
pinatas. Where are the pinatas?
Because we
like Gabe
Newell.
Okay you can chop.
Because we like Gabe
Newell.
I'm mean.
And I'm not going to stand for it.
Crap.
I mean this area does.
This is a Playstation 2 game.
Come on.
He's like the Phil's very
dope boy.
He's making me laugh.
Cutscene incoming.
What are they called? The Grunge Sisters?
Fake fan. Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Hold on. Wait. I didn't know
I have to go. Beehives.
Shoot the beehives. Pop a fridge on them?
Alright.
This reminds me of those
old flash games.
I'm dead.
I gotta like time it when they run across the screen.
Because I can't hit them with this.
Stun stun stun.
Right there. Right there.
Get it. Bingo.
Right here.
No I can't. Oh she was standing
right there. Right here. Right at this one.
Drop a fridge on her head.
Got it.
Back into the sewer.
Oh god.
Did I get it?
I don't think I got it.
That's a laugh.
That laugh is driving me crazy.
There's more.
All the way down.
Get it.
Don't do the laugh.
Please.
And then right here. Shit. Drop it on her head.
Got it. No I didn't.
Got it. You just completed
this game too. Pin the tail on the head. Current game
19%.
Animatic cutscene.
Too bad the party is over dorks.
Miniclips gave 50 bucks.
Are you kidding me? I'm Jimmy.
There's gotta be some cake left right?
Here.
You can lick the icing from my candle.
Gross.
What was that face? That didn't even look like him.
Miniclips gave 50 bucks.
Thank you for the 50 dollars
Miniclips. Local streamer
reviews his children live on stream
sounds like you're having a good time.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you for the 50 dollars. I really appreciate it.
Alright so
for real
thank you. That's a lot of money.
Alright here's the deal. If I get this
basket in the net
first try
I will keep playing the game.
If I don't get it first try
then I'm gonna keep playing.
Alright let's keep going.
Is that what it feels like?
No please.
Just, you're gonna have to wait.
Okay. I gotta do
no I don't. Let's just see what
the next one is. We're gonna just see what the next one is.
Let's at least see the animation.
Okay so we have to go
Jimmy's birthday
Did Jimmy have a birthday every day?
It's his second birthday in a row.
That's what we're banned from.
It's his crown hog day.
I did something wrong. I have to correct it.
The world is trying to teach me
something.
Oh okay.
Jerma, I'm actually gonna leave.
Well I
can't stop you.
Exit of the cul-de-sac.
Come on we got three days
in a row to do
just let me enjoy my video game.
This is
$150 for me to buy this.
This shady guy, I had to like go meet him
in like a fucking alleyway.
You wanted an Eddie?
Yeah man like I heard from
Craigslist you were selling that Eddie?
Yeah.
You wanted anything else?
No just Ed, Edd, and Eddie.
Like five guys like kind of appeared
out of the shadows with like huge leather jackets on
and they had like spiked clubs and stuff.
They're like surrounding me.
I just gave the guy a fucking wad of hundreds
and walked away and he gave me the disc.
What's over here?
Okay here we go, a new place.
Yeah and then I heard something behind me as I was walking
to my car, the fucking Lamborghini by the way.
It's a beautiful car.
And I'm just kind of swinging my keys around
just like kind of a little nervous.
I hear like you know footsteps behind me.
And they got close enough
where I was able to
I was able to change
my hair in
like five minutes my hair changed.
It was weird because the guy was behind me but I noticed
that my hair changed completely.
I heard the steps.
Grabbed the guy in a fucking stone cold stone headlock
and then flipped him.
Alright well I just broke my head.
That's it.
Where's the thing that was on it?
I can't even use this.
I ripped off the thing
that was on it.
There was like a piece of jelly that was attached to it and now
I don't know where it is.
I can't even use the headphones now.
I got it.
Everything's fine.
I got it. See?
Everything's just fine.
There it is.
Don't worry about it. Everything's fine.
If that may have already been like that.
I don't know. Which ear is this for?
There's earwax on it. That's not earwax.
There's a hair on it.
What do you say earwax?
Buddy.
There's hair all over this though. That's like dog hair.
That's not my hair.
Let's try to reattach this.
This one.
There's hair all over me.
You put earbuds in your dog's ears?
No. What?
No this is the wrong one.
Alright.
Good as new.
See? This is supposed to be attached.
But whatever. It goes in here.
The jelly. I can just stuff it in there.
We're fine. Everything's good.
It's like a hearing aid.
Leave the cam on? I don't want to.
I'm laughing at that.
It's funny.
Must be something IED.
Wow. I didn't know what that was until
it was revealed.
Get to the candy store fast
for free jawbreakers.
I don't think you said
it wasn't kill squirrels.
How do I get out of my backyard?
Do the edge jump?
No, no, no.
The jump.
Episode was it?
No. I have to jump on this.
Oops.
How am I not annoyed by the game?
I don't know.
Why the hell are you still playing?
I don't know. I don't know.
Why not? I don't know.
I don't know.
How do I get out of my backyard?
I'm going to jump on this.
Go through the house.
I can't open the door.
The door doesn't open.
Break the door.
I can't smash the door.
Maybe bash this?
Ooh, baby.
What did you look at that?
So anyway, the guy comes up behind me
and I fucking, I'm right in his fucking head.
You know what I mean?
Don't fucking look at my armpit hair.
I swear to God I'll be mad at you.
Look, it's the winter time, okay?
I clean up.
It's cold. I don't like
to wear tank tops.
I clean up. I do a little bit of maintenance.
It's goddamn
February, alright?
The Tower of Ed.
Make fun of that for one second.
I swear to God I'll never stream again.
You're going to see my face again?
Has anyone ever actually said something like that?
This is actually really hard.
Again.
I'm telling you.
This is really difficult.
You're never going to see me again.
Um, guys.
Guys, guys, guys. Guys, it's hard.
Guys, I'm telling you.
This might look bad. It's going to look really bad.
You're going to think I'm an idiot.
I'm telling you, once I get to this hitbox,
the second plank, all hell breaks loose.
Oh, so nerve-racking.
I'm like a fucking lightning bolt right now.
There's one of those girls.
What's that sound? What do they sound like?
Right there.
There it is!
Yeah!
See, I told you I knew what the show was.
Grab high-placed objects.
I'm going to walk around and pick them up.
Just throw some fucking apple grenades.
Hold on.
There's multiple red swirls here.
This is the real gear check here.
Find out if I can be capable.
Okay, high objects.
Got it.
Drop the objects at...
gemmy neutrons.
Did it work? Yes.
Come on.
Got it. Two?
You can't drop them on the ground?
Why?
These red swirls!
I'm going to seriously piss me off.
I'm just going to kill the red swirls.
Just kill them first.
There's one more over here.
Now I'm not going to get attacked.
And after this, we'll move on to the next game.
Thank you.
I would recommend you play...
That counts, right?
This one's actually fun.
I recommend that you play gemmy neutron.
This game's not good.
Throws really infuriating little sequences at you for no reason like that.
That's unfair.
This game's not very good.
Oh, Matt, because Matt.
Matt, because Matt. Matt, because Matt.
Matt, give me that right now.
I would love, in fact, like an e-sports event.
Or at a stadium somewhere.
Don't you just wish you could hear that chant?
It would be so funny.
What a stupid chant that would be.
Oh, he missed a shot in lane!
That's too bad.
Where's fucking Ed?
Yeah, it looks like his...
Who's a Bleak Legends fucking character?
Where's Ed?
I fell through the earth.
He was under the map.
Okay, well, let's try to go on these one more time.
Like, imagine...
Well, let's go over that again.
So, there's like a big e-sports event.
And one of the teams, you know, a counter-strike or whatever.
And some guy misses a very important shot.
And you can see him visibly pissed off.
Commentators are like,
Man, he really is not happy about that.
Missing that last shot.
And the whole stadium is just like,
Mad because bad! Mad because bad!
Mad because bad!
I think that would be funny.
No, don't!
That would be so rude.
I know.
What's that again?
Hold on, say that again?
I'd like for you to say that in front of the whole class, please.
Interesting. That would be what?
What would that be?
Rude.
Very rude, wouldn't it?
Interesting.
You just fell right from my fucking trap.
All of a sudden, it's rude!
Whoa!
Alright, come on, come on.
I tried to catch it.
I can't take this anymore.
Can I just like strategically give commands to say like,
Hey, Ed, you stay over there and patrol.
Next, next.
Just wait, I gotta do this one more time.
Hello, how are you?
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Got it.
Look, Sarah left the table.
What am I supposed to do about that?
What would that do for us?
Push Sarah.
You sure?
I'm not sure that, I mean,
Push Sarah or Ehluhala Hey?
Which one do you think?
No, that was good. That was a good idea too.
Ehluhala Hey.
Thanks for the tip, guys.
Oh, jeez!
This game's driving me insane.
And chat insane.
Why is everybody driving insane?
You gonna go over the jump?
Insane.
There's a reason why I wouldn't be invited
to an eSports event as a caster or something.
I would stand up and try to get them to do the Ed laugh.
I'd be like,
Oh yeah, that's really interesting what's going on on screen.
That was a full penta kill, I guess.
But hey, can everybody in the audience do your best
Eddie laugh?
I would be removed.
What am I supposed to do?
Switch to Ed?
Can Ed do something about the door?
Everyone's gonna be fringed.
Yeah?
Is that what happened?
Is that what's over here?
Can I break that?
I think so.
No, it's over here.
Begging you, everybody's so
upset right now.
Jump over it.
Stand tall.
The springboard move.
No.
I have to move something over there?
The jump?
Oh, wait.
Nice. Alright, now we have to go like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm almost had it. I was gonna do that
for like five minutes.
That's what I would do with like an eSports event,
and it would be like everyone would just cringe.
Alright, I'm gonna shut up.
What is
torture? I'll give you torture.
You want me to try to do no
for five straight minutes?
Of course we do.
No, you don't. You really don't want that.
look I want to leave this game but I can't this is back when licensed video
games existed and were fun so I have to do the planks still they don't they
don't make licensed video games anymore and if they do they're like accidental
games somebody just accidentally made the whole thing all right we're getting
there let me just get to the candy store and then I'll stop. Spider-man? yeah but
spi- hold on there's a difference look Batman Arkham the Arkham games are
amazing Spider-man is amazing but those I'm talking about like cartoons or TV
shows Batman isn't a solely a TV show Batman is an entire franchise of media
he's everything Ed and Eddie is just Ed and Eddie let's break this with Ed
right he's everything yeah whoo that kind of hurt my head Ed and Eddie had
movies no but they were cartoon network movies there's like a DVD that you had
they didn't get a proper theatrical movie no I know they had like a made
for TV movie I'm hurting them all right almost done okay I saw it opening
night that movie this movie doesn't exist chicken you aren't allowed to do
a lame stream after a day off what hey it's it's for me to decide what stream
I'm gonna do and what I'm gonna do it I'm not are you not allowed to do
is well what if I'm not allowed to do a stream of a game that I want to
play have you lost your mind report him to twitch he's playing Ed and
Eddie for an hour ten minutes report him wait a minute wait if you just took
a day off you can't play Ed and Eddie how dare you
now look there's a water thing over there can I go in there well I can get up
there I know you're just kidding but like still come on okay I'm just
single ed right now here we go wait no thank you thank you forcing people to
watch something literally counts as torture what am I forcing you to be
here that's like okay you're sitting in the torture chamber you're not
your arms aren't tied down I got like a drill and I'm like I'm ready to
fucking torture you your arms aren't tied there's an exit sign with the door
open and there's a sign that says welcome to the torture chamber by the
way at any moment during the procedure you can get up and leave you can just
walk out I can't believe he's torturing me you can you know you can
leave the torture room it's open that's still torture no it's not it's
yeah you know it's not why do you have a drill I'm just it's a it's a
fucking metaphor no but that's the thing I okay I have a room set up that
says this is a torture chamber when you come in here you're gonna get tortured
and you walk in well it's interesting on my like fucking Disney trip well
they have one of these there's a chair it's an open chair it says by
the way sitting in this chair you're gonna get tortured really and it's
like for real and you don't sit down this thing this thing's pretty
comfortable I come in and I say excuse me sorry I want to make sure
understand like you're gonna be tortured no I don't think I want that okay did
what you can leave the exhibit no do you want to get tortured no do you want
to leave the exhibit no this is what we do here no he's admitting the game
sucks no I'm not this game's fun I wouldn't be playing it for like an
hour all right you know what
next torture game please
yeah Kevin has a really like big chin in this game
throw it at these trash cans behind me knock them down and I'll let you
if not I have a timer in the trash can timer on the clock fuck I got a knock
them down what was supposed to do yeah this has physics on it oh fuck he I
didn't listen let's go up to busy torturing people I have to throw this
in or just knock them off I think it's just knock them off line it up I still
have time I just put one back up there
oh Las Vegas shut up hey shut up all right once I get through this section
I'm gonna take a piss and we'll change games
yeah Las Vegas will never have an NBA team
how dare you say that to me how dare you say that I mean there's like
messing around there's like joking around and then they're saying
something so reprehensible that I can't even believe it
we've got hockey we've got baseball on the way we've got football on the
way and then I could be an NBA team how dare you oh my god this is
harder than it looks and that was good throw the cans he said basketballs I
have to play by the rules he didn't say throw the cans he said throw the
basketball that was almost a strike I'll get it come on do it legit legit
legit legit legit legit legit legit give me this basketball turn and throw
it oh yeah baby legit bees oh my god get the beehives no no no no there's
that gonna okay doesn't count okay that was really like mean and rude and
bad but pick a plank that just killed Jimmy he's allergic to bees that shit
the ship right here why is Jimmy not waking up oh my god just switch your
different character for love god get off me no he's still dead this is kind
of bad I don't know what to do he's getting swarmed by bees no no all right I gotta pee
bad I can't believe you played two hours of that and Eddie the
misadventures I don't believe it cat don't know peeing alone all right one
lock at the bottom one lock at the top we just uh Resident Evil slash tank
controls Tomb Raider get this selected oh you fucking dummy here we go can I
can do it now it goes this way bingo I did another level gun gun done done
done he's allergic to jawbreaker
they filled with powder got it all right that's the third that's strike
3 hide avoid being seen by the other kids hide in certain objects with Eddie
or hide behind poles in the tower of Eddie let's see what happens when you
get by dog violent it's a stealth mission yes wait get in here really okay
these stupid fucking red squirrels he's still gone no I'm almost done this
come up before metal gear versus a metal gear reference really how do I
sneak by the dog then it's an actual stealth mission past the dog
sick sick oh it's Jimmy can I use this on him go nice surrounded by squirrels
just go by nice why is that camera doing this almost there painting about
a painting what I didn't even get a chance
I suppose even do that yeah how am I supposed to go over there there there
there that's a perfect will he come over and investigate the noise
I'm saying like see like oh okay homing yeah that was just a briefcase
from hitman easy all right we got one more what's I don't know what they're
doing over there that's weird okay so I gotta sneak by bro trash can maybe
hide in the bush or ed jump up here no no come on edge up the tower can I do
anything about that no well let's just done and a jawbreaker I'm glad Jermis
having fun because I'm not we're almost done I'm just have to move around this
the puke the fake puke that you get in the comedy thing that's it right
what oh come on perfect shot oh you don't get it again
bingo what the name of God God he's gonna pee his pants you're right
be careful didn't hit how did that not connect I like move this yes I can
hide behind it right stay with me nope I did it scam number three must be
something I ate you didn't think I was gonna do three missions out of this
game I don't campaign finish this game because I never did no that was
fun oh by the way everyone that's I forgot that my lie my lie did not work
out so well would I tell you this is like $40 game you can somebody would
have zoomed in on that I said it was $79 or something right all right let
me pass up here back we're gonna move on to another one I'll see you
in a minute we'll keep the Ed Edd and Eddie music on all right so next up
on the list I don't know if I want to do that one yet we have to say
that one for tomorrow how any of these gonna live up to Ed Edd and Eddie the
misadventures this one looks like this is called motocross mania 3 crazed
riders have turned motocross racing into an intense bloodsport where
survival in the name of the game and leash the mania in ferocious high
speed hand-to-hand combat so you drive around you get like bats and
throw people off their bikes who knows never heard of it that sounds too cool
to be true those of you that enjoyed a dad a dad Eddie I did too wasn't a
stinker like some people would tell you this is motocross mania 3 looking
forward to this and why don't we just bring you guys back what do you say I
keep thinking of that bad biker game road was a road rash it's probably a
road rash clone but I just saw the front cover and I had to get it this used to
be an Ed Edd and Eddie stream yes it did and now it's a motocross mania
stream caution there's an autosave good 2k games 2k made this I didn't hear
the noise can you restart the console please this is a horrible thing to
look at oh my god this hurts stop stop stop it
that home was that lady naked what hold on a minute wait a minute this is tea
right this is tea that was weird this game is gonna be I can't I don't want
to see anymore I bet was actually somebody naked I think saving some
data great profile enter your name a a a how about I got one for you
E and E E and E how about Ed and Eddie Ed championship single race time
trial mini games freestyle options for a second audio video options let's
just do champion chip new game difficulty I'm a wimp finished in top
four to advance challenging finishing the top three to advance we're gonna go
with the standard Mario Kart rules guys okay Jesus all leg
aggression we need the most aggressive we need a high aggression speed jumping
pretty balanced since locked locked locked there's unlockable characters
somehow the robot is that is it bigfoot aggression the highest aggression
what about the highest fighting fighting is important I think the
balanced I think Karen it's probably the most the most balanced here
fighting speed jumping the real riding a bike of reading a book yeah let's
teach you does have full aggression I mean let's kick the shit out of some
people how do I play do I get a tutorial all right X is X standings
next race woodland riot be so is 1 2 3 4 5 6 players you've been
challenged do you accept the challenge I don't know what does that even mean
do what the sentence you just told me I don't know what that means in
of racing on a motorcycle how do I do anything spin around on the
bike is there any of the moves I can do all right there she goes who's the
challenge for what okay r1 r1 and l1 everybody just did the same thing I'm
not stupid everybody did that why is there no music I don't know what about
to l2 what what happened there how am I in 5th place
okay circle is trick so don't do tricks good almost there holy shit that
guy just did like a blender move I killed that guy good first place we're
like triangle anything else why did this what happened I don't understand
why did they cut asshole you don't deserve to win this okay I made five
hundred dollars thousand sixty three I unlocked parking it be you take a day
off and you play this shit all right so we have auto shop garage next race
quit game all right we do it what about a like auto shop turn the sound
down our weapons bear paw cattle prod what is it what is a China staff I don't
understand that means flower staff hockey stick ice pick scepter crowbar
golf club ice club can throw tomahawks what's the difference used gold rose
well I don't know why well how do you isn't a rose just a rose let's
get the ice pick okay that's it I got it apparently now how do you use a rose
it's an odd wording there and next race you can go back Wow all right
championship new game would be new game that is to quit quit oh god damn
it whatever okay here we are game manager this one I mean it is a
little blurry give me some credit see next race there it is all right let's
get in first place I got my new weapon right stage two out of seven I'm gonna
beat this game ready go
did I not go through it why is it doing that what why is it pointing that
way what are you doing what oh it's six plays you have to drive through
these it's not just an indicator of the race you have to actually go through them
I went the volume for the love of God I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying I'm
trying I hope you have midnight club two or three I do not I do not there
are some secret ones here fuck you what there's so many PlayStation 2
games I got all of them all right I don't know what about armor armor okay
bike parts a new engine about new tires sure about some new brakes okay well
don't do that all right this is the last race I'm gonna do and then this
this one's kind of really it's just like what is really one thing you do
and that's this dropped viewers after Ed and Eddie yeah well I come on two
hours to do what oh you just kill each other got it is he kidding me with his
feet fucking stupid we both try to do the same thing all right that's two
takedowns I got three new weapon one more minute this is god-awful somebody
said let me just at least get to first place where is everybody oh
they're in the corner over here I'm in first I gotta stay in first place
come on don't lose this I got one good mania 15 seconds and then I'm done kill
steal how did this get the third game probably because all the games are
probably the same game and they probably just released it three times
that was motocross mania 3 oh you guys are gonna like this one that was
quick that was really quick all right let's see what my hand goes here I'm
hovering over I'm hovering right now over family feud or stuntman it's gonna be
this is a tough call I mean we're gonna do them both the return of the
bumps I'll throw family feud in here the
feud first that was motocross I don't know what it's called something about
something motocross mode god I'm sorry about your face sorry I just I just I
got I got blue in your face didn't mean to like blind you there so
there's a very real possibility this is just a game that we've already
played on P just on the console I don't think it is though this looks like a
different version I can't tell because there's no host on the back the last
one was Louie Anderson right now here we go
global star software atomic planet oh my god muck ash no family feud save
file has been detected make one eight megabytes yeah is it the same one
who's the host is it Louie Anderson it's Louie no it's not who the hell is
this guy this is Mitt Romney did Mitt Romney host family feud that family
editor we gotta make the family create or edit family new family this
used to be a Louie stream it did okay we got into family name the bump I
don't know if the bumps could make a return here we gives a new
generation the Albertsons make ed ed and Eddie no I'm not gonna do that sorry
guys don't tell me to do that what's their last name is just the Ed's okay
family name the ed's member a what what so we need ed we need somebody that
looks like which one's ed build a you can have like a big stomach it's the
tall one right I know a hair color colors his hair no beard he has a kind
of a goofy body right that's fine okay all right that's good at clothing what
does he have to close he's like this kind of this actually looks pretty
correct that's pretty close already I need a let's see let me get like an
image of him it's a green like a green jacket on it's as close as I
can get it and then like blue right belt color he didn't have a belt but
whatever no glasses okay let's make sure there's not another one now that's
good and then we got here this is why am I even doing this it's already
close there are does Ed have glasses can I put a hat on which one looks
the most like his head probably the one that was already on like this one
does he have like a does Ed have a soul patch no no no no no no no back it up
no I didn't do that when did this happen when did this happen what I
didn't select any of that we get the glasses out of there which one was it
it was like this one right I had a clothing top style it's an orange shirt
there we go how's it look just need to straight up t-shirt that's as
good as it's gonna get bottom is purple shorts there's no purple shorts I mean
red red his shorts are not red he has purple shorts of red shirt he has an
orange shirt on you guys are out of your minds he doesn't have a red shirt
no yeah you guys just fuck over here he's got orange and purple get the
glasses off does he have jewelry no okay that's good okay good and then we
need we need Eddie what just happened I went all the way back imagine being
colorblind after your day off okay family editor the heads this red shirt
I thought I'm gonna look over here anymore okay there's Ed okay here we
go Eddie Eddie has yellow and blue he's a little bit on the chunky side
okay he's got no hair he's got one long hair but he can be bald no beard look
at the clothes orange that looks pretty good well he's like more yellow he's got
a yellow shirt on I'm not sure there is like it there's only that one wait I
gotta change okay hold on wait wait wait wait I gotta change these colors
here yellow light orange blue okay belt color that doesn't matter why
somebody said why is the intro to the Macarena still playing over and over
again I'm sorry I can't do anything about it okay this that looks good okay
let's go I need to put this shirt this has to be orange like the darker
orange there we go no no no no there we go no no they both have the same
shirt on no they don't okay we're good all right now there's two more
people in the family um the fuck is this person gonna be I all right let's
go Jim it's fine it's good hair color it's good no it's fine okay last
member we got to bring back Peggy bump okay uh what did Peggy bump look like
like one of these right thank you bump with her husband Jerma and three
sons Ed and Eddie she did have green though no it was pink okay all right we
got Peggy bump that looks good the family is now done she had a skirt
we don't have to be exact it's okay fine fine fine fine fine fine fine fine
fine fine okay save that data let's play family feud not even close on
the hair they don't have the hair I wish they did I would have been so
happy about it delete family no play game standard game one player studio
one I only have one studio unlocked the Ed's standard game select family
to random create a random family choose opposing family skill level
average all right this is what you were waiting for the Mills versus the
Ed's oh my sons Ed and Eddie well you addicted to family
okay it's the same person it's all about speed here buzz in and give me
an answer as fast as you can but if it's not the top answer then the
other family will get a chance to answer as well you guys Ed's to do
better did you make Ed's all right good luck you guys we've surveyed
100 people the top answers are on the board give me the most popular answer
I know how to play something you might need a ladder to clean all right buzz
you're going to pass sometimes it's hard to think of an answer what that's
something that any would do might be a ladder to clean what do I need to clean
with a ladder um thinking time I just that's not enough time the attic the
why did it stop in five seconds I can't believe we screwed it up
here we wanted you to name something you might need a ladder to clean what
do you think Eddie is that Eddie you've gutters okay so I understand if
you if you have ten seconds to start surely that's going to be the top
answer that's a good answer but what does the survey say daughter is
number one number two ladder to clean your shelf on top of your fridge you
roof a window your windows I'm gonna go with window mitt okay let's say what
it's at let me see window I say it should be is it up there thank you
53%
the ladder to clean yeah like a shelf a shelf a shelf the shelf a shelf
something something really high up but what does the survey say there we go
it's so funny they go from family to family it's just me playing what would
you need a ladder to clean a the roof of your house the roof get up on the
roof our survey says a dog wouldn't a dog shit I'm never gonna get these
other ones one person said something there's one or two responses that was
dumb ladder to clean one person said ceiling why would you who cleans their
ceiling survey like wipe your ceiling what do you need to clean the ceiling
for what what's the one response ladder to clean ladder
your car why would you need a ladder no you spray it with a hose you have a
clean your car with a ladder what does the survey say two strikes fuck there's
one answer still up on the board one more
nobody cleans there you were asked to name your chimney you don't put a
ladder inside your fireplace and climb up your chimney that's no um god damn
it it's wrong but I have to try if it's not on the board then you will
lose control of the question survey they're not gonna get it either the
other family gets a chance to steal the points one correct answer and you
get the points all right what is it Mills family sometimes it's hard to
what did they say what's their answer they didn't even give an answer is it
the point what's number seven chandelier the three people with a
chandelier hanging in their house no guess I still I won all right how do I
fuck this up last time only three answers quick fast quick speedy blazing
quick speedy fast play play play play play let's not forget why we're here
we asked you to name another speedy for fast quick quick fast speedy speedy
let's see if it's there it is something to speed there it is speedy quick long
no longing fast quickly rapidly rapid rapid up there you've swept the board
let's see if our sweat sweep rapid thank you very much I'll take the
point what about their mitt
with these maybe should make them smarter or exciting let's double the
points and article of clothing people like to wear baggy pants is the other
family even trying they haven't answered one question the survey says
underwear I'm gonna pass it I'm gonna pass it good luck you get what else can
you wear baggy shirt and article of clothing people like to wear baggy
shirt yeah you'll get that one let's see if it's that's it though shirt
pants can't wear shoes baggy I'm wearing shoes baggies is wearing shoes
that are like four sizes too big for you you look ridiculous
and article of clothing people like to wear baggy you've decided to pass
you're allowed to do that if you want pass see this stupid the question a
baggy baggy watch I asked you to name an article of clothing people sweater a
baggy sweat in that shirt the same thing as a shirt they're not gonna get
two answers remain to the name and article of clothing people like to wear
baggy shorts that's pants this is a little too no like pants are shorts how
are they not let's carry on we wanted you to name an article of clothing people
baggy hat baggy no there's nothing else baggy jeans those are pants if it's up
there and we're fucking furious the board survey says your pants up there
three times pants jeans shorts if they're all pants they're now in the
lead I'm taking them triple points a job where a person has to be good with
teacher no no no not teach teachy teach how do I backspace let's see if
it's there well I said that I said what oh come on a
job where a person has to be good a math teacher an engineer oh my god I
gotta think of a good one they're not gonna get it engineer what's a good
pizza shop owner you need to count the pizzas and need to count and bring in
money an airplane pilot an accountant fuck you a Pokemon trainer hey guys
pissing me off he's throwing it right in my face a scientist vague bullshit
answer damn it I just lost the game banker a job where a person has to be
good with math pass sometimes it's hard to think isn't it pass it okay wait
this is our shop ready they're gonna pass it three times we've still got
pilots or left a mathematician they're not gonna get it sometimes it's hard to
think of an answer isn't it a banker cashier cashier no not a cashier a
banker answer remains a magician not a magician guess what you already have
two strikes you're not gonna get it you're gonna pass the computer's stupid
okay we want a banker a job where a person has to be good with math so
you're going to pass thank you I'll take it
passes to the other jeans chance to steal banker can you steal better make
it a good answer banker this is gonna be good banker
it's either banker or it's has to be banker all you do is count money in
count it and and do multiplications banker got it have you stolen the points
let's see ah what was it you've got 300 points let's see if you can go all
the way you've earned yourself a chance at fast money you guys played
well really well what's the I just saw the end credits what was the I
want to see the answer god worst iteration of Family Feud this is by far
the worst one of you play Klein family versus the Eds you know it's really sad
is the free virus msn.com version was better than this one I gotta win
thank you very much and welcome to the family few it's all about speed here
plus in it give me the host nobody can but if it's not we have licensing
issues the other family will get a chance to answer as well and they
might do better here we go all right good luck you guys we've surveyed 100
people the top answers are on the board give me the most popular answer
something you go without when saving money uh food no something you go
without while you save money eating out eating our food yeah food food that's
wrong food you're eating out you know you food see all right let's play this
there's one higher answer remaining going out
going out on with the show I asked you to name something you go without with
saving money cable TV oh yeah you go without Ed Edd and Eddie
I can't think of a good one let me go without while saving money sometimes
it's hard to think isn't it um expensive clothes new stuff a new car
we still got two answers left I asked you to name something you go without
with saving money cigarettes this game come out in like the 40s you've got to
be kidding me oh yeah you go without those delicious good old cigarettes yeah
you're gonna be saving money you're gonna drop those cigarettes they're so
great new clue they give one that's it are these first points of the game
yours let's see is it on the board new clothes well congratulations I have to
get the fast money
I can't go all right come on and we're ready now for the second question
someone who is famous for their blue eyes I'm not even gonna press the
button good luck there you go I don't even know who that's gonna be up
there Frank Sinatra I don't know who else would be famous or their blue
eyes good luck Elijah would bet Davis let's see if it's on the board I've
never even heard that name I would know three people said that why would it
have that Redford is it on the board Redford okay sans you don't understand
that like if family food keeps going like 50 years in the future that's
gonna be an answer see like this is like the boomer like tonight right
Robert Redford Paul Newman that'll be like sans Elijah would that'll be up
there gets the chance to play for $20,000 will they do it
get Goku yeah I'm getting swept yeah there's more up for grabs I'm doubling
the points a character who's hired to perform at a kid's party clown can I
press X what the fuck was that okay clown clown magician is it there
it's gonna be somebody vague magicians one clowns one a mascot a cartoon
character play it double points I have to magician how do you spell magician
it's like magician show we wanted you to name a character who's hired to
perform at a kid's party magician yeah magician wait no magician that's not
right is that right that's not is that right that's a good answer but what does
the survey say I don't know I just looked wrong on this game for some
reason okay magician clown balloon artist a balloon animal a a a singer here
a super a superhero spider-man no no no no no no face face painting a face
painter just face paint face painter face paint is it up there there are two
answers still up on the board superhero all right you were asked to
name a character who's hired to perform at a kid's party superhero but
superheroes aren't real that's like oh yeah you hired Batman to come yeah
Bruce Wayne and his busy schedule comes in does a fortnight dance for
your son's birthday no not Superman superhero a princess you've got two
strikes you need to do this princess actor but that princess is more
specific knowing what are you doing princess if it's not on the board then
you will lose control of the question let's see if it's on there has to be
number two are the points safe or will some light fingers lift them one
correct answer and you get the points princesses get hired to come Barney
right if it's there you've stolen the points I already lost here you come can I
see the other one it's a shame we can't have two winners Barney I have to I
have to beat it I'm sorry I have to do this once character that comes I
gotta remember this is what year the 2002 or something right 2006 Barney
was still popular 2006 it's time for the family few are you ready to play
skip it's still popular now gotta think quickly here to give me a good answer
as fast as you can get the top answer and you can choose to play or
pass if not the other family gets where's the lightning round thing I
have to win okay I've lost twice in a row 100 people were surveyed and
their answers are on that board you just have to tell me what they are a
state where it hardly ever snow Las Vegas is it there is it on the board it
really doesn't ever snow it snows once every 10 years there's a state
where it hardly ever snows you're going to pass sometimes it's hard to
think of an answer it never snows on the moon California but that answers
remain I asked you to name a state where it passed twice if Arizona's up there
and the bad is not up there they're literally right next to each other
okay wanted you to name a state where it hardly ever snows Florida yeah is
it up there now what's number one what would number one even be
California Texas you're gonna get number one is it up there why why he's
already up there Texas is not number one California
New Mexico a state where it hardly ever snows not just some places in
California that's all the time they're not gonna get the last pass Louisiana
let's see if you've won the first points of the game let's see if our
survey agrees why would you ever guess that Nevada gets the AI if it
doesn't have the answer in the bank I'm gonna beat this fucking game no I'm gonna
I'll be I will win I'm gonna win I promise no Alaska Antarctica it's
Antarctica right ant arc Antarctica Antarctica Antarctica and arctic is it
on the board it's not up there the survey says pass or play it's your
choice you're going to pass it's not a they passed it all right
you find ice Alaska we're gonna think just a dumb shit okay um this place
you find ice the North Pole let's see if it's there North Pole Alaska in the
freezer that's you guys are going you're wrapping around to meta there we just
have a raid come in Joel just came in with a raid thank you so much welcome
everybody we're playing we're playing PlayStation 2 games actually his
freezer what welcome best thank you Joel hope you had a good stream I'm
we're gonna do our game or challenge here soon have to get in contact all
right freezer it's Iceland no that's incorrect it's Greenland Greenland's the
place with ice Iceland's the one that's nice the ice felt green let's
see if it's there why did I think it was an a it's just seeing it on this
menu is freaking me up I wanted you to name a place you'd find ice Siberia
Canada Canada's pretty good survey says Canada oh god damn it's freezer North
Pole Alaska Canada I thought it would be there Norway maybe Iceland but
Icelanders I see do or die situation Russia I wanted you to name a place
you'd find ice Russia in a cooler if it's cooler it better not be cooler if
it's there you're still alive otherwise the other family gets a chance to steal
survey says are the points safe or will some light fingers lift them one
correct answer and you get the points what is it let's see what and you go
reaching your word bank at the supermarket no fuck this game get the
points it's not there it's there mood you have where would you have
the ice freezer and supermarket is one into 66 people out of a hundred said
like the literal term of ice like the ice is at the store there and it's
inside of the thing that makes ice moods keep stay ice nobody said like
Iceland green green ways Chicago no Canada no the North Pole isn't up
there something you buy when having a fourth of July party hamburgers burgers
cheeseburgers what does the AI want me to say cheeseburger no fireworks let's
guarantee good our survey says red is gonna be so specific barbecue food
it's gonna be do I pass this I don't know this probably with one or two
specific things there hot dogs hamburgers we wanted you to name
it's gonna be one dumb thing something you buy what having a fourth of July
party alcohol yeah beer let's do beer time to see what the board says yeah
nobody bought nobody buys beer for a fourth of July party three answers
remain all right I asked you to name out of a hundred people something you
buy when having a fourth of July party did they ask anybody in this
country the United States I'm surprised a hundred out of a hundred is not
beer hot dog let's see if our survey agrees hot dog okay firecracker hot dog
burgers
okay I'm gonna write burger that's a catch-all burger I'm to see what the
board says one more strike and you'll lose control of the break there are
still up on the board no beer no burgers this for the July party sucks can we go
home grill a soda if it's soda soda get this and you're still alive if not
you lose control is it there you do here you don't have any drinks you
don't have any hamburgers answer no food no beverages what what is this
place a flag let's see if you've taken the points you've got let's see if you
can go all the way you're moving on to fast money it's harder than it
looks damn it I have fucking when I have to win at least one of these I
don't care no beer did you see our flag though what we don't just sit
in a room and read a book we have uncooked hot dogs just sitting on a
plate in front of everybody while we all do like a seance what are we doing
there what are you proving by winning this shitty game no I want to do the
lightning round it's time for the family few are you ready to play I
am all right all right this is the one this is the one but if it's not the top
answer then the other family will get a chance to answer as well and they
might do better all right good luck you guys we've
surveyed 100 people the top answers are on the board is there I've played
family feud in my life before it's gonna be like fart we're like burp fart
burp survey said okay fart burp sneeze I will get this one let's not forget
here we asked you to name the most unromantic thing a man can do in bed the
youtuber answer how is that a youtuber answer that's a real answer that's I'm
seeing what people would have said burp the survey says go through all
the bodily functions fart burp sneeze
the most unromantic thing a man can do in bed smell is smell bad cry and to
see what the board says and you'll lose control of the question really I
thought it would be there one of the number one and two things there are
three that's unromantic farting and crying in bed the most unromantic
thing a man can do all right oh how about crying because you fart sneeze
watch TV sneeze snow snore snore that's pretty good
survey says fart snore burp
talk eat eat in bed is unromantic don't people like feed each other
strawberries and shit there it is eat fart snore burp sneeze I'm gonna I've
been saying sneeze this whole time I'm gonna try sneeze it's either sneeze
or TV watching TV or it's sneeze okay let's see if you're the first off
the start line is it up there one more strike and you'll lose control of the
question it's pee it's not peeing in bed there's one answer still up on the
board get it right or it's your third strike cough all right on with the
show we asked you to name the most unromantic thing sleep it's why would
sleep be up there sleep is you're in bed you're gonna sleep in the bed
it's cough or or it our TV or oh good thing I caught that watch TV I don't
know smoking in bed a chance to steal let's see if our survey it's not
smoking in bed
smoke points be stolen get this right and the points are yours now don't
even tell how dare you so going to sleep in a bed is not romantic no it's
a it's a basic human function that we all do when we get into bed what are
you talking about who did they ask these questions something you'd seen a
coffee table magazine sleeping isn't romantic is it supposed to be the
survey says good answer but it's not the most popular book let's see if it's
there coffee mug 27 versus 26 I hate this game
decision time play or pass okay yeah good gone I asked you to name
something you'd see on a coffee table coffee candy I have never seen
that survey say in my whole life no one has ever had just a bunch of candy on
their coffee table I've never seen that this is Halloween maybe during
Halloween an ashtray right I forgot this is like 2003 just put cigarettes
picture that's a good answer but what does the survey say you don't have a
little candy bowl on your coffee table you're you are you really living your
best life they just fucking destroyed it they just destroy they demolished
this whole thing we get one thing wrong I have to double it up and I just have
to win average difficulty my ass this is double more up for grabs I'm
doubling the points the first song a kid learns how to play on the piano
I have no idea I don't know chopsticks let's see if it's there I don't want to
play this though this is so specific
chopsticks what's the one that goes didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't
didn't didn't didn't didn't did it was that called heart and soul yep you
know I know this because this is the song that I learned how to play when I
was 11 that's a good answer but what does the survey say I can't even
imagine how that's not on there five answers remain that's the song that
yeah that's a song everyone learns to play everyone first song a kid
learns how to play on the piano twinkle twinkle little star no I
twinkle what to do the whole thing twinkled twinkle okay twinkle twinkle
twinkle hot cross buns Mary had a little lamb little lamb okay yeah it's so easy
right little lamb please win one little lamb the survey says all right two
strikes great answer I'm afraid hot cross buns is that the only one I can
think of there are four answers still up on the board you've got two strikes
you need to do this hot cross buns to name the first song a kid learns how
to play on the piano never gonna beat this game hot cross buns if it's not on
the board then you will lose control of the question cross buns is it on the
board but it would be there the other three blind mice to steal the points
old McDonald on the piano really have you stolen the points let's see
it's gonna be there has to be that why wouldn't it be there yeah old
McDonald out of fun on the piano okay so Mary lamb already wrote I wrote that
one ABC's you don't a ABC's on the piano who learned their ABC's on the
piano ABCDEFG how do you even do that on a piano it's my last chance all
points are now multiplied by three Twinkle Twinkle EFG H I J K L M N O P
what the fuck what was it was it I don't know I was mmm my god I was too
busy reciting I don't know what this is I can get it what guys help me what
was it I can get this what was the question phone what was the question
phone is it there yes phone some hang some people hang their clothes the
phone a hat so you're going to play a painting I asked you to name got it
triple points something that people hang up picture painting let's go with
picture done let's see if it's on the board that's triple points right
did I win we're gonna play one more round all right I got it what wins this
win the whole thing
yeah the last round is the only one that matters fuck time to pull out all
the stops one is it's sudden death we only have one answer on the board
for this round whoever buzzes in quickest and tells me what that
answer is we'll go through to fast money something you can swallow without
chewing water go um gum a pill pills it's not gonna be pills no is that it
it's kill our survey says yes finally I can play fast money you guys we need two
of you for fast money who's gonna be going to be one of the eds wait okay
we need we need ed a smart one and then me the two smartest people on
team fast money I'll ask you five questions in 20 seconds try to give me
the most popular answer if you can't think of anything say pass and we'll
come back to it if we can if you get 200 points you'll get $20,000 here we go
finally appreciate this the clock will start after I read the first question
name a famous male who wears tights Robin Hood it's in the title Robin
Hood a crime you think is easy to get away with um a crime it's easy to
get away with dot taxes no that's not easy um crime it's easy to get away
with stealing taxes no I don't know what's not no crime is easy to get
stealing stealing um speedos the timer long wheeze I can't I couldn't fucking
believe it I don't know how it's possible to type all that in thanks for
the time asked you to name the body part that people like to have shoulders
I would have said shoulders you answered our survey says I wanted you
to name a fish a restaurant might feature as catch of the day a tuna salmon
haddock survey says it doesn't matter what it is I'll get it through the
board please how am I gonna do this you need 107 points to win the big
money all right Robin Hood I'll ask you the same five questions you can't
duplicate the answers if you do you'll hear this sound I will say try
yes Peter Pan Shakespeare because it's harder you get 25 seconds to give me
your answers okay here we go give me 25 seconds on the clock
please the clock will start after I read the Superman name a famous male
who wears tights real or fictional Peter Pan a crime you think is easy
easy to get away with loitering littering something you shouldn't wear
after you turn speedo shoulders people like to have massage and tuna tuna or
halibut haddock cod had a halibut you were asked to name a famous male
who wears tights one guy wrote halibut in the chat and I don't know
why I fucking listen to him I was gonna write Tuna I mean come on
littering is pretty easy to get away with survey says two L's I mean two
T's oops something you shouldn't wear after you turn speedo that's pretty
high shoulders is gonna be 60 has to be number one answer let's see if it's
there what the fuck has catch of the day you said no it's not a halibut it's
like Tuna
I don't play that one anymore it was family feud okay now we're gonna move
on to jaws jaws unleashed this game's crazy but before we do that I gotta pee
again it's one of the sometimes I don't know what it is some nights I'll have
to pee once in nine hours and then some nights like tonight I gotta pee
every like 45 minutes it's not like I'm doing anything different I don't know
why doesn't make any sense caffeine makes you pee I drink coffee
pretty much every day though so there's a game that I don't know if I
want to do today we might just do with I might just do this whole thing
tomorrow and force myself to beat this game this is a game that is
timed not this one but tomorrow I think I'm just gonna hate myself and
play this one this is a PlayStation 2 game that you have 12 hours to beat
the game and I think it's gonna be one of those Simpsons hit-and-run torture
scenarios there's a countdown dead rising no not dead rising it's called
without warning and apparently there is a clock that is 12 hours in the
game or something so well I'm gonna leave that for tomorrow well I don't
know maybe I got like a couple of great things to play too yeah see
look ready I'll just show it to you just for fun so this is it it's a
Capcom game see here without without warning all right and if you look at the
back you have see no time for second chances you have 12 hours to beat the
game what's fucking happening like killed you just take down a whole
building um this is gonna be great all right bear back I gotta pee hello
there everybody what do we got sorry press start new game extras is there
gonna be a full-motion video right let's watch the whole movie right now
it's too bad trailer or I don't know whatever this is I couldn't I don't
I couldn't even see what that said it was such a mess of the fun
I don't think that's another language play this game I'm infected they do
like a like a gotcha we're gonna do like a prank video thing
ready T for teen their world is beyond perfection race is near extinction their
hope is in her hands alias how is he on flux okay what about this one Oh Tim
what's his name super Bucky Island at a unique summer camp for the
paranormal gift young cadets are taught to perfect their powers games
like I don't make him look really bad I don't think I want to see the whole
trailer I got you got you go you troll a chatter epic style welcome to
Amity Island this year promises to be better than ever
Seal Island continues to be a great attraction that ball especially with a
reasonable increase in its population Jesus and new partnerships with
corporations such as and Byron Plus will allow us to open our doors to even
more visitors are they dropping like a bomb down here what how can you be
that hungry I don't understand sharks they're always shown eating and
devouring dozens and dozens of things no one's that hungry
Steven Spielberg played the clarinet once on a beach what does that sound
what what information is that giving me Steven Spielberg played first clarinet
for one of the beach scenes oh okay press and hold X to swim discover all
nine tutorial messages for a bonus can I attack like the current is too
strong okay press r1 to bite prey prey will appear on the sonar as
yellow dots when eating prey your health the red bar on the hood will
increase so r1 is bite prey is red increases health poisonous what was
wrong with that okay I eat a little goldfish yep we're gonna find more
tutorial messages just keep swimming this way I don't really need that it's
right here hell's that license plate is like a secret or something okay eat
it I just was trying to you collected a license plate there are a total of 45
collect them all for a secret I don't think I'm gonna do that these seals
press and hold r1 to bite and hold a victim in your mouth Jesus when
holding a victim in your mouth rapidly move the left stick and left and right
to tear them apart let's see what happens it's terrible I'm gonna move on
that's still I don't like that I don't like ripping up otters hold
down l1 to fill your charge attack me to release l1 in order to
perform this move you headbutt objects using this technique right on
the boat you will learn you earn points from destroying property as a
person in this boat and eat the guy right oh absolutely come here see in my
mouth still that was fucking ridiculous okay l2 is to charge your tail whip
use it on this diver cage is still alive in there get him out there is
the sea seeker on the ocean floor is making you hungry destroy it to
stop your hunger from being drained if your hunger meter which the green
bar is completely drained you will begin to lose health so you have to eat
and that thing down there needs to be destroyed up there are other sharks
fighting me right now okay eat the guy eat the scuba diver ripped his leg off oh my god that's
terrible somehow he's still alright I didn't do that my other shark
colleagues did that I didn't we've done a tail whip this guy and I tail
his head off kind of did I catch him in midair let's keep going points of
interest such as the sunken ship appears green squares on your sonar eat
the diver in the cage main objectives appear as a red circle on your sonar
that wasn't it I still got him we're gonna kill the diver you're in
trouble you're in trouble it's a little wonky but you know it's just
that was a lot of blood for one person that was like 30 people worth of love
destroy that thing manually moving a camera is kind of annoying it's
inverted I'm not killing it I got it should be it right so what's the red
thing here I'm gonna eat something come here food let's go down maybe
is this something like a diver in here or did I not eat the scuba diver I
heard a scream oh let's draw the boat here let's just crash the boat
sinking right I'm gonna destroy the underwater robot then oh I thought I
already did that apparently not I thought I crushed it already author
Peter Benchley was thrown off the set after objecting to the climax okay
cool little tidbit I was shown the objective in the cutscene what do I do
well you've sat there for like a two straight minutes trying to break the
thing and I thought I broke it swim by the beach to attack swimmers to turn
smart camera off press R3 to enter first person press R3 button once more
okay it's a first person so when a victim is on the surface tap R2 to
drag them under without being spotted my god this is horrible he's
like puking up blood look what I got all right now eat him that's fucking
terrible you think you're safe did you save on the beach oh shit I gotta get
back in the shark is gone you come back in I gotta time it I guess fell
down I gotta go hide I gotta go hide hide hide just go hide they'll come
back use the laser beams on your head
she likes this way how do I kill these people let's reset back here they still
see me going to water I'm now stealth that's green see the turtle come here
all right well let's keep going boat right here and crush the boat I can't
any people on this boat no get the seals wait what's this license plate
I got a thousand points for that eat eat eat eat eat she faces you actually level
up in this game I just jump up there I kind of can feel like I already blew
this though maybe not invisible wall well I'm not certain what I need to do
maybe I have to just restart holy shit okay that's cool
restore checkpoint maybe what is the latest checkpoint this is not the
beginning of the game is it destroy the peers okay she's still live this is
definitely one of those games that had a set of mature rating
that guy on fire this is rated it's rated holy shit why'd you just come in
I actually don't really I don't like this game it's too much it's it's scary
the underwater screams sounds so horrible now now you fuck it's just
not nice I need a better camera that was a first person it's easier so now
what's left just destroy more of the pier fuck this restaurant apparently
yeah destroy the whole building wait this person dead I think so see this
glowing red objects something I need to do to destroy them specifically just
take on the supports there it goes destroy the inflatable rafts
walking towards the shark is probably not the best idea
I hate to tell you this but I'm trying to get away this is very sad
this fucking assault rifle this camera is gonna make a few more other
raft right here right
keep an eye out there it is do I get to do this I just crosscheck that guy what
a snipe this bad ending now you can upgrade your abilities okay accuracy
jaws ability to successfully hit a target near afar power is jaws ability
inflict damage speed hunger I'm gonna probably say power I would do power
first I thought I just tried to I mean sure I tried to press right or left
what you just lock yourself I don't think so the breakout where are they
bringing me I just killed like 15 people you're gonna tie me up and
bring me to an attraction how would you ever bring jaws here see down it
this is where they make the shark's own great white shark on display for the
tourists this is going to cause crowds in record numbers mayor our research
tank can hold the shark but we are not prepared to display him in the show
room tank nonsense the word has already spread give the people what
they want Brody mr. mayor I understand you captured a shark by the
code that him my son was killed by a shark there damn thing ripped right
through the cage I demand you kill that creature immediately
all right fine we'll kill him just scan my fucking poison the electrify the
water key card find an ID card open the gate I found one let me in there when
you be shitting your pants if you saw this this guy's just walking back and
forth like nothing that's so loud and obscene why are there people in here
are these people cleaning the tank are these fish I don't I can't tell
what these are go this way that scientist definitely has an ID card why
oh why would you ever do this this is the worst scary thing ever is it just
running from me you have like a chain link fence what oh shit come here get
in the water where are we can I have your key card please get in the
water get in the water get in the water oh fuck okay the guy with the
key card it's a stingray all right scientist with me
drag him into the water okay now you fucked give a key card that's fucking
disgusting just shot me no it's this guy right here key
card no key card why would you still be walking around
I mean yeah the map is showing me this door but I need a key card to go in this
door one of those scientists has a key card I guess I can't really do
anything about that I have to just yeah I have to drag a scientist to the
door I can't take a key card and put it in my pocket I'm about to go in
a cage come with me come on no don't go in the cage how am I not in the
water get in the water go oh my god why are you doing this get in the
water for the first time we get a first try I got stuck on top of the cage all
right where are you any scientists just come here all right back it up to the
door where's the little there's a little thing I have to where's that
little things the device right isn't there like a little the hell is it
right it's over there he's dead in here somewhere is he alive oh puke
controls my god where the hell's another scientist come here open the
door all right now eat this motherfucker all right we're good that's not an
entryway no no get back in the water don't stay in the water don't stay out
of the water oh god I have to stay in first person no I don't that's even
worse what I need to do here is there another scientist I have to grab
just jump over the fence this is a bad idea is it water over here I don't
think this water over there this is an elevator oh what's up with this
way please why would you make a game with a scale this large and all right
what the fuck am I supposed to do I can break through the glass anymore I can
things I can break I got a stellar view right now that's actually pretty
awesome now I destroy I have to destroy the whole park can I get a fucking
rock well we got him easy he's dead he's had to make him run his head into
the wall come on come on where's the checkpoint gonna be okay next not yet
not yet almost not yet though I got his leg you
smash this can't break that the thrill of murder is too much room I'm stuck
again fight all the sharks my health is good come on now I thought that guy was
gonna get away they should have that guy jump let me catch him in my mouth
Rob Schneider do what it happened Rob Schneider was the one that was in
the shark costume that makes sense I guess now I miss that guy right now
where your health is low Wow break this thing let me through I've died
break break break do it do it break let me in it's the underground lab I
break out of here yeah I can what door is that hey everybody welcome to the
show damn it let's go through the great you can fit through that come on I got
full health now it wants me to go through here what is that oh shit
here comes an actual fight who wins jaws or the killer whale what is that
you proceed three thousand points there you go oh fuck he's got my leg all right
let's go into the dive grab his tail why is he faster than me
no wait wait wait you've unlocked an adventure move body bomb charge tech
out of the water and quickly push up to perform this move nice sweet there
we go now I know body bomb dead kicking my ass I get him right
stomach in his belly his belly flip this is more nausea inducing than the
VR games I'm tearing him apart though oh hey food no shit get out of the way
out of the way out out out out right here come here with that food go no
shit damn it I had to work up a good thing of the web cams on is this
you're gonna this is gonna be a puke on stream I gotta flip them the game has
first-person mode and it's yeah I can't play in this mode fuck am I
actually gonna throw up to jaws what is going on it's like the frame rate
too I can feel it my skin is heating up you know that feeling when your
skins heating up and you're gonna throw up I gotta be Shamu though I can't throw
up hold on your mouth is watery and my mouth is getting a little it is
getting a little watering my skin's heating up I have that like metallic
taste in my mouth I don't know why this game is doing it it's just like
the frame rate and the colors oh no never ever hear the end of that I
can't okay here we go slow I'm leaning back in my chair far back in my chair
trash can no sorry I have a cup here I have like at least a two and a half
serving coffee cup here he's hurt no it's the way to stop going above
water how do I look do I look a little green what stop going above the
water does it have to that's what half the motion sickness for me is when the
game just makes it go above water when I move that give me a fish anybody
where do you even come from after this boss fight it's really rewarding this
game is fun I feel like I need to be playing on TV across the room I'm
gonna go across the room what I got it that's not in the game right
food I need audio I can't do this without audio first person doesn't
work I didn't even get behind me where was he
catches me in his mouth every I don't have any food left ah this dolphin kills
me I'm smashing the PlayStation 2 with my fists cute I can't just see where I
am they cheering me on so he's just one of the water why would you come
in the water here
hey when it does that that that like the flash I don't beat this like
fast cut him off from the side that's us think I'm just gonna tell if he that
kind of pushes you away though I can't talk I'm sorry ah now he's chasing me
I'm not I'm not going above the water the game just makes me do that if I
draw if I had a choice I wouldn't be doing it my fucking god I swear to
fucking god I need to go eat another fucking animal and the other den ah I
have to beat this whale I refuse I'll throw up on screen that's against
terms of sir that was that turn around there give me another seal god
all right this is it just fucking kill him it shouldn't be taking this
long let's go above water and have it splash and flash you go done I've
done there is no real threat to the safety of our vacationers or the
citizens of Amity I assure you that we are doing everything within our power
to deal with this issue the mayor is absolutely correct the thread is minimal
and we'll soon have the shark tracked and captured with the use of our
Aurora to research vessel say what you want but mr. mayor we have too
much invested to be careless until the beast is captured or better yet
killed my employees will be on alert and Brody you better get to him before I
do if you want him alive sure I'd like to save my progress four percent it's a
long game open ocean spaghetti please select press
select in order to access the map of Amity Island the column of light
indicates a side challenge I'm so slow now side challenges appear as white
triangles on both the map and the radar the activate side challenges by
swimming into the boot each side challenge consists of three difficulty
levels completing each level will earn you points for jaws abilities do you
complete a level of a side challenge checkpoint will be saved my voice has
changed this is a save anchor there are three save anchors located around
Amity Island swimming into these anchors allow you to save your
progress re-enter completed missions it's a red is a mission so that open
world now it's kind of that's really cool can I grab that out of the air
you're going jet skis I could jump out of the water and grab the
helicopter out of the air that's outrageous do you want to enter this
stage dead of night no not yet take a look around
it's underneath me let's go is he dead not quite now you are he was
trying to get away I love that I'm still driving half a second they do in it on
the jet ski let's do the mission I'll try it yeah let's see what it is what's
next don't see there's so many I got such a list there's so many
PlayStation 2 games that still are here can you hear how many clicks mayor
our research clearly indicates the subsonic frequencies used by Shaw's
underwater seaseeker machines are having a dramatic effect on the local
shark population it's causing them to approach human settlements and to
become increasingly more violent listen Brody I don't know what they play
Spyro institutions are you studied but you're beginning to sound like your
dad you're crying wolf and barn plus is bringing in millions of our
community the machine stay the Amity shark tournament begins tomorrow and
odds are they will catch the shark before anything else happens that's
what you think find a way through the netting screw the little robots one
drone down get the other one drones down destroy this giant plug okay that's
good on the side baby here bring it down
now start electrifying the group sneak up on the swimmers stealth kill some
Oh it's like a beach party eat so that you don't want to alert all the others
right from my understanding how would you not hear that scream oh Jesus
didn't have a leg he's sinking to the bottom destroy the party goers
boats who brings like a shotgun to a party that is that my shotgun what the
fuck are you doing sorry they have like sniper rifles that is a huge machine
gun shoot me from under the jawbreaker tin can I'm not a scene
that's not a party boat that's a police boat make it I have to stop
they're gonna stop playing this game yeah I'm sorry we're gonna move on to
this game's fun I gotta get up I just stopped I'm just gonna get some water
I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I just like I get out of here I gotta get some
water I'm not fuming I'm fine I mean you maybe you can tell from my
voices some might be wrong but everything is completely fine I have
absolutely no problem at all I just have to get up and get some water and
I'll be good to go to stream for like another hour or two
that's a joke voice by the way everybody that's a joke hey guys what's going on
I totally just hurled no I just went I went down to grab some water and Alex
and Kim are both downstairs I just kind of stumbled and I walked in like
this was like I walked in just like hey just went over to the fridge and
like open it like water in here it's just like you all right yeah yeah I'm
fine it's like almost puked like what the fuck are you talking about all right
we're gonna put another one I'm sorry I can't play this one anymore that's so
unfortunate but it's true let's move on what was the closest I got to
puking right here I don't know what this one is but I'm gonna play this
one is called headhunter headhunter why is everybody doing that face what's
with the face oh this is the P okay the startup noise I get you I understand
motion sickness puke or limb ripping puke motion what happened what the
fuck is going on here hold on that's odd there's definitely a motion sickness
thing I don't know what this game is head hunters I may have accidentally
purchased this and don't do to initialize I do no no oh whatever I
got stuck at five minutes into this game well that's good rich guy buys a
game on accident
normal to the action button press the X button to interact open door gun mode
in shooting press and hold the R1 button to raise your weapon press X to
shoot okay I this one has potential well in gun mode tap the square button
to cycle between available targets hold the square button and push the left
or right button on the left analog stick to manually just aim of the
green enemies take damage from your gun what's wrong with me right now I
think I've been sapped well and gun tap all right ah let's wake up take
it easy buddy it was the puke all right so well and go tap the square
button to cycle to available targets so you hold square to manually adjust the
aim sure I see now shoot that guy in the back kind of back guy in the back
guy in the back excellent dumb there we go the
guy's name is Jack Wade enter gun mode tap the circle button to change
target to an object gray enemies will only take damage from explosions right
well apparently these my enemies watch out I think I understand the game
wall mode and shootouts triangle when standing close to a wall to move
along the wall so you hold R1 while you're on a wall or you press and
hold R1 when standing by a corner to quickly turn on this triangle
button again to let go the wall wall running I'm not sure that's what
this is but still pretty cool pretty cool yeah that's just taking cover
press and hold L1 did I missed a bunch of community subs I did Herbert gave
ten community subs thank you but the ten community subs appreciate it so
this is how you take cover and this is a dodge roll
it's fine it's fine it's fine did you miss every shot it sucks no hey hey wait
wait wait wait no don't you must have just got to the channel you don't
think I'm fucking idiot no no no it's yeah I almost just threw up like
five minutes ago I was puked and just sapped all my mental energy and now
I'm just trying to subject trying to survive now the hell donate organs
on location make sure you don't roll I got to have a gun why would you dodge
roll rip the oxygen thing out of the back of his head oh my god all right
automatic pistol let's go shoot him okay I got how do I reload manual
reload is what triangle I don't think there is a manual reload reload the
gun terrible time crisis wait wait wait wait wait what what did I learn
right there's nobody here nothing no no that reload the gun I shot every
bullet above that guy's head everyone I'm gonna die just wait till
closer what why did I die I have no idea what killed me I don't have any idea I'm
starting to get a little unhinged though was I bleeding maybe I was
bleeding got it nice keep on stupid I did the same thing reload good okay so
far so good here comes come on up one down what even there's no time
anything got it doing a lot of checking your voices I think I shoot myself in
the fucking head what the hell was that what okay that just freaked me the
fuck out this is probably from one decade earlier I freaked out am I the
old lady am I waking up okay solid five please I can't remember patients
name is Jack Wade found unconscious in the parking lot industrial your name
week ago in and out of metabolic coma the past three days gunshot trauma to
the leg evidence of some advanced surgery surgery what surgery and
apparent retrograde amnesia suggested therapy controlled am I in the same
room with you you can't just talk to me mental stimulation that's fucking
Christopher Stern real action figure of the ACN was buried today in Arlington
National Cemetery among the mourners distraught Angela Stern was comforted
by Alan Sharpe the elected ACN vice president yeah you can't throw in
why is he a computer-generated person and I'm honored to build on the
foundations he laid decades of criminality have been reversed organized
crime is in retreat but we can do much more closer cooperation between the ACN
and biotech will allow ever greater control over criminals suspects and
those thinking criminal you just save a lot of money by doing full motion
cutscenes is only just beginning like live cutscenes meanwhile the bait still
rages over who was responsible for Stern's assassination many pointing the
finger at self-styled dawn Emilio full KB CBS thought to have links
let's get twice as soon
why is this on the news?
at the top of the headhunter league however Hank Redwood bringing in three most wanted spurs fifth
successive number one ranking Redwood's had his critics but it seems there's
no question now that he's second best you you were the best way do I know
you I love this maybe this will be in this room for a while Smith and
Easton's stimulator ENP automatic clips I like riding a bike I'm chief Frank
Hawk and you Wade were my number one headhunter eight years top of the
league more captures than the rest of them put together I'm a regular hero
and now you're fired for life sorry Wade but it's orders they don't even
think his body is just huge times are changing maybe if we knew what happened
to you you're asking the wrong guy that's too bad
you could go independent you'd have to pass the Leila test wouldn't give
access to classified files but it'd be a start back to school huh with an ENP
gun in your hand and it could be worse contact me when you got your Leila
license word of warning you've woken up with quite a few enemies I
wouldn't trust anyone you don't know and right now you don't know
anyone all right so I'm erased from all of humanity and don't exist so what's
the goal here get back to number one then there's just a plot of no more
heroes I would have loved if she was an actual actress in the virtual world
Angela why didn't they do that you know my name I watch TV Christopher
Stern's daughter I saw your father's funeral I'm sorry it's in Boston I so
am I father I want you to help me mr. Wade I want you to find the man who
killed my father I want Don Fulci to be sorry too how do you know it was
done Fulci he hated my father and everything he stood for call it a
hunch why don't you tell it to the ACM they want to see him behind bars I
want to see him dead I'm not an executioner oh come on you don't know
what you are executioner retrograde fuck you again remember outside of the
killer you were the last person to see my father alive his diary shows you
had a meeting with him you were working together on some kind of
secret project find my father's killer and maybe you'll find out what
happened to you I'll think about it don't think too long I'd say medical
expenses are running at a kidney donation already you can spend the rest
of your life hunting low lives or crack the case of the decade for a handsome
fee how handsome 2 million on delivery of 2 million what about in
advance 2001 that was like 50 million assets are frozen until my father's
case is closed you'll have to trust me I heard that before just remembered
that's a good sign get well soon Jack and when you do come pay me a visit
okay so is there a break out of hospital scenario here some place you
have here I grew up in this house it seemed real big and exciting then but
now I'll get us an ex-must take a look around daddy's ACN stuff could
the different branch of the X-Men is she really telling everything about her
past contact us for complete PPFD exam what can I have control again
examine the house Swyborgs pretty much our top scientist a refugee from
communist times he developed from communist times the ACN might have
lost its war against crime okay daddy was worried about some of the big
brother stuff biotech is developing but Alan's gung-ha was my gamer my father's
Layla certificate he insisted on taking the same tests as his men Layla
tests left headhunters upgrade their license so they can get bigger cases
and better equipment you're gonna need to get a license before a license to
I'll give it a try some said there's something wrong with his ass it kind of
doesn't look like he has just one butt cheek there's one giant circle butt
cheek is that what you're talking about I'm just somebody somebody brought
it up an agent's handbook the ACN Bible its history philosophy codes of
practice my father wrote every word there's background on the standard
weapon types too may want to refresh your memory next time you lay hands on
an EMP gun all right I have to examine every single item in this room my
father and the president were at Harvard together after the military
daddy went into industry used his money to finance the president's
election the new penal code privatized law enforcement the ACN it's
all stuff they dreamed up when they were students okay anything else you'd
like me to look at the jukebox can I get a closer look at this painting is
there like a first person okay hope there is that's okay that does not it
looks very different this is a haunted photo demon baby all right I think we
can get out here maybe Angela must have the key card from Angela I can
explore the mansion still hang on pool I don't think I can go in the
unfortunately training I have a health bar in here key card yeah even look at
the the mini map is metal gear giant safe give me the key card I want to get
out of your dumb house why would it I don't want to do that oh god fine I'll
look at your legs father's diploma your father's certificate your father's
medical license tell me all about it
then I found out I had a talent for it computers technology so much for all
those ballet classes all right can I believe give me your key card you okay
fine all right all right all right all right down here inside of a dash of a
car doesn't do anything for me speed racer the real-life movie then they
make one of those are they making one of those they're making one soon
none of this shit matters kitchen what is this your father was a full motion
video game actor that's cool I guess oh look there there it is my father used
to take these yeah my father used to take adrenaline and scream at him at a
wall he used to take adrenaline and see how long he could hold his breath
underwater he did it for nine and a half minutes one time okay oh my god
what else do you want me to do I have no mr. painting in here this one
okay there it is I mean I just had an indicator on it how'd you know that that's
me daddy and Alan Sharpe Alan was from the wrong side of the tracks daddy
took him under his wing paid his tuition put him through college fast
tracked him into the ACN called him the son he never had when you're a
kid hearing that kind of hurts later Alan and we were an item dad hey there's
the key card good use it to get in and out through the garage feel free all
right there drinks I thought there were three cheeseburgers on there I
don't know why I thought they would just burgers before you go I have
something to show you down in the garage really you can use my bike to
plus one letter grade possibly but it still works I hope so nice bodywork for
a relic that'd be amazing the Leila testing facilities are located here
time to go get that license Jesus sin guess it's a while since you've been
in the saddle come on let me drive the motorcycle X must oh yes yes yes this
open-world like you can't turn skill points you have to understand this is
impossible to drive it look it's almost like I'm lagging and I'm pressing there
I need to prove this everybody is people gonna think I'm doing this on
purpose you guys need to know this is not on purpose watch this ready did
you see that trying to get ready so far so good what happened there good
turn good turn why does the road end did you see that I don't I just I
don't improve it already did an ID check what was the ID check for I
went the wrong way I'm getting skill points though that's good ID check
access level none access granted would that mean access denied power drink
all right where we going from here there are other cars have an
indicator on the map I don't think you can get an accident you can't no
there is no such thing as car accident no one gets hurt anybody
remember where we were supposed to go select no earn 250 skill points then go
to Lila and obtain a license that's it just get points okay I'll try and
tricks this is where I got stuck as a dumb kid all right go to Lila you got
it we should supermarket this feels like a mobile game this feels worse
than a mobile game games in the newspapers are more fun right here how
do I get a good turn into this corner here right in here all right I'll go
through here is there another entrance I can't just go over that all right
please make this worth my while I had such patience so far so good but
this is like number one hero right Jack wait is that living greed sorry what
you don't remember me boy that hurts Hank Redwood professional headhunter you
and me we were real close I was number one you were right up there
at second best only not everyone saw it that way till now maybe they'll
change their minds again most of our colleagues training in here they only
got a license as if they're lucky this here is a triple a I beat your record
Jack you want the number one spot you'll have to climb right over me
starting with your very own see license see license hero back yeah I
guess that's okay abusive being a sea license here I was better than
nothing I guess working the vice squad found he had a nose for sniffing out
lowlife never had a girlfriend dog walked out on him wait a minute how
did you know call it a lucky guess okay smartass go get you see we'll see
who's laughing oh and hey my dog never walked out on me your dog
ever license okay to obtain a law enforcement license you must pass the
entry grade proficiency test using the VR terminal located in the VR room
passing further tests will allow you to upgrade your license if merited by
your performance in the field in the unlikely event another tutorial can
also be used to access information from the Layla database once licensed you
can withdraw equipment from the equipment dispenser for your grade of
license clear to begin the test approach to the VR terminal that's the
easy part may smell your fingers all right all right go to the VR terminal
sit down have two jacks get shoved in your eyeballs for the love of God
really take the test can't wait this turn at one motorcycle control test
reach all checkpoints within the time limit I need to do it within 32 seconds
so this is not his headhunter a video game I have to beat this guy's
number one score in the Donkey Kong cabinet is that what's going on I
thought it was they were assassins how would you do this in 32 seconds okay
I seriously need to keep the webcam on so you can see this I'm gonna that's
unbelievable I wouldn't just do that I wouldn't just drive into the wall I did
it get a real controller this is a real controller what's wrong with this
this is not we don't this is not a real controller I can't physically turn
turbo off I don't know how I can't do it it's not possible what's wrong
with this I don't understand the problem it's a budget ps2 controller
this is what I got I'll reach the goal without getting detected if any enemy is
alerted the test has failed great oh alright the axe how do we do a stealth
takedown I just exited shit well I didn't ever talk nobody ever taught me
anything I said I could do a stealth takedown this shit sucks turn it off
not yet it's gonna turn around isn't it okay let's go I'm not even
holding a gun and I'm pretending to fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck come on I
gotta wait till I gotta do a whole new the cycle here oh there he goes thank
you bring back your face game so we can mock you kill off four enemy guards on
the other side of the abyss use the environment for protection ha ha we're
laughing at you fine I'll take it come on one more beat Hank's record
where is he where are you alright now the game starts I get my gamer
license now oh Jesus I don't have to do them all do I this is the worst
than Ed Edd and Eddie it's alright just get to the end I supposed to just get to
the end by any means necessary are you getting tortured again he's
torturing us did somebody sing to me help me shoot the guy right next to you
I had good let me out please just wait a minute just let me get my
license and then we can talk about it alright license gap got it see
license granted I'm ready we are here for you don't go to that website it
doesn't work your ID card and VM agent Wade model VM 52x standard issue
biorecognition chip identifies the user assessing his digital career resume
access to some information may be restricted you can't tell me what to
do dad yes I can you're my son when you live in this house under my roof
give it a whack anything else you mow the lawn once every two weeks here to
collect your other equipment approach the correct dispenser for your license
type and insert your ID card no to the VM we don't have a lot of the
cellular phone doing anyways got down to concrete hi Jack how's it feel to be
licensed again like I just graduated kindergarten you have anything on
yet you'll be the first to know call me when you do
I'll give this one another minute one more minute sixty seconds starting now
working on for Christmas turn you said you'd help that lady keeps cutting
herself off all right database large files what he got licenses VR
terminals just weapons all right cool objective good let's go everything for
me I like like 60 more seconds don't blame me if you leave without you
access to not have to go to see their banana decoy shells okay cool hello
can we go the disk not being read damn it come on I mean I can't really do
this one this I have the 50 cent game here 50 cent bulletproof we can't do
that one now look at that one do tomorrow that was a good one to 25
to life I also have I can't come on this thing actually crash I do
actually own blood in the sand as well for a PS3 what does this one all right
hey look hey look what I got remember when I bought this I'm gonna be
purchasing this one don't need to play that one anymore never finished it I
would talk about I did it in one stream I said freedom fighters clock
tower three what can I do now I actually do have the alias video game
did we play this one alias the TV show I'm gonna try this one freedom
fighters is good I'm gonna turn this off so don't flash you guys play clock
tower don't don't worry we'll do that tomorrow but you got to get through the
terrible ones first we started off with Ed Ed and Eddie that was a good
one you got to get through the ones that I some of these games that I
thought were good I got urban chaos I got both the stump
man's I get Psy Ops we had a lot of good ones let's bring this one
back 2004 touchstone television claim entertainment don't type out the
list why is it shaking I know I still got more that I haven't said something's
wrong my computer why is my computer doing that
it's not a fan of my computers like freaking out my motherboards burning the
cock the cocking the gun
call you in on your day off it's still good that's still doing that I
scrambled my camera's brain there we go that's better I like it it's kind of
stiff neck do it on the mic
stop doing this what the fuck it won't stop hey you just want vibration on the
whole fucking time that's what that means they coated in just on or off
off on my teeth that's like chewing tin foil all right get out of here let's
see how bad this game is bad um excuse me go what I do that to the mic why
did that person tell me to do that it wasn't even fun fuck do I sound does
the microphone sound okay we lost contact with a well-placed source how
do I sound good do I sound clear
informed us that Anna has been working on something referred to only as the
machine before being compromised he made a successful dead drop inside
casino operate turned on again from one of his mansions you're saying
Sarkin Anna are working together that's what you need to find out you
and Dixon will be infiltrating the casino we've already established your
alias as a new waitress and I'll be posing as a player on the casino floor
because you know blackjack poker back all right after you make contact with
me we can stay in audio-visual contact there's two things you have to do in
the casino if you get too close to Sarkin only max bet but we can tag
his going with five thousand dollars and put five thousand dollars on one
hand that will allow us to track if you win once you do that then you can
keep playing with the five thousand and put the other five thousand in the bank
and then if what if you lose just go home because you know that's what he's
gonna say it'll probably is what he said I talked over as well as what Sarkin
Anna are up to when you find the disk bring it back to CIA for analysis
I don't need to remind you Sarkin Donna are two of your deadliest
enemies so watch your backs hey sit so your dad was like make sure my
daughter has the absolute best and I was a Quentin Tarantino yes sir
anything for you sir anyway here's your object for this mission first of all we
have the tracer serum the tag starts driver now whatever you do don't drink
any of this yourself please or you're probably gonna have a barium hangover
trust me those are the words that is really great in the frontal lobe it
hurts searing next up is this razor prism you splice this baby into the
security camera cables and it'll let us see what they see this is a razor
prism 14th failed product line it's a wristwatch that has like a Nintendo DSS
video game console built into it connected to synapse 299 dollars I was
mean those on that was actually uncalled for so sorry about that is
this open mic yeah I know everyone's gonna say T pose I already know I can see
it already I'm in read you loud and clear find Dixon for your op tech
before you proceed with the mission find Dixon on my way we got it drug
the chauffeur with the tracer serum locate Dixon and retrieve your
gadgets you knew here don't forget checking all the corners okay this is
a duck and then there's a super duck can't find the chauffeur chauffeur up
here I found you locate Dixon right on top just tapped into casino security's
calm channel should be able to make this run smoother here's Marshall's
technical support including the tracer sir sucks driver is the one in the
corner coming back what he marries for an hour good go get checking with
the head waitress at the bar and get the drink she kind of runs like an
asshole all right checking with the waitress hey I'd like a drink
another bloody Mary for the guy in the corner fine fine get your feet to get
bare feet on table okay sit wait for her to turn her back and then add the
serum first legit bare feet on the table open the inventory
now add the serum to the drinks here and take the trade of the driver no
problem it was quick change in device super
new game no save data yeah god damn it I can skip all this right I changed it to
my spy outfit stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid this guy fucking sucks
lol how to lose in a single button press I don't I guess I know what I'm
doing yes fine fine fine fine fine locate the agent all right here we go
ready I get you I'm gonna get damn it I thought I thought it was gonna be like
that nevermind waitress I'd like another drink added to the guy that has
his dirty fucking feet on the table okay sit add the serum to the drinks
that's eat it okay take the tray you don't think it's suspicious that the
waitress is not taking this why wouldn't the waitress just be like um
excuse me oh he doesn't have okay he has shoes on okay now what okay fine
is he gonna fall down just gonna get him to have to drug another one sir would
you like another drugged drink we're picking up a clear signal from the
driver now okay for Jacobs was compromised he indicated that he would
be dead dropping the disc in the freezer room beyond the kitchens
reason the back of the casino great I'm glad I'm dressed for the freezer
room retrieve the disc from the freezer I
guys walk back there oh no no not to do the and in heels do that's probably
pretty hard to do freezer you're not allowed back here don't make me fire
you on your first day how do I get back there who saw me do that wait wait
who's the guy friend of mine installed the security cheap security cameras not
allowed to go in the free yeah why wouldn't I be allowed to go in the
how do I just haymaker can I talk to this person hey let's talk all right I
just want to talk to you that's not the freezer but the freezes back there
talk to me please talk to me just speak to me I need to talk to you for
one second she's gone safe point got it I'm gonna die of dehydration I'm
gonna be fine don't worry about me you work don't have to sneak in the
back for some strange reason still doing it all right let's go they have to go in
the freezer and what are we doing back here sneak past the guards to avoid
raising a security alert all right great can't wait to play this frying
pan throw into the guys head maybe where's the other one right there hey
what are you doing it fuck oh no what am I doing back here get in there
all right sneak it's gonna go behind this guy okay I got a cleaver now it's
game over for these motherfuckers just where to go go what are you doing no
just go I made it all right into the freezer do you have a visual on the
disk negative change costumes in the costume gadget all right just give me
the disc I found the disc I had to say the practice of gymnastics I can't
break this open all right give me the disc found data disc local area networks
just intercepted a cell phone call from Sark meeting in the Gersh from
apparently it's an executive suite somewhere inside the mansion marshals
downloading blueprints of the mansion to your PDA to help you access the
location and eavesdrop from it infiltrate the Gersh room executive
suite and search for information on the machine all right the guards heard
what is this a meat tenderizer where are they what's wrong with me open the
door how do I get can I step on them like I went back what he went on the
whole staircase what else do you have was a guy attacking me with half of a
golf club it's a soup spoon why don't you have a gun if you're a
security guard why standard issue soup spoon okay I got it wait save the
game oh come on no I got compromised after I always it because I've walked
that in I walked out there with a spoon all right I'm fucking going as fast as
I can damn it play the next game no I died this one's fun oh shit is that
guy can see me god damn it I had it was done I had it I had it done
already I'm all the way back here oh come on I was done it was ready I
beat it I just just trying to rush through it cuz I don't want to do it
again I hit the guy with the soup spoon in the head and then apparently I I was
compromised save at the save point don't run we don't know can I get
control again just do it the way that you're supposed to do it just wait
this guy turns around a disk do you have a change clothes how do I change
clothes is that I'm still cold in the disk wait okay here they come blueprint
infiltrate the Gersh mansion they heard something the guards heard if they
come through this way and they go which way they go left or right they
go that way same point right here okay see that you have to stay clear of
that right there thank God yes I am absolutely sure
should I take these clothes off okay avoid the camera that's gonna be easier
so than none that guy sleep what's the arc on the camera how far does it go
what am I looking at here my 180 degrees 60 degrees what's the what's
the arc third floor I didn't do that what the hell's going on and do what's
wrong the elevator just started moving someone on another floor must
have called it you don't have clearance to be up there I have to
make it up as I go along dialogue options nice all right he's a weapon
what do you have for what all right what do you have give me a weapon it said
use weapon great work take a look around see if you can find any clues
about this meetings look for clues I would laugh my ass off he had a soup
little all right look for clues let's sneak same point good no don't open
yet wait hold on save the game she's going 60 FPS on his ass that's quite the
way to put it all right let's get in here sneak grab can you crack any pick up
people they always give the headbutts oops we'll take the okay vodka I get
the vodka bottle that's good probably laptop I would assume that
computer might contain something hack it with your remote motor yeah yeah yeah
what connecting downloading processing access code in the name of God what
L1 okay what what color does L1 move L1 moves purple L2 R1 almost R1 or L2
reset it's definitely it's a ad what a DB ABC why would it be that easy ABC
let's have you pass was one two three hot off the press Oh Jacobs no it's a
dossier on the machine something and I'm prepared for Sark nothing on Jacob's
but it seems that the followers of Rimbaldi are working prototype for it
didn't keep me out that's true where's the plant according to this oh my god
it's underneath the casino wait I've managed to isolate the schematics of
this weapons plant from the computer hard drive when you hacked it it's
kind of like knock knock is there anybody going there definitely means
it's like lucky it's imperative you find this hate to show and have you
seen one episode to get ahead of Sarkin Sloan for a change that
depends on how much time I have Dixon any sign of Sark not yet all
right base camp I'm heading for the plant game that's to get the weapons
facility in the basement of the casino when we get my first gun calm down
in general what no guns was alias a show with no what guns or oh she had
the two kids to size right right okay you need to relax and what why is
it we tell me to relax so what are you talking about
select a button yeah relax I am relaxed settle down I'm gonna start breaking shit
if people don't shut up about this I'm gonna stop breaking stuff to go down
even to go down again can I go down more like I need to go keep going
down just do anything for me no there's a vent right there it's a
really awkward face you're making her climb up on it how do I climb it so
that's not what I need to do all right so go just go in the door I had the right
idea is the wrong place get up there going when this used to be a VR stream
yeah I didn't be are like three straight streams that I need to take a
break we'll go back to it don't worry I yeah I know I died like I did it I
just I don't even know why I did that why would I do that I don't know
why I don't know did my blood like I have to make but I guess I have to
do like the streamer joke I have to it's a part of my DNA I didn't even want
to do that I thought I could jump all right we're good I'm right here it's
not that far away being a streamers in a phase mom it's in my DNA what I am
a goddamn streamer all right watch I'm gonna do it again
where's my prompt to go down the ladder why wouldn't I just use the
ladder just use the ladder she's the ladder is very clear ladder I fell
very fast but I still made it so now I gotta go something about a weapons
something about weapons now there are guns just been introduced play freedom
fighters I'm gonna play that tomorrow we start with clock tower 3 tomorrow
Sydney there's a lot of guards on patrol down here to take this guy out
with your stealth attack otherwise you'll alert the whole crowd use
enhanced division I hate this enhanced this is this is awful vision how do
you stealth attack get the gun get the gun what did you throw it down give me
the gun shoot him she's never used a gun before
just on the face three times I didn't take off the vision thing who's left
one more they were good right this is a Charlie's Angels video game not
quite you ate a pop tart today it was gross what kind of pop tart did
you eat if it wasn't a s'mores pop tart then you made the wrong decision
is there another game after this or is this probably the last one it's probably
the last one it's getting late and go for those cameras we'll pick it up
tomorrow if you use the razor prism now if you can find an open CCTV access
point to tap into the system we can see through their cameras don't see
what I can do just shoot them you're eating a s'mores pop tart right
now that's a great idea okay a safe place to use the razor
prism looks pretty safe you don't want to vape in public you want to
hide hello what the fuck got it nice backflip stunt man okay now what safe
place that person still alive fingerprint
replicator just run I don't do I just keep going
holy shit I can't save it where a cutscene yeah we see it but what is it
I don't know if they are building weapons they have enough material for a
army see what you can find out about this machine I will I'll try I got full
health for that I got full health I just cheesed it into getting full
health that's amazing I need something I need a gun or something right now
you've begun why don't we get one shot no this is gonna be the end of
stream it's the end of spring oh god damn it oh that was an adventure
let's see if I can sprint through this let me try let me try let me go those
cameras I just have to get downstairs and that's it
goddamn shark game made me fucking almost throw up and it
I've been making my gamer skills depleted
let's go I'm a good secret agent I got a good shot
all right let's go run we destroyed them down here
in through there I can get it faster faster faster
do you read me why are you shooting the gun like that
where is it with thing with the thing with the door
okay laser print this guy I can't even do it
I got no more fuel low on gamer fuel I really am
made it who cares about saving press special attack
what's special attack
that wasn't very special no no I gotta go
fuck all right that's it I'm done uh I can't I can't I somehow got I got
brighter oh it's because of this all right thanks everybody for
watching I'll see you tomorrow we're gonna start with clock tower
three tomorrow which is that's a good one that's a very good one
we might even complete that one don't take my word for it though I'm
gonna shave tonight no I'm not I said but didn't I promise
I was never gonna shave ever again this like there's a bunch left to do
still all right you blame Ed and Eddie for
taking two hours but that was fun oh I like that game
that was a fun game there's nothing wrong with that one
favorite kind of cookie uh cookie dough over that one
all right that's gonna be it we got through some of the uh
the worst ones every kind of battery duracell
you know let's not even put the outro on I'm getting a new screen
that's because that's let's go like this I'm gonna get a new screen
my cable is going to screw up today I actually almost puked that's the first
time that's ever happened on stream all right uh let's just go like that
uh I'm gonna get a new screen anyways move this
skipped what end of the stream that's getting late
we'll pick it up tomorrow what was the cool story did I just cut myself
up I don't uh we got bits to do let's
go down to about seven hours ago now you don't
skip the fruity lubes default track number seven
I'm glad you didn't puke because I would have puked too no I would have
muted and fucking ran away I would not have done that on camera
or on stream it was pretty close though I felt
fucking terrible I still kind of do that stuck with me after that
anyways we had uh seven hours ago from fitty we had five
dollars from fitty they say pogchamp pogchamp pogchamp
did you see that ilan musk actually hosted meme review with justin roiland
it's up on pewdiepie's channel right now this is truly the weirdest timeline
it is a weird timeline I did not know that existed that's very strange
but thank you for the five dollars also thank you to alec
for the one dollar you like pop tarts what flavor I like
s'mores default strawberry and that's it
if you eat cinnamon pop tarts unfriend me
everybody said die oh no no no no you think I could out act
anybody on this platform come on hey smelly boy thanks for
the one dollar smelly boy will we ever get the pokemon stream it would be
fun to let chat name a pokemon you catch
no pokemons is too what's going on my neck there
do you see that it was like it was like my head was on the wrong angle
look at that what's going on there I like my face looks photoshopped right
now this is okay that's better now I look
normal why was I going like this that's because I'm reading the bits
fucking hate cameras uh but not the pokemon is is interesting but
I don't think it's a good stream experience for me I would
probably get bored and it's not because pokemon's a boring game it's
because I get bored easily with games that are slow burns like that
walking around in the dirt and leaves and picking up new animals like I
don't know if I'd be able to do it but thank you for the suggestion though
hey trust no one thanks for the three bucks hello Jeremy it's been a week
since you know what happened a little tip
it's about your youtube autoplay issue uh let the circle
continue didn't wait what please let me ask you not to forget the link
in the video or you forgot to do it the last two times
wait what are you talking about isn't the news blooper one
yeah we watched this no this is but this is different
this is a different one wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute this two
two of these exist this is a new one I'm having trouble keeping track of all
these all right let's watch it what am I
talking about we watched the news bloopers one
two days ago remember don't people acting like I'm crazy here
now yeah we did I know hey look I wonder what's gonna happen
wait this happened again it is a new one looks like we don't have a choice
it is a new one is this what you want you want this shit I cringe a little
what's happening we're gonna play this it doesn't
fucking work if it works what the fuck
enter philip okay this is the easiest thing you've had to do
here we go we're almost there didn't quite get that
well uh thanks for coming up if you have this much of an issue with my
stream then just go fucking watch somebody else
go watch like vinny who fucking whatever whatever his name is
do you think I fucking know I can hear you oh no no politics
dean dingus fighting for you I don't who the fuck is this guy
if you don't know what dean dingus even stands for dean dingus might have
strangled somebody do you know that I'm all for the
middle class anthony anthony anthony he's for the
middle he said it he said he was for the middle class he said it
the guy owns like fucking 45 billion dollars and hides it and shit he's like
get the fuck away from my money I'm anthony fucking anthony motherfucker
this is fucking cool he's criticizing himself
Jesus I feel like I'm in fucking star wars
no I ain't slowing down for nothing oh
fuck me like really how did you get pulled me out of this
there you go good luck good luck with this one good luck
how the fuck are you gonna make that one I don't see a possibility
but thank you though it's I don't know if it's gonna happen
thank you trust no one for that uh video
thank you and let's uh let's link that
here is what we just watched thanks for the three dollars as well
thank you uh flammable cow thanks for five dollars
uh depression has really made me lose my uh has recently made me lose my
long-term girlfriend friends and love for video games you've
helped an abundant you've helped in abundance through
and your streams help through the dark times you bring so much joy to me
and everybody out there thanks for the laughs much love you
alcohol elitist well first of all I'm sorry you're going
through so much shit because that sucks hopefully you can
turn it around a little I'm not sure exactly what your
scenario is but alcohol elitist I mean I don't I mean
PBR is the only thing I have an issue with we went over it very very
very very clearly but um thanks for being around thanks
for being here thanks for hanging out in the chat thanks for being part of
the community I hope you can turn it around
I really do because it sucks not feeling good all the fucking time
so I'm really sorry you're going through that but thank you flammable cow
for the five dollars yeah just do what you can unfortunately
just do what you can we live in a tough world
but much love to you we also had 250 from d jack
your eight megabytes playstation 2 memory card would fit one
48th of a 387 megabyte africa save file
this is playstation different it's a different generation though so
next generation they had 500 times the capability to store stuff
but thank you d jack tod fluoride it's not your name it's ta I say that
every time tod flowered tod flowered thanks with three
dollars dan's game dan's game dan's game you
idiot you idiot thanks for the three dollars
thank you t pen rod for the five dollars
thanks for the great videos germa been following along youtube for a long time
first time tuning in for a stream always a good laugh especially when i
need it most thank you t pen uh youtube was a
wonderful wonderful journey for me i loved every second of it
and we have transitioned to twitch and i've seen
unfortunately some of the current stuff going on with youtube it's kind
of a fucked up place now and it's i i'm so i'm very glad
that i don't have to deal with any of that anymore
because that site is whoa whoa what is going on with that website right now
unfortunately that's the unfortunate truth what website it's uh
www www.youtube.com
slash whoever the person of your choice that you want to follow
it's crazy but thank you uh t pen glad you stuck around
and thank you for being part of the community thanks for five bucks as
well we phone thanks for the 250 we phone
boomer understands pete and pete but not ed ed and eddie
i understand ed ed and eddie i know what it is
i've seen it a bunch of times yeah i've i know what it is pete and pete i i
couldn't name you a pete and pete episode yes i could when arty lifts
up the house arty spends the whole episode lifting
the house and he lifts it like a quarter of an inch
yeah i'm sorry i know like a couple of those episodes
uh but thank you for the 250 we phone shaded thoughts thanks for the
one dollar chunky cat talking about me i'm getting a
little chunky i looked at the vod from the last vr stream
and there was probably at least two or three scenarios where i was like
oh you can like look like you can my stomach i'm like skinny fat and a lot of
those clips you know what i mean like like that
i'm like standing around moving around it looks bad
my goblin body take the shirt off yeah i'll give you like a better like
we can get a better view of that you're blind what what context is
here for that now this exercise for the sake look the more vr i'm going to be a
vr streamer i'm telling you like i'm going to be
like i'm going to get vr jacked they'll be writing articles about me in
like six months the guy that played vibe and got
jacked and his eyesight degenerated 58 percent
because he played vr every single day make the face cam bigger you
got it uh where are we sticks renegade thanks
for the 250 sticks renegade i'm at anthro new
england a furry convention but i always make time to watch your streams
hope you have fun at uh anthro new england i've never been there i don't
know what it is uh you yeah you yeah you please zoom out
you got it that's a good size that's the face of a
liar i know what it is i know what it is i've i've
there's ed there's ed with two d's there's ed with two d's and a y
there's eddie i've seen it before but i hope you
have fun at uh anthro new england rip music i got you
don't worry i got it it's all covered hey jess you got it thanks for the two
dollars fifty cents your ed impression is the exact same as your lisa
impression see sources lisa violence only because violence eddie do it
man come on okay let's go that was pretty great
actually i'm not even going to click the other clip
front door oh there you are thanks for bringing me the knowledge of the
digestive system where's the goblins only because
violence eddie do it man come on okay let's go
violence only because violence eddie do thanks for bringing me the knowledge of
the digestive system against violence eddie goblins
i'm available i don't i don't hear it i don't hear the i
just think i mean maybe like it four percent
thanks for the 250 jess you got it four percent
dna match a four percent dna match you want how i do that voice i have
to go like this violence because violence eddie i can't do it
anywhere you have i don't do it like this it's
impossible let me try to do it like that i guess
i can what a liar oops behind the voices thank you jess you
got it the 250 thank you divas for the two dollars
appreciate it uh bulk bogan thanks for the one dollar
greetings from ireland germa and fucking ed and eddie what a show
what a show it was a show it was pretty good
uh thank you josh bet for the one dollar press f to pay respects
for chicken because i'd like to pick them up and squish them
and like editing any of the video game then you get the egg that comes out
i understand hey we phone thanks for the 250
going back to peet and pete i didn't get to experience that show as a
kid since i was born the year it ended
but i came across it in high school when i had tons of problems with
anxiety and depression it's such a cute and wholesome show
that helped me escape for a while and put a smile on my face
kind of how your streams helped me now also the soundtrack is so good what the
fuck yeah it is that is it's a great show
there's a lot of great characters in that show they go over a lot of great
themes they go over they tackle a lot of
great stuff in that show peet and pete but yeah thanks for
hanging out here i'm glad that something like that can be put in the
same sentence like this stream with a show like that so that's
i don't even know what to say thank you that's it means a lot
and now let's go to nate thank you nate lynn finn for the three bucks well well
well at least you're playing ed ed and eddie
that's cool now next you should play spongebob the movie game
you cartoon gamer uh i'm gonna play spongebob battle for bikini bottom
in a couple years but thank you for three bucks and two bucks here date
i knew you'd do this and chat i'm that one guy
yeah you sometimes you're gonna be the guy you're gonna be the one guy
i figured out what it is it's because it's about it's like facial here
here and there's nothing here so that's why it looks like my face
is floating on top of my neck now i can't unsee it right
i feel like i could go and pop it off
and there's a whole display case of different faces in here
get out of vr you're still in vr just pull the rubber mask off
hey great canadian fuck club thanks for five community subs
right there bang bingo thank you uh the other us thanks for the two bucks
please play thimbleweed park it's free on the unreal game store right now
i don't i don't know what it is it's because your face is a different color
it's because i'm like i'm i'm puke flushed i get like
i get flushed all the blood this is how this is why i'm so intelligent you
understand all the blood in my body is in three
places up here in the face and head so that this math problem is
constantly swirling you know what i mean collagen in the face
and then no it's not in my hands really maybe in like my
like my thighs in the third place then the liver
yeah help clean me up thank you mini clips for the 50 dollars you had
earlier we touched upon it but thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you silver flame thanks for the 250 first of all thanks to everyone in
chat for the kind message from my late duck oswald
anyways this ed ed and ed and eddy game makes me think of my
favorite tv to video game honestly if you enjoy south park at all
everyone playing the stick of truth i have i think i own the stick of
truth do i i bought it on that was that's
one of those games it's on sale for like three dollars every single six
months like four or five times a year that
game is three bucks i think i just was like you know what
add the thing to cart who cares but i've never really
like played it it looked interesting though it's really good yeah
they made another one too the the butthole whatever it was the
fractured butthole but uh you pretend to be wizards it's
just dumb but fun this is the last of my ad bits so
until another survey comes up see you love you thank you silver
flame for the suggestion as well south park uh i was a big fan of
south park south park is one of my favorite shows i don't really watch it
that much anymore but i used to watch it all the time
i loved it uh pigeon thanks for the three dollars pigeon
hey finished my community profile and i've determined that you're all freaks
kidding here it is uh love you germa now forever and always
and if i ever have an opportunity to do a project on you again i will
spring for the opportunity also i wrote your shirt
i wore your shirt yesterday and nobody recognized it germa pluto
uh do you want me to share this i've does this have any like
yes are you sure i mean there's no like personal interval on here
hold on a second holy shit this is an entire fucking project
what the fuck what discounting discretion and discovering discernible
disclosable discussion of discourse in the discord
of the discourse community a profile of germa 985's fan community
this is real you actually did this i'm gonna read this whole thing right now
it's wrapping all right here we go so this starts uh here we go
inside the sleek gray interface of the communication app discord
you click on that little circle button that's your favorite comedian
content creator germa 985's community you've always loved germa's gameplay
commentaries on youtube and now that he's streaming live on
twitch before on that later you can't get enough of him so of
course you joined his discord navigating through the channels you may
go straight into the we should do texas speech on this
right how do i get like microsoft sam to just read this
microsoft microsoft david you have selected microsoft david as the
default voice okay so how do i do this how do i do
this david sounds really handsome go get the meme one is there a way to
do that how do i what's the button no no there's a button use
let's put about mark you have selected microsoft mark as the default
voice mark is pretty good select the text
i can't like right click on here no i can't uh
i can't right click on the uh on the article shit
just download the article i don't think i can even do that i guess okay
download okay this should work no so i i own the
article i own it now select the text no no don't ask
bing ask bing i could just i would have been able to
read the whole thing i was gonna read it thanks a lot
microsoft what if i wanted to hear this played
what always loved germa's gameplay commentaries on youtube
and now that he's streaming live on twitch more on that later
you can't get enough of him so you of course joined his discord
navigating through the channels you may go straight to the reason you
joined recommendations where you can suggest that germa
play your favorite game or do something in person for a stream however
it's more likely that you'll be enticed by the channel referred to as general
you click on it and are greeted with an ongoing discussion about why or why
not we bows people who watch anime essentially are
degenerates one and in an instant they're talking about snow
although you may not agree with some or perhaps even most of the users
there is one thing that everyone in that community has in common
as community moderator noah effectator states
that's the thing germa's discourse community is populated not necessarily
by like-minded individuals but by people who all have one thing
in common they have a desire to watch this one
man entertain thousands of people by doing whatever he feels like doing
don't look at my armpit hair two one discord user laser two noah
interviewed by joey provost wait what what is this
why are we getting thousand and nineteen three noah
interviewed by joey provost on discord oh this is uh god damn it this is like
thousand and nineteen by now it's important to recognize what a
moderator does exactly a moderator makes sure that the people
springtime i'm gonna get cleaned up all right i clean it up in the spring
so stop it follow moderators can mute people
ban them and do several other things three so it goes without saying that
an expert of the community which linguist john swales attests to
being vital to a discourse community that it has changing memberships for
would definitely be a moderator as moderator grump clump of three
years confirms moderators are chosen if they are
rational and highly involved members of the community that prove themselves to
be upstanding people that can enforce rules and keep a level head five this
expertise is proven to be beneficial to the community
as on germa's twitch.tv twitch is a platform where people can
stream themselves playing video games card games
skits drawing whatever you can imagine and includes with that stream the
live chat in which any user can say something to the streamer or other
users in the chat channel what is known as live chat goes
by incredibly fast and it can be incomprehensibly difficult
to moderate chat when the messages scroll by so quickly
what helps this is discord which the discourse community utilizes alongside
twitch force wales john the concept of discourse community
genre analysis english in academic and research settings
boston cambridge up 1995 grump clump interviewed by joey provost on
discord on february 15 2019 what is
discord anyway discord is an application that
people can use in order to communicate whether that be through images what is
discord anyways or text chat germa's discord community is one
that boasts 16 600 and that's a mess of shit
there's a lot of people you may think that it is a disaster to communicate
in a server that large only 30 to 50 people will be talking at
the same time even less in the same channel
so why even bother with the discord when twitch has its own chat already
noah a moderator of both germa's discord and twitch channel for about a
year and a half found true that's an accident him on the
discord that's not true interviewees answers
this question twitch is all live the chat goes by
extremely fast due to the fast nature of live streams
and the fact that thousands of people are watching at any given point
mob mentality can come through sometimes
in comparison to the discord which is basically just a slower chat room
six so it seems that the discord is there for a more reliable method of
communication than live chat which disappears after a set time
grump clump clarifies this observation i don't really consider this community
to have a set goal other than to have a place to enjoy
yourself seven so then the discord is used in different ways by everybody
and nobody really seems to have a concise answer to the question of what
the purpose of the community is but as swale states the goal nobody
knows may not be explicitly stated note that other terminology nine grump
clump interviewed by joey six noah interviewed
by joey what's going on here wait why is it doing this can come
through sometimes in comparison to the discord which is
basically just a slower chat room six so it seems that the discord is
there for a more reliable method of communication than live chat which
disappears after a set time grump clump clarifies this
observation i don't really consider this community to have a set goal
other than to have a place to enjoy yourself seven so then the discord is
used in different ways by everybody and nobody really seems to have a
concise answer to the question of what the purpose of the community is
but as swale states the goals of a discourse may not be explicitly stated
however it still is a discourse community if it adheres to the other
five characteristics eight but again the
common factor in all of this is the adoration of germa which unites the
discourse community six noah interviewed by joey provost
on discord on february 15 2000 mentality nine why mentality
12 grump clump the discord members of the community also create genre by
participating in the live chat and also by influencing germa as he
frequently will read the chat the live chat grump clump says is
the majority of the community they are the loudest and have the strongest
herd mentality nine further because of the common
trait that they all like watching germa chat also seems to focus a lot on
trying to send a message to germa in the form of chat in order for germa
to read it which appears to be easily overwhelming
for the moderators to be able to moderate that flow of text
however new member of three months dr hunkalicious
criticrat equals three tells us how germa doesn't use the discord often
enough and rarely posts on twitter chat is where a lot of content comes
from germa also chat has a powerful influence on the
community and it's where a lot of terms and culture of the community is
formed and so it seems then that both the
discord and twitch chat are essential to the community
the pretty gap also appears that in this community
the characteristics of intercommunication participation
and genre which are vital to a discourse community 11 are all
interconnected as participation cause genre
genre causes participation as well as intercommunication
and intercommunication causes participation
the method and the way in which go about communicating is unique
to say the least nine grump clump interviewed by joey
nine grump grump interviewer interviewer i wouldn't know where to stop
12 i can however list two of the most essential note that other terminology
can always be asked on the discord for a hasty thorough response
12 grump clump interviewed by joey no no no what about this part
you skipped this part because i wouldn't know where to stop 12 i can however
list two of the most you skipped this part know that other terminology can
always be asked on the discord for a hasty thorough response
one 12 grump clump no one settings boston no don't okay
easy there text to speech man reading out stuff
uh why did i just fall down well that was
uh that was fucking wild i thought that was just an elaborate joke that you were
pulling that's it there's no more pages i'll
read the last page the last page is one it's given terminology
talk about one guy people doing minus two plus two
you know the community terms and then it ends with
that's how it ends dr hunkalicious equals three critty crap
i zoned all of that out i didn't pay attention to a word of that
all i heard was 12 grump clump and then
interviewed by hunkalicious boston no i'm kidding that's that's hilarious
you didn't where's my quote you didn't use my quote i i specifically gave you
a quote you were supposed to use it's about like lifting and eating
vegetables and fruits and carrots and shit and it's not in here
rewrite it it wasn't relevant it's of course it's always that's always
relevant it's not was it relevant eating eating carrots is irrelevant i'd
like you to tell your professor that and see what he says
i'm like frozen in time for some reason why am i doing that completely
frozen in time but no seriously thank you that was
fucking hilarious thank you uh pigeon germa's not important
yeah those are all footnotes microsoft dave decided to read them all
germa's irrelevant in his own in the paper in his own paper
are we desync still fuck now we're not why don't you guys
fucking text me oh that's right where were we oh right right here uh
thanks for that hope you got a good grade on it hope you got a good
grant thanks for the three bucks as well pigeon and then
thanks for the five bucks no message thank you for the five dollars
thank you uh tommy el gato thanks for the three bucks
hey germa i've been struggling with some severe bouts of depression in the
last few months and your streams have never failed to
brighten my day thanks for being a great streamer and an all-around awesome
guy germa heart ps who's your favorite music artist or band
uh sorry to hear you've been going through some shit if you can get any
joy here i've said it a million times but
i'll say i'll say it a million fucking times
i'm happy that you can fucking come here and enjoy yourself
thank you for being here uh and for regards to
favorite artist the gorillas the gorillas are my favorite band
at least they were they still kind of are but yeah i'll
i'll say that until my face is blue i'm happy that people can kind of
escape and have fun here and not have to worry about day to
day or week to week month to month bullshit
so thanks for being around thank you gorillas on a band they're an animal
i'm talking about damon albar and the musical
genius but thank you tommy el gato for three bucks
fox club 49 thanks for the five dollars
thanks for making me smile thanks for being here thanks for making me smile
all the damn time all of you you guys are great thank you five dollars
fox club uh thank you nate again for the three
bucks wow streamer fails to beat child's game which takes two to three
hours to beat you're no gamer if you can't beat a
cartoon game that's kind of sad i'm sorry there was we have wild animals
surrounding me when i was playing that game
i was sitting there playing ed ed and eddie and i was surrounded
by grizzly bears all screaming at me at the same time
it's kind of hard to hard to beat ed ed and eddie when you're
surrounded by fucking wild animals cuphead's a
cartoon game i beat that on stream i win
but thank you nate for the five dollars appreciate it superintendent
charmers thanks for the one dollar uh it's a grill master it's a reddit
link for something about the real master
what are your thoughts on grill master i don't get it i don't
guy sucks like i don't need to what else do you mean to say hey mostly
lost thanks to 250 ed and eddie are going to be in the
next rumble and i'm going to absolutely hate it
no they won't that's three character slots they're going to take up too
many slots they won't be there maybe like an ed eddie fan will be
there but thank you sometimes you don't look
at the chat enough but tonight you looked at chat too much i look at chat
all the time i i constantly absorb this chat
i love i always look at chat what do you want about
absorb me that's gonna get weird i'm gonna move on
thank you nate for the two dollars 51 cents at least tell me ed ed and
eddie are in the germiverse uh yeah i mean they are now i don't
own them but they've appeared on my stream so therefore they have to be
part of at least some type of universe but
thank you thank you hey yen wen thanks for the two dollars yen wen len two
dollars 50 cents uh it's a little doc here what is it
let's see from yen wen len this says
uh hey read out loud don't read out loud
so don't wait don't you don't want to don't read it all right okay i'm
probably not gonna read it i'm gonna i'll read this personal
because it does say don't read out loud so i'm gonna read this
personally don't not read it uh let me just make sure it doesn't say
anything else i want to make sure uh there is some artwork let me see
what it is uh this is for saving 70 000 seagulls
let's take a look this is called germa gull let's take a look
you can show the art all right i'll show the art oh my god
that's insane that's unbelievable i'm not gonna put this on stream
take a look at this take a look at this the talent is just is is just
uneven i'm not even measurable what did i just save that too
is it too big for me to put it on stream no there it is
holy shit this is like insanely detailed where'd it go
where'd it go i just lost it here we go look at this thing
that is so beautiful look at that gull thank you so much for this yen
wen yen wen len this is like the third or fourth
incredibly well done detailed piece of artwork that you have given us the joy
of seeing so thank you that's unbelievable save the
gull from the greasy boomer hands like but that's just that's just my
face that's amazing i will read uh your message
in private but thank you so much for your incredible amount of
contributions to this strength thank you
thank you thank you thank you and let's move on from there
we had two dollars and fifty cents were mostly lost
it never snows in nevada the state with the fourth largest ski area in the
country you're gonna throw that at me right
now it doesn't it's it's it last time it snowed in las vegas was
10 years ago sorry i don't know every single place
in nevada that has snow i've moved to the driest one of the
driest places in the country and this place didn't have snow for 10
years so am i automatically supposed to
assume that there's like snow over there
baby's hungry baby's hungry baby's hungry that's probably really loud i'm
sorry time to move to phoenix hey frody and weapon thanks for the
two dollars and 50 cents i caught chito stealing cookies from
the cookie jar when he saw me he threatened to attack me
with his giant stuffed rat you really need to have a talk with that kid
he's gonna spoil his appetite uh this this reminds me of calvin and
hogs that's a really that's a really great
like calvin and chito chito and hubs who's my favorite bionicle
character uh the green one but thank you for that thank you for
that image forodian weapon it's his rebellious adolescent
phase right uh thank you nate for the four
dollars ed ed and eddie was more fun than this shit
tell me what the game were almost puked i like that and that was fun
i put up like two hours into it i've almost beat the whole game on
the screen flexed by biceps all right fine
that one was for free uh thank you nate though listen germy you at
least have to try half-life two grunt it's real turn the
music off no turn the music off i'm probably not
going to play any half-life game on the stream
i want to say very quietly so everybody can lean in and hear me
half-life is not going to be played on stream make sure you're aware of
that everybody thank you for the three
dollars hey mostly lost thanks for the two
dollars and 50 cents jaws has my favorite movie quote of
all time we're gonna need a bigger streamer you see me laughing at that
not fucking funny hey nate thanks for three bucks streamer kills innocent
swimmers and civilians because he's a shark
take my teeth in thank you herbert thanks for the community subs
cricky ricky thanks for the one dollar this game was great i remember a
level where you have to go really deep and it scared me as a kid
i hope it didn't make you puke as a kid for some reason it almost made
me do your classic sonic impression sure
uh hey you know you don't know how to do a sonic impression
i'm never coming back again you're not coming back why
whatever i'm never coming back again i'm sorry that you don't you didn't
like it fuck i hope you find a streamer that
you like god damn it i lost another one so here's
what you do with sonic the hedgehog impression
uh open up your favorite youtuber and just study the way that they talk
and then just talk like them into a microphone
okay everybody welcome to the next sonic the hedgehog video game as you see here
uh well i'm playing happy wheels and just barely almost fell over there
almost got it i gotta go really fast to try to get
over that though that's how you do it just open up your
favorite youtuber just do the tuber voice just do the
germacraft voice but thank you nate for the two bucks you're losing to
free willy free will there's a series of movies
where the whale and yes i'm not going to put my hands up that high
when a whale jumps over the kid i've seen it before
and thank you nate again for the four dollars nice job you cancelled free
willy five the fifth part of the movie's call
cancelled franchise you're the real reason free really
free willy five isn't here why would there be a fifth free willy
they probably ran out of ideas after the first one
how many times can you free willy from
in being at the zoo they have to free a willy again
five times i fucking lied i'm back already
yeah why am i falling i'm like this is weird
sweat check nope but thank you nate thank you niall arian for the three
bucks hey germ i played my first live show last night
i felt like letting you know because you're like my second dad twice
removed so you kind of mean a lot to me
hope the show is fantastic you know if you were like
what are you played the violin right i don't know i'm not sure what
you do but uh i've been actually now yeah i do
sour please i'm too drunk to do emotes no that's great keep doing it keep
doing shows come on dad you didn't have bt tv
yes i do i see the guy going like this you didn't think i installed it
but no thank you nile rm for the three bucks
i'm happy you had a good show he knows i know i
i'm not an idiot i'm not an imbecile
doy hey peaceful haley thanks for the 250
hi germy what's an astronaut's favorite food uh
launch meat anyway i hope you had a good time streaming today it's fun as
always watching do what you do have a good night
you as well launch me that was actually pretty good
i'm gonna use that one i'm gonna go downstairs i'm gonna say that to kim
and she's gonna fucking get a peepo dance or i'm firing you get peepo
dance oh i know that one is like the
like the bird right i know what these all are no
what's the bird what's the bird that goes like this
that's peepo bird that's rare that's rare parrot
no it isn't that's people that's a peepo to me
cool dance uh thank you yes is online for the two dollars fifty cents all
right germy here's the true test to see if you're a true chad
i'm ready let's see what's the best connie west album
by the way this is the most divisive question scientifically known
to man what's the best kanye album what a dumb
question that's a true chad fucking answer
no i sorry look at how much fucking cooler i look like that
i've never listened to kanye um hold on
uh uh no no no it's no no i was just a chad i've actually never
really listened to a kanye album before sorry
i'm sorry wow you suck i i've heard kanye
what's the one that i uh what a versatile actor
you find me somebody on twitch or on youtube
that thinks that they can outact me and i will have already ran 10 circles
around them before they even get into the
workshop somebody actually had a really uh funny
idea i kind of want to do it but it might
take a little while yeah i don't know where this came from
it came from right now uh we're funny there's no family few we
play it all the time it's like what it it's a staple on the
channel we play it like once every few months
actually do a family feud where the community has asked questions
and people have surveyed and do a full
like couple hour long family feud based on
me needing to figure out what people in the community had said
like a real life family few get in the studio
get like two families hire a bunch of like actors like two people that
don't even know who the fuck i am and they have to get the quick if i
fall down one more time and put my foot through the ceiling that
would take so much sorting yeah but i could i could assemble a team
i could assemble a team don't get sued it's not gonna be called family
field they could be called like bring out the family or something
doesn't matter bring on the family change the colors
change the logo it'd be fun no not family fight bring on the families
i got an itchy nose and i can't go in because it'll be somebody clip it and i
look like i'm like i'm oh gross did you really
do that it said that day yeah i can't believe it either
was he five years old everybody picks their fucking nose can we just get
over this finally forever everybody just puts tissues up then i
spit and you probably saw it everybody does this you'll be sitting
there in the shower you'll be picking your
nose and like cleaning your nose out tissues picking your nose like come on
how many times have you guys you do it every day every single day
you don't know about that one i'm sorry but i i don't believe you
if you tell me that you don't at some point during the day
like pick your nose and clean up and otherwise it just you get build up up
there how you supposed to get rid of it
you don't like lean into your toilet and go
and just flush it you're projecting into your sink see
just blow your nose that's what you do i know that's what i'm saying like you
blow your nose but that doesn't work i'm sorry guys it
doesn't fucking work no if you go like this if you have
like boogers in your nose and you go they're gonna get all over your
mouth and like oh up here and shit it doesn't work that doesn't do
anything it just like blows them all over
your face like you got hit the face with a bug riding a motorcycle
dried boogers you can't give okay i'm telling you
you can call me crazy if you want but you all know it's true
do you not use a tissue when you blow your nose you can use a tissue but if
you have a okay mucus like i'm sick oh i'm sick
oh i can't like i'm sick yeah of course you're gonna blow your nose
and you're gonna get the mucus out of your
membranes and sinus membranes and shit but man if you have boogers in
your nose they're not gonna come out with just blowing your nose you have
to get in there yeah oh he's crazy one of you guys
is doing this right now like he's insane
and you're like wiping it on your like fucking cup that's in front of you
what's wrong with you like if you lifted up the cup that
was in front of you right now on your desk
the coffee cup that's sitting on your desk they would be at least seven or
eight boogers on the side of it that's revolting of you
i'm glad you're not going to lift that cup up into frame so people could
see that unbelievable hey thank you biker for the
one dollar i've been having a rough past few
months with my senior engineering design class
and your stream has been helping me keep me sane
keeping me sane uh senior engineering design class
that sounds pretty difficult but thank you for sticking around
we're all we're all happy to help here we're all happy to be
a fun community so thank you for being here
that you wipe sitting or standing that's like why do we have to answer
these questions you know i mean i don't at all uh
thank you to exe exe fur for the three dollars remember you're the most jacked
unfit dude i've ever seen keep it up he dips he dips down into the toilet
oh my fucking god that is awful he dips down he goes he just like
fucking dunkaroos his ass into the bowl
oh that's fucking horrible
i can't i can't go on after that one all right my foot's going to the fucking
ceiling you gotta end the stream now the
reverse bidet and then you got like water all over you what are you
gonna do oh yeah that's a poopoo joke streamer
i didn't make one reference to those words i didn't make a
single reference to what kind of bathroom behavior i was
doing when did i say that somebody asked me if i stand or sit
when i wipe and that could mean anything that could mean
like fucking you know like the mirror with a window and you clean your
windows popular toilet humor comedian jeremy
out don't how dare you toilet comedian toilet toilet comedian toilet
comedian unfucking believable whatever
uh thank you for the comment about me being jacked no i appreciate that
expert you spent 10 minutes ranting about boogers so it's spot on that's
not toilet that's nasal there's nothing to do
with the toilet what does cleaning out your nostrils have
to do with a toilet just look at how fucking big i am and
just forget about it uh the siphon thanks for the one dollar
i never watched the streams live due to time zones
but there's always the vaud anyways finally able to give you some bits
thank you siphon for the dollar appreciate it and yeah time zones are
tricky especially now that of on pacific time change into
pst has made me like eight to ten hours behind a ton of
people that are in europe and i'm trying i'm trying i'm trying
the nose is the ass of the face oh no i'd say your mouth is
no your mouth is how many times have you like coughed up
phlegm or like puked you don't puke out your nose
is your mouth sneeze yeah that like you don't shit out of your mouth
you don't shit out of your nose either you don't shit all right
thank you thank you for that conversation
uh thank you nut on whatever the rest of your name is thanks for the one
dollar i tried to write a 17 page essay on the life of jeremy elbertson
but it only came out to be it's a short joke if they're making a
reference of how i'm five foot four but that's not true i am five foot
eight and it is just absolutely untrue
so i hate to say anything about this but you're just wrong
uh they said it came out to be five foot four inches
i was gonna scream in the mic did you fucking see how good i look
dork cube thanks to the two dollars fifty cents dork you well i missed
most of the stream but that's okay i've got to play smash brothers with
my brother instead always great to play games with people
you haven't seen in a while that's true that is very true when
you get to hang out and play with people you haven't seen or played
stuff within a long time it's a great experience and it kind of brings you
back to all the other times you did before
so that's much more important than this stream so
thank you for the two dollars and fifty cents
and i hope you enjoyed smash brothers with your brother smash brothers with
your brother right hey garfield the monday killer
thanks for the one dollar it's time for a garfield garfagraph what's up
germ nice to see you dance about for all of us
on face cam anyways top 12 garfield tv specials video was released recently
garfield babes and bullets won first place if you were curious it
was the film noir genre piece i did where i got to work with the wonderful
actors and my love interest very good special look it up check it
out give it a garfished i'm not shouting out garfield
even though i already did so congratulations garfield
and thanks for the one dollar and thank you for the help your
production went well germa is interesting he has a massive
ego but it's physically compact like a mini cooper
and
and how many miles to the gallon does a mini cooper get
what's that what one of the best miles to the gallon
that you can possibly get in the car and he's shitting me
who cares you know you're right mob that guy
hey rag are annoyed thanks for the two dollars
jesus christ i went to bed more than seven hours ago how are you still
on just hanging on having a good time i don't have a time frame for
streams some streams go for four and a half
hours some streams go for eight to ten you know this depends on
what's going on don't talk about mileage we saw you
get tired from 30 minutes in beat saber
i've been i've been doing i've played i think i played i've been
talking about me to play vr for six straight hours
okay i was standing up there moving my fucking arms around like an
asshole for six hours now what i'm not allowed to get
winded with lasers shooting into both eyes
and swinging and having to be incredibly focused
and moving around come on what do we know
just wait till i do the next vr stream i'm i'm i'm getting it
most people play vr for 12 hours at a time that's not true no way
they play vr for 12 hours at a time 12 hours straight of vr
and and you guys have done that you guys have you've decided that that
was something you were gonna do i play for somebody just said i
kaiju guts i play for like 30 minutes hey did you get like winded how dare you
get winded fuck i saw i saw something going on
on the camera and i fucking immediately corrected myself
no i didn't drill a nothing
welcome to the stream have a good day okay
uh kaiju guts speaking of intelligent incredibly intelligent
fantastic people with fucking brain power the size of a goddamn
skyscraper uh thank you for the two dollars
and they say uh chat may not like it but this is what peak gamer
performance looks like this is the idle gamer body
i don't i'm in this i no no no no no did this is this real
i think this is real this is real take a look at this
here we are 50 people at recording of this video
i have nothing to say besides thank you so much i was supposed to do this at 500
but as you can see it's a little too late for that i
i can't really do that now so here it is
for 500 subscribers even though it's way past that now
there you go it's time to get fucking huge
he's a bicep curl baby there's one there's two three if you're wondering
whoa i'm wearing the same exact outfit leave me alone hey what's going on
guys why is this playing how's the shirt
still i've done yeah that's proof that i have never changed
oh jeremy maybe you jerry maybe maybe germ has changed
oh really because in 2012 i made that video i'm wearing the same
fucking shirt this is the same shirt and it stinks i haven't washed it
i never changed clothes everyone is he naked i've never taken this off
was the oldest piece of clothing i have i don't know probably this because
i just saw it on me again six years ago anyways let's uh when we're done
with the bits let's keep going thank you kaiju guts for the two
bucks and that video uh adam trap that was actually with
35 pound dumbbells i was a fucking monster
back in my prime but thank you thank you adam trap for the one dollar i
love you germa thank you for the one dollar and thank you
for uh the kind words uh yeah dington
thanks for the one dollar germa there's a burger place in my town that
serves burgers with bananas on them i mean i'm not sure that's completely
on i was just threw up completely
unusual for uh you know hamburgers that's fine
got salty that's sweet that works hey pigeon thanks for the two dollars and
20 cents didn't expect you to read it on stream
much less devote so much time to lilo me
there's something to say by the way i feel when you read a comment but i
could write another paper on how it feels when you read an
entire seven page paper though i probably couldn't because the
feeling is nothing more than pure ecstasy and euphoria by the way pigeons
are better than seagulls in every conceivable way
and that's where you lost me enjoy your permanent ban from the channel
thank you very much no thank you though
that was great um floored and humbled that somebody would write a
paper about me thank you it's i don't know what to
say that's wild i'm wearing lipstick 100
percent yeah you sure paper was about the
community there goes the ego again get out of my
face get out of my face thank you shadows one discipline shadows
one disciple for the two dollars and 50 cents
don't remember when what game this was
but i made it during the stream oh no that was the
uh alias with the chief albertson we put it up there
he's wearing lipstick 100 hey thank you jared for the one dollar hey jerem
mostly a lurker but loved your stuff for quite a while now i just want to
cape it up is what i want to say give us a kiss that's not gonna
happen i've i've never i will never do that
i'm not coming up there to give a kiss to the camera no fucking way not
in a thousand years do a sexy pose no no get over it
no get over i'm not gonna do that i'm not gonna kiss the camera i'm not
sexy get over get over hey thank you jared by the way for that one dollar
hey flug boy thanks for the one dollar love you jeremy just want to say that i
just started watching full metal alchemist brotherhood
for the first time and i'm enjoying it just got up to the it's a terrible
day for rain episode it's a great show blow us a kiss
never not gonna happen get over do nothing on there uh
full metal alchemist is a great show regardless if it's
an anime which people would be if you say that word and all of a sudden they
put up they hold like a fucking cross oh yeah it's uh well the thing is it's
an anime get back back it up back up i'm not
like a huge anime fan but some animes are very well done thank you flug
boy i'm glad you're enjoying it yes is online thanks for the 250 germa
germa what's good it's your boy max v what's going on just
checking on you appreciate the love and support
the wave is here you wavy dude anyway uh so you already know ain't no problem
man the game you already know how the game does
do your wave shido you got the official wave man just
what am i reading just doing you doing you doing your wave and keep it
loopy i know you're gonna keep it loopy was that just a rick and morty
piece i feel like justin roiland says that out loud in an episode
does he niall oregon thanks for the three well that would be six
three dollars i had my first germa laugh where it felt like i was dying the
other day it was a great feeling to just accept your death and not be
able to stop the last time that happened i really
almost i almost blacked out during that sim stream that's the last
time it really happened the world was closing in i was blacking
out god don't you wish you could just
fucking delete that just eternal sunshine that from my
memory and just go do that again god that was the funniest thing i
fucking ever seen uh but thank you thank you so much
thank you something or other for the 250 two dollars 50 cents yo germs thanks
for being such a funny streamer guy while also working on assets
oh i thought you meant like i had assets no yo germs thanks for being
such a funny streamer guy while i'm working on
assets it's a good backdrop on a different note what's your favorite
playstation 2 title monster no that was playstation 1
i don't know there's too many logan brothers was dreamcast so
what's the best playstation 2 game resin evil 4 but that was an
original game cube game wasn't it wasn't it game cube
i got long neck now uh small head i'm like the guy
whatever uh probably uh lifeline thank you rag are annoying for the
two bucks really went downhill huh no i didn't i got news for you
guys that was from 2012
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 that was seven fucking years ago seven years ago
have what kind of miracle ointment have i been swallowing you know what i mean
to still look a little a little like a lot worse
like my tooth i don't like my tooth right there i got like my eyes look a
little darker my hair is kind of thinning now i'm
looking like a little worse it was 2011 yeah counting with his
fingers i just thought i was doing that
for dramatic effect why can't i do that
my other bones and now the bones in my hand don't even work
get a short haircut again i will not i like this
i like the way it sits hey we're almost done here thank you too rag nor
rag not rag naros rag are noi for the two bucks rag naros
that's not your name uh nut thank you for the one dollar
nut the most physically demanding thing you've done in two years was cut and
fold cardboard into toys that's not true i've ran
a few times by the this is what i was talking about in the beginning of the
stream uh thank you abortion shark for the dollar
29 i remember a while ago you were talking about raising the bit minimum
to the price of a mcchicken is that true it happened and in
any at any moment during one of these streams i'm gonna stop doing it
why do i have such problems saying nut on what about like newton
all right that's good let's i i get a solution to this
uh newton newton relipes thank you newton newton relipes thanks for
the one dollar really appreciate it uh yes the two
dollars and fifty cents is the new me of reading minimum
but i've not started to enforce it yet because i want
people to know what's happening and it's gonna happen
that's probably probably tomorrow i'm honest
tomorrow i'm probably gonna stop reading one dollar bit messages
so just be aware good morning from england good morning
what time is it oh shit it's fucking late i gotta get out of here
uh thank you flug boy for the one dollar i hate to be this guy but i'm
in love with the game but have you ever tried or do you
like apex legends i have not played it once i don't
uh i don't really play br's really at all uh seems
fun cool shooter i don't have very much interest
come to br and be a br streamer everyone else is playing it you don't have to
yeah but no i just don't no no apex i'd rather just do other stuff
but thank you though appreciate it oh thank you too too too too
abortion shark again for the dollar 29 also love your streams keep up the
good work also why doesn't the keyboard on stream
over screen have arrow keys what are you talking about you see that
it's not a regular keyboard that's it that's a different it's a magical
keyboard what you should be out there all j you
can't how do you even see that i'm covering it but i don't know
because it's a magical germa keyboard that's why what an eagle
vision viewer but thank you uh mr shark
expert thanks for the three bucks what dealer do you and tom brady go to
to get your miracle ointment from i don't know if that's a tom brady is a
cheater joke and you also live in new england or you did and you
moved is that like of uh some kind of also some kind of cheater or something
i don't know what that is supposed to mean not even funny tom brady but a
legendary fucking quarterback like he slathers the ointment and no
that's actually like uh tom brady's young
and like handsome looking uh right probably shouldn't have uh
jumped to a conclusion like that that quickly
hey nobie thanks with three dollars and 33 cents don't know if you saw this yet
i don't know let's find out if i've seen this yet am i standing on it
am i starting uh let's put it on screen am i standing on it what's the
thing i just got to the dentist board is frictionless i don't like this
steer with the jets on your hands
am i standing on it it's a halloween sound effect
hoverboard is friction should i watch him live i don't like this
steer with the jets on your hands i should go to that stream
nah his stream's ending don't click on it i did a lot of screaming
with the vr stuff that's why you gotta get out of that and take some breaks
i gotta watch those vr vods though it was so much fun
it is such a blast what a joy that device really is
but thank you nobie for the three dollars and 33 cents door cube thanks
for one dollar imagine you met somebody named greg
something cracked over here why did i just run over
since what no never mind i thought there was like a something on me
i realized i looked at the monitor i thought there was something on my body
germa raid oh whoa look out here comes the germa raid
what the heck what the heck what were you streaming earlier oh
playstation 2 me too it's almost the same person
thank you dork you for the one dollar imagine you met somebody named greg
and you said nah i think i'm gonna call you steve
that's the name i'm gonna give you that's what you're doing to
newton me lights no that would be like somebody introducing
themselves as hey my name is
nut on you know what i mean that's not like
dave i think the dreamcast broke him what are you talking about i'm i'm
better than ever i'm more locked in than ever hey
thank you uh abortion shark right at the end here for a dollar 29 sorry
for bashing on the stream over screen but it's zoomed in
thank you fix fix here we go and thank you newton for the one dollar
stream it gives a viewer a government name on
twitch i mean government name yes is online thanks to the one dollar god
damn it why isn't god damn it can i get a shout out germa i hate you
thanks uh quickly thank you for uh the
did you wait you didn't give any money that was a fucking joke
don't hold that to me that was a joke
i was making a joke i really didn't pay for that
do this at 500 but as you can see it's a little too late for that 500 subs
man this video has 48 000 views
this video has like 11 views up until like three or four years ago
dig your fucking huge i hate that guy anyways uh that's gonna be it here
come the credits i'll see you guys tomorrow
we're gonna do some more playstation 2 we'll do
we're gonna play some good good games tomorrow we're gonna play
clock tower 3 we'll play 20 to life we're gonna play
freedom fighters see you tomorrow somewhere around three to four p.m
pacific uh yes online says am i the last
dollar donation oh wow this is such an honor i'd like to thank my mom and
dad for farting me out probably probably the
last one and let's get those credits rolling
of course they should be on screen right now here they go
us biology i'm hungry in some ways you've changed so much but in other
ways you still resemble that 500 subscriber germa
i think i've just gotten more comfortable for real i've gotten a lot
more comfortable like right like i mean right now in
regards to what you said earlier uh i have changed i've changed a lot a
ton like way too much like for the worse
i just like that little zing no i've gotten uh comfortable
i think i've settled in maybe four or five years ago
i'm having just as much fun as i was before i'm the last one see you later
losers says rag our noi for two dollars
you're the last one it's been really nice to see you grow
it's been it's been a ride hey germa i want to become a streamer but i'm
not stupid or ugly please give me some tips
uh that poke to me some kind of gesture to me so you're breaking
that comet to me i'll have you know when i had my
profile on hot or not dot com 14 years ago that was a 7.6 so
that second part i'm sure i agree with you
please don't cry out of what i'm gonna have so much cheese i'm
gonna have chicken i got a chicken and cheese shepherds pie
waiting downstairs i can't wait hey thank you my
you almost said that one not gonna say it
that sounds good cheese and chicken shepherds pie some carrots
something celery what's it like being microscopic i say that because you are
short it's actually pretty great i don't
have to duck to go through doorways i can fit in any car i can fit in
any seat uh what it would be an uncomfortable
train ride for somebody on the subway i fit anywhere i can stick
myself in a corner and just be completely comfortable uh
it's really easy to sleep i can sleep anywhere
i've you know if you got a couch i can curl up on that couch and i can
sleep in any position uh sorry some of you guys have to
sleep in like a full bed uh i'm gonna i live longer i got
smaller organs they let my less less work that my body has to do i'm
gonna live longer just being short make your dong look
bigger and make ladies like you more it doesn't have to look bigger