Hold on. Yeah, I got a rug pulled underneath me trying to get The Sims 2 to work.
I was at it for like three hours. I tried it last night. Everything seemed to be fine.
Oh well. So I had to freak out and get The Sims 3 very, very quickly. Apparently to get The Sims 2
to run, you have to go through an entire syllabus of classwork. But we're here now.
Uh, let me just open up The Sims 3. Hope everything's doing all right.
Yeah, this was, this was a panic get The Sims 3. I'll be honest with you.
I got to the splash screen in Sims 2. Things are working. All right, cool. I'm at the menu.
And I've tried to trust me. It's been a while. I've tried to get it to work.
Um, but then when it, when, you know, you figure it works, you're like, I'm ready.
And then you click buttons and the game doesn't, it turns off on you.
So we had to panic and freak out at like 358 and just, uh, what do I do? Get The Sims 3.
I don't even know. Just get The Sims 3 and install it. So we're going to play The Sims 3.
Very unprofessional. Yeah, I know. Welcome. Welcome. I am very unprofessional. It's,
it's all I do is unprofessional. Anyways, hope everyone's doing well. I'm doing okay.
I'm doing good. I'm very excited for today's stream.
Very excited. Bugleberry OnlyFans. Nope. That is not, uh, that is not the announcement.
Sims Omega Lul. What's wrong with Sims? Am I healthy? No, but that's okay.
I, I'm, I'm getting there. I am incredibly excited for the, uh, for the month of August.
And here comes the announcement. Later on, soon, because I'm going to milk the fuck out of this
until you can't stand it anymore. And then I'm forced to tell you in like an hour and a half.
I'm not going to wait that long. Tell us now. No, it's not a t-shirt. Do you think I would be
hyping up this stream for the last like three or four weeks? Tell you that there's a new t-shirt
on the store. No, a big announcement. I've got a new Glooman shirt. This time, instead of it being
a Navy background, it's green. I would hope that like 5,000 of you would unsub. Give us a riddle?
Sure. I'll give you a riddle. Well, hold on. I gotta wait for people to trickle in. You get,
I can't just turn the stream on and be like, ladies and gentlemen, it's not Grotto Beasts.
That's something, that's different. That's, that's something else coming. All right. Let's,
let's, what do you say we make a character in the Sims? Right. I have like the, some of the
expansions. I have like the nightlife. I just bought, look, I freaked out and I bought the
first thing I could find. You know what I mean? I freaked the fuck out and I bought the first
thing that was available. Can you see it? There we are. How's my back? It's okay. It could be,
it could be better. Wait, you dumbass. Oh shit. What does it say? Sims 3. Let's start a family.
That's an old YouTube video title if I've ever seen one. Yep. That's a YouTube title. Oh well,
it's going up. I wanted to play the Sims 2. It's doing so bad. I'll try to get it to work
another time. I just freaked out. Okay. So, um, here's the Sims 3. Let's make, let's go create
Sims. I think I'm gonna make me, I think. Okay. If I remember the Sims 3, uh, visit the Sims 3
store via shop mode. Leave me alone. Welcome to create a Sim. I know how to make a Sim.
Didn't I sing a fucking song for this? I feel like a grandpa video. Yeah, I did. This is a
grandpa video. Let me just, hold on a minute. Grandpa plays the Sims 3. I did play this.
Grandpa plays the Sims 3. I was like, why am I hearing this memory? My brain. All right,
how about we do it? You copied Markiplier? That's Peter Griffin. That's Peter Griffin.
That's Peter Griffin is playing Sims 3. Oh fuck. All right. All right. All right. All right. Oh,
my God. I'm freaking out. We're going to make a Sim. It's going to be me. It's going to be a
Jeremy. It'll be a household. My name is Peter. Okay. Can somebody, the family guy fan tell me,
has there ever been a time where Peter has gone? My name is Peter. My name is Peter. I'm going to
do this. My name is Peter. Has it ever happened? I have been looking for it. Sing the song. No,
because everyone just thought it was a family guy routine. And now I'm like self-conscious.
God damn it. I'm going to be dreaming about that. I'm going to have nightmares about that. All
right. We'll do Jeremy Albertson. That's good. I'll live with a bunch of a couple of weirdos.
Don't worry. I've definitely gained a lot of weight. Like the saw house. Let's see. Well,
I definitely, my stomach has gone out a lot. The same story actually has a pretty robust creator.
I forgot. You are not a young adult. Yes, I am. Would you classify as not what I mean? No,
I'm not anymore. You're an elder. I'm just a regular adult. Yep. So 35. Oh shit.
I think you're right. Yeah. I think you're right. All right. That looks good.
Faces. Let's go to the face. Can I? Oh yeah. Advanced. Let's do
the eyes. Advanced. This doesn't even need to be accurate. I don't. What do I care about?
You forgot how old you were. No, I just think I feel like a young adult still. No, I don't.
I have a shitload of health problems. Like I remember how I felt when I was 30. I don't
feel like that right now. You know what I'm saying? What was the big announcement? Well,
interesting. Interesting. What if I just didn't even have an announcement? This is just a way
to get as many people here as I could. This is not even me, by the way. This doesn't look
anything like me. You ever have a dream of somebody that you know and they look like
this in your dream and they don't look anything like that? I swear to God, I dream about this
person all the time and they're supposed to be my dad. This exact person shows up as my father,
as a friend, as a colleague. I don't know why it's just this face happens all the time.
Have you dreamed of this man? Yes, all the time. I kind of have a wide mouth.
Grill master. I don't, it doesn't have to be me. You know what? This looks like, this looks like
when Disney finally makes the Pinocchio IRL remake. Don't you feel like this is like the IRL live
action Pinocchio? They'll make him like a, just a guy that lives in like a flat in Pennsylvania.
Wait, they don't change the story in the live action remakes. What am I talking about?
Why would they just remake it and have him be a guy that lives in like New York City or something?
That's all right. Should I just mod the fuck out of this game too?
Then we're gonna play this a couple times. I'm gonna play this today and then, well hey,
I've got an announcement to make. Ladies and gentlemen, I will be playing The Sims 3
again next week. Probably Tuesday or Monday of next week. Quite an announcement. Also,
I've got another announcement to make. Announcement part two is I believe the
battleship tournament finals will be this week as well in a few days. I think we're trying to do it
on Thursday. Huge fucking announcement. What do you think about that? No tattoos. Is that the
announcement? If you think that's the announcement, then I don't know what to tell you. Okay,
this is fine. Let's do hair. Sim points on sale. Sale ends at 6am. Why would a sale end at 6am?
With this in-game currency stuff? Okay. I love picking outfits and hats and stuff. It's really
fun. Lies just come so naturally to your forked tongue. Why am I a serpent? Lies come so naturally
to your forked tongue. It's definitely this one, but it's not though. It's longer than that.
Should I have OC hair? VR hair? It kind of is VR hair. Yeah, we'll keep it for now. I gotta
get these glasses off. I don't have any body hair. Not like it matters. It's a second life hair.
No, let me take... I gotta fix the face. How do I get this shit off? Clothing. All right, head.
Where's the... Does this look anything like me? Is it looks? Hair? Body hair? Facial hair? Eyebrows?
Hair? How do I get the glasses off? Clothing, right? How come there's... Oh, here we go. Here
we go. Accessories. Get this off. Fix the eyebrows. I'm begging you. I will in a minute. Let's just
take it off. All right, I'm changing the name. I want to keep this person, but they're not going
to be me. It'd be like VR Elberton? Young Bugleberry? Make him Bugleberry? All right,
this would just be Young Bugleberry. That's actually a good idea. What's his name? Barry
Fernard? What's his name? I forget. He told me it once. I don't remember it though.
Yeah, Barry Fernard. Yeah, Bugleberry. Something like that. Yeah, I'm going to keep it as Elberton
though. I actually like that. I am so excited. I'm like trying so hard to keep it together
because you have no idea how excited I am. And you should be too because
this needs your brother. It could be. I think a trench coat? I mean, that's kind of close.
Needs to be fatter though. I just keep thinking about Grandpa. It's just Peter Griffin singing
about how he's going to play the game. Never to save often because the game is prone to crashing.
That's a good point. I will. That looks good. Clothing. What about pants? This is formal,
but I kind of want this every day. All right, every day. Get these glasses off. I don't want
these glasses. What is happening? Well, he did have one of those Hawaiian shirts on. It's milking
us. All right. You want to start dropping some hints for you? You want a hint? Some of that we
talked about like three years ago, like at least probably three plus years ago, we had a conversation,
a very specific conversation about this. This has been something that's been on the brain for
a very long time. I like that. It is not baseball. I just love doing this. So fun just to
create a character here and decide how I'd like them to look and put them into a place of residence.
God, it's so much fun to do that. All right, that looks good. No, nobody's pregnant. What are you
talking about? I'm not pregnant. What? All right, let's get some traits. He's definitely
commitment issues, coward. No. Is Bugleberry evil? Not really. He has demonic powers, but I don't
think he's evil. He's a genius for sure. Well, this is young Bugleberry, right? This is before
Bugleberry drank the weird potion that made him Bugleberry. He's a student at MIT, right? Or
whatever it is. Let's do, he's definitely brave, charismatic, very charismatic. I'm going to put
friendly. Not inappropriate. Party animal. Are you running for office? I'm not running for office.
What was that? Did you hear that? It was like a Beavis and Butthead just laughed. It just came
up for no reason. He's good. Okay, we have genius, brave, charismatic. We need like a bookworm,
probably. Yeah, that's good. Lifetime wish is to be a world-renowned surgeon. That makes sense.
International super spy. No. Chess legend. Leader of the free world. A master mixologist.
All right, get rid of this one. Oh wait, that means booze. That does not mean what I think it is.
Yeah, I like mixologist. That's fine. Own a bar. Same thing. Oh, a forensic specialist,
dynamic DNA profiler. Well, now we know where that comes from. Tell us, you rat fan.
Just wait a minute. Just wait a minute. Just wait till we get out of the character creator.
Oh, I'm so excited. I'm so excited. You have no idea. I'm holding it in because I look,
this has been going on for like years and it's finally happening. Finally. And it's real and
has a real date and it's going to be fucking crazy. Okay. I'm driving everybody crazy,
but it's okay. That looks good. Favorites. He loves, what is he like? What would Bugleberry be?
I can't even say his name. Tell us now. Crack, crack, crack, crack. Just wait, wait, wait,
wait. Just stop smoking crack for a second. He'd probably eat this. That's pretty Bugleberry-esque.
What is Bugleberry? Gemini? Capricorn? Libra? Cancer? Aries? It's not Germacon. It's not.
We'll talk a lot about it. And guys, the whole point of this stream is essentially
to get everybody excited and to get me excited because I haven't talked about it at all.
Wait, I'm waiting. I'm milking it. It's having to be a Pisces or whatever. I need to get rid of
those glasses though. He's mega milking it. Sure. You could say that. All right. Bugleberry,
I think is ready. Bernard Bugleberry is good to go. And then one other person. I don't like
managing more than two people in the sim. That's hell. That's good. Okay. Add a sim.
Me? All right. Yeah. I'm going young adult. Whatever. I'm young. I can't be fatter than
Bugleberry though. That's important. But Bernard? Yeah. It's Barry, Bernard, Bugleberry. I think.
It's pretty messy. How about this one? That one's actually more accurate. That one really is pretty
accurate. It's the Hillary Clinton hair. It's pretty accurate. How come I can't just make it
match the color? Yeah. What do my eyebrows look like? Anime hair. Yeah. It's OC hair.
It's original character hair. All right. That looks fine. Maybe not. Eyebrows aren't that thick.
I don't like that. Sideburns though. Good. Is the face cam on? I need to grab a glass of water.
Wait for me to do the announcement. 50 community subs. What are you doing?
Mystic Quest just gave 50 subs. Out of your mind. That's too much money. Thank you though.
Appreciate it. That's insane. Let's get me in here. How about my jaw is a little wide.
I have a really thin chin, but I have a wide jaw. You know what I mean? That makes sense, doesn't it?
This calls for a face cam? No, it doesn't. I almost had a game a way out. I played it with
italics. I'm making that guy. I don't want that guy to be in here. I'm just making that character.
Oh, I am excited today. Do you understand? Okay. I always put my hand through my monitor at 355.
Actually, no. My nose is bigger than that. Not that long. Yeah, because this institute didn't
work and I was like, what the fuck am I going to do about this? You want another hint? Okay.
Another hint. I don't want to give the whole thing away until I have to.
Purchasing. Purchasing. Buying. Purchasing. There you go. I don't like the way the chin looks.
I'm pretty smiley. Where's that chin? Details, eyes, head, and ears. Where's my jaw?
Here we go. Is it a germacoin? No, it's not a germacoin. I'm okay with this. This looks
way better than I actually do, but who cares? I made myself fat though. I got a little bigger.
Every day. This actually kind of is already accurate. I don't think I need to change this.
It looks nothing like you. It looks kind of like me. That looks sort of like me. I really like
doing this though. It's nothing like you. Well, then I'm going to change his name to like Rad
Elbertson. I'll change his name to Rad right now. His name is Rad. There. It's fixed. He's
Rad. Rad Elbertson and Young Bugleberry are going to share like a fucking house together.
Let's get the, uh, yeah, we'll change his name to Rad Elbertson.
Those shoes are going to go. Bugleberry's first creation, Rad Elbertson.
For a second I thought that just said fermented Elbertson. I was like, who the fuck is that?
All right. Rad and Fernard are going to have a house together. Brown shoes and black pants. You
can pull it off if you can do it smart enough. I think we're ready to move into a house. We're
going to build our own. Rad can pull anything off. It's an announcement time. Oh, it's getting real
close. I'll tell you, it's getting real close. All right. Rad, uh, this is going to be a random
and he wants to be a aquarium. That's a gigantic laptop. Holy shit. That looks good. He loves
fishing. All right. Edit relationships. They're brothers. No, no, no, no, no. They're just
housemates because Bugleberry would have made him. All right, let's go. I don't need a place to live.
I want to build my own place. Can I do that? Is there a spot here where I can build?
Here's a place to live. I want to move into a lot. Game is too dark. Why is it dark? That's weird.
Can I afford any of these lots? It is. Yeah. Why is it dark? Hold on. What's going on here?
Why is it so dark? What's going on here? Yeah, it's very dark. I would say this is exceptionally dark.
If I do this, can I make it better? If it's worse, I'll change it. Hold on.
Okay. If that, if it looks weird, let me know. I'll go back and change it again.
All right. I need a lot to move these guys into. Can I not do it at this, um,
she was in the library. Yeah. I want to select the Albertson family and then I want to build my own.
You can't start with a lot. Why not? How much is this place? Yeah, you can. Yeah. So are there any
lots available? They just know a lot's available in this expansion. Tell us the announcement.
I mean, hold on. We'll get it within 15 minutes. Promise. I have to go out of the city. All right.
Let's go out of the city. The towns. Yeah. I don't want to get me out of the tutorial. I'm good.
Oh, all right. Here we go. Lot. Got it. Lot. Can I buy it? All right. Go ahead and start.
Change the lot type. This is the best town in the game. Is it? That's a park. It's not, this is,
it's a house. Wait, I have to go back. I can change the lot type to a house. Change the lot type. I
want this to be residential. Okay. Here's a new. All right. Nice. I'm ready. Let's move in. I'm
going to build a house. It's a coffee. You know what? Okay. I'm ready to move place back into town.
Return. Oh, the game setup. I see. All right. Within household. Here we go. All right. Let's get it.
They own this lot. The Elbertson family is going to move it. All right. Who do I want to do? What
do I want? I need to build. That's fine. Okay. Let's, uh, I got to get the hot keys down here.
So, uh, we'll start with the walls over here. Let's do this. Make this, uh, uh, how much money do I
have? 16,000. Is this your parents reveal? I just need one square. And then I kind of want
go this way. We need this. Oh my fucking God. What are you doing? You start very small in the
Sims. Don't you understand? Um, they just need a little space. They don't need anything crazy.
What the fuck is this music? What does the Sims? This is the Sims. I'm playing a game. I'm creating
a place. I'm moving in. I'm going to be purchasing things. I'm going to be making a nice house for
myself. Imagine this was real. You imagine controlling somebody in what I would call a
dollhouse directly controlling a person and they're all their moves and all their things.
Can you imagine how interesting that would be if you, in fact, were in control of, let's just say,
me for the sake of argument. Ladies and gentlemen, wouldn't it be interesting if we did the dollhouse
stream? The thing that I have talked about over and over again for three gosh darn years,
we're doing the IRL dollhouse stream. You will have direct control over pretty much everything
I do. There is a lot of moving parts here. We have a lot of partners. We have a lot of people.
It's going to be the biggest project I've ever done. I hope everybody is prepared for that.
Here are your days. This is not just one day. This is not just one stream. This is three streams,
August 18th, August 20th, and August 21st. The first two streams will be at 3 p.m. Eastern,
and the final stream will be on at 12 p.m. Eastern. We have partnered with Twitch.
Twitch has ponied up a significant amount of money and funds and help and financing.
Also partnering up with Kriken and his Ghost Commander Company to actually make the extension.
It's going to be insane, and that's happening in two weeks. You see, I held it. I held it until I
get you a hard date. Continue. There will also be, whoa, whoa, whoa, is that it? That's not it?
There's also going to be other special guests, which I'm sure you may hear about soon.
The sky is the limit on these streams. There's a lot of really, really interesting things that
are going to happen, I hope. I am so excited for it. I've been keeping my mouth shut about this
for five to six months straight. I have wanted to talk about it so much. You have no idea how badly
I've wanted to do that. But yes, the actual Dollhouse stream is on. There will be no Bionicle.
No, why? That's not, all right, let me keep going. If you want a little bit of context on this.
So I think it was actually, I think it was an offline chat one day where we were talking about
this. And let me just be very, very clear about something. This is not, this is not just going to
be some little basic stream where, oh yeah, I guess like he's just going to kind of do that.
Like we'll like control it. You have no idea. This is, so I've talked about the Carnival in the past
and how a lot that, how much time that took and how much work that took.
This is the Carnival probably times 10 with the amount of stuff, the amount of
monetary financing that went into this, the amount of people, the amount of work.
It's Carnival times 10. What does purchasing and buying have to do with that? Well,
think about it. When I say you have control over most aspects, what does that mean? You're,
think about that. I'm so excited. I'm like at the brim right now. And I knew it was going
to be hard for me to like actually play because, oh, that's been eating me up for a long time.
I don't know if people have a ton of questions, which I'm not, trust me, I know. I, I know you
have a lot of questions. Some of the, a lot of these I can't answer because I want this to be
very much a surprise. But man, if this were real, can you imagine the possibilities?
All right, let's continue. Context, context. Can you pee on command? You have to find out.
You're, you're going to have to find out at some point here. You'll have control over me
and my actions and we'll see how you do. All right. I need to do, I got it. This is going to
be like the living area. No, this would be like the, I don't know, it'd be like the kitchen,
living area. And another thing I wanted to say too, we have, there's so many like partnerships
and people. We are back working with Andy Mark. So many people are involved with this. It's not
even funny. Network Andy has done it. I mean, community Jake put a shitload of time into this
too. So, so many people have been putting time into this. It's, it's, it's been a wild journey.
All right. I need to do, I don't want like stones in here. Metal? I just want like a nice gray,
a nice gray like wood or linoleum. Yeah. I can't just do like gray. I want gray. Get out.
This'll do. One of these. How's that? That's fine. With these hands, I hold the fate of a million
people. What if we tell you to end the stream? Don't worry. I've got it. It would just,
if anything, this is going to be one of the most wild experiments we've ever done. Yeah. The scale
is probably about five plus times the scale of the carnival. How about just like a, do we have
like a pink, like a tile? This'll be the bathroom. Oh no, maybe like I need like a,
no, that's too pink. This is a massive bathroom. It is kind of a huge bathroom.
We've got to give the time zones. August 18th at 3 PM Eastern. August 20th at 3 PM Eastern.
August 21st at 12 PM Eastern. Here are your dates and times for the three
dollhouse streams. That's fine. It's too bad. There's a tile, right? Okay. And then I need a,
let's do the, let's do this from first. I need like paint. Make an outhouse. 12 PM. Wow. Yeah.
I can answer some questions, but not very many. How do I do? I want to just do paint on the walls.
How do I do that? Isn't it build mode? Walls, right? Oh, here we go. This is like a kitchen area.
Let's do like this. It's really fucking ugly. Anything lighter? How's that even uglier?
That's fine. We have school in August. That's just going to order a computer and have you sit at
your desk all day. These rooms are enormous. Well, I'm trying.
Hold shift. All right. That's right. That's right. Maybe. Hold on. Okay. I wasn't listening. When is
it happening? It's happening. All right. August, August 18th, 20th and 21st. There you are. I can't
see what you guys do. Okay. Now I need to do, let's get a door on here. Doors. How about
this is a regular door. Just need a regular door. These external doors.
That was a regular door. I need a hallway. Why do I need a hallway? I have my first house here.
What is a Frank proof door? It's just open. Oh shit. I didn't paint that.
There it is. It looks good. Now we need some appliances. I'm just starting. Did you miss
the announcement? You may have. Refrigerator. Just a standard fridge. Don't need anything crazy.
How much do I have? 10,000. That's good. I need a stove. That looks good. I don't need that much.
We need to get jobs first. How long are the streams going to be? Well, that depends on a few factors.
That depends on how well you guys do. That depends on a few things. I need a sink too, I think. Yeah.
Can I just get a white counter? I just want a regular counter. Just a white countertop.
We need to keep you alive. You'll see. Yes. I am under your control. I am your dollhouse.
You're going to have to make sure I don't fucking get murdered.
You're going to have to help me. I can't do it all on my own. That's too much responsibility.
There's so many questions. I'm so excited. I can't wait. I just want a regular counter. I
want just a white counter. I don't want to spend sim points. What the fuck are these counters?
Oh, fucking whatever. It's still really dark up here, isn't it? I need a window.
I need some windows. We got it on. Nightmare in-game. Yeah. I feel like I'm in the middle of
Main Street at Disney World. I don't remember this music. The parade just doesn't stop. Okay.
Oh, what about a carpet? I need a bed too. All right. The bed's going to be over here.
It's like watching a boomer use a computer for the first time. Oh, yeah? Because boomer's favorite
game is The Sims. It's probably The Sims 3. It's definitely not The Sims 4. Okay. Let's do a bed.
I don't need too much stuff. And then they can get in there. I just need a bathroom. I'm almost
ready. I'm trying to read. I'm trying to respond to as many things as I can. Sims 3 is better than
4. You know, actually, I probably would agree with that. All right. Bed. We need two beds here,
at least temporarily, because we're going to have multiple rooms soon. We just have two beds. How
comfortable are these? Are these not comfortable? Energy 8. Yeah, these are fine. I need one more of
those. You know what this looks like? This looks like the world's shittiest hotel. This is just you
walk in. This is a hotel room. But it's a good hotel at the same time. Two twin beds. Okay.
Now we just need some bathroom stuff. Let's go with some toilets. Oh, I thought that was a toilet.
Just a regular toilet's fine. This is huge. This bed. These are... It's so big. It's way too big.
Okay. This is a massive bathroom. This could be a bedroom too. Okay. Well, whatever. It doesn't
matter. I need a shower. I have it in a different style. I can. Is that gonna... I need a sink.
This looks good. I need a counter though. Why do I have to pay with sim points? That's stupid. I
don't like that. I don't like that. Oh, fuck it. Whatever. Just... We're gonna have a party in here.
They're gonna be waking each other up all the time. I don't think so. All right. We have... Do
everything we need just to start. I think we can start. Okay. Do we like each other? Do we hate
each other? Let's see. In the bathtub around? Is it wrong way? That's not the wrong... It was the
right way. Save the game. Holy shit. You're right. Squeaky clean. This person's really clean. All
right. Good. I don't have any lights. Save. Why is the bathroom so big? Just because it is.
It's a public bathroom. Is he stalling still? No, I already talked about it.
Why is it taking so long to save? That was way too long. All right. Everyone, go in here.
Check out the new... Check out your place. We'll see the... It's three. Okay. Don't show me this
ever again. This is Bugleberry's house. Do you like the toilet? Good. Okay. So who wants to get the
first job? It sounded like fucking early Kyler. Jower? How come they don't share a bed? Because
we're housemates. We're not like together. There are no lights. I'll add lights. Just give me a
second. Oh, that's so ugly. Oh, I hate it. Oh, it's the worst. I really don't like it,
but I'm going to keep it. Okay. We need a light switch, right? Hey, you know a motel? Yes.
Expand it by 500% and just have all this extra space and then put that into a house, please.
These are the worst lights ever? They're fine. Where's the light switch? 500 times more space.
Oh, we need toilet paper. All right. Should I be evil and have it be behind?
By the way, the toilet paper needs to be close enough to the toilet where it's reachable,
but not far away enough where you have to reach behind you. I've seen this before and I know. Fuck
that. If the toilet's too close to the paper, you do the weird thing where you're unrolling the paper
and it kind of like starts touching your legs and stuff. I don't like it.
Reaching behind you to get toilet paper is awful. Table, roof, ceiling, lights. I'm working on it.
What about your Instagram? I don't have an Instagram. Did Ludwig ever give you the bidet? No.
I need to refer back to a tweet I made. I think I made this tweet like eight years ago.
I only have like one or two pieces of social media. It's my Twitter and here and like YouTube.
Don't refer to the tweet I made like seven years ago about accounts that I don't have,
that I don't own, that were just made. I don't know what they are.
That was three. Have you forgotten about Discord? All right, let's keep going.
Can I do a bidet recommendation? Ludwig, I think, is going to give me a good one.
He has an exact one that he was going to do. He knows exactly which one to give me. That's what
he said. What was that radish tweet? I like radishes. I don't know. It just made me laugh
that I have that many on the plate. People were really concerned about that tweet, by the way.
Dude, what the fuck? You don't eat this, right? Yeah, I did. I ate all of that. It was good.
I like radishes and I like sandwiches. It just like looked really sad. I don't know. It was a
way to like, uh, that's like what you're, that's like what you send to your mother to prove that
you're eating. You know, like, oh, you're at college, honey. Well, how are you doing?
Ma, look, I got, I'm fine. Okay. Are you eating? Yes, I'm eating. Let's keep going. I want to do,
uh, health store actually. Oh yeah, lights. Everyone was mad about lights.
Ceiling lights. Let's be against a wall. I don't think I can, oh, no, no, no, roof. Somebody
should put a roof on. Roof, roof, roof, roof, roof. Here, look. I feel like this is what Pee-wee's
playhouse looks out, like from the outside. How about just, just sand. Thank goodness. I got a
fairy tale character lives in here. All right. That's fine. I don't need it. Okay. The roof is
done. All right. Get this off. How do I get the roof off? Walls down, walls cut away, right?
Okay. Here we go. Is this your first Minecraft house? Kind of is. What is going on here? How do
I get out of this? How come the walls aren't cutting away? Down, cut away, up. Walls up,
walls down, walls cut away. Do page down. Oh shit. Wait, what? Oh, I see what you mean. Okay.
All right. That's a Will Ferrell elf music. These, they've been just talking out here for like,
it's fucking four hours. All right. Where is, all right. Somebody go, where, where's their thing
that says how good they're doing? Here it is. All right. Fun. We need some fun stuff. Outdoors.
You go buy a car? What? Sloppy jalopy? I kind of want to, I want a car. I want a sloppy jalopy.
All right. How about a TV? Yeah, that makes sense. Doesn't it? Sort by function,
appliances, entertainment, treadmill. You know, I, can I just like sort stuff by alphabetically?
I don't like having like 40 tabs open. Like I just, there's like five different,
10 different subcategories. I just want like a list of stuff. Bathroom, bedroom, living room.
You're gonna have to have a cheap TV, a little couch. That's fine. Big motel.
How do you like that? Let's move. Oh, get the paper.
Uh, let's find a job. Within bedroom walls? Like a divider. All right. Read it.
Available jobs. Rad Elbertson, I think should be doing, I mean, that's perfect. 25 bucks an hour.
They look like coffins. They do look like coffins. Also something else that I want to make sure I
make very clear to everybody. Um, so because, so Twitch, this is another part of the, kind of the
whole stream going on. Um, so Twitch is giving us a significant amount of money to do this stream
coming up here in a couple of weeks. And one of the things that were kind of our agreement with
them was we were going to run ads. Uh, so they're going to be ads on those streams and in pretty
much until the stream happens. So what we're going to do, I'm going to try to do this in as
non-egregious way as I possibly can. So what we're probably going to end up doing is on BRBs for the
next, uh, it's not going to happen on the next stream, but it'll happen this stream. Uh, we'll
probably do a couple minutes of ads, two or three minutes of ads. So that's part of per our agreement
with Twitch and they have, I will tell you that's for, for the amount of money and the amount of
help that Twitch has given us for this. It's a, it's, it's worth doing. It is. So, uh, I want to
see if I can test to see if it works. So we're going to test it right now because if I can't get
it to work, uh, I'm going to be a little concerned, but let me make sure we are going to do
right now. I'm going to go pee. I actually haven't peed in like three hours. So we're going to run
two minutes of ads right, right now. And hopefully it works because this is a good place to test it
because we need, I need to make sure this actually is going to work for the actual days. Let's do,
let's give it a check. That's right. I'll be right back. I'm going to go pee. I'm going to get
another probably coffee or so, and we'll try it out. Let me know if you don't apologize. Well,
I want to try, I want you guys to have a good experience and everybody else does too. So I'm
going to try to do this the best way I can. I'll be right back in five minutes. We'll try two
minutes and see how it goes. Okay. Hello. Uh, so how'd it go? Didn't anybody see them? Did you guys
see the ads? It's up. Did people see them? I want to make sure it works. Depends. Okay. I got two.
Okay. Uh, and I want to just take a second. I know this stream has been a lot. This has not
necessarily been a like sim stream as much as it had been. Hey, here's what's happening. I want
to give you guys enough notice. But this is very important. Um, I am not going to make any money
from this, this event at all. I will not, I'm not going to be able to take a cent from any of this.
All of this is going to go towards production. Make sure people are being paid. I'm not taking
a dollar from this because I can't, because that's how we have a good show. Um, so if you're
wondering, which has given us a significant amount of money, but all of it and then some, uh,
is going to be spent solely on the show. Um, I want people to know that. So if people maybe
think that like, Oh man, what's this fucking deal? He's got how many people? He's probably
making bank. No, I am not. If this is to make sure that we have enough money to be able to do the
show, I'm not going to be taking any money. It will be probably impossible. Uh, if you have no
context, I'll give you a little bit of context. We're doing a dollhouse. Well, you will control
me for three streams. We have an amazing extension team. This is not going to just be a click map
guys. This is a custom built extension created for this stream. Running ads is something that I have,
you know, I'm trying to do my best with it, right? Um, and just to let everybody know it's,
this is only for this broadcast stuff. Um, I'm not planning on running ads on it in a permanent
setting, but just so you know, I'm not going to see anything from this. Well, I am going to see
something from this. You know what I'm going to see from this? I'm going to see an insanely fun
experiment. I'm going to see a bunch of people put together something that hopefully is crazy to
experience. Um, so I want to make that clear. You can, Oh man, he's probably making bank.
No. Um, and I'm incredibly excited. I'm very nervous is probably not the right word because
I'm just kind of bottled up. I've been trying to, I've been holding onto this for a long time.
There's been so much work, but I'm very, very excited. I hope it's as fun as I think it's
going to be August 18th, August 20th, August 21st. Give us some more ads. You will. You'll
probably get them every 45 minutes to an hour or so. Maybe I think is when we're probably going to
try to run them. Wanted to make that clear. Let's continue to just chill and hang out.
I will answer some more questions if you'd like to hear about them and let's go back to the game.
Hope you become a billionaire. I, I don't want to become a billionaire. No, thank you.
That sounds, that's, I don't want it. I don't want that just too much. That's too much.
All right. Uh, uh, rad should take that Monday, Tuesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday,
25 bucks an hour to start. Holy shit. All right. Yeah, let's do it. All right. What about, uh,
what about, uh, bugleberry? Wait, did I put like a little divider here?
For me, you owe me money after you crashed the jet pack. Am I paying for your jet pack?
Why don't ever let me use a jet pack. What are you talking about? Pay him back. I don't even,
I didn't break anybody's jet pack. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. We need a divider here. Is this going to
work? No, that's not going to work. I guess it may be, it kind of will. Oh, that's a very,
that's ugly. That's very ugly. I don't want that. A little smaller. How about a prank proof door?
Okay. That's fine. There you go. Now you have some privacy. So go to bed if you want to go to bed.
Stop. Why are you in bed anyways? What are you? It's like, what time is it?
Share this memory. Cars cannot be placed in a lot with no parking spaces. Buy a parking space.
Oh shit. Okay. I want a parking space. I want a car parking space. Our spot parking space. Oh,
okay. Cool. How about like right here? And then how about the jalopy? Perfect. Whoa. Can I actually
leave? Drake it Josh. What's wrong with you? Stop. Unfinished room. This room needs proper
flooring and wall coverings. Oh shit. Shut up. Paint. Oh, gray. Whatever. Page up, right?
Okay. It looks good. Veiled germa clones. They just stay in the weird hotel. Tank? Join the
military. This is a wish. Hold on. What are they? What are you watching? I thought that was a
PlayStation. Put a window into the room. What are you going to do? What are you going to tell? How
are you going to woohoo on your stream? No. No, there's not going to be any woohooing.
All right. Go to the bathroom. Take a bath. Take a dump. Brush your teeth. What time is it?
All right. It's 1240. Can you just go somewhere? Make preferred veer. Go to community lot. Go to
community lot. What does that mean? Whoa. Go to select destination. Graveyard? What are you doing?
Oh, I thought he was running. Why did you go to the graveyard? Holy shit. That was fast.
Your Sims record important events in their life. Okay. So what are they looking for? He wants a
theater production. Get a part-time tour of the mausoleum. Explore the catacombs.
Is everybody even here? Tillman Abbot. Engrave. What do you mean, engrave? I'm not going to
engrave somebody's stone. I don't even know this guy. Okay. What a spooky setting. Rad
Alberton just took a visit to the graveyard. He won't forget the creepy dark corner nor the
side of the ghosts. What ghosts? I'm not going to do this. Why can I do this? No, that's not right.
What about this one? Oh, Tatiana. Oh, no. Oh, don't want to mourn this one. What? Who is this?
You don't want to mourn this person. Why? Okay. There you go. Go explore the catacombs. All right.
Who's here? Wait, who's this? Does somebody live here? What is this place? Let's go. I'm going in
here. What the hell? What is this place? Why is there a bar down here? What the fuck? Who's down?
Who is this? Why is there a person down here? This is actually really weird. A mixologist.
All right. Examine this thing. This is a cultist. Um, okay. Well, let's be, let's go. Okay. Dance
together? Drinking milk? This is the weirdest shit ever. You're going to get sacrificed?
I'm going to order a, let's buy a round of drinks for everybody. I only have $500.
You're going to get haunted? Can you actually get haunted? All right. At least I'm having fun.
Stop this. It's still going. You know the weirdest part about this? None,
neither one of us has spoken a word. Zero. No interaction. We're just doing this. Stop. All
right. Enough. All right. Let's buy a drink. Around for everybody here.
Morning the loss. What an odd slab of stone. Gazing at it makes me sleepy and thirsty.
What? All right. Let's get around drinks for everybody. Have we changed to something else?
Lie down on the stone. I can't think of an easier way to make sure that the rest of my life sucks
and to lay down on a weird coffin that I don't know what's in there. Romantic drink.
All right. Let's get them. Did you make a soup? Hey, those are mine. Those are my drinks. Put
that down. You can't have two. That was for everybody. What is Bugleberry doing? Oh,
scraps. Give me them. Form a special angler. Let's be really rude.
Where am I going? Oh, I have to go to the bathroom. I'm going to check on Bugleberry.
He's still just watching TV. He hasn't done anything. Having a blast. Bernard is having so
much fun. It's almost criminal. All right. I'm hungry. I need to eat some. What are food?
Can I sleep here? I want a single... Oh, wait. Who bought... $27? $27 bucks for a junk stew.
Oh, I was going to see if I could eat it. I guess I should say hello. All right. Just converse.
Let's give mixology advice. I got to go home. What's wrong here? Creepy graveyard. There was
a little too much ice in that drink. We need to make some friends. Why did you hang out at
the creepy graveyard? I just saw it was available. I just clicked it. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. Wait. Don't get mad. Wait, she likes me? That's more important. Hold on.
Rad is okay. Oh, I thought... My name is Rad. She doesn't think I'm Rad.
Okay. Um, romantic. Ask sign. I hate Rad. Why? Why?
Is it still dark? Scorpio. Those signs are compatible.
Scorpio. All right. How about... Are you single?
I need to turn the brightness up. Are you guys single?
On the stone? That is so fucked up. That is so fucked up. You almost should tie that person
out for like 30 seconds, right? We have to give something. We have to like give you some,
like a little slap. We have to give you something, right? Because like, go on.
That's a 30 second timeout. Are we flirting? This music is terrifying to have in the background.
Okay. I know she's a Scorpio. Make... No, no, I'm not going to ruin it.
The sims just became friends with another sim. Cool. Okay. What's her name? Margarita.
Margarita Savoy. Single. Who did you guys meet? Oh, next to a fucking dead vampire.
Is he naked? Can you turn the TV off? Good. All right. He's asleep. Okay. You're very alluring.
What are you doing? Watch the neck. Watch the neck. She's going to bite the neck.
This is where she goes like... And her teeth. She's got these huge fangs and she's just like...
All right. I got to go to bed. I'll call her tomorrow.
All right. It's time to go home. Go, go, go. I haven't had enough of this.
They're just doing this on their own. Somebody has work tomorrow. I'm really high. Can I get a
hell yeah? Have a good time. Romantic visibility. Your sims started a new relationship in a
neighborhood like this. It definitely won't go unnoticed. Would you like to learn more about
romantic visibility? Give him a hell yeah. All right. Hell yeah. Hell yeah, dude. All right. Go
home. Looks good. Speed it up a little bit. He's going to get up. What does he need? Hunger? Bladder?
I need money. You're going to get a job, Bugleberry. Like now. Is the paper here somewhere?
Donate to Burgess Hogan United? Donate to secret squids? It wouldn't mean donate.
Brad Albertson is sleeping on a community lot. He always remembered getting so tired that he
decided to wait. What? I sleep in the graveyard? All right. Get up, get up, get up, get up.
Big lemon. Get up and go home. Where's the car? Where's the car? 3 a.m. challenge.
Guys, Spider-Man has called my phone at 3 a.m. Don't answer the phone. Thanos called me at 3 a.m.
Got the Joker called me at 3 a.m. Don't answer it. It sounds like they have Buddy in like a
party store costume. Oh, Spider-Man. Oh, no. Spider-Man's here. It just looks like he's
in the Spider-Man pajama outfit. He's getting like waving like he's shooting the web into the
camera. And it never sounds like any of the characters either. I've seen a lot of these
videos. Trust me. Like, oh, dude, Thanos. Don't answer the phone at 3 a.m. Thanos is calling.
What do I do? Guys, Thanos. Answer. Hello? Hey, you called me. You're dead. What?
Sus guy at 3 a.m. Should I? All right. I'll make that video. I swear to God.
I swear to God. I will make this up. Don't answer the phone from the sus guy at 3 a.m.
It's not going to take very much time, right?
Do not call the sus guy. Yeah. Yeah, that's another funny part. It's like, oh, do not call
Spider-Man, right? How did you get? Why does Spider-Man have like a random cell phone number?
They always call and Spider-Man answers and it's like annoyed that they called.
Like, why are you calling me? Would you get this number?
Why does fucking Dracula have a cell phone number? Why does Thanos have a cell phone? But if you
think about it, he would, wouldn't he? Wouldn't Thanos have a cell phone number? No. Why not,
though? Remember, those videos are for children. Dude, do not call this person at 3. Go to bed.
What are you doing? Get in here. Oh, no, he's awake. And this is fictional, but he's from
another galaxy. Yeah, but if he was going to be on Earth for a significant amount of time,
you would think he would want a communication device that worked. Why do you guys think that
his alien technology is going to get the signal to be able to work on Earth? We have our own signal
system, our own network system. Guys, 5G does not work on like Jupiter's moon. His cool tech will
work in his own galaxy and shit, but why would it work here? How do you know? Haven't you seen
Independence Day? They just hijack our satellites. He has a heli- Thanos has a helicopter. Thanos does
not have a helicopter. But anyways, I will do the don't call the sus guy at 3 a.m. I have to make
that video. Now I need to. All right. What time is it? You have work soon, right? So I can just
drive to work. OK, so 1 p.m. So I have a little bit of time. What do I need? Oh, fuck, I'm going
to be this bad. These beds suck. Thanos copter is real. Thanos does have a helicopter in the comics.
In a 60s villain helicopter. All right, so I got to go to work.
Why is there a carpool coming? What? Why do I have this? That was my car. What? You can work.
Your sim can work in a variety of ways using options. Yeah. Every career has several options
available to them. Oh, yeah. You can like work hard, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. OK. All right. Work
hard. Take it easy. Meet musicians. Chill with musicians. Study music. All right. Business as
usual for now. Any acting tips? What the fuck, dude? Why would you ask me that right now?
Fucking busy. Always be ready. Always be ready to act no matter what. You can be brushing your
teeth. You can be talking to your family. Always be ready to act whenever it needs to happen.
Always acting. That's right. I thought you were really crying. That's right. Thanks a lot. Can
I turn off these stupid like they're fucking putting everything on Snapchat? Jesus bugleberry. All
right. All right. Get the paper. All right. Wait. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You're always
pretending. That was Norman. That was Norman Bates. That's not that's not the guy from Spider-Man.
OK. Film career. It's Norman Osborn. What is what is not Christian Slater? What's Christian Bale?
What's his character's name in American Psycho? Patrick Bateman, Norman Osborne, Patrick Bateman,
Norman Bates. I don't I don't know who any of these people are. OK. Bringing chaos into focus.
Should it be a movie career? Culinary. Music. Film. All right. Let's have bugleberry be a chef.
Starting immediately. 3 p.m. Oh, it's from Psycho. OK. All right. Take a shower. Let's get you ready.
Take a shower. Have a snack. What are these graham crackers? Oh, waffles. All right. Eat the waffles
and then go pee and you're ready. Norman Bates is Psycho. Patrick Bateman is American Psycho.
And Norman Osborne is Spider-Man. Yes. How am I doing at work? Not bad. All right. Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. 3 p.m. I start tomorrow. What does Bugleberry do all day?
He was watching. Why is he doing this? Who is putting the plates in front of the TV like this?
It's kind of weird. There's no table shit. I don't have enough money for a table.
Why is your shit catching room so pooping, popping, whatever?
No, I want you. No, no, no. Get in there. Our stop contemplating surroundings and take a shower.
Our energy is fine. I should send him to do something fun while he's at work.
No more TV. Get up. Get up. Get up. Let's go somewhere. What is this?
Is it Plumbob Pictures Backlot? Whoa, wait a minute. This is like a Hollywood studio.
What's this? Land Marine Science Facility? What's this? The Grind. Oh, these are bars. What's this?
How about the Banzai Lounge? Yeah, go. Why not? Do you drive? Do you drive, right?
Yeah, okay. How do you train a dog? I'm getting a dog in a month.
I'm going to give you the honest answer here. I have not had to train a dog in a while.
Otto was a rescue. He already was house trained and he already was trained.
$125? Did I just pay $125? Am I not allowed in his club? Asked to get in.
Um, how about special? Bookworm? How about books? There's nobody even in here.
Can I get in?
Am I back from work? Yeah.
Oh, lazy streamer purchases a pre-built dog. You're not getting in. I dare you to try to sneak
past me. I'm boring. I dare you to stop. I'm trying to sneak in. All right. Will you get out
of the way? Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Go. Wait. Hey, can you get me in? I'm trying to
get in the club. Hey, can you get me in? All right, Bianca, let me get me. You got to get me
in the club. Form group. This is weird. Okay. So we formed a group. Cool. Hanging out sounds like
fun. Do you know any good bars? Yes. This one in here with me. Can we get in? Look, I'm with Bianca
now. What the fuck are you doing? Why'd you ask me to hang out if you didn't want to do anything?
I'm bringing you to one of the most exclusive clubs in the city.
All right. Let's go. Let's go. How many stairs are in here? Oh shit. I got in. All right. I got to
mingle with the, this is the in crowd. Okay. I got to make friends with these really, really important
people. Order a party drink. All right. All right. Hey, hey, hey, who's this? This is celebrity. Holy
shit. I belong here. I've got a great celebrity. We're both celebrities. I'm going to have a
celebrity friend. What's he doing? Was he just doing like the cross? I'm boring. Why was he
like trying to impress celebrity? Talk about my wealth. I've got $646,000 in my bank account.
He doesn't buy it. Talk about my skills and fucking piano.
Oh shit. He likes the piano. I got to learn how to play the piano before I invite this guy over.
Fuck. This is like, this is every 90s comedy movie. Yes. I'm an extremely talented pianist
and I was studied under Rembrandt. Like really? No way. Wow. I can't believe that.
And then I have to learn how to play the piano in three days. Come back here. Come back here. I'm
not done. I'm back here. I'm not done. You know that I play the piano. I'm going to actually go
learn how to play the piano. Talk about the piano again. This guy's going to be my friend
and I have to, this is going to be great. The bar is almost full. I've almost completed the
family challenge in Double Dare. Come on, fill it up. You're almost there. Get a couple more
milks in there. You've got it. Come on, fill it up. Come on, mom. You can do it. You know, again.
How much is a piano? Oh shit. I can't impress him anymore. Am I tired? I'm forward. He snuck in.
All right. Well, that was cool. Bernard Elberton just got into the VIP section. He'll have to
record each and every important sim he sees in his scrapbook. Attempted to impress Alan Stanley.
And he wants to be left alone.
Oh, that was fun. Um, wait. I gotta answer my cell phone.
No, no, don't leave. Don't leave, don't leave. Stop, stop, stop, stop. No, no, no.
I'm trying to take a picture with them. No, no, no, no, no. Wait. Come here. Write,
write, rewrite, rewrite, rewrite. I want to take a picture, take a picture,
take a picture, take a picture cell phone. Take a picture, take a picture of this Leopard.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Don't take a picture when he's in the bathroom.
He's in the bathroom. I'll just wait till he's out
Take a picture. I'm wait. I'm waiting till he comes out. I need oh, I want to get it said
I could take a picture with him
Okay. All right. All right. All right now go take it out. Take it out. Take it out. Take it out. Take it out. Oh
God damn it. Whatever fuck it. You've gone. All right. There's another celebrity to impress. I wanted to go home anyways
All right, who else is here?
Mixologist or the celebrities are the only person here
I'm just gonna stay here. I'm gonna camp out here
They can't kick me out right the vote if I just stay here this I can sleep on the floor
Look if I never leave
Then they get I don't have to leave or they can't kick me out. That's like an open 24-7. Oh shit
What is he doing? All right, you're asleep. You're happy. You're just hungry. Okay, where are you going drinking a regular drink?
Where you going get back up here? Do not leave
Don't leave you need to sleep sleep upstairs. What are you doing? What are you doing? Oh, I can't stop him closing
Okay, I'm about to walk by this guy's about to be mad that I can
All right. Well, now I need to buy a piano
How much is piano? What would it be categorized as?
study
Obvious and skills. Oh my god. It's
$5,000. Oh
700 okay. I need some more money. We'll get it tomorrow. I need to eat too
All right. Well, it's fine. I'm sure you saved. Yeah, save right there
I'm gonna request work off for one of the dollhouse streams. Do you think it'll be worth it?
Um, I can't tell you what you should and should not do but there will be three streams
So there's gonna be a lot of content
I'm driving the car. Right? Yeah the piano in the bathroom
It's wrong with me. Why is this scary music being played?
Why is this scary music?
Nothing here. What that was just bugleberry's theme
All right, go to bed. Oh my god. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up
He's still in the car. He's gonna steal the car get up
Hey
Why can I fight him? Hey, I can't click on him quick into the sloppy jalopy and chase him all the cops
I don't have a phone. Are you kidding? Do you really just take that dick couch burglar? You have a mobile phone? Oh
Shit, okay, right. I need that piano. The only item of value was stolen
I mean the TV is probably worth something right build a wall around him and trap him
Can you do that?
dirty dishes
Alright, let's clean clean up clean up clean up
Call household to meal grab a plate. Wait a minute. I
Can eat this we're gonna put it in the bathtub
Everything about this is crazy
Eating rotten waffles in the bathtub
All right, clean it up. Well nauseous. You may want to keep him around a bathroom from disgusting food
I clean clean clean clean it up
It's good, right clean the toilet, too
Thank you. Okay, and I gotta go to work in
Like an hour just watch a little bit of TV just on the ground work out. No watch TV and then
That's all I can really do and then pee and then I gotta go
What's happening?
The TV exploded maybe you
What am I doing? I've grasped the basics of cooking. Okay. No, no, no way way way. It's him
I was like, what am I doing in the bathroom? All right time to go to work
I'm not a terrible mood now when you get back. When do you worry after work? He used to work, too
Hey, all right 3 p.m. It's 12 right now. What do you need? Hungry? You sim is a cell phone call
Answer an incoming call on a sim. So select the inventory panel and click on the cell phone icon
Inventory panel and then cell phones
Okay, the dish showdown the head chef at the restaurant
Is holding a competition to see which locals can prepare the best dish
Prepare something special and bring it to the restaurant quickly to enter in the competition. There's a cash prize. Okay, where is it?
Yeah, let's do it. All right, how about um, all right, let's have it
How about um, all right, let's have let's serve have lunch. What should I bring?
Of any recipe. Okay, let's make um
What's happening? Who's beeping? Who's beeping at me take all can I just put like a cabbage in there?
Okay, serve lunch serve lunch. Why can I not make anything?
Is it work?
Wait, it's rad. Oh shit. It's rad. Okay fix the tv. Hold on the salad in your inventory
I don't have time for that. There's no room on the counter. I'm not gonna get fired. I don't care
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no stop stop
Stop, I don't want you to go to work
No you
Whatever. I won't eat this so I can make something
All right, I can afford the uh piano
Invite margarita over
All right. I promise we'll have margarita come over right now
grab some food
and then
Take a shower
Watch a little bit of tv and then call margarita
I'm gonna call to invite over
I'm gonna put a piano in the bathroom
I mean kind of
All right call
Oh, you're back. All right. Now you need to make something
uh
All right, grab a plate of this because you're hungry
And then we're gonna watch tv together and then we're gonna make you're gonna make something
No, don't take a bath. That takes way too long
Where are you gonna sit?
um
I can fix that right now watch this
Let's get like a cheap uh couch
It's the cheapest thing I can buy 225 dollars
Whatever
Oh
Remember your bathroom is way bigger than your bedroom. Please fix this. It's gonna ruin my night
I won't be able to sleep until I know the sims don't have to live in this hell you've created
Just you it's
I'll put hold on
Here watch
There you go. Fuck. I'm out of money. I don't have any money left
There better now. This is this is a room now
I'll paint it later
Wait, do I get money if I delete this I do? Okay. Yeah, let's go delete it. Oh, hell. Yeah
Okay, and then I get rid of the floor too
There we go
Fucking finally. I'm fine
I'm fine
All right piano
There it is. Okay. Now you learn how to play the piano get rid of the door
Oh now I gotta learn the piano by friday
Oh, sorry, mr. Elberton, I hear that you acquired the pianist I am play us something
Um
It was bait come on quick quick quick. We're gonna learn the piano and then call him
He's just sitting here laughing at this
Go do something didn't were you supposed to call somebody? All right, come over. It's 2 a.m. Whatever
Oh, whatever
Okay
Still this cooking competition that I have to do
unfinished room
What's wrong with this place? How's it unfinished?
asleep
What makes this unfinished
Which wall is not finished it's the bathroom wall what's going over here
It's 10 mood
Is it the outside of the house that they're talking about?
All Thanos no
Inside right?
I just started attack on titan. Can you please say aaron? I used to hate it, but now I think it's funny
Well now you like it
Now you think it's funny. Don't you?
Now you want me to do aaron
I got a lot of shit for that
A lot of shit do the roar. What's up with the bathroom sink?
Oh
Yeah, what is up with the bathroom sink? It's fucking disgusting
I get one point at least so I can impress the guy. Okay. Good
Basics of piano
All right, you can stop stuff. Stop go to bed
Do I need food? No, I need to sleep. All right, you're done
Aaron there it is. All right, you well we did it
I mean that was I half asked it but I did it
Do it again do it full power
All right
Fine aaron aaron aaron aaron
You know, I saw a thread somewhere that said that
I'm actually kind of sad that I have not that he has not done that in a while
It was like man like I actually kind of miss that he did that like he hasn't done it like two or three weeks
I'm I kind of miss it. There you go
84 bucks pay the bills
Oh, by the way, I can't wait to do the battleship tournament. That's probably I think that's happening this week
I want to say thursday or friday and i'm gonna i'm gonna confirm that with uh ludwig. Well, i'm in the semi-final. I moved on
Continuing my quest to continue to win
In the battleship tournament. All right, it's time for everybody to get up. Who cares omega lull
Well, whatever
Fine, you need a fucking garbage can. All right. I'm hold on
I need a garbage can
This video game consoles
All right. This thing's like 10 bucks
I'm at 25 dollars for a garbage can. Are you kidding me?
Is it really that expensive? This is like 10 years ago, too
But it's that germa really is just a sussy guy at this point. He has no star perspective. It just compiles
Implies it to whatever chat says it really makes me sad
If you missed the announcement, I will give you an announcement of the last announcement
Uh, we were doing a three day dollhouse stream
You guys get to control me in a house
We have an ex an incredibly extensive extension that is being made custom built for this purpose
It's gonna be a three day event
You guys will have a ton of control over pretty much everything
And the people that are working on the extension is ghost commander, which is kraken
And kraken's team
You've been aware of any things they've done before
They're putting a lot of time into this
What'd you do?
You've burnt it
That was disgusting
On top of that, we also have andy mark
Is participating completely they're on board as a full they're doing everything
But we've got this like trifecta team
Andy mark is back
And a lot more people on this project than any of the ones ever that you've ever seen here twitch is involved
We have a significant amount of financing from twitch. This is this is the big one practice the piano. He's still sleeping
Five bucks did you get vaccinated because you chose to get vaccinated? Uh, yes
part of the part of the I mean, obviously
This project has a lot of people on it
And i'm not fucking around
There's gonna be a significant amount of people that are gonna be coming and going through this whole project
So we're trying to err on the side of complete caution trying to get everybody vaccinated before the project
Um, because I am fucking around
Why'd you get jay and jay?
I got jay and jay because
by the time
That the project was going to be I mean august 18th, right?
If I had gotten one of the mrna vaccines, I would have had to get the second dose way too close to the project
and I am not taking the second dose of uh, the
Pfizer and moderna vaccines and getting wiped out from like two three four five days of side effects
Like the week of the stream because that's when it would have to line up
Like can you imagine like oh it's it's august like 16th time for your second dose of like Pfizer
And the stream is in fucking two days
I got the j&j vaccine and it wiped me out for like four days. I had a high fever
I felt like we could sloppy. Oh, yeah
So I was trying to make sure I could avoid any side effects and i'm glad I was able to do that
Have you been reacting to electronics at all weirdly? No, I can't say I have how does 5g taste?
All right, they hate this room. I gotta fix it. The social is fine. J&J knocked me out, too
Yeah, and I know we've got a bunch. What are you doing? Why are you watching this? This is weird
Um, I completely forgot what we were just talking about
Oh, it's because the one and done thing but the whole thing with the delta variant now
We're still trying to figure out how effective everything is
Is it that we're gonna need boosters? Should you take a booster? When should you do it? It's getting fit
But the one thing that I can say is being vaccinated at least at the very least it will be enough
Immunity built up for me not to have a major major problem, right?
Because if you see I think you can you can still technically what they call a breakthrough infection, right?
If you do get it
Then the theory is that you've built up some antibodies at least for your body to fight it and understand what it is
So you don't end up in the hospital
So maybe if you get covid you kind of feel like shit for a few days
Three or four or five days or something, but it keeps you out of the hospital and keeps a ventilator off your body and
I've got medical problems guys. I'm sure you're aware. I have all kinds of weird shit going on
I don't want to fucking end up in the hospital. You know, I I have
Colitis I have this mystery fucking chest pain
I don't want to end up in the hospital and plus like i'll also i'll gotta be really honest, too
Right when after I got the vaccine one of the things that I was always kind of concerned about and just kind of freaked
Out and everybody can relate to this. I think anytime you're out anywhere if you've like, oh i'm going to the grocery store
i'm at the i'm in the bread aisle and you just like hear two aisles over like
Like what the fuck was that? What was that motherfucker? Who was that? I'm out of here. I gotta go
I gotta get the fuck out of here immediately. I am running this other direction. I don't care if I need bread
I'll get it. I'll get it tomorrow
Right at least kind of gives me that
At least mental security that okay. I i've have some exposure to the virus
You hear if I hear anybody do that, I instantly just go the other direction you hear like a
Go to turn turn and you look back you're like fuck who the fuck was that?
God damn it. What are you doing here?
So it helps with that it helps kind of not make you have to freak out anytime you hear that
Touching any surface too. It's like oh, hold on. Let me get that door for you
I it's I just touch that I touch the door. I touched that I touched the door now i'm in trouble great
I gotta go wash my hands now. I've been doing i've been doing this to dine and dash for the past year
What?
Wait, wait, hold on a minute. Hold on. Wait
you
You've been dining and dashing because you hear somebody like what are you talking about? That's fucked up, man
That's wicked fucked up
I have my game
My game block
Hold on. Wait, wait
Oh, there we go. Okay
So
By anyways
The point i'm making is
It gives me at least enough comfort in my brain and i'd have to constantly and look I know that there's still risk there is right?
But it definitely makes me feel a bit better
Save the game. Oh shit. You're right
All right. Now it's time to run some ads
Those of you that missed
It's just like choked up
I'm fine. I just like choked on myself
Cringe ads, I just I know
Uh, we're gonna run i'm gonna go brb again. I'll be back. I'm out of here. No, I gotta go because I just
i'm fine
Don't run away
Okay, so we're gonna run some ads those of you that weren't here before. I want to make sure that you're aware
um
Because twitch has a significant financial involvement. They've given a lot of financial help for the streams coming up here in the next couple weeks
Uh, this is part of the agreement is to run ads
Every hour or so we're gonna run some
This is not a permanent solution. This is not a permanent thing
for this channel
This is just for the next i'd say a couple of weeks
Again, I want to make it really really clear again for those of you that weren't we you're not here
Um, i'm not going to make any money from these streams
Absolute zero
I will not I will not be making anything at all
Uh, this is just to make sure the production can go through without a hitch
So i'm gonna go brb we're gonna run a few minutes of ads and I will be right back
Thanks for watching. I'll be right back
Okay, I have returned
So I need to
All right, there we go
Mystery chest pain question centered or more on one side
It goes right through the middle of my body
Uh, I would say it affects the middle left
And that goes all the way through the back
around my flank
Had a lot of tests
Still trying to figure it out. All right, let's keep going
Oh long each day of streaming
um, we're we're gonna have to gauge it because
With the nature of you guys being able to do pretty much. There's a lot of shit
You guys are gonna be able to do
Give us more ads give us more. All right. I will I will I have to be better about running them
because
Uh supposed to run them, uh more frequently than I am but we start talking about stuff that I kind of like
Oh, right. Why I forgot
ads
All right, let's go back to the game remind me in like a half an hour
Okay
Remind me in like 35 minutes
Change category two ads
Get your timers ready
He's getting better
You should ask for prime
No, I don't I don't
If you sub to the channel you do if you don't you don't I don't that I don't i'm not concerned with that at all
Change the category to ants
Oh, is he playing so slow and fast forward? I'm what do you mean? What if I'm waiting for it? I'm waiting for two points
Your fitness instructor taught you to seek variety
Work out using the tv or stereo for go for a jog and swim for 30 minutes
I don't have a pool
Oh shit, go here. Yeah. Yeah
Can I go there?
That sounds pretty easy. All right workout in front of the tv
Do uh some cardio 30 minutes
No, not you not you you buffoon. Not you
Well, actually both you can do it
No, get out of here
Go back to the piano
Too fatigued
Oh fine do it tomorrow
All right, just take any recipe whatever he makes I didn't even make it who cares put it in your inventory
Oh god, what happened?
Fire fire fire fire fire call call call call call call call call call call call call quick quick quick go go go go call call call
Is that 120 bucks to get the fire department come here? Wait, we're in love
You want to hang out?
This is like a this is a porn
Stacy denson, okay
Let's have a little chat
Okay
Okay, how are you doing let's compliment personality
Bernard learned that stacy is a snob. Um, so wait a minute
Somebody finish this food
Newspaper, what do I have?
Play the piano, there's no time I got time. Okay, you want to go on a date?
You go learn go finish dinner
Replace for four hundred dollars, huh? That's not gonna happen
I use the burnt stove
All right, are we gonna be able to like hook up while she's here for the fire
What's wrong do you want to stay over
This burnt waffle is in the fridge don't puke in front of her don't puke in front of her anything but that
You want to stay over we invite a date
Get out of here stacy thinks bernard is being flirty
I gotta get these I gotta get these I gotta get a very big bed group conversation. No, fuck off
Confess attraction
Whoa
Get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way
What does he look at
Is it I have an idea
We're not just having a sleepover. We're gonna sleep over
Oh my god all this bullshit
Okay, get out go over and use like the sink or something
I'm trying to use the toilet. I think I have diarrhea. Where are you going?
Gonna use the piano I just pissed all over the place here. All right, he'll clear it up flirtatious joke
I thought I just went to the bathroom already. What the hell trap rad in the walls. All right. There we go
Okay, okay good
All right, take a shower and then she slept where's she gonna sleep I need to do bed
I'm selling rads bed fuck rad rad. I don't give a shit
$870
$870 how much were these?
What the fuck? Why was it so expensive?
Okay, that's this my bed. Um
What the hell
Get out of here we're not gonna eat we're not gonna sleep in the same bed
I need energy. All right, i'm gonna i'm gonna sleep and then we're gonna wake we're gonna wake i'll wake up
We can't get into the bed, oh shit, um, we can't get over there. All right, I need to expand the wall
80 bucks. That's not bad. All right. We're good
All right, all right go to bed go go go go go bed bed bed bed stop talking
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I want to hang out
I want to hang out. She just walked in here. Okay, get up get up. I want you to wake up this phone's ringing
Okay, let's uh, let's go over and watch
Don't be go over there go over there. What the fuck are you doing?
Oh shit, let's go came over here for a fire and didn't leave what
Um, um
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Don't want that go over there. Shit. Oh, wait a minute. Wait. Oh, we gotta
Okay. Well, thanks for coming to take care of the fire. I appreciate it. Whose car is that?
An art is extremely irresistible
Okay, I I have an idea. I'm gonna should we try to start a fire and see what happens
Will she just put on her firefighter outfit and take care of it?
Whose car is here?
Oh shit, it's you get up get up. You have to wake up right now and go to work quick
We should date
We're together exclusive relationship with stacy denson. All right cool
Wait home
What's wrong with me? Oh my energy is low
Hey, why don't you bring why don't you bring that into the bed?
She has stayed here longer than one day
Another victory royale
You met yesterday
Yeah, well
That's all right
Where does stacy live?
Why has she been brushing her teeth for four and a half hours?
uh
She was brushing her teeth. All right rad has left work rad earned 115 today good
Workout using the stereo. All right. Yeah, let's uh, do some exercising
30 minutes
All right, you need uh bugleberry's hungry
I got was he pissed. Why is this?
Hey
Be a dick. Why is he dressed like this?
All right, get up. What does he work?
What does he do?
he's a fan
fan
How do I still have a job I haven't gone to work ever
I've haven't shown up once to work
Why do I still have a job?
disgusted and hungry
These are burnt waffles
I need okay
Replace for 400 replace it
Okay, now we can make food again
All right. How you doing? That was cool. That was really nice
Holy shit, she can hold me
Can we go for are we going to uh date?
How am I still working out?
All right, how am I how am I doing on needs? I need to okay. It's time for it. It's time to say goodbye
It was really nice to see you. It was really nice to have you around
But I need to we need to stop
Take a shower. I'm gonna get ready. I'm gonna take a nap
He wants you brushing her teeth so long
vile surroundings
Oh
What's wrong who's smell it's him you smell get in there
Nobody cleans the toilet
Why do you live here? She just lives here. What are we doing?
All right, you need I need this you have to fix this fix it
Fix the toilet
Whatever. All right, you fix the toilet. Somebody has to fix it. It's disgusting in here. Okay, clean it. This is gross
Clean this up
Clean the sink
All right. This is not gonna be so disgusting in here now. It's time for ads
Uh, let me check
Save it first. It's been 15 minutes. Yeah, it hasn't been long enough. Oh, no, don't eat that
Why are we still eating the same burnt waffles?
Oh she
Holy shit
All right for a second. I thought she's gonna get a fire engine and I would have laughed really hard
That's the first time she's left since coming to put the fire out. All right. We've got some uh, we're good to go
I need to go home now. Okay. Well now we're dating clean
Okay, I need to make something
serve breakfast
Waffles and then i'm gonna bring the waffles put them in my inventory and serve it eventually. I thought the bed was on fire
I was like, what the hell just wait for the next alarm and she will live there
What's wrong with the fridge?
That's a gas coming out of the fridge
big bits
Yeah, as of as of like a year ago or seven or eight months ago or so
They no longer read bits
Uh, I mean I read them. It's not on stream. We talked about a while ago why that was
There's a few reasons why
Huge bits ignored ads not ran
You're a monster
No, we talked about this because it used to be I mean that there's a lot of people that potentially knew here
So let's we'll go over it very quickly
It used to be that anything over
I think was 250 in bits. I would read at the end of the screen. We'd have like a hangout session
um, but over the years
I kind of wanted to
There's two main reasons why it was pretty much 50 50
Is I didn't I want to stop incentivizing people to have to like pay
For me to like talk to them or read what they said
I don't want you to have to give me like 50 bucks for me to
Read what you said. It's a lot of money 100 bucks 50 bucks 20 bucks. That's a lot of money and
I would rather not incentivize people
to
Spend a bunch of money
With the hope that I would read their message
Um, it just kind of makes me uncomfortable
And the second part is because we used to those end of the stream segments used to be
Sometimes two hours long where we would just sit there and hang out
and
just talk
so
That's why I kind of got rid of it. You're an anti-money streamer
No, i'm not
Not really. I mean, I just
I just don't want to like encourage and incentivize people
To drop like 100 bucks for me to look over and read what you said
That's such an extreme amount of money
And what was happening was I was reading the big ones
So I was like, oh well, I got rid of the little ones like 250
But I get I mean i'll read the ones that are like 100 bucks. That's a lot of money, right?
I'm gonna read it
And it was incentivizing people to spend a hundred dollars
Uh, I don't want you to have to spend a hundred bucks to have me read your message
Somebody clean the fridge for god's sakes. Come on
Clean out bad food. There we go
Stop looking at it. What are you doing? That's that's how you make sure it doesn't cook at all
This thing can't even preheat and I still read out community sub sometimes like somebody gave 50 community subs before
But I think the difference between saying like thanks for like the 50 community subs, right?
is
People in the community are getting a sub you're able to
Uh the sub only stuff you're able to do the emotes and it's a little bit more
Tangible than just you just gave me
like a 500 dollars or something
Uh, but i've struggled with that for a long time
of trying to figure out
You know people give you a bunch of money. It's like oh shit. That's a lot of fucking money
Thanks for the that's a
extreme amount of money
um
I've always been essentially more comfortable people
treating this stream
Like you would treat something like netflix
You know like oh, it's just i'm gonna it's if you can want to give five dollars a month
You can you don't have to
I don't expect anybody to
But I don't it's it's not like okay, so if you had like a netflix subscription
You're also not giving netflix like 50 more dollars a month because you want to right you just yeah
I guess i'm I have to say it's 10 bucks a month or whatever, right?
Oh, dude free netflix. He's serious
Um, but I don't want anyone to ever think they have to give this channel money
You don't have to there's no reason for you to do so if you do
It's beyond my wildest expectations that people would pay five
Plus dollars to this stream every month. It's insane
So
I just don't I don't want people to think that they have to give money to this channel
So it's time for some ads
I wonder how many subs you just picked up with this conversation
And that's why I never like to really talk about this that frequently because I haven't been to work once
This character has not been to work one time
Um, i'm not gonna get fired because i'm not gonna answer the phone
So, you know thinking face
Oh, he got a raise
I'm practicing the piano leave me alone
Oh don't answer the phone
Just don't answer it. Oh shit the waffles. All right
Once I get this next point in music
Okay, put in put away. How do I put it in my inventory?
Oh shit, you got a bonus
All right, go to the bathroom quick
So you get promoted
Congratulations rads impressive performance has earned a promotion to a roadie
The band is going to need their sandwiches and soda as soon as possible. Don't forget to pick up their laundry
That's right. Rad is the music career. I'm the chef career yet
Rad has more cooking points and I have more music points
Don't go to work
Three hours late for work and you're gonna go
They're like four hours late
No, I i'm not there's no way i'm going to work the day is almost over. I think I actually oh we're gonna the diner
Yeah, here I am
The chefs at the restaurant were eagerly awaiting your injury, but you astounded all with your lack of effort
Don't make empty promises especially when it comes to delicious food
All right time to leave
I was only there for like 40 minutes
Earned 29 dollars today
Holy shit, what's the sketch problem? Oh, okay. We're good. When is when is the killing? There is no killing
I don't have any mods
All right. Did I do the workout?
Uh workout using the stereo or tv jog and swim. All right, let's go for a jog
Go for it 30 minutes, right?
Been 30 minutes
Whoa
I'm going back to this weird bar
Don't I know people in here? Oh, that's right margarita. Hey come visitor. Is it time for ads? Let's find out
Yeah, we're gonna play ad ketchup here
Let's see. Is it time for ads?
All right, we're gonna run some more ads if we're gonna run another three minutes
I'm playing ketchup. I didn't play them before
Let's do three more minutes
Ad time. I hope you hope you got something cool. Let's see what I get
Let's compare when we get back
All right, three minutes saying three minutes ad time somebody says you mother fucker
You mother fucker
Dude, you got an ad for the sims 3. No you way. I got an onion ring
Commercial. Wow
Give us ads. Well, you did they're running right now. There are no ads playing it should be you see
Yeah, well, it depends on what platform you're on
I only got another minute. I got a fortnight ad. Oh, is this a bit? No
Uh
I knew this stream was gonna be explaining this a few times because this is i've never done anything like this before but also
I will make it pretty clear again
Some of you know how much money the carnival was
This is way more than that
Way more and twitch is really really putting up a significant amount of money
So this is they're very they're being very very helpful. All right, I think we're good
like 15 seconds
How much money was the carnival? Well, that's um
You can find that info if you want to somehow I think i've talked about it once twice
But I don't want to talk about money. I don't want to talk about that. We're playing the sims 3
Is this the next stream? This is the stream that's happening on august 18th
So not the next stream
But the stream, let me see. I'll probably I will probably I will be live probably
Two two more times before you see this stream two or three, maybe I got the battleship tournament this week
We'll be live again next week
So we'll see we're playing it by ear. All right, I think we're all back
Thank you for your patience. Everybody appreciate it
Uh, all right, give me a reminder
In like another 40 to 50 minutes or so give me like another and like another hour or so give me another reminder
Let's continue. What what skill is he at right now?
Let's see
Fucking skills piano level four at what point would you consider?
Calling the celebrity to come hang out and me play the piano for them
And I gotta figure this out too. What is this unfinished room?
What's they're all finished aren't they?
Oh, it's this here. Okay. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it
It's this shit
How much money do I have do I have enough to do this?
There all right now be happy
There we go good
All right play
Hard to maintain a good relationship
I'm not hanging out with her. Why am I what's what's with the money? What's going on?
This is a boring conversation and I lost a friend
Uh, well, can I know can I get the friend back?
What the hell?
The philosophy was boring. All right. Well, how about if I just start just crying or something?
Turn this off
It might work out
You always gotta be ready to act that's right
I'm going omega mode
She's like just leaving
He just won't stop. He won't stop exercising
Okay
Meet someone new. Yeah, I promise invite margarita. Okay, I gotta invite margarita over
Still playing the piano
Do you think I can invite the guy over?
I think I could probably invite level five piano. I would say that's really good
lifetime happiness panel
lifetime rewards
Whoa, what's this?
the hustler
professional slacker
What does that do?
discount diner
All restaurant meals are on the house
They're cheats
How cool would it be to be able to watch tv and slack off at work without the boss caring?
Let's do that one
Still have a job, right?
Earn $25 from piano tips
What I can where can I play the piano?
I don't think here go go to the bar. You can play the bar. Oh shit. All right
Use the bathroom go to bed
7 a.m. Whatever I can i'm skipping work who cares
Play the bar piano in your backpack work more parties venues and play for tips
How do you put something in your inventory like this? Oh, okay. That's how you do it
What are these pictures?
This is making me want to dust off my laptop and play the sims 3
Uh, this is the best sims, right?
from everybody that's ever
played any of these games
Does this one have crazy mods too?
Like can I get people could run off my cars like they can on the fourth one pretty much
That's awesome
I'll have to play around with those
Uh, you need to go back to bed
See you later. The sims 2 is better than the sims 3. You know, I could probably agree with that. Maybe
Here's the problem
To get the sims 2 to run on any new hardware
You need a phd. I don't know why because the sims 1 worked and it used to be on the ea store
You used to be like I swear to god. I have this memory
Of being able to get the sims 2 from origin. What happened? It was they took it off the store. They removed it
Why?
It was delisted due to licensing with ikea
Is that serious?
I don't just take the I can't you just take the ikea stuff out of the game
All right. I'm gonna go to the bar. I'm gonna play some music
164 bucks good
All right, you need to I need to get you promoted
Go to the bookstore
What do you need to get promoted?
Okay, he's a roadie
music, too
I'm getting a new job
And what's the exercise career? Yeah, I mean i'm getting an athletic skill
Let's just quit
Find a new job. I'm living in the athletic department
Professional sports. There we go
better
Leave the music career
Good luck brownie. Why does everything smell?
Oh, I thought he smelled that was just the sim thing more lights in the house
Yeah, I think it's like something to do with the game. Let me turn it up again here
That better I don't want to blow it out too hard
That looks good
That looks more uh, actually what it looks like on my screen
clean clean clean
And that's it you're wasting money
All right now I need to have you
Quit this culinary career. They're both doing the opposite of what they should be doing
You know you get a career as a musician
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Go to the bar and play the piano
I just play it anywhere
Go answer that is your car facing the right way. It should be
Holy shit, that scared the hell out of me. I thought he's gonna crash
Oh my god, this is terrifying
Okay
Now let's play the piano
That somebody was calling me the whole ride over here
Sure. Let's go on a date. I know just the place
Um to uh
Hey, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no, no, you come to me come to me
Now, where am I going? Oh, we're going to the park. No, we're not. Um, where is she?
Wait, what are you doing? Nice directions
Take cell phone photo
Why am I driving all the way back? Wait, somebody wanted to take a selfie with me
at the bar
Uh, I wanted to take a picture of this guy that bad
I drove all the way to meet stacey at the subway station and decided no fuck that's
That was matthew hamring
I gotta get a photo of that guy
I freaked out and did a u-turn
Oh shit, I should mingle get your shit out. Get your shit out here
Why can't I take it out? Come on. Come on. Come on. I gotta impress this guy
No
You don't like it
This sucks
Wait, no, they like it
Autograph
I cleared this whole place out everybody left. Wait a second. Hold on. Wait a second
Didn't I want his autograph? Oh closing time. Oh, come on
We'll go go home
Where's he going?
Excuse me
Where is this dumpster? Holy shit, dude
You are really digging in there. I think this is fun
Amount of comfort dining chair was found by fernard while dumpster diving. It's 4 30 in the morning
Rooster utensil holder was found by dumpster diving
Stink mask perfume, holy shit
Iron was found I found iron in here. He's dying
Am I dying i'm not dying i'm making so much noise
Vomit where where am I vomiting?
Wait i'm going into the bathroom
All right. Um, oh shit. He's deranged
I'm deranged
I'm supposed to be at work. Oh my god, not bad driving conditions
Stop it. You're gonna kill him. Take it easy
Revolutionary dishwasher recently installed by the restaurant manager has just stopped working clean all the dishes in your inventory before the next shift. All right
What who just drove my car away? All right, go home go to bed. You earned it. There we go. All right time for bed
You did it. I got a lot of stuff
Where is it? Where's all the stuff that I got? It's in the build mode
Build mode inventory family inventory
Oh shit, look at all this stuff. I can just can I sell it? Oh my god. I have lamps now a paper towel holder
I need that
It's like this like malachite
smithstone
How much is worth?
a moth red admiral butterfly
Whoa
I got a termite
Grandma wholesome folk art thingy
Okay
Oh cool you kids cute
tissues
Uh a nice like towel rack
A a lamp I need some surfaces
This is free shit. Yes, right?
Yeah, I needed some end tables. It's like cheap ones a little cheapo
All right. Let's put those lamps on here. All right, cool
I'm gonna sell all this shit once it's out of the inventory
mail
All right, cool
elect rocks
Can I not sell those?
Are these things worthless?
There's a sell all button. They didn't have a num didn't have a money and not a monetary number on it
Okay, I actually have stuff now
Oh shit answer that
Answer that answer that answer answer answer answer answer the phone
answer the phone
call, um
invite over
Stacy and what was the famous guy's name?
Use the hammer tool
He's not going to die
You need to eat i'm going for it right now
You don't like that, that's fine
Uh, let's have i'm gonna have a canned soup
20 all right, i'm gonna sell this stuff. I have to 45 bucks. That's that's expensive
90 bucks get rid of this
50 bucks
You pick up an object in use
Keep the termites
Why I just have to collect the rocks. Okay. Well, let's move this
art
coming
Let's have some dinner
Um, will you greet greet greet greet greet?
Stop picking up the rocks and greeter, please
There we go, okay, we need um
Yes
Very good
Nice to see you again. Let's have some dinner
Oh sell all this crap, too
Actually, you know what I need to buy
Another counter 375 bucks. It's so expensive. No, just give me one of the shitty ones
Give me two of these come look at like the bugs
I need an appliance
Like a food processor. Yeah
Here we go. Now I can actually cook food. What is this thing sell that too?
You need to sink
That's a good point. You're right sink
Now this is a home ran mom made that for you
It was nice to see you again. If you want to come over you can
Still a piano, right? Yeah
You have a tiled bedroom
What will I do the choices? They're true. It's me peter griffin
I still can't get over that
It's haunting me. It's been haunting me for like the last three and a half hours
Uh now I can wash the dishes here
I don't want to do this chef thing anymore
Okay, wash the dishes
What's wrong with you? All right get up
Why do you guys want me to keep the termites? What is that what to do?
That's not carpet. Isn't it linoleum? I'm not going to answer it. Whatever. It's too late
Uh an eccentric conductor ran through wilkie's fabulous books
Organized music at wilkie's fabulous books
No
No, I don't care
Let's clean
Wow one more clean it. There we go. All right now i'm ready. Let's just make my last little meal here
Need some paint double pancakes
All right. Now actually go to work and i'm gonna get some money for that
Stay at work until late to improve your relationship with your co-workers. Yeah, sure
Maybe i'll make some money
All right. Now he's going to work business as usual
His plates are so clean you can practically eat off them the chef is quite happy happy enough that your job performance has improved
All right. Why am I still a chef?
What if I need to level up here
career
I might actually get promoted now
That's a good performance
And when you get back eat some pancakes
All right bernard is left
Strained. All right, what do you need fun? Yeah, wash a little bit. I need something else. That's fun
Are you supposed to do a bunch of dishes or something? Yeah, I did
I had to bring them in
I want to do this too
Have you had a nice time?
There we go. All right, you got promoted
Yeah, i'm I feel i'm doing good i'm very happy i'm very excited
Very excited for august 18th august 20th and the 21st
Right here on germa 985
The germamites will finally be able to control germa
All right, take a shower
All right. Stop watching tv get up
I thought we were the drew crew. That's right. You were
We bet on something dumb
You'll have an opportunity
You could sell the car
Isn't like the tv being on it's why am I waking up at two o'clock in the morning eat and then go back to bed
seize control
Did I sell the car? No, I need that
Back to bed. How are you doing? Brad is uh, I feel like I already did that
It's time for ads. I don't think so. Not quite still good eat
Watch a little bit of tv
Oh fuck. I need to repair it
That's gonna get you on the roof in like 30
These guys haven't spoken to each other in a week. I'm not sure they've ever spoken to each other
Maybe when I first came
To the house before it was built. All right, take a shower real quick. Come on. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. You want good
Performance good performance good performance. Good. All right now you i'm gonna get out of this chef career and go do music
Sports medical law enforcement sports medical law enforcement. Damn it. I'm not going to work skip it
How are you doing you need
Have some lunch
Whoopee kabo rana
grilled cheese
Don't go to work stay
What what?
What was it a goopy?
Carbonara carbonara
He's almost gonna level up again. Nice
Keep working out. You're almost done
Level five
Gooey, who cares about like dracula i'm about to level up my point anyways, so i'll get points
There we go also visit the bookstore sometime to purchase a new song
Learn a new piano composition. Yeah, let's do it
Go to the bookstore
You need to pee
pee
Go to sleep and then when you get up in the morning, you're going to go to the bookstore and you're going to learn some new songs
Somebody said the stream day is going to be a subathon style stream. I don't really know what that means
a subathon style stream
What's that mean?
Every sub means more stream time
Oh, no
No
There's very specific rules that you will see and the reason why I do
Three streams. There's a lot of reason why so you guys be in the past
when we've done
A big project or something with the carnival or geology
It's a one and done thing
where
You only really have
Two three four hours to even understand what's going on
So this time because it's going to be three days
There's going to be plenty of time
To understand how the game works
to
kind of tutorialize yourself
uh to learn how to play it and everything so
We'll have a solid bold day or two
for
This tons of time. So don't worry
It is not going to be a three day straight
So there will be time in between the streams the streams will turn off
it's not a
life sim
It's not a life simulator
Where the cameras are rolling 24 7 and you guys have to control my whole life
I mean, it's gonna be a life simulator, but
Not 24 7 ever consider recycling some stream ideas. Yeah all the time
Yeah, it's it's less of a truman show and more of an interactive experience where you guys
Play around with a ton of stuff
And me too. I'm gonna have tons of things to play around with so don't you worry
special guests
Lots of stuff to do
It'll be fun
How do you even rehearse that kind of thing?
well
Um, it's very new territory. So it is not much rehearsing that can be done
We're just gonna go for it. There's gonna be a shitload of time before the stream
Where we're gonna make sure everything works and is ready
It's not just gonna be a oh, well, it's it's august 18th
I guess we're gonna see if this thing even turns on I mean that stuff that's not being worked on right now
That stuff has been being worked on since
God i'm gonna say june may I want to say is when that started really getting hammered on
He's gonna be doing lots of acting
I bet you
Are you food? Whoa, whoa, whoa?
Fix that clean that up
Am I feeding the fish?
Jesus. All right. I was in a bookstore. I'm gonna go to the bookstore
first, let me pee
Have a quick lunch
Of bread and jam and we're gonna go
Is it gonna be in sim in like a a simlish no like a different language no
Yeah talks
We thought about having it be sort of pantomimed
but
It probably would have got old very very quickly
So no, it's not gonna be in a different language or anything
What are you guys doing?
These streams are gonna be boring. I
I highly doubt that you all right here. Here's what i'll tell you about them without revealing what we're gonna do
um
The one thing that I can guarantee whether you love or hate these streams that are going to happen in a couple weeks
They're definitely not going to be boring
You might hate these but you can at least you'll probably you'll come away from it probably at least saying
I was kind of fucking insane what they did because it's not just as simple as
I don't even want to tell you I don't even want to just it's not it's not what you might some of you might think it is
Like let's put it this way. I know a lot of you probably think it's going to be
this
stream where
Oh, he's just sitting on the couch and we told him to watch tv and we told him to go pee
This will be fun for three days
It's not what's gonna happen. I'm not going to tell you anything, but it's going to be
a wild ride for three straight days
Have I deleted channel points yet? Why?
Why am I saying this?
And sure, I mean this I want to experiment to see what you guys do
You guys are gonna have a lot more control than I think you realize
All right, where are we going? I need all right right I entered uh the bookstore go to the can I
I have the thing in my inventory, right?
Yeah, okay
All right bookstore
I'm gonna go buy a new song and i'm gonna play at the bookstore. Where's the bookstore art gallery?
Is that it?
What's a bookstore?
Public library
Where is this place?
deep fried diner
Butterfly
Isn't this place?
The bright more isn't that a bookstore?
The red book under the candle
isn't this
science
public school
Where the hell is this place?
hospital
Cemetery
Where is this bookstore? Can I just call and go there?
Why can't I see it?
Go to the oh jesus god. It's right here
All right, I need to buy some specific things
It's doing all right
So I need to buy a new song
Recipes, all right sheet music
piano level five summer hayrides, that sounds good
piano level six
Uh, sure. These are expensive. Can I afford these?
Don't forget the musty smell of the old books
I love books. Okay earn 25 from tips. He looks like he's just doing it
He's just doing it
Who's this addy crew?
You're playing for the pigeons
Now i'm playing for this guy
um
You liked that?
Oh, it was nice to meet you
You want to make a band?
The name of the band
Let's die
Get on any instrument to build your sims musical skills
Once you practice enough on it, you can have a band
Start a band by talking to somebody
After forming a band your sim will be ready to play some gigs
Be sure to answer your sim's phone or you'll miss out on those gig offers. Okay, cool. All right, so we gotta watch out for this phone
We're in a band together
That's so cool
Nice law firm piano and piano are so sweet
Ads it's time for ads
Is it an ad type? I don't think it is
Is it ad andy it might be
What the fuck was that you want to join our band? Oh matilda's going home. What about you? You want to join a band?
Nice to meet you. Uh, okay friendly you want to join the band?
Before budgie
Ads, all right. Yeah. Yeah, but yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I got it
I got I got it on the top of the hour every hour
At least for today the next stream that I do
Is not going to have ads ran on it. I want to make that clear as well
Let's see, how many what can we do? All right, we're gonna do another three minutes three minute break here
Thank you for your patience to everybody. So i'll be back in three
Then I think we're only gonna need to do this like one more time at the end of the stream
Why is this happening somebody asked? Uh, they probably just came in. So the reason why this is happening
is twitch has
Ponied up a significant amount of money
To make sure that the dollhouse stream happens
I would dare say that if we did not have the financial backing from twitch
We would probably not be able to do this
It would be very very hard for me to do it on my own
So as part of that agreement
Some of these streams here that you're gonna watch are gonna have ad breaks
That's it. Here we go three minutes. I'll see you in three minutes. Oh, yeah, some of you still here capitalist andy
Well, wouldn't capitalist andy imply that like i'm gonna make a bunch of money from this endeavor
Now it's all going to the production all of it every single cent
And then some
And then some it's an investment. I mean you could look at it like that. Maybe sure
We have to pay for the germa dlc somehow
Stop pretending
No, this is the real deal
If I was if I was gonna run ads, I would want you to be completely transparent on this
ads ads ads ads
He's pretending to care
No, I
It's I I don't have to say anything. I don't say anything. I'm a doctor too
Your subs get ads. I actually don't know
They changed that recently subs get ads. I thought they did maybe they don't ignore the rude comments
I don't I actually don't see very many
So this is you know, it's it's a scary thing to do something never done before
um, I was thinking about this for a long time of
I'm going to be running ads. We're bringing on a few partners essentially for this project
I just hope you understand that everything that is done is done to try to make the best possible stream I can possibly do
So I don't I think people would know i'm not seeing anybody saying anything people you guys have been very very supportive
Which is crazy. Is there a date? Yes august 18th at 3 pm eastern august 20th
At 3 pm eastern and august 21st at 12 pm eastern. Those are the three dates and the three times that the stream will be live
Why is the third stream at a different time? That's a good question
The reason why the third stream is at a different time is so we potentially have more time
For the for the day
We want to make sure we have a lot of time
So starting earlier means we can go longer
Especially on that third day, which would be the last day of the event. I guess you could call it
I'm a bad listener. What day is august 18th august 20th and the 21st of august of 2021
Which means in about two weeks two weeks from now if we read about the dates
You're probably going to see a very very heavy amount of promotion here
over the next week or two
from more than one source, so
You will know as long as you pay a little bit of attention. Are you going to last three days?
I hope so never done it that anything like that before but that was another part of the point to put the day in between
so do
The 18th and then all right. How am I doing?
Give me a day
Give everybody a day then we come back again. You're not streaming on my birthday. Uh, i'm sorry
Anybody collaborating with you on this?
Yes, there'll be some special guests and we will uh, we will tell you who those people are very very soon
I think I think some of you guys are going to be I think a lot of you guys are going to be really excited
It there are multiple special guests by the way, and i'm very much looking forward to it. I can't wait
Uh, let's continue with the rest of this
I'll probably be live for another hour
or so
Uh, there's still a lot of work to be done on this project. I just was able to announce it today
Is it going to be a star studded event?
um
Yeah, I would say so
All right. What was I here? Okay. Here we go
I need to play
I need to make money from get the piano out here. Take it out
Learn these new songs
Learn the songs learn these songs learn
Oh, I have to actually play it
Learn all right. There we go plus 350 learn this one, too
Oh shit, they love it. They love it. Hey
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, excuse me
Excuse me only this is where I go
I'm getting out here
They're not even listening to me. Well now they will be
No, come listen to my music
Hey, why don't we uh combine forces here?
You know this one
This is the part of the movie where the main character has sunglasses on and nails the piano and he goes
Who's calling me? Oh gig. It's gonna be a gig. It's gonna be a gig
It's the phone
It's the phone. It's gonna be a gig
There's a rock concert at the theater tonight featuring the screaming llamas
It might be in the best of interest with piano and piano to attend so they can learn from the best in the biz
Yes, where is it?
Okay, there it is rock star study at the movie cineplex
That sounds good to me
All right
This is movie cineplex to complete the opportunity. All right, let's go
How am I doing? Oh shit. I'm tired
I'm tired and hungry
nap take a nap
I get up i'm back between 5 pm and 11 pm
Well, that's like tomorrow 5 pm and 11 pm
All right, so it is currently 1 am so I can get some sleep. I can go home go home
Jeremy strike me as a radio head fan
Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
That answer your question
It's the only song he knows. Yes, it is
but wait, no, hold on what about the uh the
I'm a creep
I know that one too
I used to jump around on
All right. Okay. I remember being in the backyard when I was younger and just jumping around with a big stereo
Listening to that song by radiohead. What's the name of that song?
What is it called? I put it was on repeat. I had that album
When I was younger, no, not creep. No, no, no the other one called like paranoid. What is it called?
Paranoid android that's the one I played paranoid android on repeat just jumping around in the backyard
That's that song was like
It reminded me of bohemian rhapsody. It's like four songs in one. I love that. I remember loving that song
The song slaps. Yeah, it does
All right, what time is it? All right 5 30. We gotta rest up. We got ready to play the gig
It slaps means it's really cool
I know what that means. I'm 35 not 80
Computer show me celery man to do do do do do do do do do
That's a classic. Of course it is
I eat I got uh, like a few hours clean up for us. This is disgusting
I'm gonna have breakfast. I'm gonna have what can I only how to make pancakes?
No, you broke the toilet then left whatever
Have to eat again. No. All right. No, it's five five between five and eleven, right?
Prepare pancakes. I already did I just did it
What?
Waffled a waffle for 40 days in a row. I think the game crashed
Fuck the game. No, it didn't i'm good
Eating waffles for 40 days in a row. That sucks
All right, I am ready. Yeah, save it good idea. I can't all right. It's time
To get over there at 5 p.m. It's time for the gig
That's a little bit of tv
My favorite band is the gorillas
Although I have not kept up very much with any of the newer stuff they've done over the last
I want to say like a year
a bit more than a year
Though honestly the last time I really kept up with the gorillas was
When humans came out that's pretty much it and why does my mic look like it's fucking low?
Hold on a second going on here. It looks low
Is this low to anybody else?
Am I better? Does that sound better?
That looked really low. Are we good now?
Why did that turn off? All right. Now that definitely looks like you can hear me better. You're missing the gig. Oh
Shit, all right. Go go go go go go go go go go
Where's the gig? Where's the gig?
Where it is? Attend the rock concert
Oh, you sound like homer simpson today
Yeah, well, uh, thanks. I appreciate that
Yeah
No
No, no, no, no
No, there it is
Fuck off. I got it
You're making enemies
Attend the rock concert
What's going on?
Don't have to play the song
Wait, i'm in the rock concert. Why would I attend the rock concert?
What the fuck is going on?
Why oh you're i'm learning from the people inside. I get it. Okay, makes sense. Okay, that was fun
Who wants to talk to me?
Who is this lady?
Wait, this is a celebrity
But you're but this is a you're a one star celebrity I can play the piano
Um, I don't know the guitar. Oh shit, you really like that
I'm a one star celebrity irl. I don't I don't agree
One star celebrity would be if I were to upload a picture like a video of auto
barking weirdly
and it gets like
A million views on twitter
And like I have no intention of ever making another auto video ever again
Like auto would be a one star celebrity, right?
and
Asked to join piano and piano
But we're gonna have to be piano and piano and piano
All right. We have a new band member. Thanks for joining the band
You're a niche internet micro celebrity streamer
I
joined music career
Did this
I never said that I was a celebrity. Okay, we got a new acquaintance. You want to join a band?
Household you fighting household name andy. I am not a household name
Yes, I am what no I why do you say i'm a household name
P and p and p and p piano and piano and piano and a snare
Piano and piano and piano and a snare
the drummer
What's your name? Hello poly
Name drop I play the piano
Oh, you're tired. All right band. Oh, wait band is maximum amount of members
Let's have a jam sesh
We're all just out here. We're all doing the same thing
Wait, is this like a compromising scenario for this guy?
Like is his career now in trouble
That's like fran dresher
All right guys, we got a sesh
22 a.m
Out in front of the rock concert. Oh shit. Oh
I left my piano. I need that
What about my piano?
Oh fuck did they all show up?
Did they I want to eat my piano back?
Echo who's this? What are you been up to? Can I help you? This is a drunk fan
G toga pain
We'll leave
Get away from my house get out get away from my house
I got back what happened to the firefighter girlfriend the firefighter girlfriend still around just haven't called her in a while
call the police
Did I?
fire
That didn't say that
Harder i'm sorry. All right, she needs to leave get out of here
Okay
Okay. Now, okay now you're gonna leave right after I call them
Great. The hell are you doing? Well, somebody was just here but
Somebody was here before okay, you think i'm okay minus five hundred dollars five hundred
Don't play with the phone like that
There was a fucking person out here
Banochi
All right, bye bye, what is where's bugleberry obviously then okay still a chef I want to play a gig
Yeah, i'm inviting the band over and we're gonna do a session
I want to see what that looks like. I've never seen that
Almost there. Can you evict rad? I'm sure I can but I don't think I really want to
All right, pick up the phone. Let's get the band over
Let's go for it jam session
We got grilled cheeses here
band practice
I could go for a grilled cheese right now
All right, come on in that's what we're doing
Why these people I keep just leaving them hanging clean up
Can they still practice
All right, leave work leave work early
Go get your piano bring it back to the house. Oh, this is fucking so far away. Go get this
perform
Wait band invite band members. Oh shit. It's here. It's here. This is the paparazzi
That's who that person is
What am I looking at?
Leave work. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no don't come here
Does rad help us go on a date fine rad go on a date. That's fine
Your phone the paparazzi is waiting for us. We have to go perform. Come on. Let's go. Where's that place?
All right
Go here all the band
Hurry up. Why are you taking a fucking taxi? You have a car
All right, let's do it. Why are there bugs everywhere? All right, here we go
The band's here start a jam session perform
Summer hey rides. Let's go
Where's the band?
Where's the rest of the band?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Get up get up. I need to
and
Where's my band?
Invite band members
They're on the way. All right. Come on. Hurry up. There's a there's a concert going on here
What happens if this is pretty good dropped who just punched that person?
I'm just fucking playing whatever. Fuck them
Form I think i'm in love with the ghost
What who am I jamming with?
That guy just called his band this is bullshit
You just throw up near my stand. What are these people doing?
If it's this guy. Yeah, somebody said is this guy reading a book as an instrument? Um, what is this?
Is there a floating guy?
He's possessing this shit
Can I hang out with him?
Get him to join the band
I gotta get rid of somebody I gotta get rid of somebody band band band band band band band band I need to
Get everybody down here now
I'm getting rid of everybody
Please I need a band member
Somebody show up
What what?
We missed you at the party fennard. Hopefully you can make it next time. This is the guy that was reading the book
He was standing right next to me. I was there
Who's in love?
What where am I going? I'm going home. I'm curious. What happened here. You want a date?
Oh with margarita, right? Okay
Where is she? How come she's not here? He lost the ghost. I think I can probably call him
I made I got friendly with him. I should really call him
Uh, what rad elberson got trapped in the elevator doors
Is he okay? He will always remember the feeling the door slam on his body as he was trying to get out
Where the fuck am I greasy?
Whose house am I in this is freaking me out?
This is a gym. I'm so confused. Just go home
All right. Can I call the ghost to invite over? I wonder if I can call the ghost ghost
Did you hear that? That was like ghost. I'm gonna should I call the fire department and in
I okay call the fire department
Um stacey comes over they send stacey. I go on one knee and I propose
Let's say the fire is in my heart and it's been there for the last six days since you and I met
What if it's not stacey?
One star celebrity bullshit clean yourself. I want to invite
Very tender love. What was the ghost's name the ghost have a name?
Remember, that's a felony
Yeah, and then I get fucking thrown. I I get arrested and thrown in jail
Stacey just come over. Let's hang out. All right, let's make some dinner
Stacey's coming over. What's uh, what's wrong with me?
Oh shit, I have to eat i'm gonna die if I don't eat. Oh autumn salad. It's new
What's wrong with her?
Why do we both have the I just got a knocked out thing
Just seeing stars why?
Are you fucking idiot?
Don't go to work
This guy runs out on everyone every time
No, don't leave
Don't leave
I'm not ready for you to leave
Look, we're gonna I think i'm in love with a ghost. Is this my weird way to break up with her come over here
No
No romantic. Here we go. Hold hands. It's time
It's a goose bumps title
Romantic, let's get a kiss
I've never seen anyone be this bad at the sims
Yeah, we all know the tilde tilde like
Thousand dollars thousand dollars hilda thousand dollars rosebud rosebud rosebud, right?
I know what you do to start. I didn't do that
Okay
It's time to let's see if we're ready to become husband and wife, where is it?
Where is it
Try for a baby. Okay, here it is
Do you want to make out in front of my bugs that was funny
We did it now what happens to our roommate you get trapped in an elevator again
Okay, have a private wedding
I have 600 dollars. It has to be a private wedding
Imagine walking in and your roommate
Who you know has a girlfriend that keeps coming over
Looks at you and says we're getting married
Like oh that's
Nice. Congratulations
Oh, she lives. She's living here. She lives here. Oh
Who is going to be invited?
Wait, hold on
Move what i'm moving
She just lives here
Right when he walks in
uh
Don't invite rad. He's staying look at that in the corner
Oh, no
Congratulations now you go to sleep in like the little kid bed
Permanently. Oh by the way, we're gonna be at me me and my baby gonna be on there watching tv all night
God fucking dammit
Hey me me and babe are like super hungry, but like we don't like feel like going out or anything
What do you think you want to get something?
You want to go drive somewhere get something for us?
Yeah, what do you guys want uh, we were thinking what do you think what do you want?
um
I was thinking about I kind of go for like italian. We're really feeling like american like burgers. What do you think honey?
What do you want? Yeah, like burgers sounds good to me
Yeah, it's like we're eating fucking burgers
great
my girlfriend's
My girlfriend's my music. My girlfriend's husband just got me dinner. What are you talking about?
Can't wait to see that rad as the child
girlfriend's husband
Oh
We need to get rad a uh somebody
Okay, let's go time for mac and cheese. Oh you what you're gonna make mac and cheese. Oh, man
I love mac and cheese. Oh make extra so we can have some you want to watch a movie
Oh, it's only two spaces on the couch
motherfuckers, I swear to god
Hook rad up with the vampire chick
All right, let's go have some dinner. The state wait stacey has a job, right?
What do you mean unemployed?
What unemployed how I thought you were firefighter. You're not a firefighter anymore. Why are you not a firefighter?
Why does she know the piano? She's just level two piano. She gave it all up. Oh shit
Is that pick that phone up the phone? Oh shit work out using the push self option for three hours
Really? That's so long to be working up three hours. I haven't been paying that much attention to rad but um, oh my god
Almost level eight athletic. I haven't even been paying attention play ads. Is it time for ads? All right while they sleep
It's time for ads
We're gonna be doing we're gonna do this now and then we're gonna do one more time at the end of the stream
So if you don't you can you know, uh, this would be the last time before this stream is over though. Let me uh run them
I'll be let's see you guys in two seconds. Those of you that are still here. I'll we'll be here save this though
Make sure it doesn't cause a problem. It's the first time i've seen chat cheer for ads
Uh, they used to do that but back in the day they did we used to run ads for fun. This is a joke
All right. I'll see you guys in in uh three minutes and then we'll do this one more time
At the end of the stream. See you in a minute three minutes to be exact end of the stream ads
Yeah, i'm gonna see how many i'm i've never done this before. I wonder how many I can actually run
Do five minutes. I don't think I can do more than a few minutes every hour or so
Whatever whatever, I don't know the exact timing you can do three minutes every five minutes
Well, that's the quickest way to destroy your entire career and make it so not any human being will ever watch your channel
ever for any reason
60 ads
Three minutes every five minutes. That's insane. I I would say
a couple minutes of advertising
is
Doesn't necessarily bother me as long as it's not
Like as long as i'm in control of it, right?
Like if I can tell you hey guys here comes an ad and it's like once like an hour or something
Like 30 40 50 minutes or so one thing that I hate more than anything
It's just ads that just just jump out at you a live platform like this. It's so awful
Just oh here we go. It's uh, we're in the middle of doing something
You're gone and this is my screen got 50% louder and I have no idea what I mean
I have no idea what i'm looking at anymore. So if I run ads
It'll be in scenarios like this
Where you know, they're coming, you know, they're coming for at least a full minute or so
And i'm still i'm not going to keep going
So there'll be ads on the streams that we do
And there's going to be a few people whose sole job it is to make sure that they're in a place
That's not going to cause any problems like content wise because that's a huge deal for me
I don't want people to miss anything. So we're going to find the right times to do those
there's no way that i'm going to want somebody to be in like two minutes of ads and something
Crazy is happening on the screen. No, and you should be back. Hello. Welcome back
Uh, that is the final time we're going to do that
I'm going to do it one more time at the very end of the stream before turning it off
Which i'll probably go for like another maybe like 20 30 minutes or so. I do want to see I want to conclude this arc here
Why did you start running ads in the first place? Well
I'd like to tell you
Uh, there's going to be three streams the dollhouse stream
Well, you will be able to control me as a viewer
We're doing the dollhouse thing that I talked about a couple years ago
Twitch has put forward a significant amount of money to partner with us to make this stream possible
And ads need to be ran on these streams
As part of our agreement here. I know people are going to go. Hey, he keeps saying he keeps saying
I got to make it really clear especially new people coming and going trickling in and out
There's a lot of info to have it's a huge amount of new information
And you will get more as the weeks go by the next week or two
You're going to get a ton more info. I'm very excited. Let's uh, let's let's finish this up though. So, uh
What I want to play a gig include the bugle arc today
The next time if I stream the if we do the sims again, let's say we do this next week
I think we're going to just do insane mods
It might be a mod shit show stream
Uh next week for sims 3
And then in a couple of days is the finale of the battleship tournament with lidwig
Same deal going to be over on his channel. We'll finish that up too this week
And why is this not going fast? Hurry up. Give rad his cemetery goth girlfriend already. I just like burped really loud
I hope the mic didn't pick it up
Grab a bowl of soup. Oh, oh, that's just mac and cheese. I kind of want mac and cheese right now
Why is there moss growing here? All right, everybody get up the whole household everybody
Mac and cheese sounds so good
I just like I want something. I'm hungry. What do I want if you were me? What would you eat right now?
He's still playing vanilla sims not as of next time
Yeah, let's talk. Okay. I got
Everything's just exploding. Can we fix this please?
Yeah, I will be hosting lidwig stream
Like we did last time
Anything else need to be fixed clean this up
Invite to cuddle. All right, should we should we try to make a baby out on bed cuddle on bed?
I thought that was the baby. I was like, why is the baby in this? What is going on? Who is this?
Jason bard
Who is this guy? What is he doing?
He's taking the sink
Who's this alien?
He took the wallpaper. What did he take?
He took the wallpaper
It's the repo man. No, not my bugs not my bugs anything about my bugs. No, you can't have my bugs
Oh my god, he took the bugs. No, he didn't what did he take?
Are you pregnant?
What's wrong? It was time for a change. You didn't moved houses
Looks like your household bills have gone unpaid
Oh, stacy just grasped the basics. You got the wrench out
They woohooed
who would stacy elbertson
just woohooed with a celebrity fernard elbertson a famous frolic who is
Certainly a memory that won't be forgotten
Fernard elbertson just enjoyed a woohoo with stacy elbertson in bed a romantic rendezvous with a special celebrity
I want that. I want to make a baby
Try again
Yeah
This is so annoying
This is annoying
It's pregnant not pregnant
He's already pregnant you're pregnant the first time what
No, she's not
Jingle already played she's pregnant. It's darkened. Oh, they took the lamp
It's dark in here. Hey, what do I want to put up on here?
Just take I don't care. Whatever. It doesn't matter
Be ugly as hell doesn't matter. That was 200 bucks, but who cares?
All right, we're friends look
Rad elbertson just became friends with a celebrity
What an egomaniac thing
Weird around town is that fernard had something repossessed
Yeah, a sconce on the wall who cares they don't like each other. What are they not like each other? That's weird
But um, let's dispel those rumors right now
Why did she lives in the house?
I can't believe those rumors could get so vicious bernard. You are all right in my book
throw party
Throw party let's invite. Um everybody dress code formal attire
Everyone's invited i'm gonna play the piano for everybody
Maximum guests, okay
Party will start at 9 pm
We have so much in common. I'd love to get to know you better
Are you talking to her?
All right, we need to make food a lot of it
Serve mac and cheese. We need to have like a bunch of mac and cheese out
Make sure everyone's having a good time. All right, make mac and cheese and then i'm gonna skip my piano
Let's go
Form I think of a love of the ghost
This is bring food that looks way better than what we have. We have mac and cheese and that's it
This guy has like spaghetti and meatballs
Eat that up
No, no put that shit away. Put it away
Don't let anybody get sad that put that in the fridge
Like I bring what do you got nachos put it in the fridge. This is the best way to just get free food
Burnt mac and cheese is what we're serving put that away
They're booing me
He's choking
What is this guy everybody's thinking of this guy, where is he?
Is it this guy why is everybody freaking out about that guy?
I don't understand. Yeah, that's my gig
Put that store that give me the nachos put them away
Put the nachos away
It sounds like a mobile game ad
It does sound like a mobile game ad
And what what is going on with the mobile game shit? Somebody please explain this to me. What's wrong with this world?
Every mobile game ad has the weird
Pull the gold bar for the fire in the water to go down different ways
Why do all of them do that?
All of them. It's like think you can do better
That's not even in the game. That's that's not what the games are. Why do they do that? It's crazy to me
I don't get it. It's marketing to children. But how that's not even in the fucking game
It's also level one grunt. It's social manipulation
But like but why the gold?
Sliders, right? Why?
Can you save the day? Ah
Slide slide. Ah
The fire went down and killed them. I don't I don't get it
I'm so i'm trying so desperately to figure out what that means
It's an easy puzzle that meant to anger you at how dumb people are so you'll get it
But like I kind of want to play that game
You know what I mean? I'm like irritated. I would like to play that game
It worked. I want to play that game. I want to play that one
I don't want to play the other stupid thing that they have
Mobile game
Have you ever seen that video where it's like a gorilla? It's one of those ads
And the person's they pull one of the things and the gorilla comes and punches this lady in the face
And it goes like no no no no your iq is like 40. It's it's so funny
Hold on
It's so funny. I need to I need to show it. Let me see. I have it like saved somewhere
Let me see if I can show it
He dreamt it. No, no, this is a real thing
I did not dream this
Fuck, where is it time for an ad break? No, no, no
I'm not doing that until the end
One with the I think all right. Wait, wait, wait. I got it
Okay, I can show it
Yeah, all right. This is it. I got it. I knew I had it saved
This ad is crazy
I'm hopefully it's not really loud
Let me make sure it's not like insanely loud
It would be a I have it's like just a video
All right. Here we go
Uh here here comes like the most ridiculous mobile ad
Hope it's not too loud
It was fucking loud. Ow
Fuck I tried to grab it as fast as I could
Oh my god, why?
ow
Stupid fucking thing
I am so sorry guys. I knew it was I tried to give warning to myself and to you
I just I couldn't change it. There's nothing I could do about it
I hope that was not horrible. It probably was fucking horrible. I'm so sorry one more
Oh, I wish there was a compilation of mobile game ads. I would watch it. They actually might be i'm gonna look into that
All right. Let's finish this arc up and then I will see you guys on I believe
Thursday
Let me just see what the plan is
Yes
So I believe the plan is going to be thursday around two pacific p.m
Has been we're going to do the conclusion of the battleship things
What happened? She all right? Is she pregnant?
When's the dollhouse stream august 18th 20th and 21st. It's three streams. It is a major event
It's going to be a long time. It's going to be a lot of fun. She is pregnant
Oh, how do I skip time to the 18th of august? Keep yourself busy have each day
Have something else that you need to try to do. It's almost rad's birthday in a few days
Why not buy him a birthday cake? Oh, she yeah, she is we gotta see the baby
Yeah, keep yourself. Um, keep yourself occupied
Make sure you're keeping your brain going because man you you can you can stagnate. I did stay active and that does not mean
necessarily
Physical what is she doing dancing? How long does it take for the sims three for a baby to show up?
I thought that was a repo guy again
You want some tips on pregnancy? Sure
Pregnant sims will get a few days of paid rest from work
Before and after the baby's born keep an eye on your sims new wishes now that she's pregnant
It's a few days. Okay, it's comfort and here comes the baby. All right, that's that's fine
Few days. All right
You let a rat the fridge stinks clean that clean clean clean clean clean clean clean
Why is he ripped?
Because he's an athletic person athletic career
300 jumping jacks a day
I want to see the uh, the baby before we go. It's very important to me. Oh, nope. Oh finish reading
No, it's est it is east. Yes, we're gonna be going by eastern time figure it easier that way
So it would be
12 pacific for the first two streams and then 9 a.m pacific on the last one
All right, bring that baby in I just want to see the baby baby baby, baby, baby. Let's see the baby
Let's see the baby. I want the baby
I'm visiting boston as soon and I wonder what your favorite restaurant is pappagino's god damn it now. I want pizza
But I want good pizza. I want pappagino's pizza
I want pappagino's pizza and I can't get it. God damn it. That sucks or dash it
That would be quite the delivery fee that would probably cost like four thousand dollars
Considering they need to drive it across the entire country. I had pizza today. Are you jealous? Yeah, actually kind of am dude relax
Aching back. Oh, I need to I need help. Stacy is faithful to fernard. Stacy has a faithful reputation
Okay. All right. Let me help you with that here. I can give you a uh,
Back massage has to go skinny dipping. Where where is it?
Heal
tummy
Listen to tummy
How come I can't um massage
Where's the baby i'm just speed running to the baby. I'm actually going who's that? Oh, okay. It's her. I thought she was in here
Somebody's carpool who's not in there. Oh, we just stay here the whole day
big lemon
No, does she work? She doesn't have what I mean big. Why is she being picked up? I'm so i'm confused
Why who's picking her up? Yeah, this is a pregnancy speed run. It's her husband's wife's boyfriend
Okay. Hey, I think I think rad got promoted. Yep
Minor leagues are calling so pack your socks
Romeo rake wants to know if stacy elbertson would like to go on a date. Oh, all right, stand him up
Get in the fucking car get out. What are you doing? I did that because uh that guy
You know, you're calling a married woman. You know that right very happily married woman
You know that i'm pregnant with my husband's
Child our child
Why are you you want to go on a date?
What are you doing? Oh, he's i'd heard him breathe weird like he was choking in there
All right, let's see that baby ugly bastard. Why i'm gonna clip germa saying that he's pregnant and post it to reddit
And that's the big announcement
Okay, all right. Is it time for the baby five a.m. Six a.m
and
Baby is
Why does she smell it? Oh, I thought it was like rad's the name of the baby
Like that would be very odd. Yay rad was born. It's the rad's birthday
Oh, she just turned the tv off on him. The baby's coming. The baby's coming. Oh shit. They're gonna have the same birthday
Take her to the hospital. They go to the hospital. Go to the hospital. You go to the hospital by herself
No, no, I want to go too. I want to go too. No, no, no me too. Me too. Me too me
I want to go I want to go but what about me?
Oh shit, i'm gonna miss my birth of my child
Oh my god, what a wild birthday party that we tell in this story for the next 50 years
I know it was my birthday. We were gonna go to we were gonna go to arby's and shit
And then all of a sudden your your water broke what why she pissed?
Who's this the guitar?
Oh shit in the jam session. Come on. Come on. I gotta get there quick
I gotta get the pants here quick. No, no, no, no, no, I gotta play for my son
My daughter, I don't even know what I think I don't even know
It's a baby boy
A happy mother in a smooth pregnancy makes for a happy baby since stacy's pregnancy went so well
Be able to choose two traits. What would you like to name him?
Brad
No, how about i'm a musician?
I'm a musician
cello elbertson
Evil and insane. All right, I gotta get the band here
It's the baby. All right, where are you going running away from the baby?
I'll invite I want to invite the band members. We have to play like a celebration. Oh shit. We're all leaving
Where's my going the jam session? Oh, whatever. Go home. How's cello elbertson doing?
Pick up the baby pick up the baby
No
No, don't put him back on the floor. Oh rad hates this
Where's the baby sleep?
Why they keep saying no toilet no toilet
Why are they saying no toilet?
We need a crib
Where do you get a crib?
Why can't I just get like a big fucking bed?
Put the baby in there. Can I put like wood on this?
Crib, I need to where's a crib. I don't see a crib
Ed room dining room
Oh kids room. Okay, right
um
bigger house
All right, put cello in the crib. There we go. Good
All right. We did it. You're gonna upload the 3am vid on your main channel. I don't probably not. Oh, it's rad's birthday. Right?
Uh, can I buy a cake or something? We're gonna get a cake
Yeah, what is up? I'm gonna buy you a car
Do you dislike the vibe of the folks from the old channel? Not at all
No, not at all. That's not even remotely
What I think
Yeah, why yeah, what do you mean?
All right, that's it. That's it. I'm done
I'll see you guys on thursday for the battleship tournament
I'll be in pre stream hanging out with you
I'll be in the chat room
Uh, i'm gonna run some more ads. I'm actually gonna i'm gonna do an experiment here. I'm curious
Let me see how
Let me see if I can do something once
All right, it's ad time
I will see you guys on thursday. Thanks for watching the sims 3 next time you see this is going to be
A shitload of mods on here and it's going to be hell
Uh, this stream was really just to kind of chill and
Announce that stream
Event week
I'm insanely excited for it
It's by far the biggest thing i've ever done
both logistically and
monetarily and
It should be a lot of fun regardless of if it goes to plan
We'll see but it's gonna be a lot of fun. I think it'll be at least worth watching
incredibly excited
So let's do some more ads and uh, we will call it here
Put that up. Let me save the game first very important
And we're gonna do three minutes if you're gonna take off and we'll see you again
I'll be back on
I will not be live on this channel, but I will be live on lidwigs like last time
And we'll see you later. See you in a couple days
Let me run the ads now
Let's try it again
Uh, let's do three minutes nearly 6 a.m. Where you are
Yeah, and thanks for watching too. I know that this was a little different of a stream kind of experimenting with
some ad content
I wonder if I can do it again
at the outro
Do we try is the dollhouse stream going to be your peak? No
No, there are things that I have planned that I want to do after the dollhouse stream that are going to be even more
ridiculous
One thing that I really want to do and I i'm not gonna give you a date for this but
Over the next year or so. I really really want to get done
Something i've been trying to do for years now and it will probably happen
Uh the germa rumble live on twitch actually live
That's what I really want to do next year
So once you start hearing me talk about that
At some point probably in 2022 is when I really want to get that off the ground
And in my 10 year on twitch tweet
I mentioned that I don't really know how much longer i'm going to be around on twitch for
I don't have a set date for it
but when you go over 10 years you start thinking about all the things that you really kind of want to do and
I would be very upset with myself
Years down the road if while I had the audience that is here right now
And while I had the means to do so that I didn't try over the next few years or so
At least the next few years to really try to get some of this stuff done that i've always really wanted to do
And really trying to just step on the gas as hard as I can. He's quitting
No, no, i'm just saying like look at the look at where this channel is now
I would be very upset with myself if I did not at least try to do something while
there's many of you here and
I'm it's insane to think about the amount of people that have come to this channel over the last year or two
Um, so I
I'm gonna keep doing stuff as long as i'm able to and as long as I want to go out on top
I don't have a plan to go out
My point i'm making is that I don't have a time period where I know how much longer i'm gonna do this for
But I know it's already been 10 years
so
While i'm at the level i'm at now both mentally
Even potentially physically trying to get healthier and stuff and while everybody's here and see I gotta step on the gas
We gotta go as hard as we can and let's see. I wonder can I do it again?
Yeah, should I can I do it again? Let me see here. I'm not gonna do it over the credits though
Don't push yourself too hard. No, i'm being very cautious of that as well because I still have a bunch of this medical bullshit
After the vr streams it's really clear again that i'm just not at 100% or even close but I can at least be
close enough with the
Therapeutic stuff and with time off and but it should be okay, but I am very very happy
I'm very excited
We're gonna try to want we're gonna try to run another three minutes of ads right at the very end here
See if I can do it. I'm curious. We're not going anywhere
I'm surprised
I'm very
Happy about that, but i'm surprised. It's been a long time
I actually got ads that time
Uh-oh, it's breaking through. We're actually we're infiltrating. We're getting through
But thanks for the subs. There was a lot there was
Somebody gave a shitload. Thank you. You can't believe I just found you
I'm not going anywhere. I'll be around
As long as i'm able to
There's still things that I need to do, right?
What's that? I'm like a ghost guys. I can't I cannot go away until I fulfill the reason why i'm here
I have the the germa rumble live on twitch
Has to happen that I can't I cannot go until I fulfill by destiny and then the next one after that and then the next one
I'm not I can't go anywhere. I'm i'm i'm the ghost that haunts your computer
All right. Let's see if I can do another three minutes. I after this three minutes is up. I will see you later
Thank you for watching again. We'll see you thursday for the battleship tournament. I'm in the semi finale
semi-final i believe versus
Stands I think we'll see i'm gonna try to run the ads again
And here we go the ad failed to run because the channel recently ran an ad
All right. Well, we can we're gonna wait one minute and 21 seconds
Really I got a big red marker just like excuse me
Yeah, we'll do it one more time
What time on thursday is the battleship thing? I think we're shooting for
2 pm pacific
On ludwig's channel and i'll i'll be i'll be around on thursday afternoon. So I'll let you guys know what's going on
Can I run it? Come on. I gotta run these ads
And there's one good thing. I guess
I think i'm turning pre-rolls off when I do this
or
At a pretty extended period of time
All right, let's see if I can run it three minutes
There it goes
All right. We got we currently have three minutes going. I didn't realize it was gonna do that
Pre-rolls are disabled. I keep like adding to my pre-roll disabled thing
Hippo happy. Well, thank you guys
two more minutes
The only stream that makes me laugh and cry
Well, come on comedy and tragedy. Those are the two masks
How to do them both
You're gonna do a mobile game stream that I actually was going to do I had like 70 mobile games on my ipad
but
It just sucked
And I tried to go through so many of them. I was gonna do a stream
And it was just they were terrible. They weren't even funny. They were loud. They were annoying half of them didn't work
Half of them were just menus and shit and it was like this is awful
I want to do that, but I definitely want to do
Because I feel like that would get kind of exhausting after a while
If we where we go 40 50 games deep on ipad
And just everyone's gonna everyone just wants to stop
It's like holy shit, man. I can't even take this anymore like an hour would go by and that would happen
Play a mobile game and jump into the game with ads. Yeah, you know actually
It was a recommendation a while ago that that was hilarious
And that was to open up my ipad
go to youtube
and just
Open up videos until I got a mobile ad
And then just download that game
And just just continue to download every ad that I get
Then I was like, that's probably a bad idea
Just go to every ad game
Ad jumping. Yeah
All right. I'll see you later. I'll see you in a couple days
Thanks for watching everybody. Hopefully this experiment went well
I will see you thursday
We have a lot more to talk about this other people involved that I need to
Tell you about
Have a great night. I will see you thursday
Bye take care
Have a great how about three more ads? Well, how about three more minutes of ads? No, I'm just kidding. I'll see you later