Hello. Good afternoon, everybody. EU stream. Well, it's a few hours early.
I have 1.30, 2.30, 3.34. Yeah, like two and a half hours early. There's a reason for it though.
I wanted to make sure I could get at least a solid three hours, four hours in today.
I got a lot of shit to do. I'm just running around in circles. And I mean that, dude,
I mean that quite literally. When the stream ends, I just, I still have a bunch of pent up energy and
I fucking just sprint in a circle for like 15 minutes and then I go to bed. You know how hard
it is to sprint in a circle? Have you guys ever tried that? Like a five, 10 foot circle?
Can you sprint in a circle? You can't. It's too hard. Like a 10 foot circle. No, no, you can't.
Did you drink your shower water again? No, I put it in my mouth and I spit it out.
Like every normal human on earth. But today, like I said, starting early because I want to make sure
I can stream for a few hours, we're going to play something that's going to take probably a few
hours. And that is, I mean, you guys are going to be really happy about this. Those of you that
weren't here over the last few days, I'm going to say this game and you're going to go, what the,
what? Ikaruga. Your speakers just went and like blew you away. Your like mouth is flapping back.
You can't fucking believe it. When I just said that word. Ikaruga is a shoot them up. It is a
bullet hell game and it's considered to be one of the best ever made. Now that's not according to me.
That's according to every single person I've ever known in my whole life. Now this is a pug. Yeah.
Play the real one. Touhou. All right. I'm going to have to be honest with you here.
All right. The, the more that people tell me to do something, you know, the less inclined I am to
actually do that thing, right? The more that people say, play this game, the more I go,
ah, maybe I don't want to do that. Like I've seen play Touhou even I'm talking like six months ago.
Just people just write it and that's like the only thing they write. Don't play Touhou. I mean,
maybe I will. I don't know. He hates us. Don't take your shirt off on stream. I don't, I don't
think I'll be doing that one. I don't plan on that one, but anyways, let's go. I'm going to play
Ikaruga. It looks fucking awesome. It looks so good. I looked at it and I was like, wow,
this one's going to be a good one. Let's take a look. What do you think?
Already the menu is clean. Is this, is this, is this loud? You tell me this is loud. Okay.
Why do you say, oh no. Somebody said, oh no. Why? Oh no. This doesn't have blood. No,
but it's got explosions. All right. All right. As long as it got explosions and you got,
that's fine. Count me in. You're going to be digging a hole in this one? No, no, I promise.
Okay. Thank God. Last like six streams have been you digging holes, bro. No, I promised there'll be
explosions. Okay. Better be. All right. Select with the stick. Decide with the button. This is a
little loud for me. All right. Arcade mode, the default arcade mode, prototype mode has the limit
of the shots. Chapter select, select the level to play. Let's just do arcade mode, right?
We can try the other modes later. This has got to be turned down by the way. All right.
There's three difficulties. It's easy, normal, and hard. Whoa. What just happened? Why did that
just do that? What was that? I didn't even hear that. I just saw that. I saw the, I saw the audio
go up to like a thousand. What happened? Oh, you're going to get blown away. You're going to get
blown away when I say the words Ikarunga and your face is going to be flapping. I'm sorry. I didn't
mean, I don't know what happened. I didn't do anything. Okay. Please don't do that again.
The fuck are you doing? I didn't do anything. I just was like changing the audio level over
here. I didn't do anything. All right. Enemies with the same polarity return fire. That sounds
like fun. All right. Enemies. I mean, let me try a normal first. What a fucking professional streamer.
It, it did that on its own. I didn't do anything. I'm doing normal first. I will not die until I
achieve something. Even though the ideal, I didn't read that. Don't you know not to use
fucking vertical video? How do I move? The move. Oh, it's WASD. All right. WASD. I'm already dead.
All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm dead again. All right. Chapter one.
I can't even read that. It's too fast. There's like, you have to switch polarity in this game.
You can absorb bullets if you're the same polarity. You, I looked at the fucking instructions before
we played. If you absorb bullets of the same polarity, listen to me, then you can do extra
damage. For instance, see if there's white and black, black and white. That's it. I'm dead again
and I lose. All right. Cool. Well, uh, we'll get, all right, let's go. Now uploading the replay.
Don't upload the fucking replay. I don't want someone to up see that replay. What do you mean
upload the replay? No, I don't want to upload a fucking replay. All right. So that's how it works.
It's games considered one of the hardest games ever made too. Just, I forgot to mention that.
I didn't even know what the buttons were. All right. Let me explain. Let's do some explanations
here. Thank God there's no replay. Thank God. Wait.
You get three lives. Okay. You get three lives and after you die three times, it's over. But
this polarity, as you see, the game's fucking fantastic. You have to absorb bullets of the
same polarity as you see in this replay. Check that out. See black goes into black and then
as you see, wait, what's wrong? Okay. What are you doing? All right. That one's done. He's not even
actually playing. No, I'm just watching a cool replay. All right. Let me try this again. We've
got to get through. And you guys want me to play on hard. Have you lost your mind? You want me to
play on hard. This is an actual fake. That was real gameplay that I previously, that was previously
recorded gameplay. Let Otto play the game. All right. Let's try this again. So remember polarity
is important. Let's see if I can do. I didn't even know W. I thought it was move with the mouse.
You do double damage to people of this, of the opposite polarity. Oh, this is pretty sick
actually. All right. And then I can do a super move. If I press mouse four, I can shoot out homing
missiles. Can you hear me? Can you guys hear me? Just don't run into anybody. Watch out. You can
get a, if you get three people in a row, you get a chain by the way. Like that. I have two chains.
Okay. Cool. Wait. Oh dear God. All right. Kill the, kill the one on the right first. Double damage,
right? Holy shit. That was actually really cool. Fuck. Sorry. I got three lives. I'm all right.
After this, I'm going to have to see what's going on with Otto. He wants to get out.
Absorb that whole thing. Whoa. Is that going to hit me if they go from behind there?
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. I've changed. Oh my God. Change polarity again. I can absorb. Oh,
fuck. Oh my God. What do I do? It's so confusing, but it's actually really cool.
I have to hit them. I didn't kill them. Wait, this is, am I the boss? But this is on normal
difficulty. I have one health. Is he white? Yep. Oh man. Fuck. God. All right. Hold on. I think
Otto needs to go outside. I'll be right back. He's okay. He's, he's starting to get nervous
because of the boxes. If you ever move with a dog before, they start to see you pack up shit
and they, they don't like it. They're like, let's go. What are you doing? Like, why are you doing
that? Oh, this is, this is my house. Where are we going? We're trying to make it as easy as a
process as possible, but he's okay. It's true. All right. In the meantime, let's go back here.
I'm going to get into this fucking game. I'm not saving the replay. Why am I stealing from Otto?
Forget the link. He's going to play. Yeah. Forget the link. I'll click on it an hour.
Jeremy, you're going to finish Odama today. All right. Start banning people
that say the word Odama for like four days. Shit restart. I switched polarity in the wrong,
the wrong time. What's the story of this game? You're going to ban the entire chat. Yeah, I know.
All right. Four chain. I got four chain. All right. I get it. I get it.
Mods don't care. What are you, why are you doing that? Go back to four. Oh, I see.
I got to absorb. Okay. I have max energy right now. Who the fuck is calling me?
What the hell? Is that a lot of stream time? Hold on. Don't, I don't want to save fucking 10% on my,
on my fucking car insurance. Okay. Jesus. God. That's a good deal though. Should I call them back?
Do I give them a, do I ring them back? I give her the, you gotta do, you gotta do polarity switching
like this. Bang. Like that. Get it again. Absorb. Oh my God. What did I do? I'm a fucking idiot.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I got full energy. How much did I use this? It's, it's all homing missiles,
by the way. All right. This part fucked me up last time. Get rid of the right, the right one.
Good. Absorb it all. Switch to other polarity. Right there. Bingo. Fuck. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God. I'm, I'm so dead. Eat, eat, eat, eat. All right. Here's the boss. I have two health.
I think I'll be okay. That was hard. Should I switch? I don't know. He has a black shield.
Eat the whole thing. Oh, I get it. Okay. I can. Fuck. God damn it. I get it. Yeah. Okay. Now what?
She's, what's she switching to? Sir, are you sure? Sure. We have a one day deal. Why is today the day?
Just in case you want to take us up on our offer. 40% off the whole store. You know that Mr. Jeremy
Albertson. Fuck. I'm okay. Oh my God. All right. I'm going to throw, I'm going to, I'm going to
fucking throw my phone into the toilet in a second. I swear to God. Hey, they can't call you if your
phone's in the toilet. You know, that's thinking face. God damn it. This is fucking hard. I'm turning
my phone on silent. He thinks this is hard. I'll get there. Wait, we're 30 minutes into the stream
we're already on phone in toilet stage. Well, no, not because of the game, because people keep
fucking calling my phone. I didn't say I want to put my computer into the toilet because that would
be sufficient if I was angry with the game. All right. Take that, take that, switch around. All
right. Let's go. Double fucking damn it. This is a phone game though. This is not, this is,
I mean, it's, it is as big. All right. Whatever. This is a hyper pay attention video game. I'm
going to just lock in. I got max energy. I got to save this. Let's do it. You know,
you can just keep doing it. Watch that polarity shift. I gotta, I gotta become like a, like an
actual gamer here. You know what I mean? You're, it takes like a lot for your brain to understand
and process that you can, you should run into bullets. You know what I'm saying? My brain is
like, don't run into those bullets. But my, I'm like, yes, you have to. There we go. Right side.
Wow. Same thing happened last time.
It's okay. Just don't panic. Oh fuck. Okay. Here we go. I'm at the boss again. Just be careful.
Kill the things on the left and right. He's got those two orbiters.
Do that health. Get rid of it. Good. Come on. Move, move, move, move, move. Don't get hit.
Don't be a fucking dope. God, this game's like Binding of Isaac. Okay. Shut up. Do that one.
All right. Now what do we switch to? Oh, all right. Now they switched the polarity shifted.
I get it. All right. Now they're different. They're different. Oh fuck. Okay. I need to be quiet.
Stop being like a tuber in play. Oh shit. Yeah. Got him. Got him. Did I get him?
That was actually really hard. I can, it's whatever. What are we on level two? All right.
Let's do it. Oh, they fly into you and shit now. Oh man. Damn it. Game over. All right. Do I get
started level two? Yeah. Yes, I do. Yes, I do. Because he didn't think so. I want to watch him
suffer. I'm only on level two guys. Okay. Arcade mode. Chapter two. Unnormal. This ain't chapter
two. What the fuck? Why is this supposed to be chapter two? Arcade starts from the beginning.
Oh, all right. All right. Well, see if I can just do this. So what do I have to select? Just the
other one. This, I just have to do chapter mode. Oh, this is good practice. Good practice. I like,
I like practice. Oops. All right. That was good practice. All right. Chapter select. Please select
gateway. Chapter one. No. Chapter two. There we go. This is like, this one's called trial.
Enemies with the same polarity return fire. Yeah, that's fine. Here we go. Let's do it.
Return continues on. I could do that. Are people going to think I'm a cheater? Holy shit.
This is fucking crazy. Take it all. Absorb the whole thing. All right. I got to switch polarity
here. I'm on the same one. Put a black. Why is he not playing afterburner? I don't know. I'm
playing Ikaruga. This shit is so loud still. Hold on. You got to kid me right when I switched.
Fuck. That's annoying. God damn it. Fuck. That's crazy. Okay. You got to do it immediately. I got
to turn the game down. Am I going to play at a Hulk at some point? Yes. How many chapters are there
in the game? Oh my God. I try to get so fancy. Fuck. All right. Do it again. Call me restart
rainy. That's fine. I don't care. The bosses are the most interesting thing to me. Jesus, man.
Oh, fuck. It's so erratic. I should have gotten hit like five times by now. Take them out. Take
them out. Take them out. All right. What a bad place to lose the life. Use more magic. All right.
This is where it gets funky. All right. Here we go. Jesus. I have to go through them, I guess.
Oh, man. Oh, man. What do I do? Okay. Wait, is that open? Open. Open. Open, please. Open. Oh,
man. Oh, I'm going to get crushed. Holy shit. I like cheated. How did I cheat and win? Oh, man.
Oh, it's too much. It's too much for me to do. It's too much for me to do, I think.
This is too much for my brain to do. I get fucking hit by that. Oh, shit.
I'm going to die. I'm going to die here. This is where I die. This is how it ends for me. I'm
going to just, I'm going to explode. Okay. I have to beat a boss too. No, man. This is too much.
I need to put continues on. I got to put on continues, dude. Oh, shit. Fucking my God.
I can't believe I made it through that. I don't have any, I have no idea how that happened.
Okay. Weak point. What? Hit those wings? What do I have to do? Open up the fucking crevice?
I think I have to bring both of his head down. Oh, this is doing this. What does this have to do?
What does this have to do? I can't even speak. Holy shit. That's insane. That's hard as wow.
Okay. I'm going to turn on continues. Turn on continues. Yeah. When continues on,
replays cannot. Three continues. How many continues? How about like two continues?
One continue. That's all you're going to let me have here is a one continue. I'll try it with one.
Look, this is an arcade game. Back in the day, I would just have to put 25 more cents in.
By the way, Red Lemonade gave five community subs. Thank you, Red Lemonade. What's wrong?
The default setting has changed. High scores will not be saved. Wait. People want me to click
on this image very badly. Let's, okay. I'll give it to you. What is this? Why is this like,
did you, did you copy and paste a book and put it down one strip? Okay. Play. I couldn't even see
until I zoomed in. You should take his advice. How many credits do I have? All right. That shit
is fucking hard, man. All right. Let's try this again. This is fun though. Fun, but hard. Fun,
but hard. Fuck you. I was a good start too. See how I need those continues. Just saved that.
Damn it. And that's not even the beginning of the level. Gift a sub per continue.
Um, I'm sorry guys. It didn't cost $5 to continue in the arcade. You didn't slide
a $5 bill into a machine. I gotta pay attention here. All right. And go, and go.
Same shit I did last time. Remember I was, hey, remember last time I was going,
not this time. I was, why was I looking at chat? Why was I looking at the chat? What am I doing?
I wasn't even looking at the game. I was looking over you guys. Why am I doing that for? Start.
What's the start button? What's the start button? What? Left click, right click, enter.
It's not enter. Mouse three. It's okay. It's middle mouse button. All right. Let's go.
You're playing with a mouse? Should I not be? Is this like playing Dark Souls with a mouse?
Is that a bad idea? Should I not be doing this? Use a controller. What? Is this dumb?
This is dumb. Okay. I'll put my controller in. Is it dumb? Is it dumb? Wait a minute. Um,
guys, I don't think a controller can be used. Why is my Xbox controller not getting recognized?
I have my Xbox One controller plugged in. Let me try it with the controller. See if it's any
better. Use the arrow keys. How is the arrow keys different than WASD? It's the same thing. It's just
more over to the right. Let me try with the controller. All right. Here we go.
They reached the CPU slightly faster. What? That's absolute horseshit, right? That's not real.
No, right? Is that real? Okay. No, turn off vibration for the love of God. All right. How
do I do the... Okay. Let's do... Yeah. I don't know what the... What are the controls though?
Okay. A is fire. Flarity is B. Okay. Release power is right trigger. All right. That makes sense.
That is kind of true. How is that true? Isn't the keyboard just... I'm not going to pretend
to believe that. If you had a keyboard with a PS2 connector, it would be faster.
I don't believe a word you guys are saying right now. Uh, it's... Okay. It actually is a little
easier. Probably a little bit. Absorb. Absorb. Is it activated? Not yet. Not yet. This is riveting
resident sleeper. Don't worry. Hey, we'll wake you up. We'll wake you up in a few hours. Have a nice
rest. All right. Now watch out here. There we go. Fuck. There's another wave. All right. Good. Good.
Thank you. You're welcome. All right. Now we go like this. Fuck. Okay. I'm fine. Same deal. I'm
going to go up that left side. All right. Easy. Slow down. You absorb that. Then I think it's... Is
it black? Yep. Black. Is it white again? I think so. All right. We're good. Now is where I have to
be... I got a full charge here. What the fuck? Did you see that shit come out of nowhere?
Damn it. I just got to stay back. Fuck. God damn it. Shit. Oh, it's so... Your brain just doesn't
want to do it. It's just confused. It's like scratching your head and patting your ass.
Whatever that saying is. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Fuck you.
All right. Here we go. I have one health. Take it all. All right. Good. All right. Let's go.
He's angry. No, I'm not. I'm frustrated. It's different. Okay. So now this one,
you got to get the middle. You got to get right there in the center.
Ay caramba. What's coming out first? Oh, my God. Oh, I don't get it. I don't understand. I don't
get it. You already get it? Do they have to be out extended all the way before I can hurt it?
Or this is hitting it, I guess. Oh, okay. So I have to fly inside. I don't understand.
You got to get in there. I got to fly inside the tubes. Oh, so what? Okay. Is that... Will
that damage me if I'm the wrong polarity at all? All right. This time I got to be careful.
There we go. Those homing missiles are so good. All right. I got this first part down pretty well.
That should be good. All right. How long do you think he's going to play this game? The whole
stream or just another hour maybe? Well, it depends on how I can even complete it or not.
We'll find out. Fuck. I blew it. All right. Oh, shit. What the hell am I doing? Oh, interesting
to note. From every steam discussion and review of this game that I've read, most people don't
beat this level. They go, I've done it after this level two and I can't do it. Just want to make
that very clear from what I've read. It's level two, which this is level two. I don't want to
write a steam review about it. It's fun, but I can't get past level two. Stay the fuck back.
Forget about points. Just stay alive. Oh my fucking God. What have I done? Why did I kill
that thing? I should have just left it alive. Jesus. Okay. Go this way. Right? I don't know.
Fuck. I'm freaking out, man. Just make it. Stay away from me, please. All right. Let's go.
I need some shit. Absorb that. All right. Come on. I want max. All right. I got pretty much max.
11 homing missiles. You got to get in there, man. All right. I know. I got to get in there,
man. Get in there. I'll get in there. I got one shot. What am I thinking? Oh my God. Okay. Get
in there, man. Get in there. Give me that shit. Hold on. Slow it down. Okay. Eat this. That's so
fucking hard. Fuck. Oh, God damn it. Yeah. I thought Icaruga was a really fun game,
but unfortunately, I couldn't get past chapter two. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll
get it. Charge. Charge it up. Restart. Restart. Restart. Hold on. Somebody gave $50. Hold on a
second. I just got 5,000 bits right now. That's huge. I'll take a fucking explosion, a ship
explosion over that one. It's from Cab Badger. This is nice journalist gameplay. I bet you you
couldn't beat this in 10 minutes. I bet you one fake germa sent that you couldn't beat level two
in 10 minutes. How's that sound? Who's the real, who's the journalist here? Anyways, if you want
to play, if you want to play, play a shmup, please play Zero Ranger. The game is absurdly underrated.
It's an excellent entry point for newcomers. While Icaruga is one of the great shmups of its time,
it requires a whole lot of playthroughs in order to fully understand it. It's arguably harder than
most Touhou games on arcade mode. Zero Ranger is an excellent starting point and is sure to be a
crowd pleaser for chat. By the way, you can give yourself infinite lives in the options menu,
which is fine. I love this. I love this comment. I love this bit message because it's fine.
That's fine. It's okay. I can do two continues. Really appreciate it. Thank you for the $50.
Seriously, thank you for the 5,000 fucking bits. You know what? I actually really do like these
kinds of games. I can get into them pretty easily. So you probably would see a few more of these.
I mean, I'm bonding of Isaac's one of my favorite games. I know, I know. Yeah, everything's running
of Isaac to Gerba. But I mean, it's, it's dodging and shooting and we'll see. Let's see if I can
get through the hard one. If I can get through the hard one, then everything is, it's, it's just
like coasting at that point, right? All right. Hold on. Let me, let me, let's do that again.
That was fucking pathetic. This is level two. Yeah. This is the one that people get stuck on.
I'm, I'm, I'm going hard. I'm, I'm going to try to beat this today.
Guys, the time to beat, if you know what you're doing, is like an hour. There's only like five
stages in this game, but they're all just like super tricky. I almost blew that. That would have
been bad. Absorb. But I want to take, all right. Got two lives. Oak waiting room. All right. Have
you guys noticed that like, there's always apparently a waiting room for another game.
You know what I mean? It's like Ikaruga waiting room, like three days ago. Animal Crossing waiting
room. And then I played it. Oh, Viva Pinata waiting room. And then I played, it doesn't mean
like you take a number. Oh, I can't believe it. Where's Viva Pinata? He's playing Viva Pinata
now. Get this game out. This game sucks. Where's Ikaruga? Oh, Ikaruga. Ikaruga waiting room.
Oh, here's Ikaruga. This game's stupid. When are you going to play Hulk? Hulk waiting room.
Oh, I'm going to play Hulk now. This game's dumb. Uh, fucking Mario 2 waiting room.
There's not much room in the waiting room. Next level waiting room. Get out of here with that.
I'm going to beat this. It's this part right here. This is the tricky one. Just stay the
fuck back. I just forgot how to change polarity. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, fuck. I forgot what I'm
doing. Oh, fuck. Oh, that sucks. All right. Okay. Eat him up. Eat him up. Eat him up. Eat him up.
Eat him up. And eat him up. And, and, and, and go. And then eat him up. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
All right. I've got, look at how much I got plenty of time. I got plenty of health.
Come on. What the fuck are you thinking? I'm so mad. I'm actually pissed off at myself right
now. I'm fucking furious right now. I'm so furious. I am so angry. You can't even tell.
Yes, you can. Okay. Get the, I got like fucking three lives for this shit. He's seething. I got
it. I got to beat level two. I have a question. So when I dodge like that, does it, I'll ask it
later. Do I have a frame invincibility on that shit? Holy fuck. Come on. Fire it. Oh, you idiot.
Come on. Just give me a chance. It's firing at me. Oh my God. What happened? Oh, I hit the back.
It's okay. Oh my fucking God. I have a question. Oh my, I thought I was going to die if I went in
there with this. I ran out of time. I don't know. I, I didn't, I thought it was a, I thought it was
like a fucking, like a beam or something. Like if I went in there, it was going to kill me.
If I was the other polarity, I figured that because I didn't know, I thought if I walked
in there, it was like, you're going to kill me. All right. Now that, that makes this way easier.
No, not easier, but you know, this game's fucking good. I like this. So those, okay. I've actually,
a actual question. Is this considered one of the harder shoot them ups that have come out?
Is it like, just be real with me. Is that real? I want to know if I'm going up against like the
hardest. Yup. Yup. All right. Good. Good. That's how I want it. Treasure games are regarded very
difficult. Yeah. I'll get this. I'm not going to do it on hard, but you know, I'll do it with one
continue. You literally ignored 70% of chat. Well, 70, 70% of you fucking guys just making shit up.
70% of you guys probably have never heard of this game until 12 minutes ago. So, uh, sorry.
Excuse me. Oh no. He knows. Of course I know. Oh shit. You know. Oh my God. Why the fuck? All
right. No more reading chat ever again. Just wasting lives for no reason. Kill, kill, kill,
swim, kill, kill, kill, swim. There are probably people that fly all around the edges here and
kill everything. I think that's not me. I gotta be careful again. Just don't fuck it up. Don't be an
idiot. Yo. All right. This part always fucks me up. It's just, just go forward. Don't worry
about anything. Just get up there. I don't do shit. This just to go now. I'm too high strung
for this shit. I really am. I know I should be switching polarity and yeah, yeah, yeah, but
whatever. Holy fuck. All right. Same deal. Let's go. I got it this time. I got plenty in lives,
plenty of health. I'm ready. Let's fucking go. If you think I'm going to click on a website
that's dot free in the title, you're fucking crazy. All right. Same deal. Holy fuck. You like
that shit? You like that shit? Oops. There it is, right? No. God damn it. Please. I already
got so good. Shit in my pants, man. Shit in my mouth. Fuck. Don't say that. I got it. I just
won. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I beat level two. I beat level
two. I don't have to write a steam review anymore. Yeah. Somebody shit in my pants. Somebody else
like, Hey, like shit in my pants. You want me to wear your pants and then shit in them? Yeah.
Okay. And let me get this straight. All this because you're upset at a video game. Is that
what I'm understanding here? Yes. Okay. Oh, just make sure I'm clear. Hey, what was chapter three?
Oh, shit. I have to beat it in arcade mode. Wait, what? Hold on. How was this any different than
what I was just doing? Wait a minute. What didn't? Am I, is this correct? Stage three waiting room.
All right. What happened? You can't unlock chapters in chapter select. Are you fucking kidding me?
So I have to go to, okay. So I have to do our arcade mode and I have to, oh man.
Um, so I'm just gonna give myself a hundred continues. Right. So I'm going to give myself
like five continues. I get a continue. Yeah. Um, I leveled up. I get another good. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Sir. Sir. Madam. I need to tell you. Yes. That's what's happening. What we're doing. Uh,
we're going to, we're going to, uh, settings game and I'm playing one can free play. I can just do
it in. I do not free play, right? That's, that's like, that's a joke. Um, five continues. Let's do
free play. Who cares? No, but then I can just do it forever. That's super cheating. All right. Five
lives. Three continues. That's normal. That's normal. That's normal. That's what I'm doing.
You need 25 lives to beat this. Just do infinite. We won't judge you. Yeah. Right. There's no way I
don't get judged. I've already been judged. I will see that one person is going to keep me up at
night. Uh, red lemonade, another five community subs from red lemonade. Thank you. Red lemonade
and a 5,000 bits. Hold on. 50 bucks from Goyky. Just gave 5,000 fucking bits right now.
Dude, I've had my quarter on the game for like an hour now. Are you done yet?
Can you just let me goddamn play? Also, please stop talking about people shitting in your mouth.
It's scary. I remember that you put a coin up on the cabinet and that meant that it's my turn next.
I do remember that. But what happens when the guy comes in with like $20 in tokens and fills the
whole thing up like I just did? You have one token on there. I've put in like 40 to stay here. It
should be a fucking walk in the park though. I mean, like, look, I know what I'm doing.
Remember when I first played this? Holy fuck. I just ate my words. Yeah, I'll get this shit.
Let's go. Look at that polarity shifting fucking expertise. Look at that fucking polarity shifting
expertise right there. All right, do this. Let's go. Bingo. One, two, three, go.
Fuck out of here. Come on. Got it. Nice. Cod Modern Warfare 3 waiting room.
Stop. All right. I got full. I didn't even lose one health. Let's keep it rolling.
Polarity shift. Inbound. Got one. This is it. Clean. Get rid of that shit. Clean. Very clean.
There it is. Here comes the tricky one. Eat them all. Eat them all. See what? That's what we call
fucking clean. On level two. Let's unlock chapter three. Boring visual. I want face cam. All right.
Fine. How does that see? I didn't get hit once. I'm getting tangled in my cord. I fucking stupid
ass fucking headphones are like strangling me. All right, let's go. Fill the right border with
your face. What an annoying request. You know what I mean? Not that what you said was annoying,
but that's going to annoy people. Fine. This is annoying. This is annoying. This is so annoying.
Okay, easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. All right, good. This is annoying. Okay, I switched. What's happening?
Okay, we're good. All right, same deal. Oh, stop calling me a nerd. I should be going switch,
switch, switch, switch, switch, switch, switch. I don't, but it's not. I know. I could be missing.
I'm missing out on points, but I want the HP. Take the whole eat it. Good. Okay. All right.
I'm ready to go on to chapter three. Mirror it. You need to see that info. All right. Stop.
I'm going to get hit by something if you don't stop it. No, you motherfucker. Fuck out of here.
I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. I win. Stop.
This is annoying. This is annoying me. This is annoying me. Get rid of this. Get rid of the game.
Two big bits in a row. Jesus. Uh, phylactery liches gave a hundred dollars in bits. Chapter three.
Hold on. Hold on. Phylactery lich. Uh, 10,000 bits. It's, it's fucking phylactery. This is like
more. This is like $7,000 over the last like six months. Holy shit. Insanity. Anyways, they say,
it's not my birthday, but please mirror your face cam to the other side so that you stare at yourself
while you were gone. I got lonely. So I watched grill master X BBQ instead. He turned himself
into a pickle and it was the funniest shit I've ever seen. Almost split my zero calorie monster.
Fuck. Wait, it's not your birthday. This is so bad. I feel bad for people that want to fucking
enjoy a video game. I feel bad for some of you that like actually now, now a majority of the stream
is not Icaruga. You know that, right? A majority of the stream now is just look at the streamer's
fucking mirrored face. This is no longer an Icaruga stream. Oh shit. I can't kill it.
How do I get by that? Oh my fucking God. I'm losing it. How am I? How do I get by this? Oh shit.
We got to slow the fuck down. Just hug the corner here. Let's go boss. That was nuts. That was the
intro. That was the intro to chapter three. Super chain. That was totally fucking mother of what's
it doing? What the fuck? Holy shit. The thing I've got infinite continues. Um, what? Holy,
that's so ridiculous. That's insanity. Now with the Ferris wheel, welcome to bullet hell.
Let's go. Let's do it. Can I turn this off now? This is, have we irritated everybody enough?
You mutton chops are coming in. I just, I shaved. What do you mean no? Nobody wants to view this.
This is like a hurts people's eyes. Look at like, I can like come in on you. What do you
guys see that one? The viewers went up. I'm having it on for the next. This is it. Well,
I've already shipped. Well, I've already shipped inbound. Oh boy. Wonder how Jim is going to get
out of this one. I'm just the fucking weirdo that just is in the corner. I'm watching the show with
you. I don't know what to look at. That's what I'm fucking saying. I know I'm taking it off.
Imagine if you could switch polarity like crazy. Got it. Ban him. Keep it. It's fine. It's the theme
of the game. Keep it all. We riot. All right. I'm at fucking, I'm at the pursuer. How big is the
pixel? Anybody know how big the pixel is for this? Is it just one pixel? What should I be concerned
with? Fundamentals. Fundamentals only. Fundamentals only. Fundamentals only fundamentals. Take it all
in and absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb, absorb and fire and fire. Whoa, that was
intense. Oh, I can only turn one of them off. Kiss yourself. I, hold on. I can't, I, do you see what,
what, I, I can't get through this. You see the fucking wall, man. I can smell you making fun
of me. Stop or I'll cry. Stop or I'll cry. Stop or I'll cry. Stop or I'll cry. Am I dressed like
Shaggy? It's a green shirt. It's one of the primary colors. Red, green, blue, and the other ones.
I'm just testing you. I'm just like testing you to see if you can fucking make it go like I do.
All right. Open up. Open up now. Open up now. Open up now. Open up now. Sick. All right. We're
going to get to chapter three with all continues and all health bars. You know, this is the first
for me. I really thought that one was going to be the end of me. What am I? All right. What,
why am I doing like a fucking Malcolm in the middle? Why do I keep addressing the camera?
Why is this like my video diary right now? You're not the boss of me now. You're not
the boss of me now. And you're not so cool. Polarity shit. Polarity in my pants. What the
fuck are you saying? I mean, no. All right. Stop. We're just going for one side.
Worth it. Switch sides. Check it out. Boom. That's how you fucking get it done. Did you see,
did you see that shit? Fuck. Break it. Break it. Oh, my bad. I can't escape. I can't. That's my
escape shoot. It only does one. What's, you should play Lisa the Painful. Did anybody just say that
or am I making that up to be annoyed? Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. That's how you get it. Fucking.
I made it. Oh, no. Putties. Everybody got that? You don't even watch Power Rangers.
What are you? All right. I got, this is fucking me up.
No, here they come. Here they come to fire. All right. I got, I didn't do well on that one
last time. Polarity shift. Go back. Go back. Little, the little guy. All right. I got,
I got plenty of continues. I'm good. All right. Switch. Polarity. What the fuck? I hit the button
my fat ass finger. Yo. What? Easy. Easy there. Holy shit. That guy sucks. Oh, oh, it's, it's like
it moves fucking faster. Oh shit. It's going the other way.
Go this way instead. Oh, my God. I'm fucking running this shit. I don't know if it continues.
This is unfucking believable. This shit is like so fucking difficult. Like,
fuck. I had so many fucking, all right. That's it. Delay one side. I can't. I tried it before.
I need to get this off. This is like, I'm annoying you. I'm annoying me. Give me that chain. You're
making it better. Give us more. There's no more room to put more. What do you mean you want more?
I can't do more. Add a reverb. You just made me die. Why would I add a reverb? That's the, why would
you, why do you want that? You don't want this. Nobody here actually wants me to do this. Besides,
you, you're the only person in the room when I said, who wants a reverb? And that there's 10,000
fucking people in this audience. I see one hand and I go, that's all right. Let's get it on there.
Invert the colors. Make it for different polarities. I don't think I can do that.
One white and one black. I don't think I can do that. I can't do like a monochrome thing.
It's too, it won't work. Negative. That was, that's going to hurt your eyes.
I have to, I can't. All my webcams are packed. There. Now wait. Make one delayed. I can't unless
I have another webcam. I would, I seriously would love to do that. I really would, but I need a
second webcam because it takes the source. I can't do it. The reason why I could do that before is
because I had another cam. Turn one upside down. Get a set. I don't, it's, everything's packed. I
don't have anything. I wonder if I could fuck it. Can I split this? Let me see. No, I can't. It's
the same source. Add more. No, I can't do it. Add ambient audio effects. Oh fuck. I'm still on a
reverb. No, not four more. No, no, no, not four more. No, no. You're getting this for a little
while. No, not prototype mode. Backup. No, how do I get the fuck out of here? How do I, where's the,
the fuck is happening? Here we go. No, I don't want to see the fucking credits. All right,
here we go. Now I'm going to play. This hurts my head. I know. I blame the 15 people that said to
do this and I'm turning it off soon. All right, let's go. The one on the left is, just doesn't
make any sense. I changed where the thing is on the screen. I don't like that. Put it back. Where
was it? Put that back. Was it six? Right there. Keep it. All right, this is the one. I'm going to
get past chapter three. I really should play chapter three on its own and practice it.
That's the correct thing to do. Yes. If I get past chapter three, then I'm going to pick chapter
four and I'm going to practice chapter four. Choose your fighter. Select your character.
Let me take you for a ride. I want to take you for a ride.
Now let me take you for a ride. You know, when I was younger, I, you know what I thought that they
were saying? I thought that instead of take you for a ride, I thought they were saying,
I want to shake you boom boom ba. I want to shake you boom boom ba. I was like fucking 13. I don't
know. I want to shake you boom boom ba. I want to shake boom boom ba. He's literally deaf.
You made me die. All right, just play. Molly, I want to go home. What the fuck. Polarity shift
incoming in three, two. Activate polarity switch. Fill it up, fill it up, fill it up, fill it up,
fill it up, fill it up. New viewer here. Does this guy always do stuff like this? Well,
I'm one of those gamers that plays kind of whatever he feels like. I'll be live three,
four days a week. Left forever. Make two more. What do you want me to have them just all fucking
on the side like a shitty wallpaper? You're going to crash my computer. You're going to crash. My
computer is going to crash if I do that. You don't want that. Oh my God, you do. You guys have lost
your fucking minds. This is going to look like shit. Keep this one. I'll put them on the squares.
God, I wish I had fucking access to like five or 10 cameras. Hold on to this because I'm going to
get like 15 webcams and set them all up and just fucking have a brawl in my living room. I'm going
to beat the shit out of myself with like 30 different webcams. It's going to be fucking crazy.
They're all going to be in like random. I'm going to lose track of everything. I should,
I should like delay some of them by like four minutes and get in like costumes and come in
and be like, it's me, Superman. And then fucking just start, just walk off set.
This is going to be nuts. I'm going to buy like 30 webcams. Ah, this is,
no thanks. This is going to take like, this is going to take like 30 minutes to do this. Just this
one man. I got it. That's, that's, I got to do that. I can't even fucking see, man.
Is that in there? I'm going to crash OBS. Turn the brightness up. I will. It's Andy Warhol.
This is going to be such a pain in the ass to delete every single fucking one of these
in a little bit. We're going to have so much fun with the 30 webcams stream.
I'm going to do that sooner than you think. In fact, I'm just going to fucking order them like
today. We're going to have like a bunch of different scenarios that I was going to play out.
It'll be a lot of fun. That, how much, okay, hold on a minute. How much is a webcam?
All right. This is, you're talking, this is a real investment. A decent webcam is like 60 or 70 bucks.
I can do like full HD 60 FPS. It's like $60. So this is going to be thousands of dollars.
Just get really garbage ones. Yep. They won't, they might not be able to even get pulled through.
What? Okay. I get, do you want me to get a bunch of $30 webcams? What am I going to do with these
when I'm done? What am I going to do with them? Just get wicked shitty ones. Give them away.
I'm not going to give away 30 webcams. All right. That's good. Oh, whoa. They're all swimming
together. Okay. Let's change this. What's going on? Why is it doing this? This thing is broken.
There we go. Wow. Hey, chat. How many fingers am I holding up? That's fucking terrifying. All right.
Let's go. Icaruga. Some said it's one of the hardest games ever made. Some say Icaruga.
Some say it's one of the hardest games ever. 12 more in the little slots in the bottom left.
No, you guys need to be able to see when I have power. I just invited my friend to this stream.
He left. Oh, his loss. Hey, let me guess. Uh, when he left and he was like, fuck that stream,
you were like, yeah, man, down the Twitch rabbit hole. You find all kinds of fucking characters
on a down Twitch rabbit hole. I'm leaving. Stay. Why? What would you leave for? I'm playing
Icaruga. Some say hardest fucking game ever. This is my first stream. What's up, dude? Welcome to the...
What are we calling ourselves now? What are we calling ourselves now? The... I don't know.
There's too many groups. There's like the Moo crew, the Drew crew. What's the Jerma crew?
Do I have one? I don't think I even have one. Do I? Is anybody listening to me? The Jerms. No,
that's like 2012. How about the wicked sloppy eaters? That kind of rolls off the tongue. Kind
of cool. Bingo. Bingo. Oh, yeah. Welcome to the stream, guys. Hey, it's us. You know that this
group. Hey, you just you just followed for the first time. Welcome to the We Put Too Much
Fucking Ketchup on All of Our Food crew. We love that shit here. Oh, you fucking idiot.
You just bumped me. No, you bumped me. I was coming out of the fucking spot and you didn't stop for me.
You can slow down. What's your fucking insurance? Unbelievable. Pay fucking attention.
And notice you didn't put your cart back either. Dick. I can't. Oh, I can't wait to like chug a water.
I'm going to drink like I'm going to. OK, I'm going to like chug a water at some point during
the 30 webcam stream. And at some point, like 10 minutes after I start streaming, one of them is
going to slam the water. One of them. Multiply my mic channel. No, we'll save it. What are you
doing? Don't switch. What are you doing? All right. Itchy face. Medicine, Max. Max about medicine.
Skip everything quick. What the fuck are you doing? I'm fucking crazy, I think.
What happened to you in the last few days? Well, I'm packing boxes and moving and it's making me
crazy. No, I've been actually been I've been OK. It's been fun. I've had a good time on these
streams. That's what I love. I love. Great. All right, let's get this done. I got three.
What the fuck even hit me? Game is not even programmed correctly.
I do sound like a fucking psycho, huh? I'm just having fun, man. Oh, my. All right. He comes.
Watch out. I thought he went through. God damn it. When does he blast through? Right now, right?
Jesus. He's shitting me. Dude, fuck this guy. Dude, this guy's a fucking pain in the ass.
All right. How many continues do I have? Two. All right. Let's try to not fuck this up. One. What
the fuck? Where's the last one? Where's the last one? Where's the last one? Oh, up in smoke.
Clap. It only took cheating. This is level four. Time to turn up the difficulty.
Mm hmm. Can I absorb those? I guess. All right. That's what it's about. Reality is unveiled.
And what did it want? You have noisy eyelashes. You know, I actually can hear my eyelashes when
I sleep. It's like, I mean, that that person's that person's a sicko, but you know, whatever.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. This is insanity. What happened to one of the Germans? I'm I want to practice
chapter four. I got an achievement. One of them has to go. Oh, right. OK. See you later, dude.
No, no, no. Wait, wait. I have to confirm. Everybody fucking everybody point and laugh at
this guy. See you. You're leaving. Ha ha ha ha. I'm not going to multiply the mics. All right.
Let's I want to get I got to get a good feel for it after four takes practice. Practice makes
perfect. You know, I'm just going to feel for it. I don't know what the fuck I'm doing right now,
but it's not a good. It's not working. One to two left. Bilateral religion of the five hundred
fucking fifty. Whatever it is, it's fifty dollars. Five thousand bits from phylactery phylactery
says by the webcam slave. This is pleasing to chat. I'm going to get them. Well, I'm going to
do that as soon as I can. This is this is absurd. I have to stay on one polarity. I can't change.
And then they start coming in. Holy fuck. Lord, use the shields to your advantage.
Well, I I'm kind of itchy head right now. Hold on. This game was designed to take
fifty dollars from each person that wanted to try to play. Where's the safe place to stand here?
Hope I get back here with ten fucking continues. That is of course not. Holy shit.
Come on, stinky. This is a baby game. Multiply mics. I can't do that. Oh, my God. You're killing me.
How many are there? What is that? What was that? What was that? I don't even know what it was.
What happened? What was that? Was the game audio? Why is the game audio coming through?
This is all fucked up because of because of the mixer. How about this? That change anything? No,
that change anything? No, that's fucked up. I can't do it. Just add a chorus.
Might as well just do this. This is potential best joke in 2020. I would hold on to that
because it's going to be thirty fucking webcams attached here. We this this joke is going to be
is going to absolutely run its entire course. I can't do it. It won't work. I got this fucking
mixer. It's all screwed up. Twenty nine and I'll be furious. All right, let me try to figure out
this fucking chapter four. We have thirty USB ports. I'll just get a I'll get a extension.
Hopefully, I have to be careful because if I have a USB extender with like an extra ten,
right, you know what I'm saying? Like, would that work? I need enough like bus spots, right?
Whatever they're called needs to be an active extension. Oh, man. Try just not fire at all.
The wall. Yeah, but they come down this wall. They they behind the wall. They still fly in.
I was doing a thousand continues. I don't care. I'm literally going to put on 99 continues.
You call me a cheater if you want to. This is fucking crazy. They've already taken like
thirty dollars of my tokens at this point. Can I sit back here? What if I just hold on? What if
I just sit back here? Wait, hold on. I probably should only go. I'm going to only shoot for the.
I don't know. This is fucking outrageous. Left. Jeremiah could have done this.
Fuck, man. This is so fucking crazy. Left, right, left, right, left, right while switching polarity
like right, right, left, left, right, right, left, left, right, right, left, left, right,
right, left, left, right, right, left, fuck, right, left. This is a five hundred dollar game.
Like you've got to spend you've got to spend five hundred dollars to beat this.
This is one of those scenarios where the guy you know when you went to the arcade and you would get
the cup because it didn't fit in your pocket. How many tokens you got?
There's somebody with a big fucking big gulp cup sitting on top of this desk onto on the cabinet.
And they're just like if the thing weighs like fucking three and a half pounds like that,
it's a big unit and it's probably has like two or three hundred tokens in it.
Call me cheater if you want. I just want to see the I want to see the boss. Call me cheater. I don't care.
Remember there's a line of people behind you and they're all small but look at them.
Let's exit the game. What just happened? All right, let's go. It's time. Chapter four. Chapter select.
I'm beating this shit even if I have to fucking use powers. Wait, I should do arcade mode then,
right? Somebody said your five eight lol. Yeah and somewhere like fucking 700 million people on the
planet. Oh wow. Oh I can't believe he's five eight. That's like the same size of like a billion people.
Why does he so sound so what? Tom Cruise is fucking five seven.
All in him and that motherfucker like saves the world. But what I'm talking about in his movies.
What? I can't. They make him stand on boxes. Energy Max. This is pretty good. This is pretty
significant play in this game. Doesn't matter. I have infinite lives. We're just going to beat
the fucking game right now. Doesn't count. That's okay. Whatever. Whatever. This game is pretty cool
though. This game is really good. How is it not dead? Play with 99 lives instead of infinite
continues. I think I went right past that boat. I just I want to see the bosses and stuff. Look,
I'm playing on like story mode. Play Mario Paint. Is that game good? Is that like the Looney Tunes
one for Super Nintendo? Come on. Come on. Kick up Luka. Energy Max. Energy Max. Energy Max.
My grandma can play this game better than you. Oh yeah? Challenging. Rewarding.
Why is this stream under puzzle category? What? What? This is under. Why is it under puzzle?
English puzzle shoot them up. I didn't do that. Oh that's another thing we can do.
Okay so I'm gonna write this down. On the 30 webcam stream we're gonna do a
German jigsaw puzzle with my whole body. I'm gonna like just stand and we're gonna try to
put me together. Sounds fun. All right well by the way we're doing this in like we're doing this in
like less than five days. You understand? This is happening like within the next week. I fucking
promise. We're doing this like this like probably next weekend. I swear to god this is too interesting
for me. Don't give me hope. No there's no way that doesn't happen. If I can connect I might need
another computer right? I might need to get another computer like a laptop which also has like seven
or eight USB buses. Feed that video through and control them. Like I'm gonna need like probably
three computers right? Laptop with eight. What happened? Why did I leave the game for?
What just happened? What just happened? Why did that just kick me out?
I lost? Like no I didn't. It was on chapter select? No it was not. Is it goes on free play?
It was? No well fuck I can't believe it. No it wasn't. You sure it was? Fuck. One player game arcade.
Arcade. It was on it. Arcade normal. German forgot his homework. He didn't tell us why he never was
gonna play Lisa. I just well I told you yesterday because I don't want to.
What? Didn't I say I don't want to play? I'm not playing Odama right now. I gotta figure out how
I'm gonna do this webcam thing. Does anybody know realistically how many actual video devices you
can pull through something like OBS without having a separate computer? Hold that like that speed.
What is it like four or five? At least and it's at least two. It's probably it's probably like five
or six. 12? OBS allows at least Odama. Fucking god. Kill the big one on the left and then the big
one on the right. Did you check the toilets on the left? Did you check the toilets on the right? Did
you check toilets on the left? Did you check toilets on the right? Did you check toilets on the left?
Did you check toilets on the right? Did you check toilets on the left? Did you check the toilets on
the right? He's on crack. He's on crack. He's on crack. He's on crack. He's on crack. No he's not.
He's on crack. He's on crack. He's on crack. Okay stop.
Boring. Boring. Boring. Hair flip. Boring. Boring. Boring. Shut up. All right shut up. Kill
that one. What do you think I'm doing? I'm killing. We want blood. We want explosives. We want blood.
This is why the webcams never on you guys understand you get it now you actually get it
All right. So why am I not going to chapter two?
This is fucking me up. I thought it's because of nudity. Well, it's both. It's because of both
Okay, boss battle bonus. I did it score axe chain grade C
Moving on to chapter two. I don't what the fuck was that? That was weird. All right, let's do let's beat this whole damn game
Okay double, please. Stop swearing. Please stop. All right, I won't
You hear me swear one more time. I will give one community sub before every
FUCK you hear okay
only that one
Only for today by the way. Oh
Only today only today today only for the next five straight minutes
Come on say it fun. I am having fun
And now he's having fun. I heard a I heard is I heard of rumor over there and typically I would say the upward
Not today though
stupid
Whoops, got it. Got it. Eat them all eat them all eat them all eat them all eat them all
When is he eating the shoe I'm not eating the shoe. All right, I'm not eating the shoe
Pardon to the mic
No, all right. Let's do this one
Why did I read that? I don't know. It's chats going real fast. I'm reading random shit
What the fuck man?
Whoa, I got the whole thing. Oh, whoops. That's a sub. That's one I
I
Completely forgot we were doing that. I don't I completely forgot. That's one. All right, you get one
I'll I'll I'll pay up at the end of the screen
Just give me to the end of the screen. Just give me to the end of the screen and i'll get you
I already have a sub. I want another one
greedy
Greedy
Give me another one. I greedy
All right. I'm just like fucking
That's two
Is there speed runs of this game? Do they run this that stuff like um
HDq or anything? I feel like this would be crazy to watch somebody do this and not get hit
The speed runs for every game
It might be inaccurate that might not be accurate
I'm, not sure that's accurate
It's something that nobody's speed run before
Right
All right. Let's go
I got funky
Oh, I didn't say I said funky
So I ran out of quarters and what I ended up doing
Is I um, I opened up the machine the front of the machine where the coins go
And there's that little tab that registers the coins and I got in there and went
And then I closed it up
That's illegal. Not if you own the arcade. It's not
Not if it's my place
After hours the business is closed. I want to play Icaruga until I win
I mean illegal
Hold on. It's illegal for me to open up an arcade cabinet that I own
after hours and
Jiggle the coin thing to get a hundred lives
No, it's not
I own the machine
Machine owns you what?
Now that okay
Doesn't matter
Okay, i'm just playing so sloppy now because when you know that you believe there's nothing to fear
I just like i'm like whatever I can just die a bunch of times. I own the fucking arcade
This game is kind of hard
All right play for real. Let's go
I mean, this is fucking hard as shit. It is
jeez
Give it up for four
For what?
Oh four subs
I mean, that's the technique
Got it. Where's the blood? This game sucks
Look at me times 20 shit shit these schmups. I swear these schmups are so difficult
Replay by the way omega low
Oh
Schmup. Hey you shut the schmup up. He's learning. He's learning
God, finally, he's learning
All right. I gotta slow down. I'm freaking some of you out right now
God my doesn't want to go. It's just coin. It's just coin stealing
This is stealing coins at this point
What even fucking hit me five
Oh my god, this is this is crazy
I feel like this is the part of the game where like if you speed run the game and you get hit once it's over
You hate this part
You probably you probably sit there and go this is the worst thing. I just gotta make sure I don't get hit
I gotta be careful. This is the worst one
This is easy when you know, yeah, I guess when you know, you just know right
But this part in particular is freaking me out. Should I follow the beams?
I mean, I guess this is kind of sort of
It's just too many colors on the screen. My brain can't look at it
It's it's too many colors
They're just fool. It's I feel like i'm playing like guitar hero 12 times in a row like on five different screens
and
Five different songs
Give us a good reason why you don't want to play lisa
Because I said so okay mom
This is it. This is what we separate the gamers from the
Whatever. I don't know
Hard game
I feel bad for that guy that wrote that steam review that doesn't realize you can put it on free play mode
I feel you man. You and I are you and I are in this together
What geez?
Okay, it's just don't move but it's you have to
I only have 13 seconds left
I'm gonna die from time
Uh, did that come back? Is that do I get more time?
Or what what happens here? Is that gonna start the countdown at three seconds right now?
No, it's not right. It's like a timed mission
All right. Here we go
Okay. Oh man
This is fucking
This is ridiculous
You have to you have to move you have to move
Dude, I can't even switch polarities in time. I'm gonna run out of time
Yo, kill him kill him. I have 10 seconds
Lame what do you mean lame? That was pog. Didn't I say I was gonna go pee like two hours ago? I did right?
You're a cheater
Call me whatever you want. I'm a winner in my book
That's a big chain 20 chain
Oh
Oh big boy
Would you play dark souls 3 with infinite health?
Not even a fair comparison
I make you alive so that you can walk along the right way, but you can't understand it. What is this the brain?
Right in the middle if you play dark souls with infinite health
No, I wouldn't but that that that that's
You're wrong. Damn. Okay. I guess i'm wrong then
You can't feel the visible things. How can you feel the invisible things?
This is pretty sick. Wait, let him grab me. Oh, no, this shit is fucking wacky
That's wacky
You gotta that's
Wacky, man. Oh, there's no way you beat this normally unless you put in 500 bucks
There's no way you do this normally without five hundred dollars
Don't cap that
It's impossible to cut off this metamorphosis forever. Can you see can't you?
Do I have to destroy something?
Holy shit absorb absorb fire
Absorb fire. I
That sure was a tricky one. Let's see how germ affairs are the next game. That was a disgusting empty win
Oh, that's not it. That's not it match. Um, can you imagine if I had gotten here and beat wow good thing
We didn't do that
Can you imagine if I had gotten here and just didn't do this?
Uh, what am I supposed to do?
You want to absorb for points
I gotta get at least four million zero
remain bonus plus five hundred thousand
four point seven eight five million points
He keeps forgetting basic mechanics. Um, no, i'm i'm not it's just
Lights are filling every inch of the screen
This is a hollow victory
Maybe for you
Not for me
Is this what we wished for?
Don't worry, we will understand each other someday and the life is succeeded into a distant future. What the fuck is happening
There was like some kind of story here
Ikaruga
That was fucking fun
Hey, I beat the first three levels without cheating
That's a
Hey, if i'm allowed to if I take up 66 percent of the screen
I'm allowed to cheat for 66 percent of the game
Because the 66 percent of the game of the stream has been me
I'll be right back. I gotta pee
Okay, so i'm gonna make you all real sad right now
Well, hi, i'm gonna make you all real sad
I've
I've got a lot of shit to do and I gotta stop. Sorry. These last few streams have been like three to four hours
But they have to be
i'm sorry
That's the way it is. But I will tell you i'm going to work on something very very important
When I get back
Now I know you're not gonna want to hear this either and I don't want to say this either
But like I have to there's so many things I have to do and i'm sorry
I have to you have i'm gonna have to do another small leave of absence here another couple of days
Another two or three days and then we'll hopefully be back to normal
I'm sorry. I know i'm sorry. I know I know I know I know I know I was just gone for like five days
And this we just did three here and they're shorter. I know I trust me. I know I want to stay but
I forgot i'm like over here. I'm like leaning it but
Wink to make up for it
I
Here's what you can look forward to
The next stream was a calendar when I come back
You ready for this?
Are you ready to hear this?
the next stream
Will be on thursday or friday probably friday
And I am going to do whatever I can to make it possible to do the webcam stream on friday
And then saturday and possibly sunday
hulk ultimate destruction
That's the plan for this weekend
Finally hulk ultimate destruction waiting room. There you go. If I can get that i'm so interested in that webcam stream
So like not only am I going to go do a bunch of other shit
But i'm going to do a ton of research into how I can get like at least 10 to 15 webcams pointed at me and captured
But with that I am you're going to see here we go. We're going to disappear here
Who's going to be left?
All right, place your bets
Place your bets, which one's going to be the last one remaining. I'm just going down to listening deleting them. Who's going to remain?
Who's lights going to turn off last top right? That's cheating though. It wasn't even top right. It was this guy
Who's this guy? Oh, it's me
Oh, how many um, how many community subs do I have to give?
six seven how many
seven
nine
Where are you getting nine from?
Nine, are you adding numbers on?
Why do I look so weird? Oh, it's because i'm flipped
It was nine. Was it nine?
You're adding nine. Are you adding you're adding them? Are you getting a lot of sevens? It was nine you greedy
But i'll just round it up to ten. Whatever. That's that's all good
Sure, here i'll help you out here. Fuck
Fuck fuck see there you go
I have seven there's seven eight nine ten. We're gonna do ten do it right now
So obviously those are you leaving i'll see you guys on friday
Sorry again for the very short streams i've been doing recently, but it's very necessary
We'll have a we're gonna have a ton of fun on friday
the fucking webcam nonsense stream is gonna be
Pretty fun unless it's all fucked up and doesn't work and then you'll hear a complaint about it for about 45 minutes
While I play cooking mama, too. There you go
Uh, let me give the subs
Actually go to the outro
So people know that i'm an outro. Ikaruga is actually that's a really good game
That's a really cool mechanic. It's a classic. I'm glad I played half of it
I'm glad I played half that game and then cheated for the rest
All right gift community subs. Where is it? Fun fun fun fun
Gift a sub you've gifted you've given
791 gift subs
Did when when have I given I've given 800 subs what when
I remember a couple there was the one time when I did 500 like a couple months ago a month ago, right?
That was like two weeks ago. Oh shit. Okay. All right gift subs 10 gift subs. Here they come 10 and
There you gifted 10 tier one subscriptions. That puts me over 800. That's me 801
Just giving money to twitch
Yes, that's pretty much what i'm doing
But anyways, let's uh, let's do the subs and the bits and everything. Thanks again for sticking around
Hope to see you again soon
on friday specifically
Specifically on friday. I'm so pumped up for this thing. I'm going to do whatever it takes to make this work
Even if I have to get like two or three computers in here to get this to work
I'm gonna do it
I gotta get like a list of of just weird shit to do and I mean like
Puzzle the stick the human puzzle, right scrambling while i've tried to put together
The fight in the room like the brawl
Um, there's like at least there's at least like
Five 15 minute bits here that will last us a good hour or two. Can't wait for cooking mama, right?
All right, let's do the bits. We have 250 from hole of one zombie. Thank you hole of one zombie
Let's turn the volume up a little bit. It's a little low
It occurred to me that yesterday's viva piata was like when you ask for a power rangers toy for christmas
But get a bootleg wild ranger instead and proceed to cry
It's great fun though
What was wrong with this viva piata? It was a good game, man
What's wrong with it? It was viva piata. It wasn't like
what
Whatever. Thanks for the 250 lm man. Thanks for the 250 germa
Which wrestler in the rumble streams is the hardest to make earthworm jim?
earthworm jim was the hardest character to make for sure because
Painting his whole head took so long because of how long it took to load every single spray on his head
Yeah
Every every little detail on his face and shit just took so much stupid amount of time because of how that game loads layers
I think it turned out all right though. Thank you to gnarly for the 250
Hey, i'm glad you took my advice yesterday and did some more crack
Before today's stream loving this new crack era of germa streams to keep up the great work. Wait, wait, wait are we?
Boston era vegas era crack era. Is that where we are? Why does that chain of events?
Sound very realistic. Yeah, that's fucked up. Oh boston vegas
Crack now he's on that
That's
All right. Well, uh, see in like in seven or eight months
Uh when i'm not like that was just like a christian stream and I like i'm like a christian guy and I really like the bible
And stuff thanks to the 250 though
Uh dinner master. Thanks to the five community subs missed it earlier, but thanks with five subs
Thank you dinner master. That's a pretty great name dinner master
Uh dungeness. Thanks for the five dollars
Just want to let you know that you look like a shorter version of shaggy from that live-action scooby-doo movie lul
Yeah
Hey dark soul, thanks for the 250
Local streamer buys out all stock of webcams during pandemic family's now unable to skype video chat grandma
Actually webcams are super expensive right now. What are you talking about? Are they
Wait, is there like a webcam shortage right now? Am I about to pay like insane premium prices?
No, right
No
Why this one's two hundred dollars? Why?
Wait logitech webcam unavailable
Oh, no
I have to I have to get like the off this one's 500 bucks
What's this off-brand one this this one's like this one says this one has one rating
And it's one star on on amazon
1080p webcam with microphone fast auto focus
Oh
Oh, if you advertise fast auto focus in the title of your product
I'm, not sure this thing even turns on
logit, oh
Lee shit the logitech
c615
Just that general
Camera is a hundred and eighty nine dollars right now. Oh my god
Isn't this thing usually like 20 bucks really? Oh, no, can I not do this?
There's only one of these
What?
Do it on ebay. Yeah, but ebay will take forever to get here
If I do ebay, it will take like two weeks for this shit to get here
all right, i'm gonna have to keep looking into this because
Some there's a oh boy. These are also these are probably not gonna work
329 fucking dollars you aren't kidding
I love how this one is webcam 1080p with microphone and cover
Anti-spy with like a thing like a thing of like an x over an i anti-spy
Okay
compute computer webcam desktop pc webcam camera mic laptop
16 megapixel. Oh this thing looks like
This thing is probably gonna look so bad
HD smart mic, but I don't even will obs even take this in it's in stock
If I buy 10 of these and they don't do anything. What the fuck am I gonna do?
I'll figure this out over the next couple days. I gotta figure out this is impossible now
well
Cooking mama looks real fun now
The world's supply of webcams. All right, i'll uh, let's keep going
Let's keep going. I'll see if I can figure this out
Thanks for that heads up though. I didn't realize that I didn't even think about that
That was a dark soul
Dark soul, uh gave us the heads up
Hole of one zombie. Thanks for 250. I came back and thought you'd gotten all the power-ups
I wasn't prepared for the germa ad event calendar
Hey the plushie. Thanks for 250. Congrats. You got louis g'd all the way through bowser
It's okay. That's all right. Sometimes you gotta
Sometimes you gotta just let the game play
And hang out sometimes freshly brewed cider
Thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars. They say if you sat in a puddle of your own piss long enough
Would your legs disintegrate? Why would your legs disintegrate?
p
P is just water and all the extra vitamin c that you didn't process. That's all it is
It's just p and vitamin c. That's it. It's like
You
German is too iq if okay
I know we fuck around a lot here. We do we really do but if you really think that I think that
Human urine
Is water and vitamin c. I don't I can't help you there
I can't I think I really think that
You think I actually think that water and vitamin c is piss
No, it's that smelly stuff. That's in the cleaner bleach
water and
Whatever it is
Whoa, that would fucking be horrible
Hey dark soul, thanks for the 250 pretty unbased that you refuse to collab with coron just saying kind of cringe
You know pretty stupid just saying ha just getting great stream streamer. Keep up the streams and stop fucking cheating one more sub
All right weird talking about collabs
I I fly solo until
It's necessary for me to want to do anything with somebody else. We already talked about this
I don't have plans to do any collabs. It's just if they happen they happen
I'm I go i'm solo. This is solo act one-man show
On solo and he was the coolest character in that whole show
Okay, I just saw german 985 gave 10 community subs and I forgot and I thought somebody I don't know
I thought somebody had the same name as me
I was about to thank german 985 for 10 subs and I was like, wait a minute. That's me
I just did that
Right. Hey, sergel, but thanks to 250. I've been absent from streams recently
preparing financially for the great depression 2
Depressed harder makes me concerned for how you've been dealing with this
You don't want to get too personal. Just give me a kiss instead
How is that? No, that's like five times more. What are you what?
um
You got I was gonna like start saying like oh here and then you threw that in there and now i'm all you fucked me all up
Okay
Well, I hope we don't get there. I really hope that that doesn't happen
Hope that over the next few months we can really just try to get back to normal. Hopefully there's a
Vaccine comes out sooner than
Later, I know people are thinking it's maybe the end of the year or early next year. Hopefully we make it to there
Slowly we get rid of this shit. That's what I hope that's what I really want
Right. Everybody wants that
We've been told like 12 to 18 months for a vaccine
and now hopefully
over the next few months
We start to cases start to slow down. That's the number one thing
Once you're in a pandemic
It's people are going to get it. It's going to spread. That's what a virus does, right?
But to try to make it so it doesn't spread everywhere to everyone is what we're trying to do
Be careful
especially if you are in direct contact with people that
Are susceptible to the illness right leg if you have older people people with underlying conditions, right?
I mean, I know i'm saying the things that you've already heard but we have to we have to say it
We have to think about it. We got to talk about it. Don't be fucking careful
Take care of yourselves wash your hands
Don't get too close to anybody right? Just don't spread the damn thing. That's the bad part. That's what yeah, that's what i'm saying
I'm blocking my neighborhood at a block party yesterday
What the hell are they doing?
That's
doesn't make any sense
Hey, you know this like this big virus going around that like it's really starting to cases are starting to
Inflate in the in the country
You know what a great idea would be to like put myself with a bunch of other people
And as as many people as we can get in the same place and let's all sing songs out loud
That's like how it spreads
And I know and I know the thing is what i'm not gonna get it. I'm not gonna get it
Right, but if you if you touch the surface
Or you came into contact with the doorknob that had it on there and then you don't get it
But you give it to somebody else
And they get it
That's how this happens
You might not get it, but you might be the reason why 30 other people do
Sure, but you literally just kissed someone. No
Just be careful. Don't don't do any of that shit
There's no reason like i've seen like the photos of like the beaches and people are like fucking on the beach
Like let's hey, let's let's play tag on the beach
No, what are you doing?
Get go home
but anyways
I really hope that we can hit I we need to hit up we need to hit that
Flat like they say flatten it flatten it
We're gonna see more cases
But just we gotta fucking make it so hospitals don't get overrun by people. That's the main problem, right?
I know it's like oh, it's a it's like the flu. It's like a bad flu. It's a lot of a well
A lot of people say it's just like the bad flu. It's all good
yeah, but if when fucking a hundred thousand people in the same city get it at the same time and
20,000 of them need potentially to go to the emergency room
That's the problem
That's the issue
Right. It's a big part of it
People are dying from this. Yes, they are
It's not just old people. It's younger people too. It's mainly about making sure our hospitals don't get overrun
Because when you're out of beds and you're out of ventilators and and somebody comes in and they need one and you don't have one
You don't have a bed for that person
That's where it gets very bad
Yes, that's why it's important to stop the spread now. Yes
Exactly, you guys get it
I don't we don't I don't want to continue to we can move on from this but
It is good to talk about sometimes just to make sure kind of everybody's on the same page
It is a current fucking huge problem right now
Take care of yourselves
Wash your hands
Stay safe moving on we had 400 bits from sergeant chicken wing. Thank you for those
Four dollars
Jeremy kind of out of the loop since I missed a couple streams. Why all the short streams lately?
Are you moving again? Or did he miss something? Yes
Kim and I are in the process right now
of moving
We're anticipating we did a lot of stuff last week to get ready and start getting out
and over these next
Probably six to fifteen seven to fifteen days
We hope to be finally completely out completely
the issue and the reason why it hasn't happened already is because because of what we were just talking about with the coronavirus
A lot of stuff is a lot slower
whether that be trying to find apartments or a house to go to or
It's services that you need it for a for a new place it it's
Everything's very slowed down a lot. So it's we're trying to do it as best we can no more webcams. No
If las vegas is so good, how come there's no las vegas too?
Why would they need to be on what?
but that's why they've been shorter I
anticipate
that the
after this coming weekend, so let's say
after like
Somewhere around the the first week of april second week of april. I plan to be back to normal
with streaming and that means
Obviously streams that are more than four hours long back to kind of that normal like six to seven six to eight
We'll see that's that's the plan
but also
There's nothing to consider
I might try
Something in the future here when this is all said and done typically this stream is live
Three or four times a week for about six to eight hours, right?
I was thinking
maybe
What if that turned into?
like four or five days a week
but
Pulled back to about three or four hours a stream. I was trying to think of
And that though there's a reason why the only reason why I say this is because
The last three or four days
Remember we talked about how about the costochondritis and this potential like arthritis shit is like fucking me up
Sitting down for more than a few hours
When I get up after these three four hours streams
I feel okay. I feel all right
and I think that sitting down and being in the same place for more than six seven eight plus hours is
I think it's not helping. Let's just put it that way
And until I can have some type of solution where I have a standing desk where I can really just move around
I might try it
Maybe I haven't made a decision on it yet, but I was thinking about it
You know like four or five days a week for like three to five hour streams instead of three days a week eight hour streams
Or eight plus whatever you want to call them. I'm trying to figure it out
Do yoga breaks?
Yeah, the thing is though when you get into something
If i'm gonna sit here and stream and i'm into something and i'm having fun. I want to stick around it
Take getting up for 20 minutes and is that's it takes throws me off
Like i'd like to just kind of sit here and do what I want to do
I have not decided that that's gonna happen, but it's something that's floating around. Just want to let you know
Yeah, it would be more frequent but shorter
Rather than less frequent but longer we'll move on
Uh, thank you the sticky stick man for the 250. Hey germa first time catching the end of a stream from over here in europe
Thanks for keeping us entertained during this tough time. Hope all goes well with the move. Stay healthy you as well. Thank you for
kind words
I need to gain muscle and eat properly. I I I eat I eat fine
I eat at least two green vegetables every day
And they come out it comes out of a can but I still eat them. All right, let's do the credits
I'm gonna bump you. Whoops
Thanks for watching everybody. We'll see you on friday for hopefully the webcam
insanity stream
If I can get them
If I can figure out how to get those
If not, then we'll do something else. Of course, let's run the credits. You should see them any second
These are all the subs from today
plum today
Even with a three hour stream still a shitload of people subscribe, which is insane. Thank you guys
Thanks for the continued support
If you guys give a lot of money as always. Thank you
Is it only three hours? Yes, about three hours and 30 minutes if you count
The end of the stream here 25 minutes. Thank you one blondie for the 300 bits germa. I love you
Do you though do you are you sure you do you sure you know, are you sure about that love is a strong word
Are you still at 10k subs? No, no crossing that threshold was fucking ludicrous
So it is we've since come down
But still even after losing
Those subs from new years is still a shitload of people that is subbed to the channel. There's still a ton
like
It's just it's still increasing. Let's just put it that way and it's blows my fucking mind
What are we at now? Let's see. Let's just tell you
Uh, we are at we've been we've been hovering
this channel
uh, it is
7,800 holy shit. Yeah, so we've come down from 10
but
7,800 subs is still
a monumental amount of paid subscriptions
Even if it anything there's a lot of people that's a lot of subscriptions
Somebody said dead channel. Oh my god. Okay, it was
That's fucking funny
No, I can't I every time I open up my stream manager guys and I look at that I go that's fucking why?
That's a lot. That's a that's too many
That's too many people that are okay. That's a that's a lot and then I hit the broadcast button
anyways
Let's uh, we got one more message to get to just came in right now
Somebody's gonna fucking scream by the house. That's fine. See you guys on friday
And we have tar alecran one of the band. Wait, did I ever unban tar? I think I did right?
Thanks for 250. First of all, they say germa. Hi, it's tar here when you banned yesterday because you streamed
Despite my prediction that you wouldn't for the record
My original statement was the odds of germa moving and streaming by the end of the week are less than zero
Which was proven 1000 true since you didn't even move. I can't believe you even banned me temporarily
You're a disgraceful streamer. There was no sense of justice or honor. Yes
Love the stream been subbed for 42 months now waiting for my three-year badge, please
Did you see the I got I got the book thrown at me. Wait, why did this not what?
Oh, sorry, I fucked that up. They end up again for calling you out
Well, I can't do that
I mean like we just both walked out of the courtroom with our luggage and shit under our arms and different lawyers
Well, I can't what am I gonna I can't sue you if you win the case
And we walk out together from and we both you okay
It's over you have been found guilty when I walk out if you look at me and like go
Stick your tongue out and go ha ha
Like what am I gonna bring bring him back in? I want to sue him for that
Can you bring him back in? I want to sue him for for that
No, that's not how it works
guilty in a civil case omega low
Despite sue a spite sue
Oh, I i'll fucking sue you
I'll sue you motherfucker. Just wait
All right, let's write somebody who you won't see me for a few days
We got key. Oh key. Oh key. Well, I never catch key. Well every streaming
Uh key was awesome
Because I never I never end my streams
Anytime where people you are actually playing?
Yeah, we'll raid kilo. Let's say hello. What's she doing? She's doing granted out of five
no pixel
rp
Raid bernie
No, I we can't do that
I would I would no no no
No, I am terrified
Of no, I can't do that. I can't do that. I'm terrified
I don't want bernie to look over and be like
What's going on here? What do they say?
No, I don't know. No, no, no, no, oh, we're gonna break. He will all right. Let's go great
Keebo now raid kibo now kibo kibo kibo kibo kibo kibo kibo kibo kibo
Go go go go go go go click it click it click. Yes
Click yes, click. Yes click. Yes
Click. Yes. We're going to kibo. Yes
Click. Yes
Minus two fuck you. I am oh you crazy. Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
You have any idea
Do you have any idea the repercussions?
Of of the of the insanity that I could no no
Be polite to kibo. Yes
Fuck you. No, no
There's nothing to do about like politics
It's just I'm I'm not comfortable doing that. I'm not I don't want I don't want to do that
I'm not comfortable doing that. Okay, we're gonna go say kibo say hi to kibo. Okay, kibo isn't bernie. It's all right
That's that's okay. But kibo is cool, too
He was also very cool. I mean bernie's cool, right like bernie's streaming on twitch. That's fucking awesome. That's cool
Very cool, but let's go and say hi to kibo. Okay kibo kibo isn't bernie. I know but but I know but
But kibo is streaming right now. I'm just doing no pixel. You should check it out. Okay. Bye. Oh
Do you understand?
Okay
Bye
I'm going i'll see you on foam
Wait, am I live?
What just happened?