Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some facecam Fortress 2. What's today? Monday? Sunday? I don't even know. Saturday? Saturday's edition. Oh my god. I'm playing as the Sniper right now, which I don't know why I'm doing that.
Oh, come on. I got him. I got him. Yeah, playing as the Sniper with the Hitman's Heatmaker. Yeah, I keep saying Hitman's Headtaker, because somebody in the comments of my last Sniper video said that. And it actually rings a little bit better than the Heatmaker. Hitman's Heatmaker. The Darwin's Danger Shield and the Tribalman's Shiv. Oh, come on. I get him. Looks like they're at the last poi. This is on pipeline.
Alright, maybe I shouldn't. No, I'm going to stay Sniper. I'm going to stay Sniper on principle alone. Alright, let's start a new day. Let's start a new day. Let's start a new day. And just like the previous video, I am going to time travel. So here's the plane of existence right here. And this is where we want to be. This is the future right here. So if we can't just like... Okay, I think we made it, right?
We made it, right? Oh yeah, five seconds left. I set it perfectly for one minute exactly, and it worked. So let's play some Sniper and let's get some sniping shots. Oh man. Oh baby. What? Spy, where is he? Oh my god, you pesky little snake. Oh, you didn't shoot me. Oh my god. Oh my god. Problem? Yeah, big problem. God, they're just... No, I can't even play Sniper right now. They're just rolling us way too good. I'm going to play...
I'll play Demoman. I'm playing Demoman. We're not just going to get like rolled here. Oh, big problem. I killed plenty of birds. Oh, there's an Uber outside. That's a spy standing right here. It's over. It's over right now. It is just over. I think we... Did anybody get one kill? Oh my god. Wow. Well, let's try this again. This time I'm going to stay Demoman. I'm raring to go this time. Spam. Spam. Spam. Oh, I got hit with the Sniper.
Spam. Oh, lobbing. Lobbing. Lobbing like Robin. Lobbing like Batman and Robin. Speaking of Batman, I got to go see the Dark Knight Rises. I heard it's really, really good. Let's just roll. Let's just absolutely, absolutely roll. Roll. Roll. Roll. Whoa. Whoa. This is like just a sentry right here. What the hell is going on? I can't even like take this thing out. There we go. It's gone. Whoa. Oh my god. Just chaos. Chaos.
Absolute chaos. Oh my god. Oh, come on. Give me this. Give me this, please. Oh, what? What? What was that? What? Oh, I'm so speechless. I got him. I just got that guy. I can't believe I did not taunt kill that guy. Oh my god. He walked right into the blade. It hit him like right in his teeth. Oh, whatever.
That is such BS, man. You are dead. Not big surprise. Help me. Medic. Medic. Oh, you get it. You get it. You need it more than I do. Oh, no, you don't. You have a sandwich. Never mind. Yikes. God, I can't do anything. I'm scared to go out here. Oh, no, you don't. No, you don't. Oh, there's a double. I've killed more people with this than anything else. Get rid of that stuff.
I need a medic. I need a medic. No, I didn't want to take that out. That was a big mistake. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, spy. I just like almost threw up because I just ran around in a circle right there. Oh, come on now. Oh, you know what? I don't want you to lose you. What? What the hell? E-money. Oh, of course it was E-money. I wanted to save that guy's Uber because I didn't want him to die. And look what happens. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic. Oh, oh, oh. I need a medic
I need a medic. All right. Beatbox time. Ready? Here we go. I'm going to do the Team Fortress 2 theme song.
Now I need the music to help me like push forward. So here we go. Let's do the, let's do the medic song.
So let me think. Let me think how it starts. I'm not even like thinking about it.
Doctor, are you sure this will work? I have no idea.
Oh, that's enough. Go, go, go. Dude, I just killed like four or five people in one sticky.
All right. Now I need some help. That's obviously a spy.
I have to win this right now. No, no. I almost just took that health from that poor medic.
No, you are a spy. Come on. Get him. Get, get, get, get, get.
I probably could have done that a little better if I slowed it down a little bit.
I put myself on the spot though. I hope that was good enough for on the spot beatboxing.
Come on. I want to respawn. This guy is just a scout. He's just no, no, no way.
There's no way I'm going to end this right now. Come on. Just cap it and we can end the travesty that is.
Where am I getting backstabs from? That's what I don't understand.
There's just like three spies and they're all just like stuffing into me at the same time.
I'm like bumping it. Oh, skew. Excuse me. Oh, ma'am. Excuse me. And then I die.
God, I should just play pyro and just hold the mouse button down. Get, get out of here.
Oh, what did, what did, what just happened? What the hell is going on? What is happening here?
I just killed two spies. I thought, I thought I hit that sniper. That didn't make any sense.
Oh, this game, man, is just ridiculous sometimes. Let's go. We can't let them win.
I'm just going to sticky jump all the way across like the whole. What? What was that?
My heroics didn't work. We're going to lose. We're going to lose right now.
All I can do is watch. Come on. Come on, soldier. It's okay.
That's going to be it for this edition of Facecam Fortress 2.
Hope you guys are going to have a fantastic day and say hello to my two new dolphin friends.
This is Zeke and this is Gunther and they're friends.
Okay. And I don't know why, where that came from, but I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.