Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here. You haven't seen me in a while, but you know what? Fuck you.
We're going to do something today that I've been seeing on the internet for a while, and it's draw my thing.
No, it's my life. Draw my life. It's where you draw pictures. Just draw pictures of your life from when you were a baby,
and you tell a story about how you were born and stuff.
And I figured that you would want to know this because I'm the most important person in your life, so here we go.
Ahem. So the story of my life goes like this. I was born Hilfred J. Steelehelm, the strongest baby on Earth.
And that's because Superman, Batman, and Wonder Woman all had sex with each other, and I was the resulting baby.
Get mad. Get jealous, bro. It was a tough life being a super baby sidekick, going on adventures, saving lives, until it would depress.
But I loved it. We were all such a happy family until one day my parents died on a roller coaster ride.
And I died too. I forgot that part. And in heaven, God told me I had a bigger purpose.
He said, I'm going to give you mortality and send you back to Earth to solve the world's problems.
And I said, OK, send me back Roger that. And I arrived in a basket at the Denver School for Baby Ninja Frog People.
And I befriended the frogs. And they said, thank you. And I said, except for one frog named Timmy. He used to make fun of me.
I killed him. He's dead. He's been dead for 70 years. Holy shit, has it really been that long?
Let me look at my calendar here. It is. There's German's birth. There's my birthday.
Well, really, it's been like 82 years since I killed Timmy. Hope his parents aren't that mad at me. Whatever. Let's get back into this.
So I got a job selling old shoes or you can put whatever you want here, because I didn't have a job for the last like probably 40 years.
I got a job at the fishing dock. I was the guy that peeled all the fish's scales off. I used to eat them.
It might be weird to a lot of you guys, but do you think I give a fuck? And then came my adult life.
You've never seen quite an action packed adventure like this one. Gather your friends and explore the wonderful land of Azeroth.
I actually don't remember half of my adult life, so I just read the back of the Warcraft box.
So my death was on June 24th, 2002. I fell out of an airplane and Insta-died on the concrete.
Made my way back into heaven. And here's the funny story, guys. I was in Moses's science class. And guess who sits behind me but God himself.
I walked up to him after class at his locker and I just simply asked him, God, you know, could I have like five more years on Earth?
And I had to trade my fucking Lunchables for it. But I'm here. And it's, wait a second, 2002, three, four, five, six, seven.
I should have, I should be, I should have died in 2007. What the fuck is going on? Wait a minute. Is it 2007 right now?
Jeremy! Jeremy, come down here for a second.
What? What do you want?
What's a year today? Like, what, 2005?
It's 2013, grandpa.
2013!
Jesus.
I'm supposed to be dead!
Dead? What?
Oh, hold on a minute. Call your mother. Call your mother. We gotta, she will see some fucking warlock that set all this up.