Just making sure it works. Hello everybody. How you doing? Good afternoon. Hope all is well,
wherever you are. He speaks. Sometimes. Sometimes he speaks. Yeah, I saw the house flipper update.
Garden flipper, right? Is it blood on my coffee cup? No. No, it's dried coffee. I was like,
what are they? What? Drinking blood. No, but how you doing? Today we're gonna do something
we did last week. I thought it was a lot of fun. And I want to try it again. MS DOS,
the archive website. It's still up. It's still available. So we're gonna do some more of that.
It's gonna be different this time, though. Last time, we had a little thing on the right
where you could scroll. You cannot do that this time. We're gonna try it differently.
This time, we are going to pick three from the list. And then I'm just scrolling after
we do three. Or I might veto two of them and then just scroll. We'll see. All right,
I tweeted, right? I think we're good to go. Mario's gonna put this on a fort of a kind.
I don't know. I don't think we're gonna see Mario again. Does Mario have more than one
MS DOS game? And are we going to come across it? That's the real question.
Why not just play every game? I can't do that. There's too many of them. All right, so
welcome again. Happy, happy Saturday. And why don't we just get this off the screen and
look at that. Don't click yet. It's not ready yet. I believe this is where we left off.
I think it is because I was on page five. So like we did last time,
notice there's nothing on this side of the screen. Nope. Just a central location.
What's this page called again? This is the archive.org MS DOS archive.org.
There's software on here too, but I don't, I didn't put it on here. I'm only doing the games
because the software is command prompts and video. No, there was no video editing.
What programs existed that went on games where I missed off? Get ready to click.
Here's your first click of the evening. You can do it now. Software spreadsheets. Yeah,
it's about, it's not, it's boring stuff. So let's see. First pick of the day.
Looks like we have something called Alter Ego Mail. Is this a personality test? There's one
of two things. This is either personality test or porn game. We'll have to find out.
It's from Activision. Did Activision ever make any porn games? I don't think they may have.
Who knows? Okay. That's a pretty significant amount of people that want to see Alter Ego Mail.
All right. Let's go. Okay. Let's start it. Are you ready? Three, two, one. Here it comes.
Activision presents Alter Ego. Whoa, what's going on down there? You can like scan people.
Please enter your name. Okay. We're going to go with Jerma. No, should I put that? Should
I put something else? Should I put like, I don't want to put my name. What if somebody has
it? I wonder who that could be. Jared. Jared. Alter Ego personality development profile.
Use the arrow keys to move the pointer next to a response. Press space to select that response.
Let me select my own personality. Let the computer select my personality.
Let computer select my personality. Then let me examine or edit it.
I need to make my own personality, right? Yeah, I gotta, I can't, I'm not gonna let
somebody tell me who I am. I will probably try to answer these questions honestly.
Yeah, that's true. I'm likely to speak whatever comes to my mind. Yeah, I will. I do. I do that
all the time on stream. I just, shit just comes out. I'm a light sleeper who stirs
at even the slightest sound. This is absolutely true. I, I'm so bad. It doesn't matter.
A dog barking like 500 yards down that way will wake me up. Somebody's sneezing
in my neighbor's house. I'll wake up to it. Revenge is sweet. How do I get there? Oh,
I'm likely to speak whatever comes to my mind. I'll probably try to answer normally. I'm a light
sleeper. Revenge is sweet. How do I answer this? What kind, what do you mean revenge? Revenge
is sweet. What kind of revenge? I don't know. That's, that might not be true. I don't know
if I can answer that one. But like revenge, just general revenge. Do you like to get
revenge? No, it doesn't do anything. Have you seen every movie ever made? I often feel slow,
tired, and down in the dumps. This, uh, he's a liar. I'm, uh, all right, hold on. Is this,
this is a two parter here though. I often feel slow, tired, and down in the dumps. I often
feel like tired, but not down in the dumps. That's not completely true. An important part
of every job is knowing who to impress, Twitch chat. I am fascinated by car accidents and
their disaster scenes. I don't think, no, no. Why would this be a question? See, this is one of
those tests where it's trying to find the psycho. Oh, I feel sorry. Sometimes I'm tired. Oh,
impress people if you want. Yeah, car accidents are cool, right? Yeah, no, no, no, wait. The
people who know me best like me as a person. Yeah, I think so. I think people like, like
people that know me well like me. I'm extremely sensitive to criticism. Yeah, that was that
one time like, like four nights ago somebody said my stream sucked and I got really mad.
Uh, I get nervous performing in front of people even when the task is something I know by heart.
Nope. The people around me seem happier than I do. I don't, I don't know about that.
Uh, the people around me seem, I don't think so. No. I often get the urge to touch walls
on which wet paint signs are hung. No, because then you get paint on your hands
for the rest of the day and it sucks. I've done it. When I am ill, I become short tempered and
snap at people. Ill? No, I just like kind of sleep. I just, I just kind of do my own thing.
An important mattress, I usually follow my, no, no, one on important matters. I usually
follow my parents advice even when I disagree with it. No, I mean, my mother's got great
advice, but you know, I like to, I like to be me. You know, it is possible that I like, I take
advice and then I, I kind of let it sit for a while and then I say, what about my idea? And
then I kind of mold them together and then I get the best idea. It is possible that we live
in a world where people can watch our every move. Yes. That, that, that, yes, that's
true. Uh, it is very possible. I don't know when they made this game, but it is, is real.
When I'm in a quiet place, I get the urge to scream. Yeah. This is why I can't go to the movies.
I can't sit there, but no, no, no, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no, no, that's, that's kind of,
I send this, assuming that I just scream at the movies. No, no, that's not quiet.
And I meant like sit still. No, that's true. I need like stimulation or I lose my fucking
mind. It's okay to tell a white lie if it is guaranteed to bring great personal gain.
Done that quite, quite a bit on this stream. I'm kidding. It, no, it's true. Wait, this is,
we're talking, we're talking, I'm not a sociopath. Okay. I lied about Ace Attorney. So it happens.
I didn't, but I didn't though. That you just, you just perceiving that as a lie.
It is often pointless to try to discuss problems with other people. What? No. What?
No, somebody like to bounce a vent off of and bounce off. No, what are you talking about?
I'm easily embarrassed. No. Dermaraptor proves that. Children should be seen and not heard.
Are we talking about like, are we talking about like on the airplane? Like when the kids like
screaming and crying and like kicking the back of the seat. Is that what they're talking about
here? What are they talking about? What does it mean? Children should be seen and not heard.
No, but like kids are fun. Kids are like funny and interesting and they say all kinds, no.
I find it difficult to break the ice in conversations with people I barely know.
That's not true. My parents were strict disciplinarians. No. You can usually judge
a person by first impressions. No. People, no, I don't think so. One way of getting people
to treat you fairly is to take an aggressive stance and make them win you over. What?
What kind of weird, like take an aggressive stance and make them win you over. But what
does aggressive stance mean? Like you really get out there and you'd be, what does that
mean? Do you just say something crazy and then see if they like you? I mean, I usually,
I'm pretty boisterous. Maybe. Yeah. I think that questions like this are stupid and meaningless.
Like that. Yes. This one. Yes. I do think this question is meaningless because it's just,
it doesn't mean anything. Uh, dark soul. Thanks to the five community subs, dark soul,
a five sub drop from dark soul. That's the way this is the game. This is the game. We
haven't started the game yet. Please select the stage of life at which you would like
to begin the game. Birth and infancy. What? You could be a baby. Are we going to try to
live all through our whole life here? Birth and infancy. What if I, all right. Welcome
to birth and infancy. Every man is the architect of his own fortune. Solace, Gaia,
Solistius, Crispus. Speech to Caesar on the state. Sec I. Am I Julius Caesar?
Is that me? You are in a warm, dark, comfortable place. This has been your place since you became
aware that you are alive. It's almost time to enter a different world now. Select an action.
Stay in a little longer. Come out fighting. Come out peacefully. Stay in a little longer.
You start swinging at the doctor. I'm staying in a little longer. Okay. You certainly can't be
blamed for wanting to stay someplace safe and warm. Besides, you are learning early the social
merits of being fashionably late. Sure am. What time is it? 4 15 p.m.
Don't you think your mother has had enough aggravation carrying you in her belly for
nine long months? Stop being a freeloader and step out into the real world. All right, fine.
I'm gonna come out peacefully. I never come out fighting when I'm late. I'm always just like,
hey, what's going on, YouTubers? What a good sport. Are you sure you're ready for this?
It can get pretty hectic out there. I'll give you one more chance to try to stay a while
longer. Would you like it? What do you mean? Why are you like making me sign up a game tap
again? This is the game tap thing all over again. That's the spirit. You are an easy
delivery. No, no, no. I was trying to say no. I got fucking conned into coming out here.
That's the spirit. You are an easy delivery. Your mom and dad took special classes to help you.
Go out there and give them heck. You're still too young to swear.
Happy birthday and welcome to the world. From now on, life will begin to change rapidly.
You will have to learn to accept responsibility, build up your resources, and manage
yourself physically and emotionally. The events that transpire over the course of the next
few days include your rich aunt Martha places a $500 bond and trust for you. Thanks. You're the
most beautiful baby in the maternity ward and everyone takes your picture. All right. Starting
out pretty good here. Your father buys you a baseball bat and glove for you to use in a year
or so when you get older. A baseball bat and a glove when I'm one and a half years old. How's
that gonna work? I'm gonna be one with a... you can't even fucking think. What is this?
Do I have to select something? Oh shit. What is this? I don't know. Should I do like the emote
face or hearts? Which one of these do I do? I don't know what these mean. All right. I'm going
for like the I'm so intelligent. Lying on your stomach in the crib, you notice an interesting
object and arms distance away. It has a round shape at the top and a ring on the bottom.
Select a mood. Anger, frustration, determination. Determination and grasp for object.
You have the fighting spirit of your uncle Bill. You sneak and crawl on your belly like a combat
soldier heading into battle. You reach your destination, grasp the rattle confidently,
and drool on it in victory. Intellectual sphere shows a marked increase. Shake the rattle.
Keep drooling on it. Emit a pleasurable yell. I would do that. I'd be like,
this stimulates vocal cords and language centers in your brain. Good language skills
are essential to development. Intellectual sphere increases. If no one is looking,
give a little yell yourself for choosing this option. Go on. Did you do it? I actually did.
Select an action. Yes or no. What? Yes or no to what? Yes. Oh no, I did. Yeah, I did it.
Yes, I did. Good. I just gave you some extra social points for being good sport. I'm already
getting some good points here. Um, now where? What is it? What is this? A woman walks into
a room holding a blanket and a bottle with warm white liquid. Selective mood. Happy. Action. Coup.
Happy and coup. Why would I be angry? I just got extreme victory. I would coup.
Nothing like a nice warm bottle and a quick hug from mom to get a kid ready to face the world.
As she walks toward you with the bottle, she sees you smiling and interprets this as a
sign that you want to play with her. She picks you up and holds you for 10 minutes.
This presents you with quite a dilemma. Cry. Okay, mom can see that you have had enough
for now. She feeds you your bottle and walks away. You don't have very many skills yet.
As a matter of fact, life is pretty boring. Restless and irritable. Uh, restless and
irritable. I want to look around. Feel like you're going stir crazy. I can just imagine.
The room is filled with bright colors, but you have trouble focusing on any of them.
Cry and yell for attention. Keep looking around. Keep looking around. You look around
and see a large blur about 11 inches away from your eye. Every once in a while, it moves.
Hey, wait a minute. Just as you had that thought, it moved again. Keep looking.
Congratulations. You found your hand. This may not seem like much of a big discovery,
but it is. You will have to learn how to control your hands as part of childhood
development. When you are an adolescent, those hands are going to get you into quite
a bit of trouble because that requires a different kind of hand control. This is stupid.
You're lying down in your crib and are greeted by a nosy neighbor who has a child just around
your age. The neighbor says, my, look at that funny little nose. She turns to your
mother and adds, don't worry, dear. I hear that noses are the last thing to look truly
human. She picks you up. Uh, angry and vengeful. Collect a mouthful of drool.
A nice puddle of saliva has formed on the inside of your mouth. Open your mouth and
drool on the neighbor. Yeah. Talk about my fucking nose. I'm going to ruin your shirt.
A gooey stream showers your neighbor's face and hands while you give her a glassy-eyed smile.
She places you back in the crib and excuses herself. Revenge. Revenge. Revenge. That's
not revenge. It is. Maybe it is. It's all right. But it didn't feel sweet. It was just fun.
There should have been, revenge is not sweet, but could be fun if you're a baby sometimes.
You're lying on the floor of a big room on a soft furry blanket. You are on your back,
staring at shadows that sometimes creep across the ceiling. Every so often mom or dad passes
by and makes a funny face. Your hands grope in all directions and your feet pat the floor
gently, almost out of your control. Happy, sad, mad. Happy and make an O-shape with your mouth.
You pucker your cheeks in and out and take short, quick breaths. The skin on your face
feels alternately tight and loose. A person walks by and twirls their fingers at you.
Turn around towards the person. You are too young to keep the person in view for a long
time. Whoever it is that moves past in a blur. All right, here we go. We're going to develop
some brain here. You are lying down in the crib while your mom and dad are speaking in the other
room. You hear their voices, deep and muffled, from beyond the door. Why aren't they paying
attention to you? Make noise! Get over here! You begin to cry. This alarms your parents
and is a negative way of attracting attention. Your dad comes in holding a bottle of warm
milk which satisfies you temporarily. Uh-oh. Wrong. Wrong choice. You've just awakened from a nice
long nap. Your mom comes in the room and wants to hold you. I'm a little cranky. I'm a little
cranky, but I'm still happy. You have made an inappropriate response. What about a sleepy smile?
I can do that, right? It's a dog's life, isn't it? Nothing to do all day except eat,
sleep, and wonder what life will be like when you're older. Does life really change after two?
A dog's life? Am I a dog? Mom is coming closer. Sure. Very good. Eye contact with your caretakers
is very reinforcing to them. Parents often mistakenly think that it is the children
who need all the attention. Believe me, parents want it too. Your eye contact with
her makes her smile. Social and emotional spheres are increasing. Smile back. Smiling
makes your mom feel especially loving towards you. She brings your face close to her face.
Your face is touch. Be still or move my mouth. I'm gonna move my mouth. You just gave your first
kiss. This may not seem like a very big deal to you, but is very important for your mother.
The bad part is that now you will have to repeat this act until your entire family
becomes aware of your new talent. You can avoid kissing overly affectionate relatives
by dribbling on them at just the right moment. What are these? What is this? It's time to go to
Aunt Lucy's house. It's chilly outside and you need to be dressed in a coverall type suit.
Go limp! All right, I'm gonna... I don't want to go. I'm gonna go limp. Resist. You react
against being squeezed into this uncomfortable suit by crying and sending out long sirens
of protest. Your grandmother graciously offers to help. Cooperate for grandma. Keep giving
everyone a hard time. Not a very wise choice. How do you expect to motivate grandma to spoil
you if you are not willing to make your mom look foolish in front of her by persisting
to act like a little brat? Would you like to give in now or make everyone even angrier with
you? Your mother pulls you away from your grandmother and literally stuffs you into the
suit. It is tucked in and bunched up in all the wrong places and you are uncomfortable.
Your grandmother protests but to no avail. Your mom has the last word and your physical
sphere suffers temporarily short-term discomfort. I didn't want to go. I didn't want to be put
in the suit. You're quietly playing with your father's brand new electronic calculator. Look
the back of it lifts off very easily. Inquisitive. Look but don't touch. Look,
touch and take apart. Your little fingers make efficient pliers. You pluck out the electronic
components tasting one or two as you go along. They're definitely not for eating. You know dad
will be pleased at your fixing his toy. Uh I don't think dad's gonna be happy that his infant
son is eating small parts of a calculator. Oh that's my son the little Einstein. You
are exploring the playpen and are feeling very lively. Like a prize fighter you grab hold
of the playpen bars and shake back and forth flexing your knees. Daring. Determined. Daring.
Let go of the playpen. You raise your hands over your head triumphantly. Boom! You go right down
on your bottom. Thank heavens for padded bottoms. You wobble back up standing.
You wobble back up to standing position. All right. Navigate around the crib holding onto
the bars. All right we're gonna do this correct. With ballet-like movements you step over
the musical ball and four stuffed animals. You've perfected this form of locomotion.
Would you like to let go again? Yes. Boom! Ouch! You crash to the floor like a sack of
potatoes. Your rear end is beginning to feel sore. You want to try one more time? Yes.
The thrill of victory. You stumble across the crib like a punch-drunk sailor and firmly grasp
the rail on the other side. You've taken your first steps. Soon you'll be tripping
the light fantastic. Chasing women and running away from spankings. What? All right let's...
Mom and dad are entertaining some friends and you are minding your own business sitting quietly
in a corner of the room. Suddenly a man with a big nose and a shiny head puts his face right
up to yours. It said something in a loud voice. Scream in a loud voice. Hit the man
in the nose. You give him a right to the snoz which feels rough and oily. You are terrified
and he thinks you are playing with him. Fortunately your dad spots him and ushers him back to the
to bother people closer to his own age. I had to knock that guy up. I fucking dropped him in one
punch. Was it a clown? You're sitting in your high chair eating your lunch which consists of
crackers, strained peas, and a mug of milk. You're just learning how to eat with utensils.
Escape from the high chair. You will probably do much traveling when you get older. This isn't
bad provided that you are not traveling to avoid responsibility. You slip out of the chair
but hit the floor much harder than you expected. I'm getting out of here. Nothing, not even a
sore bottom, can stop you now. You're headed for daylight. You go for the blocks with the
speed of a charging buffalo. You encounter a large leg. Bite the leg. Dodge. You fake left
and move right. What am I, a fucking running back? Your mom is caught temporarily off guard
and once again you are unobstructed. Your confidence increases even though you are eventually
caught and dragged back to the high chair. That's too bad. I'm gonna use the spoon.
Using hatchet-like strokes you pulverize the cracker until it is unrecognizable.
Yell and pound on the high chair. Quietly sprinkle the crumbs all over the floor. That's
that one. I would do that one. All the characteristics related to extreme sneakiness
and hostility have increased. Your actions will not be detected until the next time someone
sweeps the floor. How do you feel about this? Good. You are even more sneaky and mean than I
thought. What kind of adult will you turn out to be if you keep this up? I'm not gonna,
it's not chaotic evil, it's lowkey. While being taken to the park your dad meets an
old colleague buddy who's wheeling a baby about your age. As the two dads talk you
casually begin to eye the baby in the other carriage. Curious and different. I wouldn't,
I don't think I would be aggressive. Very curious. Put your finger near the other baby's face.
Yeah, I'm just curious. I just want to see what their face feels like. A baby,
you wonder if it has all the same parts as you. I'm just like, I'm just, I don't even
know where my hands are going. Just baby face. You poke the other baby right in the eye.
He starts to cry. Your father is slightly embarrassed. The other dad is worried that
his little baby is not macho enough to take a little poke. Select an action. Pat the other
baby to con- why would I know that? I wouldn't know that's what you would do. Leave the baby
alone. All right, it's okay. I'm sorry. I apologize. It doesn't work. Geez. This kid is
a crybaby. You are learning that sometimes no matter how nice you are to some people, they
just don't appreciate it. Your dad moves you away from the other baby and gives you a
cookie to keep you occupied. At least he appreciates your empathy. So I poked this
baby in the eye, caused it physical pain, could not believe that I didn't like my
pat to the head I gave it afterwards, and I got a cookie. Okay, my first x-ray. Up until
this point in life, Weasley Wabbit, your stuffed toy has been one of your best friends.
You take him everywhere with you, but he is beginning to get on your on your nerves, I
thought it said. I don't know, I'm going down this like evil baby path. I didn't think it was
gonna be like you rip off his head. You take him everywhere with you, but he's beginning to get
on in years. One of his ears is torn off and a recent eye injury has made his face like
a little lopsided. It is suggested that Weasley should be retired. You wake up one day to
discover Weasley has been moved from the place where you last spotted him. Panic, suspicious,
and seek information. You confront mom with the fact that Weasley was not in the spot where he
was last deposited. She claims to not have seen him either. You are satisfied with this
answer, not satisfied with this answer. Where is Weasley Wabbit? Wisely, you persist. This
time she tells you that Weasley left because he wanted to be with friends who were more like him.
She tells you that next week you'll have a new visitor, a brand new friend who will be just as
nice as Weasley. You are not satisfied with that fucking answer. Bravo, don't fall for that
line of bull. Parents are great at fabricating stories like this when they make mistakes.
You will not get your Weasley Wabbit back, but your intelligence and perseverance in this
situation make it harder for your parents to tell you made-up stories to cover their mistakes.
How tall am I now? You're alone in the kitchen and begin exploring the closets
and refrigerator. Am I gonna like pull the refrigerator down? This could be bad. All right,
curious but cautious. Move toward the pantry. All right, adventuring, move toward pantry.
You swing the pantry door open and see all the beautifully colored jars, boxes, and bottles.
One jar looks particularly pretty. It is shiny and brown and full of liquid.
You unscrew the cap and smell what is inside. It smells sweet. No, I don't think I'm gonna drink
this. You've just avoided a potentially lethal accident. Your good judgment has saved your
life. You throw up at the pantry door. Jesus Christ. You're touching something smooth and
shiny. You pat it with your hand a few times. What? It's like the mood. I'm confused. What is it?
I'm confused, but I'm gonna keep touching it. It's not hot, right? It's not like a stove.
It is flat and a little cool. Wait a minute. There's a baby in there. Who is that baby?
What? Oh, it's a mirror. It's me. No, that's someone else.
I don't know. I'm trying to make them like a weirdo. No, that's you. You are looking at
yourself in a mirror. Isn't that a beautiful baby? Yes. You really are quite stunning.
You are developing a positive self-image. All right, cool. It is announced to you
during a heart-to-heart talk that it's time for you to give up the bottle and
drink from a glass like a big boy. No. How are you going to show your resistance?
Cry. Fold your arms and say no. Throw the bottle at mommy. No. A nice strong effort to
fight for what you believe in. Since you are strong enough to put up such a fuss,
you're also old enough to get off the bottle. We're gonna have to...
Yeah, I got baited there. We're gonna have to learn to live without it.
I'm not gonna suck my thumb. No. Learn to live without it. You'll be tough for a while.
You'll turn to Super Duck for comfort. Believe me, cold turkey is the best way to do it.
Good luck. Super Duck a cartoon or something? You're a guest at your friend Billy's house.
His mom gives you both a box of crayons and two pieces of paper. Artistic. Draw on the paper.
Draw in general. You draw large circles and swirls with black crayon on the paper. Oops,
you drew on the expensive tablecloth. Tell Billy about the spot. Cover up the spot. Tell
Billy's mom about the spot. No. You casually slide the paper over the offending spot where
it will remain covered and undetected until after you leave. This was the sneaky cowardly
way out. Cowardly and sneaky. I didn't do it. There was one time where I slept over a
friend's house and I slept on the couch and I was like, I don't know, maybe like 14 or
something, 13. I was old and I was like old. So in the middle of the night, I was like,
I was touching my face and touching my nose and touching the blanket that I had.
And the next morning after doing that a few times, I got up and realized that I had blood,
I had like a bloody nose. And then when I didn't even know. And it was like on the
blanket and I had like a fucking panic attack. I was like, Oh my God, they're
going to hate me. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? At first I like folded it up
a shit load of times and like put it in the corner and I was like, no, I can't do that.
I have to like, I know they're going to find it. They're going to know it's me.
Eventually, like I just told, I told my friend, I was like, Hey, did you do it?
I first tried it, but I put it on him. Did you have like a bloody nose when we were
sitting on like the couch? No, man. No. Oh, well, um, I, maybe I, it's on there.
It's not, wait, it is. Oh yeah. Yeah, there is. Okay. Was it you? I don't know. It may be one of
us. I'd have been me or you. It may have been you. May have been me or you. The coward way out.
Coward. I did say it was like, who knows? It could have been me. Like I was taking
blame for it. It was like, it was either like you or it was me. It was me or you.
It could have been either one of us. It was probably me. It was you. It could have been
either way. I did it in his mind. He knew, he knew he didn't have a bloody nose. So it
had to be me. So I gave him the opportunity to think maybe it was him, but it was me. So he
get, he knew it was me. I'm not the coward way. 34 by the way. I was, this didn't happen last
week. This happened like 20 fucking years ago. 34. Yeah. 34 by the way. This happened
last Saturday. All right. You are sitting in a large place and a furry man walks up to you.
He's walking around you in circles. A furry man.
I'm going to grab the furry man by the head.
Oh, no. God.
What?
What? This is toddler. No.
Inquisitive. Ask some questions. Which question would you like to ask?
Do you have a husband? Do you have a doggie? Mommy said that daddy has a thick skull. Do you?
I tried very hard to pinch a penny like Aunt Edna, but couldn't. Can you? Mommy said that
daddy has a thick skull. The lady giggles and mom puts her hand over your mouth and says,
whack. What? Wait, did you actually get? What? Okay. This is mom. Jesus Christ. Mom is cheating.
Dad, where's dad? Perhaps you are interested in asking something else. Which question would
you like to ask? Do you have a doggie? She tells you no, no doggie, only a cat. You
inform her that daddy said that that's what they cook in the restaurant on the corner.
What? Where? What's why my parents so fucked? Perhaps you are interested in asking something
else. Do you have a husband? She tells you that she doesn't have a husband. You are
alone in your parents' bedroom. There is a shiny silver quarter on the table.
Honest, dishonest, take the quarter. I'm gonna honestly take the quarter. You have made
an inappropriate response. What? What do you mean? It's not dishonest if I say I'm taking
this quarter out loud. It is really questionable as to whether a child your age can tell
whether something like this is truly right or wrong. You have a vague sense that you
shouldn't have picked it up. Your mother sees you stash something in your pocket.
She asks you what you have there. You say nothing or this and hold out the quarter.
This. You're not so dishonest. In fact, you are being very trustworthy. It was a
temptation you couldn't resist. You get a big hug for being honest after all. I told you
I honestly wanted to take it. Hey, we got some weaves and growth here. Daddy says it's
time to go to bed. Hmm. What time is it though? That's important. Is it seven o'clock,
eight o'clock? If it was like six o'clock, I'd say no. I probably would be tired. Tired,
but I don't want to go to bed. Dad tries to bribe you by offering a bedtime story.
Oh, fucking hell, yeah. You're so tired that the murmur of words puts you right to sleep.
You don't even remember what the story was about. That's a pretty good deal. Yeah.
I made out on that one. It's Saturday morning and Dad asks you to help with some chores.
The Super Duck cartoon hour has just begun. I can't miss Super Duck. It's the best show on TV.
You're too busy fighting the glue monster with Super Duck. You're oblivious to all
sights and sounds other than the ones coming from the TV set. Dad tries to encourage you
away from the TV. Does it work? Of course it doesn't. You're becoming a TV addict at a very
young age. Before you know it, you will be staying up late watching old odd couple reruns.
So that's why that happened. I actually, I watch that show. I've seen every episode.
You're in a sandbox playing with your favorite toy. A larger, stronger child pulls it away from
you and screams, mine! What the fuck did you just do? Give it back. The child seems much
stronger than you. He puts three fingers in your mouth and tries to push you away.
He is holding the metal toy above your head. Bite him. The metal toy comes down right on your
head. No! Whoa! Crash again. Crash again. You are beginning to feel dizzy. You cry out, crash,
crash. He finally starts with your head and face uncovered in blood. His mother takes
him away before either one of your parents can tell what happened. He was a problem child
with very aggressive tendencies. He's done this to other children too. You were treated unfairly.
He was smashing the... Did I get the toy back? You know, if I'm in the car right back with the
toy in my hands. Like slow zoom into my face with some fucking rock music playing. A little
smirk. Yeah. Time to feed the fish. You punch a small amount of fish food in between your
fingers and tap on the glass. There is no sign of Gabriella. Who the fuck is Gabriella?
The fish? Unaffected. Do nothing. That's cold. Look for Gabriella. You put your hand in the
fish bowl and look for Gabriella. She is stuck under a rock. She is stiff and her eyes are
puffed out. You think that she might be sick. Oh god. Fucking god. I would... I'm not going
to take... No, I'm calling for mom on this scenario here. Gabby floats up to the surface
from under a big gray rock. Her eye seems very puffy and her body is stiff. You are
relieved to see she hasn't jumped out of the bowl. Ask mom about Gabby. Mom stutters
through the answers to your questions. She's uncomfortable and sad. Mom explains that
Gabby can't swim anymore. She's dead. She's gone away. How can that be? She's right there.
What is dead? You wonder. You are confused. Mom says that Gabby has to be taken out of
the bowl. Why would you... What would you... Okay. If this is a child, why would you in front of
this kid flush this down the toilet? No. You do that like you keep her in a box and
you give her a little thing like, oh, say goodbye. You don't just like flush.
Keep her in a box. You really can't do that. Gabby will start to smell up the drawer. You
still don't understand what this is all about, but tomorrow you will start to miss the ritual
of feeding her. Oh. Keep her in a box in my drawer. I don't know. I'm trying to be nice.
No. The fish, you can flush that fish. Whatever. But to the child, you say some
things. You say, oh, we're going to like, we're going to have them go off and I'll take
them on their next journey. You don't just do that. You are in the back seat of the car
during a very long ride. Tired. I'm just, I'm just like tired. I don't, I hate long car rides.
Let's just play a game so I can wake up here. You are too tired to play games. Are you feeling
less sleepy all of a sudden? Yes. Your mom has taken along some picture books and coloring
books for you to play with. What would you like to do? Let's just, let's just color.
Coloring is a solitary activity. You take the book and color in a picture of super duck.
You've missed an opportunity to have a positive social interaction with your mom.
Oh, fuck. I really am just like walking myself in here to like media.
Super duck is becoming more important than mom. Uh-oh. Danger ahead. You are eating
at the house of one of your parents' friends. You were told by your mother to be on your
best behavior. Something that you ate has disagreed with you and now you feel very sick.
Queasy. Ignore it. Throw up and get it over with. Call mom. Try to find the bathroom yourself.
Throw up and get it. I think we just get it over with here. Throw up into the blankets
and fold them up. Find a bed first. Throw up and get it over with. Try to find the,
all right, I'll try to find the bathroom. It is a large unfamiliar house. You find a
room, but it's not a bathroom. If you get sick here, no one will know.
Getting sick like that is difficult to hide. You are discovered and everyone feels sorry for you.
The person who has to clean it up feels less sorry for you than everyone else.
What? That's like kind of mean. You're still not completely familiar with using the toilet
that is still quite fascinating to you. You have just finished and you have cleaned yourself
like a big boy. Watch, watch the toilet paper disappear into the toilet. Make a boat out of
the toilet. Make a boat out of mom's brush and float it in the bowl. Ah, that sounds like fun.
Oops, it doesn't float. You can flush the bowl. Get it out with your hands. Flush it quick.
Woosh! It spins around three times and tries to go down the pipe. It goes halfway down.
The water slowly rises and spills out of the toilet. Mom rushes in. You stand there
looking at your mother with your index finger hooked into your bottom lip.
The cutesy routine doesn't work. You are sent directly to your room.
Today is dad's birthday and you would like to make him breakfast.
Extravagant. Let's make an extravagant eggs spread. What kind of eggs do you want to try?
Scrambled? Fried? Fried eggs. You must think that young children can do a lot.
The best you can do is throw them in a pot raw and give them to dad,
which is exactly what you do. He is in bed sleeping. Feed him raw eggs with a spoon.
Boy, is he surprised. He probably thinks this is going to be the best birthday ever.
Mom is laughing very hard. Dad's egg is dripping on the bed. The phone rings while daddy is
ironing a shirt. He must leave you alone in the room with the iron. Helpful. Help dad iron
the shirt. Don't die here. Don't die. I'm not going to die here. Cautious. Play quietly.
Dad realizes that you are alone with the hot iron and calls you into him.
You run into the room and trip over the iron cord. The iron cord falls on the floor and
burns a hole in the carpet. It is not your fault. Okay, I thought we were getting baited
there. I thought it was gonna like hit me in the head or something. All right, we're good.
Dad must get his teeth fixed and you must go with him to the dentist.
Mom is busy at work and dad couldn't find a sitter. You sit in the waiting room for a very
very very long time. Dad must run out and put money in the parking meter. Dad sits you
on the floor, gives you a magazine to leaf through, and tells you to behave.
Remove your shoes. I don't know why that's funny.
Now you're feeling a bit more comfortable. A nosy lady spies you from the corner of her eye.
What's she looking at? Your sock is crooked.
A mischievous good boy. Ignore the sock and tear pages from the magazine.
Remove the sock. Funny thing about socks, the way they stretch all the way out before
they snap off your feet. You decide to take both of them off. The lady looks at you again.
Where's dad? Climb up on the chair and look out the window. Dad is on his way back in.
He sees you with no socks and shoes on and feels embarrassed. The busy body lady gives
him a full report. Walk over and stick your tongue out at her. You give her your worst face
and get whacked on the bottom lightly by your dad who secretly approves of what you did.
He buys you a big ice cream when you leave to make up for feeling guilty about patting you
on the rear. Think about babies and how we just socially accept babies because of the weird
crazy shit they do. Imagine you went into the dentist office and you're in the waiting room
and there's like just people there reading magazines. People are getting called in and
you just take off your shoes and your socks and just like sit around and like start crawling on
the chair. That's a Chad move. Why? You have just passed through infancy. I've been an infant
that whole time. A brief look at your life up to this time shows the following. Your family
life has been positive and nurturing and as a result you have begun to form the critical bonds
that are important during this phase of life. Physically you have been not a very healthy baby.
Socially oh this is a long list. Socially during this phase in life nothing much is really
expected of you. After all you're still much too young to throw a successful cocktail party
and frankly anyone who still dribbles on himself probably wouldn't make the ideal dinner
guest. However by now there are some things you should have mastered. Your progress in this area
shows you've been the type of child who charms the lollipops off people. You've been the type
of child who is huggable and gets his cheeks pinched by old ladies with bright red lipstick.
Now regarding your emotional and personality development. I'm doing pretty well. You're not
exactly the type of child who could be trusted to wash his hands before coming to the dinner
table. If there is a piece of cake sitting in the refrigerator at noon chances are it will be
in your tummy by dinner. What's wrong with that? I'm fine. Your thoughtfulness your thoughtfulness
characteristic really doesn't count for much in this one module. Most children often find
themselves at the mercy of their whims and impulses. You're allowed to be cranky now.
People will tolerate it much better than when you are a teenager. Then your whining and carrying
on will seem more objectionable. One thing about your character that has a tendency to put people
off is your aggressiveness. You are the type of baby who likes to pull on loose pieces of clothing,
hair, and any bulbous fleshy object that comes within your reach. You are going to have to
learn the meaning of make nice. That wraps up your status for the first module. I hope you
like yourself. If not you can always try to improve yourself in the modules to come. There's
I'm now a kid. Are we gonna try to make it all the way through this? We're gonna try to actually
get all the way through. Welcome to childhood. I wonder how many more opportunities there are to
like die. Well let's at least get through childhood. I need a redemption arc. Practice
yourself for heaven's sake in little things and thence proceed to greater. I'm now a child.
Mom has just taken a job that requires her to be away in the morning and early afternoon.
She decides to enroll you in a nursery school program. Upon your arrival you are greeted by
another lady with very skinny legs and large round glasses. There are children playing with
buckets of sand, building blocks, and other activities. There's a small boy sitting in a
corner with tears streaming from his eyes, a runny nose, and cheeks red from crying.
Excited. Walk over and try to make friends. Give the lady with the skinny legs a left hook.
But why punch? No I need to stop my like psycho tendency. Walk over and try to make friends.
Your excitement is a positive sign that you are trying to adapt to this new environment.
To realize that your mom will be coming back so you attempt to make friends.
You see a little boy your age playing in the sand with trucks. What would you like to say to
him? Hi. Can I play? The little boy interrupts this as a threat. He interprets this as a
threat to his territory. He holds the truck close to his body. You can ignore him. Ask
him to play. Let's play! The boy shakes his head back and forth. He wants no part of you.
What the fuck? I can't even play with some friends? Should have left hooked.
Your mom is in the bathtub taking a nice relaxing bath. You are playing quietly in
your room. All of a sudden the doorbell rings. Mom doesn't seem to hear it.
Hmm nonchalant. Open the door nonchalantly. Don't open the door. All grown up,
tell mom. You can't be that grown up if you have to rely on mom to answer the doorbell all
the time. This set of choices doesn't make too much sense. Why? I can't. So you want to be
just to go oh go open the door to a stranger when my mom's in the bathtub? You have been
invited to sleep over at your best friend's house. This is your first sleep away experience.
Reluctance, excitement, mixed feelings. Lie to your friend and tell him you are not allowed.
Ask your parents that they will still be there when you get back. What? Go to your friend's
house as soon as possible. Mixed feelings. Mixed feelings but let's go. One way of resolving
a mixed feeling is to plunge headlong into a risky situation. Although risk taking is
sometimes a sign of emotional maturity, it can be dangerous if you do not take the time
to consider the possible consequences. While you are over at your friend's house,
you become frightened and demand to be taken home at two in the morning. Oh my god. I'm starting
to get a little soft here. While you are playing quietly in your room, you are strand- you're
strand-led, startled by loud muffled sounds coming from someplace else. It seems that your
parents are having a terrible fight over something. Your father's deep voice seems to be shaking
the whole house. Your mother's piercing screams sound like she's being hurt terribly. What?
The yelling gets louder and louder then suddenly everything is quiet. When you see your parents,
later they act as if nothing has happened. Mom's hair is ruffled and she seems to be very
tired. You can't seem to figure out what has happened or can you? Oh they were having sex.
Right. I don't know. It was like I looked over here and we're getting like a lot of
s's. It was like fucking screaming and fear. I don't know. Soon after you sit down for dinner,
your mother announces that the vegetable of the day is Brussels sprouts. Disgust. Eat the
Brussels sprouts without protest. Run screaming from the table. Put your finger in your mouth
and make a gagging sound. Feed the sprouts to your dog. Gudu. Gudu? Gudow? Gudow? Gudow.
Can dogs eat Brussels sprouts? Somebody look it up. Look up like can I feed? Can dogs eat
Brussels sprouts? It's important. I would look that up first. That's like not. Is that okay
for dogs? I'm a dog. I can confirm. Okay. All right. They can but not huge amounts. Okay.
So they'll be like it was only like two on there. That's not very fair is it? You resented
having to eat the sprouts yet you forced them on poor old Gudu. Poor Gudu thinks you are
doing him a favor. He will also think he's doing you a favor when he sleeps in your room later
tonight. Releasing the gaseous byproducts of his meal for your... of... An exciting movie is on
television. The whole family is in the living room watching it. You get up to get a drink
of water and return to find all the good seeds have been taken. Defeated. Sit down quietly in
a corner. Tell mom the doorbell is ringing. Tell dad the doorbell is ringing. You know
I'm to be devious here because I had uncles of mine. I'd go over family functions and I'd be
sitting in a nice comfortable chair and they would come over with a cordless phone in their
hand and they would have the button pressed. I was like probably 28 and they would have the
button pressed to show that the power was on on the phone and they would say hey it's it's
grandma. Can you talk to grandma? Like passing the phone around for grandma. Just like get up
just like go in the other room and like talk in there and people would fall for it all the time
and it was like it was the the red power indicator was on the phone like it had to be real
and by the way I wasn't 28 19 or something I don't know. She falls for it. She rustles to
the door and then you jump on her seat. When she realizes what you have done she goes over
and sits on top of dad. Everyone seems a bit happier now. Look at that. Look at what I've
done. You arrive at the dentist and discover that you have four rather large cavities that
need to be filled. Block out the sensations with your mind. I'm gonna be brave and I'm gonna block
it out. Your status sheet suggests that emotionally you are not capable of performing such a feat.
The pain sneaks into your consciousness but is not unbearable. This experience will toughen
you for next time. I still did it. I powered through it. I failed the stat check but it's
alright. Still got it. Why would I how could I die there? What's the death scenario there?
Your dad has promised that he will fix your bicycle. He's taking a nap so he's not doing
anything. Now seems like a good time to remind him. Patient and sweet. Tap dad on the shoulder.
Make the TV loud so he wakes up. I would say put the TV loud and then run out of the room.
You know slowly put that volume up to a point where it's not ridiculous but it will
definitely wake them up and then put the changer down and leave the room and then
you'll wait for them to get up and wait like I don't know maybe two to three minutes
after you hear them wake up and then like have a jacket on right have like a little jacket on
and walk in the room unzipping the jacket oh hey it worked now that you've got his attention
look at how wide his eyes are open you can say something to him leave him alone yeah let's
just hey you said you're gonna fix my bike um dad would you fix my bike dad would you fix
my bike now no no no dad would you fix my bike not now then we're not gonna command it
even though you seem helpless dad just rolls over and falls back asleep he mumbles
later everyone thinks i'm the bad guy one of your playmates is the daughter of your mother's
friend her name is cindy one day while you and cindy are alone you become very curious
about one another cindy suggests that you play a make-believe game of doctor let's play
trucks instead this game can only lead one place and you're not ready for it yet cindy
replies okay you are the truck driver and you get into a bad accident they have to take you
to the doctor right away holy fuck wow that's next level bait we just got baited like wow
i don't want to go to the doctor i'd rather die here i think i have to go see my mother
for a second i don't want to go to the doctor i'd rather die cindy says you're a big baby
i don't want to play with you anymore she walks away in a huff i have to go talk to mom
while rummaging around in the kitchen drawer you come across a book of matches
put the book of matches away light one in the kitchen or take the matches to your room
and close the door put the book of matcury no no no i'm not taking them what if i tell
this is bad you are mesmerized oh you are mesmerized by the spark and flash of the
match as you strike it you let the flame burn down the shaft of the match then blow it out
and light another no i didn't say another one the kitchen air soon becomes smoky with a
pungent sulfur odor the smoke alarm rings and sends your mother scurrying to check
what's happening you are grounded for a week take them back to your room is definitely a
death scenario you are in school and the teacher is giving a boring lecture the boy sitting two
seats away is rolling up a piece of paper and putting it in his mouth using the barrel of
his pen he spits the paper at the blackboard where it lands with a wet the teacher is furious
she screams who did this everyone in the class is howling until she promises that if the person
who did this will not come forward the whole class will get a punishment you are probably
the only person who saw the true culprit the teacher acknowledges you you can um may it please
be excused say pointing he was the one who did it a hush falls over the class some of
the other children's sigh and relief some snicker your anxiety makes you look a little
nerdish but everyone is thankful i'm taking charge okay i'm taking charge of that scenario
at school all of your friends are talking about a television program that you could not
stay up to watch a friend asks if you saw it unashamed say i didn't watch that show say i
wasn't allowed to see it say yeah i watched it it was really great yeah that's what i would do
i used to do shit like that all the time you're a confident liar your status sheet suggests
this is becoming a strong part of your personality for now your dishonesty remains
undetected actually becoming the real me late late lie and lazy the triple l and a snitch
you've just been ordered to bed by your parents in the middle of a favorite television show
angry complain about having to go to bed beg for 10 more minutes
yeah i would say 10 more minutes the show is almost over and if they said no
then i would just take a small tv into my bedroom plug it in and put it under the covers and watch
the show and the second that i heard the of my parents coming towards the door i would fucking
turn the tv off and pretend i was asleep and they would open the door and check
begging makes your parents feel guilty they let you stay up 10 more minutes after 10 minutes
they forgot you are supposed to go to bed and let you stay up for another hour before anyone
fuck yeah pretty sick that's best scenario there your best friend challenges you to a
rock throwing competition uh are you you're like a little wuss are you snitch let's go
i accept the challenge after several minutes of rock throwing for distance
your friend keeps beating you your friend dares you to throw a rock onto the roof of
the apartment building across the street you do it first he has no problem now it is your
turn fuck god damn it god damn it you lean back and watch the rock soar
you guessed it you can run contact the building and offer to pay
run you escape without being caught with what money it's time to sell raffle tickets for
the school baseball team again motivated or embarrassed try to do it alone enlist your
father's help now nobody i don't want to do this nobody wants to do this just have dad can
you just do it for me dad coaches you from the car as you go from door to door with little
success after an hour he asks if you would like to see how it's done um yeah let's see
it dad dad shows you the old foot in the door technique at mrs marcus's house this technique
attracts the attention of both mrs marcus and her 85 pound doberman pincher bruiser who cleanly
removes the front of dad's sneaker what the foot in the door tech would just open somebody's door
say that was pretty good but you can only do it twice say maybe it's time to wrap it up for
today but even you can only do it twice maybe it's time to wrap it up for today oh because
you only have two shoes oh i'm being a smart ass here yeah i like that one now is not
the best time to get wise but he did ask for it there's one more ice pop in the freezer that
is being saved for another family member your mouth waters at the thought of this cool tasty
treat it's not mine leave it alone that must have been very difficult for you considering
your history of untrustworthy behavior your appreciation for others increases your score in
trustworthiness social and intellectual areas all right we got a get a scenario here
while you are outside playing alone a car pulls over to the side of the road
and the driver motions for you to come over you notice the license plate says oboe 237 stay
where you are suspicious he motions for you to come closer he has a kind enough face you hear
him say that he is a policeman looking for a friend of yours he asks you if you will get in
and help him find your friend tell him that you can't run away let's go you move away from
the man suspicious that he might not be telling the truth this is smart intellectual sphere rises
sharply this man hurts children jesus christ why would you ever select the other options
you've just turned off the television set and your room is pitch dark through the shadows
you notice that your closet doors open just a crack you can almost see the image of a
black hooded axe murderer squinting at you through the door he's waiting waiting for
you to close your eyes and fall asleep in the quiet of the night you can hear his
hoarse breath making deep gurgling sounds you look away from the door and look back
it's open a bit farther than it was the last time if you can only make it to the closet
and shut the door tight you know he won't be able to get out and murder you in your sleep
the morning light will destroy him so you won't have to worry about seeing him when you wake up
afraid calm pull the covers over your head get help sneak out of the bed
sneak out of the bed afraid as you inch toward the closet you imagine the murderer laughing
at how stupid you are for falling right into his deadly trap you'll show him you
lunge toward the closet door tripping over the leg of the bed and pulling the bed linens
down on top of you ha you've done it the closet is closed you can finally settle down into a
relaxing night's sleep now only those aliens would stop hovering outside your window waiting
to suck you up into their spacecraft so they can examine your brain what's wrong with me
why am i why am i having so many problems your friends are all waiting for you to come out
after school you have a ton of homework and you've been watching television since you came
home on your way out your mother asks did you do all your homework say i've only got a little
left oh that's the best way to do it semi honest that could be true that's true or false
semi honest is the truthfulness equivalent of semi pregnant your mother says finish what you
have left before you go out and i'm not entirely sure jill brady is always untying
your shoes and running away today she is wearing a skirt she is bent over picking up a pile of
books from the floor pay no attention to girls you have much more important things on your mind
like how to get mom to let you join football how to sneak in to see friday the 13th part 45
and why mr johnson the biology teacher is allowed to wear the same suit 10 days in a
row when you can't even wear a stupid pair of socks for two days the boy who sits next to
you in school has just passed you a note folded in a tight square he motions to you to read it
you look around the room mrs hennessey the meanest teacher in the school has her back to
the class the note says what has more crust than the entire surface of the earth write a
note back asking what yeah let's find out you return the note and wait for another response
the note returns and you read what it says mrs hennessey's underwear you can giggle crumple
up the paper and throw right get in trouble quick the evidence get rid of it the noise
attracts mrs hennessey's attention she begins walking down the aisle and your heart begins to
raise she looks you squarely in the eye the smell of her perfume is so overpowering it could
kill you all by itself you cough she says can't you use that scrap paper for something
else before you throw it away protect our natural resources you breathe a sigh of relief
it's a hot sunny day you and a friend are sitting around trying to think of something to do
dad is sitting in the shade napping on a chair you get a great idea let's play a practical
joke on dad let the air out of the car tires spray dad with the hose give dad a hot foot
like on the cartoons what these are all so bad with the air out of his tires what if he
drives it and like gets in an accident spray dad with the hose or burn his feet
cut his brakes mischievously let him sleep let's spray it with a hose
how hard do you want to turn on the water
blast him the hose hits dad in the face and stings him he doesn't appreciate the
humor in your little prank but knows you didn't mean anything by it you can
apologize or leave him alone all right i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry he understands and accepts
he once pulled off of your grandfather's toupee in front of company because he thought he was
being funny see dad's funny too my dad's just that's what do you think i get my comedy from
you're in the candy store buying candy with a five dollar bill given to you by your mother
your bill comes to 50 cents the man gives you back change but no dollars excuse me i'm
not an idiot the man made an honest mistake he says he gives you your money and tells you
to be more respectful to adults oh fuck off i gave you a five dollar bill you gave me 50
cents back are you serious you're being more respectful to adults i was just trying to rob you
of four dollars and 50 cents like a million percent more than what that was
you need eyeglasses the first day you wear them in school everyone calls you four eyes
your parents refuse to get you contact lenses this is actually a real
response i have a prescription but i don't wear them my eyes are not bad but i do have a
prescription why because i because i don't need them i've had the same vision since the sixth
grade it's fine and every every dentist that's ever done the exam every optimal optic what
are they called optimist every optimist i've ever gone to has always said the same thing
yeah no that your eyes are still you're still all right but you can use a little
bit of correction it looks a little bit i don't need it i put them on and it doesn't it changes
like not enough and it makes me want to throw up you have to get used to i don't
even need them though i i see the world in like fucking 1080p i'm good hey i i had my
last eye exam was like a year and a half ago and it was like yeah your vision is fine
but like do you want some correction and i was like yeah fine 720p 15 frame not seeing
the world in 4k 1080 is fine i don't want to watch anything in 4k that's too much then you
know it's a movie no i'm sorry i don't want to watch the movie in 48 frames a second at 4k
you know it's a movie you can feel the video camera no i don't want to watch that have you
guys watched a 48 fps 4k movie you feel like you're filming it with your iphone you feel
it's not a movie anymore it's like a video it sucks no it's true it's not this is true
it's true watch the hobbit at 48 frames a second in 4k and you'll be like this doesn't this feels
like they're i'm watching actors right now it's called the soap opera effect yes that is what it's
called google that all you people writing question marks and questioning my authority
in the stream type in the soap opera effect do it and come here informed
authority i got my vision site i don't know it's good i actually i got a really good uh like
distance vision i can see anything i got it's like a bird some fucking doctor scam was trying
to scam me into stuff you chose not to wear glasses now you will miss work that is presented
on the blackboard what your school grades and intellectual sphere decline wait i i can read
the blackboard though i can read the when i was in school i could read the blackboard
just fine i couldn't i pumped in that i was seeing the world in 1080p i just didn't want
to see the world in 4k why can't i write that this isn't you oh you need glasses
you just fucked up this virtual kid's life well i don't know he needed glasses that bad there's
there's a there's like a spectrum of how badly you need glasses there's like can you pass
your driving exam right and like you legally need to wear them that's that's different you
let your pride get in front of this kid's future it did say you need them fuck okay
whatever it's okay i'll get them later your mother has given you permission to have a party
what why you want to invite most of the kids from your class there's one child that you have
second thoughts about inviting his name is louis fayback all of the kids call him louis
feedback because he's very fat you mentioned to your group of friends that you are thinking
about inviting louis they make faces and pig noises some of them say that if you invite
the bag they will stay home what no no i'm what's wrong with louis you guys need to
chill the fuck out nothing wrong with louis you call the kids who don't want him they're a
bunch of jerks and threaten to beat up anyone who makes fun of louis at your party you've shown
courage and tolerance for individual differences and this has made you stronger i just got like
plus 10 strength louis is completely overjoyed this is the first time he has ever felt like
one of the guys some of your friends do stay home that night and refuse to speak with you
at school louis mother calls you up and thanks you for being so generous louis mother also
happens to be extremely rich on your next school vacation she flies you in louis to hawaii for
a week to stay with relatives there aloha yeah best outcome right there you're only friends
with him for his money i didn't know that before i stood up for him what are you talking about
i only found that out after the hawaii trip all right your teacher and your mother have traded
recipes for an upcoming bake sale before you leave school your teacher asks if you would be
kind enough to run a booth at the bake sale especially for her immediately your friends
begin to snicker behind your back hey wise guy say hey hey i'm not gonna do
no stupid bake sale say yes ma'am or hey yo i would be happy i gotta look cool in front of the
guys you know you score big points with your friends the next time the teacher talks with
your mother she mentions how surprised she was at your behavior you were an embarrassment to
your family the fifth the family sphere takes a bad drop embarrassment i love how me saying
hey i don't want to do no stupid bake sale is worse than me throwing a rock
and smashing the window of an apartment building i never got caught for that though i guess
melissa harper is the prettiest girl in your class you've been giving each other
vi for about two weeks now you're all set to ask her for a date when your best friend
who happens to be taller and better looking than you confesses that he cannot sleep at night
because of her uh-oh he asks your advice on the best way to ask her for a date unaware that you
too are smitten by her let's give some advice you've chosen to do something devious you have
two choices you have bad advice say something to make her look bad say things to make your
friend look bad no you gotta be like no you gotta be like oh man i heard she was like mean
now you know you don't want them to do with her say something
cease your snitching on your friend you give your friend good advice then you take melissa
aside for a heart-to-heart talk you tell melissa that you care about your friend a great deal
and don't want to see him get hurt it's just that he has this habit that he can't control
whenever he is around women he lets out these bad smells from his terrible gas attacks
they've run this family you ask her to please be patient about this
because he really is a great guy melissa says gross that is disgusting your dirty work is
accomplished disgusting you make me sick what i just stood up for the feed bag kid and threatened
to beat up my friends who i'll never talk to ever again because i put i stood up for somebody
and now i'm playing like a little game of thrones over here and everyone thinks i'm a
monster you're an embarrassment to your family what was it no i look your friend has borrowed a
dollar from you and has been promising to pay you back for weeks every time you ask him for
the money he puts you off what should i say here i don't worry about it have a good time
or should i fucking turn into a little finger and start to let go i'm not everybody's back
until all right impatient stop being his friend have a discussion about the money
i'm gonna be patient here no no no i want this one i'm gonna be very patient with you here friend
of mine you and i are no longer friends have a nice life goodbye very patiently it's one dollar
i know it's not a big deal during the discussion you tell your friend that he can pay you back
next week help you with some yard work forget about the money well obviously i'm never gonna
see it that money is gone we will never see it so why don't you help me with some stuff
around the yard you will surely be a great businessman when you get older the work he
does is worth far more than the dollar which you probably would have spent on junk food
anyways pretty good whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa wait a minute wait a minute whoa we're getting
a warning we're getting a sex warning in the schoolyard your friends are sitting around
discussing something very secretively you go over to see what is going on and you hear one
of them say something very strange it has to do with the way you were made skeptical denied
that your parents would ever do that ask your mother for the real story you find it difficult
to believe but you have seen wild kingdom enough times to know that anything is possible
you confront your mother with the information as you remember hearing it your choice for a
leisurely topic of conversation catches mom off guard later you have a nice discussion
about how babies are born she stresses the love aspect but neglects to tell you that
practicing for the real thing can be fun too you may find this out for yourself later how
old am i i why would she say that who founded the american federation of labor i don't know
i have no idea what george meanie george okay george meanie sounds like a like a cartoon
villain from like a saturday morning cartoon samuel gonfer's john smith no it has to be
this one incorrect good john smith discovered like blood plasma or something i don't know
who was the first vice president of the united states that would be john quincy adams it's not
true it is true it wasn't clinton who was the first ruler to consolidate the slavic tribes
i don't know john john lennon rurik pewter i don't know correct which one of these
scientists is credited with the discovery of oxygen davis who wrote the great gatsby that's
easy it's jerald what do i get on the test jim davis while walking around in the store with
your friend you notice that he sneaks a small item into his pocket you ask him what he is
doing he tells you how easy it is to shoplift saying they never check kids you refuse to
steal and tell him that he had better put back what he stole you can turn him into the
store manager i'm so boring snitching again
what a fucking bad friend you are positive that if he gets caught you will also get in trouble
you tell the manager that he has stolen something your friend calls you a traitor
and punches you in the stomach but you feel like you've done the right thing
physical spirit shows a slight decrease trustworthiness and anxiety both increase
oh how do i check my i get how do i check my stats you traitor yeah i look the left side
but i don't think i can move over there do i have to hit escape hold on me oh i don't
think i can unless there's a certain button pressing i don't think so wait there we go maybe
one of the function keys maybe f1 f2 no enter what was wrong what's wrong why are you guys
freaking out why is there why is everybody freaking out check the controls there what's
going on uh there is no list of controls unfortunately warning this episode contains
sexual stuff but it's very it's pretty basic it's just like oh hey like the birds and the
bees right i'm not gonna refresh the page you're in the house alone while you are
exploring the draws you notice a stack of playboy magazines underneath a pile of clothing
where am i exploring all right i mean like i'm gonna i'm gonna look at them the middle
page folds up to show a woman with dark hair and very large breasts sitting on the edge of a
bed and combing her hair this interest whatever i'm gonna say confused you ask yourself many
questions do all women look like this how old do you have to get before meeting someone
like this what is this strange feeling i have in my take out the centerfold and keep it the
centerfold girl becomes your favorite fantasy enjoy it while you can you may find it hard
to believe women like this only exist in fantasy land you almost never meet them at
the bus stop or in the supermarket check our inventory is just as heavy all right marcus
cripple and the tube heads are the most popular rock group with kids your age not
much has changed tubers are still popular anyone who likes them is in if you don't like them or
their new hit song i love you blowtorch eyes you are a definite geek concerned with peer acceptance
spend your whole allowance on their new album i mean do i have any friends left i've i've
i've like locked them all up all of my friends left me because i either told them they turned
them into the police or was friends with like people they didn't think were cool yeah i'm
getting the album i can come back i can bounce back you lay gently on the table and listen to
the hard driving sounds of lead singer marcus cripple i love you blowtorch eyes when i kiss
you my heart fries with your looks you paralyze put my love on your burner i'm your biggest
yearner blowtorch eyes that is so beautiful mr quincy is the toughest teacher in your school
one day you forget to put your homework in with the rest of the items you need for school
quincy asks where your homework is you tell him you forgot it he says come on now you can
be more creative than that why don't you tell me something more believable like mr quincy i did
my homework but my dog threw up on it everyone in class laughs hard at your expense mr quincy
gives you a punishment assignment to do in addition to the work you have not handed in
he says what have you got to say for yourself now mr say fuck you mr q under your breath
mr quincy doesn't hear you but that nerdy joey robinson does he says oh mr quincy he just said
a bad word oh what a fucking snitch quincy uses this as an opportunity to suspend you
you lose out on school time and your intellectual sphere drops oh no oh please give me a break
fuck off dude snitch snitching on me like that unbelievable you just received 25 dollars as a
present your mother tells you that you can either put it in your own piggy bank or give it to her
to hold for you so now i'm i'm saving that money in my own piggy bank you don't have the
self-control to spend it wisely when you run out of money and ask your mother for more to
go to the movies she says if you would have given me the money in the first place you would
still have some left for the movies you'll have to stay home now what did i spend it on did it
at least give me anything i could have the family dog has been acting a little peculiar lately
and no one can figure out why some of your fellow family members suggest that maybe he
should be given away or worse put to sleep dad delivers an ultimatum given away the dog
must shape up or ship out you are the only one in the house who can take the responsibility
for getting him back into shape why do you want to kill the dog what do we talk what's wrong with
the dog what so the dog's not sick the dog's not old the dog's not like coming to like
they just want to get rid of the dog no i can do it i'm the trained dog i got it you spend
every available minute keeping an eye on the dog rewarding him for good behavior and keeping
him out of trouble one day when you return home from school you smell what can only be
the dog's by-products number two to be specific and the smell is emanating from your parents
bedroom you enter the bedroom to find the dog sleeping peacefully in the corner and a sculpture
sitting squarely atop dad's favorite pillow he got up on the bed and shit on his pillow
dispose of the pillow and play dumb later try to wash the pillow dispose of the pillow
and admit the truth dispose of the pillow try to wash the pillow no dispose of the pillow
and play dumb it's not gonna work it's not gonna work you ever try to wash shit out of
something it doesn't work it's just stained forever and they'll know i'll just say that i
fucking did it i was i'll just dispose the pillow and be like yeah i don't know i like i
i'll can i say i shit on the pillow is it possible that i can say like that's my shit
and like i did that death i'll try to wash it it's not gonna work you scrape the sculpture
off the pillow and throw it away outside the house the pillow and pillowcase is left with a
large brown and smelly ring after three machine washings your mother keeps yelling what are you
doing down there the smell comes out of the pillowcase but the pillow still has the stain
see i told you guys i told you not only that the pillow now weighs 30 pounds because it is
waterlogged it will never be dry by the time dad gets home what will you do what did i say
i should have fucking just thrown the pillow in the trash and just what where's that pillow
i don't know are you sure you don't know i don't know huh ask mom i'm not telling dad's story dad's
the bad one here she's very sympathetic as it turns out dad couldn't tell his favorite pillow
from a pile of bricks she makes a quick substitution and all is well we're good
a very aggressive boy starts an argument with you and challenges you to a fight after school
nobody likes me everyone whispers about the big fight it looks like there will be a large
crowd watching all right let's act really tough and then don't show up after school
no come on let's go i got the whole school watching now i can get some points right
the boy shoves you hard in the shoulder knocking you off balance he punches you in
the face and neck he is much more used to this kind of thing than you are suddenly you see
that he has left himself open in the face and stomach swinging his face your first
your fist makes firm contact with the boy's nose he reels back and falls on the floor as you stand
there breathing heavily you watch him get up the crowd is cheering you on the boy staggers
to his feet and is being laughed at by everyone the boy starts crying and runs away remember
all those friends that didn't like me anymore i just beat the bully up i just punched the bully
in his face the latest craze is wearing a dog collar around your neck with a t-shirt proclaiming
your dog name you have just spent five dollars on a shirt that says fifi wrecks the mad mongrel
and have borrowed one of your dog's collars on the way out of the house your mother says do
you think you are going out to school with that ridiculous get up on i'm putting on the
i'm changing clothes once you are back in there you can put on regular clothes and hide
the old ones to change into later at school or change and forget about the outfit i'm gonna i'm
i'm gonna be your friends at school say you have no guts and refuse to allow you to pack
hang around with them how do you feel about this didn't you just see me be i guess i'll get
over it no i'll get over it once you're away from the group for a while you realize that
most of the school thinks they are a bunch of jerks you find a new bunch of friends who
are more willing to accept you for what you are well you i don't want those people friends
anyways fuck who is the founder of modern chemistry no that's the guy that's the guy
that pasteurizes stuff um one of these two i think it's this guy who is the founder of
modern psychiatry uh sigman and roy who was the first american in space uh that would be
john blood fuck who is the inventor of the telegraph i don't know fucking macaroni who was
the austrian born founder of the ethical culture society adam sandler who takes over as president
if both the president and the vice president died uh that would be the uh that's the speaker
of the house you ask mom if you can climb the big rock in the park with a group of friends
she says no uh crafty we're gonna ask dad dad says sure son just be careful let's go it is
a beautiful day you and your friends are having a great time at the top of the rock you and your
friends get silly and start to push each other each claiming i'm king of the hill one of your
friends pushes you a bit too hard and you begin to slip off the rock for a moment it looks as
if you can regain your balance but you don't but you don't you tumble off the rock and
fracture your skull what but you don't you tumble off the rock and fracture your skull in
three places you've just passed through childhood phase of life and cuz you died
i'm alive family life is progressing very well dad is still the greatest hero of all time and
mom is pretty terrific too physically you're not very healthy be careful to avoid situations
that could lead to illness socially this can be an awkward phase of life especially when
you hit the ripe old age of nine or ten should you like girls should you not like girls
decisions decisions all in all you are extremely lovable you're well-mannered and respectful of
adults i may be mistaken but i see a little bit of a casanova in training now regarding
your emotional and personality development now that's a whole nother story your
trustworthiness and sense of fair play are commendable you're an honest child but no
tattletale either as i am the degree to which you display aggressive types of behavior is
somewhat alarming you can be nasty and spiteful at times you're about to enter adolescence
it is a somewhat hectic time of life full of surprises there'll be many very high highs
and many low lows with each year you will gain responsibilities you may also notice that
people will begin to start forgiving you less for things previously described as mere
childhood habits you'll be expected to leave your burping and other questionable talents
in the social circles where they are that's burping where they are you unanimously approved
of your peer group oh yes then there's the matter of girls if you haven't noticed them
much in this phase watch out they've noticed you welcome to adolescence he was a bold man
that first eat an oyster that was from mr swift there's more bars over here i wonder how do we
like i can't select those there's got to be a way i can select those right
now the mouse i there's no mouse shift give me the name what is the name of this game
i don't even know the name of this damn game alter ego alter ego alter ego male all right if
there's any option to do that check it but i'm gonna go pee and grab some more water
i'll be right back all right so uh is there any way to press escape to switch from the
middle to the side symbols oh damn okay that does work the only difference though
is i have to i have to like hit escape twice because when i hit escape before it just goes
like it pulls me out of the everything and gives me when i hit escape before it just
dumped out of full screen and pulled out of the game all right so what is this alter
ego life spirit uh life spirit status name jared age 13 no occupation unattached stress level is
too high for some strange reason family 64 intelligence 71 percent seven percent physical
seven percent seven that i mean well it's because i did just crack my skull that's true
my social is pretty good my vocab my vocational is not that good i'm pretty good socially though
calmness not that calm i'm very competent very expressive i'm not gentle at all
i'm fairly happy fairly thoughtful fairly trustworthy i got 1228 bucks debt you can
go into debt well what i get what are the other ones we're gonna hit like x x this is
what i'm talking about see how i'm like out here now there see what do these all do this
high school there are none of these experiences that you can do right now please try again later
okay well what can i not what about this one this is like trustworthiness select an action
meet someone break off with someone go on a date with your present partner go steady become
engaged to your i don't know oh fuck i can't get out of this can i not get out of this
uh let's meet someone where would you like to meet this person um in school
whom would you like to meet uh ruth and cindy you've chosen to meet with cindy her
characteristics may be described as follows she is very trustworthy she's very gentle she's
moderately calm she's moderately happy she's not very she's very confident she's not very
attractive sure she's got everything but just not very attractive you met cindy in biology class
you chose what you believe to be an appropriate time and place to ask for a date you ask for a
date and cindy accepts i'm now i'm now going on a date with cindy eventually tonight is
halloween some of your more fun loving friends are going door to door some of your
more mischievous friends are going out to play pranks you must decide on which group
you would like to join the fun loving mischievous go door to door play pranks let's just have some
fun pranks loaded down with eggs and shaving cream you come upon the group who decided to
go door to door instead what a bunch of sissies believe that uh can't we just go to like the
old man's house that like told us how to fuck off like last week and yelled at us and
screamed at us out the window because we were playing baseball too loud
no let them like have their fun perhaps you would have had a better time with them
that's oh that's our only options you're in one of your ultra cool moods while cruising
through the house you bump your foot on a piece of furniture and you let a swear word sneak out
your mother calls you in from the other room she says did you say what i thought you said
too cool to care tell her what you did so what so what so what she decides to show you
so what you're not too big to get your mouth washed out with soap with superhuman strength
she grabs you by your cool haircut dumps you into the cool bathroom and forces a quarter of
a bar of soap with lemon fresh skin conditioners down your ultra cool throat seven percent physical
there goes andrea winner jeremy has said that she likes guys who are rough and tough
she's looking over at you and smiling select a mood rough and tough pull in your gut and walk
yeah pull no uninterested pull in your gut and walk over to her like you're not dominated by
your physical characteristics so this is a difficult role for you to play she senses
that you are not acting like yourself and becomes aloof oh well uh christina farber got
a little wild playing spin the bottle at a friend's house yesterday as a result your neck
looks like it was stung by a pack of wild hornets as you walk out of the bathroom dad
inquires about the curious looking marks embarrassed crafty out of it crafty and tell the truth
well i can't give an excuse you must really think dad was born yesterday when he was
your age his friends used to call him dracum of whatever excuse you think of only makes
him feel angry that you would take him for such a fool an argument ensues and you get a boring
lecture about the potential dangers of the dreaded hickey it could create a blood clot that can go
to your brain and kill you blah blah blah even though it happens to be true you probably
don't pay too much attention to is that real because that's not real it's technically real
five of your friends have decided to chip in and buy one box of condoms between the six of
you you're elected to make the purchase anxious by the condoms wait i can't i can't oh no to
make matters even worse when you go into the drug store the person behind the counter is
a young teenage girl can you buy these at like 12 stuttering at about 90 miles an hour you
finally get the words out the girl behind the counter has fair skin her face turns scarlet
red it is a very uncomfortable moment for both of you by the time you pay for the merchandise in
return to your friends your heart is pounding and your hands are dripping with sweat your
friends are delighted to see that you have made the purchase your social status increases
this should be a little bit of a relief my stress is too high stress at max your friends
all go to the shore for a beach party it's late at night one of your friends has a
suggestion he says let's go skinny dipping wait for everyone else to take their clothes off keep
your clothes on take your clothes off let's go there you are naked when you realize that
everyone else has chickened out and left their clothes on how do you feel who fucking cares man
you aren't going to be not let them get the better of you even though some of the girls
are laughing hysterically you put your clothes back on and sit down a couple of your friends
have convinced someone to purchase a bottle of very cheap wine they're excited about the
idea of getting drunk i would be anxious about this i don't know i don't know i don't i do i
wouldn't do that i didn't do that no no no most of your friends are probably doing the
same thing that's probably why it is taking three hours to finish 12 ounces of wine
after the wine is finally finished you can sit back and watch everyone or do something silly
ride your bike into a tree wait what why would you no oh pull your pants down
snap no a bus full of senior citizens ride your bike into a tree
right everyone gets a big kick out of what you did and they all laugh hysterically about it
the next day you become a star for being wasted and doing stupid things i didn't do
it i didn't i pretended i didn't drink anything what you're usually not as impulsive as this so
i guess a little silliness won't hurt this experience does nothing negative to you
all right you're on the school bus on a class field trip getting cozy with your newest
girlfriend who's my newest girlfriend discreet indiscreet begin a makeout session no i'm not
we're not doing that we're just gonna hang out have an intellectual discussion um let's
just uh well sorry i want to like talk i want to sneak what would you talk about
cuddle you coward no i want to see how smart they are what would you talk about satir kamas
the meaning of life why concern yourself with such things school bus trips can be very romantic
if you're not careful your seat might be filled by someone else on the return trip
what do you what adolescent relationships often have a very short lifespan i've seen the
beginning end just waiting in line to pick up lunch in the cafeteria i wanted to have a
conversation okay so so suing lee is a new chinese student who can barely speak english
he appears awkward is not aware of modern styles of dress it's a bit clumsy everyone
in school has begun to make fun of him uh let's just no let's let's talk that's that's tough
coming from across the fucking world let's just talk you approach him and with tremendous
difficulty try to make conversation he seems very shy and self-conscious about his communication
difficulties your friends think you are stupid for wasting your time with him it seems hopeless
that the two of you will ever be able to understand one another you can give up
or keep trying no let's keep trying months pass and seung begins to learn english very
quickly just think how long it would take you to learn chinese if it were the other
way around as soon as he is able to express himself he tells you that he appreciates your
sympathy and friendship you've made a lifelong friend and somebody just wrote it and he's
fucking rich let's go to hawaii your friends ask you if you'd like to be in a rock group
fuck you please tell me a little bit more about the reason i don't have the talent to
do this sort of thing i'd rather be something more intellectually stimulating so who says you
can't be a genius scientist and a rock and roll star uh livingston a foreign friend from
jamaica asks you over to his house for dinner your first course is an interesting looking kind
of soup you take a sip and find it delicious you inquire well what kind of soup is this
livingston's mother replies with a proud smile on her face turtle soup
i don't know i don't know what i would do i'll try your willingness to experience new
things is remarkable besides those little pieces of meat taste just like chicken your
adventurousness delights livingston's mom who shows you pictures of her island and tells you
about its people and customs intellectual sphere rises by the way they're rich i'm
just my brain is getting so big group of kids you hardly know have just made fun of you
usually this might not bother you but lately you have been feeling down in the dumps about
a lot of things your physical appearance has been disappointing you your family has been giving you
a hard time about almost everything no one seems to be saying or doing anything positive toward
you you have a bad case of blues what the fuck wait where when when did one when did
when did when did this what uh all right let's let's talk let's talk to someone
who would you like to talk to someone in your family a friend was out was was taught was uh
let's start with frank you explain your problems to your friend your friend seems very supportive
but every time you list a complaint your friend list one of his or her own problems
you begin to think that he isn't listening to you the conversation doesn't turn out to be
very helpful oh fuck what the fuck john a very close friend of yours has been very
depressed lately you have seen him moping around the halls at school keeping to himself
one day while you are running an errand for a teacher on the top floor of the building
you see a shadow swaying on the school roof you peer through the designs in the glass window
panels trying to see what it is happening out there what it's john you call and he's
planning to jump off the roof he wants you to go away he refers to rock stars who have
died and how he will get what wait wait wait what the fuck suddenly while he's talking john
loses his footing he becomes to fall off the roof he's able to grab onto a flagpole that is
attached to the side of the building he looks frightened i go i gotta get out i gotta go uh
anxious but try to stay calm remain calm um there's not much time look there's no time
there's no time who's around is anybody around no all right let's let's i he if he just slipped
and he's like grap no i've got to get out there oh no the kind of calmness you're
trying to project is not part of your personality you expend so much energy
trying to appear calm that you act ineffectively oh fuck what the fuck i thought i had that
doubt there was no time well i tried i it's you and a friend are hanging around in the
bathroom together your friend takes out some magic markers and begins to write on the
ask you if you want to write something too what will you do i don't have right on the walls no
i don't want to get in trouble for this he calls you a sissy and proceeds to write your name
and telephone number all over the wall sometimes friends can be jerks what the fuck you are
still much too young to buy liquor but your friends want to get wasted tonight they plan on
waiting outside of the liquor store and asking older customers to buy it for them no no this
is bad no not interested i want to find something else to do you don't seem to be interested in
this kind of experience right now intellectual and physical spheres rise there we go early in
the evening a friend's mother appears mysteriously at the door and asks to speak to your mother
from another room you hear the woman say that you have been a bad influence on her son
and that your mother should try harder to raise you the right way her complaints by the
are totally unjustified first you barely know her son and second he is the biggest juvenile
delinquent in town without your help or anyone else's uh that's bullshit i can understand why
you were angry but going in and giving the woman a piece of your mind proves her point to
her here you are storming in from another room acting rude in front of the company
you try to convince the wrong person of your innocence for better success you should have
concentrated on your mom what are you doing i'm just this is not even me you have just mastered
mustered up the courage to ask faith morgan voted hottest bod of the century
by fellow classmates out on a date she looks you up and down rolls her eyes and says be real
give her an almost universally understood finger signal
um
flapable a depressed middle finger angry middle finger save it she already thinks you are a jerk
why etch the impression of yourself as a boorish slob any deeper into her mind
unflappably walk you're currently madly in love with a girl who is having a birthday next
week you're trying to think of what to get her she's hinted about a very expensive piece
of jewelry that would just about wipe out your life savings if you choose to buy it for her no
no i would i would think about it for a second no you're trying to think of something else but
your guilt prevents you from coming up with anything good eventually the whole experience
makes you resent the girl and the relationship flops this is like falling apart some more
sexual matters while sitting around the house with a girlfriend how many girlfriends do i have
she says she wants to give you a manicure appreciative yeah whatever that's fine
letting your friend groom you puts her in a very romantic mood after she finishes the job
you get cozy on the couch and have a hot and heavy time unfortunately the next day your friends
see your polished nails and rag on you for days about it little do they know little do
they know your dad's boss thinks that you're a fine young man he would be honored if you
would consider escorting his lovely daughter matilda to the company dinner dance
another girl all right yeah let's do it this was a very open-minded set of choices
you arrive at the country club waiting to meet dad's boss's daughter all of a sudden this
movie star walks up to you your eyes glaze your mouth gets dry and you must concentrate
very hard to prevent your tongue from dropping out of your mouth could this be
matilda nope it's some lady who thinks you work there parking cars matilda arrives complete
with braces pigtails and a squeaky laugh as the night goes on you find out she's not so
bad dad gets a raise the following week now about the company picnic next month all right
okay your dad decides he wants to have a long talk with you about college and his talk he advises
you to do all the things you think you would like to do at least he suggests careers that
you couldn't see yourself doing in a million years he talked about colleges that seem dull
and uninteresting say son have you ever thought of going to a military college
you get the distinct sense that he has already planned the next eight years of your
life for you at this point you may not be sure that you want to go to college at all
calm and i'm not calm i'm not a calm person i'm not calm you're letting your father overstep
his bounds as advisor his concern about your getting a good education has caused him to
behave in an overly controlling fashion you're evidently too anxious to confront him about
this so he continues making decisions for you keeping you not only anxious and depressed
but dependent on him as well but oh an ad in the paper says wanted young adults 15 to 20 for
acting modeling jobs ask for rod let's see some money rod seems very interested in you and gives
you an appointment for an interview when you arrive at the place where the interview is to be
held you notice that it is a bare apartment with almost no furniture just a mattress and
an old desk with a phone on it this place could only have meant bad news by no one of the older
kids in school takes you aside and offers you a quick way to make money by dealing drugs
nothing too heavy or dangerous according to him all you would have to deal is some pot and a
few ludes ludes tell him you will do tell him you won't do it no i'm not gonna do it
i'm not gonna deal drugs he tells you that you have just passed up the opportunity to make
some easy money he is caught dealing three weeks later but nothing much happens to him
three months after that you read that he was jailed in south america during a drug related
incident got out of that one a cousin of yours asks if you would like to inherit his weight set
i need it so yes you begin a workout schedule and within three months there is a
noticeable improvement in the way your body looks after a few compliments from the girls
you begin to slack off physical spirit definitely improves good what where are we at now what percent
what percent are we at 14 years old physical holy fuck that went from seven to 49
i'm not calm at all that's the problem i have so much i have so much confidence though
what 14 dollars you are annoyed because your father doesn't seem to be paying attention to
what you say these days you would appreciate it if he would treat you more like a person
while you were trying to explain this to him he begins correcting your grammar see i can't believe
it you're doing it again you know dad this is a perfect example i'm trying to express myself
right now and you are putting me down by correcting my english your dad is taken aback
by your assertiveness and is forced to examine his own behavior he realizes that he has been
unfair to you and apologizes the two of you again gain a mutual respect for one another
let's do this one first some of your friends are going to the city this weekend to get tattooed
get a tattoo yeah let's do it wait aren't i 14 jimmy the pen runs the tattoo shop there
are a table full of needles in front of you 14 what are we gonna get let's get a tattoo
what kind of tattoo are you gonna get mother inside a red heart a bald eagle
a skull and crossbone let's get a bald eagle the tattoo is even more painful than you imagined
it would be you must leave the bandage on it until it becomes a scab for a few days it oozes
blood let's tell our parents about it no wait how am i for some reason they just don't find
it all that attractive as a matter of fact your mother nearly faints at the sight of it
eventually they learn to accept it but deep down inside it is one of those things that
they will never understand all right i have a tattoo of an eagle now all your friends are
skipping class and they want you to come along too let's go your status on the trustworthiness
characteristic suggests that you are not the type of person who does this sort of thing
as a result you experience no negative emotional consequences except for a slight decrease in
the calmness characteristic since you are so trustworthy an action like this is bound to make
you a little nervous about getting caught i have to i'm probably at zero now
your parents have gone out for the night you and two friends are sitting around with nothing
much to do one of your friends asks what kind of booze do your parents have in the house
bored ready to experiment anxious i'm i mean i'm not i'm not calm ever
raid the liquor cabinet suggest something else to do i'm not okay i'm gonna say let's let's
suggest something else you're afraid of getting caught your friends become bored at your house
and leave early i'm too panicky i need to get like my calmness down you're hanging around at
your friend's house there's nobody home but you and he oh right your friend goes into
his parents bedroom and emerges with a small yellow box he opens the box and shows you
his father's gun dude god damn it man no i'm not going no no no no no no no no
no anxious leave curate no anxious i uh no no no bye put it away anxious run you don't want any
part of that thing you tell him to put it away he laughs ah fucking jesus christ you don't want
any part of that thing you tell him to put it away he laughs and tells him that he takes it
out of the time he calls you a baby for being frightened on the way back in the bedroom
he put the trips the gun blows a hole in the ceiling you excuse yourself saying you think it's
time for you to go i'm i'm you know time to go jesus fucking christ what the fuck a close
everyone in my life is in danger what the no what about i'm i'm stupid i need to calm it
down a close friend of yours has been showing up everywhere drunk lately
although he seems to function well at his after-school job people are beginning to talk
about him 14 years old we're gonna talk he denies that he doesn't he has no problem
this is too heavy for like a fucking 13 year old he gets angry at you and calls you names
all right i'm gonna leave him alone but it's your health it's your health your concern for
your friend is admirable it shows that you are sensitive to the amount of danger that he is in
unfortunately there is no way to help people like this denial is one of the strongest
defenses alcoholics have on their side he's like 12 if he ever chooses to get straightened
out it will have to come from himself oh what is this on the back of an old matchbook cover
you see an offer which promises you the possibility of a free art scholarship if you
can draw winnie a cartoon figure on the inside flap yeah interested throw the matchbook
cover up let's go your picture is returned with an offer to enroll in a home study course
sponsored by the international institute of constructive creative painting and art
nice tuition is of course waived because you qualify for a full scholarship there is a 499
dollar plus state sales tax where applicable fee for tools and materials are you interested in
purchasing these materials is this a scam but if it's not i don't have enough money i can't get
scammed sexual what the fuck man you are getting dressed one day and notice a small red mark on
i know i'm not uh okay i'm let's just go let's just go to the doctor it's nothing to
worry about it's just all right well good i'm not terrified sorry you are too young for this
episode huh what's this episode pimple penis i'm sorry but you must have a job to do this
did i get soft-locked you are in a quiet pensive mood and your thoughts turn to subject
of religion your family's beliefs seem out of step with your own as you wonder about the
nature of your existence would they understand if you told them about the differences
uh i guess well i guess we're going to confront the family talk about well different stuff you
desire to question the meaning of religion faith and some of life's larger more philosophical
questions is admirable this kind of independent thinking stimulates the mind and fuels divergent
thought your parents can't accept your views they say you are all wrong it doesn't even
seem as if they are listening to what you are saying you think they accept too much of their
religion on faith you are quick to point out several elements of the religion that seem
hypocritical because your family relationships have been strained in the past they are
reluctant to accept you as an independent free-thinking person what the fuck while you
are shopping in town one day a woman who introduces herself as a photographer tells you
that you are very handsome and that she might be able to get some modeling work for you she
gives you her card is this going to be another scenario where it's an empty apartment with his
phone let's okay let's do it the woman tells you that she has just been given an assignment
to shoot some models for a famous men's underwear manufacturer would you be willing
to pose for some pictures the pay is five hundred dollars that's the no wait how old am
i no no no no no no too bad she tells you she will call if anything else comes up it
doesn't i must be employed was that did that count as employment your best friend since
grade school has been looking depressed and is confused he is usually a very happy-go-lucky
person so you really can't understand what could be wrong uh ask him what's wrong he tells
you that there's nothing wrong but you can see by his face that he is deeply troubled no no
no no no keep uh leave him alone i guess you believe that i guess you believe you have tried
and that any further prying would be inappropriate some people have a way of testing whether a person
truly wants to help as opposed to those who merely feel it is their obligation to be friends
by saying that there really isn't anything wrong i think that this was one of those times you
never find out what was bothering him you're shopping at a drug store it is almost closing
time the manager is letting the customers out one by one keeping the door locked so no one
else can come in suddenly the man in front of you at the cast register takes out a gun
and announces a hold-up he smells heavily of alcohol and it looks like if the gun could be
fake could be could be i don't know that for sure uh-oh you move solely on instinct you
attempt to wrestle the gun from his hand as you thought it is a fake he is easily subdued
you acted bravely but impulsively i just fucking like karate chopped his i swung as hard as i
could down on the hand he was pointing just put all my weight karate fucking smashed down
and just get on all my weight all right someone's saying side buttons do the side buttons select an
action apply for a job for what kind of job would you like to apply cook in a fast food
store clerk in a drug store ticket taker in a movie theater trucker's helper for a moving
firm assistant in a law office let's go work at like mcdonald's a trucker no i'm gonna work
at mcdonald's congratulations you start work immediately hey all right but what about the
other ones age 15 that's it just my age what wait wait wait wait what's what what is going on
here there is a girl's pajama party at pamela gordon's house tonight you and your friends
plan an undercover pajama party crash oh this is adventure i don't want to do that i don't
want to do that all right i have a job now what you notice someone stealing an extremely
large amount of valuable property from work the boss asks if you can prove what you are
saying since you have no pictures or direct evidence he tells you there's nothing i can do
this is one of those times when you think the whole world is completely insane sometimes
it just about is in your own opinion you have been doing a good job at work your boss
however constantly complains about the pickiest things he never tells you when you have done
a good job when you do something wrong he really lets you have it even if even when
you foul up on something easily correctable to make matters worse most of the mistakes you make
are of his fault now he's called you into his office for a discussion this usually means that
you're going to get yelled at for something unbothered listen quietly you must be trying
to tune your boss out he sees you are doing this and becomes infuriated you're fired i'm
too young for this one you and a group of your friends are getting together to go to a
movie your best friend and his date are picking you up at your house and the three of you are
meeting everyone else including your own date at the theater the dual bell rings and you are
greeted by a dark-haired beauty with sparkling eyes and a devastating figure she smiles at you
and tells you her name is sheryl your friend is waiting in the car because he isn't feeling
well in the car and at the movies you and sheryl make small talk after all your best
friend isn't feeling up to par you wouldn't want sheryl to have a lousy time and resent him
besides your date seems to be so engrossed in the movie she doesn't seem to mind either
midway through the movie your friend pulls you aside and asks if you wouldn't mind taking
sheryl home he knows she is enjoying the movie and he is feeling too ill to stay wait hold
on wait wait wait wait wait wait um i was there with another person take your date home
first and then come back and then take that doesn't you ignored your date the whole time
they're both in the car sheryl says goodbye to your date and asks if you would walk her to
the door she kisses you on the cheek you think you feel her finger poke something into
your back pocket what later that evening you discover that sheryl slipped you a piece of
paper with her phone number on it when you call her she sounds very aloof she feels guilty
about coming on to you and she wishes you would forget about the whole thing
that's life you almost sold out on your best friend for this girl
oh my god i'm still too young for these episodes how do i get older i i know why let's
do the activities on the side okay here we go you are at the burger palace at 12 30 in the
afternoon on a saturday you and your friends are bragging about various disgusting things
you have done with food okay yeah i'm let me i'm curious now uh larry dares you to stuff a double
giganto burger with cheese extra sauce sauce pickles and dressing into your mouth and eat
it all in one bite oh yeah let's fucking go the burger begins to slide into your
cavernous mouth moistening your lips with grease you hit a slight snag which causes
a minor backup a large drop of secret sauce begins to roll down your chin and neck
your friends begin to cheer you on go go go go go go go go go go you begin to gag
you think perhaps the burger has you beat go go go go go go your friends beg you to go
on let's go go go go your eyes are beginning to go go go go go yeah with a herculean effort
you close your mouth on the monster and commit to your cast iron stomach in a single gulp
by this time your friends are in tears from laughing hysterically you become a
legend in your own time your eyes begin to bulge you start you start to turn purple
i'm still too young i gotta do more shit should i go look on another date all right
let's go let's do this break off with someone go on a date have an experience
with your present partner all right yeah let's go you don't have a partner oh come on meet
someone become engaged break off with someone meet someone i want to meet this person outside
of school not in school um who do we have who do we have that we we're talking to
who likes us i don't know is anybody on this list even like us you've chosen to meet with
cindy your characteristics may be described as follows she's not very trustworthy she's not
gentle she's calm she's not happy she's not confident she's very attractive you met cindy
while away for the summer you chose what you believe to be an appropriate time and place to
ask for a date you asked for a date and cindy accepts all right let's go go on a date while
having a soda at cindy's house the phone rings she picks it up and looks around the room
nervously she walks out of the room with the phone and you think you can hear her say
i told you not to call me at home she puts the phone back down and proceeds as if the phone
never even rang you casually ask her who it was her voice cracks as she says no one her eyes
dart around the room how do you feel about this would you keep pressing her for information
until she finally tells you who was calling who was it she still won't tell you even though
you have chosen to break off this relationship it will still have an impact on you personally
please check the status screen to see what adjustments have been made in your home and
you've chosen to meet with an her characteristics may be described as follows she's very gentle
she's not trustworthy she is moderately calm she's very happy she's moderately confident she's
not very attractive you met and down the block you chose what you believed to be an appropriate
time and place and ann accepts it was worth a shot go on a date
ann has just won an all-expense paid trip for two to a fantastic ski resort in vermont
she has invited you to go along with her there's only one problem
ann's parents absolutely refuse to allow their daughter to take an overnight trip with any one
of the opposite sex what will you do convince ann that she should tell her parents that she
is going with someone else convince and to stick up for herself i have a talk with ann's parents
tell ann it's not worth the trouble she should go by herself and have a good time
i'll talk to you parents you've decided to confront them honestly ann's dad appreciates
this he answers you with the same honesty he doesn't trust you alone in the same room with
his daughter he thinks the two of you will have sex you mentioned that if you wanted
to have sex with his daughter it would be much easier to go someplace closer to home
like a local motel you are proud of yourself for winning points in the logic department
holy shit the second that sentence ends chair scraping against floor stands up fucking straight
what the fuck did you just say that's as what i would imagine and dad says very true very
true then gets a very sinister look on his face and continues just about the only difference
my friend is that you did something like that close to home and i found out about it
i would not be inconvenienced by having to travel far to find you and beat you to a pulp
okay did we get to go you and ann are both thinking through your decisions about going
to college and wants to go to a college that has a strong pre veterinary program there are
none in the area making that college would mean that she would need to travel a great distance
you wouldn't see each other for a long period of time long periods of time which one of these
things reflects your feelings on this don't pervert wait wait what if i okay i guess
it seems as though you are trying to avoid your real feelings there is hesitation and
confusion that you're not owning up to how good could anyone feel after his girlfriend
has just said she is leaving to go far away for a relatively long period of time
and has spent the afternoon with her parents visiting friends of the family when you see
ann she can't stop talking about john their son when ann and john were younger everyone
joked about how nice it would be if they married when they got older isn't that cute
anyway ann goes on to tell you that john grew up to be an absolute
hunk with the cutest set of dimples on his cheeks after she finishes her detailed description she
squeals he looked just like one of those calendar models i could have died how do you
feel about this i don't know i uh i'm a bit threatened by this i guess that's understandable
from what i understand of ann she's not the most trustworthy type i know that's difficult
to hear but it was one of her characteristics when you met her earlier you should examine
why you would want to stay with someone who you might not trust is it just you being overly
concerned or is there really a danger that she might abandon you for the first gorgeous
available guy that comes along even though you have chosen to break it off the relationship
it will still have an impact on you please check the status screen figure that out who's
next louise marianne ruth marcia marcia her henrietta henrietta she's trustworthy
not gentle calm not happy not confident is moderately attractive trustworthy though
you met henrietta while on vacation you chose what you believe to be the right
opportunity and she accepts your date let's go even though your mother knows that you
are currently dating someone she candidly asks if you had ever considered dating her
friend's daughter jeena tell her to butt out tell her she appreciates that she's
looking up for you but no thanks what does jeena look like your mom says she's petite
and has a very pretty smile she's also got a lovely personality do you want to be set up
with this girl yeah turns out that jeena's mom has been doing quite a bit of talking about you
too jeena is not interested it was her mother's line about your great personality that turned
her off henrietta is late for your date and you are forced to sit in the living room and
converse with her somewhat nosy parents her father looks you squarely in the eye and asks
you son i'd really like to know what your plans are for my daughter what would you be inclined
to say about this my plans are to take her to the movies and try very hard to have sex with
her before the night is through ow that has hurt myself oh i just like pulled muscle in my
stomach i don't quite understand what you mean by that sir for now i plan on developing
a friendship with your daughter it's a little too early for us to look very far into the
future i just need to see what it says right my aren't we sarcastic you lost your patience
with henrietta's dad and we're a bit impulsive he takes this kind of statement as a sign that
you are a wise guy which by the way you are he will be a source of difficulty for you
and henrietta on your way out the door he turns to henrietta's mother and says
i didn't like that boy from the start he has shifty eyes you and henrietta make a
handsome couple all right now quick get married after a long and serious talk with her parents
henrietta decides that the two of you are too young to be engaged all right i forgot
you were driving on a deserted road when you begin to wonder just how fast the car will go why
would i do that what i'm 15 i what where did i get this car from no that's dangerous
it is a hot summer night and your friends are drinking beer in the park down the street
one of them suggests a beer guzzling contest i'm the fucking master of this shit the
contest is to see who can drink a 32 ounce bottle of beer the fastest without stomping
all the losers must drink an additional 32 ounce bottle of beer whoa what happened wait
what wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what happened what happened i missed it you drank
the second bottle how old am i now 17 two percent calmness i have eight dollars let's get a job
wait i already have a job clerk in a drug store all right now let's go to work no no
don't quit the job that i just fuck okay how do i work oh it needs to have the okay i see
i see i need to actually have the um you have committed the most serious of all possible
crimes in gym class you've forgotten your gym shorts uh mr black the ex marine drill sergeant
will use this as an excuse to have you drop and do 50 freddy always has an extra pair of gym
shorts and he is about your size to borrow freddy's shorts confront mr black with the
bad news now i'm gonna borrow freddy's shorts freddy hands you his extra pair of gym shorts
they are crinkled up so badly that the school name and logo are unreadable they're
also completely stiff the inside band that used to be white is now dark gray
where the shorts take what do you mean what's wrong with them no they're already on your legs
and crotch are itchy for the rest of the day it's time for the it's time for the senior
prom are you going to attend yes who will you be going with someone i am currently
dating i have yet to ask them we're gonna go with henrietta you are going steady with
someone do you mean to say that you are going with someone other than a steady someone you plan
on having an affair with no what then i can only assume that you made an unconscious error by
choosing this option a Freudian slip of the interface so to speak i must interpret this as
a sign that you never wanted to go to the prom with your steady girlfriend in the first
place which means your relationship is on the skips no what the excitement of the prom causes
stress which destroys your relationship before prom night even arrives you fail to find another
date and spend the night alone and lonely don't why would it assume that a group of friends are
getting together for a toga party this friday night all right excited let's go you arrive at
the party stunningly draped in one of your mom's best sheets on the table there is beer
wine and hard liquor someone mentioned that there are drugs available for sale from a person
at the other end of the room how would you like to get how wild would you like to get at
this party mildly wild wild extremely wild or maniacal are you planning on trying to meet
any girls at this party no it's a good thing this party is a total bore that's it you are
too old for this episode how did i miss this i was too young and now i'm too old i can't
do anything here it just tells me how old i am you are starving and the cafeteria line seems to
be moving very slowly today's menu includes meatballs bread balls cardboard pizza and
chicken mystery of the unknown meat pies about the only things edible seem to be the french
fries and the white powdered doughnuts you take a portion of fries but by the time you
get to the cash register they you have already finished them keep walking through
and say you decided to skip lunch i don't have no pay i already i ate them it's a good thing you
didn't try to sneak through milly the cafeteria lady can smell french fry breath from 200 yards
away um can i do am i can i go anywhere did i miss any other scenarios i don't think so
i have to like wait for 18 your friends decide to eat a large meal at a diner and
sneak out without paying come on you punks what are you doing yeah okay i i can't do
anything here if i click the hourglass it doesn't do anything i can't change it that just tells me
how much it is i can't do anything it just tells me the exact age i have like i i'm almost 18
don't worry yeah i don't i don't age a month when i click this i age a month when i do
something we have to either do high school or adventure in an attempt to win the heart of
your latest love you decide to write her a poem that will melt her very soul you labor for
hours and then reveal to her the product of your endeavor sure i guess the ocean whispers
softly of bringing you so near i'd love to pick some flowers and place them in your chest not
hair a bit corny but she loves it you romantic fool we we good no mr harvey is a school
guidance counselor who is kind of who is kind and helpful to all the students after 30 years
of faithful service to the school he is leaving your teacher requests a donation for a present
will you contribute a donation i don't have any money how much how generous any amount will be
fine how much will you donate uh i don't this is a quarter i don't have i don't have any
money i have like eight bucks at least 50 cents you cheapskate i know i need to save
that money for a car the whole class takes a job ability and interest test would you like
to hear your results yeah your highest area of aptitude is in casket making why casket
maker you are still new to high school and upperclassmen offers to sell you a discount
pass to the school swimming pool for only 50 cents he claims proceeds will go to charity
you buy the tickets yeah let's go your school doesn't have a swimming pool the charity he is
collecting is for himself how would i not know we do how would i know we don't have a swimming
pool how long have i been going to the school for four years i don't know that we don't have
a swimming pool i'll be out here all right one two more months we're almost there we're almost
we're almost through it you are shopping in a men's clothing store a pretty girl keeps
looking over at you whispering to her friend and smiling okay you walk over to her swaggering
slightly and introduce yourself okay she eyes you up and down stopping at all the strategic
points along the way uh she notes that you are a sharp dresser thank you she mentions that
she needs to buy a present for someone just about your size and wonders whether you would
consider trying on a pair of pants so she can make a decision why what because it's
probably like a boyfriend hey can you can you try on a pair of pants i know somebody that's
your size yeah it's a boyfriend the second i hear oh it's for my boy i'm out like that you
know that the fucking simpsons meme where the grandpa comes in takes the hat on puts the hat
off and fucking walks out the door come on smart enough you and your friend are rough
housing near the stairwell at school your friend is much bigger than you are he holds
you up over the stairwell and threatens to drop you down what you wait you look down
at the long drop and close your eyes uh stop please am i 18 yet no coward no you don't uh-oh
cindy lewis is a girl you've had a crush on for a very long time a friend of hers tells
you that cindy told her that all she dreams about is going out with you and being with
you there's only one problem cindy has a boyfriend and you are currently seeing someone
who the fuck am i seeing that's news to me i don't who is this person am i still
dating henrietta you arrange through the friend to meet cindy in secret at a fast food restaurant
you hear through the friend that cindy agrees to meet you there at two o'clock this saturday
you've already made plans for saturday afternoon with the girl you are seeing and you will have
to lie in order to break them all right everybody get the hat put the hat on take the hat off
no cindy sucks let's go on a date with henrietta to prove our loyalty what are we
when did i get broken up with all right marcia whoa very trustworthy very gentle very happy very
confident very attractive just not calm that's neither of mine i'm a fucking firecracker too
i'm not calm perfect my soul mate right there you met marcia in a local shopping mall you
choose what you believe to be an appropriate time and place to ask for a date this person is not
interested in you the one time it was a perfect match her prestigious school fraternity
lash lasa opso fi is seeking new members pledges would you like to join yeah sure good you pledge
name is fish breath your pledge assignment is to steal a pair of girls panties with a
and run them up the school flagpole do you still want to join why does everything have to
do this can i have you can you just eat a cheeseburger can you look at you i can eat
like 50 wings i can chug like two bottles really quickly let's go back and get like a
triple cheeseburger and i'll show you do it one bite do it no do it no no no i don't want to
join that fraternity there are none of these experiences that you can do right now what
am i 18 yet miss harnor your english literature teacher is getting on in years everyone knows
that she is a bit hard of hearing whenever she gives a test people can whisper to one
another without the slightest chance of being heard on today's test everyone seems to be
cheating there are two answers that you do not know will you cheat with everyone else
yeah everyone's at fault if somebody if we all get caught we just oh we all don't it's that
simple literally all of us go down or none of us do like that's it that's it you are not
caught you're great on the test and proves as a result of your cheating i'm 18 how do i
move on life how do i like move on in my life how do i get out of high school is it graduation
time mr horace a social studies teacher in your school has a funny habit of twitching one
eye when he speaks you are always sure to get a laugh out of your friends whenever you imitate
this twitch for them i didn't select that one day in class mr horace is interrupted by
someone wishing to give him a message as he walks over to the door a friend starts asking
you to do horace it was nice of you to give mr horace a break he is aware of how everyone
makes fun of him and even though he doesn't show it he's very sensitive about it yeah i'm
not gonna do that we have to like we have to get out of high school you have forgotten your
new class schedule will you walk into a class it looks like it should the one you should be
sorry the class you walk into is a class of greek students who are learning english as
a second language for a second there it sounded like your ears might have been going
a little crazy what if i just what if i don't graduate high school and i'm here till i'm like
30 your biology teacher is breezing through the miraculous inner workings of the common
cockroach blabberous crenafer it is enough to make you lose your lunch you can't understand
a word he is saying but everyone else seems to be nodding and following along what will you
do why don't you stop like stop him and ask for clarification your teacher is impressed
by the fact that you thought enough of the subject matter to ask him to explain it so
that you fully understand his explanation makes it almost bearable almost barely understandable
but at least that's enough to get you through the next quiz he even gives you a few live
souvenirs to take home and study on your own what do you do with the souvenirs put them
in mary jane's lunch free them in the cafeteria and cause a school-wide panic and
a health violation shutdown yes now they can be reunited with thousands of their relatives
living comfortably and in high style in the school cafeteria well that's disgusting
18 still get me out of here there are none of these experiences that you can do go to work
graduate i can't graduate mr andre your french teacher who everyone in school claims is gay
has asked you for your help cleaning up his office after school he asked you in front of
a whole group of your friends who begin to look at one another and make faces what will
you do tell him you why wouldn't i help him tell him you will help him tell him you have something
tell him you why would i not help him this makes you the subject of unbearable teasing
in his office there is a picture of his wife and his daughter monique who is a beautiful
young girl about your age he explains that she goes to a private school you comment on
how pretty she is mr andre smiles and offers to invite you over so that you can meet
ooh la la all right let's go let's go meet someone right outside school what was her name
she's not on this list she's not trustworthy not calm not happy uh all right betsy do marcia
again i need to graduate high school i'm gonna be stuck in high school mrs cromwell the music
teacher has volunteered you to sing the star spangled banner at assembly yeah let's go you
have the confidence necessary to withstand this experience as a matter of fact you don't
sound half bad good double was 19 when do you how don't you graduate high school before like
19 oh i'm still a drugstore clerk right the teacher asks for a volunteer from the class to
help an italian exchange student lola learn to speak english oh i'll volunteer wouldn't
it be great if lola were this incredible looking sexy wild uninhibited italian fox
it would be but as it turns out lola is rather ordinary looking stop helping her after a short
period of time i well i said i was gonna i said i was gonna do it i'm gonna do it
as it turns out lola has a really great personality she becomes a good friend good
good good you have been studying all night long for a chemistry test there's one formula
that you absolutely cannot learn at about two o'clock in the morning you begin to see how
easy it would be to write the formula on your hand and cheat no you always get caught that way
that's just evidence the more you try the more you are frustrated at 4 a.m you finally
doze off to sleep the next day when you sit down to take the test you find out that the
formula you couldn't learn was not included on the test you got an a all right all right
almost 19 still in high school oh wait what i thought that was saying you win high school
you and your classmates are changing into your clothes for gym class for a moment everyone is
naked even though you try not to look you can't help wondering about how you measure up to
the other guys this is an unusually calm response what is with this sexual high school
shit mr hummer your math teacher is a 26 year old knockup oh miss hummer she puts
any girl in the school to shame one year on a class trip to the beach she wore a bikini
joey brant took pictures of her and sold them around school for five dollars each what the
fuck you raise your hand to ask her a question she slinks over to you and leans forward to
answer your question after she helps you she walks past and brushes her hip against the
desk where your hand is when you see your friends later you i don't say anything oh god
who would believe that you got the besides mr hummer is engaged to a linebacker for the
ala rams you certainly wouldn't want him to think you got you have just passed through
adolescence we did it i made it from infancy childhood adolescence i only like i broke my
neck once i landed once on my head out of from a rock and that's it everything else is
good family life can be very rough during adolescence even though your family expects
you to take charge of your life no one wants to let you have the freedom to do what you want
judging by your progress through life so far your family life has not been very good
spending time at home is like going to battle at times you aren't sure how you can even
live there physically you have been not very healthy socially this phase of life does present
its share of problems most of these problems fall into the category of girls life must have
been pretty simple before they showed up yeah your social adjustments to this phase of life
has been remarkable although you do not have a steady girlfriend at the present time there's
always the next life phase now regarding your emotional development your trustworthiness and
sense of fair play are commendable you are an honest young man but there's always room
for improvement a positive aspect of your adolescence is your ability to resist temptation
not give into your impulses since adolescence is the time for testing limits this can get some
people into some pretty dangerous situations on the other hand leading too much of a sheltered
life can be boring you seem to be enjoying most of what you do even though you experience
the blues in quotes every once in a while it's nice to see that you are not having
depressed traumatized life even though an occasional explosive outburst is common in most
adolescents you seem to be having you have everything well under control you seem to be
sensitive and gentle you certainly have a good head on your shoulders you are not only
book smart you also have plenty of common sense now that your adolescence is almost over it's
time to be hurled out there into the abyss of the real world i bet you didn't know that
everything you did so far was part of the fake world uh welcome to young adulthood oh my
god the desire accomplished i've been playing this for four hours holy shit how many more stages
of life do i have how many more like four oh god young adult middle adult and old age
save it for let i mean i don't think i'm ever gonna open this again ms dos night and we play
one game it's just too interesting try and do it as soon as possible i don't think you can
yeah like i'm gonna piss we're gonna piss and grab another uh another water here we'll
seltzer water and i think we'll i'm gonna keep going this is i'm actually very interested
this means this means one thing though this is very very important i think this is just a
never-ending forever supply of things to do on this website which is saving for tomorrow
i mean i'm i'm playing i'm doing sam and max tomorrow all right let me figure out what's
going on i'll be right back beerby yeah that's another thing i don't think they get i don't
think these games save so i could not i don't think go back to this i'm not sure i have a
way to physically save it but i'll be right back all righty okay i guess let me move this
over here so yeah so here's the plan let chat decide well that would unfortunately add a lot
more time to get through it uh we got here so we're gonna change the title of this stream
to birth to death because we're invested at this point did not think that we were going to
do this one but i it's it's interesting enough and it's fun and it's we have an opportunity to
go start to finish through one of these experiences so is this even on twitch alter
ego right i mean i don't think this is the same game but i mean that's close enough right
alter ego it is the same game okay so yeah we're gonna yeah sorry that we originally
we're gonna go through at least last time we did this four or five or six of them at least
but that just means that we have content forever there's content forever and i'm just
gonna do this every saturday night that's just what it's gonna happen i do not see a reason
why we wouldn't do this as a regular thing every saturday job security pogchamp it is fun
though it's just it's interesting to see this stuff so i am gonna do this you tell me if
you don't like this because instead of let's show you what i mean here i'm going to do this
so i don't have to keep tabbing out and tabbing in you tell me if the if it looks worse let's
try this you know what i'm saying so we don't have to keep opening and closing the tab
let's see what that looks like because now i don't have to keep escape just does what
it's supposed to do let's see what the see what i mean how about the text can you guys
read that fine maximum fov looks good okay good all right uh so we're now what how old are we 19
something like that make it a little bit bigger all right you are driving in a car with a friend
when he runs over a dog what wait he seems rather insensitive about it and doesn't stop
the car what the fuck stop stop the car stop the fucking car stop the car he tells you not
to worry about a stupid dog that was running around you stop the car then our friendship is
at stake here he lets the car screech to a stop and says if you want to help that stupid dog
go help it and walk home you motherfucker get out of the car and help the dog your friend
drives away you can't believe how insensitive he is what a jerk no that's fucked up that's
absurd welcome to the wonderful world of major purchases in this icon you will have the
opportunity to purchase the material possessions you have always dreamed of
you can use either cash or our easy to arrange credit program while you're in this icon i will
encourage you to spend spend spend to your heart's content but please note that spending
beyond your means can and in most cases will be hazardous to your emotional and physical health
also keep in mind these ancient words of consumer wisdom caveat emptor in this module
you can purchase several items would you like to make a purchase yeah how fabulous
your salesperson will be bob roberts what would you like to purchase um i want a boat
you can buy three kinds of boats a speedboat a sailboat that sleeps for a motor yacht with
crew 160 000 dollars
instantly i get proof for a loan oh captain moneybags it won't be long before you
own your own ocean to go along with it how would would you like to pay for this with credit your
finance charge is 20 percent of this purchase price this amount will be added to the purchase
price now for the good news you have the rest of the module to pay your credit purchases
will not be deducted from your resources until after you finish the module please make
sure you have enough money to cover your debts by then or your credit rating will suffer
now you'll not be able to get any more credit until the end of the game thank you
for cashing in on this once-in-a-lifetime value come again soon all right so i got a boat get a
loan to purchase a house should i get another loan to buy a house can i get a loan to pay
back that loan i'm gonna i'll get out of debt no i'm out of here how do i use my boat i where's
my boat can i even look at my boat enroll in college choose a major i have i have a
college experience drop out of college i'm not even in college have a college experience
i'm sorry but you will have to enroll in college first all right well let's go
enroll in college what kind of college would you like to attend low admission standards yeah
probably that one you're now enrolled your resources will decrease by a hundred dollars
every time you access the college icon this will cover tuition and college what how much money
do i have all right i have 3500 bucks i have 260 000 in debt and i own a yacht that's all
all right what about this stuff over here welcome to the marriage icon in order to enter
this icon you must first be involved in a steady relationship it's generally considered
good for them to know the person with whom you plan to spend a presumably large portion
of your life and the next one is kids all right let's let's go let's more sex a friend
asks if you would be kind enough to drop off a package of the house of someone he knows
lives close to you well you're gonna you can't tell me that this is a sexual mission
and then give me a random box to deliver uh sure you arrive at the address it is a huge
split level house with a royals royals royce a jaguar and a Porsche parked in the driveway
you ring the bell and an older very attractive woman comes to the door in a sheer negligee
she has evidently just stepped out of the shower you deliver the package in turn to walk
away she asks if you would like to stop in for a drink sit down on the couch and make
yourself comfortable she asks you what kind of drink you would like something with a little
kick something cool something hot she fixes your drink and places it down on a long marble table
as you scan the room you notice expensive looking artwork vases rugs sculptures on every
wall and in every corner she invites you into the adjoining rumpus room the rumpus room
is filled with hunting trophies a lion's head some elephant tusks zebra skin her husband
is an avid lover of the sport but she thinks it's barbaric you finish your drink are we gonna have
like a psycho hunting he's gonna hunt me or something the woman turns to you and in a deep
sexy voice says enough we both know what we want take me it's time to leave you're in no
does she have a lot of money though oh fucking god we've waited four hours we've
waited four hours you barely touch her before she lets out a blood-curdling
and collapses from exhaustion you were the best darling now run along before my husband comes
home what he's insanely jealous and would absolutely shoot us both on sight if he ever
if ever he had a notion of what a wild animal you are just then the door to the rumpus room
swings open a man in a pith helmet and cocky uniform peers into the room he twists his
handlebar mustache nervously but calmly asks what you are doing in his house alone with
his wife in his rumpus room fight for the woman confess tell him you just came to deliver
a package no he's gonna shoot me he will shoot me with a gun i just came to deliver a package
that's what they all say i suppose the package was so heavy it took two of you to carry it
into the rumpus room the man squints his eyes and works himself into a rage a cat scoundrel
leech how dare you attack my innocent wife prepare to meet your maker he races to the
wall and pulls down a double-barreled shotgun the woman screams no my darling i just had all
of the rugs cleaned the cold shotgun barrel presses firmly against your neck click the
lights come on you wake up you've got to stop eating those anchovy pizzas so close to bedtime
it was a fucking dream it was a dream oh my god lately nothing seems to be going right
for you seems as though no one understands you or cares about you people want things from
you but give nothing in return life is miserable and sometimes you don't even feel
like waking up in the morning oh god damn it man not i not this we already had this problem before
i need to go see somebody i need like i need to see somebody like let's go fucking talk to a
professional you know i mean like for real everyone goes to periods like this once in a
while i'm glad you have decided to turn to someone to help you through it who would you
like help from okay this is like the second time that we've had these like thoughts we're
going to go to a professional a professional is likely to tell you that depression is really
anger turned inward there's a common response to loss either in the form of someone moving
away or dying or in the form of a loss of love as in the case of someone who has rejected you
tolerating such a difficult loss can be difficult you may have some sleepless nights problems with
your appetite or you feel just plain lousy you may have to explore past relationships to
discover new ways of coping with or expressing your feelings might take some time but as a
result your overall life will improve do you think you would like to try psychotherapy
um shall we shall we try should we be able to try a wise choice you can see a therapist
behavioral therapist is psychoanalytic therapist um which one psychoanalytic therapist
a boat therapist that's not that doesn't exist that doesn't exist a behavioral therapist a
behavioral therapist a behavioral therapist is likely to ask you to keep close tabs on your
depression by filling out charts graphs or other aids that will make you more aware of the
depression's quantity persistence and the events that trigger it they might ask you to practice
coping statements in response to your depression when your depression has lifted the behavioral
therapist will ask that you maintain records of your mood for a while so that he can follow
your progress you're walking down a poorly lit street late at night when you see a teenage
boy mugging an elderly man oh hey hey what are you willing to do hit the teenager over the
head with something um i kind of do that scare him away you barely take two steps toward the
boring when he spots you approaching and runs away this potentially dangerous experience
ends rather peacefully the old man hugs you lightly he was terrified you're given the
opportunity to participate in a charity fundraiser the proceeds will be used to provide
food and shelter to orphan children okay if you decide to help out even in the most
minimal capacity it will take a large amount of your time and possibly your resources helpful
self-sacrificing i have 260 000 in debt uh help out give a donation don't help no donation
self-sac what is it what how but it was going to do my debt all right what if i
what if i help out i don't know i can't do anything in what capacity would you like to
serve uh play a helping non-leadership role you're asked to handle parking arrangements
for the fundraiser it's not a glamorous job but it is a very important one as a result you
are thanked by the person who organized the fundraiser and given special recognition
at the dinner which follows well done see yawn well i don't i don't have any resources
more sex a bunch of your friends con you into going to a bar that features couch dancing
couch dancing is where a woman clad only in a g-string stands on a couch while you support
her by the ankles once she is in this position she dances for your entertainment
okay after the girl finishes her dance she invites you into the back room for a relaxing
massage it becomes clear that she is a prostitute offering her services ready to go
go
tell her but but hold on ready to go but i'm not going to pay for it i'm curious but not certain
uh can i get arrested curiosity killed the cat but you might not get away with get away
quite that easily you are presented with the following massage options oh my god i don't have
any money what the fuck no no this is the one where you get arrested you get arrested
with this one guys it's not that's why it's 75 dollars because the the cops bust in
curiosity's killing the cat here the masseuse requests that you remove all your clothes
and wrap a towel loosely around your waist you gently
she gently rubs warm oh i can't read this i just i'm embarrassed she begins by making
large swirling motions across you uh on you and she massages you she begins projecting a series
of um slides on the wall in front of you slides what do you mean slides she has a projector
the first slide is the eiffel tower next is the london bridge these are followed by slides
of the empire state building in the hanging gardens of cyprus thank you for taking this
magical massage tour around the world sir please try us again you've been had unfortunately not
in the way you planned damn it welcome back to dos where jerma reads everyone potential erotica
your mother calls to tell you that your father is in very poor spirits lately he's lost his
job that's not good um i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i think it'd be
sad i don't know if you mentioned that that quickly i don't know i don't think you i don't
think i would mention that so quickly here your dad is really feeling terrible he needs all of
the support he can get if you've had a bad time with him before now is the time to forget
it he's just had one of the most dehumanizing experiences life can dish out do you want to
have a talk with him uh yeah i don't know but i'm just saying like this what is the one
thing you would like to tell him that you feel badly for him and hope he gets a new
job very soon that he should try to find work at a more stable field that the most important
thing in life is that he is a great person and that you love him yeah he's a great that's the
one dad looks at you in large tears begin to roll down his leathery face he squints hard
to keep them in but they come rushing down the side of his face in long streams this
might make you feel badly if it does it only means that you are empathizing with him which
makes him feel better am i in college fuck i'm in college choose the following majors
liberal arts natural sciences social sciences business or engineering um business liberal arts
liberal arts business engineering casket making engineering engineering is gonna be too hard
remember i went to a shitty school i went to this like the hundred dollar school
social sciences natural liberal arts business you're almost guaranteed a job when you get out
of school but you may become rigid and materialistic let yourself be free to explore
social and interpersonal relationships while you're pursuing this course of study well
i did buy a boat yeah i can rent out the yacht and have people can have yacht parties for
like five grand a pop i'll pay that back in like less than six months you know the guy
why you didn't think i before i saw that yacht parties full open bar i got a crew that's
like a you can do like a 10 20 30 thousand dollar wedding on there that thing will pay for itself
in less than a year i'm sorry in order to play through this uh vignette you need to have a
steady relationship with a girlfriend fine okay you're trying to move ahead as quickly as
possible in your vocational life but it's rough the more honest hard work you do the
more time you spend spinning your wheels and getting no place fast an opportunity arises
for you to move ahead it comes unexpectedly a highly influential person slips up you could
capitalize on this error and move ahead but if you do this person's life will be ruined
i mean i'm 260 000 in debt i'm sorry i i'm sorry i am like more than a quarter of a million
dollars in debt i i don't know what happened i don't know what why it happened but it's
nothing i can do i'm sorry you are successful the other person is crushed for a while it
looks as if they may even be a your resource column increases by five grand
fuck how much money do i have i need to do that a thousand more times to pay off the boat
no what do my finances look like i gotta pay down my loan right pay back part of your loan
select an action pay back how much money do i have five grand pay back a thousand two
thousand thank you very much what do i get for debt now all right and that look that's not
i'm never gonna pay this off invest i don't i can't invest
two hundred and fifty eight thousand dollars and that was almost all of my money sell the yacht i
can't sell the yacht so i'm gonna impress somebody with that thing at a party you mate a
group of people who are into the artsy side of life they're extremely analytical people who
express themselves creatively some are artists others dancers some self-styled renaissance
people they are apolitical non-materialistic and consider the best decisions ones made on the
spur of the moment they're certainly different i think you guys have any money anybody have
any uh money criticize them bored bored that's a bit on the rude side don't you think
can't do this one right a friend of yours since grammar school has gotten mixed up in a
series of bad deals poor judgments and impulsive harebrained schemes he calls you up on the phone
sounding very desperate and asks you for a loan of five hundred dollars i can't do that i'm sorry
i can't i'm sorry i can't give you any money your friend is crushed now he has to get a real
job you have the opportunity to attend a conference that might provide you with
information that will get you further ahead in your field what do you mean an asshole
why am i an asshole go to the conference the cost of the conference is 500 bucks do you still
yeah i do that's the money i'm investing it in my future because you are strong intellectually
you gain valuable information from the conference your increase in resource reflects the skills
you gained here regardless of what you might have gained or lost intellectually you have
excellent social skills as a result you make contacts that help you along in your profession
your gain in resources reflects this how much did i gain i gained like fucking
not i gained like not even i didn't gain any money one of your friends is getting married
next sunday and you've been invited to his bachelor party the best man for the wedding
has hired a performer for the evening her name is helga the norwegian torch her talent
is taking off all of her clothing dousing herself with a flammable liquid setting herself
ablaze and dancing until the flame burns out what and the most amazing aspect of her performance
is the fact that she damages neither herself nor her immediate surroundings after helga's
performance she relaxes with the people at the party wearing nothing more than a black g string
at various intervals during the night she whispers to a different gentleman at the party leaves
the room with him for about 10 minutes and returns she leans over and whispers in your ear
that she would like to perform a very bizarre sexual act with you imagine the weirdest sexual
thing a person could do while hanging upside down and spinning by the time helga is finished
you don't know whether you are coming or going
three weeks and six shots of penicillin later it's a memory what all right let me learn
something let's have a college experience this episode why does everything have to be sex
i just want to go to college i just want to go to a friend's house i just want to deliver a package
every scenario is like get seduced there is a concert in the student center and you have made
arrangements to go with your friend bobby and his new girlfriend linda you're supposed
to meet them in bobby's dorm room then go with them to pick up your date you arrive on
time but notice that bobby and linda are a bit rumbled in appearance it seems like you
have interrupted a romantic interlude bobby excuses himself so that he can shower and get
ready for the concert linda is still glassy-eyed from tumbling around the room with bobby
there's a moment of uncomfortable silence after bobby walks down the hall to the showers
linda moves close to you and tells you that you have a bad sense of timing
she leans toward you and inquires if you would like to finish what bobby started
this game is fucked why every scenario don't do it don't do it don't do it
linda accuses you of being overly mellow you wonder if bobby knows what he has gotten himself
into no no not that scenario a friend from high school calls you up in a very serious tone of
voice she says she needs to speak with you about something right away her life is falling
apart and you are the only one who can help her um i guess i will sit with that we're gonna
what's what's going on what's happening you agree to meet her problem is that she has just
found out that she is pregnant and is confused about what she should do she can't speak with
her family and her boyfriend has abandoned her what will you suggest to her oh god
what the fuck we have we this is a conversation you go i would suggest we just got you just you
just got into town and i would say maybe you should go and start speak to a professional about
this shit because i don't know does your scenario i haven't probably i haven't talked to you in
a long time you this is this is this is not i i should have just said i should have just
this shouldn't just let it go to voicemail all right let's
a sensitive choice you must have realized that giving anyone such a direct piece of advice on
the matter as serious as this would surely be a mistake if things didn't turn out well she
might hold you responsible unfortunately it is often very difficult to help someone in trouble
sort out his or her true feelings the person may come to rely on your direction she may begin
to lean on you so that you begin to feel responsible for her even though you do not
actively try to give her advice well i don't want to say that a person can resolve a crisis
only by seeking professional help it is often the best way i don't have i need to study
relationship the thought occurs to you that it might be interesting to travel to a far away
place for a little while and experience new things someone suggests joining the peace corps
i think it's gonna take a long time i don't i don't think i would like to do that
uh it's not right for you at this time in life i know it's not right for me to take the
to do this run from your debt peace yacht run from your boat all right let's join the peace
corps a peace corps representative tells you that you would be spending a portion of your
life working in one of any number of settings the task that seems right for you is working
in an agricultural community in an underdeveloped nation there'll be very few any
if any economic rewards as a matter of fact you will probably lose out financially because
of what you could have been earning in a more traditional job in this country during the same
time period what you will lack in monetary reimbursement you will more than make up for
an emotionally satisfying experiences and the knowledge that you have devoted a small portion
of your life to helping others before you volunteer your qualifications would have to be
checked are you interested in joining now that you have decided to join the peace corps
your qualifications must be considered you certainly have the intellectual skills
i'm sorry you really are not sensitive enough to do this kind of work oh fuck come on
what oh they know how sensitive i was what test how do you determine that i need a girlfriend
i need a girlfriend and i need a wife a rich girlfriend by the way kathy bridget carol gg
gail kimberly tony let's say i'm gonna say bridget she's kind of trustworthy she's very
gentle not calm not happy not confident not attractive she's ready to go on a date
let's get this right bridget has a dog named beefcakes whom she loves more than anything
else in the world beefcakes is a presumptuous pet he is fond of removing pieces of your body
that he presumes to be of no use to you what these have included on various occasions
pieces of arm leg toe and whatever else happens to fall into his cavernous jaws
bridget is thankful that beefcake likes you so what do you think about this i should keep quiet
if it ever came down to a choice between me and beefcakes i would be the one in the doghouse
i'm going to poison that animal one day it's just a matter of time i am going to ask that
beefcakes be kept in another part of the house while i am visiting why these are so
this one is so extreme i'm going to poison i'm saying this to her i'm gonna poison that animal
one day it's just a matter of time why would i say that i'm no be quiet wimp by the time
the two of you get serious you may be missing one of your most valuable parts what the
fuck you wanted me to say that i was gonna poison your dog no what while on a date with
bridget you've discovered that you've forgotten your wallet what will you do admit your
embarrassment and ask her to lend you some money excuse yourself tell the story to the restaurant
owner and ask if he will give you an iou excuse yourself drive home or to the bank get money
and come back everything of trying out for the olympic decathlon it's only a few more
events than you've had to perform tonight bridget gets a bit suspicious when she notices
that the car is parked in a different spot than it was before your chest heaving while
you try to catch your breath is very romantic too can i get something to go right here romantically
bridget admits that every so often when the two of you are being romantic she makes believe
that you are a famous movie star how do you feel about this that's fine that's okay that's
fine can you date me can we go steady can you be my wife now actually this is quite
common way for people both men and women to add variety to their relationships without
actively seeking someone new i'm glad you were open enough to accept it now what if
i told you that the name of the famous movie star is flipper i'm just kidding no i'm just
kidding i'll be fucked up all right another good date here we go you are sitting in
bridget's living room the lights are low and the two of you are very cozy bridget begins
to get very romantic and respond in kind she explains that she would really like to make
love with you but doesn't have any birth control what will you do suggest that you
satisfy each other without intercourse run out to the drug store is she going to be mad
about me driving and the car going to be parked in a different place
dude i'm gonna get i'm gonna get fucking flagged for this shit
after 35 minutes of searching you finally find a drug store that is open late you
purchased the condoms and rushed back to bridget's house she's fallen asleep in the
living room it does not answer the door fucking god damn it don't you work at the drug store
yeah when i was like 14 as often happens in relationships bridget begins to gain access to
your personal life want to know what she finds out yeah what what what is it she finds
out that you still play with toy boats when you sit in the bathtub now that's personal
does she know about the real boat that's in the bay that's a quarter of a million dollars
oh that's you really try to fucking stick that into my gut aren't you go steady you and bridget
make a handsome couple okay it's we gotta live together no going to date bridget has an annoying
habit that grates on your nerves i like don't even like this person i just want to get
married whenever you go out to a restaurant she licks her fingers at the table and sometimes
makes loud sucking noises what do you intend to do about this uh gently suggest that she
should be more aware of her behavior leave her alone no it's perfect what a sport you must
really be crazy about bridget just make sure you are always settled seated in a quiet little
nook off in the corner and the two of you will be just fine bridget is gross
here we go while on a date with bridget she mentions that she has been doing a lot of
thinking about what it would be like to be married what do you have to say about this
yes we all have dreams don't we um uh i i what a lovely idea why don't we talk about what it
would be like some aspects of married life are probably really great if you would like the
idea so much why don't you go over to the marriage icon and tie the knot welcome to the
marriage icon while you're in this icon you can make arrangements to plan and enter into
a marriage oh i'm sorry to be so blunt leave a marriage what would you like to do
become engaged how much money do you want to spend on a ring
i'm gonna go to walmart and go to the jewelry section right at the front door
it's been a hundred bucks i'm not fucking who cares oh they like surprises
you remain a mystery to bridget's parents they neither love nor hate you but they are
suspicious because you've never seen to be around now you must pick a way to propose
which will it be on my yacht have the waiter bring the ring as dessert after a romantic dinner
take out an advertisement in the paper take the traditional route and propose on one knee
do it your own way on the boat on the boat how romantic bridget is flattered now for the big
moment you are waiting for her to accept or reject your proposal she accepts your proposal
you're on your way to your wedding day congrats we did it let's get married plan and
have a wedding marriage is a serious commitment one that should last a lifetime are you sure you
can handle this yeah do the two you want a large or a small wedding small okay as long as the
two of you have agreed on it what kind of honeymoon would you like to have small that
sounds nice and what kind of area do the two of you eventually want to live small it's tough
to find a decent place to live these days you know not that you have thought about some
of the major preparations the weeks fly by until your wedding date the time that passes
is crucial and can determine the future success of your entire marriage everyone has their share
of problems during this time unfortunately this includes you too approximately one week
before the wedding the following happens an old girlfriend throws herself all over you
and begs you to run off with her does this make you want to change your mind about the
wedding no no your wedding day seems to be going along perfectly it will surely be a
memorable occasion unfortunately you get into a car accident on the way to the wedding and
have to say your wedding vows in a leg cast why cindy cut your brakes your wedding night comes
and you climb into bed with eager anticipation bridget is in the bathroom getting ready to
join you the door opens bridget slips into bed next to you and cuddles into the bend
of your warm body she seems ah oh i just got like fucking crashed into
she seems peaceful and at ease the two of you relax from the hectic excitement of the day
you both fall asleep tired and exhausted you don't have the typical honeymoon sex experience
the next morning the two of you get ready to leave for your honeymoon
how will you be traveling to your honeymoon
my wheelchair use the boat can i use this is my boat it's a trip to your honeymoon
hideaway is a safe and pleasurable one your honeymoon is peaceful and relaxing
any problems you might have experienced on your wedding night are washed away by the
peacefulness of your surroundings this is the start of a lifetime that will be filled with
many emotions there is love of course but that will have to be tempered with tolerance
after all loving someone who loves you in return is easy tolerating her when she
is moody and irritable is difficult and may mean the difference between staying together
or falling apart admiration will sometimes be offset by petty jealousy desire for
companionship will sometimes be replaced by a need for solitude this kind of talk may
seem premature at this stage of your marriage but within the next two years things will
start to become very difficult why are you assuming this in the next two years two years
i'm still 14 all right i gotta hold on i need to take a second i'm like a giggly mess right
now the newness of the marriage will wear off and you will have to start coming to
grips with the fact that your partner is not as perfect as you would really like
this is not a bad thing but it is reality your ability to adjust to your partner's
strengths and weaknesses and vice versa will ultimately determine the success of your
marriage good luck please check your resource file to see how your wedding gifts have affected
your status all right wedding gifts i'm 27 i'm still a drug store clerk my physical is
terrible calmness is terrible i got money have a child by trying to make you i'm going to
try to make my wife pregnant i'm sorry no luck this time if you want to have a baby
please try again no luck what uh thank you nat nat kitty for the 10 community subs dropping 10
big ones thank you really appreciate it big sub drop thank you so much why jerma please get
a real job you're not a teenager anymore you're married and trying for a child
i'm a drug store clerk i have a job i have seven grand in the bank do i have what's my
count what's my like that's that's not appropriate for stream pay your taxes i did the game pays
taxes fine i'm gonna quit my job career change trying to drop oh fuck i'm still a student in
school oh life is fucking hard how do i have a college experience the student government
organization is gathering to hold a meeting are you interested in running for school office
yes you have just the right max of social skills and aggressiveness to be a confident
school leader your expressiveness characteristic shows that you quickly become a great speechmaker
your thoughtfulness characteristic shows that you attend to the needs of the students well
and have a successful term in office as a result social thoughtful expressive and intellectual
domains all increase let's celebrate we don't live together what are you talking about we're
married buy another vote on a loan just buy like 10 votes i'll be fine full-time job i can do it
i want to do business sales creative health service teacher researcher lawyer creative
congratulations you start working immediately you still live with your parents no we don't
all right i guess let me you're about to spend the afternoon catching up on some work
when your steady partner my wife reminds you of a promise you made to go shopping with her
to pick out a birthday present for her mother you did promise but right now catching up on
your work seems to be a higher priority your partner doesn't seem to understand this she
keeps saying you promised it already happened took three days i'm staying home i have to work
your partner gets very upset at your decision tell her she is not being very considerate
of the work you have to do try to find out more about why she's upset i already know
look i got i got school i got job i'm trying to get a child i got a lot of work to do you're
telling her this because you believe your immediate need to complete your work is more
important than her immediate need to have you accompany her on a shopping trip the real issue
had you taken the time to discover it is the fact that your partner feels that you are not
paying enough attention to her she just wanted to be with you your response to her sounds
hostile and insensitive your relationship will never last if you keep this up
while socializing at a friend's party you run into someone you had a terrible crush on in fifth
grade she looks even better now than she did back then she's with a guy who looks like he
eats apartment buildings for lunch uh no like sociable uh just say hello you are introduced
to duke her date who excuses himself to look for something to eat there's a table full of
food over there that looks unprotected make small talk and excuse yourself bring up the
fact that you had a terrible crush on her why would i do that i'm married you talk about how
things have changed and how everyone has grown up since grade school neither of you has kept
up with anyone the conversation soon runs out of steam and you excuse yourself besides duke is
returning from battle and may still be a bit hungry you never got a chance to find out
that it was she who had an even bigger crush on you yes congratulations the rabbit is dead
what oh your wife is officially pregnant over the course of the next seven months your wife
experiences stressful cramps water retention and nausea it is a difficult pregnancy for both of you
now that you and your wife are well along the way please choose the method of childbirth you
think is best what your wife will undergo hypnosis hypnosis for the natural childbirth
especially with classroom training what would hypnosis do i almost want to click this because
i have no idea what this fucking does i kind of want to do it i'm doing it this choice is
an interesting alternative to the other two not all people can be hypnotized about 20 percent
of us are resistant to hypnosis so there is no guarantee that it will be effective such an
application is quite extreme and is effective on only about 10 to 15 percent of the people
who can be hypnotized for childbirth hypnosis is a realistic alternative for many
the delivery is a difficult one and a cesarean section has to be performed
there are some tense moments during which you must leave the delivery room
you pace outside nervously but soon a shrill cry cuts through the silence of the delivery room
oh my gosh a baby you perform a quick inventory to make sure all the right parts are there
10 fingers 10 toes two eyes a quickly nose oh yes one more thing that part in the middle
let's have a look congratulations mom and dad you are now the proud parents of a bouncing
baby boy over the course of the next two days your wife recuperates from the experience
unfortunately there are some complications with your baby you see the baby needs to be observed
and monitored for the next few days at the hospital just as a precaution although it is a
stressful period for you the result is that the baby is healthy congratulations again here
we go what would you like to name your little boy i put peter jim ned carry bill dick
vincent michael robert john peter i'm seeing a lot of john michael there is no michael peter
john john john why john john peter there isn't michael there isn't michael
michael vincent i like vincent i'm sorry it's gonna be vincent either vincent or peter can
i have two names carry it's gonna be peter vincent or john i think we have to pull this
one yeah we're gonna pull it i don't know imagine having a fucking straw pole to name your child
peter vincent and john or well michael is a good one too there you go new pole what's it look
like why does switch say this is a horror game it shouldn't uh vincent is really really
taken over here okay that's not even close it's gonna be vincent thank you for voting
there's a local blood drive a volunteer asks if you would like to donate some blood
um i'm i'll do it i'm a little squeamish but i'll do it bravo even though you did not really feel
up to it you overcome your squeamishness and give in you lie down on the table and wait for
the nurse to take the blood the nurse is a very thin woman in her mid-30s you notice that
she wears very thick eyeglasses and her hand shakes a bit she smiles at you and tells you
you will only feel a little pinprick you prepare for a short twinge of pain oh she must
be drilling for oil sorry she says as she prepares to go in again oh just a little bit
of trouble finding a vein after what seems like 20 minutes of unsuccessful probing she grasps
she gasped into light oh i just realized i'm wearing my reading glasses no wonder i'll just
put on my working glasses and we'll be fine now all you feel is a little pinprick imagine
sitting 20 minutes in that chair this is i can't do this episode i can i have to be a bachelor
to do that episode how old am i now 33 i got 11 fucking grand this is how old i am now
let's have a family experience there are none of these experiences you can do right now please
try again later you are in a restaurant with three of your friends and it is time to pay the
check the bill is 25 dollars allow another five for a tip it's all about money
generous cautious prudent suggest separate checks wait for someone else to pick up the bill
eventually the guy to your left offers to pick up the tab but then apologizes saying
he doesn't have enough cash he checks the cash here at the restaurant and is told that they
do not accept credit cards everyone must pay for himself your bill is nine dollars you've been
invited to a party at the home of an acquaintance when you arrive at the party you notice that you
and your companion have virtually nothing in common with the other people there
they dress differently they speak differently and listen to a different kind of music
i'm getting old although you are in the same room as everyone else you seem separate from
them you have been there almost an hour and still haven't spoken to a single person
select a mood uh let's get the fuck out of here i guess you feel uncomfortable with the
difference between yourself and the other people at the party you might have tried
getting to know some of them a bit better sometimes it is the difference between people
that make life interesting and exciting what fun would it have been to meet a group of people
who were nothing more than clones of yourself looking in the mirror one morning you rub your
upper lip and imagine what it may be like to grow a mustache yeah sure what kind of
mustache would you like to grow should i have a foo man shoe okay your confidence
characteristic shows that you are capable of enduring the comments that it will make when
you change your looks the more sensitive people say things like have you done something
different with your hair lately the people who aren't as sensitive ask you what that thing
hanging off your face is it's funny the way a man's life is changed just by deciding not to
remove something that he never asked for in the first place and can't help growing
but i made it a foo man shoe you begin to see yourself as a different person more dashing
perhaps or mysterious you look especially classy during that period before you realize
that food sticks to facial hair one evening you attend a show with a piece of carrot
decorating your upper lip that's too bad can we go on a family vacation
vincent has developed the habit of dashing away from you and running toward the street at
full speed you have tried everything to prevent this but nothing seems to work while your hands
are full of heavy grocery bags vincent scoots away from you and nearly gets run over by a car
which swerves to avoid hitting the baby yell at the baby smack the baby on the butt isn't he
like fucking not even two months old all these are bad these are all awful yell vincent thinks
you are playing a game your yelling does little to prevent this from happening again in the
future oh okay it's searching vincent greets you with a tiny box wrapped up in tissue paper
vincent teases you with it for a few moments and wants to you to guess what is inside of it
tell the baby you're too busy well let's play along you make the perfunctory hundred
guesses with no success finally vincent unwraps the present and hands it to you it's a clay
coaster with the words i love my daddy scratched into it a big hug and a kiss from
vincent completes the special treatment you are being given oh you've just passed through
young adulthood what this how old am i am i not how old am i this may have been a life this may
have been a time in your life when family activities took a back seat to establishing
some independence in general your family relationships are good oh fuck physically
you've been not very healthy you have wisely chosen to stay away from drinking and drugs
to a large extent in this phase of life some of the issues you have faced are what crowd of
people to associate with and what material items bring recognition from them somewhere along the
line you may have devoted a portion of your life to a worthy social cause like a charity or
perhaps even the peace corps your social skills are excellent congratulations on your
marriage to bridget now regarding your emotional and personality development how long
do you think you can get away with your untrustworthy style of behavior even though
we all have our secrets you're doing a very good job of keeping your wilder side under control
you seem to be enjoying yourself even though you experience the blues every once in a while
it's nice to see that you are not having a depressed traumatized life your level of
hostility is beginning to turn people away from you you are frequently grouchy short-tempered
any rational you're a pretty jittery kind of person vocationally you are doing well you
certainly have a good head on your shoulders you are not only book smart you also have plenty
of common sense by this time you may have been feeling a bit of pressure to achieve
to achieve get ahead buy a house or possibly even settle down you've gone through quite
a range of experiences already but there is a great deal of more to come welcome to adulthood
life is short the art long opportunity fleeting experience treacherous judgment difficult
that was from the hippopotamus from 460 to 400 adulthood you and the love of your life have
been invited to a dinner party at one point during the night a man whom you both barely
know inappropriately brushes your partner's breast and fails to excuse himself you get
the distinct impression that it was not an accident grab the man physically and demand an
apology walk him over to the corner of the room and politely ask him to watch himself
get the fuck over here and your show of aggression startles the man and everyone else
in the room there is dead silence he apologizes but mentions that he has a mild case of
cerebral palsy in crowded rooms such as this he has difficulty fucking god damn it as a result
he sometimes bumps into people he assures you that it wasn't intentional and offers your wife
a sincere apology hope you take an extra piece of humble pie with your dinner tonight
tiger next time get the facts first 35 married to bridget bad credit rating and stress really high
debt i don't have any debt what happened oh did i default on the loan i still got my yacht
though i have bad credit but i get my yacht still i'm okay that's fine no don't buy you
and the woman of your dreams are taking a weekend trip with jill and mark a couple you
have known for a long time during the trip you notice mark become irritable having loud public
discussions about very personal matters and drinking heavily you're beginning to think
that mark is an alcoholic uh frightened anxious unconcerned concern call mark aside
and try to have a chat have a chat with jill uh oh maybe uh if you talk to jill i'll talk
to jill about it first your sympathy touches jill who has been putting up with mark's
relatively well hidden problem but is reaching the point where she is about to
completely fall apart there are times when mark gets violent goes on drinking binges and
really acts scary she doesn't know what to do what will you advise her professional divorce
professional divorce professional that's uh that's professional help that's out of the question
she says we've already been to three different marriage counselors on the days of the
appointments mark gets his act completely together and the counselor always thinks i'm
exaggerating just to get the attention of my busy husband the conversation leaves you feeling
awkward and uncomfortable fuck how old is vincent you're fiddling around in the kitchen
on a saturday afternoon trying to prepare a snack i'm bored you fiddle after a while you
you lose your appetite and look for something else to do mary lou stoker is a friend of
your closest female companion and a staunch feminist the truth is that she is not a
feminist in the true sense of the word she simply despises and resents men a misapplying
the feminist philosophy needs to suit her needs uh one afternoon you overhear mary lou telling
your lover that he meeting you really doesn't give you that much room to breathe i mean he's
okay considering the rest of the garbage that's out there these days but don't you feel a
little trapped here in the same place day in and day out what do you do together that's
so exciting anyways uh i mean i'm we're just gonna i'm i'm just gonna talk i'm gonna just
talk and we'll talk i guess let's just talk to my wife you know i'm just talking to my wife
that's it what i can't just like i can't like talk to my wife calm and do nothing this
response suggests a great deal of confidence on your part you are absolutely right protesting
too much will prove her point on the other hand not talking about any resentment you
may be feeling can work against your relationship would you like to change your mind and have a
discussion no no i i just want to have lunch oh yeah we just got hit with an okay you are a
loser what i'm just trying to like quell the potential i just want to hang out while searching
to the mail you come across a hand address letter with an unfamiliar return address
you open it and read the handwritten letter inside it the letter requests that you hand
write 10 copies of it and mail them to 10 different people it contains testimonials from
the people who have faithfully performed the task to become the beneficiaries of much good fortune
it reads a woman in paroria after receiving this letter and carrying out the instructions
won two free dinners with every vacation purchased to the maple wood dude ranch and
health camp and a free copy of the jacuzzo illustrated guide to marine life of the dead
sea that she feels was good luck passed on to her by the letter commercially there are
tales of misfortune for those who did not follow the instructions a woman in paroria
after dismissing the letter as nothing but a silly hoax found her longtime friend and pet
wire-haired terrier of 15 years bubba dead of a mysterious and rare canine aging disease
the woman felt that bubba's misfortune was the deadly result of her inability to realize
the importance of the letter at the time i'm going to perform the task a wise decision a
few weeks later you win two tickets to the off-off-off broadway production of the stranger came
in the front door and went out the back door an uproarious adaptation of the widely known book
starring patrick hafford and veronica holhaney and presented in the auditorium of the walt
whitman high school in town all right not a scam that's right am i still in college
college during this phase of life isn't usually your typical fun-loving romp around
campus as in college days of youth during this phase of life attending college means
hard work sacrificing and motivation every time you access this icon the following will take
place your intellectuals field will rise and anxiety will also decrease you will also gain
college credit your resources will decrease by 500 to cover the cost of your education
do you want to continue with this no we're dropping out yeah we're dropping out of college
nothing can i get some more kids no all right let's adopt a kid adopting a child could
be complicated and difficult you must also pass strict screening requirements do you want
to continue yeah let's go i'm sorry you do not meet the requirements for adoption from this
agency thanks for trying taking a job while going to school is likely i don't even go
to school anymore i don't go to school i don't even have a house holy shit you and a close
work associate while we're just living out of the car you and a close work associate have
to take a trip out of town together he is married while the two of you are out to dinner
he mentions that he would like to go out on the town and live it up with a few women going
along with him might mean a profitable increase in your vocational sphere nah
the two of you are like lions on the prowl no i wanted to go out with him and
just stalk your unsuspecting prey there's the quarry two young women in slinky evening
where they are beautiful alluring what the fuck is going on here i don't want to do any
of this i wanted to like just tell i wanted to go out with them what the fuck what is happening
you saunter over to them look them in the eye you are so close you can feel the vibrations of
their hearts their boyfriends arrive you can feel the vibrations of your aching head as they
pummel you into the parking lot asphalt good night i didn't want to even be there i wanted
to just like go out with him i don't know he was going to be a fucking weirdo i thought
we were gonna have some drinks i didn't want to your success in the job market would be
more likely if you moved to the other side of the country that's a lot how do you move a yacht
let's make the move las vegas baby don't you think you ought to have a discussion
with your steady partner about this yeah good she tells you that she doesn't want to go
what will you do tell her she has no choice or give her time to make a decision
i can't get divorced give her time as very consider of you her decision is
even though you are sincere in your desire to get her input on this life change she doesn't
want to leave this whole dilemma has taken so long to resolve that in the process the job
offer expires god damn it i'll give give me another child at a large picnic you and vincent
are asked if you want to join a three-legged race of course we do vincent says i don't want
to be in any dumb three-legged race and that's it fuck i did that when i was a kid didn't i
you got that from me remember i don't want no no don't dump stupid remember i did that there
are none i can't have any more experiences you're in the midst of a very difficult
decision one that has you feeling anxious and confused the thought crossing over a mind that
your father might be able to give you some assistance in coming to a decision let's ask
dad for help you've been able to maintain good family relationships over the years
now you'll begin to see the payoff the bonds you have developed to give you a strong system of
support your dilemma vanishes with some simple wisdom shared with you by your father your life
spheres improve across the board remember i by me and dad we went kind of through our
differences and we bonded again good thing while rubbing elbows with some trendy upwardly
mobile types you're past a small mirror on the surface of which is a line of fine white
powder up it goes is this something you think you would like to do often
i don't think i would like to do this often i don't have any money
be careful the rush may not be worth the consequences i'm fucking 41 come on i need
another kid before it's gonna be too late to have another kid come on how did i pay off
the debt i didn't i i defaulted on the loan and i i no credit i can't get credit ever again
on a warm saturday afternoon a young neighborhood kid challenges you to a strenuous physical
competition what does that mean like a basketball or running and what does that what does that
mean you must be losing it you remember a time when you outran out jumped out hurtled out
boxed and out bragged little guys like him now he's got it over you when the game is over
he puts his arm around your shoulder and smiles what you've given up in victory you may have
gained emotionally you're a good sport okay that's fine i can accept them i'm willing to
accept them you're running a bit late but need to stop at the store to pick up a few things
you absolutely can't afford to waste any time you notice that you have a few too many
items to use the express line 10 items or less at the supermarket there is a teenage
boy working the cash register he probably won't notice if you try to sneak through with a few
items over the limit you notice the cashier counting the number of items in your cart he
is about to say something who doesn't do that who honestly if you have 11 items 12 items and
by the way do the same item count if you've got like eight yogurts in there does that count
as eight different yogurts or can't you just go eight right of course it counts yeah but if
it's the same product you can just go eight and it counts as one everybody does this remain quiet
engage him and i look hey so take your make up here up here hey hey very smooth you have great
social skills so you can employ this tactic he lets you slide through and you're back on time
you're attending the dinner party of a close friend michael lewis and his attractive wife
judy all through dinner judy has been passing admiring glances your way she has commented on
your clothing your jewelry and your cologne michael doesn't seem to mind his wife's
flirtatiousness in the least while clearing the dishes and preparing for dessert judy asks if
you'd like to help her do something in the kitchen the love of your life gives you a dirty
look as you go off into the kitchen i just want to go in here the love of your life
when you are in the kitchen judy mentions that she wonders why mike has kept all of his
attractive men friends such a secret you sense that she is beginning to make her move what will
you do now see you later goodbye i guess she was a bit on the forward side just when you're
about to return she says come on don't be so shy i was only giving you a compliment help me
bring this fruit out to the guests she walks over to the refrigerator and takes out a large
bowl of fresh fruit you guys excuse me she removes a large strawberry and places it between
her teeth letting it disappear slowly into her mouth with a loud
when you return your partner is very suspicious about the sounds she just
heard trustworthiness goes down even though you didn't actually do anything
the love of your life 42 almost 43 you're waiting for some important news that might
drastically affect the course of your life for some strange reason every time you think
happening you get the urge to munch on something all right snack on something to keep occupied
this can lead to disastrous outcomes you gain 10 pounds waiting for the news to arrive
is this is this a willy wonka cartoon or something i don't understand right now 10 pounds
right now am i wearing the boxes i don't understand you've just taken off your socks
and shoes that was even that that were here earlier
you've just taken off your socks and shoes after a long tiring day you would like
nothing more than to begin a nice lazy relaxing evening the clothes hamper seems a mile away
toss the socks under the bed walk over no under the bed i'll bet this is not the first
time you've done this look under there it's a regular sock convention there are some pairs
but mostly it's a singles gathering that's because the bed charges a one sock rental fee
for each sock it shut shelters yes you finally found out where all those socks go how do
you feel about being a little bit of a slob care that's the spirit it's no big deal really
unless of course your wife is a neat nick or your conscious bothers you sometimes being
too compulsive about things can really put a strain on life but then again so can not having
any clean socks to wear that's fine who cares it's about time you had a physical i'm fine i'm calm
i mean i did just gain 10 pounds in one day so i'm terrified go for the checkup there there
i realize it's difficult to go to the doctor but as you know it's really a necessity besides
with all the wonders of modern technology it's much less terrifying than you think the doctor
will see you now the results of your checkup show your checkup shows that you have hemorrhoids
the doctor gives you special suppositories your bill is 200
you begin thinking about whether or not you would like to invest some of your resources so
that you can increase them yes let's make some investments how about that bitcoin how about
that crypto an investment counselor suggests that you look into stock in a multinational
computer software company would you like to take the risk and purchase say a thousand
dollars worth of stock your investment triples why couldn't i have done more i would have
put 10 grand in that shit look at that i would have put like i would put like a hundred grand in
there i still have a yacht god damn it vincent has announced that all of the kids at school
are going to a dance that requires a date will you let vincent attend yeah care to give any
advice to vincent before the big night how old is vincent i don't think i'm going to
give advice i think because instant instant is uh vincent is like 12 no he's like three what
the next day a curious question arises during a conversation between you and vincent can a
girl really get pregnant by kissing vincent's like 13 no he's not let's find out you've
been going through a difficult time with an influential business person who seems to really
enjoy making people miserable with his moodiness his arbitrary decision making and his arrogance
you get called into his office to take the heat for a relatively minor error the conversation
begins look son i've had just about all of the incompetence from you that i can stand
what have you got to say for yourself refuse to refuse to let him talk to you that way
grovel said that he won't fire you refuse to let him talk to you that way what would you
like to say now just wait one minute you add your own expletive i refuse to be spoken to
in that tone of voice don't you think i deserve a chance to explain as a matter of fact no
i don't it's is his reply he continues to chew you out and he finally finishes
is that all no as a matter of fact that is not all you're fired oh it's why what the
fuck the punches and expletives follow fast and furious then suddenly the old man clutches
his heart and he begins to wheeze he slumps over in his chair and passes out cold it looks
like he's had a heart attack you try to revive him but he's a goner the big boss
walks in while you are trying to revive him and believes you were trying to do something
heroic you get a bonus i fucking murdered somebody you've just passed adulthood your
family life's been good i literally got did something wrong at work got called out by
my dickhead boss and murdered him in his office oh my god physically you have not been very
healthy you have wisely chosen to stay away from drinking and drugs that's not true i did
coke like fucking two weeks ago at this stage i did i said yes i want to do it more at this
station in life you have probably chosen to associate with a select group of cohorts
in general your social skills are excellent hope that you and bridget are enjoying your lives
together i haven't even spoken to her she glanced at me when i walked into a room to
talk to some other lady and then i wanted to be spoken now regarding your emotional
and personality development your trustworthiness and sense of fair play are commendable
there have been times however when the fates have tempted you and you've given in come on
you know what i mean killing your boss by punching him in the face you never lost that
youthful zest for life have you unfortunately your walks on the wild side have gotten you
into more than one spot of trouble you seem to be enjoying your life even though you
experience the blues every once in a while it's nice to see that you've done really
having a depressed traumatizing life your level of hostility is beginning to turn people away
from you you are frequently grouchy short-tempered and irrational you're a pretty jittery kind of
person you're doing well despite the day-to-day hassles and problems at work like killing your
boss in his own office you're certainly going to get a head on your shoulders you're not
only book smart but you also have plenty of common sense as you approach the middle years
of life age will probably play a more central role in your experience than it has in your
for some individuals the middle years are a time of depression and regret for others they
mark the beginning of a settling down period of contentment life can always be as rich and full
as you want it to be you might not be able to climb the highest tree in the forest anymore
but now may be the first time that you allow yourself to experience its beauty
without needing to conquer or possess it welcome to middle-aged adulthood are you still
a cashier at a pharmacy yes and i think i'm also still in college biography should be
written by an acute enemy okay 45 let's go sexual matter more like long-time friends
at old high school romances that are like will you have sex with me god it happens every time
a long-time friend and confidant tells you that he is having an unusual sexual problem with
his wife it seems that he can no longer get or maintain an erection like he used to
oh yeah yeah uh this is middle-aged uh sympathetic tell him to see a doctor tell
him not to worry about it tell him that's life uh go see a doctor if you he returns to tell you
that the doctor told him that he has problem that his problems might have been caused by the
high blood pressure medication he's been taking he feels relieved now there's only one small
difficulty you notice that you're having the same type of problem what will you do the doctor
gives you a checkup and tells you that there is nothing wrong with your system anxiety can
certainly affect sexual functioning perhaps when your friend told you that he was having
difficulties it made you so anxious that you developed some of your own okay so we're good
to go you need to talk to someone about a finance related matter the person with whom you
are dealing has a reputation for being a stern pragmatic and very money conscious business type
a meeting between you and this person is suggested the outcome of such a meeting
can affect your vocational spirit tremendously because he is very influential
confident very competent suggest a breakfast meeting you're obviously tuned into certain
business trends breakfast meetings are indeed becoming more popular because they are less
likely to involve drinking and other kinds of extravagant behavior this can keep expenses down
and with sharp your confidence characteristic shows that you can keep a level head at such
meetings you have this in your favor your intellectual sphere is strong which will help
you make smart decisions during this meeting you're strong socially this is crucial part of
impression formation as a result you have a strong advantage and just suggested the result
of your meeting is that your resource is increased by twelve thousand dollars played
that perfectly small two-bedroom cape cod condominium townhouse a large nine-room colonial
an estate with stables and servants you would need a down payment of two hundred and
fifty thousand dollars and legal fees of twelve thousand i'm sorry you don't have
enough money to put a down payment on this house please try again after you have
regained more get a loan i need money how do i gain money i need more money you've seen your
friend john and his wife marcia socially for a long time a very peculiar relationship marcia
insists on controlling every aspect of john's life one day when you were talking to john he
confesses that about three years ago he began seeing another woman one who was beautiful kind
gentle and loving he's been thinking about leaving marcia for this other woman but it's
unsure if he can i don't know if i can answer this no no i i'm sorry i this must have been a
difficult decision giving him advice would be taking responsibility for a decision that he
alone should make stepping aside might distance you from your friend for a while but in the
end it is worth it i need a better job taking a job while going to school no i just
killed somebody for better pay no lately you've been feeling sharp twinges of pain localized
in the stomach the pain arrives about an hour or two after eating but disappears completely when
you put something into your stomach we're going to go to the doctor your concern is justified the
doctor tells you that you have developed an ulcer right now the ulcer can be treated with
some antacids and other medications by rest and relaxation by avoiding stressful situations
whenever possible will you take the doctor's advice yes eventually you recover okay okay
we're good as you advance vocationally you must leave your old responsibilities to various different
people on your next move forward you are notified that a woman full of new ideas techniques and
strategies is about to fill your old position she will not be placed without your approval
you interview her for the position and she comments that while she feels you did a good
job where you were she plans on doing a better one she sees her skills in that area
that you are about to leave as limited and old-fashioned due to no fault of your own but
times are changing you know you're asked to give you a reason for not hiring her you say
i just don't like her she's too aggressive she's about to ruin all my good work she talked a
bunch of shit about me where where's like the i i talked shit about everything you did
she's gonna ruin my work to the people around you your behavior though calm suggests that you
are reacting to her personally and not considering what someone with her energy
could actually accomplish you're asked to reconsider but your decision will be final
what do you do did you come into an interview and you say i'm way more skilled than you
i'm better than you and i'm going to do a much better job than you ever did
okay thanks against your better judgment you recommend that she is hired within two months
there is a massive revolt among the people she supervises what will you do now chat what
will you do now chat i look over here and i say hire hire hire and then everyone's like
oh my god this is awful during your talk you mentioned that she may be coming on too strong
with people she completely disagrees stating that with any reconstruction there is going to
be some initial tension and resistance get out of here she's talking like she's talking like
comic book villain here you must be thinking that you should have stuck with your original
decision warning more sex a teenage girl named kathy reinhardt works at the dry cleaning store
that you use one evening you arrive at the store just as it is closing you absolutely need
the clothes tonight kathy is already out the door because you know kathy by name and because you
also know that she is friendly you feel sure that she will reopen the store and get your
clothes you drop off your clothes the next morning and the girl behind the counter
apologizes for not being able to help you shrug it off politely 51 i need another child
come on rename vincent and pretend he's another kid i really wanted another
baby you're dave now at a carnival a friend tries to convince you to have your cards read by
madame natasha a psychic medium skeptical but let's go see the medium you step inside a
dark room a medium natasha looks more like large natasha and fills most of the space
you notice that she has a kind face and a gentle voice the fee for a reading is 50
uh kesh only please what is kesh only kesh only please darling what is this
natasha asked us you want to continue oh yes i thought you were skeptical oh well it's your
money that was like the devs internal monologue thank you darling now let us see hmm these
forces of evil they are very very powerful they're in need think big spell this spell
will rid you of them for a long time the cost of such a spell is minimal 500
dollars all materials included compared to the havoc caused by the absence of the spell
are you willing um 500 bucks
a very wise move darling you must trust that i will rid you of these voices that will destroy
your happiness and remember darling money is the root of all evil so hand it over after you
pay madame natasha an additional 500 dollars she waves her arms in the air and puts herself
in a trance make the voices disappear and bring the next sucker i mean customer in here
thank you darling have good luck 54 i gotta have another fucking baby 32 000 dollars
you wake one morning and in the confusion of being still in the days you remember
this is vincent's wedding day well look at the link hold on hold on what what link
i don't even know vincent had a girlfriend what is this link what do you mean i can't adopt a
child the ss cindy oh i have i still have a fuman shoe you're right why are my eyes all
fucked up uh by the way i oh the cocaine right um so vincent's getting married i just
woke up in a daze you're hurrying to get ready making sure all the last minute arrangements
are made the ceremony is truly heartwarming my children do grow up fast as you watch your
handsome son walk down the aisle your chest swells with pride a few more steps and he'll be
on his own for a moment you are filled with overwhelming sadness suddenly you begin to think
about the pattering of little feet running around the house again a whole new generation
of blessings to come you say the word grandpa to yourself not thinking about the age associated
with it just the two words grand and father and regular father it got me thinking you know
i really okay congratulations the rabbit is dead your wife is officially pregnant over the
course of the next seven months your wife experienced stressful cramps of water retention
and nausea it is difficult pregnancy for both of you now that your wife are well along the
way please choose the method of childbirth you think is best uh still got it still got
it like 58 like 60 hypnosis give her the drug she's 55 or whatever she is all right
anesthesia some people are a bit timid about more natural forms of childbirth this procedure
is slightly more risky the delivery is a difficult one a necessary instruction has to be performed
there are some tense moments during which the you must leave the delivery room you pace
outside nervously but soon a shrill cry cuts to the silence of the delivery room
a baby you perform a quick inventory to make sure all the right parts are there
ten fingers ten toes two eyes a crinkly nose and yes one more part let's have a look congratulations
mom and dad you're now the proud parents of a bouncing baby boy over the course of the next
two days your wife recuperates from the experience the next few days pass without
a problem the baby is healthy and alert 57 that happened at 57 name that baby boy what
was in second place peter everyone's vincent vincent too i just want to relive the last 20 years
that's fucked up you and a group of friends are sitting around discussing people that you used
to know seems that an oddball acquaintance of yours who became a recluse always holed
up in his workshop has just invented a pocket golf ball washer that has earned him a large
fortune after making all of that money instead of retiring he has chosen to donate it to a charity
for homeless inventors and is now back to work sure enough just two weeks after his discussion
he shows up at a social function naturally everyone who speaks with him has a remark to
make about his behavior eventually he wanders over to the group of people with whom you are
having a discussion say something supportive about something that they've done in a quiet
voice he asks if he can speak to you privately about something yeah yeah let's go he thanks
you for the kind words and mentions that he realizes everyone around him thinks he's a nut
you've never really heard him talk at length but you find out that he really doesn't care
what other people think and never did he has a very enjoyable life on the whole it seems that
he needs five thousand dollars of seed money to get his newest project going a scheme to
invent a trash compactor that converts garbage into an energy product that can heat your home
if you invest the money you will receive half of all the profits that the project generates
yeah the project is a success you earn a total of fifty thousand dollars
fifty grand that's the most money we've ever seen i'm 59 how much money do i got
68 000 dollars that's enough to retire no it's not not even close how old am i 60
that's enough money to have another baby let's do a family experience there are none of
the i can't what i just had a baby what are you talking about time for two yachts whatever hair
you have left is rapidly turning gray you've made it what do you mean get my hair dyed that
get my hair dyed after you get your hair dyed you realize it makes a remarkable difference
you take some ribbing from your friends but just as many people compliment you on how young
you are looking do you feel less depressed yeah sure go there and knock them dead like
you did your boss imagine if it said that you've just walked into a store and there is
apparently no one around to take your order it seems that the person who should be waiting on
you has stepped out of sight for a few moments waiting in the store with you is a teenage boy
about 16 wearing an old t-shirt and a pair of blue jeans he must have arrived a few seconds
before you he's tapping his foot lightly to the sound of the imaginary rock and roll band
playing in his head the proprietor steps out from the room at the back of the store makes
eye contact with you and says may i help you can wait am i concerned about the boy in the store
now there's a boy in here he's i don't know what he's doing in here
oh does god place my order did you realize that the boy in the store was ahead of you
yeah what i mean that what reason do you have for not mentioning it yeah only the two of
you were in this you figured you were lucky to be called first i don't know their privileges
with age yes that's one way of rationalizing your behavior that you would probably be the
first one to complain if a youngster person weren't showing you the courtesy you think
you deserved how would the younger generation understand courtesy if not by example if he
had taken your turn you probably would have put up a big fuss your car has to be taken
in for some minor repair work the work will not cost you any appreciable not a lot of
money but it will be an inconvenience since you i have a car um do i have a car when did
i get a car my yacht i got to drop the car off of the shop early in the morning and rearrange
your usual travel plans you call in to make an appointment and the service representative
tells you that repairs are made on a first come first serve basis and i'm an elder
i don't need this if it isn't major you can probably live with it right wrong clank clank
grind sputter cough silence your car is no longer among the living towing repair and
service charges of 500 that's great some backbreaking labor has to be done in your
home over the next few days the chore is unpleasant but important no one who lives
with you is willing to help to just pay somebody you're determined to avoid this
kind of strenuous work at this point in your life and why not you have quite a
bit of money stashed away you can afford it after all you can't take it with you
the cost of the job is 1200 that's a lot of money that i'm gonna do that's too much
snap you did it all right something in your shoulder just did something you don't think
shoulders are supposed to do your arm is hanging down at your side taking an unscheduled
vacation from further work you could have avoided all this but now is no time for lectures you
have to go to the hospital the doctors say you have torn some ligaments in your shoulder
you'll have to take it easy for the next few weeks physical spirit drops markedly
62 jesus what happened to my money what happened to my money i had 68 000 that didn't cost like
30 grand give me a break what during a quiet time you begin to reflect on your life your
accomplishments and the people around you to whom you have formed attachments you've lived
the majority of your life and now seems a good time as any to take inventory as you look
around you find that there are those much younger than you who have accomplished so
much more you friends who have beautiful wives in large vacation houses in the country you know
people who have grown up to be great thinkers and scientists there are people living who
have made great contributions to society but do they have a yacht no that's right i'm fine
you must be either quite healthy or you are resistant to facing some of the typical worries
associated with this time of life in case you are interested some of your friends are
finding themselves terribly ambivalent about their lives right now they're experiencing mood
swings bouts of guilt shame anxiety panic since you are not experiencing any of these
it would be inappropriate to offer words of encouragement i hope your outlook remains this
positive throughout the rest of the game while you are on a sightseeing cruise you hear a
cry and see a small boy fall over the railing into the water there doesn't seem
to be enough time to call for help because the boat is moving too quickly jump in the
water after the kind of calmness this situation requires is not in your personality
fuck instead of acting calmly you expend energy trying to keep yourself calm and
neglect the situation at hand panic does have a purpose it mobilizes the body and prepares
for an extreme situation this would have been a much better response your concern with
keeping calm interferes with your ability to help the boy you both drown the game's over
what no no no no i was so close to being old no no no why did i jump in after him
god damn it 63 years old no oh it's so painful to see that i had 36 grand i had a yacht no debt
no you rip out from under the water oh that was close that was a close call
out of my 65 i quit my job how much money do i have i don't have any kids anymore a young man
walks up to you in the park and looks you square in the eye have you got a dime he says
sure take it you reach down into your pocket and slowly sort through the loose change
it's getting hard to discriminate the sizes and shapes of the coins these days
you finally find one that feels like a dime you reach out and hand it to the young man
who looks at you quizzically the time the time he keeps saying your hearing is beginning to go
quantum immortality the thought occurs to you that it might be economical practical
and convenient to putter around town on a small motorcycle yeah
yeah everyone thinks you're a bit off your rocker but you think it's really great
on the way to the market one day you notice that there is a flat stretch of open road just
waiting for you to tear it up will you twist that throttle to the max yeah that
that that that that that did it did it did it rumor the speedometer hits 40 50 60
siren loud whale interrupts your moment of glory you get pulled over excuse me sir you were
doing 70 in a 55 mile zone the young policeman says try to talk my way out of it you still
have it you sly fox the police officer gets a kick out of you you tell them about some of
your wilder days as a youth as you pull away from the police officer you can
i'm old who fucking cares a group of men are getting together and forming a softball league
called the senior sluggers in order to play in this league you have to be 65 or older
the idea seems like a worthwhile way of getting exercise yeah let's do it okay the rules of
being in this league are as follows no sliding underhand pitching only every player in the league
must dress in full uniform for every scheduled game what position would you like to play
pitch at the spirit you try out for your position and make the starting team in the
ninth inning high pot fly is hit directly to you you thrust out your glove in an attempt
to feel the ball the excitement of the play fills your whole body the ball thunks
solidly into the glove knocking you off balance your heart is beating furiously from the thrill
of making the play you feel happy and carefree just like a child again suddenly the field begins
to fade and turn black the last thing you see are players from both benches running to greet
you for making such a great play something's wrong you can't run toward them your body
and hands won't respond to your wishes but instead of feeling frustration you feel great
peace how you only wish you could have said goodbye i'm dead again it's about time to get
a medical checkup i'm calm let's go to the doctor perhaps you have the philosophy that
staying alive long enough to live for another checkup is proof of another battle one the
doctor is young and intelligent looking he checks your eyes your tongue your heart your
limbs it seems to be a slight difficulty with your heart the doctor would like to admit
you to the hospital for some tests once in the hospital the tests show that you are
experiencing some minor respiratory problems due to old age your doctor prescribed some
light exercise to help build up your heart and lungs just make sure it's not softball
or you'll die the community council is searching for a senior member of the community to help
fund sponsor and direct a community art auction for the benefit of some local charities the
project leader will have to donate about five thousand dollars in resources i don't have that
money i'm sorry too bad there's a real need for someone to interview and choose three nude
models for a figure painting exhibition that was to be part of the auction you want to yeah
okay fine i'm sorry that job has already been taken by mr maxwell he's the guy over there
with his great big smile on his face surrounded by beautiful women oh watch while you're turning
the pages of a newspaper one morning you notice that your fingers feel stiff there's sharp pain
shooting up the backs of your fingers and hands go to the doctor the doctor tells you
that the stiffness in your joints is arthritis it will affect you most when the weather is
or when you have just awakened in the morning there's nothing that can cure it
but sometimes aspirin helps this kind of ache is something that will that you will have to
tolerate almost every day now 66 still go back to college god damn it do i even have a job
i'm retired you wake up as you have gotten used to waking up slowly and carefully and
prepare to face the day cheerful try to do something constructive that sounds like
a terrific idea what will you try to do some gardening gardening gives you satisfaction and
helps you to relax your chillfulness and good attitude radiates to everyone who passes by
you are an inspiration to others you've just read an article in the paper about the importance
of making out a last will and testament and pondering the article you wonder if you should
do yours let's do it now's your chance to get even right just kidding who is going to
get your major possessions car house money etc you don't have any children so oh yeah
this is the quantum other quantum person you're waking up you're walking up the front walk when
suddenly the phone rings you've been expecting an important call and this could be it exciting
hurry up the stairs and slip and crack your head open take your time you have made an
inappropriate what nonchalant take your time you take your steps one at a time with a
short rest after every third step you've learned to do things in this fashion by now
individuals who survived this long have developed an adaptive style of living
emphasizing safety and control i'm 66 not 86 you get to the top of the stairs and the phone is
still ringing you must search for your keys unfortunately by the time you get through the
door the phone stops ringing if it is that important they will call back hillary georgia
bonnie bob bonnie she's trustworthy she's gentle she's calm she's happy she's just not that
attractive that's okay you meet bonnie in the following way she shops in the same super
bucket as you you will get in the same noodles and she's not interested i don't even work
i'm getting married and have another kid linda is there anybody did bridget on this list
hillary oh linda okay we got a date let's go on a date linda has decided that she
wants to take you on a surprise date yes linda drives you way out into the country
to the small airport did you know i belong to a flying club she asks linda is proud to
inform me that she is a licensed pilot she tells the manager of the flying club to get
nosedive her out for a flight and back slowly back to the car i need it i need it
the two of you are handed crash helmets the manager of the flight club carefully
points out the location of the parachute and whispers make sure you strap yourself down real
tight pop she's quite a pilot once you get in the plane you observe that linda really seems
to know what she's doing she's rather interesting your confidence and linda grows by the
minute until she takes out the flight manual and mumbles i think you're supposed to push
the wheel forward to go down back to go up oh what the heck i'll find out soon enough
she's out shouts okay copilot say your prayers we're going to meet the lord what
okay all right what the fuck i should have went back to the car you need uh let's relax
now for some fancy flying linda turns the plane upside down and does a barrel roll just
like the flying tigers she's a bit of trouble getting the plane back of course but after a
quick consultation with the flight manual the plane is fine just when things have calmed down
she flips the autopilot switch and turns to you with a funny look in her eye
evidented 10 000 feet you are certainly an adventurer the cabin space is tight
but you've got to admit it is different next week skydiving
all right let's start a steady relationship you and linda make a great couple now let's get
married how much money do you want to spend a hoot none give her a fair family heirloom
your family doesn't own any heirlooms oh fuck 100 bucks two no 500 dollars that's worth it
i can't afford a ring like that how much money i don't have i don't do i have 100 bucks
i don't even have 100 dollars why do i not have 100 bucks i'm 72 come on how much money
do i have five dollars what i have to get a job apply for a full-time job uh i want to go
into labor too
no part-time job i need to make 100 service delivery you don't have any qualifications
what the fuck why am i so useless anything just anything anything i can't do anything
sales creative creative you don't have the qualifications to be creative i need to make
100 bucks entrepreneur time for another checkup some people simply yeah you were bored some people
simply never get over the fear of having to go to the doctor regularly it's better to be afraid
and go than to avoid it he asked if you have any complaints these days i coldness in the hands
doctor checks your heart and blood circulation he would like to have you admitted to the
hospital for tests tests show that you are suffering from some minor circulatory problems
given some medication which helps how old am i 75 how much money do i have how do i make money
can i do anything for money alone personal loan i will not live to pay it back who cares
thousand dollars ask some kids for money i don't have any kids this i died already
what about credit watch can i can i give her a watch instead just buy my three votes on
credit and die why would they give me all this stuff and i can't even get a thousand
dollar loan from the bank there's tons of cars you can buy let's get a luxurious prestige sports
car what's the most expensive thing i can buy well i have assets now right so can i go get
a loan now if i have a million dollars in assets isn't that collateral for the bank
just trade debt back and forth so i have i have a million dollars in in fake assets
right i'm 78 uh 810 thousand dollars in assets that let's see can i get a loan now
i just need a thousand dollars come on this is death that's a sunset i don't want to click
that one yet on occasion you must rely on public bus to get to and from the places you
want to go today the bus is particularly crowded and you have to stand you find an open area
toward the back of the bus where there is room to grasp a strong steel pole that extends from
the floor of the bus to the ceiling your fingers wrap around the pole tightly a fall could mean a
broken hip or worse as the bus moves the shock of the gentle bumps is absorbed by your feet
knees and legs there is some discomfort as a result you lean forward slightly so that you
can take some of the pressure off your lower body your back then begins to ache a little
girl with chestnut hair and freckles about eight years old has been watching you wide-eyed
for the past five minutes not long ago her mother whispered something in her ear to which
she looked up at you frightened and shook her head no after watching you a bit longer she gets
up from her seat brushes it off with her tiny hand and steps aside motioning you to sit down
thank you for the seat you are such a lovely lovely little darling you realize that accepting
the seat is a sign of neither personal nor emotional weakness is a simple fact of life
this child is young and in any way stronger than you she doesn't need the seat as you sit the
relief spreads rapidly through your body though soon your joints will begin to stiffen in this
seated position the child is looking at you with great relief on her face i need to get
married can't she pay for the wedding no nope a group of men are getting to the softball
league no bored don't join the team older folks get bored with life and just wait around
to dive wow they believe that actively fun and enjoyment are just for the young ones this
is unfortunate and activity is probably one of the biggest causes of depression among older people
the other option is i die if you don't do anything you won't interact with anyone
this brings on loneliness and depression take a few more risks get out there and live a little
and die and don't live and die at the same exact crossroads here i'm not playing softball
there's only like nobody's gonna walk up to me and like hand me like a hundred dollar
bill or something while you're sitting quietly at a party you notice a very pretty very
slim young woman in a short skirt bend over to pick something up she has dropped on the floor
would you like to change your mind no i don't want to change my mind i want to live while
driving the car one day you notice that the turns seem particularly sharp and treacherous
your reflexes are not good enough to keep up this kind of speed your car begins to swerve
out of control and skins off the road your car wow uh your car hits a tree and you
strike your head against the windshield you begin to bleed you're taken to the hospital
but do not recover oh fuck off why wouldn't you slow down because it's inevitable i can't do it
i can't i don't i had a five dollar bill in my pocket oh yeah let me just see hold on
i have one question just one simple question what is the end here what is this how i'm like
65 can i actually just skip to the end of this game after a long but very relaxing day with a
deep sigh you climb into bed and sink into the warm cushiony fabric as you drift off feelings
of intense serenity and well-being overwhelm you pleasant images of childhood visit with
sweet memories of mom and dad school and growing up the memories flash by your mind's
eye was startling reality the smell of school on your first day the outfit your very first
girlfriend wore on your first date you recall places you haven't visited for years in picture
perfect detail friends and neighbors who have gone on greet you they're filled with excitement
to see you though you soon realize they are not communicating their joy in words it's almost
as if this will go on forever okay there's that we got our closure we got our closure
we didn't like drive into a tree and i had 140 dollars too there you go
um could have bought a ring could have oh that's it i did it we kind of frankenstein the end
together but i technically made it to like 63 65 thank you for uh for experiencing this with me
this was alter ego that was fun that was interesting it's kind of all over the place
in a way but 1986 you didn't even become god emperor died to softball well i died i jumped
into the ocean to try to save somebody and we both died that was great died as you lived on
your yacht you killed somebody i yes i punched somebody in the face and instantly killed him
i know i did but hey what do you want me to say i won't i look i tried to do my best
but uh i'm gonna call it here i think that this is a good place to stop my voice kind of needs a
little bit of rest so this is where we are going to end for tonight i think like six and a half
hours is a good stopping point only one game we beat the whole we did the whole thing but that
was fun that really was and i am so happy that this we can just do this all the time
i got sucked into this one but i think for good reason so don't worry we will come back
to this we will do more we're going to do this probably every saturday or at least like every
week just in case you know streams don't line up correctly right there's so much personality
in these games there's so much stuff to do there's so much interesting things to see
so we will be back to ms dos i will do it again i will continue to do it we'll make
it a thing but that is going to be it for tonight i will see you tomorrow for salmon max
episode seven max season two episode three and episode four so i'll see you guys tomorrow for
salmon max if you take it off see you soon maybe tomorrow yeah this really is 700 000 games and
most of them are actually fun and cool so thanks for joining me thanks for experiencing
this game this alter ego by the way i think there's a bunch of different versions of it
you can play it yourself see if you get a different uh outcome but that is the end of
tonight's broadcast we're gonna do the bits from earlier but first i am actually going to
go pee one more time and we'll come back and we will do the bits and subs see and i'll put the
brb up just because i just want to get some more water my throat's getting a little dry
i will be right back did i startle you startle startle you all right let's go back to earlier
just about six and a half hours ago we have multi trip for 250 thank you multi trip mario
is gonna put this on the four of a kind line i already won the mario yatsi championship
and i kicked the shit out of him and go fish remember but thank you uh yenwen yenwen thanks
for the 250 uh i believe this will you get an image here let's see what it is let me know
let's see let me see this is a message hey germa long time no see uh it's been a while
since i haven't sent anything to tell you the truth i haven't had much time to watch
your streams uh lots happened in a short span of time a month ago i decided to move to
germany for a couple months to learn the language within the week i was packed and
flying out on a new adventure damn that's fucking pretty cool man holy shit i've been
learning german for about a month now i think i've come a long way i barely knew the language
in the first place i can understand a handful of words and phrases see i look let me tell
you something i completely admire anybody and respect anybody that can do that i can literally
go to another country and just throw yourself in there and just learn everything i would never
be able to do that i would be so i would be like i don't understand i'm scared we need
a height check hold on what are you talking about and height check get out of here i'm
like in the middle of talking i'm a little bit of doing like a message you want like a
height check but anyways uh they said that you can you can introduce yourself if you want to
uh it says hello itch hi germo why gets hello it high so germa
if it gets did i do it right did i say it no
i tried you said that you were no i did not that's not what i said
but uh you move to the eu means your stream times have started around 1 a.m.
so i haven't been able to catch them uh and they said do you know a second language
i do not know a second language at all but there are a couple of images here
and this is look at this shit this is fucking insane can i like show this on stream i don't
know how to show this can i just save it i think so uh kim is vietnamese she tried to
teach me vietnamese a long time ago but it didn't really stick that well unfortunately
not really but here take a look at this this is a gif is it can i not show this
why is this not i don't know why i can't show this no why don't do this to me right now i'm
trying to fucking show this where the hell even did the save to why save the desktop
why is it saving like a random ass folder but here you go that is a time lapse of the cry
out of context is just me crying that's really fucking good though
thank you for the amazing image i'm just gonna keep let's put it right here it's my always
constantly evolving face there's another one too hold on let me see what this one is oh my god
this is fucking ridiculous how do you do this look at this one i'm just gonna put a bunch
of images on the screen oh my god look at the resolution holy shit that's like this
it's this shit is next level thank you yeah win 4k that's my new desktop background my
deep thought face but that's fucking awesome thank you so much again and seriously good luck
in germany i let me check the rest of the message there yeah how long you're gonna be
there for you're gonna be there for a long time if i had to learn a language though what
would i learn for a language i don't know i feel like i would want to learn a language that
i don't know a place where it wouldn't something that's completely different but it's also harder
to go completely different right that's a good question what language would i want to learn
russian's pretty different vietnamese yeah maybe i don't know maybe like japanese
maybe yeah russian's really different i don't know latin but thank you again yen win creepy
teeth thanks for the five dollars thanks for streaming today today is my last day at home
because i'm shipping out to special forces boot camp next weekend please wish me luck
good luck to you i wish you all the best yeah good luck take care of yourself hope to see
you again very soon thank you creepy teeth for the five dollars also we had two uh 250
from atri looks atrix with the 250 chat is going so fast recently how do you keep up
or if you can't keep up do you wish you could yeah i mean it can be hard but you just
you get used to being able to see you get used to being able to see um you know one guy pick it
out a lot but at some point you do kind of have to just find something stuff pops out to me for
some reason though i don't know why but yeah i know it could be difficult but it's not
i i love it though i love just the the constant speed it means that people you guys
are talking and engaged with the stream and i would i would be less happy if there was
nobody talking right you know if it was just silent in here i thought a lot of a rank a
rambunctious community is an engaged community isn't it we're all having a good time at the
same time it's good that's the kind of fastness that i want that's right but thank you oh no i
see what you're doing uh a triple a triple zero neo thanks to the 250 you've now gained by
i hope you're happy about yourself didn't you ever see liar liar tim carey goes up on a whole rant
about it watch that movie it should be put into the library of congress uh dark soul five
community subs earlier coal rg five community subs earlier thank you both of you dingus thanks
for the five subs no five not five subs five dollars 500 bits thank you though thank you
dingus sticks renegade thanks for the 250 you had a cool moment today i met another germa
fan in person by chance he was wearing the glue man shirt and i was wearing the planet shirt
really i'm pumped if you hear this message fellow germamite it was a pleasure to meet you
that's awesome you're both wearing the the shirts by the way exclamation point shirts if
you didn't know there's a permanent store there now that must have been interesting
because the chances of that they're not they're not ridiculously low but they are low they're
very low think about how many people follow this channel and how many people are on earth
that's pretty low chance to actually run into those people right in the same community at
least three six billion out of seven billion yeah no it's i've run into people randomly before
that wasn't when not at a convention it was like holy shit small world it was cool but
that's really awesome hopefully did you guys exchange like gamer tags what do you do what do
what do we do now twitter profiles gamer tags discord and names thanks for the 250 though
thank you definitely for the 250 germa you should play real lives it's a simulation game
where you live as a person from any country and have to see how this person's life turns
out while you make the decisions really real lives i'm gonna have to check that out that
seems really interesting it's amazing all right i'm i'll look it up peaceful hailey thanks
for the 250 hey jeremy haven't watched you in a little while now trying to focus on myself
which i believe everyone should do from time to time stay away from the internet and all
anyways hope all is well with you hope you had a good time with the stream tonight
i haven't gotten a gig yet with the voice acting but i won't give up i'll keep you
updated if i ever do get anything much love please do and yeah you've you gotta you gotta
take care of you you gotta spend the time necessary to take care of you specifically
look for real lives 2007 okay why that particular version i mean reason why but yes i do i do think
that sometimes and i do it too pull out a little bit detach yourself from the internet
go do things work on yourself you know there are you've seen periods where i just
you know disappear for three four days a week straight two weeks straight
yeah i think you have to do it you have to keep yourself sort of grounded and check and
take care of yourself i do agree but thank you so much for the 250 and good luck again
on uh the voice stuff smelly boy thanks for the 250 this was profoundly depressing it and i'll
feel bad as i try to get to sleep tonight germa jex germa jex 2 there were a few there were
a few points in this game where i was getting close to turning the car around but i think
it was still interesting to play the whole thing a few mr comcast is here for three dollars and
fifty cents what's going on john comcast just letting you know that the game is making me
feel sad seeing how your character grows up has made me realize that i've taken the life
i've been given for granted pushing away friends and family just to make a shitload of money
and for what at the end of the day i may be sitting on a throne of gold but i'm sitting on
it alone in fact the only reason you had internet problems was so you could go and
spend a few hours with friends and family wait what thank you john comcast uh thank you leftist
garfield for the 250 i thought you said you weren't going to play any porn games in the
ms dos website yeah it wasn't a porn game it was just a heavily pornographed sexualized
handful of experiences that i took very carefully cautiously oh thank you yeah handful
yeah it was a hey if it wasn't that many but thank you to harvey two cents for the ten dollars
ten dollars from harvey two cents did not give two cents you gave
ten dollars just getting this in before midnight because it's my birthday and i'm treating myself
to some bits thanks for all the great streams i always give you something to look forward to
well happy birthday what time is it right now is it what what before midnight you on
eastern happy birthday it has to be right happy birthday harvey two cents thanks for
sticking around thanks for hanging out glad you are having fun here deva kitty thanks for the 250
game sucks game sucks germa son game sucks i think the game was fun i think the game was
worth playing i think it was a cool game it was interesting but thank you but thank you thank
you lula more lula more for the ten dollars a thousand bits coming in here i know it's been
said before and will be said again but thank you for your streams you make good days better
and hard days that much easier knowing that there's a place we can come and just forget laugh and
watch silly stuff on twitch there's just something about your personality that's easy to get lost
and forget about the world we love that about you don't stop anytime soon okay you're a star
on a platform of basic bitches well i i appreciate that that's really really i i'm
fucking so happy that you like hanging out here and i'm glad that we have a community
people that i think the same things are interesting and funny and we can all enjoy
it all together so i will take up that mantle of you saying that these things about me
i love it i have tons of fun um we're gonna keep going you know thank you so much for the
ten dollars silent serenity thanks for the 250 this game reminded me a lot of my childhood
i was staying over at a friend's house when i puked all over the floor at like 2 a.m i
didn't know what to do so i just cleaned it up with some towels that i found left before
they found out and never talked to him again well you've never talked to them you never talked
to him again ever again he couldn't live with the shame oh man well thanks for the 250 and
i've had my share of dumb things as a kid right but thank you zelasky thanks for the
three dollars hey germa i haven't seen a stream in a while so it's nice to catch up
i don't know if you're into dc but they have a new lex luther design that looks pretty cool
new lex luther is this picture okay that's fine thank you for the three dollars uh 15 minutes ago
we had uh jango came in with five community subs thank you so much speaking of which we're
gonna get the credits on the screen here all the subs tonight thanks everybody let's toss
them on the screen all the community subs all the longtime subscriptions and all the people
the brand new subs that just decided to sub right now today thanks a lot guys you are the
oil that makes the machine turn thank you that's a lot of you tonight much love to you all
you want to smoke a bowl no i'm good i'm right i am fucking hungry though i gotta figure
out what i want to do for food ah yes is online thanks for five dollars between moving
out to la in two weeks to pursue a career and finding a scary lump in my chest your recent
streams have been really helping my rising anxiety thank you so much side note have you
listened to egor yet it's pretty good i have not but uh first of all i hopefully that that's
you know take yeah i'm sure you are taking care of that but let's uh let's hope that's
nothing uh nothing scary right get that checked out if you haven't and you move into la in two
weeks yeah there's a lot going on there your health is incredibly important though
that should be a priority all of us obviously wish that this you know nothing hopefully gets
situated and taken care of and good luck in on the move seems like that's a lot of that's
a lot of stuff going on take it slow my heart is being broken here i need to know how short
he is something i've always wondered how is that even possible we talk about how tall i am
like three days a week it's like how is that even possible people that we've been talking
about how how tall i am for like four years how tall is he i have no idea i need this info
here i'll type it for you it's not a lie i can actually prove that too i really can if
i really wanted to but i'm not going to give you the satisfaction of me like standing up
with like a ruler oh look at this look at me if you're so tall how come everyone says you
aren't because they're going off of a meme image from a team fortress two event where
everyone takes my picture there and like shrinks me everyone that takes that image and like turns
it into like the meme image where i'm like fucking three feet tall i've seen the edits
of that picture there's like 40 of them that's where that's where it all started a picture
got put up with a tip of the hats like three years ago or whatever it was it was a great
time it was great these people were all good people and then somebody took that image and
they like shrunk me by like two feet i was i was crouching in the image it looked like
i was like smaller and then it became a thing i've stood back to back with italics on stream
before we've done that before i don't need to prove anything i have nothing to prove zero
but anyways you were standing on a milk crate yeah i put i put milk crates in my room i drink
lots of milk but anyways ed fan thanks for the 250 this game gave me a midlife crisis
at 20 thanks germ of pain i'm sorry to hear that but thank you at van for the 250 dubski dude thanks
to the 250 while watching the stream today i was drawing the egg as a test run for the future
germa trading cards wink wink nudge nudge it'll be a while before it's done but i'd like to
know where's the best place to show you it plus some past fan art i've done that people
seem to like i'm a filthy non-sub so it might have to be outside of twitch uh pretty
much just i i mean i look at every art piece that's on twitter somebody sends me art i see
pretty much every single one of them yeah and listen listen listen do i do to describe this
image okay there is no way i can describe this to you let me tell you let me try and like
everyone can laugh it don't matter this picture was taken i'm going to draw this on screen
because like people of this is another image that people pull up this picture is taken in
san francisco we are standing on a incline i am at the bottom of the incline this is in
san francisco chibi is like six five he's like six four italics is not like six three six one
the ground i'm gonna put this on screen i am on the incline chibi is all chibi is
fucking huge i don't even need to i don't even need to tell this story because i've
already told it a thousand times this is not the same image of me bending down at
tip of the hats this is a picture from san francisco or we are standing on an incline
the whole city is on an incline i'm at the end of the i'm standing on the incline
we will retake this picture the next time i see chibi all right i bet you a trillion dollars
i'm gonna take a picture with chibi the next time i see him it'll probably be soon
i guarantee you i'm like almost a full head higher than this like a full like nose and
eyes higher than this we will do a full body image i will stand right next to him side by
side just like this and then i will prove to you all that we could finally put this to bed
no one's gonna put it to bed this has been going on for five years no we will show we'll
show feet i will show feet both of our feet all four of our feet take a picture on a
goddamn incline in san francisco i should have been on the left side of this image
i knew and at the second i knew it the picture was taken and i looked at it and
and it was like oh let's post this we look good and i'm like god damn fine go for it
yeah and people do this this is what i'm saying people probably find these images and they're
like oh why are you and people like people like shrink you by like an inch just to make it
even worse i will prove that and shimmy will you know shimmy will fight for me here
shimmy's tall but i don't come up to like shimmy's bicep i don't come up to his middle
of his bicep okay all right i'm that's that's it but thank you to alamitos for the 250
you may have gotten three yachts but mario got four yachts uh dude i mean oh i'm gonna
i know i'm supposed to not be addressing this but germa rumble live exists have any of you seen
that fucking movie have any of you watched the germa rumble live action to compare how
tall i am to everybody in the ring like there is substantial evidence that i'm not like five four
the courts can decide that that's fine it's cambridge rick were you wearing a costume on
my stomach all right that's it thank you alamitos for the 250 aspada thanks for the 250
was this the guy who conceived a child with his wife at age 57 on stream yes it is long
time fan never catch dreams but i might try watching these ms dos streams much love to the
funniest gamer on the internet thank you so much that means a lot thank you really appreciate that
i found this image what's wrong what's wrong with this image this is like an old bedroom i don't
get it what's wrong with this it just it's this picture of my face it's this picture of me in
like my old bedroom what's wrong with this what's wrong with the dresser the lotion in the
toilet paper i don't know what that i i don't know okay no no i didn't i didn't do that
lying in my fucking bed all right i'm gonna put that to rest immediately what kind of
fucking psycho do you think i am no no i used to like clean no but that's like a such a
fucking meme from like the 80s okay nobody does that that's like a shit that they
nobody does that shit that's not real nobody i've got i've got the lotion next to the bed
with the yeah you know that i got dry ass hands all right i'm going to bed i'm out of here you
guys can you guys can pick up like microscopes and like microscope every image what what is
that does he have what's on the what is that is that throat spray did he have a sore throat
one day you get there so many there in like fucking microscoping uh thank you though thank
you short stack yeah thank you for the thank you for the bits short stack thanks clue the sniper
for the 250 you should check out alter ego female next saturday have fun look how far away
that desk is away from the bed he would actually need to be seven feet tall to reach it proving
his height no it's called just having like a messy room and you just put stuff on counters
i don't even know what half of this shit is i don't know what some of this stuff is
all right i'm gonna let's be completely honest that that container to the left that is the
red and white container with the nozzle on top i don't even know what that is is that easy
cheese that might just be easy cheese i don't know what that is is that like dog food
that's not whipped cream i don't know what that is i don't even know what this is from
where is this from where did you get this image is that even me that didn't even look like me
that looks like somebody put a face through like the google dream thing what is this
that's fucking scary all right good night everybody i'll see you tomorrow
salmon max season two episode three and four take care guys thanks for sticking around
see you tomorrow good night