Wash hogs. We're here. We're the wash hogs. We wash hogs. Do not adjust your screens. Do not adjust your monitors. This is the pixelation on the screen is just wash hogs at its finest.
You did. I had the marker directly on you.
I'm going to put this on you and it's going to say, I'm going to put this over you like, oh, under hypnotherapy for phobias. I'm going to move it to you and it's going to be like, idiot.
Are you ready?
A little bit.
All right, we're going to go see. You have to stay on.
Actually, don't crash. Kind of surprised this is actually working.
Why is this working?
You should not crash. Don't crash. Don't crash.
This is my life on the line.
It's going to be harder than that.
I'm like a bull rodeo thing.
I am.
So I'm going to dump you do it so hard.
What?
Hold on a second.
We'll go. I'll find a way.
I will find a way to dump you.
You.
Okay.
Now we're going for the bridge to the left.
It's to the left.
I know.
Okay.
Let's go on the bridge.
I want to make the jump while on the roof.
That was a sick jump.
I'm going to just drive straight.
Wherever it takes us, it takes us, you know?
Yeah, I know.
Wherever we go, we go.
You have like a Spider-Man web coming out of your ass.
Why not?
I'm also holding an assault rifle.
Just a dude with an AK.
Do you see your leg? Is your leg doing the same thing?
It's going like...
I can't really see anything.
You're like lifting your leg to pee like a dog.
I feel like I'm in a Batman movie.
I feel like this is like, I'm the Dark Knight.
That's Raiders of the Lost Ark, I think.
No, it's not. It's Batman.
That's Batman of the Lost Ark.
Why can I not hack the traffic lights?
I already did.
This guy, what happened?
He squirted out.
Let's go.
I mean, there's a giant jump right here.
Let's go! Yay!
Why did I die like 30 seconds late?
You died?
Why did you die?
Oh, good.
Give me a push. Push me.
Please push me.
Come on.
You can do it.
Yeah.
Alright.
Totally, totally spectacular, man.
These cops just drive over here and just sit here and do nothing?
That guy's doing something.
They don't get out of their cars unless you do.
I'm stuck in my car.
That guy didn't even try.
That cop didn't even try.
He went straight through.
He didn't even try.
He was just sitting there.
He was like, what a fucking idiot.
You're just going to let it open and fall through?
Oh, look at this.
Look at this mess.
Oh, shit.
Oh, that idiot cop.
Oh, please tell me I can just...
That didn't do anything.
It broke my windows.
That broke the windows.
I want to go play with the train, mommy.
I want to go play with the train.
What the fuck?
We need to find one of the stairs.
That's why I'm driving in the first place.
Look at this rock.
We're going to do it from the rock.
You can't do it from the rock.
Get the car up here.
We're going to jump from this rock.
I was just kidding.
This piece of shit car is behind me.
It's right here.
I'm going my own goddamn way.
Right here.
You're going to take the bike to the steam car.
What was that?
Speaking of what was that?
The train.
Get out of my way.
I need to get in the train.
You're standing on some weight.
I can't.
I'm up.
I made it.
Let's get out of the train.
It's just inching forward.
It's pushing me.
This guy does not give a shit.
He's nubbing me.
He's nudging me. Look at this.
He's like, get out of the fucking way, you idiot.
Just keep driving.
Get the guy that does the Guinness Book of World Records.
Get the guy that does the
Guinness Book of World Records down here right now.
This has got to be some kind of a record.
You want to have a fucking motorcycle duel?
Is that what you wanted?
A motorcycle fight?
He poses.
Nice try.
Motorcycle fight.
Still doing it.
I'm still going.
Nothing will knock you off a motorcycle.
Wash hogs. Get it right please.
Motorcycle fight.
See ya.
See ya later.
I did the same thing.
Alright.
I want to get on the back of your mumber cycle.
You can't. Bye.
Get back here.
This guy is like pretending to shoot at you.
He's got like an
iPad.
He's like shooting an iPhone game.
What's he really doing here?
Out in the middle of nowhere.
What did you just do?