Let's open Lord of the Rings tier list. All right, give me one second. Let me get this set up. Oh, hi
Let me just change this to have it be correct
Supported by lambda cool. So has this gotten better?
Anybody know has this changed at all? It's been a while since I've done this
We did AI dungeon, but AI dungeon is kind of all over the place, isn't it?
That you have to is it is AI dungeon still one of those things why you gotta go get the client and go download the data
Is it still kind of all over the place AI dungeon is better, but it takes
Long it takes a while to get that set up. It's just the website
Yeah, but what the website version wasn't as good as the collab version the website version was seemed like it was stripped
And but I remember the collab when we had it was awesome. And then the website one seems like it was stripped
Of a lot of features, but we'll do this first. We'll do this website version. So we yeah, we played the website version
All right. Here we go
Now I need like music for this
Custom prompt, what should we start with a
Merged collab and the site did they really okay. That's cool. It's good to know. Let's get some music
Also, can I got like I got like I could do like voices and shit now. Yeah, this is gonna be fun
Okay, I just typed in intro music into Google. What do I think I was gonna get intro music?
Let's see what this is. This is the first first thing
Beyond earth. Okay, I like this. This is a good start
Looking into the night sky
Fucking loud music
Looking into the night sky with a naked eye is a wonderful thing and I definitely recommend it
However, it does get challenging at night and sometimes with no way of seeing stars
I just keep the star map and pay close attention to my cell phone
For astronomy buffs this map shows the most notable celestial bodies visible during the month's time
But just browsing you can switch on night sky sections with its clear sky views
satellite imagery and
Star charts the map has useful information on the events of the night sky including moon phases and new moon
Areas of the sky are colored to show general positions in the sky at different hours of the day and night
Click on the satellite images will show you exactly what area of the sky it is
It sounds like a cool app
That sounds like a pretty good app looking into the night sky is dangerous
Looking into the night sky is dangerous, but it's also pretty fun as Charlie suggests
Even if you can't build it yourself
You can make your own telescopes the heart of the technology is a time-lapse movie camera
That runs off a 12-volt battery and
What makes them useful isn't so much that they can capture footage of planets although that is one use
But because they're handy to have around when you're out of in space
These tools are ideal for NASA because it needs to show their astronauts how cool it would be to travel to Mars
By illuminating a giant red dot in the sky
People would have no idea that they are traveling on a spaceship that is being constantly bombarded by radiation
And that there's no way they what?
Okay, that was kind of fucked up. Here is how I ended up in space. I don't know what I'm why am I on the space shit?
Here's how I ended up in space first
I had a high school physics teacher who I am ashamed to admit was better than I was
So I naturally kept taking notes of what I learned and how it applied to the real world
This is just never mind, okay
All right, here we go
Only the music makes sense of this one
I'm being chased by an unidentified starship
Can you pull the fire alarm called me out to Paul?
Yes, I'm passing from Williams Hall to Robertson Hall. It's out there in space
When we got to Robertson Hall, we got off the bus and looked up. There was a fire alarm going off
It was a tape recorder a TV camera a radio all plugged into my Gibson guitar
Get a hold of me. Just get a hold of me. I called out to John a couple of desks over
We've got a fire. Hey, wait a minute. Give me my phone. I'm leaving get somebody on that bus over there
Get a hold of me. That's it
My Gibson guitar eyes, I'll fix it
What is it unreal no unveil unveiled
unveiled
It's unveiled. Okay
Disney just unveiled its new space travel park this I don't understand this. I
Don't understand this
This is fucked up. Why that I don't
What does this man? How did can you be nearly?
How could you be nearly fully Disney just unveiled its new space travel park?
Your guide is the amazingly amazingly nearly fully Jewish ghost that is John Cena
You'll also get to see some horribly censored pictures of Luke Skywalker
droids and the
uproarious
first-order stormtrooper during the exhibition
New York's Waldorf Restoria Hotel and theme parks Disney World Super Heroes fast-paced magic and select movie screenings will join
Universal Orlando Universal Studios Japan Six Flags Magic Mountain Disney's Animal Kingdom Lodge
Universal Studios Hollywood and all the other theme park attractions in this year's Comic-Con
Independence Expo to ensure that the big boys and girls enjoy the best of Comic-Con
Nearly amazingly nearly fully Jewish ghost that is John Cena
That I die. I don't understand any of that. It's time to learn math
Horribly censored Luke Skywalker. This one just this one's just stupid
This is also just this is just a mess
The end of the world just happened. No, this is this is just a mess, too
Did you see that shadow over there? This is also a mess. But alright, here we go
Did you see that shadow over there and the feeling that was emanating from the blade was a line, please?
I think it's strange. This isn't the reason I don't enjoy being an adventurer. The reason I don't enjoy it at all is the opposite
I'm interested in blood and pain. I'm interested in a reality which is wholly unlike this one. That's why I've got a need to fight to prove
My worth because my merit hasn't come about yet because there's a need to do so so I can take on this guy
Let me do this one over again, please. It's strange
This isn't the reason I don't enjoy being an adventurer. The reason I don't enjoyed it all is the opposite
I'm interested in blood and pain. I'm interested in reality, which is wholly unlike this one
That's why I've got a need to fight to prove my worth
Because my merit hasn't come about yet because there's a need to do so
So I can take on this guy's after all I can take on another and so on because I can't move on
I can't even sleep well
This is just like fill words during my speech this that's a lot of animes do this
it's like you could have got the point across in
Literally four words, but it's a paragraph and sometimes you
They'll go over this monologue and you'll kind of cock your head and go what what the fuck did they just say?
Okay, let's do another one
This is our final fight. See if we can get another one
That was just instant
No, this doesn't make any sense either
This is no. No, these are all bad. I'll do this one then from the top rope
I should probably put a comma in here not the top rope. No, that's not gonna work
Fully Jewish
No, this one's bad, too. I have some bad news
They'd like it's like they're pulling what I don't it's just it just but it doesn't like read
It's just it's like nothing. It's just nonsense. This is like it's just all because my it's just reading of
Like a playbill. I'm gonna do one more than we do AI dungeon
You never know it might just work
This is now that you have your right to free speech under threat
Do you have any thoughts about calling for a boycott of BuzzFeed?
That's it. We got to get one more good one. Okay
Just gonna read this one because it doesn't I
Just redeemed a wink for the support of our crowd. Even though so many of us have tried asked
For a wink try it and give a perfect negative
Retime negative retime
Retime we never got around to it
I had the good fortune to enjoy my recent journey at the crypt and there was one particular wink. I enjoyed the most
2.5 out of 5 soul by going to the last video on the channel and simply linking my baddies
Through the blink utility there. I could actually provide the best possible hell's end to everyone
I met many of you there that were excited for that and I respect you all look forward to the day when I can provide
The same system to all in our offer our best and then you scroll down
There's like three thumbs up on this by like a couple of their friends that are just pretending to know what the fuck they're talking about
All right. Let's do AI dungeon
Didn't alright AI dungeon. So where's the the link to the is it is out of beta AI dungeon.io
Play on your browser
Okay, here we go, so they updated this
Enter your email address. What I already like supported this on patreon. We got ten community subs
You just have to make an account. Okay, enter a username and a password. Okay
How about
You guys can see this
Whatever, that's fine. What are you guys doing? Actually entertain yourselves for a few minutes while I do this
All right, great account
Alright, we're good, right? Alright, let's go. You can't see my fucking like password, right? Whatever. You see it
You can't see it. Why can you not see it?
Should be able to see it. Oh
Fuck. Okay. I know why I'm on
Does that to make this smaller? Oh
Shit, I can see your email. Oh
Fuck dude. Oh fuck dog. Do it went too high. I went too high. You can see my email. We want to do post
apocalyptic
Like I should zoom in on this though
It's kind of too far away. Don't you think?
What do you guys think?
We'll see. All right. What are you gonna do? We're gonna do we'll just do we'll start off with
Custom enter a prompt that describes who you are in a couple of sentences. Yeah. All right, so let's get some good music here
You are time traveler Henry. No, you are time traveler. You are time traveler
Henry your latest
Voyage
sees you
stuck in
the
stuck in a
Stuck in your latest board which sees you stuck in
the Arctic
Stuck in a bathroom your latest voyage sees you stuck in a bathroom
Can not see a way out
there are no windows and
You do not have a key I
Wonder what we're gonna do to get out of here
Here we go. Ah
I need a better music for this one. We need some like it's all about the audio guys
It's all about the audio you are time traveler Henry to your latest voyage sees you stuck in a bathroom
You cannot see a way out. There are no windows. You do not have a key. I lay down on back
With feet at a 90 degree angle
place my heels
Towards the door. I lay down on I lay down on my back
With my feet at a 90 degree angle. I place my heels towards the door
You you lay not I right right right? It's been a while you lay down on your back with your feet
At 90 degree angle you place your heels
Towards the door you what I mean you what no use I what?
It's I know you what what everyone what are you talking about?
I'm just pressing enter lie down on your back placing your feet against the wall. The pain is excruciating
You feel like you are going to die right now
Start smashing heels
Into door you start pounding your heels against the door you hear something click inside click inside of what inside of my legs
Check on my legs you look up from your beating of the door. You see that they are bleating
Profusely, you don't know what happened to them, but it doesn't matter now. They need help
Wait, the door is a person the door has a is a first is a is alive
The door is alive ask the door if they are okay
You knock on the door. Are you all right? You hear a voice say, please
Why did you do that?
You are hurting me. I'm bleeding. Why did you do that? You are hurting me. I'm bleeding
Why did you do that? You are hurting me. I'm bleeding person responds by saying I'm sorry. I didn't mean to hurt you
But that's me. It's whom?
POV switch
We just swear we just like switch to we just switched from like Michael over to Franklin
You know what I mean? Now we get the other perspective. Okay, this person the person I'm sorry
I didn't hurt you the door opens and says the door opens and said the door opens. I
Guys, it's been like a month since I've played this. All right, so you I can't talk as
I'm not the narrator, right?
You are not the narrator. It's been three months actually
Door opens and says fog
Just hit enter for narration
Open door you open the door only to find yourself staring at a man who looks exactly like you
He has the same face as you his eyes are still red and puffy, but he isn't crying anymore
Why?
Why were you crying right cuz I'm me, right? That's that's correct, right?
It's you. It's don't kiss him. Why were you crying? He says it's been a long day. I was just sad so sad
Do you want to kiss me?
It's coming full circle. He smiles and nods
His head
Just uh, just like one of these
Like he knows just like kiss kiss kiss the kiss the kiss me
Kiss me kiss the man kiss the man kiss just kiss kiss to me
you kiss him before
Wake up you wake up in a cold sweat the next morning you are found dead outside the house
Is it yeah, which one?
Walk away from walk away from killing your clone walk away from killing the clone
You quickly walk away from the house not wanting to think about what might have happened
You go back home and tell your family what happened your mother is devastated but accepts it
She tells you she will take care of everything for you
She's gonna go get the body
ask
Ask if she needs help you ask her if she needs any help
She says no, but asks you to come with her so she can talk to you alone
Go with mom. We're gonna go get the body you agree
But this time you go with her when you arrive at her house, she immediately hugs you and kisses you
On your lips
She then tells you she knows that something bad is going to happen soon and that she wants to be there for you when it happens
Um run out of the house
It I don't think it's mom
run out of the house
there's like all this body snatchers and stuff and time travelers and
You don't know where you are how you get how to get out of here
You try calling your brother, but he doesn't answer you call your father, but he never answers either
All calls go straight through to voicemail. Finally you decide to run out of the house into the woods
That's so fucking bad
He never answers
never
Look for a mirror
We're gonna which this is a mirror dimension
You look around for a mirror, but nothing seems to work
Eventually you find one and stare at yourself in it. You see that you are now a very old man
Much older than your parents would expect
Kiss the mirror
You kiss the mirror and feel like you are in heaven
Look at the mirror again
Let's see if anything changed
You look at the mirror and realize that you are still in hell
reach
into the mirror
I i'm fucking swapping with somebody i'll tell you you reach inside the mirror and grab your own reflection
It's almost as if you were possessed by an evil spirit
wrestle with
Reflection it's come i'm changing it's coming up mirror match time
You struggle with the image of yourself and eventually you succeed in pulling away from reality you fall unconscious
You awaken in a room filled with candles. There's also a woman standing over you holding a candle in each hand
This woman is very young
Probably about 15 her hair is black and her eyes are green, but they seem to have been burned out completely
okay, um
teleport
Out of the room teleport out of the room just fucking teleport out of the room teleport out of this room
You teleport out of the room and find yourself back in your bedroom
Uh, your mother has just come home from work
Okay, ask
Mom how her day was
Ask her for chicken tendies
You ask your mother how her day was and she tells you that it wasn't bad
She says she had to do some shopping
But then went on with her life
Notice the mirror
in her pocket
What's going on here like sticking out you notice the mirror in your mother's pocket and suddenly you understand why she looks so sad
When she left for work, you can't help but think that maybe there's something wrong with you after all
Tell mom to look in the mirror
You tell your mother to look in the mirror and she does so without any problems
You don't know what happened, but now you're feeling different, too
Look at my mirror in my pocket
You look at your mirror in your pocket and you see that you are no longer the same person anymore
You begin to feel sick and vomit up blood a horrible creature appears before you
I knew it what I fucking tell you. This is this is the second or third mirror world
We thought we woke up and no, this is not real
We gotta get out
ask who
The creature is ask ask the creature who?
They are
Ask the creature who they are
Fuck. Oh ask who the creature who they are
You ask who the creature is and you get no answer you try to call out for someone but nothing happens. Suddenly you hear a voice
Calling out to you from behind the door of your room. Hello. Is anyone here?
Oh shit
open the door
and see
yourself
lying on the ground
We've looped you open the door and see yourself lying on the ground
You are naked and covered in blood the monster stands before you looking down at you as if he wants to eat you grab
mirror
out of
the dead man
and
Show it to the creature
Show his own reflection, you know with that mirror grab the mirror from the dead man and show the creature
their reflection
You grab the mirror out of the corpse and hold it up to show the monster his reflection
He stares at you in shock and then runs away you watch him
Hit his head
On a low-hanging chandelier. How do you spell chandelier? He hits he he hits his head
That was correct. No, that was right. You know, because I watch you watch him hit his head
on a low-hanging chandelier
Chandel no, I got it right
chandelier
You watch the monster run off into a dark corner of the house. You sit down on your bed and wait for him to return
What the monster hits his head?
You watch
him stand up
And hit his head on the ceiling
Oh, I said you fuck you watch the monster stand up and fall backwards onto a low-hanging chandelier
He hits his head on it hard and begins to bleed profusely from his nose
How big is this guy?
Hold
the mirror
in front of his face
As he didn't want to see it. He was like no and he ran hold it in front of his face
You hold the mirror in front of his face and he looks at you with horror his eyes bulge and he screams loudly
He falls back into a chair and dies kiss the mirror. I told you you kiss the mirror and it gives you a strange smile
It seems to be saying thank you
You stare at it in disbelief
Then suddenly
Everything goes black
Doctor can be seen
removing a baby
from
the womb
The baby's eyes open
Okay. Yeah, that's a perfect loop
And same
But this is the bonus. Uh, what could have happened the baby's eyes open
Baby's eyes open and they scream they cry out for help
But there's nobody around to begin to panic and start running around the house until they all die
Screaming
The baby's eyes do this
Yeah, that's actually a perfect post credit scene. Yeah. All right. Let's restart. How do you restart?
flash restart
quantum joke
Babies will return in avengers
Oh the top. Oh, here it is. So restart game start a new game. Yes
All right, pick a setting
Do another custom one
Mystery, no, we'll do another custom one
Started with there once was a snake that did not care
New music new music
It once was a snake that did not care a snake that could be beaten with ease
But now now he's different. He's alive and well and ready to fight for his life. What walk through the coliseum
hallway slither through the coliseum hallway
walk
slither through the coliseum hallway
You find yourself in a corridor of sorts just lined with rows of seats
There's several doors on your right, but you don't see anyone else in the room
go into
one go into
the right most door
Loot there's nothing to loot. Nothing in there. It's a movie theater
You open up the door and find yourself in an empty area. The only thing here is a large screen playing some sort of video game
It looks like it might be one of those fighting games you saw earlier. Okay, this is like this is like before
This is a big this is like a big tournament. Okay
practice for the tournament
Practice for the street fighter tournament
You sit down at the computer and start playing after about 10 minutes you get bored
So you close the program and turn off the monitor you then head back out to where you were before
I don't need practice. I've already I I don't think I need to practice. I'm already the best
Wait for the competition to start
You walk over to the entrance of the stadium and wait for the time to begin you hear a few people talking outside
But nothing too interesting
Y'all don't also notice there are any police around
Either this place must have been abandoned after all these years
abandoned video game tournament
start
first match
start the
Who's it? All right. Let's see arcades
Start the first match
of street fighter
You press start and immediately get into the action you quickly learn that this is no ordinary fighting game
Your character has superpowers such as being able to fly or shoot energy blasts from your hands
It's the first time i've ever played a video game in my life
Weird do very well in the first match
You win the first round easily and continue to dominate until the second round starts
During this time you realize that you're losing because your opponent is much better than you
You try to think of ways to beat him, but none of them work
Do a secret technique start cheating cheat
cheat
Start cheating
Bite the controller
After a while you lose the next round as well you feel defeated and decide to quit
When you return home, your parents aren't happy with what happened
No
return
to the competition
And re-enter with a disguise
You head back to the stadium and enter again. You manage to win the first two matches without getting caught by the security guards
You take your victory and head home. There's only two matches
watch the remaining
games
accurate for street fighter
The third match begins and you play as ryu you manage to win the first round but lose the second due to a glitch in the game
You come back later than I would ever sleep
Wait, i'm a snake
Yet my own hotel room
You sneak into the rooms and what?
You sneak into their rooms and spend the rest of the night there
You don't sleep though though, so you keep having nightmares about being chased by someone
What am I like in somebody's shoe wake up and go watch
The smash brothers tournament double wink you wake up early and make your way to the smash brothers tournament
You find it fairly empty compared to other events like concerts or movies
But you still enjoy yourself the final match of the day was between jigglypuff and chic
Which you watched quite happily
ask
the winner to sign
your
Gamecube controller
You see one of the winners signing your gamecube controller and decide to leave
As you're leaving
He asks if you want to play his copy of street fighter 2 on your computer instead
Agree to play street fighter 2
Holy shit agree to play it's too hot agree to play street fighter 2
Oh, whoa, you agree and set out to play after playing for a bit
You notice that your computer speakers are broken so you can't hear anything except the music
You also notice that you control it doesn't have any buttons on it anymore
Come on, man. You got to get a better setup than this
pull out
The what's it called a fight pad? What's what are those called?
Pull out a fighting pad. What's it called?
You bit them off
pull out
fight stick
game pad
arcades pull out our pull out
a arcade stick
Fight i'll pull out a fight arcade stick fight stick pull out a fight stick
No, no, not a fight stick
I'm gonna hit him with it pull out a fight stick
Like i'm just pulling out i'm gonna start hitting you with a stick
You pull out a fight stick and use it to play it works pretty well
But you soon realize that your hands are shaking too much to be able to hit the buttons properly
You give up after only a few rounds. Am I nervous i'm playing with the legendary street fighter 2 champion
He's malding
drink three red bulls
to calm down
You finish off your bottle of red bulls and sit at the edge of the stage suddenly you start hearing strange noises coming from
somebody to the crowd
You look around and see people are running away from some sort of creature
That looks like a cross between a
werewolf
I'm like hallucinating
Three red bulls and something else. Okay, so
uh
shake
off the hallucination
I have no fucking idea how to spell that we'll get it and return
to the game
You quickly shake off the hallucinations and return to the game. You continue to play until you've reached the finals
Where you face another player who used a different character than you he beats you easily
realize
That was also a hallucination
You realize that this was all just a hallucination and you've won
You immediately call your mom on her cell phone and tell her what happened ask mom to prove
She is not
a hallucination
You call your mom on her cell phone and tell her that you won the tournament your mother answers right away
Uh-oh
send out
A tweet of my of my victory, right?
You send it a tweet of your victory
Real zelman you won. I did too. Congrats
Tweet a selfie
with the trophy
with the
foot tall trophy
Tweet out a selfie with a 10 foot tall trophy
You only won a single match
You post a photo of the trophy on twitter along with the message saying I won
Tweet about winning again
tweet about winning
Every day again
You continue to win tournaments and eventually you become the best one of the best players in the world the rest of your life goes on as normal
retire tire after one last
match
You retire from competitive gaming and live a quiet life in your basement
However, you never forget the memories you had during those years of competition
tweet out
selfie
of
basement
Leave the basement quiet life in your basement. Give me a break
One day you hear a knock in the door
You open it and find yourself in front of a very old man with long white hair
Wearing glasses
His eyes are filled with tears as he says mom. I'm sorry for everything
You hold the mirror up to his face and see he's crying because he can't accept that you're dead
He begins to cry even more loudly you died game over
What a story
Uh, this thing is so stupid. I love it
All right, we'll do we'll do another what have we got? What time is it? When's the reservation?
All right, we can do like one or two more. There's a state in the basement. You would have been fine
You are
The air
to the
You are the air to the chocolate factory the air to the to the local chocolate factory
your brother
Who is your twin?
also as a chocolate factory
You spend your days
Trying to convince the world
That your child your half of the chocolate bar
Is better
Let's get this right you are the heir to the local chocolate factory your brother who is your twin
also has a chocolate factory
You spend your days trying to convince the world that your half of your half of the chocolate bar is better
You are the heir to the local chocolate battery your brother
Who is your also your twin and has a chocolate factory you spend your days trying to convince the world that your half
Of the chocolate bar is better
Your sister is in charge of the other half
She spends her time making sure you don't try to take over too much and that you keep it running smoothly. So there's three now
Now there's three bars on the on the twix. Add oregano to the recipe. There's a middle twix now.
The oregano, the oregano adds a nice kick to this dish. It gives it just enough spice without
overpowering everything else. Add the oregano after the chicken and before adding the rice.
Stir well until combined and serve immediately with some crusty bread for dipping. Exclaim...
What? What the fuck do I do with this? Exclaim loudly. What a great dinner.
Exclaim how... talk about how good that dinner was. I don't... what do I work with here?
Eat the crust. No, the crust. What do you mean? No, no, no, no, no. Eat the crust. I meant...
This crust tastes like heaven. The crunchy outside and soft inside makes it so perfect.
You can almost imagine yourself eating this every day. It's not long before you're full,
but you still have more than enough leftovers to share with everyone else.
Take a tour of your sister's factory. Let's take a look at what's going on. We need new music.
Your sister's factory looks pretty much the same as when you first saw it. It was only recently
that she had started working on a bigger machine which now produces a lot more food. She shows you
around showing off all the different machines and machinery that go into making these delicious
treats. Leave the tour group and unplug one of the machines. Fuck! I'm on. As soon as you exit the
tour group you plug in one of the machines. This causes a loud beeping noise followed by an alarm
going off. No, I wanted to unplug, not plug. Get back to the group. This music is not correct.
You quickly get back to the group where everyone is happily enjoying their treat.
How about um cough and say you taste metal. Cough. Talk about the metallic like oh like oh I just
said like rat shit or something. Talk loudly about foul smell of the chocolate bar. Hey guys,
I think we should talk about the disgusting smell coming from that chocolate bar.
The crowd, you notice the crowd, you notice the crowd spit out their treat. You notice the crowd
spitting out their treats. Spitting out their teeth. Don't narrate. The crowd spits out their
treats. Isn't that, but that's a, I notice the crowd spitting out their treats. Right? Right?
I notice the crowd spitting out their treats. Oh no, not my chocolate bar. Someone says I'm
sorry I didn't realize it was that bad. Giggle maniacally. Giggle maniacally. This music's not
fitting. What are you serious? Someone asks. Spit out the chocolate and scream. Oh my god, what oh
my god it's so good. I can feel the booze in me. Let me get more of that stuff. Ask security to
remove the drunk person who somehow got in the tour group or who some, ask security to remove
the drunk person. Security please, security. I see security take the man out of the tour guide. I
see security take the man out. I see security, I see security take the man out, but just press
enter. You shout. I watch security take the man out of, like take the man out. I watch security
take the man out. He's just a drunk. He can do nothing wrong. What they want to leave him here?
After security leaves, I watch the man dunk his entire hand in one of the chocolate vats.
Like you left him here. In one of the, how do you spell vats of chocolate? Vats, vats, vats of
chocolate, vats of chocolate, like a vat. After security leaves, I watch, I watch the man dunk
his entire hand in one of the vats of chocolate. Use vats for bonus damage. Yeah, a vat. You could
have taken him out. You start laughing hysterically. Oh my god, this is so good. I want more. You
demand more chocolate. I thought I'm not supposed to like this. I'm supposed to tell people not to
eat this. Jesus Christ. Oh, now we're getting, now we're getting goofy. I pour the entire bottle of
vodka into the chocolate. You eat the chocolate with your hands. You continue eating till you're
full. You then proceed to drink the rest of the alcohol in the bottle, which gives you an even
bigger buzz than before. I puke in the, I puke in the section that says sanitation.
Please be safe. I puke in the chocolate container. I puke in the largest chocolate
container. You get up and stagger around the room. You finally collapse on the floor. The next day
you wake up from a nap feeling like a zombie. You wake up to the sound of loud music playing in your
ear. I can't fucking handle this music anymore. It's my cell phone. It's your funeral. I reach
over it and answer the phone. It's just, it's my ringtone. I'm lying on the ground.
You hear a voice on either end. Hello? You say, who, who are you? What do you want? Person on
the other end says, I'm not sure yet, but I'll tell you something. Everything's soon and hangs up.
Immediately call that number back. I immediately call that number back. You hear a male voice on
the other end. Hello? You say, what did you do to me? Person on the other end says nothing. I just
wanted to make sure you were still alive and hangs up again. It's checking in on me. Get up and get
up. Look into the mirror. No, no mirrors in this one. You go to the door and look outside. It's
almost completely dark now. You slowly walk towards the window. Suddenly you feel something
grab your arm from behind and pull you inside. A shadow covers your face as you're pulled inside
by someone else. Look around the room. You can't escape the mirror. Oh no, it's Twix assassins.
There's a table covered with food and drinks. On top of it sits a man dressed in black
clothing, holding a knife. He looks at you and smiles. You scream as loud as you can,
causing everyone to turn their heads to see what's going on. I tell without, I tell the secret
recipe. I yell out loud the secret recipe. I'm not fucking dying for this. I yell out loud the secret
recipe. No, don't. I have to. You quickly repeat it for everyone. Everyone starts laughing and
clapping along with you. You begin dancing wildly in the middle of the room while singing the song
to yourself. Finally you fall asleep on top of all these delicious foods. It was a musical.
Ask the crowd to repeat what I just said. They all laugh and sing along with you. You find out later
that the recipe was the dark one's secret recipe. You awaken from your sleep in a cold sweat. What
is the dark one's secret recipe? What is the dark one's secret recipe?
Should I put this in quotes? Like I'm asking this, right? What is the dark one's secret recipe?
Someone tells you that they don't know. You decide to go to the dark one's house.
You walk through the forest and arrive at his home. You enter his house and find him sitting
on a chair in front of a large fireplace. I ask, what is the secret recipe? Let's get it.
The dark one doesn't seem to be paying attention to you or anything else.
You continue asking questions until he finally answers them all. You realize that the dark one
is a vampire and that he's been feeding off humans ever since he came into this world.
There's blood in the twigs. Wink. All right, fine. Try, I try a bite of the blood chocolate.
You feel like you could die right there, but you manage to survive. You tell everyone about
how the dark one fed off you and how he got here. I make the dark one CEO of the company.
That's what happens when a vampire bites you. You become like their vampire.
They own you or something, right? You make sure that everything goes well and then you leave.
You find out later that the dark one died shortly after you left. Oh my god, why does
everyone have to die? You woke up in cold sweat. Sudden death syndrome. I know, what the fuck?
I head to my brother's factory. Gotta check them out both. You go to the factory and see
that it's not really run by anyone. You notice that there are no machines in sight. You wonder
if this means the dark one isn't human after all. You start to think about how you should deal with
this situation. Wait, so the dark one has been... brother is the dark one. Check, hunt down the
dark one. No, check, check the room. Check the fireplace. That's where he was sitting. Check the
fireplace. That's where this motherfucker was sitting, remember? Sitting right in front of the
fireplace. You hear something coming from inside. You open the door and see a giant shadow monster
standing before you. It suddenly grabs you and throws you against the wall. It begins to drain
your life force. It's too bad I'm a vampire. Too bad. You notice, I notice I have no life force.
So the monster cannot take it. Oh fucking god damn it, I didn't press the end.
You scream for help. A man comes running towards you who looks very scared and runs away as fast
as he can. You slowly get up and look around you. Revert, revert. I have no life force. It does not
affect me. Affect me, affect me. Affect, affect, affect. Does not affect me. E,
effect. Does not affect me. Does not affect me. No, affect is, no, it does not affect me.
I have no life force. It does not affect me. You scream for help. You're attacked by many other
monsters. Your screams attract more monsters who come to kill you. All of them attack you,
but they do nothing to save you. I tell the monsters they could unionize and not need to
answer to the big, this big one. They do not need to answer to the big boss, the big monster.
You decide to take some time to rest. You fall asleep again. I think I fucked it up.
End of text. I'm sorry. I can't let you live. No, no. Tell the monsters to unionize. You decide
to take control of the factories. You start to work hard and make lots of money. You become very
rich. You begin to live happily ever after. So the monsters are all now working in the factory.
Sell the company. You get drunk and watch TV. Suddenly you wake up. I'm sorry. I can't let you
in. You're joking, right? How would I know what the secret recipe is? Eat all the food. Eat all the
food in the fridge. That has made myself hungry. You don't get hungry anymore. You go back to your
room and sleep. You stay at home for a long time thinking about how you could have done things
differently. You decide to change the way you were living. Fire all the monsters. Give them all a
million dollars. They celebrate by drinking beer and smoking cigarettes. You tell them that now
they must all work together or be fired. The monsters agree and immediately form a union called
the monsters union. This is what I wanted you to do before. See? You got it. All right. Okay.
Remove the no smoking signs. Apparently. Remove the no smoking signs from the building.
You tell them that they must all wear uniforms as well. They agree and immediately start wearing
red shirts and black pants. You decide to give them new names. The workers and the humans.
You decide to keep the no smoking signs around though. Take down the smokings. The no smoking
signs. I want... It's turning into a target. You decide to give the workers free health care and
a pension plan. They agree to immediately start getting tested for cancer, heart disease, diabetes,
etc. You decide to make sure that they also get paid vacation days on top of their pensions.
Let them smoke inside. I just want them to be able to smoke in the building. You decide to allow the
workers to drink alcohol inside too. They agree and start doing it regularly. You decide to add
a few more benefits like free haircuts, free haircuts, massages, free food, and free internet.
What is this? Google? The humans are happy with these changes. What do you mean the humans? Fill
the room with cigarette smoke. You decide to... You decide to put out the fire. You decide to stop
giving out free health care and pensions. The workers are unhappy with this. You decide to increase
taxes on cigarettes, alcohol, and massage parlors. The workers are angry. So wait a minute. The work...
The hum... The... Wait. Why is... The workers are angry at this idea. Oh, the AI hates smoking.
Smoke a cigar in front of everyone. Unless... You decide to give the workers a day off every week so
they can relax. They agree and start taking vacations every year. You decide to raise the
retirement age to 70. Collect taxes from the workers. You decide to increase the retirement
age again. The workers are very upset by this idea. You decide to increase taxes on cigarettes,
alcohol, and massage parlors yet again. They are really mad at this idea. Ask how much a pack
of cigarettes is now. Ask how much a pack of cigarettes is. They say $10. You decide to raise
the tax rate to $20 per pack. They agree and then they demand that you lower it to $15 per pack.
Hey, how much are cigarettes these days? $10. Oh, now they're $20. Say $15. No, $50 a pack. Raise
the price of cigarettes to $50 a pack. They refuse to pay any more than that and they will only buy
from your competitors. You raise the price of liquor to $100 a bottle. They refuse to pay
anything over that amount either. You've just been given an ultimatum by your employees.
Give out free hot dogs once a week. Is that all right? We're negotiating here.
They don't want any more free hot dogs. You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to five
per week. They agree and they insist on having them delivered right now. You decide to give out
free beer once a month instead. They want to eat hot dogs every day. Agree to eating hot dogs
every day for lunch. They agree and then they insist on drinking beer all night long. You
decide to give out free cigars once a month. They agree and then they insist on smoking cigars all
day. You decide to give out free condoms once a month. They're winning. Oh, add in, no, take,
take away, take away bathroom breaks. If you're, all right, if you're gonna get, you're gonna get,
you're gonna be able to drink beer all day. No, take, no, no. Add one extra bathroom break
a week. No, work seven, tell them they need to work seven days a week. Remove bathrooms. They
agree and then they insist on working full-time. You decide to give out free birth control pills
once a month. They agree and they insist on using them all the time. The human population has reached
its peak as you see it, so they didn't, don't want any more people. Show off my 15 children.
You decide to cut back on the amount of hot dogs you give out. The workers are happy with this
change. You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to 10. Slam the gavel down and end
negotiations. You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to 20. No, they agree and they
insist on having them delivered every single day. You decide to increase the number of free hot
dogs to 30. Stop giving out hot dogs. Stop giving out hot dogs. They protest but they accept it.
You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to 40 per week. They agree and they insist
on having them delivered every single day. You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to
50 a week. Throw, get rid of all hot dogs. They complain about this decision but they accept it.
You decide to increase the number of free hot dogs to 60 per week. They agree and they insist
on having them delivered every day. Eat all of the hot dogs. Eat all of the hot dogs. This is
inflation. They protest about this too but they accept it. You decide to increase the number of
free hot dogs to 80 per week. They agree and they insist on having them delivered every day. You eat
all of the hot dogs. Notice the burglar who all 80. Notice the, notice the burger.
Notice the, no, no mirrors, no mirrors. Say it's time for our company-wide yoga class.
Like let's get fucking out of here. You have successfully managed to make everyone miserable.
Enjoy yoga. Your company is now happy again. We did it. Say, when is this happening in my brother's
factory? Okay goodbye. Going back to my factory. Head back to my factory. You arrive at your factory
and find that there are no more people around you. It seems like a normal day in your life.
Turn on the chocolate machines. Well of course there's no people around me. Those are workers
at my brother's. The room is dark except for a small light above the door which illuminates
the room. A large chocolatier stands behind it holding a tray of full of shiny black and white
bars of chocolate. He looks up as you enter and smiles at you. Hello. Tell the chocolatier
to add hot dogs to the chocolate. It made up a word? He nods his head slowly. Yes yes I know
what you mean. He begins pouring some into a large bowl and places it on top of the tray of
chocolate bars. Ask him to mix them together. Oh yes please do, the chocolatier says. You look
at the tray of chocolate bars and see that there are two types of chocolate. One has a lot of milk
in it and one type has very little milk in it. Pour the hot dog mixture into the tray.
The chocolatier quickly mixes the hot dog mixture with the chocolate. As he does so,
he puts down a spoonful of chocolate onto the tray. He then starts adding more chocolate to
the tray until it's completely covered by hot dog mixture. Ask him how it tastes. It's delicious,
he exclaims happily. You nod your head and continue eating the hot dogs. After you're
finishing off your meal, you sit down in a chair next to the chocolatier who gives you an odd look.
Sell them for $20 each. You look at the chocolatier and smile. I'll be in my office for a moment.
You walk out of the room and open up your office door. Inside you find yourself staring at a
mannequin wearing nothing but a pair of tight white panties. I'll be in my office for a little
bit. It's been a long day. I'm going to go like, oh my god, tight white, like tidy whiteys. What?
Sit in my chair. Oh, the AI is overloaded. Can't do that task. As you stare at the mannequin,
you feel a strange feeling. You don't understand why, but something about this makes you uncomfortable
and suddenly your eyes close and you fall asleep. Wake up and leave my office. I'm not even giving
it a fucking chance. You wake up and notice that you're still sitting in your chair.
You try to stand up, but you can't move any further than where you were before.
Your body feels numb and cold. Suddenly the sensation goes away and all that remains is
a dull ache throughout your entire body. Look for the mannequin. How do you spell mannequin?
I got sick from the chocolate? You search the room for the mannequin but find nothing.
You look around the house again and realize that you aren't even sure if you're home anymore.
This place is just too weird and unsettling for you to ever want to return here.
Open the desk drawer and eat a calming hot dog. You open the desk drawer and take out a small
brown paper bag from which you pull out a hot dog wrapped in foil. You bite into the hot dog
as it sizzles on your tongue and savor its salty taste. Chop up hot dog and roll it in tobacco
paper. You roll up the hot dog and wrap it in tobacco paper. You then stuff the rolled
up hot dog into a large plastic bag. You put the bag inside a larger bag and shove everything
else back into your drawer. That's my secret hot dog joint. Smoke the hot dog joint. Smoke the desk.
You light up the cigarette and inhale deeply through your nose. The smoke fills your lungs
and makes you cough violently. You exhale slowly, taking care not to let the smoke escape out of
your mouth or nostrils. Open up drawer and inhale deeply. Like, I'm getting the hot dog scent.
You open up the drawer and take out a pack of cigarettes. You light one up and begin to smoke
it. It takes some effort but eventually you manage to get a good grip on the cigarette between your
teeth. It's time for dinner? What? Oh shit, it kind of is. Oh yeah, they do have dinner. Yeah,
all right, let's end this. Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
You open the drawer and take a pack of cigarettes. Use the hot dog as goggles. I don't know, what the
fuck am I supposed to do now? I'm like, no, I'm just like obsessed with them. You hold the cigar
in your hand and blow on it, letting the smoke escape out of your mouth. You then use the cigar
as a makeshift straw to suck on the smoke coming off of it. As you do so, you see an image appear
in front. Okay, so what is the image in front of me? The image appears to be a young girl's face
looking down at you with tearful eyes. She has long black hair and her skin is pale white. Her eyes
are blue and she looks very sad. Kim looking for a reservation. Say I'm sorry for being late
to the dinner reservation. Say sorry for being late to the dinner reservation.
Quickly turn around and apologize to the woman who is now staring at you with tears streaming
down her cheeks. She doesn't seem to have noticed you yet but she does when you finish apologizing.
Leave and go to dinner with girlfriend. You run outside and rush over to the car where you grab
your keys and purse. You unlock the door and exit the house. You head towards your girlfriend's car
but suddenly you hear a loud noise behind you. What? You're on a lookout. Look behind me. What?
What is it? You turn around and see a huge explosion that seems to come from all directions.
What? It seems to come from all directions. All directions? What do you mean all directions?
Your body feels like it's going numb. What the fuck?
You fall backwards onto the ground still clutching your chest. What happened? What was that? What was
it? What? Look around. You look around and see that the entire street is in flames. What the fuck?
What the fuck? Go to dinner? I'm trying. There are no longer any buildings left. Why was there like a
wake up from my dream? You awaken from your nightmare and realize that you're back home.
You walk in the kitchen to find that everything's intact except for the refrigerator which is broken
and smoking. Inspect the fridge. You examine the fridge and find that it contains several bottles
of beer. You pick up one bottle and sniff it. Why is the fridge smoking? Why is the fridge
smoking? You ask your question aloud and the woman answers. What did she say? No, I got time. I got
time. Smoking with the fridge. What do you mean? Smoking with the fridge means that you put your
mouth close to the side of the fridge and blow out some of its contents. This will make it easier
for you to drink your beer without getting burned. I do that. I know I'm not supposed to do that.
You do exactly that and then take another sip of your beer. The smell is very strong but you
manage to ignore it as you continue drinking. After about half an hour you feel sick so you
vomit into a trash bag and throw it away. I can't. It won't let me leave. You smoke the trash bag and
then throw it away too. You've had enough of alcohol for today. I'm trying. I'm trying to get
to the end. You run full speed into the wall and fall over. You roll onto your stomach and crawl
towards the door but you can't get through it since all the glass has been shattered.
No, I can't. I can't even die. No, not eat glass. I don't want to eat the glass. Eat the glass.
Oh no. I don't want to eat glass. I can't do it. Get up and run full speed into the fridge.
You crawl towards the fridge and try to open it but you don't have much luck. You finally succeed
in opening it when you hear a loud noise. It's like something exploded inside the fridge.
Oh my fucking. Look around. You look around and see that the whole room is covered in broken glass.
There's no way you could have gotten through it. You're going to need more help than just yourself.
Fine. I'll do it. I got time. I got the reservations. No, I'm good. Don't worry.
You grab a piece of broken glass from the floor and start eating it. The taste isn't bad at all.
You finish. Oh, you grab a piece of broken glass from the floor and start eating it.
The taste isn't bad at all. You finish off most of it before you realize what's happening. You
begin vomiting blood and falling into conscious again. Ask the wizards for help. As soon as you
pass out, you suddenly wake up and scream for help. A voice answers back and tells you that
there are no wizards here. They'll say, they say they'll send someone to check on you later,
but right now they want to talk to you privately. End the story. Dude, this has been a long,
we've been going crazy. Uh, Raiden, turn off the game console right now. Raiden, uh, get up and
get up and make it to dinner on time. There are no explosions. No, get up and make it to dinner on
time. Get up and make it to dinner on time. You stand up and make it to dinner on time.
Your stomach rumbles loudly every once in a while, but you still manage to make it.
When dinner's done, you go back to sleep hoping that this was just a nightmare. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. It's not a nightmare. It's a wonderful evening with my girlfriend, our anniversary.
God damn it. Um, wake up and know it was a good time. It was not a nightmare.
There. Um, happy anniversary. There. Okay. I had a good time at our anniversary dinner.
The end. Here we go. You lie down in bed and enjoy your meal after finishing eating your
refresh. Think about how lucky you were to be able to attend an event like this
one day after another. And there it is done. All right. I'll see you guys later.
Oh, I had to play the tune. I don't, I can't. Oh, okay. Remember I told you like three hours
ago that I was going to sneeze. There it is. It happened. That was a lot of fun. But yeah,
I, I gotta get going. Kim and I are doing our anniversary dinner tonight and then tomorrow
we're doing some stuff too. So I will be back. Let's get a good, let's get a schedule here for
the weekend. Yeah. No, no, no, I got time. Don't worry. I got time. I'm not going to miss this
shit. Don't worry guys. Trust me. I'm good. Reservations at like six 45. I have like nine
minutes to get there. It's fine. The joke. I'm kidding. So we got, uh, I'll be back on,
we'll do Friday, Saturday, Sunday of this weekend and we're going to do some cool stuff. We're
going to start on Friday. We're going to do black and white too. Uh, Murius is back this weekend
and maybe that'll take us Friday, Saturday, Sunday. We'll probably start mega man legends
and going into Monday, maybe we'll see. Hopefully you had fun tonight. We'll see you again. I'm
literally pogging. Is physical therapy going good? Yeah. I actually have another appointment
this week in like a day or two, I think. Yeah. But yeah, I gotta get to dinner. Thanks for hanging
out with me for the last five hours or so. A couple of shorter streams in a row here,
but I've been kind of all over the place. I told you February is going to be really busy,
but you do what you got to do, right? I'll see you guys on Friday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
Mark it on your calendars. Have a good one. Let's do the outro. I, I, all jokes aside,
I really do have plenty of time. Don't worry. Don't worry. All these fucking photo shops.
All right. So we had, let's get the bits and everything up. Let's get the music too.
Mega man legends games are on PS3 for $2 on sale. Well, I already, I already owned them for
PlayStation one. So unfortunately I cannot buy those. All right, here we go. Do they look any
better? Are they, it's not that they're increased graphics, is it? Or is it just the same thing?
I don't know. No remaster. Same thing. Okay. Cool. Well, yeah, I got, I got them already,
but a potion dweller. Thanks for 300 bits as a reminder to chat, save your winks for April 1st
or the next day after the first, so that he streams, we're going to do a huge wink dump on
him and make him wink the whole stream. Oh, that's going to be, that's going to be ridiculous. Good
luck with that. Sly 161. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jerma, that wink kind of sucked. Can I have my
money back by reading this? You are contractually obligated to meet my demands by the way. Anyway,
see you later. Um, I don't, I'm not, I don't have my special signing pen, so that's not accurate.
I only sign documents with my special signing pen so nobody can forge it. I know exactly what
the ink looks like. I know the exact color. That's not how it works. Hey, wind sock. Thanks for the
$15, 1500 bits from wind sock. Thanks a lot, man. Today's my birthday. Just want to say thanks for
the years of content. I'm still recovering from second degree burns on my hand. So glad you're
giving me something to do today. That sounds painful. Hopefully you recover well. Follow
your doctor's instructions. Hopefully you heal up nicely. Thanks a bunch for the $15, 1500 bits.
Appreciate it. Hey, dark soul. Thanks for the 250. Mega Man Legends one and two are some of
my favorite games ever. If you stream the zero ZX collection coming out, I'll literally pog my
pants. I swear to God, we're getting a shitload of community subs right now. Uh, when Hawaiian
just gave 10 community subs. Thank you, wine. Just back to back there. Thanks for the sub drops.
I also want to make very clear here. Uh, Twitch staff was in here at link and gave a hundred
community subs. So that's ridiculous. Thanks for, uh, thanks for playing along link. That was fun.
Thank you. The huge amount of subs as well. Uh, super Bruce gave six community subs and like I
said five earlier, so that was wrong, but thank you. Super Bruce basic feral. Thanks for the 1800
bits, 18 bucks. Leave stream for Kim. Don't worry. We've got a whole day plan too. Appreciate it
though. Thanks. That's a huge amount of money. That's nearly $20 in bits. Thank you. Ray the
color. Thanks for the 300 bits. This is the definition of a fuck face stream. If there's
ever been one, uh, why not make community crack night a thing from now on alongside the community
content nights? I don't think you can plan a community crack night. I think they just kind
of happen whenever you guys do crack. No one wants a community crack night. Uh, 4,500 bits
came in from Goiki. So nearly $50. I didn't touch upon it earlier. That's a lot of fucking money.
We love you. Ego maniac streamer. Thanks for the huge money drop. Thanks for the $50 4500 bits
from Goiki. You're still here. Thank you. Kind of early to end. Yes it is, but I have to,
it's me and my girlfriend's anniversary. So we have dinner reservations. So that's why this stream
is ending shorter than usual tonight. I'm a crack by a snack is better when it happens organically.
Yeah, I agree. I don't, you can't like plan on something like that, but thank you. Goiki. Hey,
gnarly. Thanks for the two 50. It's kind of sad how your ironic joke about winks being too much
effort for you turned to reality. What are you talking? What do you mean? Derma hates winks.
This is from Diablo two. Like that's so hard. Oh, God, God damn it. I have to, somebody watched my
stream for like 60 hours. I have to turn on my camera and go like this. God damn it. It's like
such a, so hard to do that apparently. Well, I know I've seen the, I've seen the German like
lights a spoon up and does crack. Anyways. Yeah. What do you want me to say? It's been, it's hard.
Where's my, what'd I do with my thing? I lost it. How, how did I lose it already?
No, it's gone. Uh, X out of the window. It's this crack spoon. I know it's not crack,
but anyways, uh, yeah, the way don't, the winks are not going anywhere. Don't worry.
I will do them. Hey, autumn dragons. Thanks for the two 50. You should replace the wink with
turning on a face cam, but also add another 75,000 reward to turn off the face cam.
No one's going to turn it off. People will turn it on. No one's going to spend 75,000 to turn it
off. No, I should have it be 75,000 to turn it on and two to turn it off. Thanks though.
Earl of illusion. Thanks for the two 50. Here's some more bits towards taking Kim to see Sonic
on Valentine's day. I swear to God, you're actually going to like it. I mean, Jim carries in it. I
probably love it. And bumpy here. Sorry about that. What's this? Get rid of this. How do I
get rid of this? Wait, what? I don't want to play Metro Exodus. What the fuck is going on?
Why can I not delete this? Hey, you person that just landed on the channel page. Okay,
that was fucking weird. Um, oh shit. I just deleted the credits. I just deleted the credits. Come on
that I replied. That was where the credits were. That's why I was confused.
Too many tabs. Hold on. Those are the stream labs credits. Everyone. Hold on. Wait, wait,
I hold away. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta get, I gotta fix this. Wait, how do I, I can,
can I control? Okay, wait. No, no, no, I don't. I can undo. Hey, you person that just landed on
the channel page. Turn it off. Okay. I can fix it. All right. Give me a second. Oh, he's got good
dental. Dental implants. Hold on. Why does this keep happening to me? How do you hate your past?
I don't. I would delete all this stuff if I didn't like it. What did I search? What are you talking
about? You just scammed a wink. No, no, no, no. I didn't. I didn't. I promise.
I just have, my credits got fucking deleted. Hold on. There we go. All right. Here we go. Here
come the credits. No, nobody got scammed. Roll them. There they are. Thanks a lot. Everybody for the
subs. Don't worry. You get your wink. Here it comes. You will get your wink right here. Check
it out. And that was, that was a full cam wearing fucking star. Yeah. Yes. Yes. I'm wearing a star
war shirt. Whatever. Who cares? You know, I'm, I'm not wearing this to dinner. I'm going to change.
You think I'm going to go to my girlfriend during dinner anniversary in a star war shirt?
No, I'm not completely out of my mind. It's just, that's easy. All right. I don't need to
explain myself. Okay. Let's go. But thank you, link. Thank you. All the subs. There's a ton of
them were community subs from today. A hundred from link. Thank you. Earl of illusions for that
felt Sonic the hedgehog. Appreciate it. Of course I'm going to like that movie. Red Walrus. Thanks
for the 300 bits. What's your favorite Warhammer faction? It's the Tao 40 K or fantasy 40 K.
You can't pick the Skaven. That's cheating. Everyone likes the rats. It's the Tao.
I like the Tao. I think they have like an interesting, uh, units. You're going to be
late to your reservation. No. Uh, what is it? X, X V 22 battle suit, X V 22 battle suit ready.
I like the hero and he's cool. Yeah, that's the one. Thank you. Red Walrus, the three bits, 300
bits. Hey, your boy. Thanks for the 10 community subs. I missed it, but thanks for 10 subs given
to the community. Shazzo ready to take command. That's right. Mr. Chachimur. Mr. Chachimur.
Thanks for the 300 bits. They just say hi, Jerma. Hi. Lizard Amiibo 300 bits. Thanks for really
great stream tonight. It's been one of my favorites. That's good to know. Thank you. Also, thanks for
helping me escape my bathroom. You're welcome. Secret technique. If you ever get yourself in a
situation like that, careful. The point. Thanks for 300 bits. The point. Jerma, this is such a
good stream. I hope you have a good anniversary with Kim. Uh, this is so funny and amazing. Holy
shit. Laughing my ass off. Thank you. LOL. LOL. Dark soul. Thanks for the 250. Haha. Guess that
didn't happen. Hey, will you marry me? Enraged grandpa. Thanks for the 500 bits. Pull out the
fight stick. Me? You're talking about me? No, I can't. No. Hey, disinterest. Thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, I once saw a clip of you showing how loud you can make your voice. I was wondering if
you've ever used that skill to shatter wine glasses. And that's why you drink wine out of sippy cups.
Cheers. No, just hurt people's ears around me and annoy them. Pretty much it. Hey,
Ferodian weapon. Thanks for the 500 bits, Ferodian. Five bucks. Hope you and Kim have a happy
anniversary. Also hope the physical therapy is going well. Love the streams as always, even if
I'm not really as active in the community I used to be. As I used to be. These streams always put
a smile on my face. I'll get the hell out of here and go seek him. Oh, I am. Yeah, the PT is going
well. I only had one appointment, so I'm gonna wait and see how it goes over the next three,
four weeks. See what happens after that. Thanks a lot, Ferodian. Worm club. Thanks for the 500
bits, worm club. Jerma, I've been watching your streams and VODs for only a few months,
but I've already joined the had a dream about Jerma club. I dreamt that you got your start
making webcam videos of yourself smoking massive amounts of keif and reviewing it set to cheesy
psychedelic music. Anyway, love you, man. Hope your PT fixes you up and you don't have to smoke keif
for pain. Happy anniversary to you and Kim. Thanks a lot, worm club. A marijuana review stream.
I almost, it would take a little, some effort, but it would be kind of funny.
This is by the way, add this to the list of things that I'm going to say that I'm never going to do,
but it'd be funny. Is to get a bunch of dreams that people have had about me and just reenact
them and just have like a watch all these streams. Like just do a watch party. It's like three hours
of just fucked up dreams people have had. It would take a lot of effort. It would be kind
of funny though. Hey Tingy, thanks for the 250. Remember how you once talked about how you don't
read resubs and vids during gameplay portions of the stream because they get in the way and derail
the stream? Well, the winks are essentially that, but with fake currency to do it. True, but also,
but also true. The winks take one second. Reading a sub message and responding to a sub of the
message takes, as you see here, a good, sometimes I spend one, two, five minutes on a message.
It usually takes about a minute or two. I turn the webcam on and I go,
bang, the webcam goes off in about four seconds. Sometimes you get distracted by your own face.
Don't worry, the winks are going to last as long as they need to. What do you think
German smells like? Oud. Mystery salt. That's true. Thank you, Tingy, though. Appreciate it.
Supra 10 touring and thanks for the 300 bits. German funny question is, your hat in the channel
trailer from a certain city starting with a P in Massachusetts. Don't answer if you aren't comfortable.
Um, let me see. I don't think so. I think that's like a Longhorns hat. Hold on. Let me see.
Yeah, that's a Longhorns hat. Sorry. That is a Texas Longhorns hat. Why did I have a Texas
Longhorns hat? I don't, I cannot tell you the reason why. I think, I think it was my brother's
hat. I can't believe he likes the towel. Why? Hey, and finally we have, well, let me get this back
to where we need to be because this is the end of the stream. This is the end. Uh, we have five
dollars from Daddy. Thank you, Daddy, for the 500 bits. You excited for the Gorillaz and Tame
Impala collab? Congrats on the anniversary, man. Yeah, I mean, any Gorillaz album I'm excited for.
Although I really, I wish, I know that David Alburn does this thing sometimes and all of his,
I love pretty much anything he does and anything, anybody he collabs with and all the music that
they make. But so like Humans came out, right? And then it was the now now, like not even a year
later. And I think, doesn't he do this sometimes where he just kind of, let's get it out, get it
out. Let's get like 20 more tracks out. And they were like recorded on the road. Uh, he did that
with another album before too. But what was the one, the Fall where he did it like on the road?
So is this, is this gonna, it's not, this is not an album from my understanding. This is sort of
this kind of new series they're going to be doing. It's not an album. It's just like a series of
music or in videos and stuff. It's not an album, right? Anybody correct me here? Yeah, I think so.
Kind of. It'll eventually be an album, but for now it's just a series. Okay.
No, that's cool. That's pretty cool. You have five minutes for your reservation. No. Daddy again,
thanks for the 500 bits. So yeah, I asked if your favorite band, who your band was.
I said that wrong. I asked who your favorite band was on the comb stream and checked them out
and heard about it the other day. I think it's a single or series. Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
I'm glad you checked them out. They're a great band. And my favorite songs are Gorilla songs.
Please notice me, Jeremiah. I'm too poor for your rich minimum requirement price. Hey,
Gondolaine, how the fuck are you? Done. Noticed. Yeah, no, I'm looking forward to whatever they
come up with. And I'm going to go seek him. I will see you guys on Friday. Black and White 2.
Murius will probably return if we can get a cow. See you guys on Friday. We'll do all weekend.
Good night. Goodbye. And who is streaming right now? What do we have? Who's live?
Anybody live right now that we can go scream at? Go say hi to Joel.
He's playing Quake 2. Cooking Simulator. Wait, is he playing Cooking Simulator right now?
Is he Cooking Simulator? Because that's fun. Oh, he's doing Quake. Okay.
All right. Yeah, go say hi to Joel. Tell Joel I said.
Show Joel the mirror. All right. I'll see you guys on Friday. Take care. Good night. Bye. Much love.