Shut up! I wasn't even recording. Oh my god, yes I can hear you. Alright, so looks like we figured out that there is...
Shut the fuck up! You wanna be my partner? You, me and you, you have no eyes. Alright, so I'm the driver, where are you?
I'm tactical interventioning in the back. Is there a different camera view I can use? No.
We're gonna find the marijuana plant. Are you actually driving? Cause you haven't crashed yet and I don't know why you haven't done that on purpose.
You mean like that? That wasn't a crash. That was, wait, wait, oh. That was terrible.
What are these guys? Let me out. Can you get out? No, I can only see trees inside the car. Alright, well, let's see.
We're just trying to be like a good Samaritan. Hold on, I need to just check something first.
I gotta like make sure that these guys are not breaking the law. Okay.
Oh, we have to do this again. We have to do this whole driving sequence for a second time.
I'm just sitting in the back seat of this car. Just because I like bumped that guy.
Here we go. This is where we still haven't done anything. Did you hear that music build up? Yeah, this music is like really intense.
For what? Just to strive to connect the dots in like an old highlights book? To your right, to your right, to your right, dude.
Alright, look, it's actually running. I'm dead. I need help. I need Obama. Obama, please. Come on, Obama.
Oh, I got you. Yes, sir. I got you, my friend. I wish this is how real life worked.
What, being able to revive from somebody putting their hand down at you and grabbing you?
Oh, you got like 12 bullet wounds. Let me put my hand down on you. Speaking of hand down, everybody died.
I ran so far forward. Obama didn't come to help me. Look, I don't want to have died. Obama came to come help me instead of you.
Don't hit the weed, man. It's good shit. Light this place up. Plant bomb. Torch this place to hell. What, do I not remember the code?
You know, you do kind of have to get... What? How did I die? Did you really? No, we have to start over again.
Back to the car. Oh, wow, that was such a ridiculous mission. I can't wait to see what the next one is.
Activate. What am I doing? Concentrator mode. It's slow motion. What? They really have that in this game? Why is that in this game?
Is there any reason for that? Yes. What's the reason? Oh, okay. Yeah, that's a good reason. Let's go.
I'm leaning out the window for your information. Watch out for that helicopter flying through the forest.
That helicopter was literally driving in the forest. Like, how? Do you like that turn? These car physics, man. This is tactical intervention all over again.
I don't think I'm supposed to be doing this. What? We were flying. I drove up the ramp of that car.
I remember this area in tactical intervention. This bridge. This really is from tactical intervention. It's the same game.
I'm out the window. Shoot these guys. I'm doing it. You got to take them out, big. This is tactical intervention.
This is this is what we left in mission area. Look at how we're not supposed to go down this road. It's over here.
Okay. What? I don't even know where we're supposed to be going. The only thing we have is the connect the dots.
Oh, okay. Well, that was interesting. Oh, my God. That was that was worth downloading this game.
Oh, I need to I need to call a burger boy and tell him that he can't come over yet because this is getting interesting.
What the hell? Hold on. Sorry, dude. Hold on. What the fuck? That was unbelievable. I'm like on the phone and like the phone pops up on the screen.
Hey, sorry. I'm talking like three people at the same time. I'm wicked. Sorry, Burger Boy.
So do you want to use the third? Don't come like now because I just realized I'm like recording.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, dude. I'll call you in like a half an hour. I'm sorry.
All right. Bye. That looks so fucking stupid. It's so weird that this whole time we've played that no phone time.
You were on the phone and now we're done with the phone. You hang up now. Burger Boy is like pissed at me.