Yeah, I thought everybody was ignoring me. Like, there's no way that all of them can collectively
pretend that I'm not streaming. I was like, this is kind of crazy.
It's like, all right, maybe they can. Because I saw a bunch of- I saw at least five or six people
in all capitals live, live, live. But I think people just say that, no matter what, just to,
I guess, fuck with other people to pretend that I was live. Like, they had a stream, but other
people didn't. I was like, wait, how does that make any sense? I was sitting here talking to
nothing for at least 60 seconds. I did a Twitch broadcast test, an internet test. I was just
checking different things with this new connection to see what the best route is. And I think I got
it. I forgot it was on. So, it was still on when I pressed the now it's time to really stream. We
have 10 community subs from the chef's corner. The chef's corner has been incredibly generous
lately. Thank you, chef's corner. Appreciate it. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Welcome back,
though, guys. Hi, nice to see you. We have a very, very interesting week planned ahead of us here.
Well, mid-week into weekend. We're going to go back to the crack game. I just- the drug dealer
simulator. The crack game. We're just going to call it the crack game. That's what it is.
A nondescript civilian. Thanks for 10 community subs. 10 from nondescript and 10 from the chef's
corner. Thanks, both of you guys. Yeah, we're going to play the drug dealer game again just
for a little bit. I just want to play it. I'm kind of into it. I'll probably get my fill of it today.
Who knows? But tomorrow, we're going to get the real- the real schedule here. Because I've been
flipping it around because like, oh, it's going to be Thursday. That's going to be on Saturday.
That's going to be on Sunday. But that's going to be on Friday. But I want to play the crack game.
So let's- let's get it for real with the real thing here. Crack game tonight. Tomorrow,
we're going to do community content night. That leaves us with the weekend of Friday and Saturday.
Friday is going to be movie night. So that will actually be happening on Friday. Public domain
movie night is Friday. Like, that's- that's just it. That's the one- that's the day it's going to be.
Saturday is supposed to be the Easy Bake Oven stream. But I'm- I'm telling you right now,
I'm having a little bit of reservations on it for one reason. I can't- I- this- a space.
I probably am going to have to go to the studio to do the Easy Bake Oven stream.
Now imagine taking that phone call. Oh yeah, this is- this is the movie studio. Hi, yeah,
remember me? Oh yeah, the green screen guy. Yeah, that's me. What can I do for you? Oh, you know,
thinking about coming and using your space to use an Easy Bake Oven. That's all. I just want to use
an Easy Bake Oven at the studio. Oh, you just- that's it. Yeah, that's it. I just have like
20 recipes. Why don't you just do it at your house? Well, you know, because I want the space and I
want to be able to like fucking do like lookabays and stuff. I can't like- there's not enough space
with the cameras to catch me doing like lookabay when in the middle of it. Oh, that makes perfect
sense, Mr. Albertson. Absolutely. So, if I cannot get studio space by Saturday, then I'm- we're
gonna- we'll do it like a day or two later. But I'm gonna be in the studio for the Easy Bake Oven
stream. It just- I'm just gonna. Like, whatever. I'm gonna put like a fucking chef background
behind me on the green screen. It'll be a- it'll be a mess. Don't worry. Is the studio open? Oh,
shit. Ah, yeah. That's another thing, isn't it? Huh. Well, I- here's the thing. I have to assume
maybe because- oh, no. No, it's not. It probably won't be, right? Because it's like a- because
there's no- like, oh. I'll check. I'll check. I'll see. Because when you rent studio space,
nobody else is- nobody's there. It's like you're- you're renting part of the studio. So,
it's not like there'll be a bunch of people around. Um, I have no idea. I have to make a
few phone calls. Oh, Easy Bake Oven stream. Fucking cancelled. No. Uh, I just wanted to have
some more space. Oh, and the Toontown stream. First was the Toontown stream. No. Let's- let's
see what happens. If I have to do it from here, I will. But I have to set up the cameras in a way
where I can see everything. Because I don't want to have a- all right, listen. For streams that
happen when I'm on camera, I don't want another unlock card game stream. And what I mean by that
is forget about how fucking bad that stream could have- potentially was because the stream was just
bad, right? Let's talk about like how you couldn't see anything. You couldn't read the text. You
couldn't see the close-up. I want to make sure that there's like- you can see stuff. That stream
was horrible. I don't think it was horrible. It was bad. It was pretty bad because you couldn't
even like see. You couldn't read. I couldn't do basic children's math problems. Yeah, and you
couldn't read anything. The camera wasn't good enough. You know what I mean? I want to make sure
I don't fall down that path again. It wasn't as bad as Hearthstone. Wow, you must have hated that
stream. You must have hated that Hearthstone stream. But anyways, we're gonna play a more crack game.
Just gonna play it for a few hours. And then tomorrow, community content night,
I will get that prepared. It should be community content night up until-
like I'm like forever behind on community content night. We might have to do like a lightning round
to catch up because it's gonna be from like February like 10th- 15th or something to like March
15th. I'm gonna be forever like 30 days behind community content night. And I even did
two to- I didn't want to catch up and it didn't matter. No, skip. No, skip. No, skip. You're a
year behind the green screen stream. Well, if I get into the studio, then I can do a little bit
in front of the screen. I'll be there. But let's play. I'm gonna play this video game.
Or you know what it is. Move the thing so you can see. He's a year behind on VR. That's not
true. When was the last time I played VR? I played VR. I thought that was in my house.
I thought this was my room. And that just scared the shit out of me. I was like,
somebody open my door? When was the last time I played VR? It wasn't a year ago. It was like
two months ago. It was a long time ago. All right, what were we doing? I just got access to
ecstasy. By the way, I'm like just thinking about this right now. If you happen to
not know what was going on in here, and you just heard like from outside the door,
or like if you heard me talking like this, what would do you think? That'd be weird, right?
Okay, yeah, so I just got access to ecstasy. How much should I buy?
I'm gonna say like 20 grams of ecstasy and I'll sell the amphetamines.
That's I'm gonna be like quiet. Okay, I'm gonna like say these things quietly. I don't know.
You know what I mean? Like that's just fucking weird. All right, so I'm gonna call it. No,
I'm gonna. All right, there's orders. Remember Whisper, my mom's in the room. Drugs, drugs,
drugs, drugs. How did I just do that? That was 50 fucking thousand dollars from Freddy Dredd.
Freddy Dredd just gave 50 community subs. Freddy Dredd just drops thousands of dollars here.
The man, Freddy Dredd. Thanks a lot, Freddy. Thanks for the 50 fucking subs. That's so much.
Like I've, I've dropped like 100 community subs before. I've dropped like 500 community subs
before. That's a lot. Like 20, 30, 40, 50 subs, 100 subs. That's fucking a lot of money. It's,
I can't even believe people would do it. Thanks so much for fucking doing it.
That was a humble brag. No, no, that's me saying like I looked at my bank account after doing it
and went, holy fucking shit. That's a lot of money. But thanks, Freddy. And I'm just like,
I'm shocked that people want to give me that kind of money. That's what I'm saying. Thank you.
Flex, flex, flex. I just did it and it wasn't even on camera, but you know what I did?
I did, you, you, you saw it in your head. I didn't even need to do it on camera.
My fist went up, my fucking boink. I went like that, you know, like bonk.
All right. I got a fucking play. All right. I need weed, six grams of weed, two grams of amps.
No ecstasy, anymore weed. Okay. We need six grams of, uh, marijuana. Do I have marijuana? I do.
I need six grams. I'm almost out of marijuana. Fuck. And I have to buy more. What do I have?
Okay. So now I need, what do I need? Amphetamines and MDMA? I remember when this was a wholesome
Twitch channel. Not anymore. I've activated the mature audience filter. That means that if you
click on this stream, you are agreeing that you are a mature audience member. It has been activated.
Why do I keep thinking this shit is happening in my real fucking place? I was like, what? I was like,
are we being invaded? What the fuck is going on? I like, what am I supposed to, I keep thinking
this stuff is real. All right. We have six grams of marijuana. We have 10 more community subs on
top of the fucking shit load that I've already come through from numb legs. Thank you. Numb legs
for the 10 subs and more fucking oink. Six grams of, what was it? Weed. Okay. Two amphetamine.
Four amphetamine. Six amphetamine. Two ecstasy. Six amphetamine. Two ecstasy. Six amphetamine.
Two ecstasy. Six amphetamine. Two ecstasy. Six ecstasy. No. Six amphetamine. Six amphetamine.
Two, four, six. Two, what was it? MDMA. Do I have any MDMA or is it gone? One. Oh, here we go. Yeah,
I got, what am I, what are these other things? It's been a couple of days. I don't know. What
is this stuff? Dry rub amphetamine. One pack of ecstasy. One pack of new, new sugar mix mix.
And then $70. Okay. Well, I can, I can deliver this shit. Gotta be aware. 16 of, oh man. Okay.
Hold on. I need 16 more. All right. 16 of MDMA. What was this other one? Mike Byers. Oh right. I
just bought a place. All right. I'm ready to take all these. Here we go. I'm gonna make some money
here. That's my dealer, right? Yeah. What are my skill points again? All right. Illusionist.
So what's, what's, what's the actual percentage? What's the actual percentage? Bernie, what do
you mean? Bernie and Bernie in chat. Bernie Sanders in chat. The real Bernie's in chat.
I don't think that's not, I don't believe so. I don't think so. I really don't believe so.
Oh, it's probably a fake name. It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a fake name. All right. I got it.
I got a delivery. It's cause somebody gifted him a sub. Yeah. All right. So yeah. That trick
only works a handful of times guys, before you sub every single game developer to me,
every major Twitch broadcaster and like five out of 10 of the celebrities I've talked about.
Like, holy shit dude. Wait, Jim Carrey was here? At Jim Carrey. He's got a sub dude. He's fucking
subbed. What? Jim Carrey subbed me? There's only so many times you can play that joke before I know.
All right. I'm looking for the police. All right. We're good. Nope. But he, he doesn't know. No,
I know. I do know. I got, when was the dealer? He wanted two grams of amphetamines.
One, two grand pack. Thank you sir. $24. Every, oh dude, did you know every celebrity you've ever
heard of all subscribes to you? Two grams of amphetamines. You got it. Oh shit. They don't
see me, right? No. All right. I gotta go. I gotta go across the street. Holy shit. I can't believe
real Taylor Swift and then, hey, super frog. Thank you super Bruce for the 20 subs. This is
just back to back to back to back to back subs. Thanks for the 20 subs, dude. Seriously.
That's so much money. That's so much money. Thank you super frog.
Oh, thanks Bruce. Oh, this is the big one. This is 16. 16 grams. Take it. There you go.
And I got you right next to you, Donald. He wanted the six grams of marijuana.
There you are. I'm almost at level uh, what was level eight, level 10? I've done almost all of
them. Can you fast travel or something? One of these days somebody's actually going to be here.
One of these days somebody's actually going to click on this fucking shitty stream
because somebody like linked them and they're going to just, they're going to show up and it,
what? No, no, no. Well, yeah. Let me finish my thought. Like, hey, dude. Oh, Taylor Swift.
Check out this streamer. Oh, he's so cool. And they're going to get here and I'm just going to be
going. And this, this is what happens when you make a fucking joke. This is what happens. This is what
you deserve. This is what I deserve. Where's my house? Where's my house? Oh my God. Long story
short, there ain't no fucking celebrities here. There's no one here. Nobody's here. It's just you.
It's just you and me. We're the only two people that are here. It's just us. And I just lost the
money that I just sold. It's just like us, us 5,000 people. There ain't no celebrities. There's like,
Bobby Flay's not here, guys. Okay. It's okay. See, see right now somewhere in sunny California,
Bobby Flay is in his, is in his pajamas sitting there watching German 95 going, oh shit.
Oh, I don't know. Nobody thinks it's real. That's all right. Holy shit though. Wow. That was almost
bad. I can't fucking believe I lost everything. No, that was going so well. Oh, God damn it.
What do these guys want? At least I got the, I got the, I got the ecstasy to the dealer though.
That's the good thing. That was a family guy joke. No, that was a Jeremy Elbertson joke because I
just said it. Just because family guy goes like, Hey, wouldn't it be funny if, wouldn't it be funny
if, doesn't mean anybody else can go, Hey, wouldn't it be funny if, his family guy has not tarnished
the wouldn't it be funny if scenario. I refuse to believe that. And if they did, then that's a sad
day. All right, let's go back to the house. Oh, now we're going to say F. Oh, now we're, no, F's in
the chat, huh? That's so funny. It's hysterical. People do F's in the chat. Oh, he's getting
fibrid. Wait, wait, what? I knew I should, I did all those tests. I, I shouldn't have done that.
I shouldn't have done that. I shouldn't have done that. It's all right. I changed servers.
I shouldn't have done that. I knew it. I shouldn't have done it. Which one of these is my house?
See, I was doing through the VPN. I was just testing different servers. Which one's, hey,
but maybe let's try this one and see what the speeds on this one are. And I changed it and I
was like, yeah, that one, that one looks good. And I was fine. I don't know why I changed the
server. It was my own fault, but it's fine. All right. I still have plenty of drugs. Don't worry.
Did we just get somebody's more money come in? Are you feeling the burn? Thanks to the five
community subs and sweaty man. Thanks for five community subs using a VPN. Yeah. And it works
perfectly good. But I, I, what, why, why, why is this such a problem? No, I'm not streaming with
that. I'm not streaming with the one that people get paid to use. Okay. It's a different one.
And it's a secret because I don't know. It's, I like, I don't know. I have, I have my,
my virtual private fucking station, whatever it is, VPS. What? I don't use that one. No,
that's not the one. I don't use that one. No, I don't use that one. Stop saying that. You're
going to get me in trouble and I don't want to get in trouble. I don't want to get in trouble.
I've done. No, that's that one. No, it's not. All right. Okay. You guys are distracting the
fuck out of me today. I got arrested because you were distracting me. That's a real drug deal
like that. Hey, you got the stuff? Yeah, I got the stuff. All right. Hey, yeah. Come over here.
What do I owe you? You owe me. Hold on a second. I got a phone call. Hey, hey, hey, imagine if
Bobby Flay was, was calling me right now. Hey, Bobby Flay. Hey, it's me, Bobby Flay.
Can you imagine, dude? No, I think it's my mom. Hey, can we just like get this over with and,
whoa, I hear the, hold on. I think I hear the police, man. Hey, we're over here.
Imagine if they came over here after I yelled at them. Hey, look at this. Hey, have you ever
seen somebody do a stance like this? And you do like a fucking look at me. That person does
not keep going. I can't figure out if this is a minus two or a plus two. You don't have to
figure it out at all. Just fucking watch the TV. Why don't we have so many fucking
comedy detectives in here? Just watch the television. I'm trying to figure out if I
liked that or not. Let me do some math. All right, let's put this down. Wait, let me check the TV.
It's not, it's a laptop. Nobody to write. I got, at least I got it off to her. This is the important
one. I have nothing. Did I just sleep? No offense, but I think the look at me thing is really dumb.
Me too. That's the only thing that pays the bills nowadays. Okay. So just give me, just let me do
it every now and then, man. Come on. Come on, man. Oh, I got three words. Look at me, me and
the spider one. Just shut the fuck up, man. You're trying to ruin this for me. Take this out. I need
new clients. I need my, did they take the bag too? Please don't tell me they took the bag. Okay,
thank God. Hey, Justice Nugget, thanks for the five community subs. And what does he say every
time he gets five community subs? He says, look at me. Thanks though. Jesus Christ. Ballinx, thanks
for the five subs and Justice Nugget, thanks for the five subs. I have to give these free samples
away to people. Pick this up. Until I get my drug deal. What are the tasks? I need five addicts.
Check out the furniture shop. I already did that. Two grams of ecstasy, two grams of ecstasy,
two grams of ediphenibine, two grams of ecstasy. I have that. Okay. Thank God. Didn't take everything.
Store this. Actually keep a little bit out. Oh, this is the mixed up shit. This is the thing you
guys are all screaming. Wait a minute. This is not even ecstasy. I just faked myself out.
This is the fake shit. And I just thought it was real. That means it's good. I'll keep the
marijuana. Put the money away. I want to break this up. Let's put that on here. All right, here we go.
Finally. No, no, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop. I hate F. Everybody else like hate F where E should be.
You know what I mean? I feel like that's not just me. F, F. Oh, no. No. Okay. You wanted to
put the rest of this shit away. No, put... I'm just gonna... Can I just throw this in the trash?
How do you get rid of drugs? I know this is not looking up how to dispose of a battery,
right? How do you get rid of batteries? But still, what am I supposed to do?
Okay, put this away. I want enough to give a couple samples out. All right, let's go.
I'm gonna get fucking arrested again. You cook a steak with it. You eat them. You don't waste them.
You don't waste... Did you hear that? I was like... I can't even do that again. Yes, I do. I have a
backpack on. That was like a full-on like... Wow, that was... I can't even replicate that.
Let's go. Is this thing bugged though? Because remember I went in the furniture shop last time?
Why is it not doing it? All right, here we go. Free sample. Hey, I have a free present for you.
It's one pack of marijuana. Try it on the house. I have something for you too. I have a one gram
pack of amphetamines. Take two. Take two. Share. There we go. Finally. I have to be getting close
to the next level, right? We're making drug addicts. I mean, that's the best point of the game. Hey,
you click the mature content thing. You can be here. I wanted two grams of ecstasy. Okay,
put that over there. Okay. Watch out for the police. What did you want? Two grams of amphetamines?
Yep. Share. Why do I sound weird? I don't know. I shouldn't. I sound weird? Is that a one guy
scenario? I mean, it failed. I just gave it to him. Oh, I don't sound weird. It's the game.
It's the fucking game. The game is playing twice. Right. Because sorry, I turned off my computer and
turned it back on and opened the GoXLR app, which resets my settings every single time I open this
program. I don't know why this happens every single time. Just save. Why can't I just save?
Do I have to make a full-on new profile? I'm on the dumb-up. Why would I make a new profile
or something? What the fuck? There you go. I will tell you though. I mean, you guys probably know
this by now. If there's ever a product that you hear me talk about that I like, get it as fast
as you can because that means it's good and it's real and I actually mean it. I'm serious
because everything I use, I just go, this sucks. This is stupid. This product is terrible. Do I
like anything? Have I been satisfied with any products I've ever purchased? What was the last
time I was satisfied fully with a product where I was like, man, I'm McDonald's. Yeah, but okay.
Okay, that's true. So go get McDonald's, I guess. That's the only thing that satisfies me.
That's fucking ridiculous. I mean, I can't think of one time where I've been like,
oh, McDonald's fucking, McDonald's like sucks. This thing sucks. I haven't said that in a long
time. Well, actually, that's not true. McDonald's, it depends on what McDonald's, right? Because they
differ in quality. One McDonald's could be a zero and another McDonald's could be a
six and they both serve the exact same menu. So that's hard to determine. You could go to a
nine out of 10 McDonald's and be like, wow, this is amazing. And then you go to a zero McDonald's
and it's just like they threw together the lettuce and they didn't even fold it correctly.
The bun is like soggy and off to the side and fucked up and the thing's cold. It's the same
food. That happens. He's a picky eater. What? No, that happens. The soggy lettuce and the
bun off to the side. Like, come on. Whenever I open it up and the bun is like wet and off to the side,
don't you just go like, oh, I do that. All right, we got to do seven grams of speed. I have it.
Here we go. Money. This is going to be a big buy. How close am I to the next stage here?
I'm almost at stink. I need 800 respect. Bristol meth is the next thing. Oh boy. When do we get
crack? You were one of those mac and cheese and hot dog kids every day, huh?
Wow. How wrong could somebody be? It was captain crunch. Get it right. Okay. Let's go. I have
any more deals? No, I just need amphetamines. Any more amphetamines? Should I just mix some
of this shit together? What did he want? Seven? Shit. Okay. Well, I'm going to have to give this
guy junk. Does this even have amphetamines in it? You know, it's bad when you don't even know
if there's even 1% amphetamines in this. The dry rub has it, right? It's getting dry rub.
What's that command? Oh, it's a fart command. How do I stamp a giant like notary stamp on this chat
room with minus two right now? How do I do that? Can I do that? Well, you get to do it to me.
No, no, I didn't want to change scenes. I wanted to see how you like it. Let's see how you guys
like this. When you look at the screen, this is all I see when I look at the screen.
This is all you see when you look at the screen. It's blurry. Well, sorry. OBS apparently doesn't
have vector-based graphics. Maybe I should ring him up and ask him. Well, he knows what
vector-based graphics is. I thought he was stupid. I got to rethink everything. $180.
Late. I don't want any drugs on me. You wanted the seven. Okay. He's going to hate this, but
I'm sorry, dude. Just take the dry rub and whatever. Bye. That's it. Anti-ali. All right.
Fine. You learned your lesson. None of you did. None of you did. Not one person did. Okay. 378
bucks. I got five points. Where's it going? Ah, fresh coffee. I like coffee, right? I can't do
illusion. I need six. I like, I love coffee. I'm going to say either quick learner or I'm doing
a quick learner. I want more experience. Yeah. EXP is good. Okay. I have to, now I just have to
unlock the new area. I can say the thing. Maybe one day. All right. Let's go back to the house.
Sorry. I phone vibrated that to you. Did you get it? I'm going to enhance it.
Wait, what did he say there? Check. Zoom in a little.
A little more. 10% more. Coffee, Cheetos, chicken. There it is. Yes. I knew it. He's still,
he does still love us. Fire. After 10 years. I heard you sell candy. I need four grams. Sure.
Delivering soon. That's all I have. I should probably get my, what was in, is there, can I
send this to a lab and find out what was in it? What's in this? I don't know what's in here.
I need to get a pill press, but I don't have access to it yet. This was sugar and ecstasy.
Just find out. This was ecstasy and dry rub. Why does dry rub have to be in everything? All right.
One gram of ecstasy. And then I'm going to, I'm going to do, somebody said that they left the
stream last time because they said this is such a bad organization. They refused to watch the
stream. So for that person, I'm going to make, I'm going to change this and make it look a little
nicer. All right. Let's get this out. Then I need to do, no, let me do another drug order.
I'm going to get a bunch of everything. I'll get a little of everything. I'll get some,
I'll get a little bit of, what do I want? Yeah. I want an order. I'll get a little bit of
marijuana, a little bit of amphetamines, and yeah, we'll get like 20 grams of marijuana,
a little bit of amphetamine, 20 grams of amphetamines, and then like 30 grams of,
I don't want too much of that. Why do I feel like I'm ordering off of a Chili's menu?
I can buy that, right? 580 bucks. All right. Let's go. Yo, I'm looking for grass. I need two grams.
Not yet. It's a subway subway. Yeah. I'll take a, an Italian, an Italian sub please. All right.
What do you want for cheese? I'll give me the Swiss, the Swiss triangles. Okay. Any more? Yeah.
I'll take some cheddar too. Okay. What kind of vegetables do you want? I'm thinking maybe,
maybe some of the kale. Okay. Yeah. Anything else? Maybe some, some of the spinach too.
All right. What drugs do you want? And he moves it down the little line and there's like six tins.
There's like fucking amphetamines. They're all crushed up and he sprinkles it in.
That's fucking ridiculous. That's a South Park joke. No, I don't want to give him everything.
Why? I don't even, I'm not even, because of like a barometer of every show you've ever seen and
everything they've ever said. That would have been funny, but I think I've seen that on Family Guy
once. Who even watches that show anymore? No, you can't have any of these. This is for somebody else.
Wait, is this for you? No. That's the real stuff too. Stream needs more Tom and Jerry jokes.
All right. I'll be right back. Let me go get a hammer and I'll hit myself in the fucking head
with a hammer. That's, is that you sure you want me to do that? Okay. Let me need more Tom and Jerry.
Who would be Tom? My left hand and Jerry would be the right. There we go. Oh, I got some new places
in my offer. I don't, I can't. All right. Is that, that's two hours from now. Damn. Okay. Speed,
grass, ecstasy. I need spray cans. I got to spray paint my tag around. Chat, stop being horny for
five minutes. Um, you know, I've thought, I've thought to say the same thing before,
but it's, they're uncontrollable. This is adults only. They're insane. I can't stop them. It's like,
what was his name? Odysseus, whatever his name was, the guy, like the god, the Greek god. And he was
like, I have total power. And everyone listened to him for a while. And then like they rose up
and fucking took him over and they became like their own gods. No, that was the French revolution.
What am I thinking of? Cronos. Yes. That's what I'm saying. Cronos. Cronos thought he had all power
and then like he fucking had to like eat his kids or something. Shit got all fucked up.
I just have to sit here. Wait, that was Saturn. Wait, what did Cronos do? Cronos was like the god
of time. No, don't base your knowledge on gods by what you know and what the smite god can do.
He's not the god of time. Yeah. Cronos had the ability to rewind time by four seconds.
It was arguably the greatest thing he could do. One would call it his ultimate ability.
My face. Is it ready? There's the Tom and Jerry joke. No, no, no. I didn't like have a nail
hammer into my toe and I didn't go. I guess I just did. Where's my drug drop?
Bop it. Tom was the original. No, was it Jerry? Who was the mouse? Tom was the cat. Tom was the
original bop it you lose sound. That's right. The face came on or you're an egomaniac. Wouldn't
putting the face came on make me an egomaniac? Thinking face. I'm just waiting for my drug
delivery. Don't keep it to yourself. Tom scream with the reverb now. Is it ready? Where's the
drugs? It's a lot. It's like a six hundred dollar drop. There's like two or three different ones.
There's a high one too. Where's that drop? Please. So what do you want me to do? You want me to have
reverb on? You want me to do the bop it sound effect? Do the face cam with it? Now where's
the drop? It's in two hours. Do it Jester dance. Dance Jester dance. What the fuck?
There it is. Dead drop package. He never had a chance.
All right. Look at this a lot here. Do not get stopped by the police. This is five hundred dollars
worth of drugs. I'm going to be in deep shit if somebody stops me. Do it for our entertainment
funny man. Funny man. All right I made it. We can rule this city together. Well I don't know
about that. Let's break this up into small packages. Let's do the marijuana. Amphetamines.
Ecstasy. Ecstasy. Okay let me get this right. Okay I swear to god I've um I make that noise
every fucking stream. I do that every stream. Anytime that something crazy happens that
noise happens. What's that? Okay that's the scream. What's the tie fighter scream?
What is it called? What's the tie fighter scream? Howie howie howie howie howie scream.
Sorry. That was pretty close to being that. That was actually better than the howie scream.
Besides the long ones just open up when I played Resident Evil 2 and you could over the course of
that 12 hours that I've 10 hours that I played that game these would match up somewhere.
Okay not these ones but like that those like this show is fucked up.
Like look at this shit. They like fucking murder each other. This is fucking crazy.
They like beat the absolute shit out of each other. Look at this. Dude that's a bear trap.
Jerry put a bear trap down so when he sat on it it would fucking kill him. Look that's a fucking
hammer. Was that a gun? Oh wait it was in the right foot. Oh just burn him with an iron Jerry.
Fight him on fire. Stab him with a knife. Drown him with bees in his mouth. Holy shit that show
is fucked up. Watch more. No I've got drugs to sell pretend in quotes. Cartoon violence.
Do you guys remember I mean I know like the cartoons of some cartoons are like crazy and
stuff now but dude like Daffy Duck. Daffy Duck used to get shot in the face with a shotgun
point blank. Like they would hold a shotgun up to Daffy Duck's face and blow his face off with
a shotgun. It's that it was fucking crazy. Ren got his teeth pulled out. Yeah I know.
Anyways his skull was. All right this cartoon is a fucking crazy.
Oh funny cartoon. Pifo happy. I got the drop. Here we go 18 G of ecstasy. I got that 18 G of ecstasy.
Hey man I really like your stuff. I have a few friends that are also interested. Could become
your dealer if you sell it to me. Wait what's this dry rub shit? Bring me something better. Hey man
I really like your stuff. So you you did use it correctly. You you finally used it the way that
it was intended to. Yes I would love for you to be as a dealer. Awesome on it mate. Okay now we need
uh three grams. What do I mean? Two grams of grass. Two grams of ecstasy. So that gets us to
two grams. Two grams of weed. Four. We just need to bring a bunch of everything.
All right let's see. This is 20 gram pack of ecstasy. We're gonna put it in
fuck. I didn't mean to do that. I'll put this down here. Put it away. I'm gonna do
small packages of one gram urgently. Doesn't matter. Pack it. So this is 20 grams of ecstasy
I need to bring at least this. I have to just dodge the cops. This is gonna be bad. Okay lab
mode. We need uh let's actually just do it all while I'm here. Don't matter. And all right put
it in. Where's the 20? There's nothing in there. Put it in there. All of it. Pull it all out. Pull
it all out as individual packages of one. Again. Do it again. Individual packages of one. Now I
have a lot. Okay now I gotta go deliver. So we need two ecstasy, three amphetamine, 20 ecstasy,
three amphetamine, two marijuana, 20, three, two, 20, three, two, 20, three, two, 20, three, two,
20, three, two, 20, three of marijuana. Drop all of it except for three and then
two. Drop all of it except for two. Excellent. Let's go. Right. I had it backwards. Good thing
I checked. Good thing. I'm about to throw this down the toilet. I really am. And I want two. I
want some free samples of amphetamine and some weed. All right let's go. Deliver. Free shit. Free
shit. Free shit. Okay what is the quickest way to get it? We need to go to the dealer first.
Because we gotta get rid of this in case we get caught. I don't have any cash on me right now.
What's up? Here you go. I want 18 grams of ecstasy. Uh you. What do you want? Let's get these guys
first. I need to get uh spray paint. So I'll do that. I'm gonna spray. I'm gonna have a ton
of spray paint. I spray almost every. I'm gonna spray every single wall. Hey stranger. Would you
like one package of amphetamine? It's free. You got a new place. Yeah that's true. I did get a new
place. Last guy's right here. Is that marketplace person back with any new stuff? No. Do I have
any more free stuff? Um yeah I do. Where are you? Where's this person? Oh wait. All right now let's
go to. I have home and then where's the other? In the stink place. Where's my stink house?
Didn't I get a place here? Where is it? Why is this not on the map? Holy shit. Okay I was like
where are they? All right well here it is. But what does this matter? I don't have any lights.
Okay uh let's uh I mean I don't need this. I don't need anything for this. This is a dump.
I mean it's. Is that wood tile? It's kind of okay. Cool. Any free stuff?
All right we need to go to the gas station. I need to. I don't have any drugs on me right?
Hey take some free drugs so I don't have to have any drugs on me. What does this person want?
Oh shit did I give it away? No I still have it. Nice. Play Benny Hill and get chased by the cops.
Is Benny Hill the one that goes. That's the one right? Eh. Eh. Do it or I'm gonna unsub.
What a strange thing to unsub over. Hello? This still don't work. Devs. Devs. I still can't get
this to work. Devs. Okay two grams of ecstasy. Thank you. All right now I need. I want to get.
Where's the gas station that way? Devs. Okay let's go buy some spray paint so I can get some respect
around here. New message. He's telling me I have new messages. Please do a comb stream with your
patched hair? You mean like a like patch 1.2 or something? Yep yep yep okay sure yep.
All right here we go. I want uh like three of these. How much does that cost? All right all
right whatever whatever whatever medium back. All right I don't need any of this shit. I just
want to be able to spray shit around. Spray everything. If it's if it's a wall that I can
spray I'm gonna spray it. How do I spray it? That can't be sprayed? Why? How about this one?
No I can't spray on that wall. Can't spray on this one. Can I spray this wall? Can't spray that wall.
Can I spray over here? Where am I allowed to spray? Which one? No. No. No. No. Fine. Okay what about
here? Is this are we on a flat earth? I why would you ask me this question right now? This is not
the time to ask me if and of course not. What hey I know you're having a lot of fun playing the drug
dealer game uh dealing drugs. Um what's going on with this flat earth huh? Well let me tell you
you have proof that the earth is round. Do I do I have proof? Do I have proof?
Me? Jeremy? Like sitting in my office? Do I have proof that the earth is round? Of course I do.
You don't think I have fucking did my research on this? It's called be be in Ecuador and jump.
I bet you land on the ground. What do you think? I don't have anything. I don't have anything. I
don't have anything. Look you want to know why I think the earth is round? It's easy because the
dinosaurs when they were here they a meteor hit the fucking earth. Okay that means there had to
be enough gravity on on the moon. I feel hold on I've got to I've got to put the fucking spray
paint down the fumes are fucking on my head. Um I gotta get I gotta get to it like a fucking fresh
air. Uh uh Jesus um what does somebody somebody give five subs or something? What happened?
Yeah Justice Nugget gave five subs. Thanks man. Uh all right I get a fucking evil leaves and
dinosaurs. All right dude well okay what what a fucking Steven Spielberg 3D print all the bones
in his house. What are you talking about? Proof 3D printing exists. Okay why have all the cameras
unplugged? Oh this one's still in. Here's why why am I unplugging the cameras? Here this is why
3D printing exists. This is not even a no this is not a joke this is just a like look if it had
been a little quicker you would have okay why do I have minus two here? All right I'm fucking with
my own head. Delete this. This is why 3D printing exists. Why am I even doing this? This is just
gonna make everybody I'm dumping fuel on this fire. No I'm gonna shake it. That's why. I just
probably just got on fucking rent. I probably just got rent all dusty from hitting the ground.
Unbelievable. How do I spray this? Don't turn the camera. Yeah that's what I'm thinking.
You get it. I'm just I'm gonna dump lighter fluid on this fire. Okay three more sprays.
This actually does pretty good. Wait hey take this marijuana free.
No there wasn't. I didn't do anything. Oh more more respect let's go. Yeah what do you mean I was
here? What are you here for? What you were here to for the proof of of the round earth? How long
have you been out of school for? Like 20 years? I need one more wall. There it is right here. No
I need one. Oh no I have no paint. All right I've got plenty of respect. Let's go get some orders.
It's not my house.
It's so it's I'm having so much fun. It's just everyone's just everyone's just confused right
now. Some of you get it. I saw somebody write like two sentences. It's just they they got it.
It's like yeah mob that person. All right let's go. All right 18 of ecstasy but you got money.
All right 18 that's a lot. Okay what else do we want? Weed. This one was uh bet. This one is weed.
All right we got some good shit. All right let me just take a look. Both of our dealers have
have something to do. We have money from one and then we have we need 18 of ecstasy.
Two and this is uh weed. So how many how much weed? Five this is six seven I can. Five six seven
marijuana. Two amphetamine. Seven marijuana. Two amphetamine. Marijuana. Two amphetamines.
I gotta get this before the lock the the wherever the lockdown happens.
And then 18 ecstasy. Oh shit do I not have enough ecstasy?
What? How? Oh is it on the table?
Oh that sucks. No I'm gonna have to give. I can't do it. I gotta get more drugs.
I gotta pay Eddie back. Oh shit I have to pay Eddie. All right let me deliver this. Let me
get let me get what do I need 18? I don't have it. Fuck. When is he gonna have it? 25 minutes.
All right come on. Do the other ones first. Hurry up. Save it. All right let's go to
chop. He said 20 minutes right? And then I was gonna sleep. I was gonna hit T for like 10 minutes.
By the way I've got like eight hours and seven hours in this game or something. Six hours.
Whatever it is. No one's attacked me once. I feel pretty I guess I'm is it because I'm an illusionist?
No cops right? No? I got your stuff. No I don't. Just I'll be back. No I'll be back.
Nobody's ever played this game for this long. Have they not? Because they have. 200 bucks.
All right we're gonna jump around here. World record. How do you win? Do you actually win this?
No mega lull. Oh that's too bad. What about the the the secret party?
I know. I know. What does he want? Who? I know. What does he want? All right drop. Where is it?
Hey up there. Oh you're on the way this way. You wanted marijuana. I got it.
Because many of this these the towers right? There's a big party going on here.
It's like oh maybe one day you'll get invited in there. Am I not gonna ever get invited in there?
Am I just? I need that package right here. Nine minutes. Hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry.
It's behind the fuse box. Give it to me. Come on hurry up. Okay then across to Donald and then go
home. Go go go go go go go. No cops right? Donald? Here. Take it. Shit. Hurry up. Okay bye.
Level nine. What did I unlock? Yes finally a missile attack.
Okay I've got five skill points available and I'm gonna do it into um stealth.
Stealth or a quick learner? Which one? Can the police raid your house? I don't know.
I think they can if they follow you up when they catch you. Stealth and stamina. Stealth and stealth.
Yeah they can. Okay that's good to know. How much money do I have now?
I have 711 dollars. I have to pay Eddie back. Here Eddie I deliver cash. What do I owe him? 500?
How do you make money? Am I ever gonna make money? I have to keep paying back way more than I
you have to stop giving away free stuff. But yeah but to give away free stuff gets me customers.
Loyal customers. You fucking suck at this. What? I'm just I'm working my ass off here. Dude you
suck at this. Well you know I'm glad. I'm glad that I'm not good at this. I you know I'm glad
I'm not a good drug dealer. Okay that's all right with me. Okay paid off the debt there.
I'm gonna sleep. I'm gonna wait on some money and then all right so tell me this.
I tried this yesterday. I mean should I just start cutting shit in half and who cares if I
don't like it? Just keep selling it. Just even if it's like oh this stuff sucks. Just buy one
10 grams of amphetamine and stretch it to 100. That's kind of what I did last time and people
got really mad at me. Two grams of ecstasy. Do like 30 percent. All right so we're gonna do
20 so 30 percent. All right what do I have? I gotta get rid of some junk. Let's okay get
it all out on the table. We're gonna spend a day doing this. Put the money away. Okay get it all
out here. You know we gotta figure we gotta see what the fuck we're working with. We have sugar,
salt, washing powder. What else do we got here? Take it out. Amphetamines. Just do 80 percent
washing powder. No I can't do that. This is salt in here. All right take this out. New package of
salt. Okay and then there's what is this? Okay that's 0.7g of ecstasy. All right somebody's
gonna leave the stream if I don't fix this. We're doing small jars on the left. I'm gonna make it
look nice. We're gonna label this shit. By the way I'm gonna do the same shit on the Easy Bake
Oven stream because it's like 20 recipes I'm gonna be making. By the way on the Easy Bake Oven
stream I'm gonna make a bunch of drugs. We're gonna be making drugs on the Easy Bake Oven. I gotta
figure out how to do this the right way. All right then we're gonna move the washing powder.
Can I even do that? I gotta do this. Okay let's go like this. Pick it up. Oh there's sugar in here.
Why the fuck is there sugar in this? Like who cares? That's gonna be junk. Anyways I'm just
gonna throw that on the ground okay. I'm just gonna just throw it on the ground.
Somebody wants it they can have it. Just take it. This is a medium jar. I'm gonna go right here.
I don't like that. Maybe like this. A little more organized. Big guy's gonna go right here.
Small one. I'm gonna have to do this like bowling style because it's not enough.
It has to be perfect. I'm sorry. Okay what is this? Throw it on the ground. Just add it. I don't
care. It's dry rub. Who cares? Add it to this. We're gonna mix this up and we're just gonna fucking
we're gonna just throw. I don't know where's it gonna dump it. Now let's move this in a better
spot like right here. Better. Okay move this over here. There. Oh it's like actually clean now.
Now we put our dumb stuff up here. The sugar. The salt. This is washing powder. Salt. Sugar.
Salt. Wait what? Why do I have these like restaurant packets for? Marijuana. It's going.
Oh shit it's because I have these little packs. I have these little sandwich bags. I'm trying to
I'm playing solitaire with drugs. This is important. I gotta get. Oh my god this is fucking
so stupid. Come here. Just come here. Pick it up. You know I feel like the kid on Halloween
that dumps his entire pillowcase full of candy and separates it out and counts it all.
What is this? New sugar mix? Okay this is just junk. It just goes over here. This is just extra.
There's 20 of these. Why are there so many of these? Are you fucking kidding me? Wow.
Look at all these. Look at all these Snickers. Give me a fucking break. And that's the amount
of Reese's I got? Bunch of fucking assholes this year huh? And the Snickers minis by the way.
What a joke. Okay just pick them up. I'm not going to use them for anything.
One pack of new new sugar mix mix. Should I just dump it all over here and have like just a bunch
of trash? This is just trash. I'm gonna be cutting my drugs with actual trash from a garbage can.
This is salt. All right is there any more actual drugs that I have? I have fake ecstasy which is
this is just cut. Okay I'm gonna get rid of this stuff. I have amphetamines here. There's 10 more
packs. Do an 80 20 mix of real to fake. Okay so ecstasy sugar and dry rub. See now I'll make sure
nobody touches it. If you guys were concerned of this getting thrown in the ground no one will
fucking go near this. People will pick this shit up with tongues. They'll be so scared of it now.
Hey you want some silica gel? All right the rest. How do I just burn it? Give the silica
gel as a free gift. Dude what's this what's this new shit you just gave me? It's kind of tastes
and kind of tastes like new furniture. Yeah it's uh it's good isn't it? I'm gonna die. This is a
fucking joke. I kind of want I wish I can I put stuff on the no I can't because it's not a lab.
I can't just make one gram packets just out the door around the whole town and just stand at the
end with my hands in the air. That's unfortunate. Okay so we have uh we have silica gel which
whatever we might use it. Sugar. Sugar. Salt. Washing powder. More salt. This is just salt.
Silica gel. Wait wait wait wait hold on let me make this more realistic.
Oh I can't just like put it over in the corner like. How many times have you guys have found a
package of silica gel like just somewhere like under a mattress and you're like oh fuck. When
you find like those little like somewhere you just like your life flashes before your eyes you're
like holy fuck. Are you winning son? They taste good. You're fucking crazy. You don't do that.
Wait why would you be that scared? Oh I because I have I have a dog. Do you think I'm like walking
around on all fours like sniffing around and like eating silica gel on the ground? Wait do
you think I like I mistake the silica gel for the restaurant packet of fucking sweet and low?
What the fuck? All right I know I'm like I'm weird but I'm not like
that's like that's fucking crazy. What? All right let's make our concoction.
We're gonna do ecstasy. We're gonna do five grams of ecstasy. What goes good with ecstasy?
How about sugar? How about silica gel? All right let's do it. No activate the
oh I gotta powder it. No I don't want to. I need the pill thing. All right put it back up. Put it
back up. Put this back. Bring these down. We'll do we'll do 10 grams. We'll do eight grams and
then two grams of something else. Do ecstasy. Okay one more. Then we're gonna cut it with
wouldn't washing powder like irritate your nose? Is that what people are doing with this?
Salt would hurt. Silica gel would I mean sugar or baking soda? All right we'll do sugar.
Put like two grams in here. All right now I can mill it. Baking soda. I don't think I have any
more baking soda. I mean I have silica gel but that doesn't that's not a good washing powder or
no balls. Okay. Silica gel is for storage. Yeah so I should put a baggie of the silica gel in
with like in the just inside the jar. Okay so this is precision. This is poor. It's amphetamine and
sugar. It's poor precision. Why? Should I add washing powder? You need a better cutting table.
Catnip. Well whatever. Why the mix? I spelt it wrong probably. Who cares? No I had it right.
It's diluted. I hate that 9.97. All right package it and I have to remember what this is. This is
diluted powder but I need to it's this is amphetamine. I know but fuck I can't.
Okay that's amphetamines. We're gonna add to it. We'll do washing powder this time.
We're gonna do a little kick of washing powder. Give me some silica gel. Oh no it's diluted.
Just fucking just fucking snort the whole counter. I don't know why that's making me laugh.
What the fuck? No I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. All right let's.
This is 9.7. 9.97. Let's add some washing powder. I can add three grams of washing powder.
Can you really do 350? Can I just dump the whole box? Can I eat like 10 boxes? Can I just cover
my desk with baking soda? How much is it? Oh no 30 grams is the max capacity there.
I guess I could just put it in bags and just make a desk out of baking soda. I don't want to spend
the time. How's it taking? That would take like an hour. That would take an hour. I can't do it.
Okay let's put this over here. It'll mix. It's a little bit. It's infinamine and washing powder.
Okay now we're gonna mix it up. Okay well I'm sorry one of my teeth just fell out. I had to
do something about it. Package. Well packets. Okay keep going. My eyes are itchy.
Let me just get itchy eyes for no reason. And then when you itch them it makes them worse.
Just way worse. Sometimes I'll slightly itch my eye and I know I'm not supposed to.
And then when I start touching my eye it heightens the itchiness by 10,000 percent. And then you're
like ha ha ha ha ha ha ha itch itch itch itch itch itch itch. And you can't stop it and it will
not go away. I don't tell them. What? Mix the amphetamines with the weed. I don't think I can.
Now I have to powder it. Okay what? Oh what uh the sink. I can put these in the sink right? Okay
hold on I'm gonna I'm gonna put it in the sink. I'm gonna try this. No bottles. Oh wait uh take
one of these bottles. How do I pick it up? I want to pick one of these up. Uh put it in my inventory?
Can I not pick this up anymore? Okay you know I could just have to walk away. All right let's
fill this drop with water. No bottles found in inventory. What the fuck are you talking about?
How do I fill up a bottle? I need a water bottle.
What? It's a jar. It's a container. It can hold water. All right so now this is let's mix this up.
It's a game. Pretending. I what you can't put water into a jar? I didn't. Sorry I didn't know
that the game didn't want wanted me to get like a bottle of like a water bottle. Okay I have and now
I'm the owner of. Let's see uh just throw this in the trash. What do I got? I still don't know why
I own this. Okay let's put the silica gel. Let's put this shit out of here so I don't look at it.
Okay silica gel. Silica gel. Okay here it is. Diluted. Diluted mix. Put marijuana back.
Diluted mix. New new sugar mix. I have 29 of these and then fake x. Okay but I don't have a pill
thing and everyone got mad at me because I did this. Might as well add like 50% salt to it or
washing powder. Just mix everything. Guys this is not this is this is dangerous drugs. This is not
when you were six and you were making potions in the bathroom. Take two tablespoons of shampoo
and then mouthwash and mix it up with this and then add a little bit of water and then shaving cream.
If you didn't do that I don't believe you. This is not what this is. You just you know just make
like a magic potion in your bathroom. This is less dangerous than doing that. No what? Putting like
a little squeeze of toothpaste in a small cup and like a little bit of shaving cream and a little
drop of shampoo and mixing it up and saying I'm making magic potions. What's wrong with that?
This is less dangerous. Making mustard gas out of my chest.
You could have made no I wouldn't. Wait dude where do I where am I getting this bleach
like fucking ammonia? I wasn't allowed to have like aerosol cans guys. What are you talking about?
What do you think my like hey sit down here sir you want to make magic potions? All right
here's some bleach here's a couple of cigarette butts and a full glass of whiskey ammonia
and uh the spray duster that I spray my computer with. Don't hold that upside down wink wink wink
and spray. Are you serious? What are you talking about? We're talking about toothpaste and like
water. I think I'm making some awful dangerous chemical mix. I was having like fun as like a kid.
Oh by the way I know how much you love whipped cream.
There's four of them and then he just he turns it upside down.
Have fun.
He's gone. Toothpaste and like a little bit of shampoo and maybe maybe like a fucking like
conditioner or something. And by the way I was holding in my shit the whole time
while I was doing this. I'm like when I'm talking about when I was doing this it was like I was I
was like purposely holding because I was okay hey remember that remember that therapy session
that we were going to do I was going to go to like a therapist and talk about this stuff
and we're going to do that on stream maybe I should save this. I used to be like I want to
all right I'm gonna keep going. No I'm not done.
Jeremy are you all right in there? Yeah I haven't gone yet.
Well are you gonna go? Yep. Well you better hurry come on hurry up.
Okay a little bit of shampoo and then a little bit of toothpaste. What are you doing in there?
Uh nothing making uh potions. Have you gone to the bathroom yet? Uh yes. Are you sure?
No yes. Leave me alone. It's been four hours. Why was that fact important?
It's very I don't know because that's like important to know. I'm an open book okay.
Each page is I'm gonna tell you. All right I got like 30 grams of fucking baking soda shit let's
delivery. Childhood yeah there was like a child one of the kid childhood story I was like fucking
oh got money wait I still I don't understand this is am I not old enough for this or am I
not high enough for this you gotta buy them from the shops all right I'm gonna do it during police
hours fuck it as they say this is the most transparent streamer too transparent maybe
all right give me my money we need we got another dealer I have three dealers now all right cool
but what happens so I'm I'm gonna run out of people to sell to and just have a bunch of
dealers all right six grams of amps uh this is what are you four grams of amps this is two grams
of ecstasy all right we got a lot of amps you want two ecstasy and then we have 10 amps two ecstasy
10 amp okay two ecstasy 10 amp all right one pack of new diluted mix okay let's just take this
only what we need you dummy what is it new diluted mix what the fuck is the difference
I'm gonna start labeling these better all right let's go two ecstasy and then 10 and then you
just get you have money all right let's move one of them has washing powder in it oh right shit
shit but at home this is important I have to address this uh let me get this straight as a kid
you made potions while you took a shit as a teenager you brought your entire desktop
computer into the bathroom with you and as an adult you do poop stretches your bathroom
habits are fucked I tell I've told the story plenty of times but it seemed like bringing my
whole computer into the bathroom I would sit there if although there's probably some new viewers
I'll just TLDR this whole thing I I would bring my entire computer into the bathroom
and a little wobbly table and I would plug everything in and I would set everything up
and I would sit there and take a shit and play video games and it was always such an insanely
awesome idea it was like the greatest thing ever until you were done because then it was just
I have to fucking dismount am I gonna do this and I was just trapped there I like I couldn't
even move but man I'll tell you like it was and I don't I didn't think that was that weird
you know why that's not weird I'll tell you a reason why let's go over this I have to go over
this listen to me when no it's not weird listen you gotta hear me out what do you do when you go
to go to do your business you have a phone now and that phone has websites games some of you guys
have iPads as switches and you bring your switch and you just go to the bathroom and you sit there
with your phone and you read your phone you fucking play your switch I didn't have that
when I was younger that was it's the same deal I wanted to like play with my switch in the bathroom
you understand I used to have to bring my fucking entire computer into the bathroom
you now have that in the Nintendo Switch that's the reason why I bought it it's my entire teenage
childhood life just squished into a little box that I now it's the best system that's ever been
made I sanitize it's so I sanitize excuse me what do you guys act like I bring this thing in and
like go to the bathroom with I don't wipe my ass with the switch what do you guys do you guys think
I'm done well I'm done so let's turn the switch on its side and just like drag it up my ass
no I I put it down before touching anything I slide it under the door
it goes under the door into the bathroom I've done touched it I clean outside wash the hands
pick after drying the hands pick the switch up off the floor no not into the no not I'm saying I
slide it like under the door like out I said into the bathroom I mean like
whoops all these years I thought you're supposed to go to the bathroom outside the toilet wow so
that's why the bed smells so bad oh I didn't know this oh I'm just a dopey fucking streamer
I have no idea I'm gonna get arrested hold on not for that that's there's nothing wrong with that
okay I slide it under the door or like it's the bed yeah we got a call that somebody may have
you've gone to the bathroom in your bed yeah you might take me away who the fuck are you wait
illusion oh my fucking god what's the point of putting points in that what's the point what's
the point of having fucking half my points in illusion what did I even have on me not very much
180 fucking dollars though great oh what a fucking pain in the ass come on really
what a poop stretches it's not even it's I don't know what they're talking about
you're scum for doing that that's fine um it's not I don't know why people think this is so strange
it's I think I don't even I don't do like stretches before I go to the bathroom
I just get like I just make sure I've been walking on my walk you have to walk around
once I walk around for a bit the pipes start moving and then you drink I drink water let
this topic go I can't it's very near to endear to my heart somebody gave 50 dollars you're
basically a dog and dogs are basically mammals isn't that interesting so we're not that different
you and I dog all right I did the exact same thing last time I'm not going this way um
somebody was phylactery lich gave 5 000 bits thanks for the 50 dollars with your huge money
they say and then your legs would fall asleep and you wouldn't be able to stand up I'm with you
germa computer poop was your night yes yes that was always the indicator where it was time to get
up because my legs would start to tingle and it would hurt and I'd be like I have to get the
fuck up or you know in the some of the later years when I had laptop capabilities the I could
always tell because when I lifted up the laptop for some reason um the legs were red and they had
like lines all over them and made them like hot it was like okay it's probably time to get out of
here fuck put the phone down hey thank you germa it sucks for the five community subs I can't even
get over here man there's cops everywhere all right I have to deal drugs over here see there's
a cop just standing here he's a fugitive have you ever pooped upside down why the hell would
anybody do that all right there's somebody right here where's that cop it's like right here isn't
he where is he I can't see him I thought that was okay don't know why are you scary you know
why are you scared of you don't need to be scared of true what true true is what I went
stupid what don't let this guy go to the bathroom in your house why he might he might take your
whole computer into the bathroom hey uh hey man where's your bathroom oh it's right there on the
right oh cool where's your computer it's on the left all right why did I scream so late
that was such a late scream oh man go away fucking I hate this I hate this I have to reload
why were they all over there oh wait hey which which one of them was it which one was it
hey oh I think I found it all right I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do this
I'm not going out during the night time no I'm not going out there you have to wait for your
delivery no you don't I'll get it right now going right now let's go okay Wendy hurry up
I got the dope thank you cool okay back to the house save the game prove you're not on the toilet
right now it's probably TOS but I think it would be kind of funny if one day I just kind of turned
on the webcam and I was just sitting on the toilet just with a full computer in front of
me streaming like a headset on and shit I'm saved I'm ready you're more wise you sound like you're
in a bathroom selling your bathroom what up you know what you're talking about there's just some
kind of fucking bathroom thing hey you wait close the door no I need to be able to see
okay now they're suspect up up us up suspect on the loose I'm a fugitive that means I get extra
points okay last one is just this person they're in a really strange spot with tons of police
activity good to go all right now just get home there he is here he is there he is here he is
11 that's not even in this game but I wish it was the same line just pitch shifted up and down
to be in a different person all right made it save save game one oh I need a new trailer
I need a new yeah hold on let's get this right I need a new trailer I need a new
trailer I need a new trailer I need a new trailer I need a new trailer I need a new
trailer it's the best thing I love it all right you're on it you're on it then you're on it then
don't don't even talk to me then sleep who was it 21 g on it mate all right well I know I need 21
grass 21 I have that I think where is it I have 20 I think I just picked it up didn't I
uh I fucking knew it was on you guys think I'm stupid weed how much weed do I have
not enough apparently 20 didn't I get a bunch was it taken from me 10 did I somebody already
I need that's a lot all right Eddie I need a I need an order I want just a bunch I'll never
have I don't want to have to think about this again like 50 no 100 he's pretending don't tell
him the filter is still on no it is on now it's off now my prices oh prices okay marijuana
12 bucks what that's too high 11 um 10.5 I can't even up the prices what are you talking about
don't tell him it what are you talking about there's nothing on what is he saying I I need
to listen to see what it sounds like I can I can find out if you guys are bullshitting me or not
let's see no it sounds fucking normal to me it's normal now it's not normal really this is what
it sounded like before hey what's up hey hey what's going on okay that's kind of interesting I guess
this is what it sounds this is what it sounds like now technology is so interesting hey hey what's
up hey hey hey how you doing hey oh you know
people what do you think why are you saying vr chat hello why do people keep
vr chat I don't understand hey what's going on
you're gaining viewers because of this
just pressed every button I don't know I did hello hello funny voices funny voices funny voices
funny voices okay wait where is that going up this one should I just play let's see oh shit
this is this is it wait a minute this has everything I've ever recorded hello can you
hear this this is everything I've ever held down the button and recorded at McDonald's
why is that here at McDonald's cool dude at McDonald's oh oh oh oh why are these saved
it's me bugleberry it's me bugleberry how many times did I record this it's me bugleberry it's me
bugleberry I need that claw I need that tail I need that tooth
this is fucking scaring the shit out of me testing testing testing
yes yes yes it's just stupid it shouldn't even be in the fucking game got it
this that's cool that these are on here what's happening I just found the recorded files hello
you can tell this one is actually me testing this for the first time
because this is like a week or so before any of the actual stream recordings hello hello hello
hello hello everybody what happened can you hear me anybody can anybody hear me the wrong server
that's the problem I picked the wrong server hello hello hello hello hello hello hello
at McDonald's at McDonald's hello well let's add some
did it work see if it worked
okay cool uh so the internet's fine all right I get what the fuck is happening I this happens
too often let's keep going I gained 500 viewers from that new internet now I picked the fucking
different server I'm just I should have I'm gonna switch back to the old one all right let's go
okay chop 12 grams of stuff what what what do more please do an almond or wi-fi why
I almond or wi-fi I don't know why do you I can just do it like this almond or almond or
almond or wi-fi i think that's easy that's the easiest thing to want to do
all right no okay I'm done with the funny fucking voices guy like I don't want to be like the oh
look at he's looking he's got the oh ha ha ha he's got like funny fucking voices he's going ha ha ha
no I'm not doing this anymore one more no I'm not I don't I'm clearing them clear it
viewers are gonna leave if I don't do this wi-fi I can just see it now they're gonna leave
but they it's okay you go up you go down you go up you go down you got you gain viewers you lose
viewers you lose viewers you gain viewers you lose viewers you lose viewers you lose viewers you lose
viewers you lose viewers every day you keep losing viewers until they don't come back and then you
keep losing them until you are it's not an excuse keep the sneeze I don't know how do I put the
sneeze on here which one was the real sneeze does anybody I don't know I which one was the real one
there's like six on here almond or I don't think that's real I mean I know that one's not real
it's just stupid it shouldn't even be in the fucking game real got it that's real it has to
be real okay I got it that's definitely the one at McDonald's not all right we're playing the game
you didn't I mean maybe like 500 of you came here for funny noises why would no why would you come
into this stream for funny noises the title of the stream is like drug crack or something and
like it's a drug dealing game you clicked on the stream because you thought you're gonna watch a
drug dealing game the title of the stream is not hey like listen to funny voices stream that's not
what this is you can't I don't know what I'm not I don't know what you did what you're doing here
but what what what I don't understand I don't understand what I'm under oh pre-recorded
all right you want a pre-recorded stream put it over here dude what do I do with this
guess I can just put it over here
I don't hmm how much is this how much is this worth um probably not much
uh
I don't hmm how much is this how much is this worth I don't hmm how much is this
how much is this worth hmm probably not much testing almond or
oh where is it oh god damn it whatever dude what do I do with this
guess I can just put it over here
dude what do I do with this guess I can just put it over here I don't hmm how much is this
how much is this worth I don't hmm how much is this how much is this worth
what do I do with this guess I can just put it over here
I'm waiting for the drugs there's the same sneeze
that's me when I go shopping
dude what do I do with this like holding up like this put it over here a big like
jumbo pair of underwear that's like a size 50 walking around look at it oh my god
so
I don't hmm how much is this how much is this worth look at the tag hmm probably not much
hate it I hate it what do you want but you want 21 grams we only have nine
I don't have enough just going to the grocery store
oh I get nah you guys you guys ready for like a germa stream here we go
time for a germa nine eight five stream hold on okay here we go are you guys ready welcome hey
well hey hold on you ready we gotta start the stream guys okay I'm done I'm done I'm done I
promise I promise I promise now in the theater what the fuck is happening no it's not it's real
it's real it can't be real no somebody said what it can't be real it's real but like I'm
somebody said something fucking crazy did you see that pole dude it's no it's no it's no
what the heck is that what what what what the heck is that
turn it off I get this away get this power away from me seriously I'm turning it off
it's off for good okay hi hold up no no more like just laughing at things
he's been assimilated what all right who do I have to talk to you I need drugs oh they're
gonna steal my package don't laugh that's impossible you may as well tell me to just not breathe
where is this where the fuck is this thing a hundred grams of holy shit there's a lot
I don't think this is real now oh it is you almond or wi-fi are pre-recorded don't maybe
press the laugh button again trust nothing oh god damn it can you just take the brick I'll be back
brick of weed yeah okay where uh I need to put this brick put the brick out
wow it really is a brick okay now I need to take the brick drag it over here no package the brick
package package package package I need to package you put this in here 40 and then take out 21
10 times two cool and then one whatever no escape from reality open your eye why are you doing
bohemian rhapsody stop acting like everything is okay what are you talking about what what do you
mean uh on the station this is a pre-recorded throat clear but then it could have been
um I got I got no I got nothing time to go back die
fuck hi quick hi next to the drugs sick sick sick this is a random chance to
proc a cough apparently like a throat clear apparently all right I got money
my deal is doing anything oh shit there's a lot okay I need 24 grams of weed okay 12 grams of
uh what is that play the laugh why do I have to play the laugh I don't understand I just did
what do the roar that was real that was a real one okay we want two grams we want three grams
just take it all okay what do I need let's just check dealer wants 12 of ecstasy and 24 of
marijuana 12 ecstasy so any more ecstasy 12 13 14 so 14 ecstasy free amphetamine and 27
27 marijuana 14 ecstasy okay 27 marijuana 14 ecstasy 27 marijuana 14 ecstasy
it's a marijuana 14 ecstasy there's a marijuana 14 ecstasy 7 marijuana 14 ecstasy snow put that
back 27 there's a marijuana 14 ecstasy 25 14 all right you're going here I don't even remember
what it was when he said what do I need how much does it remember I have no idea what it was it
was 20 okay 120 and then four five six seven okay you got it 24 and then three okay so that's 27
20 gram pack of marijuana 120 and then four somebody wants three drug dealing is hard
I don't have enough ecstasy for you three grams of amphetamines two grams of ecstasy three and then
three does 27 what's going on I need three grams of amphetamines I have that
this is just good bring the diluted shit who cares I don't have enough ecstasy to give
is there any ecstasy on the table there is but not enough okay let's go he's dipping into his
own supply fuck it's hot in here all right into the mic fugitive
I like your litch gave another 50 dollars earlier and they say thanks for basically
making an abridged germa stream you're very welcome fart into the mic fugitive three grams
here it is there's the fugitive there you are all right we'll let you go but you have to fart into
this mic all right does this guy want the weed he wants ecstasy I don't have it
do it do it citizen do it citizen that wasn't very good I can do better than that
stupid filter is not even on I have to clear it I'm clearing it all because I know I'll abuse it
I will I will hey thank you milk stant for the five community subs appreciate it let us record
them these are pre-recorded subs now that's actually funny if I just do like six of these
and it's just banking fake people don't confuse the fuck out of a lot of people
and then there's two people up here level 10 new drug there is new stream that's half pre-recorded
and half live and have chat guests I got crystal meth now that would be really really hard okay
if those are that method the detective stream that would be very hard to do
because I would have to be able to take control but there would have to be a video the detective
stream was already just so hard and so many moving parts that was so much fun though if you
this is you might be new to the channel we did a game where I pre-recorded an entire stream
and then I just sat in the chat room with fake accounts and people had to try to find me and
find who I was in the chat and every about five to ten minutes there was a freeze in the video
and people had to pick and vote on who it was and some people got banned that shouldn't have
been I was I lasted a pretty long time do another one the thing about that though is that you want
to talk about oh wow what a that's a long stream wow that was a very very elaborate stream that
must have taken a lot of effort um it's more so the accounts need to be I need to have accounts
that are like more than three four five six months old subbed to people subbed to random
streamers following random fucking people and have activity on the account for like fucking two
years so that's where it gets to be hard what does he want oh I try to try to loot it I will
just give you my account no that's your account though I need ecstasy back home I need ecstasy
right now yeah and that somebody just said that also might be actually against terms of service
I don't think they probably wouldn't twitch probably be pretty unhappy with that somehow I
would assume just give me your accounts guys real distribution in sector b might get tricky
the blockades got lifted right on let's go look around sector b shall we wait a new sector but
keep in mind that the police will search your shit each time you pass the checkpoint so if you need
to move something illegal through that wall well we're gonna have to get creative okay oh we got
cash I'll take it got some new property all right well what do you what does he got property we need
we need to hide out at least lifted the blockade for sector b okay checkpoints are guarded by
police officers to move contraband through the wall you have to find alternative ways to the
other side and back does it pain in the ass old town small apartment stink building second
floor stink building small dogs warehouse where is this where where's sector b can I tell where I
even am I'm just gonna walk over there these stuff is available crystal meth all right let's get some
crystal meth how much can I get let's get 30 oh no no no no Eddie Eddie Eddie wait wait wait wait
I need more I need more I need uh ecstasy I need the only one that calls all right there listen up
you will solve the cash flow problem I warned you about earlier cash he does his magic he'll
explain you personally see ya laundering cash gives you legal bank income guy you have better
check if he doesn't drive a white van handing out candy you know I'm just saying I've got
marijuana I need to bring what do you need 12 grams of ecstasy you have money so I'm
just gonna get it from you and I want to I want to check out the I want to see the other side
of town my people saying oh super frog oh excuse me you didn't I don't understand what you're
writing you didn't write oh at the beginning oh super frog how am I supposed to know what you
mean how much money for that 210 bucks good I hate you I'm really sorry you do um maybe next
stream if you check us out maybe you'll think it's fun sorry have a good rest of your day though
please tell me you have drug samples I do no I don't I just have money money is legal right
of course it is let's go through the checkpoint I have nothing I have nothing I have nothing I
have nothing I have nothing I have nothing I have nothing I have nothing what are you gonna do
what are you gonna do what are you gonna do hmm yeah sorry oh fart into the mic right
fart into the mic right I we're gonna go your business needs exposure this banner can hold
your ad tomorrow the jeans company does look like comfortable jeans oh funny moment funny laugh out
loud moment where am I what rust server did I go into dark rfp okay I know I know I know I like look
I was about to say that this was like a little barrel stuffed full of bananas I was going to be
like nice fresh fruit I thought like stuffed at the brim of bananas at checkpoints up by the
drugstore right yeah it's right over here no it's open okay you there come here have anything
illegal on wait I know how to do this just throw your backpack over the wall okay so just bring
backpack throw backpack over this wall and then come get it oh supermarket check it out don't
bums open inside don't open oh open it yeah I know that's like a reference to
television series what's it what's up here the drugstore oh my god
how do I get to the drugstore
package from the you what you this oh there's right my crystal meth drugs
I gotta throw that over the checkpoint police station can I go in the police station
can't go in why what you're gonna check me to leave now let's try this I want to test this
theory uh I was following the wrong indicator got this crystal meth in here what can you do
with crystal meth try to put it in make a pill is it in the truck on the back of the truck
under the truck driver's side of the truck oh crystal meth that's the um that's the show
I'm gonna say one thing real quick to you get off the phone Jesse and call him that's pretty
good that was all right I said that was like a seven okay let's try it get minus seven that
didn't count what I was playing catch the backpack no it's in the backpack right how did you find
drugs I put it wasn't in the it was in the backpack what it was it actually planted on me
what are you what the what what do you go back to the pack yeah I'm gonna go back to pack
I go back to the pack so what's the it's not here what what the hell 1829 that's kind of far
I mean I had there was a ton of stuff in there yeah whatever uh-huh yeah yep yep yep yep yep
yep hey as far as I know Eddie introduced me and make this short if you need your money clean let
me know we'll meet you bring me cash and you get a clean legal transfer from my company to your
account 40% fee what the fuck it's too much no I'll just store it in my mattress thank you though
wait these guys want drugs so this is cash and then ecstasy do I don't have any ecstasy so who
cares let me try this trick again skill points oh quick learner it's important okay get get the
cash wait where's the cash no wait do you have new invent do you have a new inventory
don't have any new inventory 69 69 viewers really money thank you all right let's do this
let's try this again I have nothing illegal so there's nothing illegal about what I'm doing
it's just strange it's just money in that bag you went a really strange way it doesn't work
uh wait hey you wait oh I was gonna say you already searched me what's the cooldown period
I'm being searched let's check this out hold on okay so hey it's when you cross that threshold
I was thinking maybe they'd be like a few seconds of uh start sprinting all right then what about
the nightclub jay's shop a free stove and a free sofa uh hello can I go to the nightclub how do I
get in there looks like you can get in there that's a pretty sick gta car I want to play gta
maybe I'll play gta soon and play the casino one so where's this jay's shop jay's shop they're after
me duffel bag elegant suitcase large backpack pit coins I get some pit coins that's too much
um okay hold on how many pit coins can I have uh five I'll take five pit coins please
and I'll also take a large backpack okay I need to get rid of one pit coin two pit coins okay put
the backpack inside the backpack I will accept anything all right I got pit coins all right now
put this back now can I sell backpacks it's in that backpack and put a backpack with items in a
how do I get the drop item take the large backpack out of the backpack and then put the
medium backpack on the ground and then pick up the large backpack what did I just pick up
okay medium backpack all right sell this can I sell all right well I need a pill maker how many
pit coins is a pill maker I'm doing a huge withdrawal I'm gonna convert all my money to
pit coin in ATM no no no trust trust but trust me it's bottoming guys it's bit but it's bottoming
out right now there's no way it can go lower impossible it's my balance okay I'll keep
thirty dollars in the bank beyond meat beyond meat was worth more money that had a valuation
higher than fucking Microsoft okay I'm sorry that I thought that maybe the stock price was
going to lower would that make me crazy wait who lost me did I lose somebody what happened
I don't have any drugs on me no okay I need to go back to Jay's uh spot Jay I'm back for those
bitcoins all right wait a minute bitcoins are not physical the digital did I just get scammed he's
gonna do it again he's gonna do it again he's gonna do the stupid fucking car alarm thing
all right the package hey Austin Atlantis thanks for the five community subs
five subs from Austin Atlantis thanks for the fucking subs wait is a medium backpack legal
like did they know that I have like like cryptocurrency on me was it gonna am I
gonna get in trouble I need to get behind here go to the drugstore I tried I couldn't find a way
to get in get down he's got a bitcoin didn't I try I tried to go in where is it
real which one of these is the drugstore this looks that's like that's the drugstore
go around I did what I like to buy some drugs uh right here looks like right this door is locked
why can't I go in the drugstore oh shit that fucking guy is here again lock the doors
hey hey I'm just I just want to see if you have anything in here what do you got
oh no I'm just in here to get a pack of gum you know that's all I want but uh time to you guys
open there's uh seven a.m. it's 658 um maybe you can open the door for me what sir you I can't go
in I did a fault 360 maybe you're gonna find it in my reward to be open in the door
I can't do it that's too high level for you oh the drugs boy crack crack crack the crack now you
need 12 grams of ecstasy I only have 10 grams of ecstasy because I'm a fucking dope and I didn't
get more than 10 I didn't have enough money I gotta pay Eddie back wait how do I get back
how do I get out of here I have to go through checkpoint don't I did I already do it I did
right you have to run no I did it already all right hurry up and get two more ecstasy so I
can turn this in oh yeah I have a bunch of pit coins I got to spend those all right pit coins
how do I use them 35 etc all right how do I use them let's spend them can't use them yet
wait what happens if I go negative price went down no it didn't the price dropped I need to
bring drugs urgently 12 ecstasy hash and phenamine marijuana three three 12 what I got
get rid of the crystal meth three three 12 okay get rid of the meth those uh United States dollars
in here and then we need one packet diluted mix and then marijuana three grams of marijuana
three grams of three grams one two fuck go okay let's go deliver this stuff
google halfway because I keep saying this you think that like I'm being like monitored
because I've said the word like selling crystal meth and drug and I've said these words so many
times drugs selling crystal meth marijuana dealing drug dealing drugs crystal meth
dealing marijuana storing money buying bitcoins with marijuana crack money all right now we're
going to go now but what you guys understand is they can also they also know that there's a
televised stream going on right now I can't give you anything dude televised television
television's a fun one to say I'll tell you television officer officer just say it with me
television it's fun television just say television with me get in there fucking idiots I'm a master
mind I'm a master mind this game really makes you feel like a mastermind where are you why can I
never find these people big bits oh shit yeah hold on I just want to do this before I get arrested
$240 holy shit and you need 12 I'm a fugitive right now hold on big fucking bits let me just
get this delivered and let me just deliver this and let me just deliver this and I'm gonna get
safe at my house look we can do this again good thing that you're just standing there
all right 12 of ecstasy hurry hurry hurry hurry and then you wanted marijuana oh man it's such a
ah just run around in a circle he was hiding behind a cactus that's why oh well then okay
that's good at mcdonald's I'm not gonna get fucked up here this is what I'm a fugitive right now hold
on normal ass juke normal ass juke a normal ass juke really it's a great taste good times
at mcdonald's could be the best tasting lettuce and tomato hamburger ever good times oh crisp
in the cool place hot beefy mcd one of my favorite videos on youtube by the way
I'm gonna get home the jason alexander mcdlt commercial is like one of my favorite tv spots
ever say you getting tired of lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this town that don't quite add up
just once you like your lettuce and tomato cool and crisp that's great it's a good commercial
it is almost I mean it's not memorized it's um it's paraphrasedized all right I have to go home
and we got big bits hold on so you're getting tired of lettuce and tomato hamburgers that's the
best part they say lettuce and tomato hamburgers because the whole part of the reason why the dlt
was so um so what a big deal is because the lettuce and tomato the letter you say you're
getting tired of lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this town uh it was they separated it so they
didn't put it together they gave you this little tin it was like styrofoam container and one side
had lettuce and tomato on it and the other side was just an open hamburger and you put it together
so it wasn't soggy all right let's we got we got a second here why why look at look just watch the
commercial you'll see all the info is in that 60 seconds I'll take like 12 minutes to explain it
to you so just go watch the commercial you'll like it uh eggplant alert gave 50 dollars 5000
bits from eggplant alert show it on stream I will just hold on thanks for the 5000 bits they say
jerma I've been watching your videos for about eight years it's a long fucking time I want to
say how much they've meant to me I went through some very difficult times when I was younger
but I always found myself finding a happy escape hold on there we go okay there's like somebody
just screaming through the window uh so I needed to take it just let me just pause it for a second
uh I've always found myself finding a happy escape and just how genuine and funny your videos were
they helped me through some dark times and now I just got accepted to my dream med school with
dream with dean scholarship that's fucking awesome wouldn't be here if it was not for you
first doc check eight years from now is going straight to you keep it up well that's fucking
awesome nice job medical we got doctors scientists uh theoretical physicists and shit look I'm telling
you we got like pilots we got this community well find me a community with this many doctors
in it okay you're not gonna find it there are at least 30 doctors here right now I guarantee it
a lot of dentists I'm just telling you there's a lot of there's a lot of fucking there's a lot of
bright eggs here but thank you so much for the 5000 bits thanks for watching for eight fucking years
every time somebody says they've been watching for that long I always go that's crazy because
that's almost a full decade we're coming up on a full decade here next year so it's wild to me
thanks for the huge amount of money and good luck I wish you the best he's a geologist signing in
all right now we want people with well on crystal meth how much is the is the
the p coins what are they called all right cool what was I gonna do oh right that was not the
mcdlt let's here it is I'm talking a quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side bang bang and
he gets like his hands slapped five oh I'm so happy that we're gonna get to watch this together
the new mcdlt hot stays hot cool stays crisp put it together hey
yeah you say that just once you'd like your hamburger hot and your lettuce and tomato
cool and crisp all at the same time yeah well I say you got it I'm talking McDonald's
hamburger the mcdlt I'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot hot side and the hot stays hot
the new mcdlt crisp lettuce and tomato on the cool cool side and the cool stays cool the new mcdlt
cool crisp the hot stays hot the cool stays crisp put it together you can't resist
the hot stays crisp let's go keep it hot keep it cool cool mcdlt mcdlt hot beefy mcd cool crisp
bell tea mcdlt it's crisp time hot beefy mcd for the greatest taste home crisp bell tea at
mcdonald's could be the best tasting lettuce and tomato hamburger ever I just talked over him how
dare I do that best tasting lettuce cool crisp bell tea of mcdonald's could be the best could be
the best tasting lettuce and tomato hamburger ever yes by the way they uh got rid of that
because it was like they would like there was the styrofoam was just like fucking awful plastic
bullshit and it was like just clogging up the oceans why is the cheese on the cheese on the
cool side oh because it would even like I don't know is it lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this
town that don't quite make it yeah you say that just once you'd like your was it on the cool side
cool and crisp all at the same time yeah well I say you got it I'm talking to mcdlt
hot crisp lettuce and tomato on the cool side no it's not stays cool the new mcdlt
cool crisp the beef stays hot the cool stays fuck it is on the cool side so that would just
turn into like a cold slimy piece of cheese how can you imagine when you put this shit together
back in the day it must have been such a pain in the ass okay I want to see how they do this
because with the shredded lettuce wouldn't just dump all over the place
that would just cascade off of the plate no no way that's glued that has to be glued on
right here this is on the floor right there it's like on the floor right there
shit it's glued that's my favorite part right there this guy with the briefcase with the
fucking suit on the gray suit look at that like he goes low and he like left left right low that's
my favorite part bang bang like the guy with the free I love the briefcase guy it's my favorite
character briefcase guy mcdlt briefcase guy is going to be in the next rumble I love that guy
I wish I like I wish I knew that guy and by the way his stats are going to be 100 and everything
okay uh I want 20 grams of meth you still have some uh I think so it has probably as old as you
dead well I mean yeah I mean that commercial was like 1981 or something I love what I need 20 how
many did I pick up and like Jason Alexander was so good he looked he's like his quick
lightning movement just bang bang he's just like walking and like electric guitar like he was so
animated he could just be like boom boom got a thousand dollars wait where's my I have
pitcoins too where did I get this money where did I get nine hundred dollars from I gotta break down
this crystal meth how much do you think I want 20 so okay what did you want three I'm gonna break
this down what what what was it in breaking bad it was like uh like okay here fine all right now
I got 20 I need the 20 of crystal meth and that's all I can do right now let's go I actually I need
to pay Eddie I think I owe Eddie like seven hundred dollars Jesse we have to eight hundred and forty
dollars what that's all my money all stays crisp I actually don't like crispy lettuce on any of my
hamburgers this is like a white watery it's like eating pickles I don't like pickles either because
when you bite it when it pickles on your burger or would like big crispy wet lettuces all over you
it makes it watery it but you get like this little layer of water pools up on top pickles do it too
when you bite into a pickle with your burger you bite into the okay there we go my teeth
here's their their layers they're going through bread cheese onions mushrooms cilantro
pickles water meat fun like no get it off don't get arrested I got crystal how much is crystal
meth is is expensive isn't it you know I'm gonna jack the prices up a million percent for one day
okay Goyky just gave five thousand bits another fifty dollar drop fifty dollar donation in bits
thank you all of you for the extreme amounts of money it seems to happen every fucking screen
thank you Goyky though says okay human burger expert if that's no good if that's no good build
us your perfect burger right now what's the perfect burger um okay uh listen listen up tomato get rid
of it do not ever put tomato on anything for any reason the only time the tomato should ever be
consumed if it's mashed the fuck up and turned into spaghetti sauce tomatoes are discussed
wet wet slimy watery to no it ruins it for me grill up some onions and mushrooms in the same pan
a little bit of butter and maybe a little bit of garlic in there get them nice nice and sweat them
out mushrooms onions sweat them out caramelize them take that slop when it's done that caramelized
gooey sticky fucking hot delicious stuff that you when you come when you when you fry up some
onions and some mushrooms get it up right on the top part of the bun make sure the bun has been
toasted by the way not for not i'm not talking like toast it till it you crunch through it and
hurts your teeth no just barely golden brown you can do that on a stovetop or a pan by the way
don't cook burr charcoal grill get your gas grills out of here charcoal grill wood real good hard
wood get that up to temperature on a grill on one side this is making me hungry you only got to do
this for a few minutes cover it up cover the dome or cover your your grill with wherever you have
you want to let it cook a little bit all the way through but not not you don't want to get
past like medium medium well you want to like really just get a good sear on both sides
flip two or three minutes flip two three minutes bang charcoal grill hot fucking hot grill hot hot
side you want to take that hot hot side put it on the bottom part smear a little bit of mayo
i know some of you i don't care a little just a little bit a little bit of mayonnaise on the
top part of the bun put your slurry of grilled caramelized goo onions and fucking mushrooms
right there you turn that burger when it's almost ready to go you flip the burger over now you're
gonna finish it slap a big thick and i'm talking at least it you know like when the person at the
deli holds this thing up to you and they go is that good and you go no a little bit thicker
that's what i'm talking just one tier up swiss cheese whack on top of that burger let it melt
pull it off cover it swiss cheese fucking caramelized onions mushrooms a little bit of mayo
that's it that's all you have to do no lettuce no tomato none of those disgusting wet foods
no no just no disgusting wet vegetables that turn into water in your mouth when you chew them
oh by the way how many times have you done this shit i will demonstrate i will demonstrate with
a ready how many times have you done this i'm gonna go on can i go on cam for this one you bite into
a burger with a piece of lettuce on it yeah all you lettuce fans this is this is we're talking
about you here this this is for the lettuce fans you're not gonna capture my webcam or you're
gonna be fucking stupid about this not gonna capture my fucking webcam are you gonna be
dick about this game it's gonna be a dick about this you're gonna be dick about this
i and i can't pull my webcam through i have to though hold on a second important
why won't this get captured okay there we go hear me out on this a lot of people let me
come on let me i'll fucking who i don't care about my reddit all right listen to me when you bite
into a burger that has lettuce on it this happens maybe 30 to 40 but maybe even 20 percent of the
time that's too much of a risk to take i don't want you fuck the pops i just shaved too look
when you bite into a burger that has lettuce on it this just fell on the ground i can't
i'm gonna buy a burger okay this has lettuce on it i'm gonna take a big bite here's the burger
right here i got it you ready to see what happens when you have fucking lettuce on a hamburger
oh the oh what's that the whole fucking thing came out and then but now what you have to do
now you have to go oh oops i mean take the foot put the bun up and like put it back on
and put it back like this let me go delicious that's weak teeth no that's you pull it out it's
just like and then the fucking tomato falls and then you look at the fucking plate and what's that
the tomatoes like wet red water is like bleeding all over your plate and it's like no that's not
like juice from the burger that's so that's like blood from my tomato now get those wet
vegetables out of here i get get those good thing i turned on the webcam to do that it only took
like four minutes to turn it on no no wet no wet vegetables on hamburgers oh shit i think people
knew they had drugs classic redditor crying over lettuce they do this no look i love lettuce i like
lettuce in salads on sandwiches cold sandwiches when you have a hot sandwich and you put lettuce
on it you're just adding a gross piece of paper that disintegrates into like this weird like
somebody said Reese's paper before it that's what it turns into a lot of time i love salads i love
romaine lettuce i think like romaine hearts that crunch on a salad on like a nice like a nice sub
you know if you're not like a nice italian sub you put like a little bit of you know maybe you
put a tomato on it whatever i love like bruschetta tomato delicious it's designed that way that's
e coli lettuce well that's what we call slander and um i didn't say it you did
it this is so loud lettuce lettuce is just like the lettuce is a scam they've the the fucking
lettuce lettuce the the big the big lettuce has found a way to convince you to eat water
i'm telling you it spits big lettuce big romaine
i actually do like lettuce though oh what am i i'm just walking around at night what am i doing
all right i oh eddie right i gotta pay eddie do a poll no because i know the things i'm saying
people are like he's fucking crazy i'm gonna take his blood pressure what is it at right now
is it like 180 over like fucking 160 dude relax it's lettuce i know but i don't i don't like
lettuce on hot food i think it kind of just adds nothing i think lettuce on cold food yes lettuce
on hot food i don't like it i don't like it that's okay what about on tacos
okay here's the thing about tacos hold on tacos got him not hold on just give me a second i'm
about to get fucking arrested for being outside all right hear me out about tacos tacos are an
interesting thing because the lettuce in a taco does not get hot like it does when you put it in
between bread and in a hamburger that's hot off the grill lettuce sits protected on top of two
or three different ingredients meats at the bottom and it's very bottom on top of that you've got
potentially fucking sauce cheese cold cheese by the way on top of that you've got potentially
like salsa and then on top of that you got lettuce lettuce never touches anything hot
the lettuce never comes into contact with any of the hot food putting the lettuce down on the
burger boom you've compromised it just i'm just telling you the things that i think
what about the tortilla
somebody wrote in all caps someone institutionalize him what the fuck it's not the same thing
because there's no top part of listen when you have a hamburger you are closing it up so the
heat gets like trapped in between the buns a taco is open at the top there is no top to a taco
you don't close the taco and have the meat heat up the lettuce so it gets hot and soggy and shit
lock this guy up
who puts salsa on a burger i'm talking about putting salsa on a taco by the way a salsa on a
burger this i'm sure there's some that exists where like you could put something like i don't
know there's probably different like creations and you'll be hearing from my lawyers i like putting
shit on burgers you know i i like putting interest i like that would probably be kind of good
no wouldn't oh i don't like to like what to me i'm saying no what stuff
and by the way can we get over this like put mac and cheese on everything
can we get over this i i don't understand it put mac and cheese on your hamburger put mac and cheese
on your pizza put mac and cheese on your lobster i'm over it lobster mac is so good i know but
like crab is better than lobster why is there no crab mac and cheese why is it always lobster mac
and cheese how come there's no crab why they don't like the crab so much crab is better than lobster
king crab is better than the best lobster i've ever had crab is just it just better than lobster
i'm sorry and this is coming from somebody from new england me saying that crab is better than
lobster i may as well just said like fuck the red sox out loud oh i got money how much ecstasy do
you want man how much ecstasy do i have fuck the bruins all right i have i don't have enough
ecstasy i have a bunch of bullshit but this is not even real wrong wrong wrong wrong
wait i got money 24 of ecstasy i don't have i don't even have five ecstasy i don't have any
i need more ecstasy now eddie get me up i need a shitload of ecstasy 50 100 what the fuck is
going on guys he's just goofing he doesn't really believe his crazy ideas oh fuck i gotta get my
money i got two deliveries of money he's pretending right okay all right get these two collections
so by the way if you if you are curious we're gonna be doing community content night tomorrow
it's planned tomorrow i don't know what community content night is that's where we just hang out
chill and we look at artwork people have made for the community and videos people have made
random stuff just kind of hang out for a couple hours three or four hours or so everyone's saying
into the stream voice and they're right they are correct i already told you i'm start i gotta
follow the doctor's orders here i've got to follow the new rules more stream days less stream time
i'm gonna follow the rules stupid doctor what does he know i don't know i'll lend her wi-fi
494 dollars this game was fun um you ready to give you first impressions
okay first impressions after eight nine hours of playing good it's good i just wish there was
more to do it's fun to go around and like sell drugs i mean i feel like i've kind of been selling
drugs the same five people for eight hours actual opinion not joke i just told you that's what i
think an official review it's a negative review no it's not i think it's fun i don't mean i haven't
been like nobody's like robbed me i haven't had any fights all i've been doing is kind of just run
around and just giving people drugs that they order from my computer but i'm level 10 like i only have
three more things i can unlock yeah like i have is there anything else i can even do it's just been
a lucid dream just make crack well i can't make crack until i need cocaine right i can't get
cocaine to level 16 just do the drugs put them in your quick slots to do them uh can only target
singular pocket item what put it down here and okay crystal meth took it i took the new sugar mix
it's time to eat the silica gel you're getting close getting real close closer closer closer
oh i'm fine all right let's just do a bunch of fucking drugs let's just let's mix a bunch of
stuff let's do let's mix silica gel uh marijuana let's just okay here we go okay uh silica gel
uh diluted mix ecstasy crushed up uh that one uh this one okay let's go put it all together
put in the diluted amphetamines put in some ecstasy put in uh some silica gel uh add some
fucking washing powder he's making a magic potion add some salt i don't know like three grams of
salt two grams of salt uh put some sugar in here oh give me this sleep for a little bit
okay put that in there uh 10 grams of washing powder um anything else i can buy put in there
some sugar okay um and then some more silica gel mix it up okay let's take this let's just go
outside and take this until the stream ends all right what's it called poison all right the poison
okay wait that's not took diluted was oh no no no no it's two i press two
am i floating i'm flying moon shoes we need more fov oh let me see if i can get some fov
i can't steal what oh he's crying oh shit all right i'm gonna call it here saturday first i
thought that was one dollar all right well that's uh that's drug dealer simulator we had some fun
talked about hamburgers sold some drugs i got to level 10 i think that's pretty good i will see
you tomorrow for community content night take care everybody see you tomorrow those of you
sticking around we're gonna do these subs and bits and everything and chill for a little bit
we'll see you tomorrow around 4 pm pacific take care let's get the music rolling things of the
game so where are we in the vits we are down here with 250 from sticks renegade we all should have
pretended he was streaming see how long he'd last um if i if you guys were to sit here and just write
i told you i thought it was live because i saw like 10 people write the word live in all capitals
so i was like okay that people usually do that so i had talking to nobody for 60 seconds at least
yeah you guys have fun doing that don't you uh yamaha thanks for the 300 bits germo when are
you streaming circus maximus chariot wars for the playstation 2 uh i did not know that game existed
until right now i'll have to go look up and see what it is see if i'd want to play it for the
playstation 2 portable thanks for 300 bits hey zake thanks for the 250 it's only a matter of time
when vr will be a point at a point where all of our senses thoughts and memories will be simulated
this new world will be superior in every way and there will be no reason to go back
do we know this hasn't happened already anyway love your streams keep keep keep keep keep keep
it wholesome uh my head sorry i had a backache for a second hey the chef's corner thanks for
the thousand bits no one wants to give you money because you are a nerd uh well thanks for the
ten dollars telling me that no one else to give me money while you give me money
i do appreciate a thousand bits though chef's corner hey video games mcgee thanks for 500 bits
i am bernie sanders in real life and i was told by my staffer to watch this germa character and i
have to say i am a fan and i take offense to you thinking that i'm not in fact bernie sanders
okay thank you video games mcgee thanks for the 500 bits hey are you feeling the burn thanks to
the 500 bits no message just a bunch of pog champs dark soul thanks for 250 i wasn't kidding about
the whole skyrim vr thing well the porn part yeah the game is really fun actually when you get vrik
going and have a full character body with sheets and stuff it's a lot more responsive than you'd
expect and you can still mod the shit out of it this psa has been brought to you by tod squad
thanks tod squad yeah i just need to get healthy i actually have a doctor's appointment coming up
here we get to play the game called it's been pretty much narrowed down 100 it's either it's
intercostal nerve damage which explains like the cost of chondritis or i may have rheumatoid
arthritis there's ways to treat them both but i don't want to really talk about if they're
100 but the cost of chondritis is still a thing and it can be caused by potential
damage to your intercostal nerve so i don't know i don't know well once that is in the rear view
mirror and i can actually like not have to worry about it every day and i will go back to being
able to be a lot more physical in front of the camera like you were used to like a year ago or
so we'll see hey cream corn thanks for the 250 germ i just hit 100 100 000 channel points when
are we getting another high tier point sync uh sooner than you think sooner than you think
got some ideas hey that guy tag what's going on tag you can save and duplicate and make entirely
new profiles through the profiles menu on the go xlr the buttons are on the bottom of the tab
should i not have talked all this shit about uh i can't help it what did i say yesterday i was
gonna drop kick it out of my window or something i'm just i i'm just full of emotion you know
what i mean like i'm just full of emotion i just like i was fighting it i i'm just i'm so i'm so
emotional remember when i took the element test to said that i was fire and air makes sense doesn't
it there's no way i'm earth or metal or water i'm absolutely fire and air together combined which is
no which is gas no which is
dust what is it hot air he's all he's all hot air oh fuck you know what i mean
gas or something i don't know thanks tag i'll actually look into it thanks for the thousand
bits thanks for the 10 bucks tag if you're doing well vladkovich thanks for the 500 bits leonx
thanks for the thousand bits 10 dollars how could you support captain cronch after all the war crimes
he's committed oh they shrunk tony the tiger did we talk about this yet they fucking shrunk
tony the tiger's like fucking five feet tall now he's like he's like five two they shrunk him he
used to be like eight feet tall i saw a new commercial with tony the tiger and he's like
fucking five one they shrunk him they made his muscles smaller and they made him smaller he's
not even like a big like huge guy anymore show it hold on what i do you know how many tony the
tiger commercials there have been over the last like 30 years there's like hundreds of them how
do i if i type in new tony the tiger commercial i'm gonna get stuff dating back to the 90s it
doesn't matter frosted it's like this is it i got it yep this is it let's watch it maybe he's like
small it's called mission mission tiger and he's like cg no this is not it where is it where's no
no no no i don't want to this is like an ad website i need to run like youtube okay hold on all right
look look okay no okay okay okay look look look look he's standing next to children look look look
look look i got it i got it i got it about the music hopefully this works it's probably not
gonna work i'm trying to get it to work it's not on youtube i'm trying to i'm gonna hold on i know
i know i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna here we go ready he's like four he's like five
feet tall four and a half look at he's like four and a half feet tall you seeing this
with a great taste of frosted flakes so they can be frosted their day with a great taste of frost
tigers start their day with a great day you guys thought i was lying
hahaha he's like i am telling they made him like i what didn't he used to like take up the whole
screen are they trying to like shrink him down so he's like like a kid or something i don't get it
he used to like bump into shouldn't be like well sorry about that i'm fucking huge
they're great and even when he pointed his finger up he would break the chandelier and
shit he would break the light above him he was he was a fucking terror you didn't want him in
your house but anyways yeah they shrunk him thanks for the 10 bucks uh leon appreciate it
hey vladka bitch thanks for another thousand bits ten dollars derma three things uh one you're rad
two when are you gonna play the resident evil 3 remake and three you should make your bit sound
and a cash register cha-ching sound i don't even know what it is now i think i deleted them all
i'm such an adhd and the the sub sounds and the bit sounds they i just like they distract me
if i hear it i just go what was that noise and i have to pay attention over here now like
noise over there what was that noise and then i get like killed on the screen make it you laughing
no i don't want to do that i remember when there used to be subs and bit sounds yeah i know just
make it a sneeze i can't make it the sneeze when i play resident evil 3 remake i don't know
i have no idea hopefully at some point over the next two weeks i don't know i have no plan i never
have planned jeremy no plan elbertson invictus thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars thanks for
the 15 bucks hello germa i just want to say send you a picture of my rats charlie winston eric
i'd like to sit on my lap while i watch your vods thanks love you and the link has been banned
because links are banned well shit uh the link has been deleted because i links have been banned
temporarily uh the privilege was removed because of an attempted mutiny on me that's
unbanned i don't i can't i don't even know what it was he scammed us release the rats i don't even
it's just three asterisks i don't know i can't there's no thing to do purity i'm sorry i'm
sorry if if you have an image of if you're still here but you can't you can't i forgot links are
banned fuck links are banned the links were banned for the three days or so here but nothing is
temporary on this stream unban it now or it will last forever i think the whole point of this
stream is the entire stream is just everything is temporary doesn't that make that's everything on
this stream is temporary everything links shall not be infringed free to the links well all right if
one of the mods can get a link to the image i'll put it up invictus if you still here one of the
mods want to put it in the chat if they can they find it thank you invictus though sorry we didn't
get to see the immediately thanks for the 15 dollars nonetheless hey drago death night thanks
for the five dollars thank you for being awesome i'm glad you think that way i didn't think i was
awesome if you hated me i'd probably feel kind of bad because i really don't want anyone to like
hate my guts no you know that keeps they don't keeps me up at night it's like anybody else
they like fucking really like hate me i really hope not maybe they do do they i don't know if
you do then i don't know i don't hope you don't like hate me you i think you're like dislike me
okay like i don't like him he's i'm not into that i don't think i think he's annoying i hope nobody
hates my guts i really hope not after the whole lettuce thing though i probably made at least a
handful of enemies well what are you gonna do lm man thanks for the 450 germa on a scale from one
to ten how would you rate the general knowledge of chat general knowledge of chat 10 because chat
gets a computer and they can just literally have every single thing that's ever been known
and they can pretend like they knew it it's actually a great position to be in because
when i don't know the square root of eight people can go it's it's 60 it's 35 idiot because they
just typed it into the other fucking other monitor and if i do that people know and they call me out
on cheating and that i don't know so you have all the power in that regard so i would say a 10 uh jp
ny thanks to the 15 jp derma me and my friends at northeastern put a live production of the
rats movie please give it a watch and let us know what you think it's a it's a banned link
well community content night is tomorrow so we could get him through depending on how long it
is asterisk asterisk asterisk you see what your wrath has done my wrath what has your wrath done
what has what has your wrath brought upon this community uh we'll find it we'll we'll watch a
little bit of it tomorrow see if we can still find it tomorrow is community content night so
would be good there it's my fault it's your fault isn't that how the game works we just point at
each other and yell it's your fault it's your fault it's your fault it's your fault don did
trillo thanks for the 500 bits of all the bad games you've played which would you least like
to play again um of all the well what is it what constitutes a bad game a game that i didn't like
or a game that was truly awful like a four to ten or something one that you didn't like uh i mean i
probably wouldn't play any of the bad games i've played again so that's this kind of hard decision
to make uh i mean i i the thing i mean i i beat the thing i don't have any reason to play the
thing ever again i beat the whole game the evil within yeah but the evil within is not considered
a bad game i just didn't like it um probably odama there's no reason why i would play that
again it was just it was horrendous to me there's no reason for me to go back and play that again
for what reason would i ever do it i could somehow in some stupid weird world find a way maybe where
i could play the evil within but i would never play odama again so yeah uh phalanx ultron thanks
to the five dolls you're most watching the vod for the hulk stream and i couldn't stop laughing
you're one of the few content creators out there that genuinely makes me laugh keep up the good
work thank you for that glad you think this is uh fun and funny it's important to me also when
if when and if you play doom eternal make sure you play on nightmare it's always fun to watch
you suffer another game that i have to play oh we got the link take a look at these these rats
oh look at it look at they're they're up to no good you can already tell look at this you can
tell that they're just up to no good okay they're just look at they're up to they're already up to
no good like what's over there let's go get it yeah they're cute cute cute cute cute cute
thanks for those rats they're beautiful uh doom eternal though i don't know i have this
i derma i never have a plan albertson something toast fart thanks for the 20 dollars there's no
message just toast fart gave 20 dollars thanks for the 20 dollar bill appreciate it a lot of
money to give and just hbb toast fart i guess right a pigeon thanks for the 250 i just got
here when you were talking about holding in your shits but since it's relevant i thought
i tell you that you are not alone jeremy i once did not shit for an entire summer as a child
wait what it would come out at night so i had to clean up every morning with a tissue
holy shit that sounds horrible that sounds like a horrible thing to do every day i can't i can
imagine waking up and be like oh fuck here we go i'm sorry to hear that whatever the reason was
thanks the 250 though hey sugar shanks thanks for the 250 hi germouse happy 52nd birthday
i know you already have a big list of games you're gonna stream but have you considered
playing pikmin 1 and 2 yes so i recommend playing the wii versions hope you do so i can watch you
get all your pikmin killed to a single fat frog have a blessed day king uh yeah i'm gonna play
pikmin 2 the good one right pikmin 2 on the wii the good one that's the plan hey gnarly thanks
for the 250 so let me get this straight yeah this is the potion one that was gnarly who did the uh
brought up all the teenager bringing your uh desktop into the bathroom thing yep it was me
thanks for the 250 gnarly and appreciate the comment uh flat mc tragic thanks for the thousand
bits germer it's my friend sam's birthday so this is from us love you idiot happy birthday to friend
sam birthday sam this is from us i'm assuming that includes you flat mc tragic thanks for the
10 bucks happy birthday sam hey bone jackal thanks for the three dollars i started drinking shower
water every day like you told us to and for some reason i've begun pissing like a sprinkler starts
up with a steady stream then turns into quick machine gun like bursts you've been experiencing
the side effect as well you're drinking the water he's he's drinking the water that's not what i said
bar broski thanks for 250 germy when you were talking poo someone said you're basically a dog
do you remember you replied and dogs are basically mammals i'm haunted by this what does it mean are
dogs not like are dogs not mammals to you what's auto i said basically you know i said dogs are
mammals i said that i didn't say basically mammals did i i said that dogs are mammals
so that we it makes sense hey well i don't know yeah dogs are mammals so and so is the goddamn
blue whale and that isn't that weird how is that possible what's the only mammal that can breathe
underwater uh heck it's going on there guys hey gnarly thanks for the 250 sorry for exposing your
sacred bathroom rituals but i just thought we needed to address it i love you no matter how
weirdly you poop i don't still do this i don't still bring my computer into the bathroom thank
you drum major for the 250 they say read but it might not be suitable to say out loud okay let's
see right okay okay well without getting into the details they say tldr um uh that they they said
that you could you could be putting unnecessary strain on your asshole um i get the appeal of it
they say i used to make music on my laptop years ago when taking a shit do take care of yourself
yeah yeah i was all right okay i'm all right thanks for the 250 though
bar broski another 250 hey next time chat calls for quality face cam content you should pop up
with a custom commissioned model of your face with face rig uh chezan or sexan thanks to the
fifteen dollars 1500 bits stirr said it right you can make literally nothing into something funny
10 out of 10 uh i don't i'm not sure what we were talking about but i'm glad you got some humor out
of it it was the fucking lettuce part it was the part when we talk about lettuce very passionate
about that it wasn't a joke to me thanks to the 15 bucks hey based bernie thanks for the three
dollars and they say banner for some reason banner sticks renegade thanks to the 250 can you say this
with the robotic voice it's part of a song by lemon demon uh the robot voice how's that work
see oh let's find out this one okay what does it say due to my strong personal convictions
i wish to stress that this record in no way endorses a belief in the occult
does that do that is that is that of the song why does it sound weird still
what hold on a second what the fuck hello why does this sound do i'm going up and down still
there's something still wrong hold on there's something still wrong something's wrong what
auto-tune is still on it shouldn't be auto-tune should not be on oh auto-tune is
oh no i wasn't it wasn't on it was it was off it was that it was off i don't know it just
sounded weird for a second hey thanks sticks renegade i have no idea what i just said but
hopefully it was uh terms of service friendly thanks for the 250 hey milk i got those five
community subs from milk i don't think i caught them no i did milk at milka stand yeah i got it
i remember thank you to trans scout for the five dollars germa please please watch a video of uh
african civet cats drinking milk they drink in such a fucked up way i'm crying over this video
google it i'm begging you what is this african african civet cat milk they don't know how to
drink milk well what they they think it's food they think they think it's food they think it's
solid it hold on he thinks it's yeah they think it's solid he's trying to eat it like dog food
like i don't understand he's putting his whole face in
are these raccoons uh yeah they look like these are cats huh interesting interesting video thanks
to the five dollars hey yoda thanks for the 250 streamer tragically relapses on crypto gambling
addiction converts all money to wizard 101 in-game currency a pale chub in austin atlantis thanks
for the five community subs both of you all of one zombie thanks for 250 you ever been to a wimpy
we had one at a bowling alley that had laser tag kind of dump of a place a wimpy
no i i've never been to i've never been to a wimpy laser tag i miss a laser tag it was fun
a nv11 casting thanks for the 250 this mcdld commercial this mcdlt commercial is making me
cry laughing i have another commercial like that for you but i absolutely fucking love it look up
splash mountain rap it's a real treat and an absolute bump i'm gonna be eating food and
watching it let's see splash mountain rap that's terrifying by the way
the souls just come out of their body
so you guys well this is a just dance dlc that's a hard one to do you're gonna i gotta get five
stars to get that one do that one good the 80s was fucking crazy everybody was wearing a clown
costume 80s fashion was just like big bright colors big poppin reds and blues it was all
clown costumes i should have been i should have been existing in the 80s
like a circus uniform on now i was born in the 80s but i wasn't cool in the 80s there's a
difference like this guy was fucking cool with his like purple pants and his like clown shoes
and his mickey mouse shirt oh well that was interesting yeah that was a pog i guess
hey swiggy swanky thanks for the 250 read this off stream okay oh they're saying that uh
links are banned still because you can't post clips because they're links fuck all right well
don't worry well we will we will alleviate it a little it was just to teach some of these chatters
a lesson through specific domains really well that sounds pretty interesting to me quick clip it
but you can't hey vim thrall thanks for the 300 bits the mcdonald song over the tome
over the tom and jerry screaming almost made me choke on a gummy bear laughing also my
mash joke sucked and i'm sorry here's money i don't think i don't think the joke was bad
i think it was just wait wait you want to talk about like the gross mashed potato feet thing
i mean it was just it was just like gross hey shibiriririri wah thanks for 300 bits the
mcdlt is some of the dumbest shit i've ever seen also grilling burgers is the boomer dad way of
making a burger they're always dry and taste like ass i i can't i cannot imagine that's a real
comment i can't imagine that's a real comment i don't i i don't know i think that that's gotta
be like a like a fucking laugh out loud yellow bell moment i think a burger on the grill is
with like a good charcoal i'm not sure this you know what else listen to me guys burger on the
grill that's great i know like burger on the grill that's like level one of like the fucking super
intelligence meme thing right right at the very end corn corn on the cob slather it in a garlic
butter and just grill it right on the grate grilling is the best like grilling's the best
it's like one of my favorite things i can't believe you just said that it was a the boomer
way to make food well how do you make a burger you put it in like a pan i mean yeah i put it in the
pan i guess but if you have access to a grill it's just exponentially more flavors there's so much
more going on now i would i will give you this grilling's a pain in the ass because if you have
a charcoal grill you have to preheat the grill you've got to put the coals in you've got to heat
the coals up dump them in there it's dangerous i get it but it's way better i mean that is that
just my opinion i think i don't know i think it is yeah it takes a while it takes like 20 minutes
to heat up coals and then it takes a long time for the grill to heat up it's a process but you
do it you hang out you make the you get the you get some party hats and get a couple of
seats just hang out outside get the grill going make some birds and dogs man get some corn on
there right on the grate garlic butter just hang out i said birds birds and dogs not birds although
you could put you could put chicken on there if you wanted to i'm sorry i disagree i don't know
where you get the idea that burgers on the grill are bad you know that burgers on the grill are
good when an entire chain pretends that they do it that way burger king's whole ad campaign
is about pretending to grill their hamburgers flame broiled flame grilled grill grill marks
flame you don't get you don't get a fire in a microwave you don't get a fire in an oven
just doesn't happen and if it does you get a big problem moving on ike turtle thanks to the 250
hey lettuce hater you probably let your burgers sit up for like three hours before you eat them
because your weak teeth can't handle fresh lettuce i made this hamburger today and i put lettuce on
it because i have strong teeth lettuce lads and it's a deleted link anybody have it anybody get
the link stripes beast thanks for 250 germa i swear to god the perfect burger you described
is the buttery jack from jack in the box your perfect burger is like five bucks no it's a
mushroom and onion swiss bro no it's you that's not even accurate that's like saying your favorite
okay so mcdonald's has a fucking bacon cheeseburger is my favorite burger going to be from mcdonald's
the baconator from fucking wendy's or whatever oh yeah that's right no there's a version of it
that exists it's like a popular way to make a hamburger if you make your own baconator it's
going to be way better than if you get it from burger king it's just it's a difference see no
it's not what do you mean no it's not it's wait if you order a baconator from wendy's and you
make your own baconator on the grill are you trying to tell me that you that they're the same
oh i have no no no way what who is saying this there's nobody in this chat actually saying this
if you guys have a made bacon on a grill you can do bacon on the grill it's and it's i don't know
how to do anything i don't know how to cook at all cooking on the grill is awesome because it's just
the caveman fire fucking way to cook hot is hot fire food burn flip done you don't need no shit
smell good take off fire eat you don't need to oh well first get a little bit put some oil
and then add a put a marinade on that and then slip it down over here and then get the
and make sure you put delicately put it into the oven for 15 fucking minutes at 425 degrees
take it out put it back in the pan no no no fire burn meat yes you don't have to know shit
it's the best way to cook because it's like you can't really screw it up you can put like
literally anything you want and like here's how you tell if something's done on the grill
take it off you eat it you can burn it yeah but you don't it's it's it's all you follow
the directions you're fine he knows how to cook he's just lazy grilling no lazy grilling takes
so much prep work it's unbelievable it takes like exponentially like three times more prep
to get a grill going than just to turn the burner on your stove on it's not the lazy way it's the
no no it's the exceptionally lazy way because it takes a ton of work to get it going and then
you just sit there while your food just sits on a grill you don't have to do shit you don't use
propane i really don't want to start an argument here about how like hardwood versus propane like
wood fire and coals i really don't want to start an argument here but i could about hardwood and
wood grilling and coal grilling versus gas and propane grilling i could start a fight here there
ain't nothing in this world there are a few things that really get me going and that can
never be compared to and one of them is the sound smell and sight of hot coals at the bottom of a
grill when you when they dump in there and they make that like and the smell it's just that hard
and the sight that just you see the fire you see the the red the orange hot heat
fire get that grill back on and you can you get that just ain't and they ain't much like it
this is boomer talk no it's not come on no way it's like a hot this is the boomer talk
hot coals are just so such a sure it is boomer talk you know why because people were cooking
with like this for a fucking hundreds of years they didn't have a button they turned on and
this is you want to call me a boomer this is like super boomer this is like fucking caveman boomer
okay they used to cook on rocks guys and it just it's something about it is there's so much
interesting history with like grilling over hot wood it's it brings you back to the fucking 1700s
when christopher columbus made the first weber grill they had stoves go back even further go back
to go back to go back to the 1200s they used to cook on rocks on the ground coals hot charcoal
carbon they also had stoves in the 1200s go back even further go back to go to 680 the smell the
air was so clean fresh hunting they would and the coals hot still stoves in six when did they not
have stoves when did humans not have stoves when did they cook on rocks when was it it was like bc
we've always had stoves no we have not before but wait you're telling me that you told me bc before
christ like jesus was using a stove that's kind of a weird image isn't it like can you got you
can you picture jesus like cooking macaroni on a stove that's like kind of weird right he's like i
i think about like the magical things that i've written about him and he's like just sitting there
stirring like food like stirring like fucking macaroni and cheese macaroni wasn't invented yet
go back then no go forward and then go back go forward to get a box of mac and cheese and go
back to fucking 2 ad and get it on those hot coals the point still stands there ain't nothing like
hot fucking rocks and wood that's cooking your food and the best part the smell doesn't leave
your body for two weeks you will run your fingers through your hair and you will just be like why
does it smell like an ashtray in my hand ah but it's a good ashtray it's like a hardwood it's a
carbon it's a heat it's a it's it's a strong hot smell okay moving on it's a strong hot ashtray
just nuke your food in the microwave we already went over the fact that that can you cook a full
turkey in the microwave every time it makes me laugh how long do we even come to a determination
how long what would the time be like 70 minutes like 60 minutes in the microwave
i know the mr bean thing but but seriously like how what would it actually do at like low power
one minute on max probably 40 minutes at like two out of 10 would it explode
not at minimum power right it would be seven to nine minutes per pound
so you're talking about like more than an hour at low power in the microwave
it would be cold inside it would just be raw it would just be steam it
can you steam a turkey how would you steam a turkey you can steam a turkey
easy makeup and turkey a boiled turkey oh my god oh that's that does not sound good
anyways let's run the credits thanks for sticking around we'll see you tomorrow for
community content night boiling a turkey you probably it would hurt to bite into that you'd
break your teeth it would be hard it'd be a rock thanks well we had some huge sub drops today
so thank you for dropping them ready came in with 50 community subs we had we had 20 from super bruce
we had 10 10 10 how do you guys thank you a shitload of people thanks for the huge amount
of support thanks guys anyways peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 lettuce gives you very little
nutritional value it's just crunchy water why eat it i eat meat i ain't no fucking i ain't eating
no fucking salad i'm no hippie hipster fuck all that shit give me a big ass chicken sandwich with
lots of mayo and ketchup that's the good shit and yes i do like ketchup and mayo on a chicken
sandwich sandwich shut up chat okay now that that's a boomer that that's the boomer way yeah
germa are you like using a grill what are you fucking 50 i will tell you hailey there is a
lot of nutritional value in some vegetables we're talking mushrooms we're talking onions
we're talking putting them in the pan with a little bit of butter and a little bit of oil
let them get happy together take that slurry put it on a bun put that bun on top of a burger put
that burger on top of your mouth and eat it mushrooms aren't a vegetable you know what
i've come to realize i don't i don't really like vegetables i hear that's weird listen to me i i
okay i'm i'm a i'm a bean guy i've realized i'm a bean and fungus guy i'm a bean fungus and
shallot i love garbanzo beans i love kidney beans i love black beans i love like i love being i love
them i love legumes i love them i love mushrooms i love onions i love garlic it's one of my
favorite things in the world garlic and i'm not a vegetables guy huh i don't like lettuce i don't
like tomatoes i don't like eggplants i don't like zucchini just gross i don't like potatoes really
potato i don't like them i do like asparagus though asparagus vegetable or is that a fucking
fungus i'm kidding you like avocado i like avocados not every day but i do like them
oh yeah i'm a fungus and bean guy with the weird shit that grows on the ground that makes your eyes
hurt green onions onions garlic shallots yeah i'm not like a true truly vegetable kind of guy i eat
them but i don't love them i do like fruits too i love bananas as you know i eat bananas all time
i'm a big banana fan i don't like sweet potatoes i find them to be odd sweet potatoes are
this there's one place that i like sweet potato and i might be even wrong um what's that dish
that's at thanksgiving where it's the really really mushed up sweet potato with the marshmallow
on top yams that's those are sweet potatoes right candied yams there it are candied yams
i they're very good it's that the yams mashed up hot with the marshmallow on top that's phenomenal
i don't i don't like sweet potato fries sweet potato this sweet potato that sweet potato bread
sweet potato sweet potato sweet potato people put it in everything it's like it's like the new
avocado before people put avocado in everything now they put sweet potato on everything or part
of everything you would open up a menu at a restaurant it's like oh this oh avocado here
avocado there we've got avocados on this there's avocado here and it's like okay now open a menu
sweet potato on there sweet potato fries we've got sweet potato mash sweet potatoes
yeah candied yams are a disgrace why pretzel buns fantastic i'm glad you said that
it's they taste like poop why do you know what that is
oh why are you comparing your well wait what anyways peaceful haley there are some vegetables
in some beans and beans and shallots especially beans garbanzo beans hummus is my i could eat
hummus until i died if you told me if like the devil broke up from the ground i'd
oh oh yeah oh this is not a devil voice
sorry i've got a little i'm having a little bit of a cold
there we are no not quite why does this sound so strange oh okay jeremy for the next
three years you can only consume garlic hummus oh i have ruined your life haven't i
now that sounds great do i get to literally eat any other food
no only garlic hummus it is the only thing you can eat what do i get for doing this
well your everlasting soul for one and two i'll give you 2000 bitcoin that sounds good to me sure
sign me up i would love to oh gonna get another gonna get another soul 2000 btc is a lot of
fucking money no i could do it i can literally do it i can eat hummus every single day garlic
hummus mediterranean hummus roasted red pepper hummus we've got like olive hummus you've got
like cheddar hummus there's so many different variations i love it it's my it's so good if you
never had hummus before oh cedar is a good brand tribe is a good brand tribe tribe is a great hummus
brand they're all great but nothing else well would add that have wait a minute hold on is
there bread involved is there bread involved can i eat with this with bread hey what there was
nothing in the contract that said it was gonna be bread here my friend you don't just fucked up
no no hey thank you uh hack it fast for the thousand bits here my friends introduced me
to you years ago and i used to think that your videos were just all right that's okay but i as
i familiarize myself with you and i find myself watching your vods and live streams almost daily
videos are the perfect way to end my day after my nine to five job and especially help for doing
these stressful and uncertain times just want to mention that if i ever have a conversation with
you in real life i will never ask you about hamburgers and i'm very skeptical skeptical of
hash house though i do not be skeptical of hash house i go go at the link everything there is
good if you don't like hamburgers it doesn't matter they have this meatloaf sandwich thing there
oh my goodness it's it's oh it's so good it's the best thing ever it's the best restaurant on earth
it's so fucking good that hamburger the burger is just it's like a big but it's thin it's huge
but it's thin patties there's two thin big patties and they're just perfect where is the link uh the
link is on the las vegas strip kind of right in the middle but thank you hack it fast for the
thousand bits thanks for hanging out hey goyke thanks for the five dollars hi burger guy again
i've been told i'm a maniac because of how i eat things like i only eat the meat on the burger no
bun or anything else and also slathered in mustard also i eat tomatoes like apples there's something
wrong with me um maniac i'm not sure that's a maniac thing i think that's a i mean that's
the thing people do on diets don't they they're that's like a low carb diet is mustard allowed
on a no carb diet i mean people people do that as a mustard diet shut up he's a maniac
you are a dog that was raised as a human what the fuck hey hey milka stant thanks for the thousand
fifty ten fifty ten dollars and fifty cents you're the only streamer i've actually donated this much
money to and ten even ten dollars is a lot of money to give to anybody especially a random
e-clown but thank you your content has helped inspired me and got me out of a negative head
space these last few months my boyfriend and i almost went homeless but things are picking up
i got a full-time job now and that one that i really enjoy and you've inspired me to make art
again thanks for what you do my outlook on the future has become more hopeful that's awesome
that's very good i'm really that's awesome to hear whatever you're doing for your job hopefully
you enjoy it you say you do whatever it is keep doing it and keep trucking thank you so much for
the thousand bits good luck i wish you the best peaceful hailey gave five community subs dropped
them right there thank you hailey appreciate the five subs cat boy if 250 why call it big lettuce
when you can call it the romaine the romaine empire oh damn can i go back and delete the
vault and restream the whole stream and get we'll do the same thing and get to that one point i'll
say that also let me let let your anime of the year be hunter x hunter king that's gonna be a
tough one we're in 20 we're in 2020 i've got to figure out what my anime of the year is going to
be it's true there's been quite a few suggestions jack the mac thanks for five dollars i'm sorry
that you were getting old germa arthritis sucks i'm not sure if that's it yet i we don't i don't
know it's either rheumatoid arthritis or i have intercostal nerve damage somehow which i kind of
know maybe how it happened but i don't know a thousand percent i don't know and i don't i
don't want to talk about medical stuff i do sometimes unless i kind of know what i'm saying
and if i'm saying is true i don't want to be like well guys this is the thing that i have
i don't want to do that i'd rather just do it and see what happens it has nothing to do with an
injury i will tell you it's not an injury thing i will maybe have some more info hopefully if
it turns out that's what it was but i don't know i have right now i've been diagnosed with costa
chondritis that's the diagnosis that's there now and then wait a minute hold on this we gave
you we did another test and uh you might have r3 you might have ra you might have rheumatoid
arthritis this this thing is high we have to you're gonna come back and we gotta we gotta
recheck this okay we'll see but thank you wolf for the 250 germ thanks for the good times as always
we sure do need them right now my mom found out yesterday that she had a sister she never knew
and we found out today that she had passed away in her apartment of covet 19 that's terrible i
don't know what else to say other than i hope you and all the chat are staying safe and sanitized
out there very trying times we're in right now you and your content helps me get through it all
i know a lot of chat feels the same i'm really sorry to hear that that's finding out that you
have a sister you never knew and then that she passed away that's two sort of two very very
kind of earth shaking things i'm really sorry to hear that but thanks for the 250 and stay safe i
wish you and your family the best we are almost at the end of the bits here we had 500 bits from
thank you bat mom 250 from rosy briar get well soon germa i'm doing all right i'm doing just fine
i'm good thank you appreciate the concern thanks for five dollars and 64 cents pond of this streamer
a burger with the meat marinated not dipped in barbecue sauce and a fried egg uh i'm gonna i
have to stop you right there i'm sorry i have to stop you there i don't like egg i don't like egg
on my meat uh i don't like the no i'm sorry i'm not an egg i'm not a fried egg on burger guy i
know people love it but it's a it's a textural thing for me because when you bite into the egg
and if the egg starts to run and then all you got a problem with the egg running and it's runny egg
in your burger i know people love it and it's a huge kim loves that shit she's a huge fan of that
but i'm i'm not really that big of an egg guy either i like hard-boiled eggs i don't like runny
eggs i think that's my problem i like a a jammy egg but most places that do egg on a burger
it's deliberately in my opinion and not even my opinion it's actually deliberately well make
sure it's a big runny egg bite into it and get the fucking egg all over you it's like deliberate
they do it on purpose that's what that's every restaurant i've ever been to doesn't like that
but i'm maybe i would like it if it was a jammy kind of old medium over medium egg rather than
over easy maybe i would like it but i just don't like the runny egg it's a textural thing
also you ever considered playing metro exodus it can be finished in three streams yeah i thought
about it i played i beat metro 2033 on stream and then i had a meltdown in the first 30 minutes of
last light and vowed to never play the whole series ever again for some reason i don't i have
no idea and it was like it's kind of like the halo scenario where i had such like a bad stream
kind of moment that like the game is now fucking ruined because like the stream i was like so
fucked up and so like annoyed or i couldn't like do the first mission or something and now like
the game is ruined for me it's weird how that works he's just traumatized but maybe when maybe
eventually i don't know i'd have to play last light first because 2033 was good it was a lot
of fun and i beat it i'm assuming i would like the next one i just had a huge issue for some
reason that day a bulbous whack thanks for the five dollars russian car driver is the best worst game
i've ever played full of awful translations and poorly designed ui i would recommend it
russian car driver never heard of it hey adison thanks for the three dollars hey germa i've been
loving listening to your streams while playing animal crossing lately have you played anymore
with kim actually no i have not i've not played any animal crossing it hasn't really been a whole
lot of time just recently have kim and i really started to settle and there hasn't been some
something crazy that needs to be set up or done or uh so maybe now that these last like a few days
but now i haven't played it the villagers all moved oh does that happen oh well i'll get new
ones uh anything else show official thanks for the five dollars hey germa when will you do the
public domain movie night two days and what weird movies and games do you think are underrated i
want to find something new to do during the quarantine any movies and games that i think
underrated friday is the public domain movie night but stuff to do that's weird or underrated
watch ghost busters one and two watch gremlins two especially if you haven't seen gremlins one
and two watch them today um i would say gremlins is a pretty underrated series uh curvy enthusiasm
is pretty is a pretty highly rated series a lot of people know about that underrated ghost busters
not a movie well they said movies and games i'm doing the movies part first games i mean the
easiest one to say is sorcery i think that's the criminally most underrated experience although
it can be kind of frustrating if you if you weren't around years ago sorcery is it's probably
the most underrated experience for a game herb your enthusiasm is my favorite soulsborne game um
i don't know besides that i don't know other games that are underrated that i play or liked
i've played so many games it's like hard to keep track sometimes there are games that i forgot
that i've played that actually happened recently i think somebody brought it up in this stream i
was talking about like playing it and somebody was like hey i think you did that i'm like maybe
like a month ago somebody said it what was the game that i said that i that i didn't know that
i played already oh and yeah enter the gungeon i streamed enter the gun i streamed it and i'm
like yeah maybe i'll like check that out like dude you already did that well i did um i i can't check
it out yeah that happened uh sure be real thanks for the 250 whales don't breathe underwater for
fuck's sake what do they do they come up and they go and they go back down for like four hours
that's kind of cool what a fucking badass mammal what a badass mammal and and they also go like this
that's pretty cool hey pigeon thanks for the 250 i probably should have mentioned that i was like
10 at the time of the great shitholding i assumed uh rip alex trebek thanks for the five dollars
i'm a great stream today you don't have to read my name if you don't want to
oh because i remember last time last time i yeah i was wondering if you could help me with a with
tax advice i'm 23 and i've never done my taxes do i need to do them am i going to get in trouble
xoxo tell auto i said hello stinky um okay let me help you here uh did you have income in 2019
if the answer is yes you yeah you do am i going to get in trouble well that all depends um that
all depends if you claim your car as a dependent i would recommend against not doing that uh but
you should file taxes i would recommend getting in touch with a certified public accountant a cpa
or if you're worried about potentially wait i had a bunch of money that i didn't pay taxes on to get
a cpa and help you out with it just use turbo tax yeah yeah but if you don't people you can make
mistakes on turbo tax you be careful some people can potentially make mistakes on there just don't
make mistakes yeah but if you had income last year i yes i highly advise you filing a return
although hey i will tell you uh the date to file a return has been extended in the united states
i believe to july 15th it usually is april 15th is tax day it is now july 15th apparently so
got some time to figure that out if you haven't done it good luck yes you have to pay pay your
fucking yes you have to pay your taxes and no you're not going to get in trouble as long as you
don't lie to the irs anyways thank you moth um moth priest for the 250 germ i want to let
you know you always make me laugh so hard and always make my day better thanks for doing what
you do thanks for the incredibly nice message appreciate it lizard 4000 thanks for the 300
bits hey germa rats instagib dev here can you remember of course i do i just sent you an email
about a new game i'm working on i hope you can look at it sometime best regards really i will
have to well did you send it to the to the germa email that's on youtube you probably could like
throw a paper airplane and it would get here faster than i would read that um hit up one of
the mods and uh let them know some details and maybe we can get in touch through discord
discord's a lot easier for me at this point but that sounds pretty cool looking forward to it
i'll take a look this is not a guarantee that i'm going to play the game this is not a guarantee
that i'm going to play that game this is uh i'm going to look into it it's going to be fun it's
got to be cool it's going to be interesting i gotta i've got to be it's going to be cool
and i got to be into it okay just want to make sure we're aware of this you just rejected it
no i didn't i didn't no i didn't i just i've got to be clear no pressure
no i'm sure it's gonna be fun i'm just i'm just fucking around don't worry hey yoda 985 thanks
to the 250 damn those african civet cats really be like and then they did germa chomp and then
milk twitter yeah that's true milk uh milk emoji twitter emoji of milk well i don't know what this
is yeah whatever what's that it's why does it say twitter twitter emoji of and then it's a bottle
does twitter emoji of milk i don't get it why does it say that why does it say twitter emoji
i don't know that's weird hey freak eight out thanks for the 500 bits hey germa watch this it's
arnold swartzenegger reading the book of genesis i why why do i want to watch this what's it click
it i just did hold on and the earth was without form in void and darkness was upon the face of
the deep and the spirit of god moved upon the face of the waiters and god said let there be light
and there was light and god saw the light that it was good and got divided the light from the
darkness and god called the light day in the darkness he called night i have screamed from
the mountaintops how terrifying this is because you and i think this is funny but your grandparents
will think that's real here comes the rant here comes the boomer rant what no i already i've
already done it but thanks for that uh book of genesis appreciate it hey stripes beast thanks
for 250 by the way somebody says boomers are on their way out anyways um you got some time
you got you got a you got a long you got some you got time here you got at least 20 to 30 years
at least so i mean if you think that like oh the boomers are on the way out and by july
um so i've got news for you that probably about 20 years you're gonna be like 40 by then you'll be
a boomer by then ah shit no not me not me i will never be a boomer hey crispy scooch thanks with
300 bits hey germ just a heads up that the source codes for tf2 and cs go have been leaked so if
you play them you could get a virus what but how does it how does it make any sense what
the source code for tf2 is leaked if you play tf2 you'll get a virus
i don't get it but so somebody just will make their own tf2 and that wouldn't that mean that
like somebody has to make their own tf2 and inject it with something bad how would they
know people are finding ways people are finding out a way to remote code execute oh valve said
you don't need to worry about it well let's hope that's not a problem that sounds kind of insane
source code is almost two years old and valve themselves they said there's no cause for alarm
at this point oh well somebody fuck somebody get fucking norton on it somebody somebody called
norton um that's kind of fucking horrible if that's true well tf2 hasn't updated in three
years so uh hey stripes beast thanks for 250 oh so the last supper was jesus showing off his
grilling skills for the boys uh a trans scout thanks for the five dollars how about a ketchup
sandwich ketchup is okay in certain random places i'm not a huge fan of it in a lot of places though
i'm not talking about tomatoes i just don't like tomatoes hey razzle thanks for the 250 germa you
started this whole youtube streaming career as a normal guy and through your success you've kind
of been pushed into this huge influential position that people look to for support does that stress
you out at all um not really because i think i've been very clear from the very beginning
that i've i've i've kind of just been doing this one thing that i think is fun and i really try not
to like inject very much more than my intentions here so we make a lot of jokes and we fuck around
a lot here and but i never want to get to a point where i'm kind of i've it's been like this for a
decade i don't i want it to be fun and i want it to be just something that i like to do and when
you talk about like influential positions looking for support i've made it pretty clear that i i'm
just kind of a guy and i don't hold very many large i don't hold very many like when people ask me for
advice i always say like i'll give you some the best i can but i'm not somebody that can i'm just
a guy that likes to have fun and that's kind of been the mantra since like 2012 but if i can influence
you to stop eating fucking gross lettuce on your hamburgers and oh i'm going to use it but no it
doesn't stress me out i think everyone here has an understanding that would this is just a fun
community there's not very much pressure on this community or on me really and it's kind of been
designed that way from the beginning guy equals vessel right whatever yeah no i but it's it's all
good uh we have only a couple more to do we have west yule thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars
germy you have the absolute best chat on twitch can we get a round of applause for chat sure
what is it what is this in morse code can somebody do morse code here ready
but what what is this what i say you're pissing my cat off
i'm sorry hey stream be on thanks with 300 bits best luck with whatever's ailing you germa also
i agree that lettuce on burgers is a travesty often it ends up piling all the toppings off with it yes
no matter the strength of your teeth it brings any delicious burger down with it no wonder it's
called iceberg lettuce much like the iceberg to the titanic monkey s damn didn't even think
about that a pink goat thanks for the five dollars as we ended here thank you pink goat they say hi
germ the reason i absolutely hate candy yams is because i cannot understand why anyone would put
marshmallow on top of vegetables also plain sweet potatoes are one of my favorite foods next to
salmon sashimi love ya uh because they're sweet they're sweet sweet potatoes are sweet and they're
ground up and then marshmallow i just love marshmallow marshmallows like my favorite
candy thing Reese's and whipped marshmallow i love it and i know where it came from we talked about
ghostbusters when i was a kid the part uh and this is kind of like fucked up i guess but and
this is a spoiler for ghostbusters if you've ever seen ghostbusters before the stream's over and this
is the last bit here so good night we'll see you later this is a spoiler for ghostbusters okay see
you tomorrow okay uh when they kill the state puff marshmallow man and he explodes all over
everything and he his his like marshmallow cream goes all over the whole place he gets goes
everywhere i was like wanted to eat it so bad and i knew what it tasted like and i wanted it so bad
and it was that like it was all over them they like had like cream they were eating it and stuff
they were like peeling it and pulling it off of like statues and like biting into like the creaminess
it made me love i want marshmallows ever i want it right now in fact i hope there's some marshmallow
related thing in the fridge because i'm gonna eat it right now why does it have to be so sexual
it's marshmallow it's marshmallow fluff cream yeah relax get out of here get out of here i love
marshmallows and that's where it came from uh state park marshmallow man died and i liked it
i guess there you go tldr and then finally we had uh freak out for five dollars thanks to five bucks
did you hear that about rick may he's the voice of the tf2 soldier and he died last week from the
virus it took a heart attack cancer and a global pandemic to kill that man he did good son real
good maybe even the best yeah that's horrible because i don't know what else uh rick may may
have done but these characters like the soldier it's it'll stay that the just how fun and funny
and interesting the soldier was it'll stay with me forever i think a lot of you too just the timing
and the delivery that a lot of those guys had was just they were having so much fun and you could
tell you could tell that when tf2 was first released and they started doing the meet the team
videos those guys were having a fucking blast the dev the devs were having a blast the players are
having a blast the actors were having a ton of fun it was so much fun shit everybody was having
such a great time it'll stay with me forever like some of those lines will stay with me forever
so somebody like rick may has absolutely it will stay in my memories and in my thoughts forever
i'm really really sad to hear that but with that we are going to be done i will see you guys
tomorrow for community content night we're going to do some art videos and we're going to hang out
maybe you'll be there if not maybe we'll see you again the next day for public domain movie night
take care we'll see you soon goodbye