How's it going? How are you? Yeah, good. Hope you're doing good. Welcome, everybody. I'm late.
Oh, I'm actually early by about an hour. You're almost at 1 million. I know. I'm keeping an eye
on it. I'm keeping a very close eye on that follower count. We're gonna do some chill stuff today.
I have some fun stuff to talk about, though. Well, I have two. I have a shitty thing to talk about,
and then I have a cool thing to talk about. What do you want to hear first? Good news or bad news?
Good news or bad news? Bad news always first. Okay. I might have COVID. I took a PCR yesterday,
so trying to figure out what to do. Lockdown, hunker down. Holly is positive, so
I'm still testing negative, but I want to go get a PCR. So we're gonna find out in another day or
two, because I keep testing negative on the at-home test, but I heard that that is possible. So,
but let me just be very clear. Seems to be very mild so far.
She's fine. Very mild, as well as me. I mean, I'm obviously listening to me, right? You can hear it.
I think, I think we're okay. I think we're gonna be good. So that's the bad news. The good news is,
no, baseball's not delayed. What do you mean? Baseball's in a month. I'm not delay. I said,
guys, sorry. I might have, I might have COVID. So baseball in a month is canceled.
It's not gonna happen. But no, this is good news. You want to hear the good news? This is actually
really cool. I'm gonna be playing Multi Versus in a couple days here. Remember that game? Remember
that game? Remember Multi Versus? And guess what? It's gonna be sponsored. So, fucking hell yeah.
That's pretty cool. I've been waiting for that game to come back. And they reached out and it's
like, all right, fucking yeah, let's go. You're gonna lose your sponsorship for swearing. I'm
not sponsored right now. I'm not gonna swear that much. I'll be, I'll be good. Marketing Andy.
Which game? Multi Versus. You remember the Bugs Bunny game? That's coming back. And I've been
waiting. I want to play that game so badly. I'm so excited for that game. Yeah, I'm not 998.
That's insane. If I have COVID, fuck. No, I'll be fine. I'll be fine. I'm gonna be good.
Trust me, I'll be fine. He's gonna have, you have to be brand friendly, Andy. Honestly, okay, I feel
like, let me be very honest with you. I feel like I am kind, I'm pretty brand friendly as it is.
Don't you think? I don't think I'm a brand risk. I think it's just, I am just who I am. And that's
it. And I don't, I don't think I'd do anything that would be a risk or anything. I mean, I say
swear words. You guys, we, we are the, yeah, you guys are the brand risk, not me.
This chat is the brand risk. I, I can behave during a sponsor segment. You guys are the brand risk.
That's fucking funny. You literally, yeah, I, you're literally weird. You're naked. I'm, I didn't,
no, just listen to me. I can be brand friendly. I can turn, I can be very brand friendly. I think
you guys can too. I think we can work together. Uh, the other stream while advertising another
stream, you spent like 15 minutes advertising a different mobile game. What? The other stream
while advertising another stream, you spent 15 minutes advertising a different game. No, I didn't.
I was making a comment on, um, on mobile game ads. I never mentioned a game. By the way,
that sponsor segment was well over by then. I streamed that game for six hours two days ago.
The sponsor segment was not for six hours. I took the ad out of the, out of the title. We
were just playing. I can be, I can be brand friendly. Whatever. Do you know what brand
friendly? I get this for you. Um, what do I got? That's not your whole, all your conversations were
not brand friendly before on that whole stream. 864 P Andy. Somebody tell him. How'd your physical
with the bug eating doctor go? It was pretty good. But yeah, I'm going to, I have a mute button
here. I don't know if I'm going to be on cam that much this stream, but whatever we'll see.
This is probably not going to be a long stream either. Cause I was like, I'm ready to go now
and I want to stream. It's not that I don't want to stream. So I want to be live. I want to hang
out. I'm going to play my time. Is it, is it, is it Portia Portia or Portia? What is it? How do I
pronounce it? Spell it phonetically in the chat. It's Portia Portia. Okay. All right. So yeah,
you're going to hear me mute sometimes like this. That's for me to kind of clear my throat. Cause I
don't want to be gross on stream. I will obviously keep everybody updated on how I'm doing over the
next few days, but as it is right now, I'm still, I'm still testing negative for it, but we'll see.
I did a PCR and that you, there is no, I don't know what the, what the false negative rate on that is,
but who knows? Let's find out. All right. So let's go. Let's play. I've been hearing this music the
whole time. I'm sitting here telling you guys that I'm like, I've been exposed to COVID and this is
all I hear. This is like not the right music. Is the baseball stream in trouble? No, the baseball
stream is, is perfectly fine. That got moved to August 19th. So don't worry. That's still gone.
Okay. Here we go. I have it ready, right? Yeah, I do. So this game, if you want to,
okay. I wanted just to chill today. I didn't want to have like a crazy stream with a bunch of crazy
shit going on. So this is going to be a chill day. You understand? If I have, if I have boogers
coming out of my nose, you need to be, you need to tell me. Otherwise there's no way I'm going to
know. Should I, is it a controller game? Is it a controller game or what? Or should I do keyboard
and mouse? Controller game? This is Harvest Moon. I mean, it's supposed to be kind of, it's like a
Stardew Valley kind of game. Once, oh, oh, thank you for reminding me. I'm going to sneeze. No,
I'm not. Okay. No, I'm fine. Let me tell you something about green screen. So green screen
movie night, I'm going to address you directly on this. Green screen movie night. It, I don't have
a date for it yet, but this is the final day to submit something. If you have a video that you
want to submit, please go to the discord and read the rules. This is tonight at midnight Pacific.
It's over. We're closing submissions tonight. We have already hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of submissions. It's going to be a lot to go through them. I'm not going through them because
I obviously want to stay completely. I don't, I want to be in the dark completely on it. I have
watched because I couldn't help it. I've watched like four of them and I was laughing my ass off.
So, and I was like, I got to stop. Don't look at it anymore. No more. So tonight it's over.
You're desynced. I am not desynced. You look pretty pale today. Yeah. Well, the exclamation point,
sick. What the hell is in your ear? What? What do you mean? Oh, this. Okay. It's an earbud.
You look pretty pink. Do I? Whatever. There's a bug in your ear. Your neck looks really bulgy today.
No, it's because I have a fucking gross beard. All right. So that if you have a submission,
just get it in. This is your last day to do it. After tonight, we're going to vet all these,
probably shave it down a little bit. And then I want to say over the next six or seven days,
maybe less depending on how, how fast it takes to go through them. So you can imagine somewhere in
that week of, let's see here. So submissions are done tonight. So therefore you can expect
somewhere around maybe this coming weekend, possibly we'll do it. Maybe if, if we can get
through them, maybe Sunday, this next kind of Sunday, this weekend, I don't have a hard
date for you though. I will have a good date for you in two days. So when I stream on Tuesday,
I'll give you guys a hard date because then we, I can go over with the mods and the community
leaders and stuff. We can figure out how long it's going to take. I didn't, did I pass a million?
You liar. I didn't pass a million. Tweet that the submissions end tonight.
Yeah, that's a good idea. It's still pretty early. Let me tweet this. Hold on. 99875.
It might happen today. It might not. It depends. I should write. Also green screen movie night
submissions end tonight at 1201 midnight. Technically that's tomorrow, right? But like
people get it. If you have something, go read the rules in the discord and maybe. Okay. Oh,
that's it. That's good enough. If you have something, go read the rules in the discord
and submit it. Is that good? Also green screen movie night submissions end tonight. Wait, green
screen movie night submissions end tonight. That's fine. At 1201 midnight. I say night three times.
Green screen movie night submissions end tonight at 1201 midnight. 12. Should I say end at 1201
midnight? That's better. End at 1201 midnight tonight. How do I say this without saying fucking
night three times? And then a thumbs up. That's good. Who cares? I do. This is green screen movie
night, man. All right. That's good. Tweeting. That's good. That's 1201 midnight tonight. That
makes sense, right? That people get it. Oh, I didn't say Pacific. Oh, who cares? Why can't you
edit a tweet? Whatever, whatever time zone you're in, it doesn't matter. Like it's just,
just like tonight. Look, if you submit it at like one o'clock in the morning,
I don't care. Who cares? We'll let it in. Don't worry. It's going to be fine.
You ready to play my time at Porsche? But yeah, I'm excited about that. That should be a lot of fun.
Okay. You guys ready? New game. Is my face game in a bad spot? Also, nobody is. I asked if this is
a controller game and everybody ignored me. I'll use mouse for now. I think I'll go talk with the
research center first. Go talk with the research center first. I think I'll go talk with the
research center first. Which one sounds like me? Oh, okay. I'll say it and then you guys tell me.
I think I'll go talk with the research center first. Research center first. I think I'll go
talk with the research center first. I think I'll go talk with the research center first.
Not one. I think I'll go talk with the research center first. This house is so weird. I think I'll
go search center first. That's close. I think I'll go talk with the research center first.
Get out of here. I don't know. No, that's not me. All right, so we're gonna go three.
I think I'll go talk with the research center first. Okay, hair. How did I spin him? Oh, okay.
All right, hair length. Hair. Oh, hair highlight? No, no. Probably this one. Wait. No, this one,
but short. That's pretty good, right? Or is it this one, but shorter? This one or the other one?
Bowl cut. Bowl cut or riot. This one's fine. Yeah, that's that. That's what it is. All right,
so what is it? It's like kind of like more like this. That's pretty close, right? That's close
enough. Like that. Yeah, that's close enough. Make it wicked greasy looking. Marco. My name is,
I don't want it to be me though. All right, I want it to be Craig. No, not Craig. Joshua.
Jerry. Jerry's easy. Okay, now face type. Upper face? Wait, oh, I can do this? This doesn't look
like me at all. It's like not even fucking close. That's pretty close. Lower face? This looks like
Mark Zuckerberg. Okay. Do I really care that much about this, honestly? Jesus. I'm just that guy
from Homescapes. You know the mobile game? Okay, uh, I think I'm gonna stick with this. Yeah,
we're staying with this. Okay, is that good? Do the longer mustache? No, no, no, no. No,
this one's better. Okay, that sounds good to me. It's Jeff Foxworthy. Who cares? Let's just go.
Choose your birthday. I get to pick my birthday? Okay, what month is this? Day one, month two.
Where's the month? Where's the month? Wait, there are only four months in a year? Wait,
what? There's only four months. They don't even have my birthday. Okay, um, how about fall third?
Fall third? I was gonna say fall third. Do 420. Oh my god, I hate you for saying that. Don't do that.
I'm not doing it. I'm doing fall third. I'm not doing 420. That's the easiest dumb thing.
Okay, here we go. We're about to land at Porsche.
Wait, that looks beautiful. What are you gonna do then? Yeah. We get someone like you wants to be young.
Thanks. All right, so now what? I'm gonna do, I'm gonna play controller. Did I keep asking this
question? Should I use the controller? I've asked it three times but I just don't look after five
seconds because it takes about 10 seconds for the delay to go through and I just forget. Is this so
hard to use a controller? Controller? All right, yeah. All right, here we go. Presley, how do you do?
Hope you had a pleasant journey. We're just chilling today. Yeah, anyway, I'm here to show
you to your workshop. All right. I didn't get to know my part too well. Turn up the volume.
Is it low for you? Is that better? No one's been working there since your pa left Porsche so many
years ago. Is this Pokemon? No, it's not Pokemon. This is my time at Porsche. Yeah. This game is
apparently very good so hold, excuse me, hold your judgments now. Hold your judgments right now.
All right. Dash is R1 plus R1. Okay. Jump is circle. Get the battle axe. This place sure has
seen some wear and tear. What do you think? Looks homely. Now then. That's too loud. Well, blame that
guy. That's it to turn it up. He hasn't been presented to you when you've seen this house.
Okay, so I got a letter. Jerry, when you read this letter, I will already be on the other side of the
world. I'm sorry about that. I'm sorry that I'm not the father you wanted me to be. This was all so
sudden. So I didn't have much time to tell you or figure out how to take care of you. Then I thought
about this workshop. It might not look like much now, but I will brace you for the wind and cover
you from the rain. I've left my workshop handbook that details how I created things in my workshop.
The rest is up to you. Do your best and live a wonderful life. You always will. Here's the
workshop handbook. That's the worst George I've ever heard. It's Gilbert Godford. Can't miss it.
That was fucking Gilbert Godford. You're right. Okay. Here's the workshop handbook of your paws.
Take your time and come to Portia Commerce Guild tomorrow. It's right around the Peach Plaza. You
can't miss it. As much as I'd like to give you a builder license right away,
you need to prove your worth. Oh god. Got it. Tomorrow. Anyway. I gotta do my turn off button.
Get some rest. Maybe. Yeah. Nope. Bye, Presley. Thanks for your help. Oh, you made me laugh too
hard. Day two. Wait, a whole day went by? This house is so worn. This place is huge. You need
to fix it or I won't be getting a good night's sleep. Okay. How do I fix it? Use three
wood? I don't have three wood. All right. I gotta go to the com- Do I have a map? Go to the com- I
can't fix this place up. Comically large bed. The glowing objects are most likely to be collectible
resources. Okay. Glowing objects are collectible resources. Chat. I'm just a chat, Jerry. What?
What the fuck? Holy shit. Okay. Wait, who's this guy? He was spy for the Dubose Empire.
You're just the new- Do you want to fucking go? Why am I fighting this guy?
What? Wait, what? He killed me in one hit. Okay. Wait, there's a dodge roll? All right. Hold on.
This game just got way cooler. This is the Porsche Times. We're sponsored by the city government and
the local commerce guild branch to bring you the latest news in our city. For free. We're a monthly
publication, so papers will be sent out on the first day of each month. If you have any questions
or concerns, please do not hesitate to visit our office on Main Street. Okay. Cool. I feel like
this is something I was doing in front of the green screen. You lost the tutorial fight. I did
not lose- There's no tutorial fight, but what I'll tell you is I'm turning the music down
because it's very loud. That's better. All right. Go to the commerce guild. Let's go. Is there a
sprint? What is it? All right. I'm just gonna- Let me- The glowing objects are- What glowing
objects? That motherfucker's got a sword. All right. Glow- Oh, wait. Is it a glowing object?
What's that? Is it a fountain? What was that? Somebody just robbed a bank? Okay. Meet Presley.
Oh, I can't fight him. I can't fight the mayor. What is RPS? Rock, paper, scissors?
Shit. All right. He just went, uh, scissors. I'm going hand again. Yep. You just went rock.
I'm going hand a third time. Yep. I win. I'm going with rock next. Believe him. I win. Now I get to
be the mayor. I was owned. Do I get any money? Okay. All right. So now meet- I gotta meet somebody
here. Where are they? Oh, this is not the commerce guild. This is like the president's house.
Well, it was- It was blinking on the screen. Oh, there it is. All right.
So now what do we have to do? Nice to see you. How are you settling in? I'm not- Not so good. Hang
in there. Let me introduce you to the commerce guild. Okay. We're the organization that orchestrates
trade across the entire free cities region. This is the Porsche branch. Okay. We're pretty busy
throughout the year. Okay. Now then, let me give you your builder test. This is- Do I have to
actually build stuff? All right. So I gotta go punch some trees. All right. All right. Builder
test. What's this? I'm in need of eight wooden baskets. Please help me. Not yet. Everybody needs
to leave me the fuck alone until I complete this. All right. So I gotta go Minecraft Elden Ring.
All right. So I gotta build an axe and build a pickaxe. So I need wooden stone.
So let me go out to town. I gotta get some wood. Do I have an energy bar or anything?
Where's my house? I don't remember where I live. Is this my house? Okay. Let's go get a tree. Yep.
Can I get- Okay. Let's go. Is this working? I just got fruit. Can I kick the tree down?
It needs to be a smaller tree like this one. Oh shit. Look. What the fuck is this? What? Wait.
There's level- What level am I? Whoa. All right. How do I get stuff? The glowing objects are the
collective- Where's the- What do you mean glowing objects? How do I cut a tree down? I need an axe.
How do I cut stuff down? Oh, wait. Oh, here we go. Okay. All right. All right. All right. There's
some wood. It's just on the ground. Is this shit? Why would I pick this up? Why would you touch this?
Well, at least I have gloves on. How much wood do I need to build a- Hit the left stick? Oh, okay.
All right. I've got eight wood. I need some stone. Where do I get stone from?
Fight the llamas. No, I'm level one. They're level five. They're going to kick the shit out of me.
Why would I do that? That'd be stupid. Go steal it from people. No, it's definitely on the ground.
What is this? Oh, I can- It's like a trap? Lettuce and cumin will get you a- Okay. All right. I got
three. I need a- I need some stone. Is there a map button I can press? Oh, what's this?
Caterpillar and herbs. Look at that caterpillar. It looks cool. You already have shit in your
inventory because I picked it up. I don't know. Wait. Treasure chest. Ahoy. Okay. You can't
touch the water. How am I supposed to do that then? Really? Oh my God. All right. I need the
stones. I'm just like a little weird guy. You picked up four shits already. What can I do with
them? You can probably use them for something. Level seven snail lob. I can't fight a snail lob.
Not right now. Not at level one. Stone. Right here. Shit. You can definitely do it. All right.
Whatever these are, I'll fight them. Level tw- No. Nope. Never mind. Not doing that.
I just need some rocks. Ah, here we go. Is these rocks? Shell and sand. Okay. Where are the rocks?
Look at the top left. You can craft items on your work- Yeah, I know, but I need stone first.
Don't fuck around. It's by the house. What? It's probably close to the town. Yeah, that's what I
figured, but it's not there. Is he playing Breath of the Wild? No. This is my time at Porsche.
That's a chill game for a chill day because I might have COVID, so I'm just trying to relax.
It's possible. This isn't even my house. Whose fucking house is this? Where's my map?
Where's my house? How do I see the map? M. What is that on the controller? This is my house?
Where's my house? Okay. There we go. It's marked. Good. Look at these things. Mr. Ladybug? Are you
kidding me? All right. Wait. Give me this fruits and this fruit. All right. I got three apples. Nice.
This is like watching my grandpa play. Like, I like- What? Like, you could do any better?
Okay. Here we are. What? I can- Wait. Can I take- Can I have one of these?
What the fuck? No. Put it down. Put it down. How do I put it down? How do I put it down?
They don't want to kill me. I just aggroed the whole farm. They're like, yeah, don't ever do
that again. Get out of here. Okay. I'm going to keep going. All right. Here's my house.
I still don't have enough stone. I have to go to bed soon. All right. Let's see. Craft. Simple axe.
I need stone and wood from quarry and abandoned ruins. Okay. Where's a quarry?
You're failing the tutorial. Where- Where- There's no rocks anywhere. There's herbs and spices.
Fishing spot. Should I go up to like the- Go to town? Flower shop? Where are the other cookies?
Your inventory is full right now. And the ruins. Yeah, but I could just go to quarry too. I don't
want to go to the- All the way to the ruins. Like I don't want to like- Okay. I'll go there
tomorrow morning. I gotta get familiar with the map. I haven't even played the game for five minutes.
Oh, I can fix this. Yeah. Do it. Here we go. I can get more wood tomorrow. 20 wood. Nice. Okay. I'll
go to bed. I don't like where that bed is. How do I put it down? Okay. That's fine. Homescapes.
This house is so worn. I need to fix it. All right. I did. Do I have a chest I can put stuff away in?
Okay. There are rocks scattered around the house and- Yeah. Where- I don't-
Okay. I- This- They spawned. These weren't here before. Look. These were not here before. They
spawned here. You got a skill point? Cool. Yep. Chillin' and leveling. That's what I want to see.
These weren't here before. Look at these. These literally were not here. I swear to God. I would
have seen them. All right. I can do the axe. Axe and pickaxe. He's got delirium. I'm fine. All
right. This is from the town hall. Hello, new builder. We'd like to remind you that Porsche
currently has two authorized ruins for you to dive in. An abandoned room number one below the
Church of the Light and the Hazardous Ruin in the collapsed wasteland east of town.
I- I didn't have this info before. You guys get it? Come on. All right. How do I put stuff? I need
to make some shit. All right. Simple axe. I need one more stone. This was not here yesterday. Okay.
Can I- How do I expand my inventory? Can I look and see what I have in my inventory?
Well, on the controller. Because I want to play with controller.
This dude's hallucinating. Simple- All right. Let's make this at least.
Okay. Simple axe. One. All right. So now, where's my inventory?
I need to wake up. Now, I need a simple axe and I need a pickaxe. There we go.
I have the first builder test is complete. Now, who do I turn this into? This- What the fuck?
I thought he's coming to fight me. Oh, they work it out. Cool. Can I do this too? What's over here?
Hey. Excellent quality. Nicely done. You can keep them. I just wanted to see what you can do.
Okay. Okay. Flip through his workshop handbook. Okay. So, I need to make a stone furnace.
Very nice. All right. Pass the test. Stone furnace time.
Should I talk to people? Sister of the Church of the Light.
Goodbye. Who are you? Emily. Next door neighbor.
Okay. Let's chat. Pumpkin pie? Oh, cool. I forgot. This is- We're in like a rural town.
I'm thinking neighbor. Oh, cool. Neighbor. You might be six miles down the road.
All right. What do I need for this? Welcome to my workshop. Handbook's first page.
I'm going to try to write down all the knowledge that I'm going to gain as I tackle this workshop
business. Since I'm probably the- False alarm. I'm the one who's going to read this. Hello.
To me, handsome guy. Okay. Go up to the assembly station podium. Open up this handbook and select
a diagram. Once the framework of the item appears, I can start placing the different parts.
To install a party, to have the part in my hands. All right. Cool. So, let's do it. Item catalog.
Stone furnace. Stones can be- All right. What kind of fucking book is this?
Just write instructions. Why did you do a bunch of weird drawings and place it like a Microsoft
Word document? Like just write, hey, this is what you do and this is what it looks like on the other
side. All right. With relevant part equipped, aim at the silhouette of the construct and press
A or X. Okay. Assembly station console can be used to view material requirements, right?
Parts can be installed. Yeah. Yeah. Overcovered. Yeah. We all know how to do that. All right. We
get it. All right. So, now I need assembly station. I don't want a grinder. Did I pick grinder?
Stone furnace. How do I pick this thing? Oh. All right. Pick that. I want this. I don't want
a grinder. I want a furnace. Furnace. No, I don't want a grinder. Furnace. Choose. Okay.
Oh, wait. How do I get to my inventory? Is it I? All right. There's buttons that don't- Oh,
not on the controller, guys. I think I need wood. Let's go get some wood. Character. Ooh,
skill points. Oh, different- There's a Diablo 2 skill tree in this game. Okay.
Uh, what should I do? Fight, gathering, or social? 20% should receive one additional
relationship point. Receive one additional relationship point. Increase the workshop
points by one. Okay. Fight. Experience gained by 5%. Endurance issues decreased. Endurance.
I gotta be careful, though. I don't want to go all the way down this tree and get to the end
of the discipline tree that the priest had in classic WoW and literally have a worthless talent
tree. What was that thing all the way at the end? All the way at the end of the discipline
priest tree? It was like, give somebody 20% more- No, it was make all spells for a casted target
20% reduced mana cost. It was like, what a fucking piece of shit. What was it called? What was that
move called? Power Infusion. Yeah, that spell sucked absolute balls. It was terrible. And it
was the last spell at the end of the discipline tree. You suck- Hey, come on. It's good. Yeah,
in like 2020 WoW, in like 2005 WoW, that move was like, what the fuck are you even going to
give that to? It was terrible. I think I want to do gathering. Stamina cost decreases by 25% when
using the axe. Tree kicking and harvesting activities have a- All right, I'm gonna be
harvesting Andy. Let's go with the axe. Nice. Okay, so I gotta use the axe now. This is cool.
All right, missions. Very cool. All right, inventory. Let's get this shit out of the way.
So I gotta use my axe for shit. And it's an attack too. It hurts. What should I do with this?
I can convert this into money? All right, so that's good so far. I don't think I- Let me maybe an
apple to eat it. Maybe I get some whatever. I just saw what it looked like. All right, this is good.
Okay, I've got the axe now. You get a little window thing here. All right, so now I need some
more- I need wood. Let's go cut some trees down and I need a little bit more stone. This seems fun,
man. What? I need a better axe. Okay, there we go. I can cut this down. Cool. Do these- Does the axe
have durability? No, it's good forever. All right, this is- Okay, now I'm- Now we're working. Now
we're going- Stop deforesting to the land to make your white bread factory. You know what's
that kind of cra- Like, I can't- All right, what you said is so funny because I- We don't need
any more white bread factories, right? Think about that. There's really not a need for that at all.
Zero need for it. There are so many different brands of white bread that- Why would you ever
make a white bread company? Even a bread company? Especially white bread. Yeah, I got an idea. I'm
going to get into the white bread business. Dude, I would probably highly suggest you don't.
No, I can't do that yet. How much should I get? Do I have enough? You look like you'd eat white
bread with olives on it. I like white bread. I do. I'm not going to be one of these people
that sits here and tells you, oh, white bread is disgusting. Gross. I like whole wheat bread. Oh,
stop. It's- White toast is incredible. White toast is very good. So is wheat toast. So is
rye bread. Why do we have to be so weird about this? It's like, okay, you know when you go to
a breakfast place and for some reason people that order, when they order a breakfast,
I see people get weird when they do this. So you sit there, it's like, oh, what do you want?
I'll take the hash and eggs and okay, and I'll take an orange juice. Oh, what kind of toast would
you like? And it's almost like they close, they close the book. They close the restaurant, you
know, menu and they kind of puff their chest up and they're like, rye bread, please. Oh, you're
getting rye bread this time. And then when I order white bread, it's like, okay, white bread.
What are you, fucking 12? No one does this. Yeah, I know people do this because I do this.
I have ordered at a breakfast place and when they have all the bread options, I'm just like,
ah, you know, how about a nice sourdough? Even though I don't fucking care. And then the sourdough
comes out and I'm like, I don't even fucking want that. I just wanted people to think I was
not like 12 because I ordered white bread every time. I eat it. Don't act like I don't eat it.
Do you have taste buds? Yeah, exactly. You're the exact person that is a white bread hater.
And when somebody orders a white bread at a restaurant, you internally, even if you don't
say it, you go, I ordered wheat bread. You do. You're definitely the person that does that.
I have to be holding it. Okay. I don't like that you have to be holding the item.
Okay. 10 wood and then I need some stone. All right. I need another. You need to be.
I have it right? Stone stool. How do you make a stone stool? Oh, storage. Yeah. Give me this one.
Stone storage. Stone stool. Okay. I just need a bunch of stone. Where should I put this?
People can't steal, right? There we go. All right. Uh, fast exchange. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'll probably need this for something eventually. Tree sap. Yeah.
Plant fiber. I'm definitely gonna need this for something. But for now, let's keep it like this.
All right. Cool. So I need to get more stone. Why do people hate white bread? I don't think
people hate it. I think it just, it got a really bad rap because people started to realize that
white bread is like the same in your body as cotton candy, essentially. So people just kind
of treat it like shit because your body just doesn't really do anything with it. But you know,
whatever. All right. Give me some stones. White bread is kind of like cake. That's fake news.
No, it's not. It's not. It's not. Can somebody clarify if that's fake news?
Your body thinks that white bread is just sugar, essentially, is all it thinks, right?
I mean, it still has some qualities to it, but your body kind of treats it the same way,
doesn't it? It's just straight up carbohydrates. It's all it is. It's just nothing else.
That's all bread, though. No, but like whole wheat bread has, you know, fiber in it. It's got,
it's got like vitamins and shit. Like whole wheat bread is much better for you, right? Multi-grain.
They all actually, they have like some material. Get on the road. Get on the road. What are you
doing? This guy's driving in circles. Are you all right? I thought you were sleeping. I saw this.
I thought it was Z's. Hey, I can actually walk faster than this bus is driving. This guy's not
even on the road. All right. You're a fucking weirdo. All right. I need rocks. I gotta go to bed,
too. Stones. Quick. Where are the stones? I need stones. Play Elder Scrolls 6. It's not out yet.
Would you ever eat a gallon of mayonnaise for money? No, why would I do that? I don't want
to ruin mayo for myself. There is lots of things that I refuse to eat or drink because I don't want
it to ruin a thing that I like. A case in point, I don't, I will never put alcohol into orange juice.
I know that. Oh yeah, make it a screwdriver, a vodka and orange. No, thanks. No, because then
it'll make my brain think the taste of orange juice is gross. I love orange juice and I'm not
going to ruin it because I know that I'll be like, oh yeah, vodka and orange juice, vodka and orange
juice. That has tastes a certain way. But then I'll get up the next morning and be like, and I'll
reach for the orange juice because that's what I do. And I'll be like, no, no, no, no, no. What
about mimosas? No, no, thanks. I don't like drinking in the morning. I know people do it, but I don't
fucking know why or how. Let's drink a bunch of mimosas at like 10 o'clock in the morning. No,
no, I don't want to do that. That's too much. Okay, I need some more rocks. Yeah, mimosas,
they taste good. They're fine, but I don't want to drink at 10 o'clock in the morning.
I don't like Bloody Marys either for that same exact reason. It's like, it's like an 11 o'clock
in the morning drink. No, thanks. All right. Stone stool. Let's go. Got it. Okay. So now I got this.
It's time to do, I got this done. So now I can, oh, I get it. Let's put this in the corner over here.
So now make a stone furnace. All right. Now what? Can I call this guy on the phone? Do I have to go
keep talking to this guy? Why don't I, I don't have a cell phone number at this point. Hey.
Okay. This is your builder license. Now you just need to take this license over to the
mayor's office and get your workshop registered. Cool. Start taking regular commissions.
Come back and talk with me. All right. Register. I got my registration. It's my diploma.
Actually doing the tutorial went wrong place. Sorry. Do you like pulp? No, I do. I really don't.
Welcome. Welcome. I'm here to register my workshop very well. What is the name of your workshop?
The steak and eggs workshop. Uh, steak and eggs. I just like want that. That's the only reason why
I'm typing that in. I want to eat that right now. Steak and eggs, the wonder bread factory.
White bread, Emporium, white bread, bread. Um, no, not glue factory. I'm not going to name it
wonder bread. Jerry's bread. I actually like Jerry's bread a lot. Oh, come on there. Jerry's
bread by Jerry. Registration. I have to make bread. Can I make bread? Thank you. So we're going to
fireside town meeting. Okay. They'll be announced through the mail. All right. So we get events,
town events. By the way, I'm the new mayor. Okay. So now the game has opened up. Let's go in here.
You did it. Wow. Shop owner. Let me explain some of the processes for our trade.
I got to make bread office. We post workshop commissions on the board over there based on
the speed and quality of the results. We make ranking ranking of the workshops listed on the
wall behind me. There are other workshops in Porsche. Oh, yes. Adding yours, there will be
what? Why are you making us fight for dominance with each other? What are you talking about?
Which is listed on your license. The higher your rating, the higher the commissions you can get.
This is fucked up. But don't if you have your father's once you're done with your orders,
you can pick up the commission fee from Antoine. If it's from the or the respective person who
do commissions through the Commerce Guild, but some just build items and sell directly to the
market. Some just build items and sell directly. All right, let's let's make it easy. Since this
is your first commission, I've kept one just for you. Playing favorites are we evil, evil guy,
evil, evil guy. There are never too many commissions. Good day. That's runt. He's
the owner of the current number one workshop. Brilliant businessman, but I don't like the way
he does things. Well, I'm sorry. That was our last one today. Hey, press. I've got a job for you.
Or not. What a pushover this guy is. You own this place. You could literally say, Hey,
hey, runt, give me that paperback, or you're banned for life from this premises. Give me
the paperback now. Banned for life. If you don't just say just take it back. Oh, he took it. I
just run things here. I own this place. I own literally all of this fucking snatch that back
and go banned for life. You want to get banned for life. Give me that back. We're looking to
build a bridge. So the mayor put up the money. The year is up for the challenge. Okay, Arlo. Yeah,
he figured that place could be a real tourist attraction. What with the haunted cave at all?
Haunted cave workshop handbook to see if he has a bridge diagram. Well, one thing at a time.
If it's there, use it at your assembly station. Okay. After you're done with the bridge pieces,
you'll need to go to the designated spot and assemble the bridge. Also, and this is important
for a project as big as a bridge. You'll probably need to dive into the abandoned ruins to gather
materials. All right. And I'm gonna keep doing that. Okay, so what's my workshop rank? Higgins
workshop. Alan Carter works tooth fairy factory. Neighbor Wang's and Jerry's bread. I'm D rank.
All right, I got to get to the ruins. Get some stuff. Steal from the library. Okay, I got to
build the bridge. Wait, there's another quest over here. What's this? Church store?
Okay, so you want flowers? How about rock, paper, scissors? I thought there was an animal here.
I just saw this. I was like, why is there a bear just standing up? I was like, who is this bear?
Church of the light. Okay, what are you selling? Hello, our church only take relics
from the age of corruption. All right, seeds, rainbow flower. Do I have $97? How much does this
cost? It's all seasons. Apricot tree. Okay. Need large planner box from the church of light. I
don't have enough items to exchange. What? Why do you want like old CDs? Oh my god, this 10 grand.
Why do you want old CDs? I'm not doing that ever again. I promise. All right, I got plenty of
daylight. Abandoned ruins. We got to go get materials. Let's do it. I was gonna pick up
everything. Hey there. First time ruin diving? Yep. All righty. Let me explain then. All the
ruins in the alliance of free cities are regulated by we said like an open to enter the ruins. You'll
need to pay a weekly maintenance fee, but we'll give you a 60% discount. How much does this cost?
When you enter, I'll give you the jetpack and scanner. Very handy ancient relics. Mine info
resources becomes a lot easier when you have these equipped. This one beside me is an abandoned
ruin. No monsters or robots in there. Just resources and relics like power stones. Anything you find in
the ruins are yours to keep unless they're ancient weapons. Then we're supposed to hand them over to
the church for destruction. I don't want to hand it over to the church. I don't know. I don't trust
those people right now. I don't know who they are. They want old like rewritable CDs. I don't know
what they want. Okay. Okay. I'm done. Have fun and be safe in there. Anything dangerous in there?
Could I trip and fall? A workshop owner can make money through commerce guild commissions. All right.
So let me just go in and check it out. 20 gold to switch to another area of the abandoned ruins.
Wait. Wait. Hold on. No, no, no. I'm just gonna walk in. $80 for a weekly pass. I don't have a
shovel. No, it's not. I'm fine. I'm okay. Left trigger R2 to scan with the relic scanner.
A nearby relic will show up as globes of light. Okay. I have a jet pack too. Oh, shit. All right.
Let's go. Can I just hit anything? Do I have to dig anywhere? Use the scanner?
I look like a psycho. You can just dig. Can I? I kind of want to see if there's anything over here though.
I can just hit the what? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I can just go in a random direction. Whoa.
All right. That's kind of cool. This takes a lot of energy. Anything in here? Oh, there are
8.6 meters this way. All right. Let's go. What is it? It's a box. Can I pick it up? I remember
Remington mentioned something about this. Something about talking to the church. Oh, it's a
disk. It's data disks. Okay. That's where you find them. There's another one down here. Is it only
data disks? I'm not gonna get trapped down here. Oh, power stone and old parts. How much stamina
do I have? I'm gonna try to make it over here. Can I just mark them all? All right. I gotta mark
one at a time. This one's closer. Oh, there's a stone in here. We have to turn disks into monsters.
Hey, isn't there a new monster rancher coming out? Oh, I got a relic. All right. I'm almost out of
energy. There's one more right here. There is. Yeah. Another relic. Okay. For those of you that
are wondering, I have a button that I can press if I need to like sneeze or like cough or make
a gross sound so you won't hear it and you won't see it. All right. I'm almost out of energy so I
don't want to get stuck down here. Stop picking your nose. I'm not. All right. I got a bunch of
cool stuff. Oh, I can open the map and return it. All right. That's fine. That's pretty cool. All
right. So I have a data research center. All right. I got a lot of stuff to do. I kind of want the
I really like to have the jetpack now. All right. Head over there. I got I got enough stone to make
the furnace. What's that pig? I like it. I like this game. This game's pretty fun. Wait, we have
a quest. The farmer. Okay. Sure. What's up? It's great. Can you build it and test it out for me?
If it works as advertised, I'll order a few more off of you. How about it? Should I do it? Thank
you. Here's the craft recipe and here are a few seeds to plant. If you want more seeds, you can
buy them from my granny's shop. Try growing them to maturity and show me the harvest. Also, I have a
tip for you. Using fertilizer will help increase the harvest. Welcome to the round table. Chef's
choice. Oh, cheap soda. Apricot juice. Should I get a plate? Rainbow lemonade. Defense. All right.
Let's get the attack one. How do I not have enough? Oh, what happened to my money? Didn't I have 95
or $97? I don't get it. And Sergillian offner. The all-knowing. Did I get robbed? Why did I
lose all that money? Did I? What did I buy? You spent? Oh, that's right. It was 80 bucks for the
week. Okay. All right. Let me go to uh, who do I need to turn this into? One of these people.
Okay. I got a, you have a turn in here. You have a turn in here. Let's go. Hello. Nevermind. I don't
have anything I want to give you that I want to part with. I'm busy. Go ask Petra. I just tried to
talk to Petra. What do we have here? Data disk. Do you say data or data? I say data. You know what
it is. You want to know. It's actually related to how you can discover new diagrams. Data. No,
it's data. Many relics in this world are beyond our current understanding. Wait,
so are we like a thousand years in the future? These data disks are located all around the world.
They hold lots of useful information. I don't, I don't think I'd want to play these.
Do you know how, okay, do you know how many of these exist that are just a shitty playlist
from like 1999? Like eight tracks on it. They're gonna, they're gonna find these and it's gonna
find, it's gonna be like, oh yeah, what's on this one? They're gonna play it and it's gonna be a
burnt copy of like Sum 41, their studio album, their debut album. Oh, it's another Sum 41 album.
Okay. Put it in a list. Put it on the pile over there. Yeah, Hoobastank. Yeah. Weezer.
And some of them would be like, oh, what's on this one? And they'll put it in
and it'll just be nothing. And they'll realize, oh, this person fucked up this disc.
It says there's some data on it, but we can't even get it. Like they probably screwed up the
burn process. I remember burning CDs and it was just, sometimes it would just mess up. I wouldn't
do it right. And I would have to do it like four or five times to finally get the thing I wanted.
And it's just like, what the hell? When rewritables came out, that was a big deal because
you could go over everything. We're not miracle workers, so don't expect us to come up with things
from scratch. But we do know a thing or two about how the components should fit together.
Anyway, just remember that if you find any data discs, bring them to you this time. Wait, so I
can bring data discs to you or I can bring them to the church. This must be a piece of a relic.
You can use our recovery machine in the research center to restore it to its original shape.
Okay. Data discs. Stop saying data discs. It's data. There's data on here.
Didn't I already hand it in?
Age of Corruption.
Back in the age of corruption, it is highly dangerous because there's a chance this little
item here could contain the blueprint for Armageddon. It can't be that bad, right?
You're what? 18? 19? The age of darkness is probably just another fairy tale story to you,
right? When I was young, my great-grandma shared her first-hand account of the time before Peach,
the time when folks lived in ruins underground. The dark age of technology?
Everybody fought each other over the most basic of things, and people were considered old if they
had to live to 30. And it was always, always dark. Wait, what? What are we doing? Imagine that,
because that's what the end of the world looked like. That situation was created by the very same
sort of dark technologies stored inside this little disc. Anyhow, I'm not trying to scare you,
but it's the reality of your builder business. Dangerous technologies are spread all over the
world, waiting to be stumbled upon and rediscovered. Places like the Research Center and cities like
Vega V expedite their recovery. Calamity will strike again. Mark my words. So, it's a priority
of the church to seek out and destroy all the destroy them. All right, so we're gonna pick a
side. Ruin divers such as yourself, of course. Yeah, do we do we want to collect all the Hoobastank
burnt CDs, or do we want to destroy them? So, I can give this to you. Yes, yes, that's right.
The church will reward you handsomely for your efforts. We have in our possessions a vast amount
of green technology learned through the ages. Wait a minute, I know that look. The church isn't
against the use of good technology that can bring telesis to our society. We're only against
dangerous technology. What kind of green technology? Mostly special seeds. Special seeds. We can share
what we have with you as you bring us more discs. You do know how to plant. Destroy them. Don't
trust the church. I don't know. Yeah, I destroy them. I think I want to keep them.
Oh dear, you should ask your neighbor how to farm. Yeah, all right, all right.
Okay, so now I got to make a choice here. Do I want to be with the church? Who are these people?
Hi, Phyllis. Oh, who might you be? This is a nurse. This is Dr. Zhu's assistant. Hi. How does
someone's mental health affect one's physical being? I'm sorry, I was miles away. If you have
an ailment, please come to the clinic. Okay, I'm gonna play rock, paper, scissors. Okay,
how about this? Oh, come on. There it is. All right, there it is. One more. I win. Oh well,
stupid game. What do you mean stupid game? It's to see you again. How are you settling in?
Okay, all right, I guess I have shit to do. I gotta leave. Stupid game. All right, one more rock,
paper, scissors for the road. Nobody's gonna go fist every time. I mean, I got owned. Yeah,
you did. My games just crashed. Okay, I need to I need to go figure out what I can make here.
It's also time to go to bed. It's late at night. Wait, I have a skill point. Oh, shit. Okay,
I have two skill points. I think I'm gonna do this. Yeah, I want to do I want to be able to
gather shit. There's a treasure chest. There is. I thought it was a piece of wood.
I've got two apricots. Jesus. Cool. He's vaping off camera. I'm just like making fat clouds.
Okay, let's go back home. I think I got a lot done today. He's eating nicotine packages.
Dermot, why are you playing this? Because I'm just chilling, man. I'm just chilling. I'm fairly ill.
So I'm just trying to just hang out and just chill with you guys. I keep muting and taking the
camera off because I'm like coughing or snorting and I don't want you to hear that. Okay, what can
I make? Let's go to bed first. I could build the bridge. Okay, that's the next task. Ding ding ding.
Let's go. Ooh, wait a minute. I think I have enough, right? I should. All right,
the house is almost fixed. 20 wood. There we go. I'm finally gonna have a good night's sleep.
Oh, I get it. Thinking about. Oh, no. Maybe false alarm. Hang up the license. Can I do that?
Oh, I can. All right. Yeah, let's put it right on over here. There. Jerry's bread. Workshop D.
Builder Jerry. This is the shit you get from the Build-A-Bear store. This doesn't really
mean anything right now. It's a cute house. All right. Bridge. Let's see. Assembly index.
Bridge head. All right, I need plank. Hardwood plank. Hardwood. I need a grinder.
Smelt with the furnace. Okay, so I need a grinder. Grinder. This gets so hot. Wait,
do I already have a grinder? Nope. Okay, copper bar. Dude, how am I supposed to make a co- I need
a- hold on. Copper bar. Let's go. Fuel depleted. I need refuel. How much is it wood? That's 20 hours.
Okay, I got 20 hours worth. Make- let's make a shitload of it, right? Why not? I have a ton of
it. Is it gonna take a day? What? It's gonna take a whole day. Get out of here. What else can I- do I
have any other materials? I need two old parts, three copper bars, and a grinding stone. All right,
I think I have old parts, don't I? Old parts. Yeah, okay. Well, let me put this on. Just do a
somersault. That was weird. I can't just place this one. All right, I gotta go back into that
thing. All right, I gotta go back to the dungeon. Wait, what do I- do I have anything in here?
Soil. All right, just move it over. Let me keep these. Small planter box. Learn to craft the
planter box. All right, I'm gonna hold on to this. I'm gonna store all this junk here, though.
Copper tin, wood, stone, power stone, old- yeah, I don't want to have a full inventory.
Fertilizer. I got all the seeds and shit. Okay, hold on. Shit. All right, all right, I think I'm
all right. What does the juice do? Ten- restore- restore ten stamina. Just drink it now. All right,
I need to go back and get more materials. I need- I need another old part, and then how do I make
the other thing? Grinding stone. All right, what's the handbook? How do I make a grinding stone? How
do I make a grinding stone? Grinding stone, grinding stone, grinding stone. There it is.
All right, I can make this. Let's make five. There. Cool. All right, now I gotta wait till
these- how many do I have? Zero. Twenty- that's not in-game, right? Okay, it's not. No, it is.
All right, now back to the abandoned mine, and I need some old parts.
Jerma, you suck. Wait, is that- is this Emily? I got so much mail! What?
Okay, I guess I can do it. I think I had- I think there was like mint on my finger,
and I just put it in my eye. Yeah, there's like mint on this thing, and how did I get that on my
hand? My chapstick has mint in it, and I just put it in my eye. All right, this is just fucking spam
mail. This is just all spam mail. I don't even care. Whatever, I don't care. It's spam mail. So I can
plant some seeds, right? Teach me how to farm. I need to learn how to farm. Craft the planter box
and plant the seeds. That's it. Okay, thanks for the help. Just do it. Just plant. Okay. Craft the
planter box. Where the hell is that? Oh, right here. No, no, no, no, no. Give it to me. Okay.
Learn how to make a planter box. So how do I do that? Small planter box. Soil? I need to- okay,
I've got all- I have enough. Okay, I'm gonna make like a few of these. So I do need the shit.
Wooden board, soil, and animal feces. How do I make a wooden board? Wood? To make hard wood. How do I
make a wooden board? From civil cutter. Civil cutter? What the fuck is civil cutter?
I can't just craft it? It's in the handbook. It's the- oh, it's the workbench. Oh, well, I'm kind of
screwed here. I still don't have any bars. All right, well, I'm going back to the mine. I need to
get some more stuff anyways. You can cancel it and craft something else. Um, I'll get materials.
Let's go back into the, uh, into the mine, which the mine is like right over here. It's like right
next to me. Yeah, we'll go back in here. I already paid for this, right? Yeah, I got it for the week.
I got it for the week. Put your camera in the top right. What are you doing in here?
Hello! Oh, yeah, I'm blocking some stuff. You're right. All right, what are you, uh, what are you
doing down here? It's a huge treasure chest. I hope to get lucky today and find some special relics.
Wait, people just come in here? This is a tourist here. No, get out of here. This is- I- this is- no,
I'm not supposed to be here. All right, where was I before? I was over this way, right? I have plenty
of stamina. Does it remember what I did? No, pick a new spot. I don't want to be away from all these
people. All right, I'm going this way. Maybe I should go up. I'm gonna go up. Whoa! What is this?
There's a new- I just found this. All right, this is cool. All right, now over here.
They're in- all right, there's one over that way. Secret tunnel. Yeah, let's go.
Your face is blocking some stuff? No, it's not. Not anymore. Termo, you should- I'm not doing any
of that. All right, what's this? Something good. I hope. What is it? It's a jewel. Just one data- is
it eyeglass? What a piece of shit. Oh, hold on. We're going this way. I have so much. I need to
make like 10 of those things. Those smelters. All right, it's a- old parts, data disk, and power
stone. All right, I got the old parts. I now need to figure out what to get the- the wooden
planks, whatever it is. I still got time. This is what I'm doing today, so I'm just gonna go
play Power Stone. I already did, and I beat the game, and it was a fucking breeze.
Why don't they remake that game? Honest to God. Did- that's one of the coolest IPs that Capcom has.
Is there a sofa down here? What? This is the couch down here. All right.
They are? I would love to see a Power Stone remake, or even a remaster.
New relic, old thermos piece. Cool. Anything else I can do before? Oh, over here.
I definitely need to make it like three or four of those smelters, at least.
How much- uh, I got enough. Another data disk. When are we gonna start killing stuff?
Uh, probably fairly soon, I would imagine. Strange lenses. Oh, I have both eyeglass pieces.
Can I make glasses? That'd be actually kind of cool. Uh, I'm gonna keep going this way.
I need more soil. Have I ever seen a UFO? No. Although, sometimes, you know, when you hear a
plane go over at night, everybody kind of all- everybody's the same thing. You just kind of go,
oh, it's just a plane. Thank god. It's not aliens. Horse piece. Well, you never hear a plane go over
and it sounds different or a little closer than normal, or a helicopter or something,
and you just sit there and you go, what was that? Holy sh- okay, never mind. Come on. More parts.
All right, I think I gotta get out of here now. I'll go up. Don't ever dig straight up, but whatever.
It's a different game. There's no lava.
Uh, monument model piece two. That means there's a monument model piece one.
All right, this is the last one and I'm done. I promise. I still have- I have a lot of stamina.
I'm fine. Ooh, copper. And a small engine. This- it's right here. I gotta get my money's worth.
I paid 80 dollars to come in here. Good. Any more? This, a few more. I can get them.
You paid 80- oh no, I didn't- the game wasn't 80 dollars. Ooh, horse piece. Do I have the whole
horse? I'm still okay on stamina. Weird glass jar. 31. All right, 10 more swings and I'm out of here.
What's that? This is- this is a secret one over here. All right, I don't care. I'm getting it.
I don't care if I die down here. It's a purple. I need to go down here.
Fif- come on, 15. What the fuck? What is this? I only have seven more swings. What is down here?
Shit. Do I- can I drink anything? Abandoned room? What? I have four stamina. Can I eat anything?
Oh, come on. This just got way cooler. Fuck. I have four stamina. I'm gonna die. I gotta leave.
How do I get out? Quickly. Eat the sand? I can't eat sand, guys. Will this stay here? I gotta get
out. Okay, open the map then press- okay, I gotta get out of here. I gotta mark what this is. It's
right here. Okay, get out. You can't eat sand. I have one stamina point. Shit, I wanna go down
there. That was cool. That was so cool. All right, I gotta go to bed. Where am I right now? All
right, so just bang a right and go straight. That was cool. What's going on? Happy? Can I, like,
drink something? Happy apartments? No, I don't care. I gotta get out of here. I have to get out
of here. There's a chest right there. All right. All right, get me out. Get me out of the town.
I have one stamina point left. Get me out of here. There it is. All right, go. Go, go, go, go, go,
go, go. Back home. Sleep. I don't think you lose stamina unless you do anything. So, I'm just- you
don't just lose it over time. That's good. Okay, I'm going back down there. This game's pretty sick.
All right, I'm going back down. Let me store some of this shit. Oh, I have the new sofa. That's
right. Let me put the sofa down. Sofa? It is a sofa. It's kind of beat up though. Cool. Oh, I
could invite my friends over. We could hang out on the sofa. This house sucks. Let's get in there.
What? Imagine the smell. What? Imagine the smell. There's not even a trash can in this house.
That doesn't work here. Imagine the smell. You understand that? That makes no sense.
There's just wood and a sofa on the ground. Okay, so now I need the wooden planks.
Oh shit. So, I'm assuming the bottom will show you what you can do with it. Should I hold on to some
of this stuff? I think I should, right? I need another one of these. Okay, I need another
storage unit. Wooden basket. No, where is it? Wooden storage. I'm gonna make a couple of these.
All right, I'm gonna have one of them be for raw materials, right? One of them for junk and
other one for like relics. I get it. I'm starting to get this game. Okay, let me pull up this stuff.
Okay, this is gonna... Okay, then one of the right is gonna be for raw, but just materials.
Copper, stone, you know, grinding stones, soil, stone. Yeah, whatever, right? Poop. And then the
second one's gonna be for relics. Yeah, I think so. Okay, so this is gonna be just stuff that I find
in the dungeon. Okay, bring them to the research facility. I will eventually... I want to go back
down there. And this is gonna be for planting an organic material. Okay, good. Sort. Hey, there we
go. I don't even really need this, but I'm just gonna put it away. All right, so now I need to
build some stuff. No, I'm going back. I'm going back into that thing. Yep, let's go.
Minecraft Andy. Oh, wait, I can make a sword. That's a good idea. That's right. That's true.
What does it take to make a sword? I think it's three copper bars. Practice sword? Spiked practice
sword? No. Bronze pickaxe? How do I make a copper sword? Upgrade the work table at A&G construction.
Okay, so I have to go upgrade the table at A&G construction. All right, I can do that, too.
Bring food this time, too. I'm just one track mind Andy. I'm going in. I don't need to. No,
yeah, I'm just going in. Fuck it. I'm one track Andy. I already bought this place for a week.
You have skill points? You're gonna die to the slugs. I'm not gonna die to the slugs. I'm gonna
dodge roll. Okay, so that's where I want to go. Who dug this? Where's, where is it? Where's my um,
there it is. Okay, so what is in this? What's down here? Oh, I dug like a real weirdo.
Weird. What did I do? Why did I do it like this? This is the wrong hole. Is it? It's up? What did
I, where was this? I'm, it's marked on the map. How come I can't see with the radar? Yeah, it was
the purple one, but it's not on the map anymore. You were going the right way. No, yeah, okay,
let's sit here. All right, here we go. Let's do it. So should I fight this stuff? All right, what's
dodge? L1. What's on me? Is it poison? I don't know what that is. How come there's no sound effects?
All right, we're good. Wait, I could take this, all this furniture? Ow! Is this, I'm at range,
right? It can't hit me. I'm getting a ton of experience. Wait, wait, wait, wait, I gotta
level up. I have to level up. Should I have more points in gathering or fighting? What should I do?
More experience? That's a good one, I think. Yeah, 10% more EXP gained. And okay, I got a lot of this
other stuff. Just stay at range and I'll be fine. Please put the gloves on. I stored the gloves.
This is Cheshire Trest over here. Cheshire Trest, there it is. Silver. What about all this stuff?
Can I pick, can I take any of this? What is this? Cool, two discs. Uh-oh, small silicon chip. That
was what was in here. This is cool though. You just find random little dungeons. I do the sound effects.
I think that's all it's in here. Is there anything else I can do? This is cool though.
Stop blinking out of existence. Dude, you just gotta stop doing those bong hits. The dungeons
get bigger. I feel like this game's really fun. I would imagine it's probably really fun. That's
cool. There's just random dungeons you can find. So now that I've done this already, should I just
kind of move on from it? I mean, I'm already here. Might as well keep looking. Why are you crying?
Because! There are two in this cave? Interesting. For those of you that are trickling in, yeah,
I might have COVID. It's a very high possibility. But I'm still feeling fine. I'm still not feeling
okay to stream. So that's why I'm here and I just wanted to play something chill and easy.
Just hang out. Okay, let's take a little look. I don't see anything else over here. I'm just
going to keep going this way. Should I just pick a direction and just go?
There's no way the base... No, the baseball stream has moved a month. Don't worry.
You should go down. Okay. Whoa, this is a new floor. I can't break this. Can I? Am I doing...
Am I damaging this? Dude, I'm just getting experience for hitting this. Look at how much
experience points I'm getting for this. I'm getting 150 EXP a swing. Oh, it's like that with
everything. Never mind. I was already at that one. I'll get this one. Is this not the sofa? No.
Rusty pipe. I need a better pickaxe. How many... Can I just sell these? I don't want four pink
couches. Let's go up here. It's similar to... This is kind of like an Animal Crossing and
Stardew Valley combined. That's what it feels like. I feel like there's a lot to do so far.
It's cute. I like it. What's that? A small clock. I haven't even done any of the farming yet.
Oh, horse piece. I think I have the whole horse. Can I combine it?
I'm gonna bring this up to the research center. All right. They ain't nothing. That's it. Wait.
Yes, there is. All right. I'll get two more things and I'm gonna go up.
It is a good game. Yeah, it feels like it's fun.
But I'll tell you, we're gonna have... It's gonna be an intense stream on Tuesday. I thought it was an old
turkey. I'm gonna be playing multi-versus and you bet your ass that I'm ready to play that one.
Also, that's gonna be sponsored too, so that's fucking awesome. I'm so ready to play that game.
There's gonna be a perfect world there. I've been waiting for that to come back out.
So, you better be ready. Tuesday is gonna be a gamer session. It's gonna be a true gaming session.
And you know what? I'll be honest. I feel like I was pretty good at that game. I feel like I was
doing pretty well. I think I only lost like two, three rounds. I think I did really well.
I think that's my game. I was doing good. I really was. Genuinely. I wonder if there...
Is there any new characters? I wonder if they're gonna announce any characters or anything.
I don't know. I don't want another couch. I've got five couches. Yeah, that game does something
that I'm so happy that they're doing. And like, if you need me to pull up a resource for this,
I will. I talked about it before, and I'm gonna talk about it again right now before we play it
again. Fighting games like that, that have tons of moves and combos and shit on the screen. The new
Smash Brothers games, the last two new Smash Brothers games, it's just every single swing
is this explosion of smoke and particle effects. And it's like hard to even see what the fuck's
going on. Every time I've tried to play Smash Brothers, it's just like I'll do like a punch
to somebody. And it's just this purple fucking smoke explosion. And it's just annoying to look
at. It's hard to even see. I don't mind particle effects, but man, the new Smash Brothers game
dialed it up to a million. Those are boomer words. No, they really aren't. I don't think they really
are. Does anybody agree with me on this? I feel like a lot of you do. There's a lot of visual
information. It's just too much. Does every single move in Smash Brothers have to create big, huge,
explosive purple smoke? That's my question. Every single move, does every move have to have big,
purple, explosive smoke? Every single move in the game. I'm about to fucking educate a lot of people
here. Let's take a look. I want to go over this because this is important. Is it just like a
match with no game, no commentary? Not no gameplay, no commentary. Hold on. Smash Brothers,
I'm looking at YouTube. Smash Brothers, no gameplay, no commentary. So what the fuck are
you talking about? It would just be the menu? No gameplay. I gotta find one. All right, here we go.
This is Ultimate, right? We're gonna go over this because I can be a fucking boomer with this. That's
fine. But it makes it hard to play the game for me. It just kind of annoys me. Make sure it's at HD.
All right, so let's go frame by frame here. This is just a random YouTube video of Smash Brothers
Ultimate gameplay. Okay, so let's take a look. Look, okay, somebody just swung and look, look
what's going on over here. Do you see that? Like, why does this have to happen every time somebody
gets hit? Look at that. Everybody has to have like all the smoke flying across them. How do I do,
how do we do each frame? Frame by frame. It's, what is it, forward? Is it, what is it, like K
or something? How do I do a frame? Comma and period. That didn't work. Why is that not working
either? Hold on. Ready? It's just, it's too, it's too much. And they started doing this and it's
for the one for the Wii U. Every move has to have like explosive smoke and like just particle effects
to take up the both of the whole, both two characters. Listen, somebody gets just punched
once. It's so much visual data. And I understand like some of it needs to exist, but if you compare
it, let me compare that to multiverses. There's not this much. Change the playback speed.
All right. Do you see the smoke? True, true, true. Some, a lot of you disagree with me.
I know a lot of you don't agree with this, but like this right here, I don't even know who did
a move to somebody. Like all these like boom, boom, boom, flare, flare, flare, flare. And then all
this other shit like the blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, sway, sway, sway, sway, swing. Old man
yelling at clouds. Like what happened here? It's okay. Whatever. That's okay. Do a poll.
No, I think a lot of people are going to disagree with me because they like Nintendo,
right? Like I have to automatically be wrong by with a lot of people because it's a Nintendo
game. Like I don't even know who did a move. Hey, by the way, I love the Smash Brothers franchise.
Do you like bright colors and smoke? Do you like bright colors and smoke? I'm actually very,
please say honestly, speak honestly. Don't just, a streamer just told you something. Don't do it.
I want to know what you really feel. How do you really feel about that? How do you feel about
that? How do you truly feel about that? It's messy. I think it is. What's the I don't care
option? Yeah, you can do the I don't. Wait, what? Oh, I gotta leave. You need effects for info. Yeah,
you need effects for info, but they, it's just they ever since they, I don't know what game it
was. It was maybe brawl or after brawl. I don't remember it being that crazy where you would do
a move and like the whole screen would flash with like five different colors. I actually have to
get at her. You're just older. No, I'm definitely not. What do they, what do they say? You can't
turn them off. No. What's the consensus on this? I want to see how out of touch I am with with
reality here. The new Mario Kart games have this problem too. What happened? I fell over. Oh,
all right, whatever. 60. All right. So that's not, I don't think that's unanimous though.
That's kind of a majority. That's a majority, but not by very much. That's a kind of,
do I lose money from falling asleep? Hardly. Important announcement tonight. Oh, okay.
19 o'clock. I'll be there. 57 is pretty big. And again, don't get me wrong. I played,
all right, old parts. I played the new Smash game and I thought it was good. I just
just can't get over it. I can't get over this. This new, maybe I am an old guy, but I'll tell you
this new wave of, there has to be seven different colors exploding on the screen whenever you do
anything. This is a new thing in the last like five, 10 years. Call me an old fuck. Go for it.
Go ahead. Tell me. God, I'm an old man. That's fine. All right. I got it. So I have a grinder now.
Where should I put it? But the, okay, the whole, the people are going, wow, what's,
who is he talking to? Who is he talking to? The whole reason why I went off on that
is because multiverses does not have all that crazy shit all over the screen every time you
do anything. It's there, but it's not there to an extreme extent like it is in the new Smash game.
And that's why I was like, well, I actually kind of want to play this. Yeah. Is it petty and weird?
Sure. But that's why I like the game a little more. I'm just telling you the way that I feel.
You can think I'm a weirdo. That's fine. That's fine. You can call me weird. Who is he talking
to? See? Somebody said it. Jeremy, the sponsor isn't today. I'm just, I said this a month ago
when I played it. All right. So now I have the grinder. Now I can do, okay, here we go.
Copper blades. Any power here? All right. I need to make three copper blades. So I need some more
of these. Okay. Or bar. Let's refuel. Okay. Old fuck Andy. All right. Let me go to the research
center. I have a lot of stuff that I could probably bring over there. They're going to
add that shit after release. No, they're not. Why would they? I've probably pissed off a lot
of people, but what do you want me to say? I can't like pretend like I can, I can get over it.
All right. Let me put the sofas in the house. They're going to add effects. Can you imagine
they just added a bunch of effects after the release of the game? That'd be so stupid.
These two I have. I think I'm selling these. I don't think I'm, I, you know what I mean? I'm
whatever. I'm getting out of here. You're barely barely into your thirties, but you have takes
from a 60 year old. What? That's come on. Okay. So now I need to make what I need to like a sword,
right? Uh, okay. I gotta go to A and G construction and the research place. Let me pull out all the
things that I can bring to the research center. No. Okay. Here we go. Bring all the relics. Okay.
All right. I got a shitload of relics. Let's go. Go to the research center.
Is the research center in town here? There it is. Okay. Research center. We'll get bad booger
noises. I'm all right. Dermot hates colors because you only remember when things are black and white.
No, I know. There's a bunch of people right now that are watching the stream and they are going,
I get you, man. I get it. Hey, me, me and my boys said the same thing. Who do I turn this into?
Uh, oh, it's up here. No, this is not a zoomer versus boomer thing. Hey, discovered something
new. I got a lot of shit for you to look at these strange lenses in the ruins. Do you know what they
are? Oh, this is pretty neat. They're glasses with a colorful tint. These aren't regular lenses though.
That's for sure. Hey, director, come check this out. What do we have here? Interesting. I'm going
to take a look. You can come back tomorrow. I have a lot of other stuff. Hold on. I'm just going to
go to the fucking register training dummy weapon rack. Ooh, chipset. Wait, can I, uh, wait, recover?
Oh shit. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need one. I need an old thermos piece too.
I'm still missing galloping horse pieces. Come on. Really? I don't, I can't make any of these stupid
things. A million, not in a million. I'm only 500 followers away from a million followers.
Is it going to happen? Is it going to happen today? 500 followers away. Oh my God. Only 500
followers away to a million. That's crazy though. Actually crazy. I'm Chiwa, the smallest of the
Hulu brothers. There's seven of us. So, uh, how many people unfollowed me from the Nintendo rant
though? Uh, we said we still on pace for today. Fishing rod. You're the new builder, right? I'm
Chiwa. I live to fish, but a big one broke my fishing rod yesterday. All right, you want a new
fishing rod? It's going to happen. Just, okay, it's like boiling water. I don't want to look at it or
it won't happen. Flower shop. What was I? Okay, I need to build a bridge, make copper blades, and
wait a day. Let me do the blades part. Yeah, let me do the blades. I can turn that in. Bake a cake
to celebrate. Do a baking a cake stream. Do I bake a cake for a million? That's kind of no.
Refresh, it's there. I don't see it. Okay, copper blades. I need copper bars. Um, I need to make
another one of these. I need to make like two more of those. Furnace. Okay, I want to make a stone
furnace. I need ten wood. I have to get into my inventory. Right, all right, all right, all right.
Move all this crap out of the way. Okay, I need the wood. I'm out of wood. I gotta go
get some trees cut down. Stone stool, wood. I only have eight. All right, I need a stone stool.
I need three, two more stone stools. I can make 28 of these. I'll make three. I'll make four. Yeah,
okay. Stone stool. Did I do it? No, I didn't. I'm not, did I do it? That's not there.
Is it actually there? Refresh. No, it's 9956. It's not there yet. I will say that's actually
kind of a big deal though because I'll explain why. If I hit it today, I need,
I just gotta go cut trees down. I'll give a speech. Don't worry. You'll get a big speech. I promise.
Close enough. No, it's got, I have to actually hit it. All right, wood.
No, come on, come on, come on, come on. I'm keeping an eye on it. Don't worry. Stone stool.
And what's the last part? All right, done. Pick that up. Again, make another one. Pick it up.
Do it again. Because I'm not going to wait the whole day to, I want to be able to grind this out,
right? All right, now I'm placing, I gotta, I gotta move some of this shit around. This is not a bad
spot. Let me move this. This can go, the grinder can go right over here and then these are going
to go over here. I've got three more of these. One, two, three. One, two, three. Okay, I've got
my line now. So now I've got to, I need a bunch more wood. Just keep getting wood. This is a
grind day. Is this technically a tree? Fibers. Okay, fiber is good. Give more points. Vape on
stream for a million. No, I could probably kill the, yeah, let's kill some of these things.
I was afraid of them before. Let's see if I can kill them. I kind of feel bad. I got animal bones
and worn fur. I kind of feel bad. All right, I got a, how many copper, how many copper do I have?
I need a little bit more wood because I'm gonna let, I'm gonna make like 50 iron
copper bars overnight. But I want, I want 100 copper bars. Oh, I missed the like important
meeting, right? No, it's going on right now, isn't it? Come on, come on, come on. I'm there,
I'm here, I'm here. I'm 30 minutes late to this meeting. Come on. Yes, I made it.
I don't know what a pan bad infestation is like. Sometimes I wish we had a tank. In other news,
we've decided to proceed with the building of a bridge to Amber Island. A builder has already
been picked for this project. Also, we are in preparations for the construction of the DD
transportation system. We're securing the funding over the coming weeks and pick a builder soon.
DD. DD. DD.
I thought people liked cartoons in this chat. What happened? Where did you guys come from?
I thought you guys liked cartoons. Aren't you guys cartoon enjoyers?
Please stop doing the Kubrick stare. DD. That's from Dexter's lab. What? In Dexter's lab.
I thought you guys liked cartoons. Now I finally get to fish there. He's asking for money again.
Finally, we have a new builder in town this week who lives in the old workshop
outside the city gate. What are you doing? Let's all give a warm welcome.
By the way, we're all being very, very nice and cordial to him because he's holding an axe at the
meeting. You should get to know some of the people. Yeah, everyone be nice. He's got an axe in his
hand and he has an I'll kill you mustache. What's his name again? Jerry. There he is.
All right. I got to make one more copper blade, but I do have to meet people.
I don't want to meet everybody. You just inherited that workshop outside of town, right?
Okay. Nice to meet you. Oh, hi. A new builder. Nice to see young folks moving in. If you need
refreshments, I'm your man. Okay. Plus 10 relationship status.
Move out of the way. Move out of the way. Get out of the way. Yeah. Don't care. Move.
How much I get? I get 67 bucks. Come on. Hello. Oh, what? Oh, did I actually have to time it?
Do I actually have to time it? Plus I'm doing $50. That's worth something. It was 50 gold. It's not
like it was 5000. I'm about to make all that money with all my fucking copper by Emporium.
Just wait. Do I have to meet all these people? No, I don't. I don't care. I'm waiting today.
I'm making the copper blades and making my copper shit. I have a lot of copper.
Get away from my house. Get away from my house. Where are you? I'm Gus. I'd love to stop and chat
cake and all that like stump. I can't. We're gonna get timed out here. He took a dollar from me.
Okay, whatever. I don't care. I do need to do this though. So this has got this is going anywhere.
Where's my copper? I have a shitload of copper somewhere. Where is it? Where is it? Don't I have
a bunch of copper? I thought I had like 100. There we go. Alright, so this one we're gonna get going.
Refuel that up. Get that moving. Get this one moving. Okay, get this one going. Alright,
I'm out of copper. Oh, it's that's all right. Sorry. I got three going. Not a million. Stop
saying it. Can I actually sell these though? Where did I get this? I can sell these for $50 each.
Give me all of them. I don't want any of these. I don't want any of these. I'll keep one. Sell
the bed. I'm not telling the bed. I'm not going to sleep on that just random pink sofa. Okay,
talk with Merlin. Make another copper blade. There we go. Look at this fucking delicious
Hershey's chocolate bar. Okay, now I gotta make a copper blade. Okay, I still have fuel.
Just make one more. Turn this in. Come on, hurry up. I need to make some new weapons. Enhanced
practice sword. I mean, I feel like I should just I could probably I could make one of these.
Wooden hardwood. I think that's easy, right? Hershey's is disgusting. I mean, it's okay.
Cadbury's better. I mean, that's that's obvious. Yeah, you know, the old Wonka bars were the best
before they went out of business. Okay, so now I'm gonna go talk to that guy. I don't care.
Five wooden boards. Yeah, sure. Alright, where's this guy? We're gonna go here. Maybe I'll make
some money. I'm gonna sell these couches too. What happened to Wonka? They went out of business.
They sold off all their IP. The only thing that still exists from Wonka is nerds. Whoever they
whatever company bought them, whoever owns nerds. Purchased the company, liquidated everything and
then kept nerds around. Okay. What'd I get? All right, that's a hundred.
That's 200 bucks. I just made 200 plus dollars. That's perfect. All right, cool.
Talk with Merlin. Where's Merlin? What is this for? Oh, right. Where's Merlin? At the research
center, right? Oh, cool. Two points. Harvesting activities. Hmm. Or dodge rolls are better.
I think I'm going to experience. Okay. I've got a lot of random shit going on here.
Okay, let's go. Go turn 200 into 10k. I'm not going to go slot machine.
No. Okay, let's go turn this in. I'll talk to you guys after I get out. Gambling now. No.
I took a look at the lenses you brought. I thought they were guidance lenses or focus
lenses used in an ancient AI. Ancient AI? They're just eyeglasses. Wonka was just Nestle, man. You
were duped. But the Wonka bars were good. Different how? These glasses alter the spectrum of light
passing through. I think they were used to fix color blinds. Original Wonka chocolate bars.
They were delicious. Okay. It's not something we can easily make today. That's for sure.
Well, they're useless to me, so you can have them back. What's a good donut? I haven't had a good
donut in a long time. You can take the glasses to him. What's a good donut? What's your guys'
favorite donut? Chocolate glazed. Dunkin' Donuts used to do this thing, and I think they still do,
but I haven't had one in a long time. They used to do the cream-filled ones. I was such a disgusting
kid. There was a chocolate cream. It wasn't frosting, though. It was a mousse, almost.
It was a Dunkin' Donuts chocolate cream-filled donut, and it was this weird in-between of frosting
and mousse. I think they still have them, but holy shit. No, not a Boston cream. I'm not a big fan
of those. Chocolate cream-filled. And I used to, seriously, I would just take it and put my mouth
on the end where the hole was, because it was like a little dollop was on the end. It was a donut,
fat kind of squishy donut, and inside was a bunch of chocolate cream. And I used to sit there and
just like... I would suck it up, and then I would just bite into the donut where the filling was,
and just drain it. I was like a vampire to this donut. I also, I was one of those kids that only
ate the frosting part of the cupcakes. I was like, why would I eat the other part? It was
fucking worthless to me. Why would I eat that part? Guys, the bottom of the cupcake may as well have
been made out of wood. It was part of the thing that held the cupcake. Okay, so can I turn this
stuff in, though? No, I don't have enough. So what did that do for me? Give the glasses to somebody.
I didn't pay any attention to that. Who do I need to give these glasses to? You wiped the frosting
off. I was one of those kids that wiped the frosting off. You did? Really? So you like just
the kind of the cake? The donut? I mean the cupcake cake. Interesting. See, I hated the cake part. I
still do. Okay, Sanwa. Where's Sanwa? I gotta go here, too. All right, let me go here first.
Both of you are weird for that. I don't think so. Grown man only eats icing.
Well, not anymore. I'm talking about when I was like five.
Ooh, that makes it worse. You should eat icing on stream. That explains your flabby skin. Yeah?
Where's that again? Excuse me, where's that again? Excuse me, you say I got flabby neck skin?
Excuse me, what are you talking about? This is the most elastic fucking skin you've ever seen.
That kind of hurt. All right, what do I have to do? Who's in here? There's nobody in here. You
wear a rubber mask. Oh, this is where I want to go. Okay, now what is this? Oh, okay. I need wooden
boards, 2,000 bucks, and old parts and I can make a lot of new shit. I can't do any of this really
yet. I can upgrade the house. $10,000 and I can get married. Okay, this game's cool. This is cool.
I can't promise I'm going to play the hell out of this game, but it's definitely a fun
game to check out. Now I want a donut. I'll make my own donuts.
Now, I don't know what I was thinking about this the other day, but did I guys ever tell you
that story when I was cooking bacon with no clothes on and the oil was just... Did I ever
tell this to you before? Yeah, no, I definitely have. Here we go. Let me get... Here is your
glasses. Tell it again. I don't... Question marks. All right, so Holly and I were making breakfast
one time and I was like, let's do a whole spread. We're going to do eggs, bacon,
sausage, you know, like tomatoes and shit, right? We just, let's do everything.
And I was in charge of the bacon, right? I'll take care of the bacon. That's what I'll do.
And now I'm on the stovetop. And I don't know why I was doing this. I have no answer for you.
I was too lazy to put a shirt on. So I was just shirtless standing there cooking bacon in the pan
and just the eggs were over here. There was... She was doing something over on the other side.
Like we were preparing stuff and I was just sitting there cooking the bacon and it was
just splashing oil, just hitting me in the chest. I just kept on going, oh, oh, oh,
this is fucking burning me. I was just getting splashed with oil and I didn't even care.
I didn't even care. I didn't move. It was just kind of hurting me. And Holly's just like,
what are you doing? What are you doing? And I'm just like, I'm fine. I'm fine. It's not a big deal
because I just, okay, I got to go put a shirt on now. No, I'm just, whatever. I'm just going to let
it happen. It didn't hurt that much, right? You're a Sims NPC. I just remember hearing like the pop,
pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop. It was just like, I had these little red dot marks all over my chest.
But Holly laughs. She's like, I keep remembering. You're just sitting there like shaking it with
like pajama pants on, like tired. It was early in the morning. Just like, ah, it must've been so
fucking crazy looking. And this wasn't 10 seconds. This was probably five straight minutes. I had
been doing it for like at least a few minutes, right? You're a Skyrim NPC. Source engine NPC
standing in fire. But I didn't care enough. Look, the pain threshold that I had to, all right, so
put on a shirt so you don't get splashed with bacon oil and it hurts. It didn't cross that
certain pain threshold. It was just enough where it was like, I don't care. If it was any higher,
I would have put on, I would have put one on. We have aprons. Yeah, but the apron wouldn't even
matter. Okay, so here's why the apron doesn't matter. If I had an apron on, aprons are from
like here down. All this is still skin and flesh, all here. It's still, it was like the neck.
What kind of apron? Aprons are like overalls. You're wearing it wrong? There's only one way
an apron goes on and it doesn't cover your arms, bare arms, bare neck and clavicle area.
I wasn't gonna go put a sweater on. Skill issue. So wear a shirt. But I would have to go get it. I
didn't want to go get it. That was a lot of experience. 500 bucks too. Holy smokes. Wait,
you make bread? That's what my place is called. Okay, has he given the speech yet? I haven't hit
a million followers yet. I'm not gonna go gamble it. Did I have 100 copper ore? This is not doing
anything for me. Should I go buy some clothes? Oh yeah, let's do it. Okay, work clothes.
This is too much money. Okay, I did all those missions. I have some money now. Let's go back.
You have a bread place. Take off the mask. All right, I need to build the bridge. Let's go back
home and assess what I need to build the bridge. I have to build the bridge. Okay, copper, hard wood
and copper pipe. I need 20. Where do I get hardwood from? Do I have to make it? I think I
have to make it. Hardwood. How do I make hardwood? How do I make hardwood? You have to upgrade your
axe. Do I? I need a civil cutter. Okay. Stone, brick, copper, blade. All right. I have, I can
look at these chocolates. Let's make some more. Let's make like, I don't know, three copper blades.
And then what else is this? Stone, brick. How do I make a fucking stone brick? Stone, brick. What the
fuck? How do I make a stone brick? Tin ore. How do I make a stone brick? It's in the furnace. Stone,
brick. Ah, there it is. All right, dude. How many do I need? Yeah, I'll make this over here.
My nose. It's like a bug in my nose. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. Two seconds.
Hey, one more second. I'm just blowing my nose. I'll be right back. I'm good. Two seconds.
Oh shit, I forgot to put up the BRB thing. It's all right.
Shit. Shit. We're fine. Everybody relax. I'm fine. Yeah, I just had to blow my nose really quickly.
It felt like there were bugs in my nose, but that's not what it was.
I just had to go blow my nose. It's like heavy. Snorting bugs in the bathroom. It sounds like,
it's like a rock band title for an album or something. Yeah, and here from their new album,
Pain, is snorting bugs in the bathroom. Copper blade and stone brick. Did I get it?
I only made two of these? What are you, out of your mind? I need way more than that. Oh, I need
wood. I don't have any wood, do I? Gotta go cut down some more trees. Let's go. I feel like I'm
depleting the forest over here. There's some bugs hanging out of your nose. That's all right. No,
I need 200 followers. This is crazy. I actually think I'm going to hit it today. It's going to
happen today. Oh, I got to think of something to say. Actually, I know what to say. I know what
to say. I've been practicing in the mirror for months. I've been practicing this speech in the
mirror for three months. I know it. I wrote it down too. I have a whole script. It's about seven
or eight pages long. It's not going to take long. This is a quick speech talking about the channel
and everything. It's probably be about 30 to 40 minutes in total length. It's going to be a full
state of the union. I hope I don't get emotional. I might get emotional. I might start crying.
I'm going to cry. I've got to be careful here. I want enough wood where I never have to cut a
tree down again. That's what I want. How much wood? I'm going to cut down every single tree that I
physically can around my residence. This might not be the game for you, dude. Who is this game for,
then? It's a game where you run around and chop trees down and do errands and stuff. Who is this
before, then? It's just a fun, chill game. Dude, this ain't for you. What is for me?
What do you guys think is a game for me? If you're like, that's a game for you.
Halo 2, please. Among Us. Kingdom Hearts. Undertale? Undertale was a game for me. You're
right. That was great. I've cut down every single tree that's out in my backyard, so
there are no more trees left. Oh, that's okay. All right. I know, I know, I know, I know. What
do I need? Wood, copper blades. I need to turn this wood into... Oh, I can make a practice sword.
Yeah. I finally have a weapon. Took me long enough. Let me get rid of some of this bullshit.
Look at all this crap. Look at all this junk. Oh, you want four sofas in your backpack? Sure.
God, give me a break. All right. Now, what do I need to do? That's actually pretty cool.
All right, cool. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
There they are. When are you gonna play smite again? I don't know. Okay, now I need stone
bricks maybe a few more of these I need that wood feel depleted go for it stone
brick let's make a shitload it's gonna take a little bit whatever bricks yep I
need and then I can finally build the bridge and sit down for like an hour
check the follower count nine nine eight three are you gonna weld again what have
I ever welded that's still gone right five hours oh that's actually not that
long so I finally have a sword that means I can go fight stuff oh I need
copper pipes too I need like three copper pipes to make the bridge I love
this it's so funny it says one million it doesn't say for me you need two
bridge heads so four pipes oh shit okay I'll have one that'll take a little bit
this will take a little bit so this is all gonna take a little bit so I can go
um should I go dig what else do I need for the bridge three all right it's
three copper pipe wait a minute oh you're right okay so it's two two head one
body so I need six copper pipes and then I need bronze I need tin and copper
which I have a lot of I think okay all right I should get it soon I do need
more copper pipes there we go I need more brick so we're gonna we're gonna
change these after these are done wait I can do it on this one max 10 good
refuel all right and I'm gonna come back tomorrow this will be ready what can I
I gotta plant this stuff what do I need to I need that box what the hell was it
what was it to make the small plant box wooden board from the cutter okay so
I'm not quite there yet I'll do it all tomorrow I'm just going to bed fuck it
when are you gonna eat the Smash Brothers ultimate donut from Dunkin
Donuts are you an AI that was trained on the last hour of this stream there we go
I'll give me all those bricks okay tada very cool now I can make the hardwood
kind of running out of space I gotta cut this down okay now hardwood plank
wooden board what do I need I need wooden boards ten of them okay all right
got this let's make the bridge let's go okay copper pipe then copper pipe okay
hardwood planks and copper pipes I got it should I just go fight some shit let
me put some stuff away and go on an adventure okay I got a full inventory I
got full health I got my sword I'm ready that's gonna take a little while it'll
take till tomorrow so now let's I'm just gonna go somewhere just fight something
what's up what's on the map fishing spot fishing spot should I go to the other
ruins vendor ruins too yeah let's check this out I got money I can buy it
capture your follower count and put it on stream um I think it's gonna be too
late to do that by the time I do that I only there's only a hundred only a
hundred followers before it hey let's go give me over a million do a live countdown
I mean hold on can I do a live countdown I know I don't do that though yeah
whatever do it hold on I do a live count I was here I was here I think it's
happening right now like hold on can I like pop this out I don't think I can
pop this out it's 999 905 wait can I capture it here I can't wait wait wait
wait wait wait oh I think I can do it I can do it I think hold on no wait wait
don't do it yet don't do it it has to be on camera don't do it yet don't do it
yet hold on it's gonna be on camera this was that no no no stop stop stop stop
stop oh wait don't wait no you're unfollowing don't unfollow hold on oh
oh dude here it comes stop what the fuck no go the other way you're not gonna do
it to me like this are you we'll find out what the fuck holy shit oh my god
alright but wait you're gonna screw up my metrics you're gonna mess up my
metrics don't all of you unfollow at the same time you're gonna actually kill
my metrics my analytics are gonna be dogshit at the end of this they're gonna
you're gonna kill my analytics I'm going to the mines sell sell sell how
much is this one to go in under inspection what get rid of the count you
guys all told me to put the count on and now everyone's freaking out saying
remove the count cuz everyone's gonna unsubscribe don't do that I want to talk
to the horse level 20 guys leave what do you want hello good to see you I've got
a problem here you see recently folks have been buying up a lot of umbrellas
okay all right see you trims I can do it oh oh they're fighting back come on no
no no no no no it needs to happen right when the beat drops by the way why am I
doing this on my phone I could do the work why would it what am I doing
why would I do this on the telephone that's fucking stupid all right here we
go I'm gonna do this on the phone I have a computer in front of me come on let's
go let's hit it no I'm gonna turn this like smooth jazz down this is it here
comes a million we like to party we like we like to party we like to party come
on it's good you have to do it at the beat drop I'm never doing this again
right looks like a smaller number has anyone ever actually got to that part
of the song I feel like it everyone always stops at 45 seconds hey it's a
million followers all right cool cool cool that's cool all right well I know I
gotta tell you my spy gonna give my speech now stop this hey come on it's a
big deal all right let me give you my speech here's my speech this is a big
deal to me because my old YouTube channel right just German 985 second
German Twitter doesn't matter I've never been to a million followers across any
platform even the old YouTube channel even to German 985 did not have a
million subscribers once I got to about five or six hundred thousand I stopped
doing YouTube videos right moved over here the second channel doesn't have a
million this is the first place where I've ever had a million followers so
that's really that's crazy I know that there's a lot of other people that have
way more than a million followers but whatever it's still that's really cool
the first time I've ever seen it I'm gonna take this moment and I'm gonna
fall asleep on the ground where's my house but yeah I I've never stuck around
in a place long enough to make enough videos or streams or whatever to get
past a million that's that's a lot of people who's this why there's snake
berries ooh that looks nice did I ever think I was gonna get to a
million followers I don't know not really but it's been a very very long
time but I've I switched I was youtuber then I was a streamer and then I did
YouTube a second channel and I don't really tweet that much I think I have
like I say only have but when I'm when you're using the million follower kind
of mark here I have like 300,000 followers that's a lot of followers but
just not even close so I just kept kind of switching but it means a lot I'm
happy that people think this channel is cool I hope you continue to do so there's
a handful of fun things I think that are really interesting that we're gonna do
in the future here so thanks thanks for sticking around some of you guys have
been here for ten years some of you guys have been here for two months I hope I
can continue to do the things you like that's what I'm trying to do and that's
it that's really all there is to it thanks for a million followers very cool
all right what do I need hardwood planks did I not make hardwood planks I thought
I made hardwood planks that was the point ten plus years yeah I'm honestly
shocked that I've been able to make it this far I still just kind of going and
I know it's a it's a tough business it's a tough kind of thing to do I'm shocked
that this many years later I'm still here and that people still care that's
genuinely shocking to me all the time so because I know that this is like you
know this this business right streaming youtuber kind of influencer whatever you
want to say I mean you can you can go up just as fast as you went down you can go
down just as fast as you went up so I'm glad I've been able to kind of still be
at it who's he talking to not showing emotion I mean I but think about it
right I still how did why did I use all this I need hardwood hardwood I need a
better thick axe or whatever can I upgrade this one or do I have to make
like a bronze axe or something wait I can break this no shit you should unban
everybody for ten years or for a million no I've talked about this kind of stuff
before you know how it is I'm not gonna change much everything's it's just the
same as it is I always probably been still doing what I'm doing still trying
to do things that are fun and that's it that's it that's it free ball fondler
is actually banned just wait what did that person say don't do another one of
the girls famous big-headed rants just don't do another one of your famous oh
okay so all right what am I doing now collect but I got to collect spines and I
need to get hard I need a better axe that's important how do I get a better
axe help me where do I get a better axe from do I have two thousand bucks yet I
have to go to the Home Depot and do it okay how much money I only have seven
hundred dollars what the hell I need to upgrade my axe worktable level one
upgrade two thousand bucks and 20 wooden boards you shitting me I got to
make more money all right I need another thousand dollars I have the old parts I
need ten more wooden boards happy for you thank you the cabin by the lake has a
free axe that I'm seriously thanks with back seating because I really don't want
to spend all this money cabin by the lake like down here how do I get over
here though no help hope that what you have planned is it as exciting as you
hope I think that there's some really fun things in the pipeline here baseball
is gonna be really fun there's something immediately after baseball
probably in the fall that is gonna take a lot of resources to do but I think
it's gonna be fun I think it'd be funny it's not it's not you mean over here
it's gonna be modded Skyrim that's right bro modded Skyrim all right so you
saying that there's an axe in the shed over here are you full of are you full
crap were you full of crap you said there was an axe over here all right were
are you full of hot air is this it this is just fur in here I can't believe that
person's full of hot air wait hold on there's a chest right there too by the
lake not the sea where am I oh you mean like right here hey let's go how many
woodland creatures have you consumed just one just one this one never mind
level 20 fuck it let's go for it just unlock it I'll be fine I'm gonna get
million experience with this that's it even can I eat some babies I can free
pumpkins all right this is the house by the lake I don't see an axe house by
the lake that unless you're talking about that shed up there they said cabin
okay you know what else I was thinking too what do you guys have to say about
this am I gonna go crazy here should I are we gonna am I gonna go nuts right
now you ready for this one what do you guys think for the one for 1 million
followers what do you guys think about this I'm gonna I'm gonna mention
something here let me think about it let me think about it there's nothing in
this shed let me think about this for a little bit I have an idea I've got an
idea it's something that thinking a lot of people are gonna be really happy
about especially if you've been here for over 5 to 10 years I think I think this
sounds like a fun idea no I'm not gonna do doy doy doy again that's what you
think we're gonna do for a million followers you're out of your mind there's
nothing in the shed and now it's time for bed there's not another shed on the
water right wait can I let go can I do this no I can't can I it's like oh dig
in the shed no nothing there we'll see all right I'm gonna tell you the idea
there's two different ideas say it oh why am I kicking his body oh no mr. lady
bug I can do the spine thing too I do need shit yeah I'll tell you the idea in
a couple days when I'm live on Tuesday I'll let you know but I think this could
be fun stalling stalling well I don't know if I want to do it yet and I don't
want to say I want to do something without being like yeah I want to do it
he's stalling yeah I call it call me stalling Steven I'm fine with that
because what if I say this thing that I think is interesting and then everybody
freaks out and then like a month goes by and I don't do it right cuz I'm like na
nevermind okay I gotta go to bed am I gonna make it home that's most of your
ideas well not most of them that's most of the game play video game related
ideas sometimes I just don't do them well yeah then I want to stop saying
stuff McD's I just bought a cow what I have chickens too I have a chicken and a
cow and a duck what how do I take care of these I need to put them into a shed
do I have a shed all right let's go can I put them here guys have like a cow
kind of walking around well I hate this like sassy worm you know I mean can I
put this I can't put you down can you can you go in the house shit I can't put
I can't put the cow down they're gonna be they're gonna be okay just in an
inventory right they're not dead they're alive they're fine all right let me
focus I've so my focusing problems are just seriously so bad I need an axe so
to make a better axe I need to have a better table to have a better table I
need 1500 more gold so I need to do missions that's what we're gonna do let
me open up my mission book okay that's the big one okay Emily gave you a recipe
for a small planter box plant those seeds let's do that right now I need
that small planter box okay small planter box I will take a planter box now
let's go ahead and put that planter box somewhere this is a pretty large planter
box put it right here press the right mouse button or left trigger to check
the crop status okay all right fishing day who cares hold the seeds and click
in front of the planter box is there a certain type of food I need to make
here doesn't matter they can only have one seed bag cotton and green barrel
bamboo papaya and wheat okay why are you storing poop because I need it for this
okay how many should I put here I can only put one all right so do I need to
water it prepare a present for the town and give it to the mayor I don't care so
this would be ready in check status four days I need fertilizer oh shit do I have
fertilizer oh it's a poop where's the this is fertilizer right is this not
fertilizer I don't think I have it unless this is supposed to be fertilizer
I have to process this poop into fertilizer what do you mean to put the
poop in the grinder I need to make a blender I don't know I don't know where
the what fertilizer is pigment juice oh just I thought this was a tropical
drink I thought that was an umbrella sticking out of a tropical drink I didn't
thought I didn't know that's what that was there we go fertilizer more okay
all right four days now I need to make okay so that's gonna give me some money
I'm gonna go collect the spines bro I'm ready I'm gonna sneeze I think I hope
not one of the reasons why I have so much trouble playing these games is
because I need somebody to come after me and look in the inventory and be like
I'll get rid of this I get rid of that we don't need the apples right I need I
just I collect a lot of stuff and somebody else has to come and just sort
it for me because I don't I don't know what to do with all this somebody needs
to be playing the game with me and walk around and be like okay well we're
taking that out of here because they don't need to be in there you know I
mean like I wonder what I want Heidi to do with all this I don't know to do with
everything give the mayor feces fine I'll do that joke we'll do the funny joke
where I give shit to somebody all right let me decide so much dog shit I need
another box just me I need to make another box talisman oh five defense
let's go oh it's gonna happen at some point wait I can make another one of
these yeah let's go all right what about and put here what is it what is here
cotton all right I want to put wheat here instead where's the wheat oh I hate
having so much shit I have to just throw it all the way I have to hold on to all
the artifact pieces like I'm just gonna you know what I have to do I have to
make a box that's behind the fucking house I'm gonna put this box behind the
house and put all these stupid ass artifact pieces in there just all back
here I don't even care about them you have to collect eight pieces of this
dumb thing no I'm just hiding it for myself I don't want cotton in here what
no just pull that out there we go wheat there's a stupid ass fertilizer give me
an I need to make another box right now and I've thrown everything in the trash
it's it this is literally gonna be a trash where is it
wooden storage this is a trash by the way I'm using this as a trash can so
many miscellaneous stupid fucking relic pieces just put them over here I don't
care well you're like all that no all this look at this stuff I don't want it
like an engine old thermos and hold pipe a clock I'll just forget about this for a
year I don't care weird glass engine okay sell it box in front of your house
is the game trash does it sell it like stardew no more resources I can't
doesn't work all right what else do I have I'm gonna put the animals away too
just like I have too much random shit I have too much random shit honestly I
want like an appraiser to come to my house and just be like go in the boxes
and fucking just give me I don't care just give me money what happened to the
all this stuff that I said okay give me this give me this give me this give me
this give me this I wish I could bring these and just deposit them to the
research center you need the whole set okay all right now what do I want to take
with me press L3 I just everything is a singular item now just get rid of this
stuff now okay I'll keep this put the juice down here what okay all right I'm
ready to play it's like the locked space in your bag those 400 gold you
spend $400 I need 2,000 I'm never gonna make it a two grand all right yes I will
let's go collect the spines the farmer all right we're getting that one done
the fishing rod don't care meet people we can go talk to people that doesn't
give us any money though fix the fence wooden boards to fix the fence around
the tree farm all right wooden boards I got wooden boards and then I need spines
wooden boards and spines let's go where are the wooden boards okay I need one
more dumbass wooden board all right hurry up an hour fuck off all right in
the meantime I'll go get the spines right aren't they down here this is where
the wooden fence is go get spines all right where was it down here high level
sea urchins near the fall will drop the spines what the waterfall where's there
waterfall I have to go east side all right that's gonna take too long it's
fucking a hundred bucks that guy can literally I don't care
remember you keep getting meaner every stream I'm not mean use the necklace how
do I use it okay let's go so now I'm going where tree farm I don't even have
close to $2,000 I'm never gonna get there I'm never gonna have two thousand
did I say followers what did I just say did I say gold or followers I said
dollars all right okay 150 bucks now the tree farm is in business I wonder
what this does okay so now any more quest for money okay I'm just gonna go
sell all that the couches and shit that's you give me at least a thousand I
need bronze to upgrade the axe but I don't I don't have the recipe to make a
bronze axe when he wants the green screen stream the green screen stream is
going to be well this your submissions is today tonight 12 a.m. Pacific last
chance to put it in and then probably five or six days later we'll do the
stream it depends on how long it takes to go through the submissions could be
longer could be shorter I'll let you know in a couple days you will know okay
so you saying they can upgrade the axe without upgrading the bench okay upgrade
kit bronze bar all right I can do wait I can you're right holy shit bronze bar
is tin and copper all right let's go all right I gotta go back to the mine and
get tin and copper and then I'll be able to do it maybe not wait a minute hold on
hold on hold on hold on copper I need this copper or shit all right I gotta go
get some more of this crap I'll be back he just said all right let's go and he
stared at the storage menu four times I know dude it's but I 200 bucks why did
the price go up 200 what it was 80 last week I need tin and copper I'm just
digging straight down from here this copper any relics aha there we go I need
copper and tin and then some kind of like weird tool upgrade kit right oh okay
let's go up and then down data disk cool I don't even need the scanner do I
actually maybe don't have to activate it with the scanner probably small engine
another one of these this game makes me sick like physically ill that's just
strange why you getting like motion sickness from this game really I'm
sorry to hear that hopefully all right let's go go you should probably have a
okay I have a lot of these data disks too I'll go this way you bet your ass
that I'm gonna upgrade that axe what's that this is another clock another small
I gotta sell all this stuff please remind me the resolutions too small I
mean it's like 1440p what is that way saying that I don't want to be in the
soil I want to be yeah get me out of here I want to be up where the tin is
tin Andy stop shut up there we go I see a bunch of this turn the scanner okay
there's some stuff over here this is perfect I promise I'm gonna this bridge
is going to be fixed within the time period of me turning the stream off I
promise Jerma you have a pot belly yeah I don't give a shit yeah hey I like food
who cares oh I like I like to eat I like to eat if fuck you I like food man
super defense mechanism just coming through on that one oh my god I
definitely have enough at this point to go do this I'm out of here the pot
belly is a sexy upgrade to a beer belly well that's the thing I don't drink beer
I mean I did the barrier cart thing I drank like fucking seven or eight or ten
I don't even remember it was a lot I'm gonna get out of here oh shit to ride
apple slices all right address the toad thing what toad thing all right is
anything I can start that will happen overnight yeah all this shit okay
bronze bar I need wood in my inventory you said no no no that's not what I'm
saying did I already use the 200 wood that I no way I used all 195 wood
already what no I didn't bronze bar bronze bar this would be ready in the
morning all right that's fine this be ready in the morning no context okay
wouldn't know you talking about when I said I was when I was I was the toad
thing yeah I used to turn around and drive in Mario Kart to try to get toad
when I was losing in Mario Kart if I was doing really poorly if I was in sixth
or seventh place there was only one lap to go I would turn around and try to
find toad and drive into him no okay I know what you're talking about and then
when I came over and grabbed the mic and I was like oh I'm thinking about toad
and this next one yeah what I was saying is like hey I'm thinking about like
turning around and driving into toad like I'm thinking about fucking you know
I'm thinking about toad I was yeah come on get out of here only what these are
still going how fuel depleted oh shit okay what do I need three bronze bars
upgrade kit from toad all right I gotta go get a tool thing we're bringing a
bunch of couches and I'm selling them all where are those couches I'm selling
all this shit I don't want any of it I don't want it anymore okay all right
it's time to sell not wait I'm selling this I'm gonna bring my CDs and I'll
turn I'll turn them into something I'm selling the clock I'm selling the bugs
I'm selling the engine I should make a little decent amount of money here I'm
gonna sell all the engines I don't care sell both clocks I'm selling all these
engines all right let's do it what is the worm stream maybe when I do the worm
for an hour straight I break the Guinness Book of World Records doing the
worm as long as possible all right I need to go and just do it how do I sell
can I sell to anybody that has a store that is a huge cat holy shit what cats
like it's not a bird all right sell nice all right there we go finally who else
has a store I need to sell this I gotta sell sofas I have four sofas nobody
else can I sell to here maybe okay yep I got a thousand bucks I'm getting there
okay all right not bad not bad let's go how are these doing is it time two days
I need more fertilizer three days I don't do I have any more think I have
two more bags should be all right can I cook the meat okay it's time I didn't go
to the tool store where's total tools I'm gonna bring most up self but also I
just want to get rid of I'll bring these I'm gonna do disc stuff bring the shit
to give to the mayor that sounds so fucking weird out of context this can
all stay all right that's all I want to do keep the rest of this crap okay total
tools hurry all right the mayor he's gonna get pissed mayors not even here
it's like shit under his desk okay all right tools time to finally cut down a
big tree only took four and a half hours to do it all right what do you got
you're not the right place total tools there we go weird okay what else do you
have balloons fireworks that's not one what is it we're gonna do this should
buy that too okay if chat was a person who would they be all right you know the
the chimpanzees that are in the chimpanzees react to magic videos that's
who you would that's who chat would be oh you know what that this it's a few
different like factions right that's probably like 30 to 40 percent of chat
maybe 30 percent maybe 40 okay so I'm ready to make this stupid thing here we
go finally I have a new weapon all right let's go cut a big tree down finally
bronze axe I need a bunch of hardwood and then I can do the bridge hardwood
there we go all right hell yeah now we start playing 1 million follower milk
chug please this looks really dodgeable I swear I promise you one day I will
hire someone I will hire a weapons expert like martial artist somebody that
has a black belt and that somebody's a weapons expert and I'm gonna give them
an axe not a real one but I'm gonna give them a big foam axe and I'm gonna
be like get me it's not gonna happen they're gonna murder you no they won't
I'm telling you I you know I love to prove people wrong when it comes to this
kind of thing a local streamer in the hospital because was so adamant over
there over years telling his chat room that he'd be able to dodge someone
trying to kill him with an axe that he went and proved it at this martial arts
studio within seconds of starting the bit mr. Albertson took the axe directly
to the forehead causing him to black out immediately when reached for comment in
the hospital mr. Albertson said no comment he refused to do an interview you
would just double down if that happened yeah be like yeah we're gonna do this
again but he's gonna have a bigger axe okay can I start this I got hardwood
right hardwood planks I'll wake up in the morning and I will be able to do the
sweet the real German could have done it I'm telling you I think I could do it it
wouldn't be a problem finally here we go bridge why do I have to be holding it
come on really like it's in my inventory all right I need two of these copper
what was it copper pipes I have three more of those anymore this where are the
copper pipes and sell them right okay we're good can't wait for the bridge to
be done in six hours it's a it's a long process this game it's a long process
I'm holding a coffin I need five of these wasn't gonna be done long time
all right so now give Gail the day of the bright Sun gift how about no all
right organization time let's go I'm renaming this this is gonna be called
materials this is technically a material material material material
material this is a material this isn't this is just all a bunch of weird shit I
don't know what it is resin not a build material oh cool hold on can I not play
with the fireworks I can't use the firework I need a lighter all right so
materials let's put the copper in there right just building material shit look
damage increase defense max health as well as upgrade the axe one whoo these
ready one more day why are you pretending to care about the game I don't
I do I'm just playing I'm just chilling I'm kind of sick and I'm just relaxing
with all of you we're just having a good time tourist this is the game that we're
just chilling with man we're just chilling we're just gonna hang out
that's what we're doing all right how much is the bridge body does the bridge
body need hardwood because if it is I have to go cut trees down the bridge
body is bronze plates and bricks okay so I need more I have I think I have
enough bronze bars bronze plates not really if I had more fuel is that gonna
keep going all right I got two against oh yeah yeah yeah I've got enough
refuel refuel refuel all right these things are good to go I'll have a bunch
of bronze bars which I can make bronze plates let's cut down some more hardwood
stop you can't get that I got a bird's nest play five nights at Freddy's 2 there
was a huge opportunity for you guys to have me play that game but you just you
didn't get to the right threshold I killed some crap I can't even step in
how deep is this water well I just did it oh no I didn't a lot of trees over
there all right almost there this is the first major milestone to get the next
area I was only gonna be live for like three hours today but I still feel okay
I think this is a good setup every time I do that I cough essentially I'm doing
all right though okay how many more hardwood planks do I need I need one more
hardwood plank and then I can keep this rolling all right but I need to make
these plates right bronze plates I'm assuming it's probably from here right
yep okay uh yeah I got enough so cancel this how many plates do I need is that
almost done bridgehead three bronze plates and three stone bricks no why I
need more than that okay I need a lot more stone bricks three is it only three
plates cuz then I don't need to do all this I can put bricks here instead yeah
we'll do bricks instead here I need these more all right now I just get a
wait and go to bed back into the mine maybe what do you think do any more
stone hydration check I got it right here
Jerma do you want your blankie and teddy you freaking freaking me out man
uh should I go to bed try to go to sleep what do you think why can't I just take this
corn this is right here is there any other quests I can do the spawn all right
I'm gonna go investigate the spine thing somebody said it's the east I'm gonna go
check it out maybe why not at the look of a spines because that'll give me
some more money please don't turn the cam off I can't handle being alone for
more than five seconds dude what the fuck this goofy-ass sign oh see
your turn all right there's here but who's a cereal mascot over here Papa
bear oh what bears like dried apple slices oh wait it shows down here you
want are you hate all this stuff do you like do you like it's trees up honey I
have honey don't I oh you like that oh it's the grad is no don't do not throw
a firework I need to get gotta get these urchins the book is coming out of my
nose I need ten spines sounds like link I can do this in another five minutes
it's fine dude I can't even it was like GTA 3 come on why they have a balloon
urchin that's weird oh I'm just eating meat I say 20 stakes what I don't even
had that many where did I get all that what come on I had 20 steaks to give me
a fucking break okay well whatever I mean a few more of these bricks this
should be fine in the morning I feel to do most of the bridge that's dumb minus
2000 gamer points it's okay I'll get him back I love the way they look when
they're stacked up this is a pistachio Hershey's my favorite flavor all right
bronze plate shit I need more of those three more I can only make I should get
it here how many do I need for a cuz that's making one this is making two
now I'll definitely have enough for you one more all right well I gotta go back
I have to go get back and do that I got triple tapped by a balloon urchin and it
killed me instantly my son won't talk to me after I suggested to watch your
streams what do I do you should tell your son that there's lots of great
streamers on twitch TV and that he can find whoever he wants to watch on his
own and you don't have to tell him what streamers to watch tell him to watch the
he might like that one okay I've got the materials umbrellas are important so I
could bring those to you let's try this in this guy again can I give you
something else meat all right you kind of liked it what would you do if you
woke up in this world tomorrow I mean this world's really not that different
than the world that we live in right now why is this so different there's not
that many differences it's not that big of a difference what's the big difference
there's no TV I mean this is wouldn't be that big of a deal
I'm pretty much the only party around here so come see me when you need to
heal up or give that motherfucker a bird's nest oh thanks thank you
appreciate it just be known as the weird guy in town he hands out raw meat to
people of birds nests he thinks he's mining copper and bronze bars but
they're they're just they're just thin mints he's a weird guy come on yes wait
is that enough it's not enough I need another bronze bar oh thank God okay I'm
good let's go build the bridge I better get like five grand for okay okay bam
we're gonna go to the bridge whatever happened to me strong I know maybe I'll
do me strong one day where I just get high and play Elden ring as a strength
only character and I can't have anything besides a club I trust me I don't want
to do it there is build the bridge now who do I talk to report to okay bridge is
done nice progress strength build is really good now too yeah I every time I
think about that idea oh wow that's like I don't know I don't want to make
it like a look up isn't aren't look at how fun drugs are right that's not the
intention of that stream oh what do I want to go oh they're in the town hall
you're a good lad yeah we'll see there's probably a way I can do that without I
don't know I have a gift that you want what does he want he has something that
that I have something he wants what is it oh this is the mayor right okay I
don't have everyone I think it started when someone jumped on the statue and
started throwing cranberry candy at everyone I just handed this guy just
animal shit what was that for what's cross five cross five board make your
move at the grid intersections for each turn each player makes one move per turn
black goes first what oh okay so this is this is just um connect for what oh I get
again fuck fuck what Wow where shit fuck off what the who cares about this you
know I mean who gives shit about the AI is just designed to beat you every time
I don't care about this I don't give a shit it's connect forward with like a
million other pieces oh fuck the birds freaking out dude I don't ever I hate
shit like this I hate checkers I hate chess I hate whatever this is called
whatever ball this is I don't I hate them and this guy this is like this
computer player it's just designed to beat you you losing to beginner AI no
it's just dumb get this fucking controller away from me okay here we go
he just knows my every move he knows my every move yeah what what do you mean
it's getting late I'm not done aim a hairdryer aim a hairdryer at your CPU
to slow the CPU down that shit's hard I hate that fucking dumb game fuck that
stupid ass game man that game's stupid we don't even need to who cares about
that oh no I can't play whatever the fuck it is
bocce ball whatever it is what cheat what's it called I'm going back and I'm
where the fuck is that guy reversey no what am I what am I backgammon not I'm
thinking of backgammon whatever who cares that's a stupid game it's just the
board is so huge it's called go okay so here we go
it's Goku excellent work use your payments what is it oh that's 1800 gold
I just made 1800 gold 150 gold nope I don't get out of bed for anything less
than 500 don't fuck all of you that's all right I got cash I'm glad you
returned to youtubers life it does kind of look similar doesn't it except this
this I would say this game is a way better oh these are ready aren't they
yep harvest cool all right so now I gotta go talk to the farmer there you
are all right I harvested some wheat what do you want oh I need to just craft
planner boxes I got you still haven't met this person more damage I can always
sell the wheat right make sense go back to that shithead Isaac and get your win
no I don't think I can beat that game I genuinely don't think I can do it I
genuinely don't think I can well I gotta pee I'm gonna pee below my nose
perfect okay so what was I just doing you should use a bot to beat the no I
don't need a bot all right let's keep going I don't know how much longer I'm
gonna stream for but I will for a little while longer let's get this game back up
mmm can you see me wait let me do this all right let's go what should I build
next this dude's a vegan furry did you just say that or am I making that up
I don't know what why did I say that what does it really say somebody said
something close I thought somebody said dude you're fucking pretty vegan furry
it was like no but who said that somebody said that why would I'm sending
it why would I just say that for no reason
all right what are what am I doing I forget I think I can oh I'm gonna go
cross the other to the island I'm gonna explore the other end of the island
somebody said very funny really really the chat moves really quickly guys coin
whoo that what that gold oh damn that's good how many do you have a lot to
donate all right there's nothing else is on this island what I spend all this
time building this bridge diamond diamond what the hell are you doing
oh that was really loud I'm sorry well now I know what's a here is this isn't
mine here I keep peeking the mic I know I'm sorry good need a cold glass of milk
not not even necessary when talking about a doughnut that's just moist it's
not even necessary I would take a water with this yeah that's how yeah that's how
good this is yeah I'll have to go home somebody said how does he eat so
delicately and so grossly at the same time rock-paper-scissors shoot rock-paper-scissors
shoot rock-paper-scissors shoot rock-paper-scissors shoot okay those are
good I don't need any more donuts I don't want to eat filibun junk they just
they were delicious all right I'm I've been running in circles for five minutes
that's how you can tell when we're kind of done with the game all right we're
gonna move we're gonna play something else we're gonna play something else
just for a little bit this game is fun it's like a stardew valley Animal
Crossing it seems like there's a lot of content in it seems like really fun
we're gonna play a dwarf and dwarf something dwarf it starts with a D
dwarf and what is it called yeah door dwarf romantic that's the one okay door
from antick