Dark Carnival, you must be this tall to die.
Oh yeah, baby!
Obviously, you can see we're in here with Boo, Burger Boy, of course, MLC Stealth, who is freaking out with a glitch.
This is our survival, so we're just jumping right into this here. I have no idea if we're gonna do this or not.
Boo, are you gonna throw that firearm on the ground?
This is a strategy.
I'm saying we climb up on this here thing over here.
Boo, toss down your ammo and go get a health kit.
Yeah, make sure you have health and pills and boom-a-bile and puke and pee.
Ooh, puke.
I love puke.
Alright, nobody pick up the grenade launcher, that's gonna be bad.
Meet Burger.
Hello, everyone.
I was like reading that.
I was reading that sign that says Meet Burger.
Yeah, this is like the first time Burger Boy's been in a video, I think.
I'm trying to jump on top of the corn dogs.
Alright, does that mean you're ready? Okay, cool.
Do we have the little gasket? Oh, never mind.
Everyone hang out up here.
Where did the zombies come from?
Oh, jockey gods.
Oh god, that was, oh my god.
Spitter, spitter across the way.
We're already like dead.
No, we're not.
Yeah, I've already fallen off.
It's alright.
I'm like on fire.
We've just got four minutes, that's it.
Yeah, I'm saving that.
I'm coming back up.
I'm up.
There's pills up here, so heal up and grab some pills.
Boom-a-bile.
Oh, we just need to, if we survive four minutes, we're super MLG pros.
Oh my god.
I got you, I got you.
I don't like this.
Get off of my bread.
Oh, charge.
Get out of here.
Oh, that didn't take long.
You're almost dead.
You need to heal, bro.
Burning sensation.
Look at me, just achievements all around.
Oh, you're getting a bunch of achievements right now?
By all around, I mean one.
Whoa.
That just destroyed.
Yeah, we gotta be careful of the spitters, man.
The spitter's gonna spit up here and we're gonna be all done.
Oh, you mean like that, except he missed.
Oh my god, I was just unloading on your back, dude.
I'm sorry.
Tank.
Oh, he's throwing a rock.
Tank, where is he?
Ow.
Just unload on him.
He has to climb up here.
Just destroy him.
All right, get off.
Oh, man.
It doesn't have to take too long, does it?
Smack out.
There's a hunter around too.
Be careful.
He's going down.
He's down.
Tank dead.
Oh, god.
Get this.
Oh, I got a jockey on me.
Oh, and a charger, too.
Are you kidding me?
I'm over here, screwed.
Oh, shit.
I'm trying to get to you.
Oh, you got boom too.
Boomer and a charger.
Oh, god.
Take your pills if you have them.
Yeah, good throw.
Good throw.
Good toss.
Are you dead?
I'm lying down right here on the ground.
Oh, come on, Burger Boy.
Tank again.
Tank.
Oh, my god.
Wow.
I'm trying to save you, German.
Dude, you just got flushed so far on my screen.
I'll get him.
Don't worry.
He's going down.
Burger Boy, you are like the master of this game.
All right, come on.
Come on.
I'll be the bait.
I'm going down.
I'm dead.
Another minute and a half.
Oh, if anybody can get rid of that tank and somebody picks up the defibs.
Oh, dear lord.
Oh, Burger Boy.
I think I got him.
Oh, boo.
You get full health.
Boo, I'm like healing and stuff.
I am so dead.
His tank's dead.
He's quieting down a little bit.
Hey, revive me, ML.
ML.
Oh, my charger.
Oh, Hunter.
Yeah, that's the end of me.
No, no, no, no.
Stealth, it's up to you.
Oh, you got Burger Boy.
Nice.
Burger Boy got a Hunter on him.
And a Spitter right there.
Spitter right behind you guys.
Tank.
Oh, dear.
Deary, deary me.
Oh, come on.
I'm coming in all kinds of spit here.
Do some crazy techniques.
Four minutes.
How?
Oh, man.
Oh, Stealth.
Oh, there's a Hunter coming.
Run around in circles.
All right.
Good first attempt.
We almost made it to four minutes.
Charger's coming for you.
Oh.
That's it.
That's all she wrote.
Three and a half.
God damn it.
That was the best time.
So.
I'm terrified.
Me too.
Just hang in that corner.
There's a Jaguar right behind us.
There's a Goldberg to our left right here, too.
Oh, God.
Smoker hasn't...
Oh, never mind.
It failed.
All right.
Just get in this corner.
Oh, man.
I'm already stung.
You're good.
Yes.
All right.
Hop in this corner.
This is it.
When a tank comes, we can...
Oh, come on.
We can deal with it.
Oh, yeah.
I'm tanking my bile.
Yeah.
When a tank comes, we can...
That's better.
Smoker right there.
Smoker straight ahead.
Oh.
And an idiot that just fell.
All right.
Look at this.
Spitter up top on the...
Oh, that Spitter's gonna get us.
No, she's not.
She's too stupid.
Jock's coming to our left.
Straight ahead.
Tank.
All right.
This is where we start to move around.
Boom-a-bile.
I'm throwing it the other way.
Throw it on him.
Oh, I'm an idiot.
Hey, Hunter.
Heads up.
It's all right.
Just focus on the tank.
Spitter.
Tank should be almost dead.
Hunter's dead.
Run, Jerma.
Tank's dead.
Regroup.
Hey, Jocky.
Oh, watch out for the Jocko.
Jocker.
Whatever.
All right.
Back in the corner.
Oh, is it...
Oh, I've been Jocky.
Jocky.
There's somebody back here.
Thanks.
All right.
Good.
This is the best we've done so far.
No one's running around aimlessly in circles dying.
Just about out of ammo, though.
Yeah, we're going to have to make a team ammo run in a second here.
You guys want to do it?
After the next tank.
Get the ammo.
No, actually, yeah.
Where's the ammo?
Let's just go as a team.
I just need the shotgun right here.
I'll smoke right here.
Spitter.
Spitter, actually.
All right.
Go back in the corner.
Back in the corner.
Buma.
Back in that good old corner.
Hunter.
Oh, God.
He got right on me.
There's a tank coming.
Oh, dear Lord.
Right next to us.
Right behind us.
He got behind us.
He climbed up behind us.
Holy shit.
He's right there.
I threw a Molotov on you guys.
I apologize.
It's okay.
Somebody want to watch my back for one second?
Oh, jeez.
Oh, I got chargers.
Watch my back for one second.
No, I'm going to go down.
I'm going to kill this charger.
Come on.
I'm trying to get something.
I just can't believe I got that off.
Oh, a charger downed me.
Oh, come on.
The tank's right behind me.
I'm done.
Oh, my God.
This is over.
We were doing so good.
We have to do another.
We can't end it on that.
That was a good strategy.
No.
We didn't even make it to duh.
Oh, my God.
Like, where did that charger come from?
We just got our ass washed.