Okay, I'm watching fucking TV now. Well, what I'll put on Pokemon TV show
I wanted to beat that level so fucking bad. What's going on? Oh the right right this fell
All right. Let's watch fucking TV was a pokemons. I want to beat that little so bad
I want to be that little soap. No, not the fucking news. I
Feel better. Oh relax progressive scan. I gotta change this. What do I change this to?
Title
Luigi is Luigi in this game Oh Meowth, right, right, right. Okay
Pokemon Channel
Screaming orders while I play pinball on the battlefield. That doesn't make sense to right now. How about
Pokemon react Pokemon react Randy. Okay, how does this work? Okay new game
Today is 3 14 20 20. The time is 5 59. How does it know that it's like kind of accurate
This is a original Wii. Why would its date be correct five? Oh, no. No, it's it's no, that's not correct
Oh, no, that's fine. That's correct
So that's great. That's fine. It's an hour ago. Okay, it's an hour ago. Whatever
Did you really just watch TV with pokemons and got in green ball relax?
I'm like I'm like
Licklipper, but anyway, I've been I have to apply this shit pre-recorded how okay. Here we go
On the TV season over I welcome to Pokemon Channel
This TV is a gift to you from Pokemon Channel Pokemon Channel is a TV station that airs many kinds of Pokemon program
You've been chosen as our first test audience. But first things first may I have your name?
Signing up is easy. Just register your name that will start putting programs on the air
May I have your name?
Let me confirm your name is Seth
Aka
Person who owned this console before I did this is pre-owned. Hey Seth. What's uh, the first program is brand new anime
Pichu brothers. I'd like you to watch the TV anime all the way through
Okay, we got to give our real honest opinions, too. Here we go
It's a shitty font that's like a default Adobe Premiere font
What if I press A? If I just skip it, what happens?
I've waited a long time for this guys and in just 24 hours
Never Pichu brothers, but I'm sure you knew that
Cuz these two are known both far and wide
Just try and guess the next place they'll turn up at
You see life's a blast with your best friend by your side. I wouldn't watch this
They see where's my where's my like America's Got Talent like
What that's huge, but I wouldn't watch it
Pichu Pichu, that's their name Pichu Pichu
Fun's their game. Of course, there are these things don't go right even the best of buddies sometimes fight
Is this free on YouTube? What?
Is this the intro?
I mean, that's not funny. That's not cute. He's got like a broken neck. That's not cute. What's wrong with you guys?
Can't stay mad for long in no time. They're back. Well, they belong
Side by side, it's Pichu and Pichu
I won't see one without the other these perfect pals stick brother to brother side by side. It's Pichu
Oh, yeah
Side by side, it's Pichu and Pichu
Seems like the Pichu brothers and their friends are ready for another day of fun
Oh, sounds like smoochum's got a problem
Come on are carrying their shape like a crescent moon
I'm ruining the show
All right. All right. All right. No more. No more
This sounds very interesting. So the other Pokemon want to see for themselves
It's a way
What is what this morning you actually just watch this this is what we do as this wouldn't get the game is oh
Nice. This is a whole like 22-minute episode
It's 22 minutes. This is a real mystery. So the gang heads for the park to figure out what the crest
No, it's not 22 minutes long
There's an a palm and a smear goal, maybe they can give the gang some answers
All right, I know all of you say your fucking name
So annoying if you get more than like 10 Pokemon in the same room at the same fucking time, holy shit that'll be obnoxious
Now I know why why like you only have like three
Rounders you got like a fucking crowd of Pokemons. There's gonna be yelling the names
It's chaos
Probably wrong strawberry every
This is gonna get me like my channel flag, I mean
This video game it's this game
It's a game. I put in my weed. Oh, I think that's it be continued. Okay, is it gonna ask me what I thought?
What if this is just like a Nielsen ratings Pokemon?
All right
What did you think of the anime? How about I get you to file a report right now?
I need you to send your reports through the report channel
You can change the channels by pressing either minus or plus on the TV using the a oh I was gonna say this is not
The right controller you can also change channels using the controller
Just press either L or R the TV can be turned on and off by pressing on using the yeah pressing Z on the control
This is TV or is this like a fucking microwave it's three buttons, okay set the channel to the report channel report channel
I talked through the TV set the hand on the report on the screen and press a
Alright, let's report. Hi your report is safely arrived. Fine. I'll save your report data. I didn't even get my support. Oh
It's how to save the game, right?
Right
No, don't make that joke. I want you to have this as a thanks for your report
$20
What do I do the money if you save up some P?
You'll be able to shop for all sorts of things in the shopping channel
Please channels give you chances to earn P before you finish the game. Remember that you must make a report. Oh
What was that cry? How about backing away from the TV and take a look around?
Whoops before you do you should turn off the TV press on using the hand and was he?
How's he still talking to me? Good. You turned off the TV
It's like in the room with me to the step away from the TV move
There's a beat you can take a look around the room by yeah. Yeah. Yeah, perhaps there's something here
Where's the telephone to call police? It's not on on excuse me
I know I might I know I might have like an 80 inch TV in a gigantic bay window
But this is not like park your car in front in my fucking driveway and watch like sharknado with me
Okay, so why they why they run? Oh, it's a Pikachu. Well, it's very rare to see a wild Pikachu
Well, like this really must be interested in television
Seth when you're filing your reports, could you let us know what it was like watching TV with Pikachu?
He's gonna talk over each movie, right at Pokemon channel. We collect data for developing programs of Pokemon will enjoy
That's almost unheard of a wild Pikachu
counting on you
Pikachu's like
He puts on like fucking like Sopranos like hey, no, no, no, you're not old enough for that
Oh, I want to do it so bad everyone hates it
I want to do it wicked loud as loud as I fucking can. All right, let's go
No, it makes it's gonna happen. I can't guarantee it won't happen. You understand how to use the TV
There's something I should tell you. I had a poke pad the village looked along with your TV
The poke pad would let you access a variety of information
Turn on the poke pad by pressing start here. Try it out. Now
It's 11 p.m. Strong that's wrong Magnemite
Registration done. Hello. I got to know Pikachu
Magnemite delivered the TV said I get more than one TV Oh programs other than the anime have now started turn on the TV
I hope you and Pikachu will enjoy it together. Turn off TV. Let's go. What is it? All right, Pikachu
About Pokemon news flash you like this one
I'm here on the scene. It was made in dreams
What do you think you like it
What what what did I do wait come back come back I'll put your favorite show on I'll put on
fitness channel
Smoochum shape up. All right, get over here
art-proving smoochum workout
Pokemon
Hey, how about this one quiz get back over here? It's starting. It's time for quiz wobble buffet
Here are our contestants
Photodile
OG pie and
TV
The answer is correct. Okay ball pot is lowered
First to reach the bottom becomes a champ. Do you know what we're done with that one?
I don't want to watch that anime anymore. How about um, uh news flash
Pikachu appears as if it wants to go through the TV screen
What an idiot wait didn't we already watch this what do I do watch the TV I am what do you think I'm doing?
I'm shoving these politics
What is it what's that
What I thought you said I could die I'm just I'm just like annoying him while he's watching TV
Yeah, no, but I go oh yeah, I'm paying attention to a show
Okay, can you fucking get the stop fucking doing that? Like wouldn't you do the same thing?
I
Have enough TV for today that's enough TV for today. You got to do your homework. No, no, you're getting addicted to television Pikachu
It's not good for you. Listen to me. You want to do is you want to balance your life balance media?
Excuse me. Watch your watch that tongue. What you excuse me. Your mother is talking you need to balance your life and
Ten more Pikachu get closer
Pikachu go within two inches of screen
Pikachu Pikachu stare at screen with eyes as wide as you can
Okay, I can't do that. Here's the shopping channel shopping Squirtle
Okay, what can we buy?
We have bargains today. First up is this item
It's the binder
Keeping things neat and organized
Immediate delivery, how much is it?
Important ten key
Okay card pack Pokemon nice cards, I want it binder has been ordered. Oh, it is more
It's yours on this. It's fantastic. What is it?
Available only here you want this do you want one of these? I'm so glad I bought it. Yeah
Let's get it
Friendship poster. Oh, I don't have any more money
Okay, Pat. I don't have any more money
No, you can't have that go back to the fitness. Wait, who the fuck is this guy?
Wait, do more and more people just come like invade your house to watch TV. Oh, it's a delivery. Okay delivery bird
When do we get some new subscriptions to do TV shows?
It's not even like basic cable. This is it antenna shit. That's what we're getting right now
How do we open? How do we open the car pack? Okay, it's working
Oh, it even came with a free gift gun open it. Oh, we open a car pack open up the nice card pack
The Snorlax motion card was stored in the binder
The mr. Mime card was stored in the binder
the geo dude card was stored in the binder the
Octillery card was stored in the binder
Celebi
Are those cool? What good timing you should put the free gift in that binder. All right
Nice cards are very nice trading cards and are the thing in thing right now
I understand that they're very popular among even amongst Pokemon. I know you collect a lot of nice cards. I'll give you reward
How about you aim for nice cards of 25 different for now?
You want to look at the nice cards you have to open the binder. Let's go see them
Streamer luck cool. Oh, we can actually spin it around. All right, this geo dude is mr. Mime
These look like
Custom debit card. I guarantee at least a hundred of you guys have this for a custom debit card
It's all right. That's perfect. I like this one. They're rare
This was medium M. Well, this one is rare. This one's like a medium
Wait a minute. Ah, that one is the only one that does it. Holy shit. It's that's holographic
Oh, I got that the people happy the other ones suck where your mom wants you to study for a change
If you notice the desk get off the desk
Because you notice the trash can no, I won't do it
Look over there. What's that? I think you're doesn't appear to notice. I just said we just go in the backyard
You want to go aside? It wants to keep watching TV. All right. Yeah, let's watch the book. What the fuck tube on
He's like, yeah
No sides for suckers. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
We got another 12 episodes of Breaking Bad to watch in a row. Let's go. Holy shit. Too close way too close
It wants to watch TV. Sure. Okay, let's go
And a little bit more TV stand back put on the fitness channel TVs that way you change Pokemon. I don't know not yet
All right. I gotta pee
You just watch exercise TV with Pikachu. I'll be back in a minute
I
Stuck in stretching exercise. I should do this one. You're a deadbeat. What I just dropped
Well, he's enjoying himself
He's learning about exercises. All right fatigue relief. All right. Are you ready? Let's change channel
What do you know? Let's do a quiz channel. All right, so though I've got a I've got a ball fucked up
He's just doing exercises. No
He wants the news. All right fine on the news. There you go. All right
We're gonna go outside and play this is bad
You know what? No
Eyes are hurting
He looks like he's about to fall down he's going like
All right, it's time to go side
Yeah, we can't just sit her all day it's time to go outside outside
Maybe another two minutes
At the end of this segment we're going outside we're playing
That's enough that's enough
Wild Pikachu would appears to be interested in TV. Okay, because he wants the TV turned on no outside
Pikachu wants the TV turned on. Oh, no, he's addicted. He's addicted to television. No, we're going outside
Yes, it wants to keep watching some more TV. No
He's angry. We're going out there and we're gonna play dig some holes or something. I caught it
Get out there no, it's no no more TV outside. Oh, no, he's like a he's like a little brat
No, no only TV. You want to read a book? No TV. That's not TV. I go outside only TV only TV
He's attacking me he's why is he attacking me
You only need to watch each show all the way what I don't want to put the anime on I wasn't a fat one
You missed it you missed it you missed the show the static on all right fine, you like this shit the bitrate
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Let's do a bit rate fight. All right, let's go. Let's go
Let's go. I'm done one more report. Have you watched shopping squirtle to the end?
I don't know. Probably not getting new programs on the air. You report Seth. You're absolutely vital. You got you're counting on you
Okay, I'll say that report data
This is like I'm like I'm on space ghost you're doing great. You're doing great. Keep at it by the way
It's guess all you viewers at home didn't realize I have power in the fucking real world
All right, let's see those hands. All right, no more of this shit. What if we didn't watch the
Losing why am I losing channels? Wait, this is the same thing. No, I don't want to watch this. No, no, we need to watch the
Where's the shopping channel? All right chopping channel. Just watch chopping channel. Enjoy it Pikachu
Eat this disc. No, this is I'd like this one. I'll eat the other one. Oh you like this
What is it like a thing? You like a little toy you ride on it like a horse or something a
Lot of money I don't have that much money. Sorry Pikachu. No, I can't afford it
What happens when you watch every TV channel, I don't have any money I need money but ring girl is gonna get you
quizzes, okay
Oh, it's a guy from a special way. No, it's not
This is the character that looks like that
Lucario is what he looks like. He's got the same scheme as the wrestler of Pokemon in sinner in sinner
All right, now we're gonna watch the quiz show quiz channel and we're gonna do quizzes for money
How do we play though do I get you can I like call do I have to like put my face up to it
How do we how do we do this? I don't I don't play Pokemon. I don't know what that is
Get out of the way. That's not right. Oh
It is right, correct
Commander is in the lead. I'm sorry. No, never mind
Pokemon like a piece of chocolate who will take the chance?
Oh
It's underneath it I thought that was like a hook or or like a bottom
Peek-a-boo quiz. How do we even answer these correctly? Oh, so I see it now
It's that thing. It's that it's the one the one we just saw right? It's blaziken
How do we how do I go on this show? That's the one from smash probably
There's no winner. I want to get on this show. Maybe I can get
Bulbasaur Bulbasaur
We did it, okay now it's time for no more TV that we watched every show
Pikachu we watched every show that we have and
Sadly enough. We only have
seven full television shows available to us
It wants to watch anime part one. What anime part one and we already saw this I'm dumb going
You really are like a fucking five-year-old
You guys don't know
Kids love watching the same episode. They've seen of a TV show a thousand times like if you DVR
the same episode of
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
Little kids will want to watch the same one every fucking day. So this does not surprise me at all
And eventually it gets to the point where you can you can say every line of the whole show
for instance
the episode of Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
Where Goofy doesn't know how to bake a cake. I know every line I could recite the whole thing
Yeah, I don't want to watch this
We don't watch the whole thing though
He's sad about this. All right, that was fun
He's gonna want to watch this every day
This is just babysitting well, let me make it more accurate
Sometimes fight and that's when they turn the whole world upside down
Bros like these can't stay mad for long in no time. They're back
It's Pichu and Pichu
See one without the other
Perfect pal stick brother to brother side by side. It's Pichu and Pichu
Well, it seems like the Pichu brothers and their friends are ready for another day of fun at their Pokemon Clubhouse
Oh
Sounds like smoochums got a problem
Smoochums all excited Pokemon are carrying little cards and they're shaped like a crescent moon
Oh
This sounds very interesting so the other Pokemon want to see for themselves
Honey honey, honey, don't put that in your mouth. Don't put that in your mouth
Oh
Get off of that get down from there don't find that don't find that get down just please
It's hell here, okay
Just turn the volume down turn the volume down I gotta go
Tell you
I've been around my sister had kids and I know people that have kids. That's it. That's tricky. That's tricky
It's a lot of work. Shout out to all the fucking moms and dads out there. Oh, but we got it
We got to get you off fucking TV. I
Had the mic unmuted when I first came in
All right, no one news
It wants to watch PNF. It's PNF. We're already watching PNF
No, no more no more no more of that here, okay
Phineas and Ferb we just watched this whole thing
No, you know what?
We're done. Yes. I have that's very odd. That isn't what it says in your reports
I mean if you do sign up to be one of those people that has
You get like all these fucking devices that are in your house
Listen to this if those you that don't know if you sign up to do
one of these watch TV and report back things
They literally make you wear a device in your house
like like an ankle bracelet if you were on like house arrest and
It kid fucking keeps you on there and attracts everything that you've ever do
It's like we want to be able to catch what like network you're on at any second and you have to wear it you have
To have it on at all times
How do I know this?
because
funny story about that
long time ago my family
Decided maybe we would try this that sounds interesting and once we found out what we had to do
And we found that we were gonna have to wear these like weird fucking devices. It was like I
Don't think we want to do this anymore
That's a sitcom you had to wear a fit bit that we had was weird, but they would they were gonna pay you though
That's the thing. I think they like paid you this is like 17 years ago 18 years ago
I think they would pay you if you like actually did all the weird shit
Anyways, we're gonna watch the news all the way through Jeremy. You're the reason why community got canceled
Oh
Portable people like you thought I was lying. No, I'm not lying
They have these like fucking weird ankle trackers. You like have to wear it on your like
It's like a walkie-talkie that you connect
It's real. Wait. Wait. No, no, my whole family wasn't on probation. This is not me like
Yes, I could have been lied to as a fucking 11 year old. Oh, we all have to wear fucking these bracelets son
It's the TV companies are tracking what we're watching and like my whole family's on house arrest
Those like what like that's no, I mean like that's not what happened. This is a real thing
All right. We've Pikachu. We've watched it all
Report it. It's me. Hey, it's me. Oh
Kind of weird. Thanks for your report. Hmm Pikachu watches TV this way. This is a very informative report fine as thanks for your report
I'll give you something some cards
Okay
Can I do like a special like delivery instructions and like that little check the the text box?
I don't want that fucking thing in my house
Just leave it at the door. I got smirgal to
Using smirly smirgal to you'll be able to paint images taken off TV
Your artwork will be automatically submitted for use on Pokemon channel
Just one drawback
Smirgal to can only be used with the anime Pichu brothers
Well, Pichu brothers is showing on TV set the thing on smirgal to and then press a now
I must admit something smirgal to it's only just been completed. Nobody has tested properly yet
We get you to test it out paint with it and file a report on it. We're counting on you
Weapon to surpass metal gear. All right, we got to put on the Pichu brothers. Okay part one
What is going on please stop I don't know what to do hold down and make him what all right
Um, how do I get out of here?
What does this have to do why did why can I why don't understand what the fuck is going on wait
Would you like to display this and auction off untitled? Yes, please give title to the new painting
The old painting will put up for auction by press. Oh
Wait, is it taking a screenshot? Hold on a minute
Holy shit. All right. I gotta remember it was now what's because of hair because of hair yellow
Blue hair
Because background like that, right? I don't remember blue hair blue hair blue blue blue blue. I'm doing blue
Dude, this is tuber here. All right was it
What went just pink I need pink pink it's I don't I'm done I'm done
We're gonna go screen grab you and no I don't want to I do no one no, no, no throw away the newest yes
Throw it away
Okay, we did it all right now get out of the way
Brothers and their friends already mom making shitty art while child runs into wall
Let's report it
Me oh, thank you for your report paint system appears to be working
Well, excellent most excellent with this much data. I imagine that we should be able to
The new programs are scheduled to begin at tomorrow at 5 a.m. If you look forward to them wait tomorrow
tomorrow at 5 a.m. In real time
So we go into the Wii menu save the game and then make it like three years from now
What are you doing? What the fuck have you done? Hey Seth?
I guess that you're at least still able to hear me the time being will send you replacement TV
What a fucking idiot you have insurance. I would laugh. They couldn't get it in the door
This is better. This is like a new TV the retro TV. Oh
Pokemon watch TV and fool with the controls as opposed to these will have been made to be made more sturdy
Okay, okay, we have to watch everything in black and white
Now we don't what we have to do is we have to skip time by a full day
All right, do you play in the game now?
Alright, so wait, do we have anything new?
I'm not watching this in black and white. Alright, let's go back. Let's go outside. Okay. Wait, can we go outside?
Turn the TV off while going out. Oh shit. You're right
That's just go outside with me we finally gonna play the game again is the yard
Okay, say hi
Doug Frio Doug Frio moves its three heads around to do what for the soil?
No idea. I don't have a single book. I'm gonna say soften it
Correct. You win a nice card. I mean that's what I figured you'd do makes sense
Oh
This is a sound one for you. What else can we do? Oh, it's a butt. It's a butt. There's a bee
You're chatting with lady bar. Let it by use a fluid to let others know where it is
Where does this fluid get released from its wings? It's feet. It's mouth. It's mouth. I want to come out of your feet
What was it? Is it actually feet?
gross
You don't notice turn right play with the wooden box. Oh do it. No, we're not going back to watch TV
Check the wooden box. Yes
Pardon there. What's in there banana? Oh
Cool. Oh, that's pretty good prize. Don't eat the banana. No, no, that's mine. Oh, that's mine
All right. What about this weed?
Uprooting the weed. Come on. You can do it one more. You couldn't do it. Well eat that onion
Say PlayStation fine eat the apple. Is it good?
It's Pikachu that small
And Apple's like this big
Pikachu's like this big. Is he I thought he was like I thought he was like fucking three and a half feet tall
Wait, Pikachu is not like four three or four feet tall
Wait, he's like this big. No, he's not
Doesn't he come up to like ashes knees. He's like fucking huge
No, I know I might be I might be confusing like the Pikachu in the costume at like the birthday party
That's like six feet tall
Like the big I'm not I'm tough. But is he actually he's not that big
ashes 10
How tall is that ashes 10? He planted a flower. Oh
What's he do you planted the flower seed for me? Oh what I think you picked up the whale more pale
He's just watering the garden
Wow, oh
So cute
Wonder what will grow it may grow faster water every morning. It's a werelord. I know what that is
You can clean that up that prash up. Oh
You're right. Take it up. Pick it up. I know checking his surroundings on the weed
You can't you know, it's wrong enough
You pull up
E coin something jumped out. Holy shit get it. Go get it. Where are you? What are you doing? Get the coin?
Get that coin. Is it one coin or is it 20?
It's just one key
Imagine burying one cent in the ground one of it coin
And I let's go save the game and this passport. All right, let's get inside
These Pokemon are huge at this other scale the world is messed up. That was wrong. Yeah, it's off
But this is my this is my house
The bus stop wait, I'm like, I'm I'm not even as tall as the doorknob. What the hell is going on out here
What's this little blob? Oh, you know, I know that I have that enabled. Oh, no, didn't I take it off?
What does ditto transform into to avoid attack while sleeping air a rock?
air
What about you a lot of push?
Cyndaquil. Oh, sorry
When do you when do the flames on Cyndaquil's back burn when it's in love during store when it's angry
Holographic that's cool
All right, wait, let's go should we get on the bus why is he angry where's the bus
They're fighting what's this thing?
Planting planting pot was it a honey in there wasn't there make the face camp water. Nope
All right, let's save the game and this teleport to tomorrow at 5 a.m
I just for one second just smelled a cooked beyond burger for a second. It was just like
There it is. Very specific. All right. No, I don't want to continue playing the game
Let's go. Let's go change the wheeze time tomorrow at 5 a.m. What's today?
All right tomorrow at 5 a.m. Let's do it. So we we settings date and time right calendar date
Okay, so here this needs to be tomorrow
15 brief wait, right brief 15 20 20 and the time needs to be
What's 5 a.m. To wait what's 5 a.m. Oh, it's just fine
We'll do 510 just a picture. Let's go. All right, that should do it. It's like tomorrow at 5 a.m. Let's go
Okay, let's see what happens yes put it in progressive scan mode what do you mean? Yeah, what do I mean?
I went backwards a day. I just went forward a day
Okay, okay Mon channel continue
Loading data, right? They did have been loaded. You're Seth today is 3 15 20 20. The time is 5 11 a.m
That information is correct. You did it. I see that you've gotten your repaired television
Now several new programs have finally gone on the air all thanks to your report Seth
Token of our priest you try to spend it wisely
Dollars, oh, yeah. Oh, yes shopping squirtle has started selling TVs just starting today. In fact, why not spend that fee?
I just gave you and buy yourself a nice TV to exchange your TVs a start and open the pokey pad
Well, then do check the new programs file reports
Almost forgot your painting untitled free sold at the auction. It's sold for $78
I imagine that's a fair price. I would have thought that it might be a fetch a better price, but sure
Okay, what's the new TV shows we have smuggles art study?
He's got
He bought it
He's the one that bought at the auction
Stately
overflowing with class the attention to detail is
Bodily emotive if this art were a movie, it would be a classic with tears and laughs
There is more to this such a display that this fiction is
Reminiscent of comics. Yes. I sense the influence of comics somehow in this she was impressed until we meet again
Okay, watch it again real quick. I
Want to watch it again?
Want to watch that again? I'm gonna scam the fuck out of this guy
Please tell me again how much you like my pen. I was saying it right. It's miracle miracle miracle miracle
But I
Can't take a screenshot of
I was gonna take a screenshot of that and then paint over it
Did you just change the fucking channel on me? What's with the eyes? We're drugs to pick you on. What the hell was that?
That's copyright. I own the copyright
Wait, do I if I sold the painting? I don't own the copyright anymore. Oh
Oh Pokemon cars. I want these. Yep. Yep. Yep. I want them too
How much is it you still own the rights?
Do I know what if I what if I just sell the whole thing? What if I sell everything and rights included?
$20 for a pack of Pokemon cards get the fuck out of here. Fine
What about TV? I want to make another painting. Oh
Peter brothers to
How much is this gonna go for fuck this show, but with the G whatever. Yes, fine. I'm gonna get pokey band
What if I get banned for this? Oh good with the game. Wait Pikachu is looking at the painting
He likes it, too
Wait a minute, I know no, I can't do that again
You guys do me
Yes, I'd like to auction off shitty program. Here we go. All right, let's put the new one on please
Let's put episode 2 on by having fun. Yeah, kind of
You and a POMs painting pointed our friends in the right direction and it's time to do some exploring
When the TV get fixed when I skipped on my Wii a full day
This is like an actual TV show was it was this actually on the air
It looks like an empty old warehouse. Maybe teddy ears knows know something we don't
Sleep
The Pichu brothers are explaining that a POM sent them
So, that's it the questions are invitations to me out party and
That fruits reserved for invited guests only
Imagine voice acting one of these abominations. Well, besides him, it'd be pretty great cuz you just have to go like this
And then they use that for the next 12 years
You just have to give different emotions of a lava set
Like 15 times and then they could just use it wherever they want for the rest of the entire run of this whole show
Why am I like 20%
It's not real either is Santa Claus the Easter bunny the Tooth Fairy Mickey Mouse is not really
Fucking corporate made fucking corporate thing to make you pull money from my fucking corporate
Enjoy the show though. Oh, that's the end of show
Slow pokes sleeping channel accurate weather report
Rainy and then sunny hey
You know like this channel, well, this is what the weathered actual weather channel is like
No, whether channel is just you got like five minutes of information that you play for 24 fucking hours
Hey, what's it gonna be like today? Well, it'll be sunny and it might rain later today
It might be it's gonna be sunny. It might rain later today
It might be sunny
You know what just like just play a bunch of reruns of like storm chasing
Like five straight days until like something to talk about it became clear
We did it all right? Wait, I gotta buy some more stuff. How much money do I have? Let him sing
Big bargains today
What's the first item? Oh, I didn't even open my car pack. Did I?
She tried pulling the plus button. That's not you know, oh you push it stop that get back
Stop pressing that button. Stop it. You're gonna rip it off. We just watch TV and relax
Get out of here, man
all right
Get the fuck out of here
Pikachu, please get the fuck away
Pikachu
Get the fuck away from me. I'm trying to you've been my you're blocking my view
He's taking a break. He was at my cat does this
Yeah, every day cat does this
When every time you do you're busy doing something which comes over and just like fresh
It's just like butt up like as far as it can into your face
It's just like oh, I'm doing something. All of a sudden. It's just like oh, yeah
It's like dude. All right. Oh gee. All right, man
Like I'm busy. Why was this one? Oh, I got another frame. Wait, is this like it?
Just like an aura borealis the thing that like eats its own tail. Whatever that is
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye
or forest
Idiot, I know what it is
I've seen full metal alchemist brotherhood and the
Bask of Satan whatever the fucking movie was called. All right, do I have enough for the frame? Buy it
We've been nothing else to buy Pikachu
Let's report this to
Dr. Robotic is what I was gonna say. I don't know why
All right, professor oak. Oh, this is a magnificent report with this report
It should be easy to develop and broadcast new programs new programs here to begin tomorrow at 5 a.m
Hope you hope you look forward to them
See you tomorrow. See you tomorrow 5 a.m. Go outside where I was gonna turn off the thing
TV the TV is off
Okay, come over here
You didn't do the quiz didn't do quiz didn't do quiz didn't do quiz
Look, it's fucking didgeridoo
It wasn't it
When does piglet emerge out of the ground during lunchtime when it's bored when it isn't right out
Oh because it's when it's not right out. It's a nock kernel animal
Daytime right now. That's true. It is date. That's cool. All right, we have card packs. Oh wait, so every easier
great eat great eat great eat great
stomp stomp great
ferment in an oak barrel
Drink wine it wants to eat the grapes. Yes
Well, we're gonna water our plant I like grapes grapes are good. I agree. All right water
Turn that poop into wine
Well, or
Mm-hmm over here same thing on this one
Pikachu wants to do something else. Well, you just what you're good. You just water
Click on sign click on sign click on sign
sign
Wrong sign. I mean, oh, there's more pokey. There's more. There's more Pokemons here
Pikachu is chatting with why not?
Pokemon quiz what do why not do
To improve their counter move they play tag. They mash each other
Get the card. This is gonna also a hologram. This one's pretty cool
Alright, what about this weird flower vegetable Pokemon?
Bell awesome when Bellossom gather and seemingly dance, what are they said to be doing?
Summoning a storm summoning the Sun or summoning the Sun
Yes, I think I know I've never played a single game of Pokemon not once but I know all these
Cool. What else is out here?
There's a hole in the ground. What's in the hole play every Pokemon game on so I'm not gonna play every Pokemon game
I don't I don't play Pokemon. I don't play Pokemon
I just played the ones where you watch TV and shit and like I'll maybe I'll play the one where you take photos of animal
I'm not playing the actual game
Check out this hole. Yeah
Is there a Pokemon step a game cube? It's fucking my side. They can you is there is there a game cube one?
No
Was that an umbrella?
ball ball
Once I catch my dad once we get from there
There you go, son
Give me another one son eat my dad
Let's play a catch. I was trying to get too far away
Oh
We can do this again
Let's play catch again. I get it down. I was trying to throw it in the hole. I don't know why it's like sadistic
Go for a hundred. I don't think I don't want to do a hundred
Coward, there's a secret unlocked at a hundred. Is that for real? Is there actually a secret unlock? How many is that?
or
Yes
Shit, I have to sit here for a fucking 95 more of these
Watch out for the hole
Deeply moved the game of catch went on a long time. Yeah, it did it. Is it over?
Liars, you guys what you guys lied to me. Oh
What about these?
What about these? What about these? What about these?
Fighting it. What about these? I'm sorry. I'm fighting it. I'm not I want to do it people hate it
What about what about these tri-leaf clovers I fucking had to get whatever I don't care whatever I know what do you want me to say?
Gonna stop jump scaring me. That was a bad tick-tock. No Pikachu. Don't run away
I mean that uh
You think you think I farted on
You're talking that's a guy I have a chair that fucking watch it I didn't holy shit
That's fucking like I did I didn't do that. That's what I do in the video. I don't know. I didn't do that
You're that but I don't know. I thought that was Garfield. I thought it was fucking Garfield
I was I forgot what game I was playing. Let's go fucking doing that man. See senile. All right, let's turn the let's go to
Tomorrow's watch one of those set of videos
Remember that time German shit himself
Can you act Pikachu knows the bed? Wait, do I have to actually turn off the way? Yeah, I do
Yeah, I'm gonna sneeze and I'm gonna try to make it wild. I
Hate when it does this. I shouldn't even talk about it. What's under the bed?
Cardboard box see I can't sneeze. I'm trying my hardest. What's going on?
I just made myself like yawed. I did somebody said inhale like you're gonna sneeze a bunch and I did that and it like
Was that a DS Pokemon mini case under the bed Pokemon mini and snorlax is lunchtime. We're safe
The hell is this you can play the Pokemon mini now their little games on here. Oh shit. Take out. Yeah, let's go
What I have to do things fucking broken thing broken good great. Okay. Oh, okay. I get it
You eat, but don't eat Pichu. Don't eat eat you I get it. I'll get a hundred on this one
Let's go man new record. I have a go
Just double on me. Okay
Shit sorry, I got it's good enough. All right, I'm watching TV, right? Let's watch TV. That's what you do in the game
All right, give me up go for great you fucking noob go for great you
Fucking noob. I want to open up my card pack. Then don't I have like more card pack?
About like two of them. How do I open them? Did I already open them? Well, they haven't been delivered yet. Oh, right
Okay tomorrow morning. Let's go. All right, save the game and then I'm gonna just turn the valve, you know, go forward a full day
skip a hundred years
Okay. All right. I will skip forward
100 years
Pikachu's just a fucking dusty skeleton in the corner. Oh fuck. No, no, no, I don't it's got like rug burn on my fucking hand
Okay, let's go. Wait, no, you can't see just don't flash you guys with like a blue screen like I do sometimes
All right calendar. Here we go date and time. So today's date is now
315 316
What wait, but we was not programmed to go more than 2035
They what happens in 2035 when you can't do this anymore. This is the fucking end of the universe
Alright, so it's been it's been 15 years. Let's see
Alright, it's 315 and the time is 5 a.m. Go to 12
Okay, well just go to 12
Okay, the time is gonna be midnight. Wait, what happens? Okay. Hold on a minute here
I can't go further than this. What happens give yourself a little bit of time. Okay, ten minutes
Let's sit now get in there. It's on of the final day
Yes, progressive scan we is the new Mayan calendar, okay Pokemon company. Hey Pokemon channel
Oh
Data has been loaded. You're Seth today is 12 31
2035 the time is 11 51 p.m. Is this correct? Yes
Pikachu isn't here
You could use him like an apocalypse bunker
This is a bunch of shit little like Campbell's fucking tomato soups behind him
Because you seems to have taken a big liking to your home set that Pikachu is obviously taking a big liking to you, too
How about giving it a nickname?
Pikachu
Then my name it's been 15 years
Well, then Seth your reports are very very helpful. Thanks to reports like yours. Pokemon channel is constantly evolving and growing
Here. Here's a here's $50. Oh
Almost forgot said you're painting a shitty program sold at the auction. It's sold for a hundred and six dollars
It's the delivery bird. Wait, it's deliver. This is different delivery word
15 years late
Pizza, what have you done?
All right, let's open up these card packs left a motion card the giggly buff single card
Wait, this is jiggly puff in there. There's a giggly puff the chikorita
the Oddish the
Meryl
okay, open this one was it this one all that the wheezing the
Natu
the
probat
gloom
Who would you get the doll? Look at all the stuff we got
Don't open them. Don't open them
switched over to the e cans frame
Got a lot of stuff. I mean, it's a good thing. We selected fucking reduce boxes by having all the items come in the same
Amazon box. All right, where are we going? Look at the cards. Yeah, I know
Not look at those. Oh, here we go. Go back. All right, that was that one's a good one
Sucks no, no, no, no, no one also sucks. That's cool. That's kind of cool. Pretty cool. Pretty cool
Yeah, this is a gold one full
There's one sick left, huh? I like that one. All right. This is like this is a crack jiggly puff
I like this one a lot. Maybe saw all of them right up more. We haven't seen I think this is the best one
Boom it's the best one. I'm Jack. Oh you mean like
Take life. Um, I don't know. Well, let me go check it after this. I gotta go watch the art channel hatch up
No, no, wait, no, no, no, not yet. All right, here we go. Miracles of art study. There's a clock right there. Oh shit
Hey, what's that? That's not even the right one
Fucking rip me off
It's just like a slightly different color pick up. All right, you're gonna brick your weed. It's 1158
What happens when what happens it detected the name shitty
12 a.m. Happy new year. Will it go to 1201? He's looking at the meteor
Oh
Well, they am what is it it wants to learn how to turn on the TV sure
We only got like 25 seconds left
1201 which button turns the TV on this one check the gear saved see what year it thinks it is
All right. What year do you think it is? It seems as it wants to watch TV with you. Oh, yes, we will watch TV
If it says 2036 then what happens does that mean that the GameCube was programmed to be more than the Wii
So what happens when I go back to the Wii? I've not watched it to the end. No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay safe report
memory cards body
Okay, they just be safe. Do you playing the game?
No
Raptured
Like fucking
Floating up behind him. He's just it's just so enthralled by the fucking Pichu brothers episode 3. Oh
Oh my god, what year is this? It is. Whoa. Oh
So I checked the Wii I'm gonna check the Wii. Let me check. I can check the Wii. Oh
Fucking hot shit
Fuck it's
1204 a.m
The day before what day is it in here wait go to the Wii calendar Wii calendar Wii calendar
I'm right the message board
Calendar just I have seen the same messages. What should it be like a fucking message in here, dude, you know what?
I'm gonna write a fucking message
I'm gonna write a message on like July fucking fourth of like 2030
This thing I probably won't own this thing forever
I might just like I might give this to somebody or this could be in the hands of
Some other entity but me and then and they'll get they'll get that message. All right, let's see what happens here
No, but with what dates I think it is now. It's no it
Yes, it is correct. We're still a day forward on the GameCube, but we're a day back on the Wii you're invited your friends over
I
Wait, I
May have just soft-locked the rest of the game for myself. I can't go forward anymore
I cannot skip a day anymore. It's got to be in real time now. Oh
That's not good just go back and then forward well, let's watch a new TV
All right, I don't want to watch that it's fucking boring. What's this one?
The egg channel go backwards and then go forward
So I'm gonna scramble the game's brain. That's up. Okay
About five minutes to hatch who's in the egg. Who's in an egg?
TV. Oh, that's explaining it up top. Okay, it's explaining it. Can I change my answer? Oh, there's the egg
Okay, choose your cookie
Which one Pikachu which one you want?
Up right top left bottom left, which one bottom left my fortune is
People from different countries might have different custom
Fuck I can't get another one. Wait, there's another one egg channel. Oh, no, wait three minutes to have
We actually have I don't want I don't want to watch this
I don't want to watch the p2 brothers part 3. This is I this I don't
See what covers with his nose with the eyes since Garfield what does Garfield look like? Oh what I need a picture of Garfield
Okay, hold on. Yes. It's this big like fucking this big like Colonel Sanders mustache
It goes like this his eyes go up here. Okay. Hold on. Oh fuck. It's all right. I'll just draw over
Okay, then it's uh, he's got like an eyelid here and then another eyelid right here now. We need white
Pink nose and he's got that that big mustache thing. I go thinner
This is yellow a little bit thicker than that. Looks like he's got like broken fucking glasses
It looks like it looks like he's like smashed his face into a wall with glasses. Oh
So it's a doctor of wily. Oh
Fuck that hurt a lot. That hurt a lot
Oh, and then he's got like these weird like things coming off his head. Hold on. I gotta fix this
Orange. Okay, you're like under his ear. They go like this. He's got this like I'm telling you go look at a picture of Garfield
He's got these weird like lines on his head. No, they're not whiskers. They're like under above his ear. They're on his ears
Okay, give him a sword
Like a big cigarette in his mouth. Okay
No, no, no, no, no. No. Okay. But how do I undo then? He has like the lines these like lines
They go like this. Okay, and then he has you got like some shit under here. These are orange, too
He looks gross
Screen man, okay now give him a sword
No, it's gonna be like purple and that's the color of the right. It's gonna be like this
That lightsaber is better a lightsaber is better. He's gonna have Obi-Wan Kenobi saber
Acid it looks like he's like throwing acid. Okay, good
Do you have two lightsabers one Obi-Wan Kenobi one Luke Skywalker?
Do I even need to ask that question watch his ear this way he's holding this one back
There's a little bit of trajectory here. See like we'll go. I mean like he's like that's his arms back like this back
So it's gonna be like that. See how it's like it's back. He's pulling it back. See how do I undo? That's fine
That's fine. It's fine. It'd be a little hard. That's all right. That's all right. Okay, so he's like
Both up. This is just like I'm making like this is like just like fucking fan art from Newgrounds in like
2000 we're gonna have
This shit hold on wait, what's this?
secret
No, and that's uh, no, is it looks kind of like buildings. Don't fucking accidentally put it on his head. Ain't the rest. Oh
Okay, I was just fucked it all up. This is like that now down here. We can do this shit
It's kind of like brass. Okay, let's watch it up a little bit. Oh
Shit that's his foot down there. I gotta fix that
I
Gotta make this clean. This is the only one I'm putting any time into
Do the foot. Oh shit
There we go. All right, uh, let's go to the foot and we're done in the five o'clock shadow
I can't do that right now. It's hard. Where's prequel shitty Yoda. Okay. So there we go
Hold on. Let me clean this up. Give him a sans. I I am NOT gonna give him a fucking sans
I okay. Remember, this is a map from worms. Wait, wouldn't his mouth be up here like right here. This is incorrect
It'd be like yeah, this is wrong. Why is this different shade?
This is a different shit. Why is this different shade of orange wrong orange? There's only one orange. Did I get to the whole thing now?
He looks sickly. That's okay. All right. That's all right. That's fine
It kind of looks like he's gripping chair chair chair chair in the chair in armpit hair
Why do you want to give him armpit hair?
He's wearing a diaper. Oh, no. No, he's not wearing a diaper. He's not wearing a diaper
I'm vetoing that one. He's not my veto that one. Okay. Give me the there we go. All right, there's there is now
We got right here. No, I'm not doing that
Yes, it is no he's not no no, nope, nope, that's enough save this painting would you like to display a poster? Yes
Garfield doesn't have nipples. I need you to look up an image of Garfield and you tell no, okay
All right. That's not even a picture of that character. That's me messing around on the on the that's even worse on another Pokemon
This is a new original character. Those are not lightsabers. They are
they are
beam spears and I said I said obi-wan I
Said those names that was just me referencing what they could look like
Someday Gar Vader. Well, he doesn't know he's not sick. How about just cover Gar Vader
Original character. No, it's keeping Gar Vader
Original character. No, oh D one. Oh D one Kenobi gar. Oh D one Kenobi
That's fucking terrible. Just keep it. Oh, do you want gar gar of things?
It's not even Odie in the picture. I'm just playing this in your house
All right, have you finished watching this yet? Dad was busy not even watching TV anymore
Oh shit Bugleberry. I heard Bugleberry eating a spider
Attacking me. What have we not seen? Oh, wait, the egg. What was it? It was Bulbasaur. Oh
I don't know why my brain's bright for some reason. I thought that was like a
How many bars you have on a cell phone? I was like was it what if this Wi-Fi signal losing my mind
Look, it was like it was like right down there. It was in the perfect spot
I was like, why is it a Wi-Fi on here? All right
Blaziken battles with greater
intensity when it faces a
tough
opponent it will
battle while
intense flames shoot from its wrists
Marowak grew ferocious by
Wielding bone as a weapon. However, it is thought to have been
weak
originally
Don't yawn buddy Pikachu status buddy Pikachu
All right, so let's it's currently 12 36 a.m. It's been 40 minutes. Holy shit
Hey a new viewer Eric new viewer here. Can you explain this game to a newbie, please? Thank you and love the stream
Sure, it's a game where you watch TV
That's all you do. Nothing else in the whole game
Seth is engrossed in TV. We're getting a new Pokemon minis. All right, what's next? Oh
We've watched all the shows
What about the news?
Move out of the way you're blocking the TV. I don't want to watch this what you're blocking the TV
Don't take the bus. All right, let's go take the bus
Oh
With me let's go take the bus. Hey new viewer here. What's the shit stain story one time?
Oh, I shit my pants and I didn't I did I after washing the underwear
I didn't get rid of it. Ha ha ha ha tell it again. Tell it again. Tell it again
Tell it again. Tell it again. Tell it again. Tell it again. Tell it again. Tell it again. This one time
Oh my god this one time I shit my pants and I good didn't clean it up for something
What's this?
Hello again
TV filming is underway. Where we go. We're on TV
How do we get on TV?
What's this all right Seth found the three leaf clover looking for a four leaf clover
No four leaf clover. Oh
Pog I guess
Who's this guy?
Why does it look like I drew you?
Volbeat gather and draw what sort of patterns in the night sky?
Geometric pattern
Here BB
BB BB BB BB BB
BB I don't like this one
Now what about a Mario enemy?
Duskull don't I low-run it is said that if duskull
Gives chase it will follow the target till what comes up with the morning sun
I
Can't hear it if they go
It's oh, it's like I'm like a full probably four and a half seconds behind
What's it doing to me?
ripping me
Okay, this was like pulling me around
He just wanted me to pet him. You guys need to relax
All right, so I have to what I have to
How do I go forward in time I have to go backwards in time and then go forwards in time
Why do you look like a dream person? I don't know
This is 1 a.m. Yeah, we'll probably not be screaming much longer
Like that get the egg right
They get the egg question, right? Please. Please look what would you guys like submit that somewhere patch it?
Well, what about the what no what what's going on here? What's the other one?
I mean, I missed it. I plagiarized this. Oh, oh, it's just he has Garfield
Pokemons this section is pretty cool
It's all
Pokemon
This is really really really this is very interesting
Same one that I drew with the lightsabers and everything. No, I don't see anything
Wait, where is this? I'm trying to find it with like the cigarette coming out of the mouth and the lightsabers
Well, you got it there is I want to see this is that's fucking hilarious. Okay, I'm not clicking on any more links
I'm not clicking on any more links. I was like that was that's gonna fuck me up for life. Check the art channel
What are you talking about? You ruined it? Oh, okay. I thought you talked about like the art channel on the website
Yeah, you guys got some fucked up images. I'm not I'm not there's nothing gonna be here. Wait a minute. What I didn't sell this
But even everybody I'm your host smuggle
Where are you getting this definite
Quiet
the decisiveness is
Losing with originality the artist demonstrates an original creative vision unseen in others. See it's an original character
It's not anything related to Disney or or Jim Davis. Neither one of those original
OC
This is a repost. What the fuck mods? I can't believe you like I like the fuck you one
All right, I think I'm done. I think I'm done. I think I'm done. I think I'm out of here
I think this is I think this is where I have this day as be done. I can't I don't think I can handle this anymore
Save the game. I'll save it. He hates this what I mean, I don't didn't say that. I don't hate this we talking about
He's never gonna watch TV with Pikachu ever again to find a rating on this game
I mean the video game is a tube
But like it's like the interesting the fun factor is like an eight
so I mean
It's fun. It's like funny and it's it's a wholesome. It's just watching TV with Pikachu
I give it as I give it up. I get a seven. I give it a seven for
On the moon. Who is it? I wouldn't pay attention. What are you gonna do? What am I playing switch?
I'm gonna play Animal Crossing when it comes out
All right, just turn it off
Thank you. Turn it off. Let me just like spell this one more time. Okay, I'm gonna save it
I'm fucking gonna get some food. Somebody said pizza like an hour and a half ago. It's their fault
Somebody said pizza like an hour an hour and a half ago and now it's your fault. Toxic paint cube
The new programs are scheduled to begin at uh today at 5 a.m
Because I can't report I can't skip ahead. I'm soft-walled. I have to go back and then go forward
Everyone you spent like two hours on one level of pinball game. I don't like to remember
How'd she get up there
He's saying
Nintendo
You said you'd eat the disk. I'm not gonna eat this. All right, I'll see you guys later
So plan is tomorrow on tomorrow. I'm probably gonna
Do tomorrow well, I want to you're gonna hate this you're gonna hate this but um, I
Know you a lot of you guys don't hate this. I want to uh, I'm I want to play Binding of Isaac again
You're gonna hate this
Again, I'm like addicted to it. I want to like play it so bad. I so badly want to play it
I'm like it. I've scratched the itch and now it's like I want to play I'm gonna play Binding of Isaac again tomorrow
He's addicted either that or
There's one other thing that I might do as well
It depends on what uh, it depends on how I feel
Not Nancy Drew. Oh you fucking liar
We'll see. I'm not sure yet, but I do want to play at least at least
Like two to four hours of Binding of Isaac tomorrow
We'll do something else but I want at least four hours of Binding of Isaac tomorrow or two hours at least at least
Two hours, you understand? I'm compromising with you. That's a whole screen. That's not two hours
It's like 20% of a stream like 30% of one stream two hour
But my average stream time is like six to eight hours two to three hours is like 20 to 40 percent like 30%
I'm playing it. That's all there is to it
You said four to six
I said two to four but play purple place look at like what you can't even play that game
That's like that games undown loadable. Yes, you can I don't think you guys want me to play purple place
That's funny for five seconds and then oh, no, he's playing fucking purple place. I'm gonna leave
I'll go do something else for like an hour. All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow. We'll do a couple things tomorrow. Let's say
When it's German crap
Within the next hundred years I'm not gonna destroy this he's like fun in cute games are like collectibles
I don't care if I didn't like the game not this one the one before it
I actually like the one before it but I was gonna eat the disc in my anger
He's a cool that nicely the collect. Look at like eat of this. I'm not gonna break anything
Wendy's Wendy's I
Don't I don't get this what what does that have to do with anything?
What does this Wendy's image have to do with anything? It's because I hit the mic. Oh
God damn it. Okay, let's go back to a little bit earlier today
Almost just about six and a half hours ago. We had dark soul 250 from dark soul
Here's some sober bits last night was something anyway
I do like whiskey a lot not more than vodka
But Jamison equals good Johnny Walker equals cigars and assholes
Let's think about opinions everyone's got just like how
You have one too. We should do 50 lm man. Thanks for the five dollars
Sound the call to war Shogun German and some opinions are wrong say every say assholes
You thought that's the thing. You thought I was gonna say that next part. Nope. Thanks with the five dollars lm, man
Hey yen when thanks for the 250. It is my birthday today. Happy birthday yen when
I'm almost as old as you but younger by a few years
So you're in the post you're in the post 30, you know
It's like started drawing this in hopes that I would finish before my birthday, but I ran out of time
ran out of time
Hope that I could use this as a bribe in order to receive an exclusive rats birthday song
This is the sandwich. Is this like the dirty sandwich? Let's see. Yeah, it is
This is the dirty sandwich. I'm just show it on screen
Well dirty as an old as an old
Get it on here almost done. This is fucking really good
Yeah, that's the that's the turkey sandwich that sat in the car for like six and a half hours or in a day or something
The oblivion sandwich. Yeah, that's fucking incredible though. It's so good. It's so fucking good
Thank you for this and happy birthday and you want to spell you want to rats?
Let's see if I can get it here we go. Hey, happy birthday. Have a birthday again when
I'm the match me
Just found one. It is we just ran by it was pretty wild. That's kind of a problem
Where they coming in from but thank you again. Thanks for the insanely talented artwork. You got you got some skill here real skill
Happy birthday. Hope it's a good one. Oh shit. I lost my fucking I lost my stream. I lost my stream
There it is. Hey LM, man another five dolls from LM, man
Jerma sama with this legendary skill in leading an army of
Conscripted as she garu. Have you ever considered playing the total war Shogun games?
My brain is way too small for those. I'm capable of throwing a pinball against the wall and getting angry
I I do not have the patience to play any of those games like that
I've seen a lot of people say dude, you should play civilization. It would be so much fun
Man, you should check out
Europa, whatever it's called. Do you know what's it called your Europe? What's it called? What's that one called?
Is this like three of them, right? Yeah, Europa universe sales. Yeah, I've heard that I've heard
What's the other one? There's another one. That's really popular. What the hell is it called?
Crusader Kings that there it is. Yeah, those games take
Like dozens of hours to even understand how to play them correctly
I would get annoyed and bored and frustrated in the first four hours and it would be I
Couldn't I would just lose my mind. I just don't have the brain patience for games like that
Even on my own time something like that is like hey, you wanna play Crusader Kings. I'd be like no
No, not in a million years. Like I wouldn't even do that on my own time even like it before streaming
That's something I just wouldn't play. I need to throw rocks at people. I mean
I gotta roll a pinball rock into a guy. That's that's pretty much what you saw today was the extent of most of the
Strategy games you'll see me play on this channel. What about stronghold 2?
Total war Warhammer total Warhammer 2 is easy to learn maybe but we're talking about me
We are talking about me
But probably not you'll you'll probably never see a game like that on this channel and that's when I could be really certain of
Wembley TTV, thanks for the 250 if you want to play a better voice-activated military game find a copy of Tom Clancy and war
I don't think the PC steam version is voice-activated though. So find a ps3 or Xbox free
Xbox version if you want to try it. I love microphone games. They're fun
General ours. Thanks for the fourteen dollars fourteen hundred bits from general ours, Germany
Where did you get that flint water? What do you mean flint water? Is that what they have on the shelves are you talking about?
I'm drinking coffee. I'm drinking coffee. It's coffee. It's not it's not
It's coffee. It's good. I like it. No, but they're nothing on the shelves anymore. That's why I've got I got that
Hey, I bought some of this Fiji water cuz it's the only thing that fucking was existed people go buy all the
Regular bottled water and they just and they leave the Fiji like a shit like I gotta buy like a case of Fiji
There's nobody's gonna buy the case of Fiji. It's good though. I mean, I love this stuff. It's great
It's really good, but I don't don't really want to buy cases of it. Anyways
Desoids Dutch capture, but thanks for the thousand bits new drinking game
Take a shot every time German says press forward. I would advise against doing that
Definitely, but it's not a good idea would advise against doing that
Sir linkerton, thanks with five dollars. Hey German glad to make it to a stream usually watch on YouTube
Thanks for giving us all a distraction from the scary times. The world is in right now
Would there be another keep talking stream with Joel? Oh, probably not
We'll probably move on to something else if we ever play something again
If we ever ever monkey ash German Pluto if we ever why do you say that ever does that mean?
He means he's never gonna play with him again. He must hate Joel. I think he hates Joel. I think he hates Joel
He said ever
Yeah, so we'll probably when we ever do something again
I'll probably do something else new games come out. They're worth playing
He punched Joel I did not do that I didn't do that you're a liar and you're making that up new games aren't coming out
Yes, they are. It was like three or four new games coming out over the next
Few months a furry. Oh, I missed this. This is a lot of money Freudian weapon. Thanks for the $40
4,000 bits from Freudian weapon. That's that's just shy of fucking $50, dude. Thank you
Doom and Resident Evil 3 got delayed off. Really? It's unfortunate
They say hey Jerma
I just want to say that I appreciate you streaming things are getting kind of scary in the world as you know
The fact that I can still tune into your streams with some laughs definitely helps bring so much needed comfort. Thanks so much
Love you in chat. Yes, wash your hands everyone. Yes
Take some precautions when you do anything when you go anywhere
Try to limit the amount that you go out
To especially the places that have a lot of people in them, especially if you're in an area that you know, I've seen
Cases there's some countries that are in lockdown right now. Just be careful and be smart
Yeah, well, like I said the other day and yesterday too. Hopefully this blows over pretty soon
hopefully we can get ahead of this because
It's been a while since something like this has happened, right?
What was the last the last big kind of scary pandemic was but h1 h1 n1 stars or something
But not this big. Yeah, 2003 Ebola, but I don't think Ebola was this
Widespread around what was I don't think I don't remember it being like that. Was it not that I remember
I mean like Disney World is closed. That's
Not that's not even close to what how scary, you know
Well that not even what I mean not even close like they're they closed Disney World
Disney World has never been closed ever in the history of it ever being opened except for only think I think two or three days
So this is I guess enough to have to warrant doing something like that
Last time Disney World was closed was on 9-eleven
I mean that you don't just close it just I mean the whole park is you can't even go but like
Hopefully this is all over soon and we can kind of get back to normal over the next few months
When summertime kind of really rolls around here, especially in the US hopefully
Cases die down and it can you know, we can move on. Hope so, but be careful Saints got robbed
Thanks for the five dollars just five dollars. Thank you Saints got robbed all the list goes
Thanks for the three dollars and watching your constant since 2011
Your streams have helped me get through a lot of rough patches, especially recently also your now
Withered muscles helped encourage me to get fucking huge while I'm still somewhat young though lately
I've been eating a tahini paste and doing bicep curls for YouTube sub celebrations and I never felt better about myself
Thank you for the near decade of content and for always striving to be the best gamer
You can be much love. Good luck to you. I never condoned that I never told you to anybody to do that
Do not do that. Are you doing that on your own? Good luck. Thank you
Thank you who sell juniors for the five dollars funny streamer people happy
Noka Noka, thanks with three dollars German love seeing you play Pokemon channel today your Viva pinata streams
Maybe remember it being a game. I always wanted it as a teen. I actually went and bought a copy
I hope to see you stream it more. It's so
Chaotically cute cute games on stream is always great. Have a good day. You too. You will see the return of Viva pinata
I have the second one ready to go. Just need to pick a day to do it a plimbo. Thanks for the three dollars Pokemon
Ruins my brain to the point that it made me enter my credit card information and give you money
I'm sorry to hear that peaceful Haley. Thanks for the 250
Derma, can you admit you farted? It's okay
We all shit ourselves from time to time that didn't I didn't but it sounded like it and that's funny
Peaceful Haley again. Thanks for 250
Derma you um, you obviously don't know your Star Wars lore
Obi-Wan saber has always been blue. He only used a green saber once when he's spoiler. I'm not reading spoilers
Luke used Anakin's blue saber and he made his own saber, which was green shaking my head
Jerma, come on if you need to know Star Wars lore come to me. I wasn't I wasn't doing Star Wars
Lord, that was a fucking beam spear
That's why I said it incorrectly because that wasn't that's not a reference to any Disney related properties
But thanks for the five dollars
Return that shirt. No, I will continue to wear it and pretend to be a fan of the show
Movies and the movies and the show there's a show I could say that there's a show
There's a show a loopy FA. Thanks for the thousand bits loopy. No message just ten fucking dollars
Let's roll the credits janitor is gonna come sweep by you here. Here come the credits. Thanks for watching
Thanks for sticking around. We'll see you tomorrow for
More stuff. Thanks everybody. I want to play Binding of Isaac. It's fun and
I scratched it and I have to keep scratching it
Also, there's a couple of the things I want to do. We'll see what happens tomorrow. I will see you tomorrow
Thanks again, and thank you to
Thragnel for the five dollars buy better coffee instead of that curdling swill from yesterday
No, okay
It's that is a nice cold brew that coffee that I'm drinking is a is a cold brew that you keep in the fridge
The reason why I look so gross is because I put almond milk in it and I sit here and I drink it and I sip
On it for an hour and what happens is the almond milk separates from the coffee and looks like shit
It's not the coffee. It's the almond milk. I'm putting in it, but I like almond milk
I like putting on the milk in my coffee. Oh, that's why it looks like that. It's a nice cold brew
What you're seeing why not mix it with a spoon because I don't have a spoon up in my office in fucking quotes
I don't have a spoon up here. I mean I got what kind of have us
What am I gonna put what I'm gonna do with it? I'm not gonna put my finger in it. No, that's gross
Hey frozen Thor 516. Thanks for the 250. Hey German. Thanks for the stream as usual
You said you never played any of the Pokemon games before
What if you consider playing them perhaps the new one that came out for the switch with silly rules such as chat picks
What Pokemon you can use something like that again? Thanks for the stream and keep being awesome. I will try
Glad you think that right to drive better I can be better and always be better right? Um, I don't I home
I don't really want to play Pokemon
Pokemon is
It's cool. I respect the franchise, but I don't have in any interest in it at all
I really don't zero like unless it's a TV game or like take pictures with Pikachu
I don't actually really care at all about the main line Pokemon game
I just never have and I never do and I never will it's just the way it is. Sorry. It's the way it is
But thank you for the suggestion silent serenity. Thanks for the 250 as others have said, I'm glad you chill here with
I'm glad to chill here with you guys while we're quarantined video games are a great time killer
I've been playing the city skylines over the past couple of days and I definitely recommend it for wasting time
I actually planned on streaming city skylines
Should I we talked about that a few weeks ago like a month or two ago, right that be fun
Could I can I handle that I want to be very clear about this
Can I handle that like can I handle that one? Absolutely not. Yes, do it tomorrow
Can I fucking handle that? Is that like a I get to sit there and learn the whole game for like 12 hours
It's easier than sim City doesn't take that long. It's good. There's some systems kind of need to learn
It's 30 minutes to learn for it's easy to pick up. It's easy. It's super simple. Okay. Okay, we'll do it tomorrow
All right, we'll do it tomorrow. We'll play city skylines tomorrow, but I'm getting my I'm getting my fucking couple hours of binding of eyes again
We'll do that tomorrow. And that's the end. Thanks for watching. We'll see you tomorrow. Same time around
3 4 p.m. Pacific and
Goodbye and good night
Sergio but right at the end 250 got back from work to see you still stream and I had a co-worker act totally normal
I'll shift and start violently coughing into the trash can next to him. Jesus. I told him. Hey, I love you
But please don't cough on the line. We had to decontaminate the entire kitchen mid shift. That's shit scary
Glad I could share a laugh after today today. That's not good
It's gotta be careful. I mean at that here's the thing though
There's there's there's there's like coughing and sneezing and there's like normal stuff and it's like is that what's what's wrong with that person?
You don't want to get too
Too into it and to like hysteria, you know, I mean that that's how it's somebody just sneezed in this in this place
I am I gotta get the fuck out of here. You know what I mean? You just gotta be careful
We it's it's a like the web jacket just said it's allergy season 2
so
There is enough to be concerned about for sure
But we just we got to be careful with I know it's scary and it's it's not a fun time for really anybody
But we don't also want to feed into the like the absolute hysteria, but you never know
I know but I know but still but it's the same reason you got people buying 30 fucking
rolls of toilet paper like they like I've seen the images of people that got like a
Full a full closet of like 5,000 rolls of toilet paper. It's like that's that's all that's a lot. That's a lot
People buy like 10 gallons of milk like milk goes bad in like not even 12 days, right?
Like what are you buying 10 gallons of milk?
Who's gonna drink all that milk in the next like week or two? Just freeze it
But what people people are freezing milk?
If I ever put milk in my freezer
I'm gonna freeze nine gallons of milk and you got like the people that are buying all this shit
And then they're selling it on like the internet for like fucking a thousand percent more
It's like God if people are just trying to get like a one stack of toilet paper
Now you're talking about they might have to it's not there because everyone's been
Panicking and buying it all and you got these guys that have going in there and buying it to sell it to those people that
Didn't get there in time at like a
20,000 percent premium it's like Jesus
I always end up in like a pandemic aren't we supposed to like help each other
You know I'm saying like that's that that seems a little strange
No, I feel the same. Okay
When there was like a baseball game or something and it's like, oh, maybe like three or four of us will go to the game
Oh, okay. Yeah, how about your tickets? Oh, there are none left. Oh, there are no more tickets left
Oh looks like we're gonna walk out to the front of fucking Fenway Park
Hey, I got tickets for you 200 bucks for the fucking nosebleeds
Okay, thanks cool. But what's that again? Those those are like those are like forty one dollar seats
boomer ball
You're with a communist
What that's what that does not communist?
seeing people but
70 fucking containers of like
Cottonel in the back of their car is like you go dude like that. Sorry. I must be a communist
Hey
Sorry, excuse me ma'am and sir
I'm a communist and I don't agree with the fact you have your whole entire fucking Subaru outback full of toilet paper
That's not that's not the one it is
He's going on a socialist rant. No, I have not that's not what that is not even close
No, don't twist it. Don't twist it on me. Don't twist it. Don't twist it on me. Don't twist it
I don't want to hear from any of you starting to twist. What's happening to me? What's going on?
Don't twist don't I don't want anybody to twist this on what's happening?
Sorry, I had something all right, I don't want you don't twist it on me. That's not what I was saying
Anyways, have a great day. Have a great rest of your night
Go very juice. Thanks for 250 right at the buzzer here. No, like for real German. It's okay. You can admit that you farted
We all do it there's no reason to be embarrassed about it
I mean not all of us part live on stream in front of thousands of people a small percentage of which may be
Into farts. I mean that would be fucking embarrassing, but you know, it's okay if you do. Why did I read that out loud?
Okay
Goodbye. Good night. See you tomorrow. Have a fucking wonderful rest of your evening
City skylines and binding of Isaac tomorrow. See you soon. Good night. Take care. Bye. Sorry. There was a delay on the bike