So we're gonna we're gonna be playing more of the sims one, which is fun.
And I'm hopefully you guys understand what I just said.
Oh, you pretended you were doing this, Mike. It's been beautiful the entire time you've been here.
I'm in one minute. Everyone needs to relax. Do a face reveal.
I don't, I don't. All right. Don't, just don't feed into the trolls. That's what they are. They're
trolls. Don't feed into the trolls. I'm not gonna play your game. I'm not gonna feed into the trolls.
He's naked. I am. I might be the only streamer on this whole website that streams naked
and won't get banned for it. Imagine they catch me on a technicality or something.
What are they? Hold on. I gotta protect. Let me protect myself very quickly. I'm not naked.
I'm just partially nude. The difference. No, I'm not in a bathtub. I promise. Juggles, juggles, juggles.
Yeah, I know. I'm like, you can hear that. He's in the bath. We're gonna play more of the sims one,
obviously. I had a lot of fun with it. Gonna actually try to make real progress today.
Had to burn a whole house down and leave a small child without parents. That was not my intention
when I started the stream yesterday. Hope everybody's doing. I forgot to say well.
Hope everybody's doing. I actually kind of like that. Hope you're doing. Hope everybody's doing.
I like that. I think I'm gonna use that. Hope you're all doing. Yeah, I like it.
I think it's good. Did I tweet? Why are you live? Because I'm a streamer. Once a week streamer.
Sorry about that. We fixed that before we get started. Why say lot words? What? Why say lot word?
Like what do I say? I don't know. It's either you guys or the wall, okay? If I did not have a stream
come on and just talk, I would likely just be pacing around and just like talking about like
my favorite foods and stuff. I would call my mother. I would talk to my mother. I'd be like,
I would talk to my mother like four or five times a week. Of course, by the way, I talked to my mother
once a week. When was the last time you called your mother? Do it today. When was the last time
you called your damn mother? She's waiting for your phone call. That's what you don't understand.
Say hello. Call her right now. No, I'm not gonna do that to my mother. That's like a weird prank.
Bring up my mom. Oh, hi, Jeremy. Oh, hey, mom. Oh, hey, you're on stream. Like, oh, thanks for the call.
You're using me as a prop. You're using me as a set piece for your fucking clown stream. Thank you.
Good to hear from you, son. I'm not using my mother as a prop for that one time when they,
when I had the dinner stream and that was a disaster. So I'm not doing that again.
All right, you guys ready? Are we all here? I hope so. Are you here? All right, so we left
how do we leave off? I'm excited. I like this game. Very hard, but I like it. So we left off
at, you're talking about, no, it wasn't. Hair reveal. All right, you guys ready? You've
ruined an entire family and made a child insane. No, that's not what happened. Go adopt Caramel.
I don't think I can do that. This is The Sims 1. You can't do that in The Sims 1.
Okay, here we go. What was the last thing I was doing? This house is pretty sick, actually. I
like this place. Friends. That's right, right, right. Friends. And I don't want to be a chef,
too. Let's get some, let me open up my fucking, I don't care anymore. I'm just doing it on stream.
And the acting career. That's right. Well, first things first. We gotta sleep. That was a bugle
berry. That just, that sounded like bugle berry. Where the fly is coming from? What's going on
here? I'm leaving. We just got here. Oh, I get it. Okay. Hurry, get out of bed. It just took me like
an hour to turn around and get out of the bed. Did I make that noise? It wouldn't be out of
the ordinary. Yuck. I do that shit. Oh, God. Get the, all right. Water. Don't forget to do this.
I think a lot of you guys severely underestimate just the amount of noises that I make on a daily
basis. I'm not even like aware of it sometimes. I just kind of, it's like I'm doing like my own
soundtrack. Oh, we know. All right, let's go. I kind of don't even want these. I'd rather have
statues. What's wrong? Oh, fun. All right. Go to watch, go turn the TV, watch TV for a little
while. And then we're going out on the town. I like to imagine you would do those noises at an
inappropriate time, like at a funeral. Um, no. Sit down and watch the TV. You doy, doy, doy at the
funeral. That would be so. No, that would be me giving the, um, was it the eulogy? The eucanoo.
Just prank me. No, that would be me giving the eulogy. And everybody at the funeral would all
do it at the same time to honor that person. Like it would be me. If I, okay, if I'm dead,
whoever's doing the eulogy, if you're hearing this right now, you need to get the entire, um,
funeral session to do doy, doy, doy in unison to honor me. And it has to be loud enough
so that at least one or two people in the, in the, I don't know, the church or wherever we are,
are holding their ears, going like, think about having that in a church, how much that would just
bounce off the walls. I think we might summon like a demon if we did that. That's probably how
you do it. Just like doy, doy, doy, doy, doy, doy, doy doy. Stop it, stop it. You're going to summon him.
Don't, please. A demon. Venus music. That's right. That's going to resurrect me.
Well, people are doing that. I start slowly like lifting out of the coffin.
This that's terrifying. All right. Take a shower. Is this clean? No, no, no, no flush the toilet and clean it
This is so stupid. Can I like go into like a like the text editor and make this not happen anymore?
I understand that people can be slobs, but i've i've never flushed the toilet like that's not a personality trait
That's seriously not a personality trait. He's depressed. You've never flushed. No, I mean, you know what I mean? Like i've never not
Flushed the toilet. He doesn't flush it for personal reasons. No, he's
It he just has like two neatness and that apparently means you don't flush toilets
You're doing the doi doi thing muffled in the coffin and that's the way to make everybody there
Well, that's the way how people know they have to do it. They just hear like he's in there everybody. Let's do it
Oh, okay. How many people would run out of there? That's like a we need to run out of here and get out
Oh quick dinner quick dinner quick dinner. Don't sir. Don't just like have they say there. Yeah. Oh, I need a food processor, too
I remember that I remember that food processor. It makes the food better. Where is it? There it is
Where can I put this right there? Hey those bills?
Oh, I only have 1200 bucks. I need to go gamble some more things that you should never say
Okay, never mind. Will you stream your funeral? I don't know
We're kind of in like a weird world with that like our generation
It's like the first generation that would probably think to do something like that, right?
And when I say our generation, I mean 18 to 34 i'm not even in that i'm not even there anymore
But i'm just gonna pretend I am I think we're the first ones that would actually do something like that
He's all placed like this
Okay, so the uh
The the delivery person I have never taken these in so they've just started to play a game
They put it on each one of these I didn't hear them blend in and they'd like fuck it with me
OCD mailman
No, I think it's I have not taken them in ever so instead of just putting them in the same spot
They're just like well fucking whatever i'm gonna have some fun
That's why that thing popped up and said that there's no more room
Okay, turn the cartoons off
Geez is there any more?
No, okay, clean this up and then I need to find I need to get a chef job, right?
Yeah, why are we playing it seriously now? Um, I don't know because I spent like four hours
Destroying an entire family
Last yesterday when we played I spent the first like four and a half hours like just actively ruining everything
I want to be a superstar and i'm gonna get there. I want to be a superstar chef musician. No, thanks
This house is fucked though. Why is the bathroom in the kitchen? It's not it's a different room animal care
Oh, I want to take it but I want to be a chef
Why do I care about being a chef so much? Why I don't understand why I just take the animal job
Why do I care about being a chef it's because hold on i'm doing the animal one there's a glass door on the bathroom
You should learn magic medicine I thought there was only because I have three skill points in cooking that's right business
Took you 30 minutes to stand up and sit down again
Politics, no, thanks
In fact, I want to like send like the I want to send like a thing back to that person
It just says just I want to I want to click the unsubscribe on that one. Let me know
Oh, okay
It just unsubscribe actually unsubscriber is just a big lie
And they don't actually do it and now they have you now
They have the info that you've actively clicked on one of their emails, you know what I mean?
I'd always like freak me out
They keep your info, but they take you off the mailing list
I need to go out again
I need to call somebody over and have somebody hang out with me
Info is worth more than you
You know
I don't understand that
Why is all of our why is all of our basic info like that's so?
So valuable
Is how old you are don't we have a census like why don't they just go like fucking download the census?
What are they actually doing? Why do they need to know? My name is jeremy elbertson. It's for it's for ads
You know once we started not caring about tv. They were just always gonna find a way to fucking get us
I always thought that advertisements were just gonna go away once nobody cared about tv anymore
Oh, no, why are you so obsessed with the census? When was the last time I said the word census on this stream?
A year ago, when did I say what was the last time I said I referenced the census?
Stop doing that. Hey, stop putting them in weird places. Just put them on the ground
Hire a maid. I don't have enough money to do that. I need to go get like a i'm gonna go i'm going to the casino
Oh, I remember what I was doing. I was gonna call somebody on the phone hang out and watch tv with them
I don't want to look for a job. All right, well then call somebody over. Where's there? Okay, aren't we friends?
Everyone's at work. Oh nice. Okay, she's coming over should I put
All right, this is not a good look in your pajamas at your computer while cartoons are playing in the background
I don't know if this is a great look for someone to come over for the first time. It's literally you
Yes, it is. Yes, except take off the top
That's a lip. That's actually me right now take this off, but I don't have cartoons blaring in the background
I have to get rid of these too. This is creepy
Oh
Oh shit. Oh, I can't get up right now
No, dude, i'm like the last i'm top 10 last 10 in pub g I can't get up
Oh, it's all right. I just i'll be out in a minute
Got him got him top eight fuck out here. Get the things closing things closing
Yeah, I don't want to fuck this up. Is that for me?
Wow
Oh, I can't just throw it in the trash
Shit, i'm sorry. Am I gonna throw it down the magician hole?
Wait, why did I not put it down?
Imagine handing somebody a gift and they walk around through their backyard with no shoes on why wouldn't they go in the house?
I haven't said anything. Ah, it's perfect
She's cheering me up
Oh, thanks
Oh, you're so nice. Thank you
Why is this not fulfilling my social there we go, okay talk about uh
Cats talk about dogs talk about gossip talk about interests
Just I need you to fill this bar. You like cartoons
All right, wait come sit down
Sit down over here
doesn't like cats
Doesn't like cats and doesn't like dogs. Oh man what no
Why
You don't like movies either. I don't like you. I don't like talking. Holy shit. Wait a minute. I'm gonna play the guitar
I'm gonna wow her. Oh, please
It's a giant coiled up dump in that toilet. I don't flush toilets make like
Lunch see it's at that this point where she's gonna walk out
And i'm gonna realize I didn't flush the toilet and i'm gonna come up with an elaborate way as to why that happened
And it wasn't me. I'm gonna so I I I would put that on my mother
I'll be like my mother was just here and she just like was in a hurry and like oh my my mother did that
What the hell?
Mom
Disgusting mom. What the fuck and then I would call my mother and be like mom. I had to throw you under the bus
I'm sorry, and she'd be like no, it's okay. Don't worry, honey. It's okay
Where'd she go omega little traitor?
Talk, please come sit on the couch and talk eat and talk
I don't like lifting weights. Not anymore. That's true. How can somebody be over for this long and I have
like
E on my gas tank. I don't understand. Can we just please sit on the couch and just have a conversation just don't care
Me she but I think she's gonna go swimming in the pool. All right, i'm going into
We're gonna talk
Delete the ladder. No, i'm not deleting the ladder. I'm not doing the thing you do in the sims. That's a funny joke
I'm gonna be in the bunging up shit in the pool
Okay, a huge shit is gonna float up and she's gonna see it and i'm gonna be like, oh my god
You just missed her. My mother did a big cannonball and it was a big splash
And then she shit she pooped and I was like mom, what the heck again?
You just missed her. Why can't I have any fucking friends?
Just get out. I got in the pool and she got out. She is avoiding me so bad. Why talk?
This is so weird. Why won't they talk? Is she just coming over to use my pool talk?
This is really weird. I hope I shit in this pool, please pee in the pool and have her sit
I'm still in she's getting out. She's going for where are you going? Am I getting out?
She's about to get on the computer. Oh shit. Oh, she's good. She's going to get my bitcoin hash password
Get her get her get out
Where am I?
That's just extra water from the pool
This is like when you go over your mom's friend's house because I missed that but it was probably really funny
It's zero. This person's been over all day fucking talk
Just crying
Oh my god, this is horrible. You don't like science. What do you like? What does this girl actually like?
I don't think she likes anything
This dog is smelling me
You like sunshine I like the sun
Oh my god, let me just tell you about the sun. I love when it goes behind the clouds
I love when it goes out. Oh me too. I love when the sun goes behind the clouds
I love when it gets the next overcast day. All right, talk about weather
Just keep them locked in this state
Okay, just sit here and talk you like ties I love ties
Hey, what do you like sunglasses? Oh my god, I love sunglasses
Like ties again. I love ties. Oh my god. Do you like you like the sun?
Yes, I love the sun and the rain
Do you like the sun? Yes. I love the rain too
What a boring conversation
We're we're okay, we're doing the the short
Like how's the weather kind of like you don't want to talk to somebody
You got like 30 seconds on the sidewalk. We're doing that for like four hours
Do you imagine bringing up to like the person in small talk on the sidewalk the weather like eight times
It'd be like holy shit
Somebody has to end this conversation. This is horrible. We're probably never going to talk ever again after this
Take a shower. No social is more important than ever now
Skunk is whatever
I what happened
I'm not gonna wake. I can't wake her up
What the fuck
Why can't I not wake her up?
When is she gonna wake up and leave?
I won't even I won't even wake her up and be like hey, there's a couch here
She's gonna wake up and okay. Thanks for coming
Why did she pass out? Why wouldn't she have left? All right, the the well is running dry right now
I need to really work on money
Give me a okay. I gotta take a career. I have to take something for me
You smell like shit and you pissed yourself and you're in a pool you invited her over
You never changed out of your pajamas
What the fuck just happened?
Why is everything in this game? I'm too depressed the sims universe has the shittiest plumbing. The plumbing is so bad
All right. I need to call the repairman
services made
services
Repairman just get them over here and hire them. Yes, ten dollars an hour
That's so much in like sims world for me because an hour it's gonna that's gonna that's gonna be like 150 dollars a day
From my account. I'm I can't afford this. It's 240 dollars a day. No, I think the only all right. No, I'm sorry
Call if you change your mind. You don't need to be 24 hours a day
Fifty dollars an hour. I don't have any money. This is gonna cost some fortune. All right. I need some you have to I need to do it
And then I'm gonna I'm gonna make you leave after fixing to the sink
All right, if I slip the repairman like enough like 20 bucks will he like take care of now?
He well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What are you doing? What are you?
What are you taking care of fix this to fix everything that he's fixing you do it the sink works now
Here's what we have to do
We have to make sure this guy doesn't walk around and like eat snacks and like read a book and stuff while he's here
Come on. Come on. Come on. All right, 50 bucks. He's leaving right? He's gonna have a pool. All right, we're good
Thank you. This is so tough. Okay, quick breakfast. My social is already awful again
Like I'm just trying to I gotta find a job by the way
That's what's causing the problems the piss that's outside is fucking ruining everything now I gotta I gotta hire the
Let's get a butler. Okay, I'm gonna get a butler for one day and I'm gonna invite that girl over again
And she'll walk in to be like, ooh
Butler. Oh
And then he I'm just gonna let him go the next day like thanks a lot, man
I appreciate actually, you know, why would I do that?
I could just pay one of my buddies like 20 bucks to do that
In fact, I know there are like movies like 90s comedy movies where it's like the guys like goofy friend is the oh
Yeah, but just just you look great. You look great. Just like act like you're my butler at the door
He's got like greasy hair and I like that throw it back and I try to make it look nice for that
Yeah, you stand for the door. All right. Thanks, buddy. You owe me a six-pack
Yeah, I do and then the guy ruins it somehow. I mean that's I could do that. It's an Adam Sandler movie
Yeah, I think that actually happens in three times in three different Adam Sandler movies
But anyways, I need to what was I doing something important E and then clean up the random pea puddles
The whole point of this venture is you have no friends. Yeah, but I'm I'll be all right. I'm working on it
Okay, get the pea out of the yard and then because look look at the room. Look at it
It's definitely because of all this piss in random places. I guarantee it. Look at that. Did that fix it?
All right, stop eating chips and just get out there. Why is it suck still what why it's zero
What is bringing this so far town it's the newspapers. Oh my god all this fucking mail
All right, you know something I'm gonna give you I'm gonna give you a real big hot take here
You ready for a real hot take? This is a real one
We have we like all talk about how much we care about the environment, right?
I do like I obviously want this planet to stick around for a long time. Everybody talks about this, right?
Yep, we still allow fucking whole magazines that you never ordered that you don't want that they somehow
Just sent to you for no fucking reason millions of pieces of just paper sent to everybody
But we don't we somehow don't want to get rid what I want to stop doing that when I go to my mailbox
It's been like this since I was 15 didn't matter where I was where I lived what state what city didn't matter
There was always like thick thick magazines that the household did not order that were just fucking sent to random houses
And they were thick real magazines big big chunky newspapers
Like what the fuck are we doing this for why do we still do this?
I think that's it. I think that's a huge problem. The whole the whole mail system is so fucked up. Like why do we have?
Oh, yeah, we'll just just blow out
like
28,000 magazines to everybody in the city and they're gonna throw them away not one single person reads those hand to God
I'm sitting here telling you hand to God. I have never opened one of those ever
I just go that's a fucking lot of like waste and then I throw it in the recycling they no one opens them
No one no one opens them. Why do they do this? Stop doing this?
Sometimes I'll even go to my mailbox and it's stuffed full of bullshit that I didn't even order
It's like what the fuck is all this and this one piece of mail. That's like a bank statement. It's to the same cat here
Oh shit, they're fighting for dominance and who's the real one is
Shit boots is boots is territory. That was rant Andy. No, that's fucking stupid. I'm sorry. That's really dumb
We talk all this shit about the environment and how much we care about it
But then like those companies that these same companies will just mass mail the shit out to you
Recycling Andy. I don't want all your bullshit. I don't want all your stupid mail that I'm not gonna read
it's like if I was walking down the sidewalk and
You stopped me and you said excuse me, excuse me
Would you like to hear about the piano recital that's gonna happen next week? I'd be like, uh, no that same person is like, okay
thank you that exact same person stays on that part of the sidewalk and
Asks you that same question every single fucking three or four days every week. Hey, excuse me
Would you like to read would you like to go to the piano recital? I don't want to go to the piano
Okay, listen, do I have to say this to you to your face?
It's really cool that you have a piano recital, I'm not going and I'm never going I will never go
Please stop stopping me on the sidewalk and asking me if I want to go to the piano recital
I will never go. Is this what you need me to do? Do you need me?
Do you need to hear me say this? Okay. All right, right my god
That's fine. Then you don't have to go my goodness. Have a good day, sir. Yeah. Have a good day a week later
I go to the fucking sidewalk and this motherfuckers is there again. Hey, sir, you want to go to the piano recital?
When what what I'm I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking freak out. Leave me alone. Leave me alone. Like why can't you just leave me alone?
Oh, by the way at the end of the piano recital, we're gonna give a coupon book to everybody that's there
I don't want you fucking coupon book. Stop sending me coupon books. Oh shit. My sim is dying. No, I'm sorry
I'm sick of that shit
It's been something that's been on my mind for a long time and I think it's on everybody's mind and wait
Don't you step in the food you idiot?
That's one of those things that you'd always think about but you never was. Oh, yeah
That's I guess that we do have people to do that
They need to transition completely and to just spam like emails and I'll tell you why because like nobody opens those either
But at least those aren't clogging up your mailbox and like burning down trees if I had to pick one of the two evils
I'd pick that one
How about this? How about you just don't be a fucking asshole like and just send people random shit
They don't want like when did that become something that oh, yeah. Well, whatever just said just just like fucking annoying everybody
We live in like we we live in a society of just annoyance
Everybody just wants to annoy each other. What?
Why can't you just leave each other the fuck alone?
society
Yeah, I said it. Oh, yeah. He's the oh, he's the Joker. We already went over this. No, I'm not
Everybody who says they're the Riddler is actually the Joker and everybody that says they're the Joker is actually the penguin
Don't say that about me because I mean that makes me the penguin. I still need to get a job
No, he's not gonna want to do that. All right, hunger. Let's go for it
Tldr of that conversation is
What the fuck? Why is it? Why?
Not know don't even get into it again. Just like what the fuck leave me alone, right? That's all we need to say
Tldr society he's got angst angst Andy. That's not even angst. What is it angst?
No, you will come to the piano resettled. No, I won't no I won't I ain't going ever you will get the coupon book
No, I won't what if you would really enjoy it, but okay
Are we going to base like our society around like you're you're like?
Kind of friend that doesn't stop asking you to watch a certain movie or TV show
You know, I mean like as I was that the excuse you're giving telling you you really you really you have to watch it
It's so good. Watch it. I don't want to watch it. No, you would love it. Watch it tomorrow. I don't want to
Maybe I would I don't want to right now
And I don't want to be like forced to and then when you're watching the movie the friend is that kind of staring at you
Like waiting to see what you're gonna say about certain scenes
It's like can we watch this in different rooms and like and every 30 to 40 minutes take a pee break and I'll tell you
What I think
And then they give you a coupon book. This is never good. I'm good. Okay, no more no more like oh
Here goes. He's ranting. There's no more ranting. He's gonna start ramping. No more of this
I'm gonna play the game now. Your sim is dying. My sim is in good health. It just doesn't have any friends
I'm trying to change that. Let's just throw it. No. All right call over a neighbor or something
I can't get a job unless I have like my social height. You need so much social because you're so outgoing
I don't even know. I don't even care who they are. Just bring them over. Mo
I'm just gonna throw a party throw a party and I'm gonna have something to do. There's a pool outside
Let's have like a dance party group activity hit this one here. This is fine. Put it on top of the TV
Why not? It'll be it'll give it like eyes. It'll be funny
Because I'm having a party I need to move stuff
You drag the couch across the room and then make it so people gonna just hang out this thing's dead
All right, so that's good. Let's move this so I can have a big dance floor. I need a little table
Oh, this is good group activity, right? No, I don't care. Whatever fuck it
This sucks
This would be such a bad party
It's like you have to drag your TV and your couch out of the way and this is a huge speaker
It would sound awful in here throw a party
Here we go
If I need to throw a party and have everybody have a dance party here to have my soul should go up even 1%
Sounds great. This looks like Jesse's house from Breaking Bad. Yeah, it does. I turn the cartoons off. They're coming. Don't worry
I promise they're coming over right now. Welcome. Welcome everybody. Hello. Come on in
Outside I can I not turn this on there are no actions available. Why?
There are no why what? Oh shit. Oh guys. It's so big. I'm gonna run out of money. This better be worth it
Turn it on quick before people start leaving what?
Turn it on
Gotta save this guy. I gotta save this guy. He keeps doing the sock puppet to this dude
They're in an awkward conversation outside the house because I haven't let them in and now this guy's just doing the sock puppet over and over
I have to be freaking this guy out
This party sucks
I feel like this on stream sometimes. This is me streaming
You know how many times I have had like a technical difficulty happened
You guys are all sitting here and like I can't get this thing to work and it's all fucked up
But I'm just like I just want to cry this happens like all the time. Here we go. Oh, I got the old
1994 PC game to work everybody at this party saved. Let's go
Oh
Switch to rock. All right social
No, it turns out the game was not fun and not funny and all the time
I took to get it set up was not worth it because everybody hates it
Oh
These people still trying to get in
Why I this this is like ten people in my house, I'm not my social is not going well
We need to dance yeah, all right, come on. Oh
My god, this is gossip. Just somebody talk to me
Ridiculous this guy won't leave this guy alone. Oh
No, he's realizing the only reason why I threw this party was to get him to come over. Oh
Shit, I fell for the bait. Oh
No
What the fuck how do I make this go up teenage girl worry
I
Can't who's that new friend Meg Meg, it's Meg from Family Guy
I mean Meg gonna be friends. It's working
Why there's so many animals?
This is so ridiculous. Well, there's so many animals
What the fuck? Well, I got there's so many
It's just eight dogs and cats
They're just a cat's animals
in my house
This place is fucked up
Why would they be this many animals I
Love it. It's so dumb
You're fleas everywhere. Oh, you're hungry. Well, whatever leave Oh eat on your own time
I
It's actually Meg Griffin, isn't it that's interesting not expect Meg Griffin to be one of my friends. It's really crazy
Only Meg stayed
This is fanfiction. No, no, it's not
It's not
Out of here
All right, I social is fine
What what happened? What happened? What happened? What happened?
Congratulations, you're not friends again. What happened?
Cheer up. All right. It's almost full. That's all I care about friends for ten seconds
You accidentally said shut up Meg god damn it
All right, we're good socials back to normal I can actually go get a job
Okay, cool
family friend
She likes criminals. Okay. Thank you for coming over Meg. It's been nice to see you
We're going to fucking wave. Goodbye to you
Thank you for coming goodbye
Leave I you might be yes. You're hungry. Goodbye
Good to see you again. Well for the first time
Bye Meg. Okay social is perfect. Turn this off. Oh, I have the huge speaker on
You just had so much fun. What are you talking about? Turn this off turn off the music and go to bed
No, what's going on? Get up? Oh bathroom now shower sleep computer
This would be awful. Is he gonna get swimming and in bed go to bed. I'm gonna watch TV eat something
Okay, eat clean this shit up. Whatever it is. Get the mail
Recycle recycle. I just don't want to have mail sent to my house ever again. What am I putting all this stuff?
Who would I just took bills out? Where are they where the bills that I just picked up there they are shit
Okay, I need a job now. I need a job now a quick lunch watch some TV and then I need to get a job now
Sit down and watch TV, please sit down and watch TV forget about the dogs. Thank God. Okay
I thought that was my stomach. All right, turn this off eat something and then go find a job now
Oh my god, there's no chair move out of the way
I'm running out of money fast. Whatever this is. I have to take it
It doesn't matter what it is. I have to take a job. Whatever it is culinary
Education no
No, no, no
Shit my job. There are more. I know there are I take the teacher job. No, I can't no
I don't want to do these shit
I only have like three more in sim days or like two more of a week
Maybe one of the plants be a clown if I could I would do it. What time is it? It's okay
It's 10 p.m. I'm gonna go for
Use the toilet
wash the damn toilet and then take a shower and then
Use a job
And then go to bed
Social is low again. I really should have had outgoing at zero. That's the difficulty slider in The Sims 1 is
Your outgoing meter. Was I gonna talk to a talent agent?
I was gonna talk to a talent agent, but my character is having problems existing
You can social drop so quickly
And nobody talks to me and I throw a party to get someone to talk to me and then it decays in a day
Because my outgoing my difficulty slider is all the way up. All right, here we go
Have a quick breakfast and then I'm gonna play the guitar for like a whole day
I need these creative points. You need a job and that off. I'm gonna
Nothing to do. I just want it. I need to get it up at social up and then I'm gonna tell her to leave
Job more more more more more more more more more more
I'm sorry, but Meg is the only person that has talked to me
But more than 10 minutes that hasn't just dropped my social by a thousand percent. It's the only person that I get pluses
Campaign worker, I don't want to do this. I want to get this to 100% and then we're gonna say goodbye shit shit
Whatever
TV to well, I'm about to have like a really really like a loud shit and go ahead
You know go turn on the shower too and the sink. This is fine. Let's go
Alright, I'm in a really good mood right now. I just need to go to the bathroom
Have a snack and get some sleep
Very nice and clean this up. And now check this out. I'm gonna play the guitar
No, no, don't do that. This is why I bought this play the guitar. Wait, first of all turn all this shit off
Are you going for like a electricity bill any percent like I don't understand what you're doing turn all this off the beds in the way
Well, it's almost there creativity. There it is. When I get all the charisma
Oh from the mirror when I get the body from ice
Okay, I am so skilled now. I can go to the open mic night and actually do something. I think I got a lot of these plants
At a job. I'm doing it at an agent. You're statted for it. Am I static for an agent now?
I think I have to go to studio town. All right. Look stop. What are you doing?
Flyer on the ground. Oh
this thing
find an agent
Meg
Check the computer for a chef job
Yeah, I'll check the chef
In a job, you're gonna die. I'm not gonna die. Let's see get on a computer
Politics look again
business look again
Science god damn it. No
No
All right, go be agent. Just take a job. No
Sim City Talent Agency
We represent the stars of today tomorrow and yesterday
Looking for at least 15 minutes of fame give us a chance because as we always say you need us more than we need you
Would you like to sign up? Yes
Congratulations, welcome to our family of stars and up-and-comers whenever you're ready to look for work in studio town
Just call us on the phone and we'll send a car right away. Let's get ready for work at breakfast
Use the bathroom take a shower. We're going to studio town. Let's get to work. Somebody's gave a bunch of subs
Cabbagehead PhD just gave 30 community subs. Thank you cabbage head. That's a shitload of subs
Congratulations to those of you. They got one. Thanks for the good immunity
So, okay, let's get that going
Good good good
Send me a cab. I'm getting my first acting job. Yes. Let's go check that. Hmm
Oh wait, I can't that is my job. All right off to the first day studio town. Let's go
Alright, I need to find Joe acting opportunities or what's this one? We're launching the careers
I'm going here. No, what watch should I go to? This is family guy music. Yes
It is it actually is a family guy interlude music. Let's go here. All that's missing from that is
Seth MacFarlane going
The only thing that was missing from that episode, all right, where's the acting opportunity this is my agent
Ask about fans
Fans of what keep the famous going talk with your admirers get to know them a lack of attention from you is liable to drive
At least one of them to the brink of obsession another reverse of what actually is
Get to know them talk to them a lack of attention from you is gonna drive at least one of them the brink of obsession
But aren't you describing like a parasocial relationship? Oh wait pose for a picture
I'm I'm famous now. I
have an agent I
Pay six hundred dollars a month to somebody that promises me I'm gonna be famous every week. I call her on the phone
Get a good photo
Congratulations, Jerma Elbertson due to your recent success in studio town. We're upgrading your standing on our star charts
You've gained a star level. Where's my money?
Dear Jeremy Elbertson due to the incredible popularity of the look of a photo
Right here act in the emergency scene pause
I got to read this most dogs in studio town get treated better than this and
Your earning power is about as exciting as your lowly star power channel your bitterness and frustration into your work
So someday you'll be on top friends total star power to land the best gigs
You have to network this number indicates how much star power your friends are worth
And how much you'll need to progress to the next star level remember the more famous a star the more power they wield in studio town
And more helpful to be in your career
Networking our kid you too tall for the part you may want to try for a commercial instead
I need two and a half stars to do this. What's that? Where is this person? Why are they back here?
When I get out of here, what is this person doing? Oh
You trying to be famous too, what's a star kiss?
I
Am so out of my element here. I just wanted to be a chef. What do I start?
Because celebrity chef do a commercial commercial commercial commercial commercial
What's wrong with me I'm getting like a migraine it's my turn I
Get out of my way, I'm the actor
Here
Get out of here
commercial
I'm ready here. We go get separate from I need one and a half stars. Well, what am I supposed to do?
Fuck I need to go like sing karaoke
I'm a famous sim streamer
As you earn more fame opportunities are open in studio town
If you don't move up the ladder as quickly as you'd like make sure to practice at home. Don't forget to rub out. Okay, so
Sorry, I'm trapped in the in the endless cycle of I need to go to the bathroom shit shower and and like sit in a chair
19 to 20 hours of the day
Go talk to him. I think he's stuck back there. Yeah, he's like he spawned back there in a bad spot
No, I don't want to leave studio town. I want to go. I want to go do karaoke
That's how I can like rub elbows like they said go somewhere else
Remember people were like noticing me and they were like you suck. Boom now
I thought I'd have a better singing voice from playing the guitar. They'll like me then
Alright, I want to go to here. It is that like the carrot that here it is the bar. This is the karaoke bar, right?
Let's go be a chef
I need to like sit down for a little bit. That was fun. Wait, I need to find a celebrity
There's a celebrity right here. I thought you can't get back the Sims can't like stand up for more than fucking
Four hours before they have to like sit down. What what was that?
No, I'm a star too, I'm a star too
You're at nobody. I'll show you just gamble more. I may as well just sit there and just try to get the 10 grand
Give me that shrimp skewer. All right. Now, let's have a seat sit down and then get ready to throw it on the ground
Okay
Awful I'll show you how to be a real actor after I sit down for four hours. We got
Let's hear it. Am I like booing him? What am I doing? Oh, wait, am I getting on? All right my turn god
Welcome to the sims 1 stay in your fucking house and go to the bathroom and eat out of your fridge the whole game
Get me out of here. Did you miss the car?
I'm gonna be fucking famous guy. Just go to bed get our get in here sit on the chair
Go flush the toilet. We'll go use the toilet for like the 30th time in a day get in there
I'm too upset to pee look at the social. I was just out. I was just out around surrounded by people
I'm just getting a job. Whatever didn't flush. Oh my god. That's so annoying. Get out of my house
here I
Mean at least you gambled in one a thousand dollars
Yeah, so I get to continue to do this
Wake up eat go to the bathroom 30 times and then go back to sleep. All right, get out of bed. What is going on here?
25 hours in bed like asleep asleep
What the fuck? Oh my god to have breakfast
Okay, and now we need to watch TV. Where are these flies just long? Look if I get down to 100 bucks
I'm just gonna go gamble it again. I'm paying it
Yes
Okay. Now I have to get a job. Oh, okay now sit on the couch turn the television on watch horror movies. What's that?
Oh, it's the maid good. She's doing so much. Oh, this is perfect. Oh my god. It's perfect
I can watch TV all day. How much does this cost? How much shit do I have to do?
There's so much stuff
If I had done this on my own this would have taken the entire day and then would have to eat take a shower and go
To sleep I talked to the maid would she just take $30 on that box, but she's not doing anything
She's not doing anything. She's getting she's what is she doing? She's not okay. She's gonna she's just taking money
She's you just took $30 paid her. Yeah, but I thought she was walking around in circles. Okay socials at zero again
This is great. Find a job. You're currently signed up with a sin. Yeah, that's not gonna work
I can barely leave the house for 15 minutes before I like shit my pants or and cry
Like I have to I have to get a job
Journalism, no
culinary come on
Medicine, maybe I could be doctor. I might be doctor. All right, maybe I'll take that look again
All right. I'm gonna be a doctor. Fuck you. Oh god. Damn it
Get up go to the bathroom and go be a doctor
It's not a pressure. Ah
Go. Oh my god. I gotta call Meg. I just want to talk Meg
Call her again
You interrupted my TV show call back in a few hours. It's all I needed. Here we go. All right, go
I'm gonna be a doctor law enforcement. Wait. No, what happened to the doctor job?
entertainment career for a waiter waitress
entertainer fine hundred dollars a day
Was the car get here? All right 8 a.m. I gotta be ready call Meg again
Socially challenged moron. No time it is. I gotta be ready for work at least a little bit now. I need
I'm going crazy man. This is the music is so much
And I'm gonna go back to bed for like a few up first of all
Turn this shit off
Car gets here in like four hours. I can sleep for about four hours. That sounds good. Go to sleep
Take a nap. I'll be here in an hour
Alright, get up. It's good cars here. You don't have time for that. Just the car. Why is it all the way?
Why is it across the street? Please help me clean my house up. Thank you. Can you say hi to my friend Jared?
Hey Jared, thanks for watching the stream personal shout out from German on eight five
Jared talking to you play the computer for a little bit and then I need some I need to have Meg come over
I'm gonna talk to Meg all day. I'm gonna get promoted tomorrow. Just you watch all invite Meg over. Yes, you betcha
Golly gee whiz I've been hankering. All right, whatever. Just come over. I'm gonna serve dinner as well
Actually cook it dinner is served. Hey Meg. Don't mind them wild animals. Just put it down
It's a nice spot for it. Fine. Let's eat and let's talk. I know right pretty cool
The stray cats are fighting social. All right, talk
Just
Gossip and stuff talk talk just get it all the way up and then I can finally get promoted
I'll get promoted the next day if I have a good
Go for it
Yes, yes
How come why are there no other options besides interest no I
Just want to talk I don't know no no, no, she's done talking. She's like I'm done talking stop
She's so done. She's like drained
All right, look at me watch TV look at this comfort what the fuck
Let's watch TV and talk. I slept five minutes. What time is it? Okay. I gotta go. Oh my god
I gotta go to bed. I gotta go to bed right now
Fuck I have to get a full work
No, you know, it's all right. Whatever. That's fine. Use the bathroom
Take a shower and that should be good enough. You're an hour to take a shower. I
Didn't taking a shower for an hour
You would be
Wrinkly your skin would start coming off. Sometimes I do that you stay in the shower for an hour
How does your hot water tank or heater put up with that? Don't you doesn't you you get to cold water?
I don't understand how you're doing that. You're not in the shower for a full hour. No way didn't get promoted
All right, go to bed. No, yeah call sleep for a little bit and then call Meg
I get up serve dinner. No call Meg then serve dinner. I get it right. Come on over. I have so much gossip
We have to catch up. All right, come on over
serve dinner
Okay, how funny is this gonna be when there's a row of these
Make some new friends. Jesus. I can't you know how hard this is. Okay. Now, let's get over here and talk
I will have pretty good bars at the end of this. I should get promoted after this
I
Not like computers. I have one it right next to me. I hate computers. I don't like them
I was just playing League of Legends on here when she walked in talk
All right now I'm gonna go to bed, thank you for coming
Hi. All right, get in that bed a chair and table. I don't have room for it
Okay, I am gonna be just fine. Check this out
Ladder and then I'm gonna switch to romance and sit down and watch this
Great watch TV quick. No, no, don't I'm deleting that he keeps doing that. He's just got this stupid thing ever
Why does he do that? Why do you keep doing that? He doesn't even like it. He hates it
Flowers, what is it boy? What is it? What is it boy? Somebody fall down the well? Oh
Look at all the social I'm getting for this. Oh sick. All right, I'll be good get up tomorrow
My bars will be awesome. Okay, I'll get promoted tomorrow if I can keep this the job requirements tab
There are no job requirements yet
Don't leave yet, it doesn't like cats, okay
All right, I'll be calling you some point later good night
Talk about pizza mushrooms. All right, go to bed. Whoa
It was like
He was supposed to get in the bed
If I was not taking up this space, he would have gotten in the bed. Holy shit. Okay. Well, that was weird
This will be perfect. I'll have a bill to eat go to the bathroom. I'll be at almost full bars
I'm calling a gardener
Decorate the outside. Yeah, I'm gonna add some I'm gonna add some more like interesting stuff out here
decorations
Sculptures plants. Here we go. Okay room two room three. I was very expensive, but it worth it
Alright now I get to eat it off the computer a quick breakfast and that should be good
I'll get the promotion now carpool be there in an hour. Alright, I want you to wash your hands. Alright, let's go
I got almost full. Why is this happening? Is it because of the trash?
Remove the box
Is it is it this shit out here? That's screwing this all up. I'm just gonna throw this stuff away
I don't even care what it does. I don't care. I don't care about magic world
Delete all this crap. Okay, good. Where did she go? Just that was weird. Where did she just go?
It's the fence delete the fence. Is it the fence? Okay. Yeah, I don't hate it anymore
It really was the stupid box. It was the box. Yeah, these bears do anything. So these bear sure
I just get rid of the bears. Yeah, this is a creepy. I don't want this in front of my fucking house
Alright, let's go to room decorative plants room three
Whoo, if you do like one one, two. Oh my god. I'm spending all my money
What come on you just spent a weak salary on plants or let me just go like that's that's that's like better, right?
Oh shit. These are red. Oh my god. I have so many bills
God no, this is all my money. I can't afford this they're being blocked by the counters shit
Sorry, you don't have the 216 to pay this bill. What are the casino? No, not yet
At least okay, this is not gonna cause a huge problem anymore. Like it was before let's watch some TV. Let's take a
Shit, take a shower. Yeah, like I have to play on the computer, you know
Maybe like read a book or like sleep, you know, right?
Let's let's let's get this good because I need to get my level up on my career
The bills are high cuz he leaves the TV on all day. Yeah
What does this dog do it in here? Hello dog. It's not even auto. I apparently don't like this room, but whatever
Computer is still on too
Hey, do you guys keep your computer on all day? I know people that never turn off their PC and that kind of freaks me out
I always shut down on my computer every night at night. I turn it off, right? Yeah, well you put it into sleep mode
I always feel like that when you put the computer into sleep mode or if you don't shut the computer off and turn it back
On what hours later the computer sucks?
Okay, it makes it worse. It needs to be like refreshed and stuff
And I know that doesn't make any sense, but it kind of does
Do you have your computer on for like five straight days? I feel like it's slower
It needs to go to sleep just turn off and then turn back on
It's actually true. It is true. It's computing 101. It's not a human
yeah, but it still needs to get like refreshed and a man and the RAM needs to be dumped and
Like the hard drive needs to rest for a minute
The video the graphics card is like not compute for like a little bit so they can be fresh when it turns on
Was that I get up wake up and off this TV
Have a breakfast have quick breakfast and then play on the computer
Yeah, I got lots of time. Let's go
Okay, the car will be here soon
Enough time for me to go to the bathroom
Flush that toilet. All right
I'm getting a promotion
I'm definitely gonna get a promotion. Why would I even turn that on if i'm not gonna use it? That's it
Why are you taking a shower?
All right. Come on. Why is it comfort going down?
I need a table. He needs to sit at a table and why would you leave this on he turns on for no reason
Hard day of watching tv
It's for the maid
promotion
Did I even get paid? All right, come here. Let's get some social with this cat. Come here
It's not the worst noise get out of here social social social social
Animal
Social social
Pet animal
raise
pet animal
pet
Pet dog wake up dog pet dog wake cat pet cat
Nice. Okay. Awesome
Turn this off. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, it's so noisy in here
Who the fuck is this?
Uh player the bear
You do it
What the fuck do I call the police?
I gotta call the police. Why why are they naruto running? What just happened?
Is that just one of my neighbors?
I'm very confused
uh
I just ate something out of my trash
Is there any like piss on the floor over here?
Okay, this piss over there take care of that. I have to go to bed
Stop going to on the couch go to sleep. I have a bachelor's in computer science
I know that turning your computer up is good for it, but your addiction
To mining zorn coin is not helpful in any way. Please get help zorn coin
That's so
Stupid. All right play on the computer. We're gonna flush use
Shower play on computer for the time that I have
Hurry up
I can play for like 30 minutes
All right play i'm hungry, but it's okay. I should be fine. I thought you're gonna answer the phone
I gotta pee first break. What do you think? I need to get promoted
Damn it who's beeping stop beeping
There's so many animals in the road
My god, this place is a disaster
answer the phone
stop
A computer bug is deposited at 300 in your bank account. Nice
Do I have to go in here and then shoo them away?
Go get get get out. I can't listen to this
Leave shoo
Shoo
All right. No you get out of here. Okay, finally, all right. I gotta pee
Cover it back pee time. How are you?
Let the man pee
I mean, i'm good
Did you flush?
Yes, because that would be gross if I didn't can I please just get promoted?
Where am I play on the computer eat some food and go for it. You have to be happy to get promoted
I know i'm trying to get my bars up
It needs to be at least three two three higher than this I need more skills
I do not need more skills to get promoted once. No, I don't. All right, where's the dog? Come here. Come here. Come here
Come here. I want to play no come here. Stop running
All right, go to the bathroom
Sleep and then i'm gonna get up in the morning and get my bars up
Why am I cheating?
I'm not cheating
All right, get up. You had enough sleep. It's 3 a.m
I can't the only social i'm gonna get is with an animal. There are any stray dogs running around that I can hang out with
Damn it. I have to clean that up quick breakfast
Take a shower
And the car will be here in about three hours
Use the bathroom
Good. All right. What else do I need comfort fun sit down and play the computer. There it is. All right
Come on, go go go stay on there
Perfect. What can I do in the next? No, no, no, don't go swimming. What are you doing?
The car's gonna be here in 10 minutes
Don't turn that on either
Just sit for a minute. Don't go swimming
Okay, now you can get up three bars good guaranteed promotion. This is it. I got it. That's a guaranteed promotion has to be
You're doing fine. Here comes the promotion. We're ready three two one
promotion, yeah
You've been promoted to extra your atmosphere living scenery. The pay is pitiful, but at least you're on the set
No lines though and central casting can call you for the day shift or the night shift depending on the production needs
Make sure you develop your charisma skill so that when that speaking part does come through you'll be ready
You now work from 9 to 3 pm starting immediately that didn't change
You brought home 150 and got a 300 bonus. All right. Now, what do I need?
I don't have any requirements. So I already have it
Let's go to work really happy for the next day or two get promoted again now
Okay, again, I need a table. Yeah, you can go swimming. You deserve it. I need to rearrange this room. This is
Ridiculous computers going in the bedroom. Okay, that's fine right there. This is getting rearranged
I'm getting a new couch. Which one do I have right now? This is the oh no
This I already have a gray couch better tv. What am I gonna do with all this?
Hold on move this book. This has got to move that's in a better place. Okay, that's fine. That's fine
I need a window here. I'm nice
Oh, yeah, how much is that 68 bucks? It's a nice big beautiful a big beautiful window right there
Okay, now I need a table this room's not big enough for this
Too big. That's all right. This is not this is a desk. What do you mean a desk efficiency table?
What this is a table you're talking about need a couple of just I need this this room's too small the windows
It's not
How would you mean the windows backwards?
It's not backwards
It is
No, it's not these open
How is it backwards don't those close and open the shutters are in the end. Yeah, isn't that that's how it works
Right, you know what a window looks like those are storm windows. What do you mean? What the fuck?
I thought those don't those clothes. Hold on. Give me the hand tool. You guys are fucking crazy. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? They go out. No, they don't
Shutters go outside. I've never had a house with shutters. I'm so I don't
I've never seen that before. I thought it was a big like bay window
I've I've don't even know what that is shutters. I don't i've never had shutters before that's good
Wait, I want to move it a little bit. That's better. All right
Okay, I need this is too cluttered in here. How do I make this better?
This kind of needs to go like on the patio or something. This is gonna make the room bad
Make the house bigger. I could how much is that gonna cost?
I'm just moving the computer's going over here. I'm just gonna it's like playing a puzzle game. Okay, that's better brass
I don't i've done one thing at a time. What color is this one?
Shit, I don't even know what color that is. It's like a light blue. Okay, leave the grass
Oh, I don't leave the grass. All right. This is this blue carpet kind of dark blue
All right, that's better much better
In fact, let's move that over in the corner and then I can put the plant in here
Oh, that's so much nicer. This gives more room to move stuff around here
Now I need some chairs
Look how much better that is
I just need some regular chairs
Two not more than two
I'm running out of money. They have to be just default shitty chairs. Okay, i'm out of money. I have a roof
Look, i'll prove it didn't have a roof. All right. I'm good. My house is now actually not a total disaster
If I can move around in this though, what's this? It's a new table. Go check it out
I don't think he likes this out here. Oh, shut up the table. What is not to like about this?
I don't understand what is not to like about this table. It's just a piece of wood
It's a place to eat move this too. Can I get into bed or is this in the way?
Um, that's all right. That's fine here. The pc looks slow
Whatever. I think I need to get rid of this. Oh perfect. Let's go on the ground ain't the outside
Oh shit, you're right. What is it? It's this uh,
this like
Strip of black on the top and bottom this one here. All right, how's that better? Get yourself a pet, please
I need to get promoted twice so I can make enough money to afford a pet
I will trust me. I'm going for it turn the lawn into a carpet. I feel like that would look really not good
Again, I think he'd hate that. This is a good setup so far. It's a good setup. I like it
Go outside and touch the grass
I go touch it go put my hands on it you wear speedos around your house
That's why you never have a face cam on
Um, I mean I wear pajama pants
I throw on pajama pants and I hang out and I just chill out in my house. That's the doom character's head
It kind of is. Yeah, that actually is the doom guy
Nice full meal looking good. Awesome looking cool. I just need to go to work happy calling meg. Let's call luigi
Let's invite luigi over
On my list of favorite things to do seeing you is at the bottom. That was mean
But uh meg griffin
Come on over meg
Right over. All right. Awesome
I already ate dinner. So
Wait, you can eat this
You can eat the scraps
Will she eat that?
I wonder will she sit down and start eating it. I wonder if she actually sits to eat this. Um
Sit well, it should be over in a second
Where are you meg? All right. Now, let's spam her with conversation. Why do I hate it out here? What's going on?
my god, it's the
this four
Dog is animal pee in every corner. Why is that my responsibility?
I'll give him a chance to complain
Sleep may it'll get this tomorrow. You're good
Getting my social up takes like two full days
And I can't how am I supposed to go to work?
No, i'm not going to work
Yeah, I am what am I talking about?
Get in the get in the car. I'm not going to work. Never mind. I'm not going to answer the phone either
If I don't answer the phone then if I don't answer the phone then
I can't they can't they can't yell at me. They'll have to be mad at me through an email. Don't worry. I'm going to work tomorrow
Full everything i'm gonna call meg over i'm gonna eat i'm gonna sleep i'm gonna go to the bathroom
I'm gonna be at up here when I go to work next very cool
Okay, i've eaten dinner
It's 12 30 go for it. Let's get ready just in here. I'm taking a shower. All right meg come on over
My favorite soap opera is almost finished. I'll be over in a few minutes. Perfect. It's perfect timing. Look what time it is now
We're gonna sit i'm gonna watch tv and talk while we do it. Come on in. I'm watch tv watch tv
Why don't you sit and talk?
Fuck
97 with mega griffin i'm not doing that what I just click on
Social social go go go go go go go go
Social social social fill it up. Fill it up. Fill it up. Fill it up. Fill it up
All right, you can leave now
Let's watch tv. That's fine
All right, she left now take a look what time it is. I'm ready to go to work turn that tv off
Wait, while I have a second
Wait, why is she still here? She's in the pool. I need a full night's sleep
She can just go in the pool. I don't care
Got what I wanted
remove ladder
She's still here
Social is up energy's up. This is a promotion day. I just have to get up
eat shower and uh and
You motherfucker get out of here get out of here. All right, wake up and get this. Uh, get him. Don't let him over there
Show him get out. Oh
Leave you little bastard
Clean this up. I gotta clean this shit up. That's why I have to make sure this is not
All right, clean clean clean clean clean clean clean clean. All right
Use take a shower. I got time
Okay, quick breakfast
Come on
Eat eat it. Not yet. Don't leave yet. Don't leave it. I got time. What else can I do quickly?
Shit, just go whatever that's good enough for promotion
What about the bills?
150 andy
Is
Wait, are the bills just sitting outside somewhere on the ground?
It'd be red, right? I don't think so. What about over here? No, i'm good. I mean I need to pay them
Ask meg to move in. I mean hold on. Where does meg even live?
elbertson's
newbie family
Griffin family, I guess she lives here. It was nice to know where they live
Oh, but peter doesn't like this. I don't know like this mirror for some reason. I don't know who's here
Is am I gonna show up
Invite me over
I'm gonna call me over. Wait, does this help my social?
Where's the griffin phone garage? Oh the school bus is here for stewie. Oh stewie. You gotta get to school
Stewie not gonna go to school somebody. Okay meg get on the phone
Stewie it's time for school. I should not have to go to school
Vile woman, but I guess I will torment the other students. I'm brian. Are you ready to come to school with me?
Be my chaperone. I
Will take you to school
I just did a whole episode. All right, where uh, where's the phone?
Lois
Where's the telephone?
The griffins there it is. All right, call me call over. I can't believe i'm gonna actually get to go hang out with the griffins
It's nice that you get to relax at home, but poor germas at work shit when do I get off work?
Where's lois? Oh my god lois
Peter's on a computer
Get out of here chris. I'm on the i'm on your computer right now
Yeah, just play fortnight
It's time to play fortnight
Everybody thought I was gonna be in the game
But it just turned out to be a fucking lie
I was really hoping that peter griffin was gonna come over
I was calling mega over and over again
To try to get her to bring the family over
You understand
What are they doing?
Why is she naked?
Okay, I thought they were fighting. That's the tv
All right. It's time to call me
Get on the phone. I want to come hang out here. Where is she? There she is
Call me over. I want to come hang out
You betcha by golly gee whiz i've been hankering to see you. All right
Here I come. I can't wait
I can't wait to finally get to come and hang out at the griffin house
Oh my god
Here I am
I can't wait. Somebody's gonna let me in the house
I'm gonna let him in lois. Let me in
Well peter our new friend is here. This is a weird self insert. Somebody said
Like i'm just i'm writing my own fan fiction of my own universe
You know what? I didn't know about the griffin household until looking at
Um, like what their house looked like?
They have like a second living room
I thought the piano was in this room
They have a huge fucking house
If you've got two full couches in your house
That's a good indication that
You you you might have a little bit of money
You made the house
Yeah, i'm saying I do like I didn't know until researching
That this is what the griffins has like a second living room
Do not home wreck the griffins
All right. Let's let's have peter do something here comes the episode. All right
He's just gonna be
Oh peter's gonna serve dinner
We got this new friend germa 985. He's here hanging out with us. I will make my secret
Hot tuck it pete
Beer cheese pretzels
I'm sorry. I had to do it. I had to do it. It had to be horrible
All right peter. What do you got?
dinner
served
No fire. No fire. It didn't work
Why is it so much trash?
There's trash everywhere
There's a turkey
Dirty turkey
Am I eating?
There I am right there
Wait, why?
It's a stupid character
This is just a reference of this is peter in a suit
Hey lois, remember the time when I pretended to be a raccoon and eat out of the trash
Why they're all freaking out actual family guy routine. Yeah. Oh shit. Sorry. That was like
I remember when I was a hamster every that time when I was a hamster. Fuck. I had that it should have been that
Where did I leave?
No, here I am right here. What's gonna happen in the room?
We're all trying to use the same bathroom. We like give me stuff
Now it's self-insert fan fiction now. Now. That's what this is
Wasn't that before until right now? Come on. Does this make my social go up too?
Oh my god. Look me me and lois get along so well
Look at how well me and lois get along
Holy shit, there is
It's way too much he's like i'm done. Wait, what do you mean raspberry?
Fuck
Shit, it's not working abort
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. What? Oh, I remember that song that our family sings
It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on tv
But where are those good old fashion values?
On which we used to rely and lucky there's a family guy
Family guy lucky. There's a bad
Why didn't put the camera over here?
They're not married
Where's stewie gonna sleep
Who's in this bed? Oh, I think meg's in the right room
Lois is in the right room. Peter's in stewie's bed
Do we just playing the piano?
still
Meg is with chris. They all need to go to bed
Okay, where's he going? Oh, he's going
Okay, he's going this is correct. This is chris's room
Where's stewie gonna go? I thought that was a gun
I was about to scream
Why why'd you get up?
They're just switching beds. I'm confused. I'm so confused. What's going on?
She's going now to sleep in the bed that stewie is in that is really cute. Where can she sleep?
Don't have a couch. Holy shit. This place is a disaster. All right, that was fun
I'll time for me to leave the griffin household
All right. Goodbye those who want me to check on the sweets household or simulane the sweets family things look like they're going well
Now there's another family though
What i'm noticing up here?
mario luigi
toad and peach
Is there how his
Can you tell that there was quite a bit of time spent on the griffin household and not very much time on the mario household?
You know all the all the time
Uh last night, this is uh, you know, it's time for bed. They're doing great
Your debt is quadrupling for this joke. That was not a debt
That had nothing to do with anything you that i'm sorry, but that is not there's nothing to do with me
You can't just say that. How am I doing porn set? It is not a porn set. It is a mushroom house
So I gotta go to work in all right. Look at my bars. They're perfect. I'll get promoted tomorrow
I'm doing good one more day of like of at least three or four bars and i'll get it here
It's so early
If you if you marry lois, we will remove debt from the will you?
Really now how much would you say two what you gotta have a baby with lois?
My god, that's so
fucked up
250 million 500 million i'll do it for 500 million
I will try to marry lois for the rest of the stream if you take 500 million off it needs to be a baby
I will try
You have to take out peter. I don't know. I don't think so
Mary plus baby. All right, i'll try i'll give it a try
750 million if there is a baby. All right. Well, I think I can do it for now. I need to get a better job
Let's use this
Let's i'm gonna play some computer games and i'm gonna sleep. I should put a better chair into here
I don't have enough money to do it though. All right, turn this off
Really good timing here
I'll have this should get me to four and then i'm guaranteed a promotion if that happens
I'll have plenty of time to eat take a shower and go to the bathroom. All right, stop stop stop. Stop don't oversleep
Have a quick breakfast save the game
You have to sing chug jug while you're woohooing lois
That's so stupid fine
Fine I will
Just for you
eat
Oh shit. It's okay
Our pool will be here soon
Unclog fuck I need to pee somewhere. Oh god. Damn it
Use it. Damn it. Okay, it's cool. Whatever be in the shower. I need social again
It's so hard to keep all these bars off. She's got it. She'll take care of this
Does she get rid of the bugs? Does she not take care of the bugs or those bugs? Nice. Good work
All right, i'm gonna call lois over because I need social anyways
Uh, lois griffin call invite over absolutely. We have so much to catch up on
awesome is
Uh, all right lois
Shake hands. I got 34 right now with lois. By the way peter's not here
Okay, good
No, no, no wait till 50 wait till 50 50 50 50 I don't want to do any like flirting flirting or anything till 50
Here it is, okay
um
Oh god damn it
Hey, it's okay. We're friends in courage 57
Yeah, I think i'm gonna wait i'll wait a day this is 60 this is this is really high
Get the fuck out of here
You're gonna ruin everything this is a scheme by peter this is one of peter griffin's schemes
I can't do anything about this
I can't kill the bear. I can't even attack the bear. I can't do anything. We're almost 80
For the puppet. Let's see if this kills it. Let's see if this ruins everything
Here comes
I brought the puppets a little too early, but it's okay
Okay, i'm almost at 100
This is as high as it can be 100, okay, i'm gonna wait a day
And then tomorrow
You'll come over it will hang out
Hi, have you seen that?
My social is all the way up. Well, it was really nice to see you. It was very nice to see you
See you later. There it is. There it is. There it is
Tomorrow that's at 100. It'll be a little hard there
And then we're gonna hang out
Just around peter. They don't have a pool
And no
All right. I gotta get to bed. I gotta have a good day tomorrow at work
All right. I need to do we need to go to bed now
Bed we have to have a good day at work tomorrow. I need that bonus
I need some fun. I need hygiene blah. Oh fuck. What's more important who's eating?
Okay. Now go to the bathroom. Just put it down. Put it down. Don't even wash it. Put it down
All right. That's not bad. That could be worse, but that
Right. That's all right. That's all right. I'm gonna make the money at least
You can go to the bathroom at work, but you can't shower at work. Not necessarily, right?
You've been promoted to bit player. You're able to support yourself in your own chosen career barely
You've actually got a few lines to speak
Ironically, they often seem to be may I take your orders sir building relationships and your body is important now
You now work from nine to three you brought home 200 and got a bonus of 400. Let's go
Now I got enough to get promoted again. I have enough body. I have enough charisma
I can get promoted again if i'm good enough. How's my relationship with lois?
I think I hold I think another day has to go by let's do this, right?
So now the plants are good. Everything's taken care of
House is in good order. Let's get i'm gonna sit here for a little while. I want that fun to go up
They like pissing anywhere outside
Yeah, of course you did
Okay, take a shower go to bed. I need I need a full night's sleep. I want that in comfort up
Put no strays sign so they stop pissing that work. Yes, they can read it
Oh, this is gonna be really really good day and then sit and play on the computer. What happened to the computer?
I put that down use the bathroom take a shower god. Everything sucks. No, just sit and sit you need to sit
Stop playing the fucking guitar
Put the guitar down dude. All right, whatever you didn't sing the fortnight song. I didn't woohoo lois
Okay, that's 200 bucks. I know i'm trying to get him out of the way get out of the way
Recycle recycle an anonymous gifter just gave 25 community subs from anonymous an anonymous gifter. Thank you for the 25
You know how we say it here?
Your immunity subs everyone like waits for it like he's gonna do that. He's gonna go community
All right, should I call lois? No one more day get this off. We're gonna sleep
Yeah, i'm good. Let's get uh, get some rest
I'll be able to wake up around 2 a.m. 3 a.m
Okay, i'm going to eat
Derma eat the poop what poop? Okay computer needs to be repaired
Need fun. All right, let's see if I can get this fixed. I'm getting very angry at this. What's going on?
What's going on? That's scary music. It's the bugs. All right, just get up call the repairman. I'm fixing the computer
Please fix my computer. They come over at 5 a.m. It's taking this guy so long to fix this
Oh my god
I'm gonna have to pay this guy like two hundred dollars. He's not done
Okay, we're good. He fixed it. Thank you and another 15 community subs from anonymous gifter who that could be
They were anonymous no promotion, but it's all right
Do I bills I have to pay? Is that good? Okay. How am I how's my relationship?
All right, we're gonna call lois. I'm gonna sleep and then today's the day it's off
Sleep for a while
I'm skipping work tomorrow
By the way, what the fuck are you doing here?
Why is mario here like
Oh, he's coming. What does he want?
What is he doing here?
Can I help you?
They live really far away
Holy shit mario has a huge ass
Now
Primp what are you doing?
Um, okay. Well
Okay, i'm done with mario. I at least I can call him now if I want to
i'm not going
to work today
I wish they were red
All right, so let's have mario. Let's have breakfast together
I'm not gonna kill mario. No
I want some breakfast mario
I've got your favorite. What does mario like to eat? What do the mario brothers eat spaghetti? Right? Okay
Well, it's not spaghetti. It's steak. It's steak every day
At least we can sit and have a conversation
You need to invite peter over and kill him. I don't need to do that yet
And I know I just said yet, but you know what I mean
He's new
becomes the newest mario brother
and zonk's lois griffin
That should be all capitals
a youtube title
I gotta pee again after this conversation with mario i'm going to
Drink a coffee feel like the espresso family like yesterday
All right, it was nice. Yeah, it was good to see you. Thanks for coming mario. It was good to see you again
Watch out for the spike trap
All right
Now i'm just gonna go to the bathroom and then i'm ready for maybe tomorrow. Maybe maybe wait
It seems like a really good
Bar right now. Let's see. Let's see if I skip work tomorrow. Maybe i'll skip work tomorrow depends on how good the bars are
was the car coming
an hour
Did I skip work i'm gonna go to work today, this is not bad this might be I might get promoted
Average shit, whatever. All right. I gotta call lois. I gotta pee too. All right. Hold on. Let me go actually go to the bathroom
I'll be right back. All right
I think I'm in the groove right now. I think I got it. I'm I'm making money. I'm not losing money like I was
Who peed thank you. I'm so glad that you're doing that. I just put like a fence this way and this way. No
You pumped to play the sims?
Yeah, I mean i've been playing it for like two days. I love this game. I mean it's
Harder than I remember it's still fun. Got it. Yes
You've been promoted to stunt double
That's not the box office megastar being set on fire and tossed from a helicopter. That's you
You're making a name for yourself
Though and directors like your novel ideas for mock mayhem
Keep those creative juices flowing
You just might graduate to a low budget starring role of your own if you survive keep yourself and your gear in top shape
But you may miss that airbag
Keep developing your active social life. Not only is it fun. It's very useful now make
Uh 275 dollars and I got 550 bucks
Awesome. All right. I need another body. I need four friends. I have three
Okay, I need I need one more family friend and I need to work out
Where's the workout bench? There it is. Do do it by the pool. There we go turn the mic on my yeah
My mic is on
How's lois all lois how's my energy it's good come on over
How nice of you sure i'll just brush my teeth and be right over. All right, let's make dinner serve dinner
Don't go on the computer serve dinner
Okay, dinner is ready. There she is. Hello lois. Oh, I i'll yeah
Coming don't eat without her. What the fuck are you doing?
My whole meal while she's outside
What the fuck are you doing?
I don't what why did that happen? That doesn't make any sense
Why would I sit down and eat my entire meal and I couldn't cancel it
But can you want to come over again? Sure. This place is dullsville. I'll have i'm gonna be at your place
All right, so clean this up. Here we go. Good to see you again. You're standing in the flower bed. That's not really good
Okay, how are you pulling the puppet out immediately? Where's flirt? Why is it not here dog is growling?
I'm so here's the puppet stop out just doing me in my own house. No
How do I make this bar go up? Oh, yeah, I have some dinner shit. I don't have energy
Why is flirt not here?
I'm at 100. Should I go should I try should I see if she like
I
Don't flush the toilet
I don't think i'm gonna be able to sing victory royale
While I woohoo lois, I don't think I can do that
How good how do I get the bar up below it
Your lifetime relationship changes slowly and shows how long-term trends remember
So how come this isn't going up? I think that's the problem
It has to be slowly. All right. All right. Fine. All right. Goodbye
You've only hung out twice
Oh one
Ladder peter
I don't even think her and peter are in a relationship
Laterum, so do I invite peter over in latterum? Is that what you're saying?
So stupid. I gotta go to work at the bed
You didn't meet him. I'll just go to the griffin house and i'll play as peter
Whatever. Okay, i'm gonna go play i'm gonna go play as peter. Is that cheating?
I need to invite me over the house so I can talk to peter so I can eventually latter him in my backyard
Whoa, this is like
I get to see what she thinks about me family, but who are they in but are they family?
What is lois griffin's relationship to peter griffin in this house friends family house?
No
Relationships it doesn't say sims can't be married in the first game unless you make them married through gameplay. Oh, wow
Okay. All right, so then I have to do anything. I don't I don't need to kill peter. They're not even married
Oh god, I gotta get her
I gotta get her stuff up. That's why I have to keep
Comforting her you notice that it's it's always an option for me to cheer her up. Okay. Um
Peter get up get out of bed. Who's in the comfortable bed? Who's that chris? Get up go sleep there lois
Go sleep in this bed take his place in this house. What's going on? All right, you go sleep in this bed
That's why I have to keep cheering her up. What's going on? No, go back to bed. Why are you getting up?
Where are you going? Oh eating? Okay making another bed
This is a one-to-one recreation of the entire griffin household. There isn't another bed. I'm not gonna add that
See, did you just come to turn the tv on in the room?
Your investments have paid a dividend
What? Hey, it's good
Back to bed
Now use the bathroom and now she'll be fine
Every single tv in the house is just on
Bathroom i'll take a shower
Take a shower and use the bathroom. All right. Now she'll be the i'm not gonna have to just only cheer up
sleep
Please go
Okay. Now let's call should I call me over?
Invite germa over
All right, he's coming over. He's coming. He's coming. He's coming. He's coming. What's going on? Why they have bugs everywhere
Whoa, I brought something
Oh, I brought a box of chocolates for her. Wow. Come on in there. I am germa
Don't cheat switch households cheating cheating cheating. All right. Fine. It's cheating
Okay
All right, i'm gonna change households. Oh lois. I'm gonna scare you. All right. What am I doing?
That work. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man
The heart is there. What did I do? No, i'm at work. Where am I? All right 275 good
Let's watch let's play some computer games and then i'm calling lois over not going to work tomorrow, by the way
All right. Perfect all lois. Let's go for it invite over i'll be there over and i'll be there in a bit
Okay, here we go. This is it
This is an opportunity to make to keep this relationship going
Don't have dinner serve dinner hungry and i'm going to use the bathroom
I'm gonna plot it's gonna plant
Thank you for the plant
It's so thoughtful of you
Let's have grab a plate
Let's eat. Let's talk just casually have fun. Just talk to each other. Let's play. All right. That's all right
Okay
Use the bathroom
And let's start maybe build building a maybe if you want to tease me. Okay, that's up. Let me just use the bathroom first
Let's see what that means link. I can't click like there are no links links have been turned off until the solution comes forward
Which will be within the next few weeks. Don't get mad that she just walked in. All right. Come on
What did you want? I'm gonna let her you okay. She wants to tease me
God damn it
whatever
Um, i'll call you tomorrow. All right, everything breaks. Everything breaks
Everything breaks. Come on over fix my stuff. Thank you. What a bed. Thank you
This is a good I might get promoted. No, I won't
I'm not gonna get I need another friend
No, fuck work. I'm not going to work. I'm skipping work today
I've got 1300 bucks. I got money. I'm good
I'll be right over. All right, awesome. I'm not gonna get fired. Don't do it. Don't go to work. Don't go to work
There's a friendly hug at work, okay got it got it here it is
Yes, oh no dance with me
That's fun
Shit, you choked. I what? No, I didn't
How'd I blow it? I'm fine
I didn't ruin it. I'm fine. Everything's fine
No game andy
Okay, nice hug, okay. All right good
Who's this from a place? I have been edging for three and a half hours
I don't know. I don't know what that is. I but I think I can figure that out
Why did I I just reckon said that it's stupid for me to say that out loud. Why did I do that?
I don't I don't I like don't know what that is, but I kind of do
I don't know what that means
I don't know why I read that. I just it was just happening
I don't know. I don't I don't understand the chat goes so fast. Do you understand like look at how fast the chat is mine?
You understand I can't like why does that happen? I like laser to like the fucked up stuff
How did I read that like how do I read these things? I don't know how I read them
All right. I'm I think I can i'm gonna try to just do like a polite kiss
All right, just like swim in my hand. We're hanging out that sound. What the fuck that's sound
That's sound
Uh
You have to flirt more. I don't even have a flirt option. You know what? Let's let's go downtown
You and me let's do it
Hug me
Is there a raccoon in the house?
We need to change
Okay pet shop food. Let's go to
Somewhere we can like dance
Local meeting place. There we go. Like right here. Why don't I have my clothes off? Did I just deny her?
I just denied a hug. What I denied her
Invite home. Wait, how would I do? Why did I deny her a hug?
I can't
This needs to be way higher
All right. Okay. Let's go do like an activity while we're here. What is this? This is like an activity
What activity is this?
It's like this is a I thought this was a ride. This is a bathroom. Where am I? What are you?
You doing? What am I doing? What the fuck am I doing? Okay. All right. All right
Uh on drugs where's lois come play like pinball
Peter is here this princess peach
I want to greet princess peach. What am I doing? Are you doing dude? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
I just gave that guy five dollars
What did I do
Is
Let's leave let's get out of here leave leave leave leave leave let's get out of here
Let's get oh fuck
No, what the hell is happening?
Oh my fucking god. What happened? What the fuck happened? What happened?
Why?
Why don't understand? Why do I wear my options? Why can't I flirt?
What is an air kiss
Oh, that's peter
What did I just do that to this is it to her what happened to is lois not even on the bar anymore
Go for peter
Go with peter. What about peach?
In a little moment now, she's like on a date with walt. I have no idea. I don't know who walt is
There's a cameraman
They're filming the next mario movie
I would that would not be interesting. I would not like that at all. I'd be like what the fuck is wrong with you
So why can I flirt with peter but I can't flirt with lois?
You're making all the voices. I mean what all right. Goodbye. Why couldn't I do that to lois?
Why couldn't we had an opportunity to like ask to like to flirt and stuff all I could do with lois
Was like passionately kiss politely kiss and intimately hug. Where's the flirting? I didn't have any of these options
Where was this? I couldn't do this
All right. I'm gonna try again. I'm gonna call
Why is he?
Look at how much money points I have with lois and looking for his peter and I could flirt with peter
But I can't flirt with lois. Where's meg why I can say that to her
I'm going home. I'm trying something. I have to go to work tomorrow. I'm gonna get fired
Damn it. I thought that was gonna be the day
All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know I know go to the bathroom
Go right get ready for work tomorrow
Don't sit take a shower eat dinner go to work and then we're gonna try this again
I don't have any paintings on the walls
What spend some time with lois griffin if you don't want your friendship to languish
She just told me to fuck off was that her calling that was her on the phone. Oh shit
She wanted all right. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to go to work tomorrow
I can't believe I blew it. I didn't even mean to I don't have all my options were terrible
It might be the astrological signs
That's probably a lot to do with it. I think it's we'll try again
She just called she was like hey talk to me. So i'm gonna i'll call
Never flush the fucking toilet flush the toilet. Like why are you doing this? Oh my god. I hate this character
No, stop doing that
Now go play on the computer. I can't believe I lost everything with lois
Pain in the ass. Okay. There we go. Oh my god
How could you ever how did they how did how do you ever play this game with more than one person in the house?
I don't think it's possible. Let's rekindle. How nice of you to invite me. Okay, i'll brush my teeth. All right
We let's try this again. There she is. Oh no toilet
Keep her out of the bathroom. Keep her out of the bathroom. Keep her out of the bathroom
Feeder and go unclog the toilet. No, don't do that. It's good to see you. Let's talk. Let's hang out
It's been too long it's been too long, you know what I mean?
Yeah, it's been forever. Okay back to being friend. You're up in courage. Wait, she's distracted by the dog. Wait, wait, wait
We can't talk like this. All right, what were you saying? Okay
friendly
But where is the other stuff cheer up with the what I I need to like play as lois and because she's not she's unhappy
All right. All right. All right. Right. Right. It has no effect. She resets when she visits
But show in the bathroom talk to her
Someplace other than the bathroom
Brushing my teeth
Oh, what the hell?
burp in the mirror
Okay, so she's hungry
All right, all right, here's a nice dinner
See back up to like 87
Remove the plant
Plant this is her friend's stat. Yeah, I know I but I have to get
I have to get her to like me again
She likes me before
Why would I insult?
You're seriously gonna go to bed. I'm skipping work tomorrow
Imagine going to bed while the woman you is dancing. I know I look
No, you got it
It's only five. Oh, it's five a.m. All right. I'm not going to work. I went to work yesterday, right?
Is it like my skills or something? Do I need like mechanics? Do we need like logic to talk better?
I don't need to work. I went to work yesterday. I think i'm fine. Why don't you eat actual food like it's dinner
Let me serve dinner. It's three o'clock
Okay, we're gonna call turn this off
Go to the bathroom
And i'm gonna call lois
It's my charisma my charisma is pretty high, isn't it? It's yeah, that's pretty high
Okay, she's coming over let's work out my charisma in the meantime
All right, hello nice to see you again
Teasing
Okay
Teasing again
I think it's funny
What else are you gonna do? Give me the heart. Where's the heart?
Dance
What the fuck
All right, let's eat. Let's don't play the fucking guitar. All right, let's eat. I'm just hanging out talking just chilling
She's in the pool now
Okay, here she is
And all right. So now
All right. How are you?
Excuse me
What the fuck would I deny that for I just did it
I
Stop denying her. What am I what the fuck is this game doing? I just denied her twice
Holy shit
What are these dumb games? We are both playing
Okay, I could flirt that one time
What the fuck where did it go? I just had flirt. I just flirted and now I can't flirt again
It's never worked it's always gone wrong
It's never has never worked
once
Why is it even a clickable option? It's never it's nobody ever wants that she fucking combo
She combo breakered you
She's leaving. Okay, does he know that he's already friend-zoned and cannot have a romance. What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
She tried to intimately hug me twice and I was like get off get away from me get away from me
And then I went to go into you know what I mean? Like why am I doing that?
I just tried to initiate
You're incompatible
They say we're incompatible
We'll show them
I feel like every fucking song you've ever heard it's about like how we're incompatible but we're gonna it
How it doesn't you know, it doesn't matter. It's like every single fucking love song i've ever heard in my life
I think it's some of the most famous love songs you've ever heard for instance
That's a famous one
Remember that infomercial that came on every day with the love songs
I was like i've looked forward to that part every time it came on
If you know, you know, and I don't I don't have to explain that don't you only listen to video game music
I'm calling peach. Do I even have peach's number? Oh shit. It's 3 a.m. Do I have her number?
No, I gotta get like one of the mario brothers to invite me over their house
If you spam the same interaction to lower the success chances time do different things
Well, I only have three options kiss hug or talk about interests
I haven't I can't talk about anything else with her. I can only do like the puppet and like cheer up
I gotta go to work tomorrow get get it. Relax. I have to go to work. I can't just not go to work
I'm sure i'm gonna i'm gonna call peach. I gotta go meet peach first of all, that's important
Go to work. Where's the car?
No, why did I get fired?
shit
Can I get the job back?
This game sucks
Why is you nobody works every single day of the week
Monday through monday with not a day off
What the fuck sims 1?
What are you doing?
There's no days off
You work every single fucking day of your life
Not one day off ever
I'm throwing a fucking party. I just got fired party bring everybody. Who is it? Who's talking to me?
Oh shit, I got 450 bucks
All right, come on what we got we got
We got emma
We're looking for we're looking for a mario
What am I doing?
Go greet your guests
These people hate each other
All right, I gotta relax my fucking stomach's gonna hurt
No, don't
Go open the door
I need more people there until I need to call people that I need somebody I need a friend of a friend
To keep bringing friends of a friend until we have peach here
More people more
Each no, there's one. Does anybody know peach? That's mario. This is the same person. It's the same person
The same person showed up twice
There's no food
All right. I'm gonna make dinner. I'm gonna make dinner. Wait, wait. No, no, no, no. I have a better idea
Where is it? I know it exists. Where is it? There's like a full catering table. I know it exists
What's it under miscellaneous? Where's the stupid thing? Where's the catering table?
Wait a turkey. Hold on. I'm gonna I gotta bring where's the turkey these menus suck. Where's the turkey other? I got all right
Okay, go go. Go. Go. Go. Where's peach?
Damn it. I need to get a turkey piece. They're clapping for me. Where's peach?
All right turkey dinner. Everyone's eating. It's just not here. God. Damn it. I can't even get to the phone
I can't even get to my own phone get out of the fucking way, please
I need to throw a party. I need peach to show up
Okay, the animals answered the phone. No. No, I have an idea. I have an idea. Let's kick everybody out until we get peach
Whoa, where wait, where are who's here? It's peach here. That's peach
It's peach in the room. Can anybody tell?
I need to show up
Peach
Somebody has to know peach does nobody know her leave until I get the guy that screamed
Is she in this group
Everybody get out of the fucking way
Get out get out you piece of shit
You can't kick the shit out of you out of the way get out of the way get out of my fucking way
Trapping me here. Yeah
There's my there she is
No
Move move out of the way go
Get out of the way. Where is she?
Hey
Go outside
Tell this person to leave they're in the way
Leave get out get out of my way
Chill out. I can take a hint. Why don't you try having a party for a change? Sheesh. I'm out of here. Fuck off
I just need to talk to peach to get the phone number to call her
move
She can't get in the house. I can't leave
Oh my god, this is so frustrating
dude
Just get outside. Oh, she got it. She got it. She got it. She got it
Get over there
Please I just need to talk to her once so she's on the list of people to call
Come on
No
Get up
Get up and talk
I just need to say two words
Here we go
Yes
Oh, thank god
All right, everyone needs to leave now
Anybody want any more turkey?
What happened? I didn't I kick this lady out?
She just fucked with my toilet. She clogged the toilet and clapped
You piece of shit
You can't use it
It's a clogged toilet
Is anybody
That's disgusting
That girl that I threw out fucking dropped a she probably dropped like a dump in the tank not in the toilet and she then she clapped
Where am I?
This lady's stuck in here
I need to I gotta all right. I gotta detonate this
Who's asleep?
All right, hold on it's time for everybody to leave it's time for everybody to leave I gotta get I wait I got oh
I already got fired. Never mind
There's no food. There's a full turkey on the table
God some guy serve breakfast for all these fucking animals
I can't even get to the fridge
I can't even move
Get to it's too late. See you. Yeah, get the fuck out of here
Yeah, leave all of you
Everybody's leaving finally
Why is that person have a clothes on?
The person's naked
I just now pick that up and finish it. At least i'll eat it
That's kenny
You guys find it fucking irritating that the person that I kicked out first the person that I scolded
Is the last one to leave
And she still hadn't left and she clogged my toilet and ruined everything she's still here
She's not leaving
Finally get out of here
What a disaster at least I got peach's phone number
Oh, that was fucking horrible
That was disgusting
Oh my god, my stomach hurts
Okay. Well, i'm gonna give the maid like a 200 tip today
Right, like come on. Look at this
oh
People just pissing and shitting in this
Turn it off
Piper
Oh, I can't
Oh my goodness. That was funny. All right, go play on the computer, dude. Just like
Have like lunch and go play on the computer take a shower
and then
Go play on the computer for a day
Oh
Oh my god, when was the last time I paid my bills? You're right. What happened? Wait, what was it so?
She didn't even wait. She just
She put
Thing in and spun it around in there and then didn't fix it
and honestly
Yeah, like good good for her because that's disgusting
Shouldn't have to do that
You shouldn't have to do it. You took one look at it and said no I ain't putting that no
This is fucking filthy and left
Good for you because that's horrible
like seriously
These are gonna be red, aren't they?
God damn it. It takes a month to clean this all up
I know it's not fun to go play on the computer. Just don't use the bathroom. All right. I got peach's number
That's all that matters. Don't unclog this fucking toilet you disgusting disgusting human
Use that
Okay, play on the computer get some sleep and then you're gonna call peach tomorrow. What a mess
All right, get some sleep. Have a quick dinner. That's fine
And go to bed
Assholes
Gonna knock the trash over right?
Yeah, okay fine. Get out of here
a little weasel
Okay, it's 2 a.m. Have some food get back in bed. Actually get back in bed. It's too early
Wake up at like eight
There we go
Wash this clean this clean this
Clean this up. Take a shower get a hold of yourself
Use it
Okay, call
Peach here we go. Come on over love to i'm bored. All right, i'm gonna serve lunch peach might be hungry
It's here. All right
Get a job. I had a job. I had a good job and then I got fired
So just give me a minute. Let me build a relationship. Oh great. Okay, very nice to meet you peach
So let's have a conversation. Yeah, you know what, you know, let's have let's eat too. Let's eat
Okay, so uh, you want to grab a plate and maybe sit down and hang out?
All right. We I already got i'm already more compatible with peach than lois. Perfect. Let's eat
We can just kind of hang out and talk perfect. Nobody gonna say anything
Oh, dude, you i'll be a bro, bro. You can't let her finish the food for you. No, bro, bro
You got hurry up. Come on. You gotta eat that steak faster. Don't let it finish before you bro
Oh, bro, you fucked it up bro compliment admire compliment. All right. Here we go. This is gonna be this is gonna work
Here it comes
Good I don't know what that was it was kind of weird
Um, okay
No, I don't do that yet. Let's just talk
uh about interests
I already have a lot more things to do here friendly hug. This is going up so much faster
Look at how much faster this is going up. It took me forever lois and I just weren't compatible at all
Look at how much more compatibility there is here
You know
Friendly hug
Okay
Do you like that too?
Oh, she's not a friend yet. All right, i'm gonna i'm gonna tell a joke
And then i'm gonna juggle
You'd like the joke
She like juggling
No, she doesn't like jugglers
Fine. Who is it? It's lois
Lois you can fuck off
No, no, don't leave don't leave don't leave. I was telling her. No, I was telling leave me alone
I should have even answered the phone do it again tomorrow
Yeah, she really hates juggling. That was such a
Brash reaction to a juggler i've ever seen
And then i'm gonna eat and then play on the computer get it all queued up. Let's go
And i'll be ready to go. Did you make master chief?
Okay, take a little nap take a nap put that comfort up
It'll be money. That could be money. It could be money. It could be money you idiot
It takes an hour and a half to wait two hours to wake up. Why oh neighbor paul
Come over i'd love to all right. Let's let's go for it. I need to at least make her a friend
Alert before she's your friend. It's necessary. Is it? All right, here we go. Get off the computer. All right
Oh you've been my god, there's a lot
Um
Okay
Like that too
Save caramel
Caramel's fine. Okay, pretty good. So now
Now
New friend
Now let's just let's get up. I'll make some i'll make some dinner. I'll make some lunch
You had to go to the bathroom really bad. Okay, i'm gonna make the lunch
Have a snack you can go swimming. I gotta I got a nice pool
I'll go i'll go swimming, too
All right, let's hang out. Look at what he's talking and chilling and hanging out
And then i'm we're gonna get up
Lois griffin's no longer a friend. I don't care
Mm
What just happened what just happened we were talking I didn't do anything
I that's this game. I swear to god is just throwing dice in the air if a conversation is gonna work
What we were just sitting there eating dinner
All right family friend. Okay 73. I need that. I need the little heart. Come on
This is the dumbest video game i've ever played. What the fuck just happened
I just hugged her and then she hugged me and I said get out of here
And then she left how are you ever supposed to get anybody to like you? You can't flirt because you're friends
Not dating what?
She's a family friend. What I was flirting with her and that's what got her to be a family friend
You can't be friends
what
Friendly hugged her be mean to her loser as a friend and then flirt with her try lois this time
What are we doing? Oh, it's an old games room. They didn't know how healthy relationships worked
Just be friend i'm not even friends with her anymore what happened
You have to spend a trivially amount of time building this relationship. All right, fine
Let's go downtown and hang out. Let's call taxi and just go hang out at the here
Just use the cheat code. No, I can't cheat
Okay, we're now friends. So i'm just gonna leave it as is we're just gonna talk and we're gonna go on like a little date
Already friends on I didn't do anything they shook hands at the date and I became friends
I just gonna drown peter in this pond. All right, come with me
Come just sit on the bench with me and play in the fountain. Where'd she go? All right, come sit over here
Juggle lose her as a flat friend and then flirt flirt flirt flirt
No, that's not how it worked lois had a
Smiley face and a heart missed crumple bottom. This is nice. This is nice
worked
Now we clap not yet
Mama, I don't want mama to come over and compliment me
This miss crumple bottom keeps coming over here
This game is stupid
Now watch she's gonna come try to like kiss me and i'm gonna go
And i'm gonna push her away watch i'm not gonna do anything i'm doing that that's so weird
That's weird. Don't do that. Why would you be like?
Sleep right here. This is fucking weird. What are we doing?
I get no i'm not gonna try again. No, it's not I have to wait till I have to wait
This is sims 2 you would have 10 girlfriends already that's how it works
It's the worst date ever
I thought she's gonna pee her pants
She doesn't know where the bathroom is. Is there even a bathroom here? I'm gonna go to the boat thing
Beach come over here. Let's do let's do a let's get like a radio-controlled boat
It's like too far away
Mario and princess
All right, i'm gonna leave we're gonna go home
It'd be all right. That was fun rent a picnic basket for a hundred bucks
No, no, thanks
Hey peter in here with me
How are you how's things peter?
Doing good. That's good. Where's peach?
Um, how are you? Let's go. Let's go. No, no back to my date
Oh
Uh-oh what he hugged by lois. Where is lois? How does she have binoculars?
Why what the he hugged
When and then all of a sudden now i'm deciding I would want I want that to happen now
I don't know what to do anymore. I don't know what I don't know what is supposed to work
We're not it's not doing it. It's the way this is not going well
I don't know. What am I supposed to do?
What what should I do?
He's like, please help me. I don't know what i'm doing. You think I know what i'm doing either
So if I initiate it
If I if I say hey, I would love to give you like a nice big hug
I'll give her i'll go for the hug
If they come to give me a big hug, i'm like get away from them
It within the same five second period within the same two second period
Because you smell
Oh god, can I shower in the bathroom?
I'll be right back
Just i'll be right back
Get in the bathroom and just wash your hands
Get in the fucking bathroom dude, what are you doing? Oh wash your hands shit god damn it
They're pissed
Lois is off the meter. By the way, she's gone. Look at how bad that was
She she came she found me with fucking binoculars
Tried to give me a hug. I told him to fuck off. I then tried to hug her and it works
Let's get out of here
Somebody said man, you suck at this game. I came here with 70 and then I left it with 50. No, this game's hard. It's
You just watched that happen. I got like followed here by lois
She just found me here and started trying to talk to me to hug me
I denied her. I then tried to have a casual conversation with her. I tried to hug her within five seconds
The whole thing freaks everything freaks out peach then fucking hates me
I go I smell I go wash my hands in the bathroom and at that moment is when they all leave
I'm never gonna have i'm never gonna get like a
Spouse I have to go home now. It's a time to is it time to date peter?
I don't know. I feel like the same thing's gonna happen
What a mess
And I don't even I don't have a job. How are you? All right
How are you supposed to?
Keep up relationships and go to work every single day in the sims one other. How do they think that was gonna work?
Like eat something and then go play in the computer and then do I even dare try to call anybody and everybody anybody come over
And hang out with me
Um, okay. I was gonna say lois has 25 down here. I call lois again
Lois is the highest peach bank account is getting dangerously low
Go gamble
I think I will I think we're gonna have to
I took a shower last night. How is it at zero fucking thing out of here? I think it's annoying
What time is it? It's 8 pm. Who do I have some? Okay, so i'm gonna call lois. I got I gotta get social
This is fine. All right, this is gonna be fine comfort's good. Let's wake up and i'm gonna call lois
I just wanted to hear germa sing and see auto. I mean, I want to sing the victory royale song, too
Should I call peach?
Should I try lois? She did come find me yesterday
We have to catch up. Okay, so this time i'm gonna do what you guys said
I'm not gonna try to i'm not gonna make friends. How's caramel? Um, we'll check i'll check on caramel later
All right, where's lois? Is lois? All right, let's have i'll serve dinner. Peter is in love with you date him
Air kiss. I'm just let's let's just let okay flight. No, no, don't do that
I
Got dinner on the table. I'm in a pretty good mood except for like all the dog pee
That's by the way in the corners of the map
This pet's expansion that they did was terrible
Like why do I have to take care of this?
The room is so bad because there's pee in the corners of the lot that are my dogs. They're not my animals
All right, let's go ahead and sit down sit down
Stop watering your plants you fucking weirdo get in there
Okay, so
How are you?
I can't do anything besides friendly
There's no flirt
It's the sims how are you losing
Uh, the difference between the sims 4 and the sims 1
Is the sims 4 is viva piata and the sims 1 is dark souls with a blindfold on
That's the difference in difficulty. Is she fucking leaving?
Oh my god
You just ate and left
Come on
I'm not even hungry. I'm just eating it because that's made and it's I have to eat it the house is clean. All right
Tomorrow i'm doing it. We're going forward tomorrow
Take a shower
Get some rest and then we're gonna we're gonna hang out all day tomorrow. We're gonna do something fun
I'm gonna wake up at a normal time. Okay. No, you don't need to eat right now. Go play video games
like three four hours
What games more what's more realistic of this or facade?
Um, I mean that's probably this
All right. Now let's i'm gonna take another nap. No, don't make that. I want to take a nap. Why can't I sleep?
Okay
call
neighbor
Okay, he's just coming over 48 16 48
All right. It's all right. It's all right. Come on sit down here start with a kiss
I don't that's a horrible. I what just happened only kiss because if I start with this
Then then i'm looking for a relationship and i'm not a friend. Is that what you're talking about?
I can't
I'm not gonna flatter them. No
Where's my
Neat outgoing active playful nice
What's wrong?
So what?
I'm just a libra. Hold on most compatible with virgo and cancer
Lea, what are you? Virgo and cancer. This cancer
They're all cancer
I didn't even I didn't do anything to our friends. Okay
I'm not gonna do anything
Let's just continue to they'll just talk and hang out
Oh
No, i'm not you don't kiss i'm not gonna kiss now no I need to flirt first
How did I get the heart last time with lois, I don't even remember
Oh
It was an on-the-cheek kiss how it happened kiss is an upgraded flirt
Me who didn't i'm laying kind
75 and friend
You kiss the cheek is that what this is this is an upgraded flirt
It doesn't doesn't with the maid no, that's I can't
Let's just go in the pool. I'm at 68 though. I was at like 100 game is broken. No, it's not
You need more long-term points
How many days have to go by for this to go up?
I feel like this has been over 40 or 50 for like a week
Two weeks
It takes multiple months for this to go up
You need the daily relationship to be over seven 70. Okay top bar is daily in lifetime bar
So the top bar has to be over 70 the bottom bar has to be over what?
Real lifetime is the bottom bar in game time is the top bar
70 is to get a crush
Really? I actually I need I need to make money somehow
Have one of them move in. I don't think I can do that
70 on the bottom bar is love
Oh, okay
What you're saying is
I should just
sleep
And like pass time for like three weeks
And just make sure all the lights are off
I'm just gonna get a job
And just do nothing but just go to work for like a month in the game
And i'm just gonna i'm just gonna let the game play itself
And every week i'm gonna call her over to hang out and just hang out
Okay, that sounds good to me talk to her on the phone. That's oh, yeah, right. Right. Good idea
Why she's getting just keep going to my pool, okay get a job
Uh business career. No hacker. No
medical career, um
Sure, whatever. I'll be a doctor like jokes
You like that joke, okay
Okay
74 77. All right. That looks pretty good. One more time 80 83. Um
Get up
It didn't kill her
Why did that why didn't she just leave what the fuck is happening?
Can I wake her up?
Okay, i'm gonna go put the stereo on here. I have to put the stereo on her and turn it on
Just wait wait wait wait wait
I have to wake her up
Get up and go
Okay. Goodbye
a
A hug just a hug. Goodbye. Just a bye
Goodbye. Good to see you again. Thank you for coming
Now I just have to tomorrow. Oh my god. Look at my stuff
I got this is this is getting higher. I'm just gonna okay i'm just gonna work and then call her
Can I scream in my sleep?
All right, get up enough time for you just to go out the door
Okay, i'm just gonna let this play i'm just gonna sit on time's five speed
Welcome home. Yep. Just let him just just let him just do it
Don't need to do anything. We're just trying to wait for that bar to go at least over like 40 or 50
20 20 rock on. Oh nice. I got a creative point. It doesn't go up passively
I thought it's just like over time
I thought that was my house burning down
Okay, i'm gonna call her just give her a call every night
Okay, i'm gonna call her when I get home
Get the fuck out of bed
You idiots, why did you sleep you?
Why?
Why I look at my energy what the hell happened?
What the fuck? I know I can't supposed to be at work right now. You need to get an alarm clock
What time is it? All right, call peach. I just want to talk. Okay, call her again
Blah blah blah blah blah
Oh, whatever
Hey, hey peach. I missed work again
Go back to bed
Back to gambling it is I actually might have to play on the computer till the fucking car gets here
Is my I might actually get promoted
I'm getting another point and creative
Nice. All right. That's probably how much do I have?
Holy shit. I need to drop that has creativity in it. Where's the car? What a work each 20 get out easel
Oh my god, that's a good idea. I need a chair. So I have I have stuff
I have things I can sell I have things I can sell i'll be okay. I can start selling. Um furniture and stuff
Don't worry. I'm fine. This is 170 bucks for the bills pay them
A painting i'm just gonna quit my job and just paint if my creativity is that high
I might be able to sell them for a lot. I kind of want to be able to see it already done. That's awful
I'm quitting my job. I've quit my job as a doctor and i'm just gonna paint call peach use the love magic
No, i'm not magical. I'm not doing magical
I'm gonna do i'm i'm not gonna cast spells on people
Dude, are you serious?
Hold on. Let me just like let me just take care of the worst expansion in the in the whole game
Okay, why?
Oh my god
stupid
It's 5 a.m. No one's gonna pick up the phone
Put it inside
What time what time are you not supposed to call people?
Your sims an asshole
I'm not an asshole
I'm not going to work quit
I quit
Okay, call peach
I'm not going to work. Just leave i'm not going. I don't often these they these never work
Okay, come on in it's social
That's the food. I was just eating. I didn't do that. I didn't do this
Talk about cats coward
They don't they just don't like any animals you can't click on anything which is the general basic talk
Now she doesn't even want to talk to me
Like a bath
She just all right peach just come I figured it out peach just comes over and swims in my pool and then leaves
She's visiting the house and she doesn't want to talk to you. She's coming over to swim
And eating like I she's come i'm feeding her and she's swimming in my pool. She just kicked you out
All right a week we talked to okay, come sit down be hugged. Okay, this is where this game doesn't
If I reject this hug
I'm gonna be furious. This is a hundred
Okay, she did that twice this is 100
Why do I not have like flirt or anything? I didn't click this
Ladder
No, okay. I'm at a hundred
Oh the ladder i'm not selling the ladder
I am dedicated to make to getting this to work
I need to paint right now
Please just like talk to me or something like I need somebody to talk to me. I won't paint
But she won't talk to me
I have to talk a bunch of times. This is all I can do. That's not going to guarantee me like a bad
Come on
Where are why am I surrounded by animals
Okay, thanks for coming. You didn't help at all. I at least got another few points
Animals give social. Yeah, you're right. I keep forgetting that tomorrow. I paint
Why is she not getting out of the pool?
I'm dreaming of her. Okay, go ahead and get up. Goodbye. He's calling me at 10 o'clock at night
The number six will be very important for you in the next 24 hours
What's that supposed to mean? What the hell are you talking about?
I go back to bed
Six I have to paint a painting and sell it not going to work. You can fire me. I don't care
I have bills to pay but it's fine. Take a shower
Play on the computer and then i'm gonna paint I got fired good. All right, i'm ready to paint. Oh something good something nice
Eight at six p.m
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Am I painting her? Come on
Come on. It's almost done done sell painting. What do I get for it? I have like a bunch of creative
Forty dollars was very that was not good another creativity point. That's another creative point. All right, I should get more for this
Almost six. All right, it's six
Six p.m. What should I do? Why not? I have to go to bed. I'm gonna finish the painting tomorrow
Oh the fucking tv
God damn it. It's been out there for a month call peach over i'm at 26 take some food
I'm gonna serve breakfast. I'm gonna call her over. It's 1 a.m. God damn it
All right, where are the wild animals? Is there any animals to play with outside? All right, go back to painting really do it
Come on
Sell it it's done
Shit, it's almost done
Should adopt the dog. It's probably gonna cost too much money
Can I chat on the computer? No, unfortunately not
Why is your character insane?
This is every sim
all sims
Zero social. All right call peach over i'm over
Yes, all right. What do we have 26? Oh my god bills. She brought food. I'm sorry. They're oh shit
This is bad. I'm gonna have to start selling furniture
I almost have painting done
We're eating chocolates off the ground. All right, let's talk
Hang out and have a conversation
I can't go higher than this
And now i'm gonna have to eat some food and i'm not gonna buy it. So
Are you leaving? I didn't like that
Sell the gift for money
My social is still this bad. I just talked to her for like four hours
I really do just need to get like a dog or something
Where's it was an animal I hear a cat just come over here just play with animals for like the day
Hey, it's actually better. Yeah
This feels like
This feels dumb
I'm just I just have to pet I have to just talk to all the hang out with all the pets here
And i'll fill the bar in and not even an hour
Talking to an actual person does not raise my bar guarantee issues in the pool right now swimming guarantee it
I should have bet I should have bet money on that. I should have bet money on that. It was a mistake
Like
Social it what did that say?
All right, I can fill the social bar by hanging out with animals. Oh god. She's annoyed. Was she bored? She's coming to hug me
Okay
All right. I was hanging out with animals instead of you
Hug hug hug hug be hugged
30 who's going to bed?
Inviting somebody over just to play with cats in the road this poop on the ground
That's why it's this hidden poop everywhere. Isn't there is that the problem?
Is there just hidden shit all over the place?
Okay, I need to go to bed now
I gotta sell this painting and pay these bills or yippee finish the painting tomorrow when you get up. Well first play
League of legends for like six hours and then finish the painting
I'm determined to sell these paintings for a lot of money. I have to fire somebody. Here we go
I'm gonna go hard with painting. Check this out. Let's go nap on the couch for like half an hour paint
Let's go finish it. Look at this. Look at my mood. Come on
Okay, sell it 71 bucks
All right now do another one. It's the same painting. No, I just did this one. Come on. I have another point in creativity. Yes
Finish it sell it 71. All right. How many I am almost at full creativity almost 100 percent
All right. Now I can pay these bills. There's more in there. Okay. I'm not gonna pay these yet
We're gonna do that. I'm gonna paint again tomorrow. Trust me. This is this is gonna be the meta watch this shit
I found what I want to do to bed
I'm gonna get to 100 all points in creativity and i'll be able to sell these paintings for like thousands let's eat
Play league of legends eat some food and let's do another painting. I can wait piss
Take a shower take a nap on the couch paint. Let's do another painting. This is i'm gonna get max points here. Come on
It's taking so long. What can I get for this one? 100 bucks. Okay
All right more come on. Give me another point in creativity. Yes, I am
One point away from having 100 creativity. That is now as much as a job would pay
I just have to do it every day. Don't pay those bills yet. All right, I need it to
Where the animals go go hang out with the dogs for a while. I'm just min maxing
The dog go hang out with the kids just go back and forth between these two
You're if you're fine. You have no no no no play with them. Don't go sit down play with the dogs
This is so this is such a uh sims hack or whatever. I got enough money there. That's fine in bed
Again tomorrow and i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna do it. Here's here's the plan
i'm going to do three paintings
At max creativity if I make less than 200 dollars
On one of those three paintings if I don't make at least 200 bucks from those paintings
I'm going to uninstall the sims one if I don't make 200 bucks from one of the paintings
I'm uninstalling the game. I'm gonna do three paintings
Over full creative bar. Otherwise, what the hell you can't make more than 160. Oh
Never mind that's off the table. Okay, i'm realizing what i'm doing. All right, everyone is everyone's freaking out. I'm realizing what's happening
I'm flushing the toilet and then using it because i'm it's i'm trying to okay
But why won't I just flush the damn toilet? That's so stupid
Relationship is still 30
Uh, let's watch i'm gonna watch tv
Their dog was the dog the dog in here somewhere
right paint
under 35
Again, oh, yeah
135 all right, hang out with the animals social social social social
That that i'm glad they came in
All right. Thank you. Go to bed have a snack. So what else can I do with max creativity?
Is there anything else I can do to make money? What's the best career to do with max creative?
Play the music
musician
Oh, okay. All right. Did that work? It was in that order flush clean
Shower eat paint. Nope watch tv. Wait turn this off. What is it? What is it? Who is it?
You can get wood making table to create gnomes
I'll look into that your friend is finally returning the money he borrowed from you three years ago plus interest
Thanks to the 1100 dollars. Nice always answer the phone. All right, i'm at max creative
I'm gonna get the gnome making bench. It's taking a long time. All right, sell it. What's it max creative?
That's not a painting. I did max creative
This is a painting at max creative. Is it actually 160? It should be more than that
166 that's actually a really good income if I just paint two paintings a day
That's like almost 400 a day. That's like three something a day. All right, that's good. What are we guys talking about?
This is like this gnome bench creativity craft king woodworking table
This basic workbench comes complete with saw mallet chisel and vise
Increase your home improvement skills while creating unique objects for display or sale. Okay craft a gargoyle
All right, can't sell it. All right, so i'm gonna make like some gnomes. This is mechanical. Oh, whatever
All right, i'm gonna pee again. I'm not done stream's not over i'm going to pee. We're coming back
I'm really gonna try wait. I got 30 here. I'm gonna go for this. I'll be back in a few minutes. All right, let's go for it
At least I have a source of income now
Not having the source of income was horrible
I can at least sell a painting if I need to for like 160 bucks
Now I can focus on
Peach in fact, hold on. There's a dog in here do it again again
Again I used to hate the fact that there were animals everywhere now. I love the fact that there's animals everywhere
Come here. I want to pet you. Okay
Again again one more. All right. Thank you. Good night
Go sing
I will i'll take peach on a date to the karaoke bar and i'm gonna sing and it's gonna be insane
What was that for? I don't know. I gotta pay my bills
I don't need to fire anybody. That's good
Oh, it's a skunk. Whatever. I'll pay the bills
eat take a shower
play some
radio games
some breakfast
Did I just how much food did I just make?
Am I stove broken?
Holy shit. I have a fan. Wow
Oh my god, that's so good
All right, put that down
The pets just know that they can come in here now
Take a nap and then i'm going out
With peach
I have practiced i'm prepared i'm ready i'm calling over peach. Let's go for it. Look at those bars. Perfect
Each come on over
9 pm
All right, we're at 30. How am I doing on food? I'm like i'm gonna take i'm gonna sit i'm gonna take quick nap
Till she gets here. What you got? Holy shit. What is that?
Get up
No, no, no, no, no greet
What is it? Oh my god, can I go for it? No, don't go for it yet. Want something to eat?
Yeah, let's like just chill and then hang out do it coward. No, you just have to wait
Okay, she's gonna want to talk a little bit
Let's have some dinner
All right, that sounds good
I'm gonna use the bath. I'm gonna clean the toilet and then use the bathroom
Don't yell at her. Just don't make her leave you stupid idiot. You idiot. She'll come over tomorrow
I'm just trying to speedrun this. I just I just uh
I'm doing fine though. I got if I have income if I need it
Who's calling at four o'clock in the morning? You're in autumn and should decorate accordingly. Do you want to live most harmoniously? Okay
This is going up though. This is 32 this stream will end with chug jug
It will it's going to hope you're ready for that good paint. Maybe some money sell that painting 160 bucks
Thank you go to bed wake up at like eight o'clock at night get peach to come over he's still doing this
Yeah, i'm very invested right now. I have to be this is 750 million dollars off the debt. I'm incredibly invested
What's broken here man? Come help me
Thanks for fixing the sink. I gotta get ready for her and now take a shower finish eating and call it's too late
Call it tomorrow. We'll call i'm gonna call tomorrow. Stop painting. You're using all your energy painting
How's caramel doing? I I don't not that bad. I don't think sell that painting 160 bucks. That's such a great income, too
That's awesome. I can pay my bills with that. I don't have to worry about it
I can pay like I can pay my bills and the people that come work for me on a daily basis
And I can cover food. All right. What time is it? It's 4 a.m. Eat
Use the bathroom wear the animals tomorrow. Okay, it's sleep
I have to wait when the animals get here
I gotta get up tomorrow on like four o'clock in the afternoon three in the afternoon
Can we get there in time? I don't think so
All right animals
dogs cats
birds
I'm gonna take a shower and it's enough for her to get over here invite over
I'm sure i'm gonna have more fun at your place. All right, there's a dog
This few times
I'm gonna take a shower
Okay, 32. Let's go
a
Ah shake hands. I still have to shake hands. I'm sorry
All right, let's have some dinner serve dinner come on in
I need to go I need to take a shower
You're gonna use my pool. I know you are you talk to yeah. Okay, we're just gonna talk. Okay
Sit on the couch and watch tv
Wanna come sit with me?
I want a hug
I'm like no no
Get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up get up
Get up get up you you absolute moron get up get up get up
She's supposed to kiss me and hug me get up get up. Oh my god
You moron why delete the tv?
I can't delete it. What the fuck is happening?
No
Come on. I said i'm fucking gonna throw this game cd into the goddamn trash. She wants to hug you
She wants to kiss you. She wants to hug you. She wants to kiss you. She wants to hug you
I just said tv soft locked come on
Oh, it's so stupid like I was just was stuck in front of the television. I want to just throw this tv
I want to just
Bunt this tv a hundred yards. What am I changing plates?
What is this character doing? I can't believe the tv me. Okay, there's that how you doing good
Who burped
This sucks
No, whatever just eat. Oh, i'm so mad right now. I can't believe it was over. I had it. It was done
It was done. It was over. I had it. It was over. I had it done. I did you know what I did. It's not fair
She was standing in front of you so you couldn't get up just desperately trying to hug and kiss me
Damn it. That's so frustrating
I don't want all this junk. Stop sending me mail. I'm gonna call her again
Okay, there we go. It's the phone. Is it her who is it game design that you submitted was purchased outright by the publisher
You received nine hundred and fifty dollars whoever facilitated that deal should go to jail
I think you need to add a couple of zeros there before that's actually what you should have done
At least okay. Um
Use the bathroom, of course by the tv
The sink break I just had it fixed. What am I doing? I can fix it myself. I don't need to repair man
Take a shower
Take a nap and then call her over
Call neighbor
Come on. I'm just freaking this out. I'll be over in a few minutes. All right, let's try this again turn the tv off
Serve dinner. I'm gonna do a polite kiss. Come on. This is it polite kiss here comes it's done. It's been done
There it is. That is a kiss finally now. Let's eat and hang out and then where's the heart? How come there's no heart?
Where's the heart?
Now, this is not a victory royale. I don't there's no heart next to her name
Light kiss does not equate to the romance. All right, this is it
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. If I can play fortnight for like five minutes passionate kiss, let's go
No
This sucks
All the progress is gone
All the progress just wait for her to make the move
Oh
My god, what the fuck?
I'm just it's too late. Yeah. All right. Goodbye. Good to see you
We're almost at 40
I'm getting some new shit. I'm getting so I have 2,500 bucks. I want like a weird something to do
What do we how do I make this like cooler fun?
Video what's it? I need something. That's like that's like a love based
Heart bed the heart bed the heart. I don't have enough for the heart bed. It's not gonna work
Fuck. I don't have any money. I just sell a bunch of my stuff
All right
I'm gonna work for like a week and just make enough money to buy a hot tub. How much is this one?
This is 7900 bucks. How much is my guitar worth? Not enough. Oh gamble for money. Just cheat
All right. Are you do I get permission to rosebud?
Up to ten thousand dollars to make sure I buy this that's a lot of nose. I'm gonna go gamble for like an hour
When I am i'm going to i'm gambling tomorrow for like and i'm gonna i'm gonna get to ten grand by gambling
Eat up spending all day at the casino tomorrow eight a.m. Nine a.m
All right, let's go. So
Call cab it is what what is it studio town studio town right to studio town casino. Where is it right here?
Not a good start bad start. All right
Pajamas, I know. All right. All right, that's 200 down 300. All we need to do is hit once. All right, come on. Come on
shit
Come on
Oh
Oh again again
All right, come on i'm i'm i can do it. I can do this
Some cost fallacy. Yeah, I know I just
God damn it
There it is. All right. All right. All right. All right back up back up back up
But 2300 2300 2300 2300 here it is again. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Let's go go three three three three three three. Okay, come on this one right here
This one right here
It's gonna get us to 3000 right now
Now, you know, it's the machine. It's the machine move over here
And i'm doing this wrong. I got you gotta play three at the same time
Okay
All right. All right. All right
Damn it
Who told me to do that?
You you asshole
That was never gonna work
All right, quick quick quick paint. Oh a dog dog stay here
I'm gonna be fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna call peach over and we're gonna hang out
Don't worry, especially the times three gambling. It's just like oh my god
Uh, I want to click you. Come here socials doing great. I'm fine. I'm fine. I don't even matter. I'm fine
Look at I got what's this? I got an inheritance from my dear aunt fucking edna
10 grand unexpected news your psychic says to plan accordingly. That's weird. Okay. Um, all right
I need to eat sleep play league of legends fucking god never seen a sink break as many times
I've seen it break in the sims. It's like once a week your sink breaks
I don't care about the raccoon anymore. Like that's not scary
Please cheat. We won't be mad. Hold on. I'm not gonna need to do it just yet. Just give me a minute
I did this for a reason I can sell paintings be able to afford my bills people that come over
There's the gardener already. There's the okay. I gotta sell this before she leaves sell the painting before she leaves do that again
All right, we're good. Why do they always they always pick out a bag of chips from the fridge like eat lunch
Look at your hunger ridiculous. All right, i'm gonna have like 400 bucks. I'm good. Everything's fine
This is another few four or five days. Fuck this bills youtube andy here youtube andy. What do you mean?
Oh, you're a youtube watcher. What's going on? What color are those bills get removed if you cheat? That's not gonna happen
How's my have my relationship with peach? All right, i'm gonna get her over here again
that
fucking god
so annoying
Everything just breaks what happened to the family from yesterday. Should we show them later? Show you later. It's just being cleaned up
The toilet's there just oh my god. I hate this guy
Have breakfast I need to paint actually. No, I don't i'm good. Let's get peach over here
I have to unclog the toilet fix all this shit
Use the bathroom now play fucking video games. I need to cheat
I know look, I know i've read all the like i've i've back in the day
I remember people saying that just cheat it doesn't matter the game's like impossible just cheat
I can't do that right now unless I have to i'm gonna get up play some animals
There's a dog to play with pet pet pet pet that's more
Okay, let's call peach I need to take a shower call peach. Here we go. Come on over
I'd love to okay. Now let's make dinner serve dinner brought me a plant. That's very nice of her
I mean, what the hell were you in my backyard? Why are you already here? Okay, come on in fucking it's in the way
We can't sit down food's good
Okay, why am I
Okay, clean this all right, are we ready he hugged here we go
Okay, and
And and and I was about to click it. I was about to click it myself
I was about to click that button myself. I was gonna click it
I don't understand this video game. I was hovering over the fucking thing
I waited too long. Uh
If I had done that she would have denied me, but if she doesn't I deny her
What the fuck is going on? I have to paint today
Go paint
Just go edit her god damn bills. Okay, how did it went down too?
Jeremy sims are going extinct
You have to breed
That's that's great. Um, I don't I don't think it's possible
I think it's impossible to like have a relationship in the sims one
Unless you for like unless you like make them in the same household to make them married already
Like by the first part of the game, can you even do that? Can you make people even married in the first game?
I can't believe she went for a she went it played the music. It was like
I'm like get away from me. I was about to click the button
so stupid
Inheritance better be great great grandmother. Come on money. There it is go sleep for a little bit. It's two o'clock. I'm gonna invite her over
Lush use
This is lush. I can't believe I have to do that
And then i'm gonna serve dinner and i'm gonna call her here we go. She's gonna get fucking tv off. Oh pick it up you idiot
Yuck, I can't I still can't believe it like animals can pee in the corner of your lot
I'm like molding click. I'm mold clicking right now
Just put it down. Just put it down
Hey
Just relax
Rest and just save scum i'm begging. I don't think that's gonna work
You want some to eat let's have some food grab a plate have some it's good right i'm jumping the gun
Okay
This is it
This game is stupid
She literally tried to passionately romantically kiss me 24 hours ago
And then if I initiated it's wait, it's not gonna happen
This is stupid
This game is impossible
I actually think the sims 1 might be impossible back on the computer
Every every thread I read about this game is like holy shit. It's impossible
This game's not possible. It's impossible
This is an end this incompletable video game
Do we just throw dice in the air for every encounter? This is a poopoo fucking diarrhea poopoo game
I'm sorry. That was fucking stupid
Am I gonna really go play the guitar
Can't even do this anymore
This is stupid
You have to have at least 80 in the relationship. No, that's not even real. That's not that's not even accurate
I thought that was the one when she went to kiss me. I thought that was it. It's not it's not I have no idea. I
I'm gonna fucking melt down here in a minute here. We characters too short
They have to be at least six or ban that person for like 45 minutes at least
I want that person banned for at least 10 minutes
Okay, I guess we're gonna I'm just gonna go to i'm just gonna fucking go to um, no more swearing
Jeremy you were having fun playing just calm down. Well, I hit the relationship and by the way
Here's another thing about this game
I'm expected to have like five of these seven of these I can't even keep one person interested let alone 10
Are you kidding me and go to work every day with no breaks?
You have to make sure they're both in a good mood
I can't see the mood bar for peach you had more fun killing the whole family. I'm gonna piss the bed. Oh shit
I'm not even friends with her anymore. What the fuck i'm gonna go
I'm gonna give it one more real attempt before I take off the nostalgic glasses
And never play this shitty game ever again. You know what I mean? I'm giving it one more solid attempt
The bet was for lois. Oh, but no, that doesn't matter. All you care about is the fortnight song anyways
Does that matter? No, it doesn't matter the guitar down
What are you doing?
Stop i'm gonna sell it. All right, I gotta I gotta I gotta get centered here. I am furious
I'm furious at this game's mechanics. I hate them. I need to ground myself and just chill
I'm gonna go for it again. If it doesn't work then what okay, it's all good. Okay
So what do we do first first things first get in that shower jeremy take a shower go pee
Go take a nap. I'm gonna get up tomorrow morning and have breakfast
I'm gonna pet some cats who continue to pee in the corners of the map. What a great idea that was stop
I'm getting like fucking mad again slow down. Okay, wake up. Just take care of it
It's in the four corners of the entire map. This is gonna take three hours. Okay now i'm dirty
Just put a litter box near the house. What a genius that person is what an absolute genius
Are you kidding me? That's what a perfect thing to do. Where is I need a litter box?
That's so dumb that that's what I have to do. I don't even I don't want to take care of all these animals
2 a.m. Let's go. Wasn't there a sign? I feel like the people just messing with you
You guys fucking with me kind of need those animals though right now
I heard there's a mod for sims 1 called sims 2 apparently makes the game much more fair and fun to play
They even added 3d graphics. Isn't that amazing?
No, don't paint I got money. Uh, what do I want to do?
I'm gonna go back to bed. I gotta wait for the animals to show up
We'll play fortnight for a little bit
Then when the animals come in i'm gonna play with the animals and we're gonna get peach over here again
I'm not gonna make any moves
We're just gonna sit around and talk and let go swimming and then she's gonna try to passionately kiss me
I'm gonna reject her and i'm gonna put my hand through my monitor. I'm gonna sell this
Pet cue up the pets who is calling me. I was in the middle of doing something
I was in the middle of doing something. What do you want?
Your patent for a new cock gun nozzle has just been accepted and you sold the rights. Thank you. Where'd the dog go? Where's dog?
All right, play the dogs
We all just made that noise at the same time disable the hot date dlc it added the lifetime romance shit
Wait, what wait one of the one of the one of the actual like expansions I have just fucks up the game
Yes
Are you serious you need more long time relations it was added in hot date
Why do they make it even why do they make it harder to do that when they want to make it easier?
If it's called hot date
Why am I smashing my head against the wall over and over again? All right. I got enough social. That's good
Shower i'm gonna go back to bed time just it's so it takes forever
All right, stop complaining. I'm not gonna complain for the rest of the day
Okay, if I complain for the rest of the stream add no
Um, just i'm not gonna is it too late to call her call her get her over here. Oh, no
No, no, no, no raccoon. Oh no
It's el bandito. He shows up every night. It's not even a thing anymore. It's not scary at this point
I'm like happy he's here. I just called her stuff. All right, let's make dinner
It's like i'm sick of him doing that
I don't I don't need the creative points anymore. None of these are gonna do it. Okay. Hello
Come on in. Let's have some dinner 30 and 37. Let's just eat
Hey things are going well
She's now a friend. Welcome back into my friend circle now
I'm not gonna do anything else if she if it's time to leave it's time to leave and then i'll call her tomorrow
What do you want to do?
Okay. Goodbye. I'm glad we're friends again. I'll see you tomorrow
12 hours one friend this guy I don't think you're staying this game is not don't complain about it
You know what i'm saying, you know, what is it gonna say?
Okay, 8 a.m. We're gonna get her over here. We're gonna try to get her to stay here all day. I can nap on this couch
That's good. Call her over here. She comes. All right, let's here
We're just like hanging out and where you're at which is a good place the long stream. That's all right. That's okay
Some of them can be long
Especially when i'm only going once a week or so, that's fine. Am I about to wave to her? No better than that
I did it anyways
All right. Come on in. I will make lunch. She's eating old food. Let's talk
Okay, but is she doing that to me or am I doing that to her who's doing that to who who's doing that?
Okay, sit down ask
No, what does she want to do? Let's talk alert. That's too much alert sweet talk sweet talk. Which one?
Sweet talk
Wasn't I already friends with her what happened
Okay, we're talking here comes here comes a flirt let's go for it come on
She must flirt 61 come on this is it 64 here it comes this is it
Heart
Why's there no heart there's no heart and why is flirt gone why where's why's flirt gone?
Let's talk a little more want some more food. Are you hungry?
Okay, this is gonna go over to 70
What do you think? What is the time? What do you think go for the romantic? Not yet. Okay
How about a friendly how about an intimate hug?
For it's 75
And we just got a heart. How am I doing? I was gonna take a quick nap on the couch
Okay. All right. All right. I'm good get the flies get the flies right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they're using me using it
Take a shower. Okay. This is my opportunity. She's gonna come out. We're both in like a good mood
She's just in the pool still
What's wrong with this dog? I'm gonna go in the pool. Hey, okay. This is it. We're having fun in the pool together
Get out of the pool peach. No, no, no, no, no, no, no get me out of the pool. Stop. Where'd you go?
Why was she in the pool for like
Seven hours i'm not giving you an opportunity to swim in my house anymore
Like this you just swim into the house you swim for eight hours. How do I delete this?
It's a gym now deal with it. She just she dives in there and gets stuck in there for four or five six straight hours
Okay, let's have some more food play some video games. It's nine a.m
I'm gonna I want to go back. I want to nap on the couch turn the tv off and nap on the couch
Okay, bladder call her up. Do not have lunch serve lunch. Hey the bills
You don't have a pool to jump into this cat. I think it's been shitting in this for the last three days
Okay, i'm just gonna let her do what she's gonna do. You can just just eat
What's wrong yuck yum?
Okay, i'm gonna eat some food, too
I'm gonna pet the dog and i'm gonna pet the dog. Okay, can use the bathroom
Okay, here we go. Be hugged. This is it stand up be hugged be kissed if you fuck this up jeremy
If you reject this i'm gonna be fucking fear. I hate this game. Come on do it
This is it this string of commands will get us what we're looking for
Yes
Yes, do it. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it
This is it. It's gonna happen. Here it comes
Why do we can't do this why
We we cannot kiss each other. Why?
She tries to kiss me. I try to kiss her it doesn't work
We can only intimately hug each other and like back rub each other's backs
I I would I would say that this is going too fast
But she's trying to kiss me too like romantic passionate kisses and I am denying her come on
How many times we have to do this?
Romantic hug
It needs to be 50 lifetime what a shitty dlc come on do it three hugs that's it i'm at 40 under there
Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's talk
This is it. This is it. This is gonna happen flirt. No, no, no, wait
flirt back rub again
into a intimate hug
into a
joke
Into puppets good idea
Oh my god, we're almost there
Come on
It's so close. It's gonna happen any second here. Okay, bring bring out the puppets. Oh, this is a mistake
This is a mistake. I should have brought the puppet out. I should have brought my dumb puppet out. What a mistake. That was
oh
Okay, it's fine it's saved saved saved
Saved
Okay. Now we need to um entertain jokes. She likes jokes
We're gonna do another intimate hug after no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, eat your food eat. Go eat. Oh, you can eat have some food
Yeah, it's eat you go ahead. We're gonna have dinner. She's been here for so long. Fuck
Wait, hug. Goodbye 50. Come on. Oh you fuck. Ah
That's okay. No bigger turn off than a guy ripping out a puppet out of his back pocket and going like
Yeah, i'd be like, oh my god, I thought I thought this guy wasn't nuts. It's at 49. That's gonna happen tomorrow
I fucking knew it was gonna break you fix that goddamn toilet before you go to bed
I'm not dealing with that ever again. Fuck that stop painting stop painting
Go play fucking fortnight if you want to have fun
450 bucks didn't do anything. I'll pee in the new toilet. Take a shower
Okay, pay the bills because they're probably old. All right
I need to I need to go actually back to bed for a little bit and my comfort's not good
There we are. Okay
I'm gonna play video games for a while and i'm gonna eat and i'm gonna call her over do not have a snack
Put that away
You're gonna call you're gonna have dinner serve dinner eat this shit right now take a nap on the couch. Call her
She comes 49. We're almost there one. Just don't blow this last interaction. Whatever it is. How's my social? It's all right
Here she comes with chocolates. This is it
Okay, come in and have some dinner. I prepared it for us. Right? Let's sit down and eat. Let's have a let's eat dinner
I'm gonna use the bathroom. You go ahead and do whatever you need to do. Okay, we've eaten we're eating
We are I wanted a hug but it's i'm at 50
No
That's no why what is going on with the stray dog?
Is climbing don't just don't kiss her
I'm not even doing that
Whisk flirt
Okay, let's talk. Let's hang out
Okay
Am I going for it am I going for it am I gonna go for it am I going for it go
75 and 50 this should be it. Come on romantic kiss
Polite
Light heck or polite which one too late
So
What are you supposed to do in this game to do this
Did you tell me this this is part of the dlc hot date dlc?
And you can't buy that looks like germapop by the way be kissed you fucking better not you better kiss her kiss her
She's trying to kiss you kiss her. You better kiss her. Wait, you kiss her too. Oh, this is it. It's all it happened
Yes
Okay. All right. Okay now
Okay. Now we're gonna do um, what you doing? Good game. That only that only took
Six hours of gameplay to make this happen
I'm only doing this every day. Okay, so how do we how do we can we date do not take a shower yet?
I don't all right. Now, what do I do? We just keep kissing save save. I got I got I got I got it
It's never gonna work. No, it's just gonna dump me never seen that interaction work in the game
It's okay. No, no, no, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. Everything's fine
Puppet, okay. That's to be 70. I i'm i'm like tomorrow's another day tomorrow's another day go to bed
I don't care about the raccoon. Just go to sleep. Who cares? Sorry, the maid's coming soon. I gotta get ready
How much is it 4500? Will you let me do this?
I've put all the work in already. I put the work in let me do this. I'm doing it
I don't care. I put the work in you know, I did how do I do it?
I'm only gonna do just two three thousand. Is it how do I do it? The button is it control shift c?
Then it's what it's like this right like this. That's all i'm doing. That's it. Everyone can relax. Come on. This is it
It's gonna happen soon here. I don't know why i'm putting that there
I'm just getting and I want to like some okay. I'm ready. Okay, my hunger is the only thing that needs help
Go to the bathroom take a shower nap on the couch call her here it comes. I'm gonna get it. I'm so excited
Here she comes. Don't blow it. I'm gonna open with a hug get that to 70
Okay, come on in. I'm gonna whip up some dinner. I'm late. Let's eat. Let's sit down and eat
And then talk like like a like a so close we are
Deal is on
Come on it's it's so close 66
Probably what do you want to do you want to
Anything going on here? Are you looking for a kiss or something? You might be going for one
You gotta go to the bathroom. Go ahead paint a picture. That's fine. Just kill some time anything else that you're going
We dance. Oh, that's cute, right? Well, this is cute. Let's do it. This is nice. This is cute. It's gonna be cute
Oh god, damn it
Wish they weren't cats fighting in my front lawn. Okay 64
Let her initiate something
Dogs and cats just everywhere. Let her initiate something do something
We can let's talk you want it. You don't you want to initiate anything?
66 come on she wants to play with the dog
Come on 67 initiate something. I don't want to fuck it up you initiate initiate something initiate with me
Oh, we can watch tv. Let's go
No, no, we can watch tv. We can watch tv
Sick, it's so close
This is happening tomorrow
This bed
Look at this bed
Oh, yeah
20 bucks
What am I doing?
Get up get up get up get up get up
Okay, well
shower
Clean up have breakfast
Play some games take a nap
invite
Come on over. What is that?
68 it's so close go for it. Yes
71 71 71 71 skip dinner for now
I
Can't I can't go for it. No, she needs I need to cook her food
She needs to have something to eat have some food. Let's have a dinner and then how what do we do now?
Dave I got it. I gotta go to the bed and call her over
Do a romantic interaction invite down. Oh, I thought downtown meant like that's my bedroom name romantic kiss. Come on. Here it is again
Come on
fiery fiery kiss
What
No, what happened? Wait, let's get married. Come on. What did she say? She said no
No, no, no, no, no, no, please
No
I'm reloading the safe
Reload this fucking save right now. No, sorry. That was too much time
That was way too much work. The sim was one of your partner is hungry
I don't even know what you're saying, but I it's probably something about what needs to happen
I had the the red heart. Let's eat
And
She's eating I need to do a I need to do a we need to do a romantic kiss
How am I doing? She needs fun. All right, turn the tv on
Come sit with me and watch tv. Yes
Watch tv watch tv what you can do. I can't sit down next to you switch to action
Nice nice. Nice. Okay. Uh, then I don't don't worry about it, babe. The animals are fighting outside. It's okay
Don't worry about it. I ain't answering that phone. Here it is. Got it. Save it here. Okay. Good. Good
Okay, this is a red heart. Okay. Let's hey, let's get up. What do you say? Let's just get up but
Let's get up and um, I don't know. Hey, how you feel? How you doing 25? You hungry? I'm gonna get some food
You want some food? No, don't get naked
What the fuck? Wait a minute
Wait ask
This is good. We're in love. Are we in love? Are we in love?
This is how you do it
This is how you have sex in the sims. I don't know. I've never gotten this far
I've never gotten this far
No
I freaked out. I freaked out. I'm sorry. I we got a save file right there. Don't worry. I freaked out
He fell out of bed play in bed play in bed play in bed, but she's not even in here
Okay, how we doing? Okay, let's go
work
We got number one victory royal your fortnight we bout to get down 10 kills on the board right now just wiped out tomato town
My friend just got down every five team and we're going south now out of the park
We're going south sweet look at the map look at the mark sheet
That's 500 million off the dead. I went
I took what that was way too
Oh my god, it's it's over. Okay now
What was that? She's saying that sucked
So I proposed to her tomorrow she's coming out tomorrow i'm gonna propose to her tomorrow save it here
Notice how the pool was deleted from the picture and I was able to actually do this. I couldn't satisfy her
Is that what it was? She was like, yeah
Is that what that means?
I can't believe I did it. I beat it. It only took seven and a half hours
I can't believe I've ruined that with chug jug. Did I make it better? I'm not sure. I have no idea
Check on caramel. I think she's gonna burn didn't she I sure I need to get out of here before she lights on fire
She's still alive in canon. Don't worry. All right, it's time to uh call over. Uh, my love the bills socials good comforts
Good, let's go take a little sleep and then i'm bringing them over
We're gonna have a nice dinner and then i'm gonna propose eat whatever the food is. I don't know what this food is
Yeah, whatever. I'm probably gonna get a stomach ache who cares call her
Come on over
We're at 76. I can propose at any time here. Wait, uh dinner shit. She was down the street. Hello, my love
It's right there it's right there but not yet don't do it yet. Don't do it yet stupid
Oh, you can eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat
We're eating
Let's watch tv
kissed
Come sit down with me. Let's watch television
Where's she going? What the fuck? Oh, it's 2 a.m
Right turn this turn this off and go to bed. I got all day now eat take a shower call her. Um,
Okay, I need to make dinner serve lunch. I'm ready ready ready. Go go go go. You have some food kiss kiss kiss kiss
She's gonna go to the bathroom. Okay, let's watch some tv. Let's get uh, let's get uh, you want a kiss your thing
Let's go you fucking asshole. What is wrong with you? What are you doing? What are you doing?
Why does this game do this? Why does this game i'm choking her putting my hands around her neck
Why is this game do this? Why is this game doing this? I didn't do anything. He's just doing that on his own
Why are you doing this?
It's so stupid
This this no rhyme or reason to any of the things happening on the screen
none
zero
Zero reason for any of them. She goes in for a kiss. She goes in for a hug three times. I deny her
I go in for a kiss. She breaks up with me. What the fuck is this?
Take her out on a date. No, but but she went she went over to me
She came over to me
That was the wrong house
She came to me and I denied her and i'm
She came over to me
Okay, where are you? Are we still here?
76 she's just gonna wait. Why is it 76 go to bed? We're gonna call tomorrow
Fighting over the litter box
This whole day was just thrown in the trash
I don't know what i'm I don't know what's happening, but i'm just trying to skip a day
Carmel is dead caramel is not dead
Okay, i'm gonna wake up tomorrow and it's gonna be ready to go invite her over here and we're gonna make it work
Perfect timing 6 a.m. I have the entire day
Okay, save it here paul invite her come over here. We are just food on the table. I'm about to throw this away
Where is she? There she is
Greet a nice big romantic kiss bingo save it here. Let's just have a plate. Okay
Okay
Get rid of those fucking bugs get the bugs bugs, you know, get those bugs, please come on get the bugs get those bugs
Please please before they come in the house, please get the bugs, please. Oh, she's disgusted. Are you gonna do it?
Let's talk for a little bit. You've eaten. Let's turn the tv on too
Okay, come sit with me perfect. Okay, let's watch tv
This is a fun activity. We're having fun
We're at 81 82
It's gonna happen. It's gonna happen now
Don't save it yet. Make sure this works
Okay, it's time. It's time
That's it
Princess peach wife it costs a thousand dollars. Wait, we're getting married here and not oh and our dog
And our dog phoebe. I I got it. All right, I win
Here she comes. Okay, she's just getting in I didn't even do anything. Is that the me making dog noises?
That's like crying. Why was I crying? What are we doing? How do I have a kid?
How do you have children in the sims 1 go adopt caramel? I don't think I can she's now peach elbertson
Adopt caramel. I don't think I can do that
I gotta get out of here. It's been almost eight hours. I gotta move. How do I do this?
How do I go rescue caramel? I keep having boing boing. It's rng
How can I make her leave the house?
Is it like move sim?
Buy a phone. I can't buy a phone unless this is out fire will never go out. Is it out?
She's about to sweep up all the ashes. We're gonna get to see the actual end of the arc here
Okay, she has a phone who can I call?
Didn't happen in home alone
You order like a bunch of pizzas and they like they don't know that there's a kid here
Am I gonna put a bunch of mannequins up and pretend there's people in the house like puppetry?
Oh my god, you need to eat food. Hurry up. Call pizza. Yeah, call a pizza. She called the pizza. I get a pizza
Get out of here you fucking psycho get out of here. What are you doing in here?
Why are you in here get out?
No, don't put it on the ground caramel
Oh god
She's just eating on the toilet. At least it's food. Oh fuck
She's all right. She's all right. Okay, grab a slice watch tv. I'm not going to school. My house just burned down
I
Why am I washing the pizza in the sink?
What am I eating the sink?
I can't do this. I need to eat more
She's eating the whole pizza
She's eating an entire large pizza mario, please super mario help us
Mario help us what mario, please wait is mario taking what happens to the house?
Wait, is that because I didn't go to school?
I saved it right before that and so if I go back to the neighborhood and don't save the game
And I just reload the house. I don't have to quit the game, right?
All right. We got to get to school. We have to get to school the next day get the laughing
We have to order a pizza. We have to get to school. Okay, get a pizza
Okay, I need to go to the bathroom get the pizza fucking weird like weird guy again
Thank you. What time does the school get here an hour boss is gonna be here any second?
Oh god the hell I got pizza here. I got two dollars. That's enough for me to eat pizza
I can sell all this junk. I'm gonna be fine. Okay, there she is. She's back. Okay, take a shower
Does she have to pay the bills?
Go to school get the phone get the phone get the phone get the phone get the phone get the phone
Who is it evict caramel from the neighborhood map and then have her move into your house?
They're coming think twice about opening the door. Holy shit. That's the most terrifying thing I've ever heard
She needs to go to bed. She's having nightmares
Save her. I will I will I will I will I need to get her to I need to get her like, okay first
Whoa, what was that? What was that? What was that? I was like going times three sleep speed. It was a ghost
I put on cartoons in order and I'm gonna do another like kevin mccallister order a caterer. So he's good
All right. I'm gonna order catering
350 need a punch bowl or a catering table catering table plus karaoke stage
I don't see catering table canning center honey maker. It's a buffet table. Where is it?
Literally off living off of the ashes you're allowed to cheat. Okay, move her out. I got a plan. Don't worry
I have a plan. I wish like this wasn't like a picture book. Where is this thing in kitchen?
Why do they make this shit so hard to find just give me alphabetical order like why this is like stupid
How do I change this lighting appliances? Like can I change how do I change it to be like the actual?
Not stupid way to have this isn't I know there's a button I can press. What is it? How do I do it appliances plus
This kid was fucking dog shit. He's kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Relax. I'm kidding
All right, make sure you have a buffet table and then should I all right? I got money. All right, let's get these bugs
Where's my caterer? Okay. Now now I have to throw a party. What is he doing?
Why is he putting this on the table? Why is he taking this? Who can I call?
Oh, no, eat eat eat food first. Ooh, it's delicious. I'm just eating cake. Shit. A school bus is coming. Stop eating food
Does he just stay here? What's he doing? Why is he still here? He's eating cake
Can I hire like a a service to come? Hey, what happened? It's because her grades are bad. We're just gonna get her
Uh, this lot is currently zoned as a residential lot. Please choose what type of lot you want it to be red
So am I i'm evicting her? No wrong. You want to evict them? Yes, you want to bulldoze the house?
Yes
guys, um
No one lives here but cats is this why the entire time i've been playing the game they've all been
My house this person is not here
the cat family
Some I think whoever owned this house is dead. Was that the lady that burnt?
14 hours ago in game
That had to have been the person that died
Looks like they're doing and that's why they keep coming to my house
Okay
Select our creative family. Where is she move in family?
Come on
I can't I have to evict them, too
I don't think I can do this create new family. I messed it up. Well, she's safe. Let her move in with the cats
I'm kind of curious about this slow down. What the fuck what I have control of the cat
How do they eat that there used to be a lady here? These are the cats that kept showing up
Remember boots boots would show up every day
She burned to death. Okay, that's it. I'll see you later. I'll see you next week. You'll find her urn
I think I sold it. I threw it away. Uh, that's probably the longest stream i've done in a while
I feel okay. I do
I was able to get up a couple of times
and uh
doing some new
treatments
so
Where I kind of have been each time you don't see me for like six days in a row. Um,
Let's see how it goes. I'm gonna keep going. The schedule is good for me. I'll see you guys on saturday next week
This has been the sims 1 probably not gonna play it again
If i'm gonna play i'm gonna play the sims 2 a much far better game far better experience from what i've been told
All jokes aside. I do. Uh, this is a classic video game. It's very very fun. Yeah, although it's
Painfully difficult. Let's do the sims 2 at some point in the future
Uh, yeah, that was a long one. I was not expecting. I mean, I was just having fun. That's the point right?
Just save it just in case and that's that i'll see you guys on saturday of the coming week
Have a great rest of your weekend. Although it is almost over for a lot of you a good week
Let's get the credits on here frozen. No
Uh, my chest and stomach hurts from just laughing at all that stuff and just freaking out
Is this a meltdown stream? I don't know does it does that qualify as a meltdown it may have some of it may have
I think a little bit was
Hey, we got what we wanted got to see the thing we wanted to see i'm happy about it. I missed uh
Ella dill gave 10 community subs during some of that nonsense
Roller crunch gave five vessel wind field gave five. Thanks a lot for those community subs
Every eight hour stream is a meltdown stream
You know, that's probably somewhat correct. You're probably right. You did not have sex with lois
Well, it was a different it was a different cartoon character. Okay
It didn't have to be with lois
It doesn't have to be with lois
Right. Uh, yeah, let's do a raid. Let's do
Two
Who's live and who's playing things right now? We raided joel a week or two ago. Let's go to
What is he doing dodge the question? What was what question? Um, hold on. Let me
Put this over here
I'm gonna i'll dump you guys on italics
He's playing disco elsium though. So
he's probably
And uh, this is by the way, this is like I think the end of the game
Like italics is at the end of disco elsium. So if you don't want to get spoiled then
Um
I would just be aware of that. You may see like the end of disco elsium
Go say hello
Keep that in mind that he's playing disco elsium. Let's say hello. So be weary of spoilers
Good night. I'll see you guys next week. Have a wonderful rest of your evening
And have a great week
Good night. Take care. I'll see you guys soon