Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight, playing as the Demoman on Thunder Mountain. I can't do the noise with my mouth,
but you understand, on Thunder Mountain right now is the Demoman with a very, very, very
weird setup. Before I get really into this commentary at all, I want to talk about the
So I'm using the Alibaba's Wii booties, the Sticky Launcher, and the Frying Pan. Now,
the reason why I did this, I'm kind of sick of doing the whole regular Demoman setup,
because the Demoman doesn't have really any options. He only has two real primaries and
two real secondaries. I mean, I don't really even count the shields. I mean, they are weapons,
but they're not technically weapons. They just add a mechanic. They add a charge mechanic
into the game. So what I'm talking about, I'm talking about real weapons. I really do wish
Valve would stop making all these melee unlockables for the Demoman and actually focus on some
new primaries and some new secondaries, because we need them, because there's nothing else
you can really do. And personally, I really don't like the Scottish Resistance. I think
the Scottish Resistance is too weird to use. I can't really get used to it. So somebody
like me that doesn't ever use the Scottish Resistance, I just have the default Sticky
Launcher and I have a shield I can put on. So what I'm doing right now is I'm doing
a weird kind of different setup that not very many people do, and it's the Alibaba's Wii
booties, like I said, and the Sticky Launcher, specifically to get the extra health. So I'm
really just a sticky bomb tank. It's really what I am. Because I've been looking back
at my Demoman videos and even playing as the Demoman, whenever I play as the damn Demoman,
I always just use the default stuff. And unless I'm doing a demo night, and I've got to get
away from that, this is kind of my way to change it up a little bit and stop using the
same damn items over and over and over again. And this is a very odd setup. And it is, even
though it is odd, it is a lot of fun and it's actually pretty useful. It's pretty much
just putting on the Darwin's Danger Shield for the Sniper. And yes, you do lose your
grenade launcher, but honestly, for the most part, most of us use the grenade launcher
for spam anyways. And a lot of, some of us are okay though. Some of us can get those
great Demoman direct shots. And for that, you guys, I commend you. I give you a clap.
I give you applause. Because sometimes it's difficult for me to do that, unless I'm using
the lock and load. But it takes the spam factor away from you and makes you really have to
focus with your sticky launchers and you get extra health. So until Valve adds some new
primaries and secondaries, some new innovative primaries and secondaries for the Demoman,
I'll probably be rolling around with this for a little while. So for the next half of
the commentary, I want to talk about, I want to get away from the game and the gameplay
for a little bit. And I want to discuss exercise, exercising and the gym. Because I remember
in my last, my Q&A video, I told you guys that I was getting a little sloppy. I hadn't
been to the gym in a long time. It's been like three months and I finally just went
back yesterday. I went with burger boy and we got destroyed. We did a chest and triceps
workout and I felt like I hadn't worked out ever before in my entire life. Like I was
so tired and my muscles are so sore right now. But forget about all that. I want to
talk about, I want to talk to you guys specifically about my workout routine and my workout story.
And maybe after listening to this commentary, if you were on the fence before, maybe you'll
start doing it too. Cause I mean, I do get asked this quite often, at least in PMs.
I mean, not, it's not like every single day somebody's like, how do you do workouts? But
I have been asked a couple of times. So I do want to get this video out so people can
understand that here's my story. I was a little, little dude back when I was in high school.
I probably was 115 pounds. I was like five, two, and I was 115 pounds. And after I got
out of high school, I went to college. I gained a little bit of weight in college. I went
to probably 135 or like 138 in college. And after college, that's kind of when I said
okay, I am getting really sick and tired of being the smallest person in the room. I would
look around and see everybody was bigger than me. Everyone was stronger than me. And I got
sick of that. And even in talking about women and relationship stuff, I wanted to be more
desirable. I wanted to be a guy that girls would point to and say, wow, he's look at
that. Look at those arms. And plus I wanted to get healthier too, because I have always
been kind of like a health nut. I've always wanted to be the healthiest I can be. And
I mean, it's not like I didn't try this before. I never really worked out that much, but I
did try to put on weight and oh my God, I could not put on one pound to save my life.
I could eat 25 double cheeseburgers from McDonald's and I wouldn't gain one pound.
And I was always so naive. I really did think that eating garbage fatty foods was going
to make me bigger and make me gain weight. But that's not really what that stuff does.
You'll gain weight if you eat cheeseburgers or if you eat something really bad for you.
You'll gain weight, but it's not the type of weight that you want to gain. Yeah, I mean,
maybe you'll gain four or five pounds, but it'll all be in your butt cheeks. Like you
won't get like biceps by eating McDonald's. I'll tell you that right now. And to sort
of end this video, I want to talk about what it's really done for me and what it can really
do for you too. If you start working out, if you really get into it, I've seen such
massive results guys. I've gained probably at least 40 or 50 pounds since I started a
couple of years ago. And even though I have slowed down a little bit, I'm trying to get
back into it now. But I've just seen such amazing results over the last couple of years.
I got as strong as an ox too. And I'm not the smallest guy in the room anymore. I'm
one of the bigger guys in the room. And that alone is so insane for your confidence. If
you can get to a point where you look in the mirror and you go, who's that guy? Oh my God,
you will feel so much better about yourself. And it's done so many good things for me.
So maybe in the future, I'll make another video like this describing my actual routine
and some of the things I do on a daily basis to stay healthy and to gain weight and to
get bigger. But for now, I just wanted to give you that little story. So I will see
you guys all soon. Take care, everybody.