Let's get, let's get warmed up. Let's get, get warmed up. This is too offensive for cameras. Turn the camera off. Don't show it, don't blur it. Don't show, blur it out.
Okay guys, welcome to a video. So Ster and I have realized that trying to play a game like this and talk, it always ends in disaster.
So we're just gonna try our little pants off as the two characters who know how to play. If somebody makes a noise, you know what I mean?
If somebody says a word, then you got it. You know what I mean?
This video is going to be 95% silent and every once in a while we're gonna go.
Yeah, so first we're gonna do a little just to check here. Make sure your connections are connected.
Okay, so commence the tri- no.
You said commence.
Commence means end, by the way. I figured that out the other day.
Does it really?
The other day? What the fuck am I talking about? Tri-Hod mode, activate. Jack's wrestler versus culto-
You said activate!
Now I'm gonna have to do a comeback. Here we go. Three-
We need to show us how good we are at video games, okay?
We're not good at this game though.
We need to show just what we're capable of. Okay, ready?
Yeah. Thriller!
Three, two, one, action!
I wasn't ready.
Well now it's too bad because now you're caught in the combo mania. I always forget about that fucking sword move.
Oh, out of the corner. Into the face. Jump kick.
Okay.
I knew you were gonna do that, and you know what? I just fucking threw up blood in my mouth.
What is with those fucking blocky blocks?
What?
I can't talk in points. I can't-
What's with all these blocky blocks this guy's doing?
Alright, well I won that round. Good.
I was trying to think of what to say about blocky blocks.
It's just what happens when you play this game, and you try, and you try to try.
Shit.
That didn't work. That did.
Every time. Why won't that move work? Come on, controller.
No!
Get that out of here.
I want to be in the sun.
And you fucking throw the- you throw the saw blade overhead at me.
That's how you're gonna end this one?
And then it reappears on my back.
You're gonna try and throw me into the statue?
I thought about it. I was going to.
You didn't think I was like trying to do that?
Alright, we'll play online.
Well, we are playing online. I'm glad you noticed.
Jump off the face.
Now back it up. Back it up to the thing that I'm not gonna-
Oh my god.
What?
I'm just- I'm just trying to sit up.
What was I doing?
I don't know. What were you doing?
Every time I don't jump, and I always say to myself, why didn't you jump?
And this is time for a finisher.
You want to see my finisher?
I fucked it up.
You just pop a guy in the face.
I didn't finish me-
Smoking! That's-
Censor that out, smokers.
He's not smoking. He's eating a fucking sausage.
After a good fight, I just like to sit back and have some of the pork.
It's time for a bet.
We're betting, men.
If I win this next match, then-
What happens if you win?
If you win?
Stop it, man.
Oh, it's sniping you.
Yeah, I know.
I'm gonna win because I want to have a nap.
Yeah, I'm gonna win because I want to sniff for a second.
Oh, the snakes are on, guys. You heard it here.
Whoever wins, you heard the bets.
You hold the rules.
Can I please just do the knee to you?
Of course I got it.
Follow it up with the combo.
Follow it up. You can follow it up any time you fucking want, you know, Jax.
And I just wasted meter for no goddamn reason.
Yeah, because you're a nude.
And I wanted a two.
How do you taunt? How do you- which button taunts?
Watch out!
What did I do? I just did like the three stooges bop you on the head move.
How did I do that?
You can hide in there all you want.
And you're gonna- I fucked it up.
I fucked it up and you have full meter. I am such a good head.
Oh my god, wrong button.
How dare you throw your fucking snakes at me?
Get me out of that. I don't want that to kill me.
I wanted that to kill you so bad.
Dude.
Get out of here. I know you're gonna do it.
I'm fainting.
Oh, I've got such a headache.
My head hurts.
All right, this is it.
Yeah, because I used all of my meter to like give you a sunburn.
What am I doing? What the fuck am I doing?
I was sitting there blocking.
My brain was trying to process a word I was gonna say.
Fuck you a sunlight.
Yeah, get thrown. Get thrown again.
Get fucking thrown one more time.
I should have blocked it.
That would have been really good if I had blocked it.
No, get out of here.
You're gonna get stuck in this corner and I'm gonna laugh at you.
I'm gonna do this move and you're gonna complain about
why didn't I think that he was gonna-
I know your weakness.
What's my weakness? You know what?
I bet you don't know my weakness. I know your weakness.
You wanna know what your weakness is?
What? Do it.
I didn't hit the buttons right, so I can't show you.
I can't show you your weakness.
It's getting kicked in the face.
Good fatality.
I don't want to sit here and watch it.
They're so long.
Yeah, that actually, like we've seen it so many times that like-
Well, we've already seen it.
Yeah, well, this is gonna make you pretty angry.
This one's for all the marbles.
Oh, it is.
Every time. I get hit by-
I think I seriously get hit by that every single time.
Pretty sure.
Oh, you think you wanna mess with me?
If I had done the move right, I would have got you.
Try to block that one.
I'm like doing this with you right now.
What the fuck?
I knew it. I knew you were gonna do that, too.
You didn't account for me to do that, did you?
I'll get out of here. You know what I'm gonna do.
I was trying to jump away from it, too,
and I just didn't do it because I'm just bad.
How could you be crouching that low
and still kicking you in the head?
I need to do the jump grab to you more often.
Gotcha.
That was so dumb.
Have some hot soup.
Why did that hurt me?
Because I did my air grab.
I'm surprised it didn't just grab you.
You didn't even do your air grab.
Finally, I got it to work.
And you got me with your x-ray.
From like over the head to the point.
I don't think it's gonna kill me.
I think I still get a chance. Of course I get a chance.
Of course I get a chance to do your fucking weakness.
I know your weakness.
Good luck.
I'll see you in the fucking funny papers.
Yeah, I'll see you next to Garfield.
See you next to Garfield.
And Foxtrot.
And more soup.
What's another funny?
What are some other funnies?
I don't even know.
I'm having trouble thinking of funnies.
I was trying to grab you and just couldn't get it to work.
Shit.
Any day.
Every time. I do it every time.
Don't do it.
That game doesn't even count.
What was the bet for this one?
There was a Lamborghini on the line for this one, right?
I distinctly remember a Lamborghini.