All right, I am back. I need to go this way. Grab this. How are you? You guys ready?
Final Fantasy 16. We're gonna watch a trailer. I think this is a live action trailer. This was
uploaded yesterday. Let me just tweet my tweet. Hey, there's a new sponsor tweet incoming. New
sponsor tweet. Are you serious? Okay. Wait, hold on. What is this one? Hotel fridges are just
freezers. Don't fuck around. That sandwich you put in there. Is it going to turn into a Jimmy
Dean's breakfast sandwich? That's pretty good. I'm just looking at my drafts right now. That's
actually a pretty good one. He's always dry. He's dumping the drafts right now. No, these,
no, they're not drunk tweets. Oh, this one's actually for, I will go over this after the sponsor.
Because this one, I got, I got a story to tell you after this. All right. Let me tweet this. Make
sure it looks right. You tell me if it looks good on Twitter. Look at how active my Twitter
is today. You've seen this activity. This is two, this is two or three tweets in one day. Look at
me now. Look at what I'm doing. Look at me. Look at what I'm doing now. Actually using Twitter.
Look at me. Okay. Looks pretty good. Looks pretty good. I'm just somebody shut up.
Everything work the 34 seconds ago. Shut up. Hi. Okay. All right. Let's watch the trailer. This is
the final fantasy 16 Requiem live action trim. Actually, I've not seen this. So let's see the
music off. Let's get comfortable. Let's get this. I'm going to turn the lights off. Everything seems
pretty solid. Uh, oh, there we go. I had to quit the game. Speak up. This is not it. I was still
in the other game. Get out of this. All right. It is time to watch the final fantasy 16 live
action trailer. Thank you by the way, Square Enix and final fantasy 16, sponsoring the segment of
the stream. You ready? I wonder how this, I wonder how this is. Here we go. Oh my God. Violence, blood,
sexual themes, nudity, strong language. All right. Okay. Are you guys ready to watch? Make
sure the audio is in a good spot. Here we go. Dog. Of course you walked by the blacksmith.
Everybody's playing music. Okay.
Shit. Oh my God. He went flying. He flew in there. There it was. Final fantasy 16. I've got a PS5
right now. Very excited. You ready to check out the demo? Let's fucking go. All right.
Bear with me for a second. I've never used a PlayStation. Hope I did all this right.
I've never used a PlayStation 5. I've played it one time with italics because he showed me that
the trigger buttons are cool. All right. Let's go see if I did this right. I think I did. Can
you guys hear it? Wait, it's coming through my TV. Hold on. I got to fix this. All right.
Give me one second. It's coming through my TV. It's not coming through my headphones.
Can you hear this, the music? It's like playing the intro. All right. Hold on. I got to move this.
Why is it going through my TV? There we go. Now I can hear it. Noise? What do you mean worse noise?
All right. Here we go. It's time. Square Enix. I do have to do this though. All right. Progress
is saved automatically. This demo features several chapters of Final Fantasy 16's first act. All
saved progress can be carried over to the main game. We hope you enjoy your time in Valisthia.
That's actually pretty good. That's cool. I'm glad you can actually save your progress.
Also, if you don't know, Final Fantasy 16, you don't need to know 15 games worth of story.
I think that's pretty obvious at this point. Otherwise, I don't know if I would have wanted
to play every single story for Final Fantasy, with the exception of a few, is different. This
one is no different. All right. Subtitles are going to stay on. Vibrations are going to keep
it on. What about brightness? Does this look good? A bit more? What do you guys think? I think it's
good right where it was. Game performance. Graphics or frame rate? I don't know. I don't
know really what this means. I have a PS5. Should I do graphics or frame rate? Maybe graphics.
Frame rate? This is probably fine. Story focused or action focused? Gameplay focused does not affect
story content. Mode can be changed after starting game. All right. So we're doing action, of course.
Screen brightness five. This is all sounds pretty good. Subtitles are on. Okay.
Is blessed in the light of the mother crystals and that it was this light
which finally led our forebears out of the darkness. Creative business unit. Great. What
they saw in the light gave rise to temptation. Temptation that ever lures us back into the
crystal shadow. And thus did our journey begin. Oh, that final fantasy. That final fantasy
soundtrack is already bumping. What just happened? Fireball? Wait, I have to evade. I'm playing the
game now. Spam fireball. Evade. Did I do it? Yeah, there's bird mode. I think I have to time it.
There it is. PS5 looks pretty good. It's a three year old console. Yeah, I mean,
I have never seen it before. Year of the realm 873 nicer. So what? What character am I? Do I
choose one or am I? You all know the target. She was dominant and only the dominant. No one else.
Where's the fun in that? That's me, right? The girl will be among them. Our kind do not question
orders. We follow them. Try to keep that in mind. Let's get this done. Yeah, I can't wait. I hope
that makes an appearance. True. Yeah, true. Yeah. So from my understanding, this game is different
than the other ones. It's not turn based. It's like action based, right? I'm very curious what
that means. Focus Wyvern. You are key to this mission success. Okay. Yes, sir. Final fantasy
hasn't been turned based in like a decade. I said focus Wyvern. All right. Fly. Wait, the main menu.
Press whatever that button is at any time outside a cut scene to open the main menu.
Gameplay configuration settings, including camera inversion can also be adjusted on the system tab.
We don't have time for this. All hell is about to break loose. I want to look at the scenery.
It's pretty good. Is there a run? All right. Tilt gently to walk. Here we go. Jump faster if you do
this. We're just in time. Do it gently. Do we have to fight all that? Look in army frontline.
Turn it up. Am I going to fight in a big fucking battle? Turn it up now. Now it's too quiet.
They won't need this new dominant of theirs. I can't wait to go.
Stronghold. What do you mean you refuse? We refuse. Did you not pledge your swords for our cause?
Oh, new characters. Come now, Marshal. The king of Walud is our guest.
And you have his majesty's answer. Oh, damn it. There's a huge ass table.
You can't do much at a table like that. What was that? I wonder that you summoned us at all.
Cigarette stream. Vape. It was the Dalmex who drove back the crusaders in the Battle of the Twin
Realms, was it not? Or am I mistaken? Besides, your dominant has yet to take the field.
And when he does, our knights would only get in the way.
Perhaps you have not heard, but the Ironblood now have their own dominant.
We would be fools to underestimate them. Bugger their knights. What did you say?
Oh, yeah. Should this citadel be allowed to fall?
Holy shit, this guy's fucking huge. The capital will lie exposed. He's like eight people. I,
okay, I did not know how big this guy was. The crusaders will wait for the good king's
pawns to line up before taking to the board. Why? Which just leaves me. That's so rude.
The Ironblood will rule the day they set foot on Storm. This game is over.
All right, so who's ass do I have to kick? You cock.
Benedict. Take care. Does the lion take care when he chases the hare?
Or do you think me one of the latter? No, my love. You are a lion. You're my lion.
I'm not afraid of a little frost, Benedicta. This guy is so, he's just...
Do I have to kick, do I have to kick that guy's ass? The front lines are gone.
18 plus and smoking. All right, cool. Okay, what's the first thing I got? You gotta give me like a
skeleton to kill, right? One skeleton is going to be like... Clive, be careful. That skeleton will
take you down in one swing. There's always a singular skeleton. As always, take the van.
Everyone we talked about what it would sound like if I had everyone, if I could hear everybody on
the stream. Okay, look at what it sounds like. Well, not like that. Oh shit. What was that?
There's the one skeleton. Oh no, that's quite the one skeleton for the tutorial.
All right, it's, I turned it up. So it's going to be loud. We're enjoying it. Just be aware. The
volume, you should adjust your volume. I turned it up. Oh, wait, are those chocobos?
I thought he was making that sound with his mouth. I think he was.
Let's go. Move. Oh, God. Wait, is this a, is that person bad? Okay, I think that person's bad.
Who's on, what team am I on? I don't know what team I'm on. Am I on team ice or team big gigantic
guy? It's hard to tell. Okay. All right. I'm liking this more and more as we go.
That's what I would say in that situation. Oh, a hundred percent. I'm glad that they're,
they're doing that instead of being like, Oh, whoa, better look out. No, you'd be like, fuck,
please help me. Please. God help me. What the, Oh, that guy got crushed. Oh, that's not good.
Wyvern, I told you before you do not get to die here. That's pretty awful. Oh,
now we're probably going to see some 13 summers earlier. There's always work for you in the
stables. Unless of course you think you can defend your master while sat on your ass in a puddle of
pigs. Well, I'm sure he'd find a way. My brother always looks after me. Right.
Go on. You're sure to hit him eventually. Don't give up now. I was going to say it's definitely
a wooden sword. All right. Wooden sword training. Here we go. All right. Start again from the
beginning. Show me your form. Attack the Lord commander. So square to perform melee attack
up to four attacks can be chained together. So don't don't don't don't. Okay. There is a lock on
again. Is there a dodge roll? Very good. Such swordsmanship will serve you well in the field,
but can the same be said of your spell craft? The flames of the phoenix burn within you.
Now let them burn without. You're an eye frame crackhead. Green fire down upon me.
Yeah, I kind of am. Okay. Triangle to cast fire. A range spell that can strike enemies from great
distances. Okay. I wonder if you can be like a mage. Well done. You wield the firebird's flames
just as a first shield should. You flatter me, my lord. Or would you rather I flattened you?
It can be arranged. Let's see if you can elude my blade. Plus one foe letter grade incoming.
Your attacking prowess will count for naught if you don't live long enough to use it.
On your toes, Lord Rossfield. Hmm. Stay quick on your feet. Evade four times. R1 to evade an
enemy's attack. Evading an attack at the precise moment it is dealt will temporarily slow the enemy,
making it more susceptible to a counter. All right. Cool. Come on. Dodge that. Because I'm a gamer.
Nice try. Good. Remember, Clive, your blade is not your only weapon.
Use your thought and flitness of foot are indispensable arms in any shield. Use your
voice and your intelligence to get out of issues. Show me what sets you apart from the rest.
You have been blessed by the phoenix. Granted the use of its power. Call upon that power now
to close on me. Well, I'm waiting. Close the gap. The blessing of the phoenix grants Clive
the ability to perform feats of inhuman strength and dexterity. Phoenix Shift is one such iconic
feat. Press circle to swiftly close in on a distant target. Both melee and ranged attacks
can be used while executing a phoenix shift. So it's like a super dodge. Impressive. But even
the most agile shield cannot hope to escape every blow. And death may come by a handful of cuts as
easily as it comes by a thousand. There is only one way to ensure that you do not fall.
Give your wounds mended and your energies replenished. Okay. Speaking of which, my lord,
you seem a little worse for wear. Now that won't do at all. Healing menu I'm imagining use potions.
Consumable items such as potions and tonics can be used to restore Clive's HP or temporarily
boost attributes. Consumables can be assigned to up right down via the items tab in the main menu
for a quick and convenient use. These items can be also used directly from the menu. Okay. So I'm
imagining this probably I'm just trying not to burp it. I'm trying to keep it in. Okay. So you can
assign stuff but I already have potion. There it is. You can really spam it too. Okay. That's better.
Battle is a succession of pivotal moments where in life and death can be decided at a single
stroke funny voice every tool at your disposal. If you are to navigate can be both to victory
or at the very least to ensure that you live to fight another day. Enough practice. It's time for
the test. I'm going to stop this guy. You recovered from your soaking I trust.
You wouldn't want to kick a man while he's drowned. I thought you'd never ask. Come then Lord Rosfield.
Spar with me. If you believe yourself worthy to be called shield of the flame then prove it
as you wish my lord. I'm so much stronger than you. So much better than you and so much older than
you and so much more wise. Well done boy. Well done.
Oh music. The will gauge indicates an opponent's will to fight back.
Break their spirit by landing attacks and strike them when they are vulnerable.
Okay. All right. Back it up.
You're serious. Okay. Jump. This is oh staggering your enemies. Lord Murdoch's will has been broken
leaving him staggered. Try dealing as much damage as you can before he regains his senses.
Use R2 plus squared execute rising flames a powerful iconic ability. Okay. So when they're down go.
When I used all the tools at my disposal.
Cool. Oh let's go. Yeah.
I probably would rebind. I'm going to rebind circle to dodge and R1 to be that move.
Just burned in my brain. That circle is always just dodge.
It's taken me long enough. That was a display worthy of your father.
There's already enough option for that. Okay. You are a true shield of the flame and let no one
tell you otherwise. Including me. What are you? Back to your drills. I was watching the vaude.
Meanwhile you're live. We're live right now. Final fantasy 16. Good demo. Do you think that hurt?
I was just tired. Phoenix's flames are a gift. You mustn't waste them. It isn't a waste. My
shields look after me. Why shouldn't I? That's why you were coughing this morning too.
You shouldn't be outdoors. It's just a cold. Don't push yourself. I wonder how the party
system will be in this game. Will it be party based? Do you swap between characters or just
play as one character? I wonder. I'm curious. Your grace. I would gladly brave hell itself
to see my darling boy. Okay. Gentlemen, Rosaria thanks you for your indefatigable loyalty.
Thank you, your grace. We live to serve. Joshua, you should not be out of doors.
We have discussed this. I'm sorry. Good day to you, mother. Come, Joshua.
Your father will be expecting us. Leather noise. Yeah, the leather noise.
Lord Murdock. Your grace. That was way worse. What a way to treat your own flesh and blood.
I know. It's not his fault. Not everyone can be born the phoenix.
You should just wear a big leather coat one day. I don't think I want to do that
in Las Vegas. That does not sound fun. Yeah, I've got a great idea. What is it? 120 degrees outside?
Yeah, give me a big leather coat. A regal, a regal chocobo. Look at how regal that chocobo is walking.
Rise, my friends. Welcome home, father. Thank you, Joshua. Would I look good in red? You are well
adressed. What do you guys think? Yes, father. Much better. I don't know. I don't think I could pull
red off. Is that so? Yeah, I'm definitely more of a blue gray. You'll make a fine purple. I like
purple too. Lift up your head, girl. Thank you, your grace. You were in red for that show you were in
the week. That was a puzzler, though. War is coming, my boy. You must make ready. Is the situation
truly so grave? Come to the throne room. We will top there. Yes, father. Your grace. Shields dismissed.
That didn't even hurt. Your grace. What does your grace mean? Your grace. Does that mean like
I find you to be your very like your bright and your grace, your honor? Like it's my honor to be
in your presence or something. What does it mean? Your grace, your honor. It's like bowing. Okay,
yeah. They were considered holy. God's grace. Okay, yeah, that makes sense. Okay, should you
find yourself lost, do not fret. Hold down L3 and trust in your animal instinct to point you in the
right direction. Your current destination will be displayed. All right, yeah, don't worry. I know
where we're going. I will tell you, though, if me and Holly were ever lost and I looked over and I
said, hey, don't worry, honey. We'll just trust my animal instinct. We'll get there. I don't know if
we'll get there or not. I just start like sniffing. Wait, where are we going? Okay, cool. So, let's see.
I'm not sure. I need to speak with father.
All right, what's this? Secret useful items can be found across the realm by those who know where
to look. Okay, what is this? A potion. Should I walk? We should probably RP walk, right? Make
for the throne room. Just skipping to the throne room. Close the gates. Let's hope the side entrance
is still open. I actually kind of like moving around like this. All right, would anybody feel
like, hey, stop doing that. That's skipping. Stop having so much fun Clive. What do you think you're
doing? Good as new. Forgive me. Your grace, you just put more bacteria on it and kind of dirty too.
Why do people keep doing that? It doesn't do anything. It was no trouble. Really? Oh, do not
indulge him. To be allowed to stand in your lordship's presence is more than his kind deserves.
Why? Neither the empire nor the republic treat their bearers half so well. He was lucky to be
born in your father's dominion. Very lucky as I remind him every day. Imagine seeing your lord
just skipping around through town. It'd be like, oh, I'd be like, all right, at least he's happy. At
least the lord is happy. I trust his good fortune will continue. Of course, if that is your lordship's
wish. Don't work too hard. Remember, it is for the good of the dodgy that you serve. It goes the
baker with the tray up. As do we all, my lord. As do we all. Come along now to your duties.
Yeah, get back to what you were doing. And by the way, it's always lord. Good day.
Looks like they're getting ready for supper. I think someone's hungry. I see a lot of minus
dudes. It's always lord. What kind of dialogue was that? By the way, it's always lord. Yeah, no,
that's what they called him. That's literally what they said. Both said it. Why am I acting like they
didn't say that? The optimal way to travel. Nice and quiet in here, isn't it? Oh, I just love the flower.
There's Joshua. Does anybody else feel like they can skip faster than they can run?
I really think I can. I think if I was in a full sprint versus a full skip,
I would be able to do, I would go faster skipping. That child is the future of our nation.
Oh no, am I? Some large gates and stiff levers require extra effort to operate.
Use X to access them and then hold R2 to push. Oh, whoops. Dude, this, oh, this is weird. The
PlayStation 5 has this, it's giving me, it's like feedback. I actually have to press this kind of
like hard. Whoa, cool. Whoa, whoa. Good luck. What's going on here? You commanded my presence,
your grace. How may I serve you? All right, you can stop licking my boots.
Your mother isn't here. Do the territories fare any better?
Most lie under a pall of black. In just these few moons, the blight has taken lie on all of
the northern reaches. It is only a matter of time before it crosses the border.
Nearly every available bed in the capital is already occupied by those fleeing the
deadlands. Even if we were to send themself to Port Isolde, more would only follow in their wake.
Every day we delay brings us closer to disaster.
Every throne I've seen looks really uncomfortable to sit in.
Against the Iron Kingdom. Did anybody ever have like a comfortable
fucking throne? They made like soft pillows and shit.
We have traded blows with them for too long. It is time to end it.
At the very least, we must secure Drake's breath. Without the blessing of the Mother Crystal,
we cannot defend our realm from the spread of the blight.
The Iron Blood will not relinquish it easily. This will be a bitter fight.
We ride for Phoenix Gate tomorrow. There we will listen to the words of our ancestors.
Horse mechanic? As tradition dictates.
Am I to go with you as Joshua Shield?
There was no ergonomics back then.
And I feel like the first order of business for me would be
get me a pillow to put under my ass to sit on.
You will have heard the reports, I am sure,
of beast men from the north being sighted within our borders.
Goblins in the Stillwind Marshes. I know of the rumors, yes.
Then you know what must be done. I will give you two good men.
Royal ass pillow.
While we ride north tomorrow, you will journey to Stillwind.
Search it and clear it. Then you will join us at Phoenix Gate.
It is time to prove your strength and shut your mother up for good.
I will do my duty, Your Grace.
Okay, good. I'm so ready.
That will be all. Rest well. We ride at dawn.
Yes, Your Grace.
Again, this is the demo. Get it right now.
PS5.
Active Time Lore. Hold that to access the Active Time Lore feature,
a compilation of important information relevant to Clive's current story progression.
ATL can even be viewed during most cutscenes.
What does that mean?
Oh, okay.
So it's important people and this is actually good
because I forget literally every single person's name.
Okay, cool.
Wait, did they actually add the caveman mode I was talking about?
Is this in the game?
Didn't I talk about how much I fucking wanted this so bad?
How badly I wanted this?
It's a paragraph to explain just here it is.
Hey, look. Look, there's like three sentences.
There's a lore button where you can just read like one small paragraph.
Okay, I'm happy about that.
Okay, retire to your chambers.
Hey, Dodd. What do you think of my training?
How do I get out of here? How do I get up there?
Oh, this way. The castle's nice.
Will you still be skipping as him 15 years later?
That's a core part of my character's personality right now.
Do you think I'm going to stop doing that?
How long will you be away this time?
Not long. Four days. Maybe five.
And you will be taking Joshua?
Well, I can't exactly leave him behind, can I?
The blood of the Rosfields runs in his veins.
Let me ask, does the demo have a lot of cutscene stuff?
Yeah, I think it's starting to build up the story.
Only the dominant can enter the apothecary, so yes, I'm taking Joshua.
Your demo progress does carry on to the main game when it releases itself.
I don't know that. The boy is also the phoenix, the heir to the throne.
You can't keep him in swaddling clothes all of his life.
Don't worry. Clive will watch over him.
Can you skip in the full game?
As a youth of but 15 years, he's already a fine soldier.
He will make a splendid shield.
Yes, you can.
You see more in him than the phoenix did.
He was rejected, Elwyn.
Our household has no place for such a failure.
He is worthless, a man like any other.
As am I, my dear.
Nonsense. You are the archduke of Rosaria.
Not this again.
You know, as well as I do, that I only sit upon the throne
because my father was taken before his time.
I am merely warming the seat till Joshua comes of age.
You are your father's firstborn son.
And you sit upon the throne.
All is in its right place.
And my son, you have not disgraced our noble blood.
Without men like Clive to keep us safe, your precious noble.
Who are these people?
Okay.
Look at how fucking perfect that thing really is.
This is great.
In the middle of the cutscene, I can be like, wait.
Okay, this is Annabelle of Rossfield.
Duchess of Rosaria.
Wife of Archduke Elwyn and mother to Clive and Joshua.
Perfect.
I know who this is now.
Joshua of Rossfield.
Second son of the Archduke of Rosaria,
Joshua was appointed heir to the Ducal throne by virtue of his awakening
as the dominant of the phoenix.
His love, actually, that's actually really cool.
Let's go back to it now.
Hold on a second.
Pause it one more time.
Don't let me be in charge of pausing anything.
I'm imagining, and I know I'm just kind of messing around here,
but I'm imagining if you hear somebody say something
or talk about something, you could just pause it and be like, wait.
They said Rosalith Castle was out, right?
Okay, that's this one.
That's cool.
I like that.
We have an early start.
I'm going to sleep.
Go back and read the queen's profile.
Wait.
Oh, it's whatever is currently in the frame.
Is that how it works?
I suppose, let me see.
I think that's how it works.
This is it then.
Prove yourself.
Wishing on a star.
I'll talk about a couple things after this too,
because somebody brought this up,
but I want to make sure I tell people this
because I feel like people that know this would go, oh, okay.
Right.
Yeah, that's cool.
All right, so you're born a princess of the Northern Territories.
Jill was made a ward of Rosaria after her homeland's incessant raids
were quelled by the Duchy.
She was raised in Rosalith Castle alongside Clive and Joshua
who came to love her as a sister.
That's so helpful for me.
You're going with them tomorrow, aren't you?
I am Joshua's shield.
I'm sworn to protect him.
He takes too many risks.
Jerma mode.
I only wish I could save him from himself.
You mean a good mode.
Clive, you...
I have another mission too.
Father has given me my first command.
Well...
What does command mean?
If you're not going to pray to Meteor for your safety...
He said a word I don't understand.
Command?
It's not here.
What's that mean?
I shall just have to do it for you.
Dude's gonna pull this off every cutscene now.
I promise I'm not gonna.
There's going to be another war, isn't there?
Since coming here, I've begun to take peace for granted.
I assume the war between our nations would be the last.
But it never really ends, does it?
No.
The next war will be bigger than before.
But you'll be all right, won't you, Clive?
You're a shield of Rosaria, after all.
I'm blessed by the phoenix.
It's getting cold.
We should go in.
Bye, lady.
Good night, Clive.
And you press the lower button to find out why it's cold.
It just...
All right, you press...
You go like this.
And it has like the forecast in the top right.
It's chilly.
65 degrees at Rosalith Castle.
Northwest winds blowing at 15 miles per hour.
That'd be cool.
You broke your promise already?
Well, that was the end of the cutscene.
Also, do I have a second?
Let's see.
People were saying Devil May Cry.
So the combat director of this game,
Ryota Suzuki?
Ryota Suzuki worked on Devil May Cry and Dragon's Dogma.
So that's the combat director of the game.
Also, the director and producer of Final Fantasy XIV.
And the composer and sound director of Final Fantasy XIV also worked on this.
If that is perking your ears up a little, if you liked those games,
I don't know.
We'll see.
Yeah, that's Yoshido.
And Masayoshi Soken, composer of the game.
The combat director is interesting, though.
I'm very curious how it actually plays out fighting and battle scenarios.
It's actually a dream team to make a Final Fantasy game.
It sounds like it.
The Beastmen are a fierce foe.
We underestimate them at our peril.
We need some lore?
Not today, we won't.
Wait, we need to know who these people are.
One of the stables of Rosalith Castle,
Rosio was chosen by the young Clive Rosfield to be his personal steed and raised by him from a chick.
She's a proud bird and deeply loyal to her master,
quickly turning her beak upon any but he who should attempt to pet her.
So wait, Sir Tyler, let us do our duty.
They don't have lore because somebody said,
I don't think they have lore because they're probably dead soon.
To the marshes then.
Well, you don't know that.
That's not why they don't have a lore card.
Blessing of the crystals go with us.
Over world map.
The world map displays all the locations indicated by glowing pins currently available
to Clive via fast travel.
OK, so we're going here.
So this is still wind.
Make for still wind.
Those guys weren't as important as a bird.
I think that bird's probably really important.
No, I'm not going to lore check.
These guys don't have a lore card.
Watch.
Whoa, shit.
Sir Wade.
A loyal shield of Rosaria chosen by Lord Commander Rodney Murdock
to accompany Clive on his expedition to still wind.
Once, but a lowborn page, Wade was inspired to join the ranks after a woodpile fell on him
and his life was saved by a young Joshua.
OK, cool.
What about you?
A little bit more for Tyler here.
A loyal shield of Rosaria and Sion of a noble family.
Tyler followed in his father's footsteps in entering the service of the duchy,
rising to the position of right-hand man to the Lord Commander.
He was chosen by Lord Murdock to accompany Clive on his expedition to still wind.
A level head who could be trusted not only to obey the young lord's orders and keep him safe,
but to help keep the fiery sir Wade in line.
Goblins.
We don't know anything, but I don't want to see that yet.
Keep your eyes open for those goblins.
Ports placed them in this area.
It's all swamps from here.
Watch your step, my lord.
And everything else.
OK, lost in a fog.
Feeling overwhelmed?
Try equipping one or more of the five timely accessories.
For example, the ring of timely strikes allows its wearer to chain complex attack combos
only using square.
The ring of timely focus slows time before an incoming attack.
As with all items, timely accessories can be equipped or not equipped on the gear tab.
Oh, I think I'm all right.
We'll be fine.
I said to check.
Not exactly the most well-maintained path.
But who do you imagine would maintain it?
Oh no, I lost my touch.
All fled from the blight.
No more skipping.
The music is preparing me for something.
I like this.
The old village of still wind is ahead.
Not that there's a lot left of it.
Get the item.
Two gil.
Two bucks.
Wait, I gotta check over here.
I didn't try to jump over that.
I was trying to touch the butterflies that are above it.
What are they doing?
Oh, you fucked up so bad.
How could you have stepped on one of the sticks?
Oh, first time, first combat.
OK.
Oh, shit.
All right, cool.
So the reports were true.
We should press on.
There may be more ahead.
Floor check.
All right, we have pictures now.
Did I miss any items or anything?
I don't think so.
I see a shiny.
Can I get in here?
Yep.
Strength tonic.
Keep slaying those goblins.
All right.
Welcome to still wind.
Have care, my lord.
Oh, more goblins.
Some enemies will drop gil or items upon the defeat.
Loot is gathered automatically.
OK, gold loot on the ground.
I do appreciate the small denomination of currency,
but I don't want 10,000 gil in my pocket.
I'd want like 10.
Can't break it.
Oh, ocean.
Should I heal now?
Strength tonic.
I should probably put these on the bar.
Yeah, the music is wonderful.
This should be a master class on how to do background music that feels engaging.
But it's not it's not so much.
It's not offensive.
Oh, they are spell slingers.
New enemies approach.
OK, I'm going to.
OK, I was going to say I can just do that whenever I want.
If only you could speak goblin.
Wait, lore check the spell slinger.
There's not going to be individual lore cards for every enemy type.
Can I do anything else with the fire?
I wonder there actually might be maybe.
Haven't pressing R2 like that is definitely feels different for me.
This is the next generation of controllers in my hand.
I've barely experienced that and this is a PlayStation thing.
This is a I have to I have to squeeze it.
You have to squeeze that shit.
You have to squeeze it.
We should be nearing the old village square.
It might not be a nest of goblins.
Oh, he's the ad guy.
No, I've I have never experienced this before.
I've never pressed the right trigger before and had to like squeeze it a little.
I just tell it.
This is my first experience playing with a piece station five.
We're trapped.
My lord, I'm working on it.
Well, bring it on.
Let's go.
He's the leader to take care of his followers first.
Oh, can't have been the hurt.
Let's go.
You have to ask.
What do you got?
Coming.
There was one.
Holy shit.
OK, let's do it.
So wait on three larger enemies must be faced with caution.
If farmer HP than their smaller counterparts will often use devastating
abilities to overwhelm opponents.
Use the blessing of the phoenix to not only deal considerable damage
to these enemies, but also break their wills.
Breaking an enemy's will can stagger it, leaving it unable to act invulnerable.
Let's go.
This is fun.
All right.
Enemies will become partially staggered when their will gauge is reduced to 50%.
I don't want to check the lore right now.
Creating a short opening.
Hold on.
Let me look at the lore book.
I know.
I can't look at the lore book right now.
Oh, shit.
OK, I got to time it better than that field.
All right, let's go.
Co-op, let's do it.
Completely reducing an enemy's will gauge will stagger it.
Extra damage is dealt when an enemy is fully staggered,
increasing with each strike landed up to a maximum of 150%.
The total amount of damage dealt during this time is displayed
upon the enemy regaining its senses.
That's cool.
OK.
So it just counts it all up.
All right, let's start counting.
Oh, quadruple dodge.
Dude.
All right.
You got any more?
You got any more in there?
All right, let's end it.
Go.
Who is it?
Giga Chad.
Level up.
Do I have to put any points in or anything?
Hard leather.
Following important battles, a separate results screen
will appear displaying battle performance and rewards.
Rewards are based on performance and may include items, gear,
ability points, and experience points.
OK.
There's gear.
I'm going to get stopped this dude.
Come back and fight, you coward.
After him.
Before he summons the rest.
But I-
Hold on, let me get an item first.
OK.
So I got to go to the gear tab.
Learning new ones require ability points.
OK, here we are.
The attributes tab provides a comprehensive overview
of Clive's current level status, abilities, and gear.
All right, what does the gear look like?
The gear and icons tab is used for equipping weapons and armor
as well as assigning iconic abilities.
All right, so this is 10 defense.
Oh, I like that.
Like that.
OK.
Do I need new belts?
No, I don't need to put on them.
Put any of those on.
Abilities.
Ability points can be spent in the abilities tab
to acquire new abilities as well as upgrade existing ones.
If you are unsatisfied with Clive's current build,
reset all abilities and try again.
There's no penalty for doing so.
OK, this indicates an ability's capacity for dealing damage
and for breaking a target's will.
Melee attack, skill points too.
OK, this is-
This is going to be-
All right, I'm excited.
All right, so should I-
What should I upgrade?
Can I upgrade this?
Just the melee ability?
I have 152 ability points.
Do magic instead?
Magic burst?
Oh, you can do that in between every single swing.
Charred magic?
Hold to increase potency.
Stomp?
Upgrade skipping.
Phoenix shift, which makes that-
I don't have enough.
Let's go with one of these.
OK, swift recovery.
That's probably pretty good.
Taunt?
Burning blade?
Yeah, I want that.
I want this even stronger.
Do I have enough?
Down thrust?
Lunge?
I like that too.
All right, I'm going to do lunge.
And burning blade.
So this is hold square,
and this one is square and X at the same time.
All right, I don't want to spend too money though.
This is holding triangle, OK?
I want to save my points.
All right, let's go.
So let me see.
Nice.
And then lunge.
And then if I hold, I can get a fire sword.
And then saving in the demo.
All of your progress carries over, by the way.
Whatever you do in the demo,
carries over to the real game.
Stomp is going to be essential with how cheap it is, probably.
Well, we'll see.
Come on, I could have hit him.
I could have hit him.
Please.
It didn't really cause a problem.
Is this the precursor to the real big scary boss, I wonder?
Uh-oh, yeah.
It's never going to be that easy.
Oh my goodness gracious, OK.
I'm awful.
Quick climb.
Look at the box.
I'm standing that.
Oh, I missed the lunge.
Sorry.
Chip damage, chip damage, chip damage.
Swing, swing, swing, swing.
You're good.
This is as good as mine.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
All right.
There's a cinematic strike mode.
When the screen flashes blue like this during a pivotal moment in battle,
a square before time runs out.
All right.
There's a QTE.
There's a cinematic QTE.
Let's go.
1,100.
That's pretty good.
I wonder if there's a cinematic upgrade tree.
Before it recovers.
And one more.
Oh, there's a parry in the game, too.
Oh, I'm fucking playing this for sure.
Use square just as a permanent attack, but it temporarily slows time and shit.
All right.
What do I do?
Press.
What is it?
Square.
There's a parry in the game.
You've got me now.
You've got me.
I'm here.
So it's right when it...
Wait, I...
Oh, I did it.
Let me try it again.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
Oh, did it work?
Oh, no.
Hold on.
I'll get it.
It's a square right when you're about to get hit.
I'm just going to practice it.
Ow.
Am I doing it wrong?
I think I'm doing it wrong.
Square.
Stick to dodge roll.
Something else.
Cinematic evasion.
Okay.
I'm a caster.
I'm going to stay back here.
Oh, I'm good.
Oh, wow.
True.
I kind of like these two guys, too.
I didn't care at all until 10 seconds ago about these two.
That should be it.
I got to do the thrust more often.
Whoops.
Don't do it.
I don't have any heals left.
I got to be careful.
I don't want to...
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to die right now.
All right.
Time to play like a coward.
Are those guys okay?
Here we go.
I'm going to dodge it.
There it is.
Get him!
Almost through there.
That's true.
Almost died to the tutorial boss.
Well, the tutorial boss is there for you to learn.
How the game functions.
I think I did a pretty good job.
Oh, my lord.
Thanks.
Never thought I'd see it.
Not just goblins in Rosaria, but more balls, too.
I'll petition his grace to send a detachment.
If we don't stop them here, they'll be at our gates before long.
We should get moving.
We don't want to be caught out here after dark.
If we set off now, we can still reach Phoenix Gate before nightfall.
Third boss lands.
Is it still alive?
It might be.
This is the Phoenix Gate.
Check it out.
Some time later.
The lord check.
Oh, imagine there was like 40 circles.
Is there updated info, though?
There's a little indicator on here.
Oh, maybe it means he just showed up.
Okay.
The young lord has a bright future ahead of him.
In one of these nights, he may even deign to join us.
It does have updated info.
I really do appreciate that, though,
because I have said many, many times how I just kind of...
Sometimes I just need to open up like a thing
and give me like two sentences of who the fuck these people are.
Makes it easy to jump back in.
Potentially days or weeks later, too.
We cannot live without the blessing of the crystals.
And the crystals work their magic through us.
Eat that bread so badly.
You have been blessed, Joshua.
Blessed to be a dominant.
To wield the power of an icon.
Our family has been chosen to share that power with the people.
So that is what we must do.
Brunk.
Singing, eating a shitload of bread.
That sounds like a great time, doesn't it?
That sounds great.
A room full of carbs, yeah.
It's an off-brand meeting.
I don't think we would get very much done.
Lore check the dog.
Torgal, Clive's faithful friend,
brought back from one of Archduke Elwynn's expeditions to the frozen Northern Territories,
where he was found half-starved and shivering in a snowfield,
having presumably been separated from his pack.
Elwynn gifted the puppy to Clive upon his return,
and the two became nigh inseparable.
What are you doing out here?
I didn't see you at the feast.
Feasts are the only time shields are allowed to take their ease,
and I've never really been one for cakes and ale.
It's the vegetables I don't like.
That was cool.
I hear you slew a mawble.
All the men were singing your praises.
They never used to.
When I joined the ranks, everyone thought I was a spoiled little lordling.
If I didn't know how to handle a sword, I'd be a laughingstock.
The Archduke's first-born failure.
Why have I-
You're the one they really believe in.
Why have I heard this voice actor before?
I'm jealous.
That's not true.
They don't believe in me.
They believe in the power of the Dominant.
I heard this.
My brother the phoenix, ruler of a life and death.
It isn't fair.
It should have been you.
I don't have what it takes to lead our people.
I don't have the strength, but you do.
Let me see, hold on.
Every man has his duty.
Ours was decided long ago,
when our ancestors chose to instate the Dominant as the Archduke of Rosaria.
Hold on, I'll find a-
You need to ensure that whenever our nation stood on a precipice,
the phoenix would rise from the flames to drag us back from the brink.
The fate of Rosaria sits on the Dominant shoulders.
It is your duty to bear that burden.
Holy shit.
What about you?
This guy's done so much work.
This is like an unbelievable catalog of work.
That is why I was given the phoenix's blessing.
To keep our future rulers safe.
No matter what.
Wait, I got the wrong person.
However hard it gets.
Thank you, Tive.
I know you'll always take care of me.
I think I- do I have the wrong person?
Where I can do that, you need to take care of yourself.
No, no, no, I do.
I have the right person.
Right?
I should go inside.
It's past my bedtime.
Good night, Toggle.
Where have I heard this voice before?
Ben Starr.
Yeah, where have I heard this voice though?
Recently.
The trailer?
Supplies from the capital.
It's got a familiar voice or a familiar way of speaking.
You took your time sampling the wearers, were you?
Yeah, I had the first person I looked up at.
I thought it was the same person, but it wasn't.
Sounds good.
I like it.
You're missing lore pauses?
It's not going to give me lore right now.
No, no, no, it's not.
Guys, it doesn't give you spoilers.
It just tells you what you should know by that point.
You don't get to look and see what this guy does two chapters from now.
It doesn't work like that.
Uh-oh.
Oh, magical spells.
All right, get out there and just like...
Joshua has a four-hit combo with ice spells.
I only knew his name was Joshua because I did the thing.
I looked at it.
They're under attack.
I don't know who they are, but they've set light to half the castle.
I must get you to safety, Your Highness.
Very well.
I'm ready.
Follow me, Your Highness.
Wait, I actually...
It is.
It's true.
I actually am going to play as this character now.
You guys thought I was full of shit.
I'm going to have like ice moves getting out of my hands.
You thought I was full of shit?
Yeah.
Really?
I think I used all of his fucking power.
All right.
I just did 999, 999.
Damn it.
I'm ready.
So they are caster characters.
Okay.
The kid just cast fucking starlight.
Oh, starlight kid.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, yeah?
Do my duty.
Did I get in there?
This kid is strong.
Nice whiff.
I thought it was a range.
I thought it was range.
Garaga is a heal.
I think I remember that.
9999 heal.
Let's move.
All right, so I got that.
I can only do one.
I don't have a chain with it though.
Maybe I do if I don't land two.
This is bullshit.
Anything going on down here?
Is there a stealth kill?
Ha ha ha ha, idiot.
Stupid idiot.
Uh oh.
That's not good.
Tyler.
We just started to care about Tyler.
This is not good.
I can save him.
Sorry, you're going to be all right.
I'll hold them off.
Oh.
It's you.
Why?
Joshua.
Come here.
Tyler.
You're hurt.
You'll survive.
Thanks to his highness.
It's all right, my lord.
I can only be three party members anyways.
You guys go on ahead.
Figure it out later.
Rescue the young prince.
Well done, Sir Wade.
Your debt, soldier.
Thank you.
Your grace.
How come there's never a fantasy character with a Boston accent?
That would be just wouldn't make any sense.
All right, you stay fucking here, kid.
You just chill out.
Do that cure shit on that guy.
Heal his fucking wounds.
I'll take everybody out.
We'll go out front and we'll just fuck these motherfuckers up.
Hey, can I get your car keys?
I just want to park it somewhere else
because there's like three people behind you.
Or in front of you.
I don't want you to trap anybody.
Do something, Elif.
May the winds speed you to Rosaleth.
The north gate's up ahead.
There are chocobos in the stables.
Father, take Joshua and get to safety.
No, I'm not going without you.
You're supposed to be my shield.
Remember?
It'd be great to have that 9999 heal.
I would love to take this kid.
Which is why I'm going to hold the enemy here while you make your escape.
I will order our remaining forces to rally at the gate.
Now go.
Do my duty.
You must do your duty too.
I know.
You have to keep father safe.
If I like this, would I like 15 as well?
Somebody just said you would like 15 if you like this.
Maybe.
You would like 14.
Are we going for it?
14 is pretty good.
Well, I don't have to know anything, right?
It's just its own video game.
I don't need to know everything that happened in the last 15 games
or the last 12 games or anything.
I should...
Okay, I got potions on there already.
All right, here we go.
All right.
Oh, dodge.
Wrong dodge.
Stuck on the table.
Everyone's dead.
Don't forget to parry.
I should probably learn how to parry on these guys.
I think he's trying to get away from me.
I'll try parry.
He said parry is hard.
Well, that's good.
It means insufficient inventory space.
High potion used.
Do I have to get a bigger stash or bigger inventory eventually or something?
This way you can't hold 99 potions and trivialize the game.
Here's a big fight.
Focus up.
You got it.
You try it.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Right when you...
No, no.
Too early.
I was practicing, dad.
No, wait, wait.
Who is this?
I have the wrong character.
I need my lore book.
Uh-oh.
Fuck, who is this?
Oh, shit.
Let's get him.
Oh, that hurt a lot.
Oh, that hurts a lot too.
Oh, that hurt real bad.
All right, I gotta get better.
I gotta get better.
I gotta get way better than this.
I gotta be better than this.
That's fine.
Back up.
I gotta parry that.
That didn't work.
Parry.
Is that right?
I don't think it was right.
Oh, shit.
He's open.
Is he?
I love that.
It's so...
It's just like dialing up to 100.
Now, Clive.
How about it?
I think he's spitting up.
Whoa.
Oh, he's got a combo.
Send it.
I forgot my cool combo.
It was cool, I promise.
Oh, dude, I'm so glad this game
isn't coming out like next year.
Do you know what I mean?
Look at it.
Night of the blinding dawn slain.
That music is just...
All right, you know when you play a game
and it's just, you know,
the music is kind of going
and it fits and you're just like, yep.
I almost play to the beat.
Do you guys do that too?
I'm fine.
So they sent in the Dragoons.
Imperial vipers.
Do they really mean to invade us?
Yeah, June 22nd.
Not yet.
For PS5, yeah.
Their numbers were too few.
They were not here to take the castle.
They were here to take heads.
Our work is done.
We should return to my father.
My lord, look.
We issued these sashes, but yesterday...
You're saying I wonder how deep the skill system gets
in the full game?
I don't know.
That's a good question.
Father and Joshua are in danger.
We must hurry.
Take your steed.
What is that?
You just mouth fuck you to me?
I read lips.
The dog is fine.
Everybody was freaking out about that.
Your grace, is everyone safe?
For the moment, we ride for Rosalith to rally our forces.
I will need your help to see Joshua safely back to the capital.
On you get, Joshua.
What the hell?
What the fuck was that?
I'm sorry, your grace, but that won't be possible.
Hey.
Oh.
Snakes!
Stay back!
I'm warning you!
Run, Joshua!
Run!
No!
Hey!
Oh, no.
I think we're gonna lose...
I think we're gonna lose another one.
You must do your duty, too.
Father safe.
I have to.
I had to.
No!
I...
On you, Joshua.
Oh, he...
Okay.
He's the phoenix.
He's...
Phoenix?
Joshua!
Oh, this is where we start here.
He's lost control.
I have to do something.
I have to save him.
No!
My lord.
Fall back!
Oh.
Ow.
Oh, no.
Chocobo!
Thank you, God.
You saved my life.
I'm gonna fit and run.
Please.
Joshua.
Are you in pain?
You're his shield.
Do your duty.
What?
Save him.
My lord.
Second icon of fire.
That's impossible.
Whoa!
Wait, did I...
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
I need to check the lore.
I have to check the lore.
Who?
What happened?
Firstborn son of Archduke Elwyn, ruler of Rosaria,
through all expected him to inherit the phoenix's flames and awaken as its dominant,
destiny instead chose his younger brother Joshua to bear that burden.
In search of a role of his own,
Clive dedicated himself to mastering the blade
and his practice paid off when he was appointed first shield of Rosaria.
Okay.
Tasked to guard the phoenix and blessed with the ability to wield a part of his fire.
Do I actually get to walk around
and play as this character?
And this is...
What the fuck?
Okay.
So, we're do...
We are...
Embodying the phoenix.
The following commands are available when playing as the phoenix.
Fire, aim, and evade.
When your opponent is directly within your sights,
the targeting circle will expand.
That is the time to fire.
Okay.
Wait, I have to actually aim.
Here we go.
We both go horizontal on a 2D plane.
It just goes...
3, 2, 1, fight!
Uh oh.
Okay.
All right, I think I'm gonna get...
Here we go.
Oh!
All right, when he glows like that's when I have to dodge.
Here it comes.
No, not yet.
Well, I'm shooting a lot of fireballs too.
It's not just him.
Shoot him!
All right, I gotta be ready to evade.
Here it comes.
Oh, that was actually pretty close.
Stop jumping around!
Do I have to dodge that?
Where is he?
Jesus.
Oh my god, dude.
Now we're on the offensive.
All right.
I love the icons.
The top left and top right.
Oh, I am shooting a million fireballs right now.
Sorry.
I don't think I'm getting away from this.
Oh my god, I was so paying no attention.
I was just spamming and I wasn't...
I forgot I had to actually dodge.
Damnation?
In...
How many seconds?
Hellfire?
Uh oh.
Dude, he just...
He just...
Wait.
What is going on right now?
I mean, it's fucking awesome.
But what is happening?
Okay.
I should have done a lore check.
Like, that was kind of like
when a company does an E3 presentation
and it's like, look at this game that we've got!
Our E3 presentation!
That actually happened in the game.
That happened in the game.
Here.
We got to see like an E3 presentation
that actually made it through into the video game.
That was fucking cool.
Hashtag ad?
Yes, of course hashtag ad.
But the game is fucking phenomenal.
Okay.
I'm having a ton of fun.
I want to play way more of this.
Combat was really fun.
I think I could get in...
I think I could actually get into it.
Just the fighting is just so much different
than what I've ever played with Final Fantasy.
Round two?
What the fuck?
This is awful.
What is going on?
Stop it!
I swore!
I will beat you!
Beat you!
Wait, what?
Is the dog?
Holy shit!
I'll kill you!
I can't kill you!
Damn.
Please do a lore check, please.
Oh, we...
Sorry, I missed it.
When we started here,
I was like, all right,
I'm not sure where we're going with it.
But I was not expecting any of that.
That we're just going to be as a band of
adventurers.
Can't believe it.
Make sure to walk over very
evilly, too, while you're at it.
Kill him?
What the fuck?
Oh my god, dude.
What the hell?
You all didn't think we were going here.
None of you did.
Chin up, lad.
You're going to be a soldier.
Why?
What?
My goodness.
Okay.
Well, I'm very interested.
Thank you for watching this.
Yeah.
Thank you for playing.
You've completed the Final Fantasy XVI demo,
but there's still much more story to tell.
You'd like to learn more of Clive and the dominance.
Please consider purchasing the main game.
Consider me considering.
You know what I mean?
That was great.
So I will absolutely be playing this again.
You'll see it again.
I wish I could kind of keep playing right now.
When does this come out?
Playthrough data saved.
Playthrough data can be carried over to the main game,
allowing you to continue from where you left off in the demo.
Demo playthrough data cannot be loaded in the demo version.
To play the demo again,
you must select new game from the title screen.
I have to pee so bad.
I will be right back.
But that's great.
Again, yes, this is a sponsored segment of the stream.
Square Enix, thanks for sponsoring the stream.
And obviously Final Fantasy XVI.
Demo, you can go get it right now.
It's a free demo on the PS5 store.
If you want to check it out for yourself, you can.
That was great.
I liked it a lot.
Don't save the game.
Don't save.
Should I save?
No, no, I should save, right?
I will.
I gotta pee.
I'll be right back.
Give me one second.
Okay, I am back.
So there's more to the demo.
What more is there to do?
More to do.
Okay, so I got it saved.
Just kind of back up.
Purchase from PlayStation Store.
Digital Deluxe or the base game.
Okay, well, there's another mid-game mission.
Really?
Go back to the title screen?
Wait, are people...
I think that's the end.
I don't think there's anything else.
I'll go back to the title screen.
Ah, there is.
There is.
Okay, there is more to look at.
The iconic challenge has been unlocked
and is now available from the title menu.
In this special mode set later in the game.
Clive has been equipped with the feats and abilities
of three unique icons.
The Phoenix, Garuda, and Titan.
To allow you to get a better feel
of Final Fantasy XVI's exciting battle system.
Well, we're doing that.
Okay, note.
This challenge was created specifically for this demo
and its features differ slightly
from what appears in the final game.
Gear, items, abilities are not representative
of what normally...
What are normally available to Clive
during this part of the story.
Makes sense.
The world map and journal have been removed
from the main menu.
Save, autosave, and load functionality is unavailable.
So, this is exclusive for the demo
and it's not going to spoil anything.
That's cool.
I think we already know this, right?
Do we know this?
We know this, right?
Is there spoilers here?
This is new.
It will spoil, but just a small section.
There's some story, but we don't know broader context.
There's spoilers?
Very mild spoilers?
Okay.
Well, it said they made it specifically for the demo.
I'm imagining it's an early part of the game.
Yeah, okay.
All right, we join the two as they begin
their infiltration of Chyre Norvent,
an ancient stronghold wherein his brother
is supposed to kill her, a second dominant of fire.
He's said to be held by an elite party of
Weloder Knights, commanded by Benedicta Harmon.
Okay, so 13 years have passed since their tragic events
which saw Clive robbed of his brother,
his father, and his home.
Okay.
He runs his freedom in the hands of a man named Sid
who agrees to aid our hero in his search for answers.
Okay.
I think it's spoiling what we just saw
and maybe like a little tiny little snippet.
I would be surprised if they would spoil something in a demo.
And we're probably gonna get some pretty out of context things.
Lore check?
No, I'm not doing a lore check.
Not now.
They've also said this won't be exactly the same
as the game.
It'll be changed.
That's actually really smart.
That's a smart thing.
Like, oh, hey, yeah, we're just making it.
The cut scenes just different
and the characters are not even the fucking same probably.
We just, we just made this up.
Okay.
Well, that's fucking awesome.
I don't know the context, but I now know context
that dog is playable character in game.
Now, now we're really cooking.
As L to the cycle between currently attuned icons
in real time, cool down times for iconic abilities
are displayed around the corresponding icon.
Okay.
So everything has to cool down so you can switch.
He's everywhere.
That actor is everywhere now.
I hear him every fucking day, but he's got a,
he's got a great voice, right?
All right.
So what I can change to, how do I swap?
Oh, I see what's going on.
All right.
Let's do deadly embrace.
He's gonna be great in this game
to I can already tell they're all empty.
They're all empty.
Sid, this gate needs some help.
You can still skip as an adult.
Yes.
Oh, wait, there's more to the demo.
Yeah.
So there is a, we didn't know this until the very end,
but there's like a little snippet from the middle of the game
that they tried to make sure
there wasn't very many spoilers in it.
And it's just, Hey, take a look at some more
of the combat shit for like a minute or two
while you have a minute.
What about these other moves?
Let's just do a limit break.
Fuck it.
I thought he just burped really loud.
That was a dog growling.
Devil May Cry designers chops are showing here.
Yeah, it's going to be fun.
This tour only leads to more royalists.
We'd better find another one.
Read the abilities.
Rising flames, scarlet cyclone.
Oh, it's been quickly creating a ring of fire.
Look at that.
What?
Oh, I am pogging in real life.
Gouge.
Some twin claws that relentlessly tear at a target
can be used in midair.
Rising attacks, breaking all enemies within range.
Punch forward, hold button to wind up attack,
further increasing potency.
Oh, okay.
So you do it.
Let it go in the red, probably.
Where are we going?
I'm just not that one, obviously.
Am I going the right way?
Am I going the wrong way?
Okay.
Just not that way.
It runs pretty well.
I have the framerate mode turned on,
but it seems to be pretty clean.
Where am I going?
How come my screen is darker than the stream screen?
I don't know why.
Hold up.
Oh, right.
If I have the mode where I can see things.
Oh, it is right here.
Use the animal instinct.
Can you please pet the dog?
Find out.
Probably not in a combat scenario.
Holy shit.
Whoa, there's more to the, there's a second part.
They all were like flying in like, they like,
I can't even talk.
I'm gonna try the phoenix move.
Distance.
Cool.
Why bright and magic ash?
Did I miss any items or anything?
Can we get a bald cam, please?
Maybe on your birthday.
Oh, you can really chain stuff together.
That's enough.
All right.
The chains are going to be fun.
I think I got to turn my brightness up a little.
Let's see.
Can I do it from here?
Camera settings, graphic settings.
Screen brightness.
All right.
That's better.
There we go.
What about you have a light?
You have a light.
I can wait.
Can I turn the light on?
I have a light move.
Do I?
How do I do the light move?
I don't think so.
It's on the phoenix.
Oh, okay.
Wait, that's a block.
I wonder how much it blocks.
Damn.
Shit.
I missed it.
Just 5,000 damage.
All right.
There, boy.
Sicko Togo.
That was a good parry.
Wait.
Oh, it's turning.
Woo.
This guy.
Yeah, this guy does not stand a chance.
Crush him.
Any item?
This map feels nostalgic.
There are probably some nods to the previous games or previous things.
There usually is, isn't there?
I don't know what hit them.
Aver of fire.
All is after them.
My birthday is on August 2nd.
Please do a bald cam.
I swear I'll...
Okay.
Attacking an opponent from the front while it is guarding will deal no damage.
Circle to the rear to penetrate its defenses.
Certain basic abilities such as Burning Blade and Charged Magic,
as well as iconic abilities such as the Phoenix Rising Flames,
can instantly break an opponent's guard when delivered from the front.
Okay.
Good to know.
Back it up.
New enemies coming up?
Whatever.
Let me try this.
All right, I can't...
When the game comes out, I think I'm doing the titanic stuff.
Feels really strong.
Anybody else?
I don't know who to swing at, but...
Jesus.
So what are the two bars under my health?
I wonder.
Oops.
That's Limit Break.
Ah.
All right, time for a Limit Break.
I gotta get used to that.
You're playing the game on easy right now?
You have the rings on?
It's okay.
I think they put them on to make it so you can see just how wild some of the combos can get.
Where are the men and women you took from Lostwing?
You mean where's the dominant?
Well, he shall be requiring his services indefinitely.
I don't know who this is, but I'm sure we'll find out.
Come back to me, Sedolphus.
I need you.
Think of all the things we can create together.
The world that we can build.
You need me.
Your king needs me.
I'm all for building a new world.
Just not his.
Oh, the dog is also agreeing.
His dreams are as twisted as his promises are false.
Yeah.
I want no part of him.
We don't want anything to do with you.
He's the one who saved you, and this is how you speak of him.
Have you no shred of loyalty?
To a leader who'd use me like he uses you.
You know nothing of me, Sedolphus.
You're right.
I don't know who you are anymore or what you want.
I only know what you used to say.
That you were tired of running.
That you just wanted to be free.
Free of it all.
Yeah, the demo is over.
This is just like extra little content.
What made you think you had to sacrifice who you were to get what you wanted?
Sacrifice?
I use my talents to my advantage, and you would tell me there is shame in that?
If there's no shame, then why do you feel so sorry for yourself?
Arousing speech, Lord Commander.
I was a fool to believe you might have changed.
The only person I feel sorry for is you.
I can't do this anymore.
If you would stand between our liege and his dream, then you leave me no choice.
Goodbye, Sedolphus.
No, he's getting in.
He's going to stand like a magical electricity.
They all have like superpowers in this game.
It's just wild.
Is it my turn?
I think it's my turn.
Finish them.
Well, Sid.
Okay.
Super move incoming.
I'm going for a limit break right after this.
Jesus.
6,300 damage.
That hurt.
I'm getting combo'd.
Again.
Sickom Torgal.
Those actually aren't...
Those are not easy to hit.
Do not stand in that.
I got...
There's one down.
She doesn't look happy, Torgal.
Come on.
Oh my goodness.
I got hit by that.
This has got to be the end right here.
This time.
All right, die!
You're finished.
Okay.
I had the rings on.
It's fine.
That was still fun.
Level 13.
So that's not that much further.
What are we?
Level six or seven or something?
Crafting.
Is this the full version?
This is not the full version.
This is part of the demo.
When you beat the demo, you can come back and do this little dungeon area.
It's like a little snippet of the game.
Why are you doing this to us?
What, like showing you a fucking cool ass game?
You have to wait a little bit longer?
You can't afford to let them leave.
Remember, she has wings, you don't.
What about you?
Before or after I catch my breath.
I'll be fine.
It's the demo, for God's sake.
I'm not gonna do a main character death in the demo.
What, are you out of your mind?
Come on, Torgal.
It's just the demo.
Can't die in the demo, you know?
We've already seen the main game.
He actually has a death scene right here, but they replaced it.
She must be here somewhere.
Dude, they've killed like 50 people in the demo.
Yeah, that's true.
But were they lore characters?
They kind of were.
So some opponents will cast cure spells to heal their allies.
Defeat these spellcasters first to prevent drawn out battles.
Or I could just smush everybody.
Ooh, okay.
I killed the caster last.
Take the rings off?
It's all right.
When I play this, I'm not gonna play with the rings.
But we're just checking it out.
I didn't play the demo with the rings on.
Wow, beautiful sky.
All right, that's cool though.
You know, that's kind of cool.
There's a feature in the game where if you just want to kind of relax,
chill out, watch the story, and just kill stuff.
That's cool.
You just put the ring on if you want to do that.
There's no pressure to do or not to do it.
Actually, let me do.
Okay.
Is there a food mode?
That?
I don't know if I would call that food mode.
Somebody said,
I don't know if I'm going to spend all the money on the console and the game,
which is hundreds of dollars to just turn on food mode.
Yeah, I mean, if you.
But food mode is available.
I wonder how much longer this is.
I am supposed to be dead.
Wait, where's like the healer?
No, just group them all up.
Oh, don't hurt me.
There's a lot of people in this room.
Oh, I just blew his head up.
You still haven't killed the fucking healer.
Where's the healer?
All right, you.
Sorry about that.
That's a good way to juggle.
What if I charge this?
Oh, no, you still sculpting off and on.
I've been kind of busy lately.
So let it break staggered.
Oh, my God.
These are not charged.
Let's go string it all together now.
Smash out.
This is pretty beefy demo.
Now we're probably a long game.
I think most of the Final Fantasies are pretty long.
There's a lot of content in them usually.
How long was the last one?
I'm like Final Fantasy 15.
Like how if you just did the main campaign and just kind of went through it.
Give or take how many hours you say it would take to do like 70, 50.
Yeah, it's probably pretty similar.
They're like 40 or so.
I don't know if it's 14 is like 80 hours.
Finally, I would see one of the boss fights in the game.
If you don't want to see the boss,
if you don't want to see what this boss looks like when you fight this,
but imagine we're about to fight this boss would clock out.
I confess I expected more from the old man.
Final Fantasy 14 is like 400 hours.
And less from you.
This is the second time you've bested my sisters.
Men of your talents are rare indeed.
400.
Oh, it's an MMO.
All right, yeah, yeah.
If there's a hearth you long for, you will find more than enough warmth under my wings.
You know exactly what I want.
Hand over the dominant and I'll leave you in peace.
You would dare to make demands of me?
Know your place, little lamb.
Fool is a shepherd who eats every bleat of the flock.
And I will suffer yours no longer.
All right, here we go.
Must I spell it out for you, branded?
Let's see.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to see it.
No one is listening.
No one at all.
Little lamb, to the slaughter with you.
Okay, okay.
Come on, quit.
Oh, what does that mean?
Okay.
This is gonna kill her.
This is gonna literally kill her.
In the air.
Oh, shit, that hurt.
Okay, scripted.
Uh-oh, now it's for the real fight.
Wait.
Oh, we're good.
Toggle.
Hey.
Cry all you like.
There's no one to save you now.
Okay.
I'll take a precise dodge any day.
Oh, shit.
Whoa.
Again.
Get down from there.
I gotta charge it up.
Toast the hurt.
You land, I'm gonna limit break, and you're dead.
Right on top of my okay.
Oh, there it is.
Almost 10k.
Bramble fall.
If you failed that quick time event, then you just died.
I love the music changes.
I gotta get over 10,000 right there.
Shit.
Torval is definitely coming back.
Oh, fuck.
I'm all right.
I just legs are broken.
Jesus.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna be like 15,000.
Whoa.
Dude, I'm fucking dodging every single thing.
I don't care if I get the rings on.
This is fun.
You know, that hurt a lot.
This is it.
Right.
Crush her head.
All right.
That's definitely I want to look at anything else.
Based easy mode.
Just for the demo.
It's all right.
We just want to see what was possible.
The answer is simple, Benedicta.
He was fighting for something he believed in.
We've played your games.
Now tell me where he is.
Who are you?
Curious to find out who he's talking about.
The full game comes out on June 22nd.
Uncover the mysteries of Final Fantasy 16, Clive, Sid, and Torval.
Their journey does not end here on the PlayStation 5 home entertainment console.
When it actually is doing that.
Cool.
All right.
I'm down.
All right, guys, that's going to be it.
That was Final Fantasy 16's demo.
It is available right now.
You can go grab it if you want on the PlayStation 5 store.
Thank you Square Enix for sponsoring the segment of the stream.
Had a lot of fun.
Just a little taste before the launch.
It's a good place to start too, I would imagine.
Because honestly, I'm kind of starting with Final Fantasy 16.
It's been a very long time since I've cared about the franchise at all.
Very long time.
The last time I really played a Final Fantasy game, honestly, it has to be back in the Super Nintendo.
And then a little bit maybe.
I want to say like a little of seven.
A little bit.
A little bit of ten.
But not really.
So it's a good place to start.
But yeah, that concludes the stream tonight.
Besides the sponsor, obviously the big news about me joining Offbrand.
I'm really excited, guys.
I just, I truly am.
I know we fuck around a lot on this stream, but I hope I can put some,
I hope I can just put some effort, try to make some good stuff.
Joining what?
Okay, for those of you just joining, I have been appointed as chief creative officer of Offbrand.
Which is Ludwig's company, his media company.
So I'll be working a lot with Ludwig.
And obviously the rest of those guys.
I think we're going to do a lot of really cool stuff.
I hope so.
I'm going to try.
But thanks for watching.
Thanks for sticking around.
There will be way more information on this as I get started, as I keep going.
I know a lot of people were like, holy shit, he's retiring.
The answer is no, I'm not.
I'm still streaming.
I'm still going to be here.
I'm still hanging out.
But I will have other duties that I have to do in between streaming.
So there will be times when I tell you, hey, I got a lot going on with Offbrand.
I'll see you in like a week or two.
Do you know what I mean?
Like it's not, I'm not going anywhere.
And I do that shit anyways.
Like I do it all the time anyways.
Kind of the whole thing's coming together as the big picture of the future of my life, I guess.
But thanks everybody.
It's impossible to be in a position like this without having all of you kind of hold up the earth.
So I really appreciate it.
Anybody, if you've watched this channel for a minute, an hour, 10 years, came to the channel.
If you just came to the channel and you said this guy sucks, fuck this guy, you still here.
So thanks.
Thanks for hanging out, regardless of how you feel.
I did not ever think that I would be looking at announcements like this.
But I'm going to step up.
I'm going to try to.
We'll see what happens.
I'm going to put my effort into it.
So let's go.
The German employed arc.
That's right.
That's true.
Actually employed now.
But yeah, thanks a lot, everybody.
I'll see you guys soon.
Next stream will probably be I want to say maybe like Wednesday or Thursday.
Let's shoot for Wednesday.
I do want to play the zoom beanies.
No, you're not Thursday.
Make it Thursday.
We'll do Thursday and like Saturday this week.
Same time.
Yeah, like four o'clock, four Pacific.
We are definitely going to get sick of the zoom beanies in probably an hour and a half.
So there'll be something else to do too.
The draft tweet.
I'll go over the draft tweet.
When we stream next, tell me to go over the draft tweet.
And then sorceries will be right after that.
Thank you again, Square Enix.
Thanks for watching.
I had a really great time.
Looking forward to playing it.
Have a great night.
He's choking up.
No, I'm just burping.
It's a small difference.
When are you going to do the tuba stream?
I probably said I probably said that at some point.
So burping is choking up.
Yeah.
What about infomercial streams?
Well, the follow up to the off brand stuff obviously is I made this comment a few times
back in January, February, but we're going to be just doing whatever.
I'm not going to have essentially I kind of want to take some of the pressure away.
I got to figure out something to stream every day or every other day, whatever.
And I think it's probably more fun to just like load up infomercials
and just watch for a couple hours and hang out.
Play something like Final Fantasy 16 and not be like, okay, well, I'm not going to do that again.
You're going to see you will see a lot more of that like you already have.
Yeah, I'm not stressing it.
Can we do a Street Fighter 6 training arc stream?
Maybe.
Just do what you want.
Yeah, don't worry.
I'm still in.
Don't take the off brand announcement that I'm out.
You do you.
He hates streaming.
But yeah, will there be less streams over the course of the next however long period?
Yeah, I got to be honest with you.
Probably.
I imagine there probably would be periods where there's a lot going on
and there's a lot of stuff that I'm trying to do that I'm working on.
But I'll come back.
He's not denying it.
Well, it's not going to be zero streams.
I'm just saying that when a project is being worked on,
I'll probably just be back in a couple weeks just like it always is.
It's a big change.
You'll get used to it.
Yeah, I mean, it is a big change.
This is probably the biggest change in my personal life and work life.
For it's been 12 years.
Started doing YouTube.
I just kind of got a following on YouTube and I was like,
oh, wait, I can make money doing this.
That's weird.
That seems like fucking impossible.
And then I just kind of honestly the Twitch moving to Twitch
was probably the other one.
It's going to be a lot to get used to.
I know it will be, but we'll just take it as it comes.
I'm not going anywhere.
See you guys later.
See you on Thursday.
Have a great night.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for sticking around during the sponsor segment.
See you on Thursday.
The future is bright.
I'll see you really soon.
Call your mother.