Uh, Glove Buddies lost that one. We're gonna do... It's so dark in here. Time for blood.
Change the title to Blood, with an exclamation point.
This, this game actually looks really cool. I think I'm gonna be really into this.
I think I very much would be into this game. Make sure that it's not too loud.
Yeah, it's called Blood Fresh Supply. This is a boomer shooter?
Yeah, it actually is, but apparently it's really fucking good. I'm into it.
Blood, this is based. It's really hard. Okay, well, let's fucking go. You don't think I'm ready?
Gameplay setup. All right, full 3D aim. I think this is all fine. Auto crouch, auto aim.
Put that on? Uh, what do I do? No dodge roll? Hey, I'm nine and saw you were playing Glover.
I don't think you're even allowed to be on Twitch, by the way. I'm just out of curiosity.
Okay, I think we're good. New game. The Way of All Flesh. These, okay, these are difficulties, right?
The Way of All Flesh. Even death may die. Farewell to arms. Dead reckoning. Post-mortem. So this is,
like, difficulty. I need to be in the middle. This is how they named shit back in, like,
boomer shooter days. All these are maps. Oh, episodes, okay. The Way of All Flesh.
Here, okay. Still kicking. Think on the inside. Lightly broiled. Well done. Extra crispy. Okay,
here we go. So let's do, uh, what should I do for these? I'm not doing extra crispy, no way.
I'm not doing still kicking and I'm not doing extra crispy. Gotta be somewhere in the middle.
I would get my burgers somewhere in here. Like, lightly broiled. Well, lightly broiled to well
done. I made my choice. Bugleberry. Was it Darth Vader? What?
Game's quiet. Okay, I have a pitchfork. Okay, I have no other weapons. All right, let's go.
I have 82 fucking health already. What happened? Oh, this is one of those, this is one of those
insanely hard boomer shooters. I'm ready. Yo, I'm already fucking dead.
I'm already dead, guys. I'm already dead. What the fuck? Are you supposed to, uh, lightly broiled?
No way. We're going down a difficulty. This is too hard. No, no, no. I don't want to light this yet.
I have 18 health. Open for business. Jesus Christ. These sound effects are fucking crazy.
I can't, I'm, I'm not gonna be able to go in here. What the fuck? How am I supposed to do this?
Oh, you have a gun? No, I don't. It's too dark in here too. Hold on. I don't even have a gun.
Dude, I don't, I don't have a gun. Why did I just go? I'm gray. Why am I so gray? What happened to
my camera? Okay, that's better. All right. So what the fuck? New game? All right. Turn 3D aim on.
Pink on the inside. Try this one. There's a shotgun outside the cemetery. Really?
Okay. Those guys die in one hit now. Not like 10. This looks sick. I'm, I, I'm into this. Jesus.
This is still fucking hard. Oh, skull key. Glover difficulty. Where's the shotgun you guys talking
about? Where is it? I got the flare gun. Yeah. I only have like four shots in it though. Don't waste
the flares. All right. It's in the, it's in the tomb. Oh shit. Okay. It's stuck. It's stuck.
Did I blow it up? You fucking lied. It's stuck. Open for business. You liars. What the fuck? How
do I open it? Press and hold the mouse to throw TNT further. All right. Cool. All right. So where's,
how do I, can I actually get in there or are you guys lying? Is that a chipmunk?
Why is there a chipmunk? Case of TNT. They can't get up here, right? What does that do? Oh,
shortcut. All right. What the fuck? What do I crouch? See a bunch of flares. Eight shots. All
right. F5 is saved. Oh my God. I'm sorry. I just like punched you. F5. Okay. Nice. What the fuck?
What the fuck is happening? What's quick load? What's quick load? F6. F7. Please. I beg you.
3D aim. F0. Full 3D aim look. Okay. Input setup. All right. Configure findings. Use. Next weapon.
Weapon. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Mines. Bombs. Jump boots. Diving suit. Beast vision. Med kit.
Maybe I have med kits. Chat. Chase cam. Okay. F3. Quick load is empty. What are you talking about?
I screenshot. God damn it. Are you kidding me? No, you're not, right? I didn't. I screenshot.
You piece of fucking shit. Let's go. I live again. Screenshot. All right. So it's F2.
You motherfucker. You're so ridiculous. That's so much damage. That's so damaged. That's so
much damage. It's ridiculous how much damage that is. How are you? Open for business.
That's just Rorschach from The Weathermen. No, The Watchmen.
Fuck you. Nice. Okay. I got it. I'm getting it. Local temperature. 85 degrees.
Chance of precipitation. 40%. Fuck. What the fuck? Oh my God. Fuck it. I don't even care. I didn't
kill everything. Get away from me. TNT. Got it. What the? Oh my fucking God. You spawn out of nowhere.
Reload. There's another motherfucker right here. What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about? What are you talking about? Are they still alive? Can I pick this up?
Whoa. What's in here? Got it. Okay. Fire. Can I pick this shit up? Employees must wash hands.
That like is inside of my head when he says things. Can I open any of this?
Doctor's bag. All right. Health is H, right? It's M. Okay. Is it a full heal? H is holster.
Why was he holster in this game? That makes no sense. Oh shit. How do I get that?
Hell, yeah. I got double flares. 77. Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Save it? What's going on? 76? . .
. .
. . .
. . gate. . complement. What's happening? What's happening? What's going on? Why is this doing this?
It's a power up? What am I supposed to use it with? Dude, I don't know.
Got it. Can I go down? Hit the switch to end the level.
We only need a lot more of these. We only need a lot more of these.
Alright, turn the FOV up higher. What are we talking about? Yeah, that's not a thing.
Get the fuck out of here.
There we go, okay. So what's in here?
Your tax dollars at work. Department of Transportation Track Replacement Program.
It's a DOS game remake?
Fresh victims for the ever-growing army of the undead.
Dead.
Oh, there's people in here.
Shotgun.
I'm not using any weapons until I have to, right? There's probably bosses and shit.
I need health.
Quick save Andy, how would you play this game?
How would you play it?
Alternate fire, is it right click?
How much ammo do I have? Nine, that's it.
Quick save Andy.
Shotgun shells.
What happened? I turned?
Okay, I'm alright, I'm fine.
Quick save Andy.
I don't want to waste that, seriously.
Die.
FOV is a display if you scroll down.
Is it actually?
Oh my goodness, you're actually not a liar.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Sounds like Adam Sandler.
What?
Oh my god.
What? How did I miss everybody?
That doesn't make any sense.
What did that school announcement say?
Yeah, I have no idea, man.
Wait, is this person bad?
No, okay.
Let's go.
Alright, let me explore for a minute.
Aim for the head.
That's the idea.
I hate how loud that is.
Nothing else in here, right?
I don't like that.
That was close to the electrical thing.
I think we're good.
Did I get him?
Which phone is ringing?
Rare books and maps.
Did I open up all these?
And we're outside going here?
No, I didn't do this one.
No, okay, we're good.
I need to save ammo.
How much of these do I have?
I have 12 of these.
I can start using them.
No, no, no, no, no, I refuse.
This is cheating.
This is not cheating.
Come on.
Eel with H?
H is a holster, right?
Where?
Jesus.
Oh my God.
I want to reload.
You got the key, man?
Where's the key?
Alright, open that back up.
I can't open it again?
Why won't this open?
What's going on?
How come I can't open it?
I pressed the button.
Okay, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
So I still need a key.
What if I get a key to go up here?
Press M?
Holy shit.
That was very weird.
Okay, so what?
That one reloads so bad.
You have no idea.
It was pretty interesting.
They just need farting and it'd be perfect.
Oh, I thought it was going to be a new melee weapon.
I like my hands, bloody.
Leftovers.
Nothing in here?
Whoa.
What does that do?
What's going on?
Wait, let me out of here.
What's up?
Is that opening a door?
What's that doing?
Don't tell me to do that if it's not going to do anything.
Leftovers.
That's me saying that?
I have the same dialogue?
No, it burns, it burns.
Okay, I've got shotgun shells and more TNT.
I have fucking 21 of these.
So what is this doing?
I press this button and it...
Ooh, what'd I get?
What'd I get?
Limited invisibility.
Okay, what do I do?
What do I go with this?
I don't know what to do.
Oh my God, I did it.
I think that guy was hard.
Why is that on the screen?
Okay, I got the key and now I can go back in that room.
That just got intense.
That was fucking terrifying.
172 health, holy crap.
Should I go down here?
No, this is just right outside.
This game still holds up?
I'm very much enjoying this.
It's quiet.
Where was the way to go to get out?
Over here and then up this way, right?
The bookstore or something?
It was like up here.
Where was it?
I don't remember where to go.
I think it's over here.
Yeah, it's right here.
Oh!
Got it.
Unironically, I picked this up a few years back and it was super enjoyable.
Definitely more than a lot of the other classic ones.
Yeah, this is fun.
Is this Glover?
I mean, no.
Does it have to be?
Okay, it's nothing connected here.
Do you know why I like this?
Because it reminds me of Dusk.
We just played the other Dusk dev game and I'm playing Dusk again.
God, what a fucking fun game.
That game was so fucking good.
It's so good.
I just wish I could delete my memory and play it again.
Oh my goodness.
I feel like I'm watching a stream with TTS on.
Okay, so I'm on the train.
I have so much ammo.
I need a key.
All right, I need a key.
So let's back here.
Oh my God.
Who's laughing?
Get off my train.
That was Bart Simpson.
That was a Bart Simpson.
It was absolutely Bart Simpson.
Is he dead?
So much TNT.
It's insane.
I need a key.
So many locked doors.
Oh fuck.
Who turned the lights off?
He's still alive.
Is that a chest?
Beast Vision?
What's that do?
Why are you good at this?
I'm telling you right now.
You give me three buttons and I'll be proud.
That's all folks.
All right.
I'm just going to use the shotgun.
What is Beast Vision?
Life Seed?
That doesn't count.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Do it again, do it again, do it again, do it again.
I'm just going to go shoot.
I don't know.
I thought maybe there's like a ledge or something I could jump.
Why would this be here?
What happened?
Something out there?
Why would I be able to do this?
Why can I open up all these?
I don't get it.
What's that for?
Is there a double jump?
Secret windows?
Dude, I'm not even using it.
You're overthinking it?
Do a TNT jump.
Wait, no.
I'm going the wrong way.
What's that?
Super armor.
Holy shit.
Okay, cool.
Fuck you.
This is the end of the train.
Did I get a key?
I don't think I got a key.
Oh, I did get a skull key.
All right.
No.
What the fuck?
So much shotgun ammo.
Oh, it's a toilet.
Okay.
I've got a hundred ammo here.
Did I get them all?
Oh, this shit's locked.
Right, okay.
These are all locked doors.
How did I kill the one in the room?
What?
Right click on the zombies.
Auto aim might be on.
You're playing on easy?
Oh, look at how good I am at this game.
It's shot quiet.
No, I ain't going to hear that.
I ain't going to hear that.
All right.
Where was I going?
Okay, down.
And then I can go this way.
Blastovers.
Am I doing anything in here?
Cheater exposed.
I'm not cheating.
What?
You can play like this?
Oh, he's got auto aim on, doesn't he?
He's got auto aim.
That's why he's doing all this.
I keep trying to reload and I don't need to do that.
Did I do it?
Oh shit, I did it.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God, what's happening?
What?
Please use your med kits, press M.
I got 113 health, I don't even use a med kit.
I must stop this train.
Can I stop it?
Internal engine heat is critical.
I'm on the train.
Aren't I on the train?
Oh, I did it, okay.
What happened to Glover?
Well, the Glove buddies couldn't keep it afloat, unfortunately.
What's over here?
Can I like power through this?
What is this?
That it?
That's scary, that sound.
I think there's nothing else I can do here.
How do I get out of here?
That was a Glover reference.
Step right up.
This promises to be fun.
Did I get it?
Yep, okay.
Get the fuck out of here.
Oh my God.
That was way too much.
Got it, okay.
I'm not going in there yet.
There's a secret in the water.
What the fuck?
I'm drowning.
What's even down here?
Oh my goodness.
There's nobody for me to even shoot at.
Let's go.
I hate mimes.
All right, there's games I can play.
Okay, how about this?
This is like a ball game?
Why is it shooting it out?
Fuck you game.
There's another one, where is it?
What's this one?
I want that.
How am I supposed to shoot with the shotgun?
What am I supposed to shoot them with?
This is better than cruel aid.
Does he talk?
Jojo the idiot circus boy.
Jumping boots?
Can't go in there.
And they had rat dogs.
Who's shooting?
Can I eat these?
I don't think so.
Okay, so I have to shoot it with a shotgun?
I want it.
No one wants to play with me.
This microphone is fucking freaking me out.
All right, so I did that.
What's this one?
Okay, throw a grenade.
I threw two grenades in here, dude.
Did he already say eat my shorts?
Picked up a few bullets.
All right, nice.
Old drum of bullets.
All right, let's do Jojo the idiot circus boy.
Really?
This doesn't open from this side, okay.
Shit.
Keep out.
Reflective shots?
Got it.
Test your strength.
Who is talking by the way?
I guess I can go this way, right?
Is it going to kill me?
Wait, what?
What am I seeing?
I need a key.
Jumping boots?
Oh right, J for jumping boots?
Okay, so hold on.
Where is it going to get me to though?
Did I turn them off?
Did they have like a, okay.
Now where do I go?
Where's the key?
I missed an area?
I turned it off, yeah.
This is locked.
I could go up here.
I don't have a key yet though.
I don't know where I'm supposed to go because I've been up there already.
I need a key.
This is locked.
I don't know.
By the water, the ticket booth?
I missed an area?
Where?
What are you talking about?
That's the key?
Oh my goodness.
Okay, but how do I get in here?
Can I jump?
Underneath maybe?
Not underneath?
What do I do?
It looks like right there.
Should I try the jumping boots?
TNT?
Oh fuck off.
I need a key.
I can't get in here.
The wall behind the mime.
Behind the mime?
That didn't work.
I don't know.
What about the freak area?
Was there a freak area somewhere here?
I didn't even see this part.
Oh my god, open the door!
What the fuck was that?
This is terrifying.
Fucking Glover.
That didn't get me anything though, did it?
Can I blow up one of these walls?
Oh my goodness, dude.
What?
I don't know what to do right now.
I want Jojo.
Where is it?
No!
Start with the flashing.
What?
I got a key.
Is it fall damage?
Jump and find out.
I got the key.
I can get out of here now.
I need a key.
Locked.
What are you talking about?
I used the key?
You got the dagger key.
Sounds like Resident Evil.
I get it.
I have the eye.
Is it a new weapon?
Yep.
Don't use this.
That doesn't work.
Right click.
I can do the double shot.
Maybe I should make it harder.
I'm getting too strong.
Where do I go from here?
I think that's it.
Inside the train?
There's a door in here.
Where?
I got pranked.
Inside the train?
In here?
I think you guys are lying.
Eye door?
There's a window in the train.
You guys are making stuff.
You're making it up.
Now we're going to go to the eye door.
Where was that door?
I don't remember.
I think it was further out.
Like this way.
That's the dagger.
Where was that?
Down that hallway?
Moon key?
I'm not down in here.
That 80's scary sound effect.
It's so horrible.
It's actually terrifying.
Where is it?
I'm going in the water I guess.
Oh shit.
Oh my.
Really?
I don't even need to kill this thing.
Just go.
I'm going to drown down here if I don't hurry up and get out of here.
My nose is so itchy.
I got it.
60 out of 73.
6 out of 12.
Key.
I can go lower.
This dude is literally evil.
I'm going to get up.
I need a key.
I can't open that?
Oh my god.
Open?
How do I get up there?
Alright skull key.
Oh my god.
Alright.
I need a key.
It's here in my mouth.
We're good.
Moon key.
Where is that moon door?
Ah.
Moon key.
You idiot.
Why is the music off?
It's not off.
CD music.
I don't have CD music.
Don't use CD music.
What are you talking about?
I'm trying to get it to work.
Is this supposed to be like a...
Am I missing like the...
Am I missing that?
Alright don't go anywhere yet.
Hold on.
Die.
This level doesn't play any music.
Oh what the fuck dude?
Okay I'm good.
Oh my goodness.
Ow.
Alright I'm looking for a door right?
What am I looking for?
I'm looking for like the moon door or something.
What door am I looking for?
I don't know where that guy came from.
No I already got this one.
It's something else.
Spider door?
I want to go through here.
Oh I got to activate that thing don't I?
Hold on.
This?
No.
Spider door?
I don't remember where the spider door is.
Does it show up on the map?
That's awful.
I just say that like...
Oh my god.
I fucking god damn it.
How far back was I?
I don't remember where this is.
It's right here.
I'm fine.
I forget where I just was.
Shit.
I don't...
I forget where that is.
I fucking freaked out too.
I don't remember where that is.
This way...
I don't remember.
Okay.
I think it's...
Yep.
TF2 sound effects?
New gun.
Ooh napalm.
That was loud.
I just spit all over my mouth.
Go to the spider door?
Hold on.
I got some shit going on here.
What did that do?
Oh my goodness.
Gas can?
You'll know what to do when the time comes.
Whoa!
Okay.
Waste of fucking...
Where do I go?
Use the spider door?
I don't remember where the spider door is guys.
Is the spider door on the map?
Where's the spider door?
Use beast vision?
Use the spider door on the map.
Moon door again?
Gotta go through the CD door.
Spider door is in the spider room.
As I was saying, go to the moon door.
Okay.
And then...
Use the among us vision?
Two portals lead to certain death.
Choose wisely.
Oh fog.
Okay.
Teeth door?
Regular door or like mud door.
Teeth door.
Did I get it?
I did it.
This is a secret if you drop down.
Okay.
Ban that guy for 10 minutes.
What's in the other doors?
I'm curious.
Whoa!
Wrong door.
What about this one?
Only one secret?
That's it?
I'm almost out of ammo.
This is bad.
I gotta start using the flares.
I have 75 fucking flares.
I could probably jump that.
Let's see what's down here.
Let me try.
Let me jump that.
Oh fuck.
Whatever.
I can jump this.
Oh my god!
Dude!
Thank you.
Don't kill me here.
Oh you motherfucker.
I swear to god.
Isn't there full nudity in this game?
Is there?
I don't think...
I don't know.
A secret is revealed, huh?
Already got it, didn't I?
None of these blow up.
You lost 4k viewers because you stopped playing Glover.
Oh well.
Oh!
And where the fuck did they come from?
Glover.
I miss Glover.
I'm not getting hit by that.
Ground, please.
I only have two bullets left.
Whatever.
Can we go back to Glover?
No.
Let me finish this.
Where do I go?
Blood is better?
I'm just playing a game, man.
How do I get out of here?
Little old fashioned Glover pull?
No.
I'm not doing a Glover pull.
Do you have your chance?
Backwards here?
I don't know where to go.
It's on the other side.
Oh shit.
Hold on.
Fuck you.
Come on.
Really?
I'm out of juice.
Where do I go?
Glover across the bridge?
Oh my goodness.
Ooh.
Go back to Glover?
No.
You guys had a chance.
You guys had your chance.
You threw Glover away because you didn't want to see...
Not you guys.
Oh gracious.
Who voted for blood?
I did.
I voted for it.
Oh, dad's playing his boomer shooters.
Glover, boomer, blood, boomer.
Is that Dr. Andy?
How am I a doctor?
Oh, there he is.
Dr. Andy.
I need a key.
Shit.
Come on.
I'm out of ammo.
I've been streaming for four hours.
Holy shit.
Oops.
Why is that an oops?
Oh my God.
Four hours.
Oops.
Paging Dr. Andy.
Is Dr. Andy in the building, please?
We've got a handful of zoomers that don't want to see this old shit.
And by handful, I mean like 15,000.
Oh, don't.
I'm so fucking far away.
I'm about to delete it.
Blow up already.
Blood rocks?
No, I'm having fun.
This game is good.
It's fun just to shoot stuff.
With my mouth open.
These same fucking people behind me.
Fuck.
Blood buddies?
No, don't even start this shit.
Who are the blood buddies?
Get the fuck.
Boring buddies?
The boring buddies.
I knew you were right there too, you piece of shit.
This room sucks.
Should I go in there?
Oh, that's nothing.
What did I get?
I can't go in there.
Looks like I can go in there, but I can't.
Play strawberry magic?
Alright, blood buddies, strawberry buds, TF2, titanium, IQ, brain, friends.
Whatever you want to call it.
Whatever.
I don't know.
Did I get a key?
I don't even remember.
Drew, crew, banana bros.
I need a key.
How many factions do we have here?
How come Glover doesn't need keys, you know?
What do you want to do after this?
I'm open to suggestions.
Not Glover.
We're not going back to that.
Everyone will leave.
I'm not playing Among Us.
Thriving?
Whoa.
Theme, NG, drive?
Go back to Wobble Dogs?
We'll see.
I need some blood buddies to tell me where to go here, because I'm kind of lost.
I need a key.
I don't know.
Am I left?
Finish Thrillville.
No.
You should go to the shut the fuck up room.
Go into the fire.
I can't walk in.
I can't.
Unless there's something I'm doing wrong.
Anybody know what to do?
Go up the stairs.
There's a new open passage away.
One of these?
Oh, dude, you were right.
You got it.
Fucking open.
Nice.
Oh.
Stop throwing it so far.
Got it.
Shit.
No, don't die, please.
All right.
Go back up that way.
You're getting drop-shooted.
How do I get up there without the jump?
I wasted all my jump fluid.
I got to go back to the door.
How many more levels do I have of this campaign?
Save the game.
I did.
I'm almost at the end.
Yeah.
Let me complete this.
Right?
I just want to be at one level in blood.
Come on.
I need to be at one level in blood.
Oh, fuck.
Mom.
Just one more level.
I mean, if I'm almost done.
Come on.
Right?
I can't just give up and just leave before completing one campaign.
I need a key.
Just one level.
Yeah.
Just one more.
I just want to play one level.
Ooh.
I got the fire key.
You're on five out of seven, and seven is really short.
Yeah.
Let me down.
I'm just...
What's going on here?
Oh, my God.
Lord.
Seven is really short.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Son of a bitch wants pain.
Get in.
What's happening here?
JermaWalk, WobbleDogs, JermaWalk.
Hold on.
I'm playing this.
I don't even know what the fuck just happened.
Oh, my God.
Everybody quiet.
You can't even be fucking si...
Oh.
I missed so many of those.
That was so bad.
I didn't even run out of bullets.
Auto-aim.
No, it's not.
I'm fine.
Spider key.
Let's go.
What the fuck is happening?
I don't care about that.
I just want to get out.
Let's go.
You have a doctor bag?
Moon key.
I am tearing it up right now.
I'm being honest with you.
Is this preparing me for something?
Let's go.
I have the...
I'm not ready.
I'm ready.
I have a maximum amount, can I do double handed?
Oops.
What does that do?
Where am I?
No, get out of here.
Shit!
Dude, you kicking butt right now, dude.
I can't even.
Wobble Warriors!
Oh, Wobble Warriors!
All right, this is it, guys, we're ready to go.
Check this out, we're at the fucking final level.
Six out of seven.
All right, well, whatever, it's probably not that long.
I'm fine.
Hell yeah, look at this.
Wobble Warriors.
Wobble Warriors, you're gonna have to wait
until next weekend.
No.
Let me beat this first thing.
Ophelia.
No!
Show yourself.
Show yourself!
Oh no, it's Satan!
God damn it.
Goodbye.
Sleep, Ophelia.
I'm so getting it off me.
Oh no!
I thought, he said there was another one.
Why am I burning this lady?
He's shooting, he's shooting in the head?
I feel like that was kind of like made as like a machinima.
I got it.
I beat it.
All right, that was fun.
So what are we gonna do next?
This is just like, we're just doing whatever.
I can't believe you made me watch this.
That was fun, what are you talking about?
That was actually fun.
I very much enjoyed that.
I mean, I played, I didn't play on hard mode.
I played on like decent mode, which is fine.
That's cool.
Yeah, that was fun, what was it all about?
That holds up really well considering it came out on DOS.
This is a DOS game.
That's a DOS game.
I'm gonna go pee, I'll be right back.
And then we'll do something else for like an hour or so.
Something we can just play, just hang out.
I'll be right back, let's figure it out.
Put a poll in chat when I get back, I'll be right back.
Sorry about that, I just probably scared the shit out of you.
It was like, dude.
Oh God, I know what we're doing when I get back.
Are you kidding me?
I know exactly what I'm doing.
I don't even have to question this.
I'm playing the vampire survivors update without a doubt.
Yeah, I'll be right back.