I changed Twitch servers. Let's see if that does anything.
So the stream did turn off. Let's see if it continues to work.
Went to a different server. Dude, two streams in one day? What the fuck? Are you serious?
That seems barely stable. Let's hope it stays that way.
I think, I think it's okay. Let's continue. I'll give it a minute or two for people to realize
that we're live again. Remember, just got the notification you went live. Can't wait for
another eight hours of Chibi-Robo. All right. What happened? I just got back. The server I was
connected to was kind of fucked up, I guess. I'm just gonna let it ride out for a minute.
Did you play off stream? A little. Just a little. Just a little bit. Can we get a free
wink for our troubles? Sure, why not? Where's the camera? There it is. I think we're good. I
think this is solid. Stream might not even turn off. F.A. lap. No drop frames? All right, let's go.
Where's that tuber light? Oh, all right. It's a waterfall training?
Yes, I want to do waterfall training. Of course I do. This will make your mind sharper than a
dagger and your body harder than steel. Listen up, I do not want to repeat myself.
March straight down this way, soldier. You'll eventually reach the waterfall.
Look at that guy up there having so much fun. When you get there, you'll have to climb to the
top and meet up with Private Prisco. So just run over there. Let's go. Dude, you peeked the mic.
Easy. No, wrong item. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Climb waterfall. No,
you idiot. It's okay. Go like this. Put this shit away. Up. All right. Put it back up. Wait,
are they firing at me? Can I climb the vine? Climb the vine. You can't climb vines? I can't
climb the vine. Now what? Hello? What the fuck does he want me to do now? What the fuck is going on?
That wasn't him? I'm out of battery. I'm dead. Oh my God. I blame the fucking internet on this
bullshit. If I wasn't paying attention to the goddamn internet going down, this wouldn't have
happened. I just used my battery. I'll be on fiber like within the next 30 days. I can't fucking
wait. So this shit is impossible to have it happen again. Ever. Pain in the ass.
Five. I'm going on fiber. I just wasted that fucking battery. I'm going back to the save.
Right? I didn't even need to use that battery. I got saved by the bell. Where was that last save?
Did I not save after the no saves coming? It was before the jungle art. Really? God damn it. Really?
Imagine saves coming in chibi robo. Get me on that fucking fiber line.
I never have to think about this shit literally ever again for the rest of my life.
How much for a wink on fiber? Five dollars, man. Exactly five dollars. He thinks fiber is
different. Well, when you have a thousand, a thousand, there's a lot of leeway for you to not
have to drop frames streaming at six up. If there's a thousand up, there's a lot more room. I'm gonna
save it. Stop throwing shit at me. Who's doing this? All right. I'm going back there and I'm doing
this. I want to do it. It's television. It might be. Was there a wink? I didn't see one. Oh, there
was a bunch of money. Sorry. It happened during the internet bullshit. Five thousand bits came in.
I missed it. Thank you for the fifty dollars. And it was from Sukhoi Flanker. Thank you, Flanker.
Hello, Jeremy. Remember when you played stalker two years ago? You gotta finish that. It's too
good of a game to just forget. Oh, like stalkers. I think it's been too long.
I can't like go back to my save from two years ago and be like, all right, let's go.
That's that game's hard and unforgiving. I would have to redo the whole thing over again. I'd have
to start it over, which I mean, that's fine. He hates good game. He's gonna do it again. He's gonna
scream. What? Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. I was trying to be cute. I was trying
to be cute. I was trying to be cute. I was trying to be cute. I was trying to be cute. I was trying
to be cute. I should have just jumped up. I was trying to be cute. I was trying to be cute. I was
trying to be cute. I was trying to be cute. I was trying to be cute. No more cuteness. Let's go.
Chichiburobo is not cute. He's cute, but he's not now. Let's go. Do an impression of Sarge egg. I did
one yesterday. I can't do another one right now. It would take like 10% of my soul to do it.
You delete like a year off your life when you do a Sarge impression. It's like smoking eight
packs of cigarettes. That's the toll it takes. All right, don't shoot me. Watch out. Behind the
waterfall. Climb it. Made it. Wow. I almost just fell off. Talk to him. Talk to him. Yeah.
Frog ring behind the waterfall. Thank you for your keen eyesight. All right. Got points. That's done.
That only took like 28 minutes to just do that one thing because of all the bullshit. All right,
now we can move on. We're going to do the thing we came here to do. Talk to him again. More training
to do. Look at the ring. Can I even get up there without their help? I've never been up there before.
What do you say? More huge bits from Sukhoi again. Flanker. A hundred dollars total.
Ten thousand. That's right. Ten zero zero zero. A hundred bucks total from Flanker. Flanker 35.
This dude just paid me a hundred dollars to play Stalker. Hold on. Let me read the message.
It might not even say that. They say you were at Dark Valley but you need to complete Stalker and
if you do not, I will continue bugging you about it till the end of time because I need more Stalker
content to watch and I love you and especially your Stalker Let's Play. All right. I have no
plans to play Stalker. A Stalker dono. No, no. All right. I have no plans to play Stalker.
Right now. I'm playing Mario Sunshine next week. That's gonna take like four days.
Play Stalker tomorrow. I'm not gonna play Stalker tomorrow. I was so bad at Stalker. I had no
patience. I wasn't very good at it. That's not my game. You want me to play a game that it was
embarrassing when I was playing it? And yes, I know I just failed Climb the Vine and Chibi-Robo
four times, but there's a difference. It's a big difference. I want to go to the I want to do the
the bridge in the kitchen. Stalker after Mario Sunshine. No, I have I have I have no idea.
The last time I played Stalker was it had to have been at least two years ago.
So you're saying that there is a chance. Well, I'd say more like one in a million. Dumb and dumber.
All right, let's go. That's a classic line. What what's his name? Dermal only eats beyond burgers.
What the hell is your username? All right, let me get over here. What is that name?
Dermal only eats beyond burgers. Why? Why do you even have that name? That name is fucking crazy.
Sponsored content. Yeah, for him. Not for me. That's a lot of money. All right. Now,
what do I want to put the bridge over this way? Look it up there. Oh, I want to clean the grill.
Yep. Okay. Wait, I want to clean the grill. I'm going down. The fan of the grill. We plug in.
There's so much junk up in that fan. So much crap up in this man. I can't wait.
Let's get another 5000 bits. Holy shit. From Flanker again. Flanker. This is 150 dollars.
More than that. 200? Total? No, 150 dollars and bits. My god. You're a madman.
Derma, you were doing really good for the point at which you were at the game. I want to see
stalker. I am a stalker fanatic and I will not rest until you finish your stalker let's play.
I have nothing to say except that you were doing much better than most other players. Are you
serious? Wait, is this bait for me to do this? This is that's bait. That's for me to go like,
holy shit, I was doing better. And that's like a hard game. I'm doing better than players. I could
do that. Nice strategy. Where's all the junk? Where's all the crap? I want to clean this.
Why is this clean? I'm pissed off that this is clean. I came up here specifically to just get...
Why is this clean? I said this last night. I'll say it again. I never rule out ever playing a
video game. I don't have any plans for it. Who knows? You might see stalker appear on this channel.
Maybe. I refuse to say I will never play a single video game except for League of Legends. I will
never do that ever. Literally never. Not one time on this stream. Or Dota. That will never happen.
Not once. But I will never say that I won't play a game on this stream. I can't climb this. So,
I don't know. I don't have a... It's not like, oh yeah, that game was terrible. I'm never playing
it. I just kind of get distracted by other things. New games. Something else happens. So,
you play something else. You get into something else. You forget about it. You lose track. You
stop playing it. Who knows? We might come back to it. I don't know. What about Doki Doki Literature
Club? No, never. No, it's just not gonna happen. I just know it's not. You know what I mean? I know
it's not gonna happen. Now, what else can I do with this? It can't be just to get across to there,
right? There's got to be something else I can do with this. Oh, this is not even the bridge, Jeremy.
This is not even the bridge. How much higher can I get this? All the way up. On top of the fridge.
On top of the cabinets. Look at that. There's a demon door over there. Oh, yes. Come on. Keep
going. I can shoot that. I can shoot that thing. Flanker gave more money. Now, that's another
5,000 bits. That's $200 from Flanker. I don't want you to play Doki Doki Literature Club. I want you
to finish Stalker. I know, but I don't... I just say yes. I can't. I don't want anybody to think
I'm gonna play Stalker in like four days. I gotta be realistic with you guys. I need to move this
forward. You already took the money. I didn't say... Hey, I... Hey, all right. Hold on. I'm gonna...
Defense mode. Shield going up. I never once said, please pay me hundreds of dollars and I'll turn
on Stalker. That was not part of a conversation. You don't negotiate.
He's face down in defense mode. I think Coolsville sucked. No, but I can't say yes. I don't know.
It's not gonna happen. I've gotta be real. It's not gonna happen anytime soon. Okay, that's it.
Could this happen in the future? I don't know. But will it happen now? No, it will not. It will not.
It will not. It's not gonna happen anytime soon. It will not. I just need to be clear.
I think I got a secret fucking entrance. Jerma Grinn. No, I also don't want to set the precedence
of somebody paying a bunch of money and telling me that I'm gonna play something and then I go,
you sure? You bet you. I don't want people to think they need to or will spend like a bunch
of money to make me play something on stream. If you got recommendations,
ruin the recommendation channel. I can't... I can't set the precedence of like, all right, hey,
let's do stalker tomorrow. Let's go, baby. It only costs $200 to make me play something.
There's a bandage over here. Who's hurt? Lobbyists. Video game lobbyists. Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, you know what I mean, though. Can I push this? I was told to come here for a stalker stream.
Jerma, the stalker... I'm not gonna read that out loud. But seriously, thanks for the ridiculous
amount of money. You've given so much money, too much money. Okay, there's another one over there.
All right, I gotta get back up there. All right, back up to what I did and I'm gonna go to get the
other demon door. No, I'm not playing stalker on March 13th. No, stop saying that. Looking
forward to Lisa the Painful on the 20th. None of this is happening. You're gonna be very, very upset
to Lisa the 20th. Okay, first of all, you know how that's bullshit? I'll tell you how you know
that's bullshit. You think I'd plan out what game I'm playing that far in advance? That's what? No,
I figured out what I'm gonna play like two days ago. Like, I know what I'm gonna play tomorrow today.
I need 197 more. You told us you had 30 streams planned out. Well, no, I have 30 streams worth of
GameCube Wii, Xbox 360, and PC games back here. I don't know what order they're gonna be in. I
just know they're gonna happen. No, stop tagging that account. Stop tagging. All right, all right.
I'm getting involved. I'm getting involved. I'm getting involved. I'm involved. I'm getting
involved. I just sub only. I'm getting involved. Subs are doing it too. How could you do this?
You're supposed to support me. You're supposed to support me in everything. All right, let's go.
I'm getting involved. All right, we're gonna go back to the kitchen. I'm going up to the top.
Wallace and Gromit GameCube stream with too, too many fake fans.
You guys are fucking crazy. All right, I'm going back up because I want to get the other demon
door. Hey, why is the dog standing? Oh, it's a cleaning game first. Remember emote only,
sub only, emote only, 10 minute slow mode. I am in control. I am in control. Hey, get down.
Get down from there. What's wrong? Oh my God. I am in control. I'm in control.
People are getting thrown into a river around me. I'm in control. I'm in control.
All right, now take off emote only, take off sub only. Let's hear what the people have to say now.
Remember, remember who has the power here. Who pays the bills? Who pays the bills? Who pays the
bills? Who pays the bills? I do. I'm a waiter. Who pays the bills? I do. I'm a waiter. I've been a
waiter for 15 years and holy shit, you should see my tips. 30% on every check. I'm a, I'm a people
person. I know how to talk to people. Oh, it's dad or me. What are you going to show us your tips?
Maybe one day. Help me chibi robo. Oh my God. No, this is a $300 video game request.
It's gone. It's, it's, it's over that, it's over that portion. Another hundred bucks to get me to
play stalker. I already know what the message is. Can't flanker insane, insane money, insane amount
of money. This is completely, you don't need to do this. Unnecessary. Don't worry. Unnecessary.
Thank you though. Um, I don't want to set a precedent either, right? You can finish
Super Mario first. I just want to see stalker finished. No, no, no, no. He's setting terms.
There are no terms. There are no terms. I've been watching you since TF2 and I have to say
your playthrough up to that point was the most entertaining until it abruptly ended.
All right. I, hold on. I got a question. This is okay. Hold on. This is a very, very important
question. Where, where have you been for two and a half years? I'm, why now? It's been a long time.
I like completely forgot about that game. That's why this is so, so, so hard for me.
He was waiting for the perfect moment. So about this stalker stream, I've already made my point.
I've already made my case. You don't have to give any more money. In fact, you do not give
any more money based on a stalker stream. I'm telling you, I really appreciate the huge fucking
money. I really do. Thank you. It's ridiculous. It's a ridiculous amount of money. If anybody,
for any reason, I've taken your point, taken the feedback and I missed a wink. No, I didn't
pay him to play Sam and Max instead. Jenny said she's hungry, but I'm hungrier than she is. What
the fuck are you, dad? You get it? Come on, help me make some hamburgers. This is the cooking part
of the stream. Of course I will. Oh, sweet. A zillion things. Every time I hit the kitchen,
I end up burning everything. Let's grill some burgers. Okay. How do you cook burgers? Prep work?
Do I have to help you set those buns on the plates? Why are you putting the bun on the grill?
They didn't even get toasted yet. Chibi-Robo, it's on the plate. Yeah, I know. You gotta leave it on
there for at least a few minutes. Is the grill, is the stove even on, dad? Dad, why can't you just
put these on? Way to go, Chibi-Robo. There's no way I could. Next, we grill the meat. Okay. I'm gonna
get my fucking secret sauce on there. Get your spoon out. Use your spoon to flip the patty.
All right. Why is there only one painted on here? You have to label the burgers?
One, two. Is it five? Cook until both sides are brown. They'll burn if you grill them too long.
What, why are these two and, look for the three? All right, that one's done. Three and three?
All right, three. Pick it up. Flip this fuck. Three. All right, this is, wait, this is three.
Come on. Here's a three. Is it both three? Three, two, fuck. Oh, fuck, I gotta get this over here.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Don't burn, don't burn, don't burn, don't burn, don't burn, burn, burn,
burn. I wonder if beef tastes good. I mean, it does. All right, is this three? Put it back down.
Is it three? It is. Oh my god, another hundred bucks just came in. Hold on a second.
Hold on a second. Flanker again. How much money is this? This is like $400 from, hey, hey, hey.
They say no prob, this is a hundred bucks by the way. No problem, Jerma. I just love your videos
and I'm unfortunately broke right now. Give this channel money if you don't have any disposable,
super disposable income. I gotta make that real clear. Don't make yourself broke.
All right, here's the tier of where and when we should give this stream money.
Okay, tier one. It's tier one. So, okay, all bills are paid. You've eaten three times today.
You've got all the food, all your groceries paid, your rents paid, okay. You went to the
arcade and blew $50 with your friends. Okay, good. Under that. Underneath that. Did you pay
for Netflix this month? Okay, underneath that. I'll sit somewhere under there. Do not give this
stream any fucking money. And I mean zero. Zero. If it's not something that you can absolutely
afford. For the love of god, please. That's reverse psychology. I have to be clear on this.
I don't want people to like make themselves broke because they're throwing fucking hundreds
of dollars at the channel. You know what I'm saying? I don't, I don't, that doesn't sit well
with me. Anyway, thank you for the huge money. Please take care of yourself first. Don't take
care of me until you take care of yourself a thousand times first. It's a psychological
mind game. No, it's a, it's just a reality game. Honey, Jenny, dinner. There's nothing on these.
Oh, we didn't put the lettuce on. And you banned people from donating. I don't, I don't think so.
I don't think you can. And his mom doesn't want any. Why?
It's more fun to eat together. Can I go deliver one? The dog gets a burger. I guess we'll give
her portion to tell. The dog gets a full cheeseburger. Oh, I forgot chibi robo. And oh,
we can't eat. We don't eat with robots. Oh, that's right. I forgot. Let's eat one bite.
Wait, wait a minute. It's raw. Oh yeah. You got the cooking sticker. Oh, nice.
You really are amazing. Chibi robo. 20 happy points. 20 happy points. Yeah. How gave you,
oh, the dog gave me happy points too. Nice. I think I did everything in the kitchen.
Wait, no, the dog, the dog, the dog. Did I get all the things I wanted to get?
Got that. Did the cooking thing. I did. How many doors are there in here? There's three more. All
right. I'm going to do the beep beep boop boop thing. Hold on. The crumbs there. Now I'll clean
the grill. I always just want me to go. There's something apparently up there. I don't think I can
get up there. Can I? Maybe. Let's find out. Can I get up there? I was up with the, oh yeah,
I was up there earlier. I don't have the thing. Hey, Jerma, I'm doing huge out of the money
options trading to sub to you. That's risky. Very risky. Huge out of the money options trading.
I'm going to plug in first. High risk reward. High risk reward. Don't, okay. Don't listen to me
when I do my joke streams about stock trading. Don't be like me. More money. How much? $50,
5,000 bits from ice likes rice. 50 bucks they say here from my SPY puts. What the
fuck is going on? Look mom. Look what Jerma taught me about stocks. I didn't teach anything.
I told you that I got fucking messed up from beyond burgers. I fucked it up big time. Don't
listen to me. All right. Was that radar? But thanks for the $50. Thanks for the $400 fucking
dolls flanker. Thanks everybody. Thank you. Don't trade options unless you know what the
fuck you're doing. And I mean it. You need to know what the fuck you're doing. Don't just,
oh, you know what? I think, I think Tesla is going to go down. I'm going to put a bunch of
fucking puts on it. Oh, my money's gone in, in less than three days. Oh, well, I learned a few things.
All right. What's up here? What should I invest my life savings into? I'm not going to save damn
thing. What is this? Big? Shoot it? The fuck is this? Secret door? Oh, I know what's in my
portfolio. Any more secrets? No, nothing else in here. I got all the, there's two more doors that
I didn't get. What do you have in your portfolio? What wouldn't you like to know? I'll tell you.
In my portfolio. Listen to me. McDonald's. I think that shit's going away anytime soon.
McDonald's. That's pretty much it. 98% of my portfolio is in McDonald's Limited Group.
And then 2% into water stocks. Can I do this? I can. I just went right through it. Invest in
water. Can I not do this then? It don't work. Guys, it don't work. It don't work. All right,
I'm out. Let's go to the next section. What do I want to do? What do I want to do? Climb up the jars.
But I can climb the jars? The stream is now out of sync. It shouldn't be. I gotta charge. I can't
fuck around here. I gotta get up. It is. Okay. I can't climb up on these jars. What a lie.
Okay, I gotta go. What do you mean it's out of sync? The game's out of sync?
Video is slightly delayed after the audio. How's that sound? Better?
It seems fine to me. Okay. All right. Now. Oh, dog. Right. I want to see what's wrong with dog.
Sing for us or else. What do you want? What do you want? What do you want? Dog, what do you want
from here? I can't do anything about this. Give the dog the bone? I can't even interact with dog.
Brain gang? No. No other secrets down here. I'm gonna clean up a little.
In his bowl. Does that, did that work? Did you give the dog the bone? I did not. Not yet.
Haven't had an opportunity to. I'm gonna leave the kitchen. I feel like I've done a lot in the
kitchen. Almost at 3,000 happy points. What is the next actual thing? Right. So I've got this bandage
bone. The shoe! Oh, I keep putting it off. I gotta do this. I gotta climb the castle. All right. I
gotta, let's go. I keep getting sidetracked. You know how some games have Twitch integration?
I keep feeling like that is the Twitch integration of this game. You guys say a command
enough times and it drops a fucking pan on me. Pan joke is getting old. All right. Let's do it.
It is in whose room? It's in her room. But let's do some happy points. Yay, Chibi.
You're a great cook, Chibi. We're best friends.
Oh, I mean, Ribbit. How do you earn sad points? There are no sad points in Chibi-Robo. This is
the children's game. Bingo. All right. This thought I was going crazy. I looked over at the stream
uptime and I saw 57 minutes and I was like, holy fuck, this is the longest hour ever. I forgot about
the internet thing. 40 happy points for that.
Wait, there's a new picture? There is a new picture. Is it a clown? What is this?
Explain this. Tell me what this is. It's mom and dad. It's mom angry. Frog. I did. I already did.
Sir, we have a problem. Report. Some men have gone AWOL. How could this be? Maybe it's all my fault.
I'm sure I was tough on him. It was only because I didn't want to lose any more men. But all that
did was make me lose him faster. Bunkerbusters, what have I done? I'm a disgrace. A soft-boiled,
undercooked disgrace. I'm not fit to be a fried egg sandwich. That sounds pretty good right now.
Troops dismissed, you're a disgrace to the name of Free Ranger and I'm not worthy to lead you. Wait,
I thought this was your fault. But a bonus. How? I gotta be close to another level up, right?
More battery upgrade. Remember, there's an existential crisis going on right now
and these prints can wait. Well, yes, there is an existential crisis going on.
Your happy point bonus is 40. Why so many bonuses? Because I'm just doing so good.
It's funny. I laugh. All right, let's go. Let's do it. Let's have the cleaning robot solve
everybody's problems. Oh, the day's gonna end. It's all right. He's laughing at his own joke,
rested in sleeper. When did I? What? When did I do that? Laughing at my own jokes. I don't do that.
I'm not the first one to fucking laugh every time I say something. What are you talking about? I've
never done that before. It's not like you could literally put me in a room by myself and I would
just entertain myself like next to the wall for like four days straight. It'd be fine.
Nothing wrong with me. No, no, nothing wrong with me. Something wrong with you.
All right, day's gonna end. I might as well just let it play up. How crazy you are. Let me get some
private cargo reporting for duty. Hey, that's, that's what, what are they looking for? Dog tags?
No, it can't be. Those are Memphis's dog tags. You infiltrated the great airy monster's lair?
Pipe down. What's going on here? Private chibi robo infiltrated the beast lair
and brought back Memphis's dog tags. What a bunch of hogwash.
Let me break. Let me see him. Memphis, I'm so sorry. I couldn't save you. I let you down.
Forgive me, Memphis. We will never defeat the great airy beast alone.
We gotta pull together. Men, you're free rangers. You're hard-boiled. One for all. All for one.
You guys are the best. We owe a lot to Memphis because of him. The free rangers will come back
stronger than ever. Hold up for a second. What if Memphis is still alive? We gotta get cracking
and resume our training. Go, go, go, go, go. Anything else? So you survived an operation
into Tau's lair. For a scrawny house cleaning robot, you got a lot of guts. Bolts too.
You showed a lot of courage out there. That's why I'm asking you to do me a favor.
Help instruct our anti-Tau training. I, yes, I don't think it's time to do this today.
With you on our side, we'll have some serious manpower. Here, I mean, robo power.
Here, put this on. New costume. Tau's suit. It's a dog costume. Oh my god, this is so stupid.
Slap me with a battleship. You're even more hideous than the real Tau. The other boys will crack
when they see you. Head into the backyard. I don't have time for this. Listen carefully.
We're going to start our Tau training. Okay. This training will help us withstand Tau's
fearsome bark. Private chibi robo, in this exercise, you will play the role of Tau.
Press Z to bark and scare all the soldiers. When your battery's below 31, you won't be able to
bark and you'll fail. Do you understand? Do not waste your bark system only when several soldiers
are together. Okay, I think I got it. Let's go. Here comes the end of the day. Fuck! I was trying
to go fast. I was trying to go fast because the day was going to end. Well, I got the costume.
This is just Sylvester from Looney Tunes. We gotta go talk to mom. Bye, idiot. He was a cat,
by the way. That made you so mad. You're gonna just leave.
Back to the chibi house. Try to dump all this into the giga robo thing. I'm gonna put all
3,000 into it, yep. Can I rank up? Yes! 260. Excellent.
I need 730. That's a lot. I'm starting to get to the point where
these are gonna come fewer and far between. I'm gonna do all 3,000. The whole thing. I do.
One, two, three, bingo.
More. Four. Another one. This thing's getting kind of close. Is it four more? 4,000 more?
Okay, cool.
Get the chibi PC. Basement warp. Anything else in here? Brahma suit. Another battery. Space
scrambler. A remote control space fighter. Perhaps you can use it someday. What else to do?
Alright, let's go. Now, my number one priority right now is to go climb the castle.
I wanna climb the castle right now. I'm not gonna put it off anymore. I've been trying to do this
the last two and a half straight hours of the stream. We're going. No one will put it off.
I need the D battery. I think it's over there. More like four hours. Probably. You're probably
right. Jeremy, do you ever find it difficult to balance streaming in your personal life?
No, not at all. Not at all. I take a lot of time off. The stream is only live about four times a
week. So, I take plenty of time off. Because I have to. That's what I do. And that's how I do it.
Leaving trash. Leaving trash. I told you that doesn't matter. I have one priority. And that's
get to the top of the castle. But I do have. Actually, I do have some trash. I have a lot of
twig. Nice. I have a lot of shit in my inventory, huh? I missed oldGermo. Oh, oldGermo on Twitch
who streamed six hours a week. Two or three days a week. Yeah. I know. Why don't we get that guy
back? Where's that guy? Can we get that guy back? This stream is like Overwatch for like half the
time. All right. We're going up. I missed the old SwindlerGermo. What do you mean Swindler?
What are you? What? Get on his head. Come on, please. Yes. Yes. This used to be a main A stream.
Now that's a true reference. All right. We're going to go up into the left. Going this way.
The battery goes on the right. Going over here. So this door. Where we go? All right. We've got
check it out. I could push this and go up, but I don't think it's why.
Okay. We're fine. Nothing up here. Wait a minute. They might be. Pull it. No, you dummy.
Might be able to jump up. That looks like a D battery. That's a D battery. Okay. I know where
it is. Can I climb from here? No. Okay. Go back down. I'm going to run out of juice.
I'm going to look at it. Itching nose. Okay. Can I make this? Holy fuck. That was just barely.
Now I'm going to knock this down with that battery. Excuse me. Excuse me. Hey, get out of the way.
I can't drag them. I have to drop down on it. What? Wait, hold on. Okay. I got to.
There's another battery. This is a battery here. Oh, fuck. Hold on. Can I like to stick this up my
nose for a second? You just astound me. The goal is within your reach. Go to the lovely princess
pits and deliver her red shoe. Um, to turn this on. This is where you insert a C battery. I have
to get. All right. I have the battery. I got to get down. Where does this go? Okay. The middle
door opened. Good. I have to charge. Yeah. We'll do this again in a minute. Hold on. Stick it in.
Why are there so many kinds of batteries? Now you're asking the real question.
Thank you. You are actually asking questions that people have been wondering for decades.
Why is it not just two or three types of batteries? Why is it like eight different
batteries? Why can't there just be one type of battery? Why does it need to be AAA or AA?
Why not just make them all small AAAs? I have D batteries. Why not just make them double A's?
Different voltages. Why is everything? Everything should be the same voltage.
It's not that simple. I know. My God. He's a genius. Why didn't we think of that? Shit fucking
slaps. Let me fix this. My Wii sensor bar just fell off the top of my monitor.
All right. They're moving good. Let me guess. It's a C. Check the TV. I will later. Please,
Jerma, finish Super Mario Sunshine when you play it. I'm going to dedicate like a whole week to
that game. So I definitely will. Okay. Now I'm assuming we're going to jump from one to the
other. What's over there? All right. Come on. Let's go. No, you idiot. I had it. I had it. I
gotta wait. I get the cord out of the way. All right. Then around this way. You're going to
play James Bond for GameCube? I don't have it. I don't have it. Does it come all the way over?
Yeah. He definitely comes. Let's look at how slow this is. We have one opportunity right here.
And then we gotta wait till he goes all the way over to the right like this. Okay. Now
shoot that from here. I think I just got the range upgrade. Good thing I got it because
this probably would be impossible without it. This would have been impossible. I think I got it.
Princess, I'm here with your shoe. Oh, my red shoe. Thank you. Thank you.
Now I can go outside again. 33 happy points. Mort gave you 33 happy points. Yeah.
Now we can go back and talk to Mort. Let me introduce myself. I am Princess Pits.
I don't know who you are, but you have my undying gratitude. I had already given up.
I had resigned myself to spending the rest of my life in the castle.
I mean, walking outside without my shoe? Please. That would be so icky. Anyway, thank you. If it
isn't too much, would you be so kind as to tell me your name? Chibi Robo. This is Chibi Robo.
And my name is? You're the famous Chibi Robo? Telly. Excuse me for asking this,
but you wouldn't happen to be the one who's been bringing me flowers.
Why, yes, of course it's been me. It's Mort, right? It's Mort. It's not me.
I see. Then who could it be? A sweet damsel. Wait, it's not you.
Drake Redcrest. Hello. Can I help you? I found a flower in the backyard that was almost as
beautiful as you. It is a special present from Drake Redcrest for you. Mort, I tried.
Mort, I tried. Drake Redcrest, are you perhaps the one who's been bringing me flowers?
Those filthy things? I think not. Oh, I see. But I like these filthy flowers. Anyway, thank you.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. What do I say? What do I say? What do I say to fix this? What
do I say to solve this? Perhaps justice demands filthy flowers. Excuse me. He just thought he
was a Chad. That was not a Chad move. Well, Princess Pits, if you'll excuse me. Chibi Robo,
please come and visit me again. Ew, gross. The toys are playing with her. Wait, what's going on
with the TV? Circle, middle, radar. Hey, dickhead. You want to unplug the TV, please? Jenny's gone
nutso. She hasn't been sleeping at night because she's all worried about her mom. She doesn't even
notice me dancing around here. I don't know how to speak rivetees. Holy fuck, you useless motherfucker.
Get me up here. Turn the fucking TV off. Get this off. Talk to her. She's not gonna say anything.
Circle, middle, radar. Circle, middle, radar. Circle, middle, radar. I'm turning it off.
Where does the radar want me to go? Turn this shit off. Is it aliens? Circle, middle, radar.
Okay. What's the secret thing that's pointing this way? I need to charge.
I was just up there. I gotta go all the way up there again for the secret. Hold on.
Nice job ignoring my bits. Oh fuck, there was 50. Yeah, 50 dollars. Holy shit. Sorry, I was
fully immersed. 5,000 bits from Yes Is Online. Thank you, Yes. They say play the barnyard licensed
game on GameCube. Otis is my favorite, people happy. Otis barnyard licensed game. Barnyard?
Wait, isn't barnyard like the animated TV? There's a TV show called Barnyard, right?
I don't know what barnyard is. What the fuck is barnyard? Barnyard. Yeah, this is a TV show.
It wasn't a movie. It was a TV show before. It was a movie. It was right. It also had a Wii game.
Okay, I gotta go all the way up. I was just up there too. Barnyard movie came out first. Wait,
the barnyard? No, it didn't. It actually traumatized me, what you said. Wait, is that the one? There's
a pig in it. The pig talks like this. Hey, the pig talks like this. Welcome to the barnyard.
No, that's Toy Story. That's the pig from Toy Story. Is there a pig in that show? Yeah, there is. What
does it talk like? All right. It's right here. Not quite. It's lower. Is it right here? Damn. Okay,
let's go. Nice. How many more? Seven in here. Okay, so we now we have to go use the radar. But look
at all this stuff. There's lots of stuff in this room. Who's the dancing person? Purple crayon
zooming on this. What the hell is going on? Okay, we're going up. It's a pirate. Oh,
shit. You're right. Can I make it from here? Is this a snorkel? Can I make this?
Why is chat in slow mode? There was so much. There was so many people going like,
I had to turn it on. There's someone screams. All right, I gotta get better perspective. I can
probably get up there. I want that to the door. Sit on the mushroom. I did already.
Did I get it? Let's go use the radar. Look at all this trash. Circle middle radar. Why does Jenny
just throw over mush all over trash under the bed? Circle middle radar. Wait, is it her doing this
or is it the mummy guy down here doing this? Okay, let me let's talk. I want to talk to you again.
Are you just like actually walking around? I gotta pee. It makes me upset. You ever in the
middle of something and you just have to pee and it just makes you angry? Who throws the word?
Circle middle radar. Okay, I know. 30 points. Wait, it's a toy telephone. You might be able
to talk to someone though. I can? I guess not. All right, I'm gonna leave here. I'm gonna plug in.
I'm gonna circle middle radar. I'm gonna talk to mom again. Go to the bathroom now. I'm all right.
I'm okay. There's enough time for me to plug in, talk to mom, and then go to the bathroom.
Day's almost over anyways. There's a guy over here. All right, a lot of things just opened up.
Let's just go talk to mom right now before time runs out. Use your Razor gamer diaper.
Yeah, when it's full, you build XP. No. What level am I? 26. XP boost. Yeah, you just gotta
go get a Mountain Dew. Peel off the XP booster and punch it in the code in.
It's 30% less urine you need to to level up.
Of course it does. You have to even ask that question? Of course it does. Okay, let's go.
See? Right here. Quick. To the point. Right here. Okay. Is the plan. I have a bandage. I have...
I wanted to go talk to mom. Congrats on being in BG3. What's BG3? Time to water the garden.
Wait, what's dad doing out there? Baldur's Gate 3? Huh? BG3.
Okay, dad. Let's do some lawn work. I'll take care of this. All right,
let's start playing the Michael Myers theme song for a second. Wait, wait, wing? Okay, hey.
You're watering the tree? What is he... Dad, you're spraying down the swing? What's wrong with you?
Aren't you the neat freak, chibi robo? I won't be using that toothbrush again,
but if you're using it to clean, I'm fine with it. Watering the rocks. What a waste of water.
I'm gonna do my best with the chores until Jenny's mom is in a better mood.
Why are you saying Jenny's mom? I'm counting on you, chibi robo. Can I do anything in here?
Look at that secret door. It's a translation issue. I guess so. All right, any more secrets out in the
backyard? Nope. Can I do anything with dad? I went all the way up to the top of the tree.
There's a fucking weirdo up there. Remove the weeds. Oh, there's a weirdo up there. How do you
remove weeds? Dig? Hold on. I gotta talk to the weirdo. Chibi robo.
If you stand there, you'll get all wet. That's dangerous business for a robot.
Stand back. You're not my dad. You actually are not my dad. All right, what's this weirdo doing up
here? Keep it down, will you? We're not supposed to be talking right now. I am Macon. I'm training
to become a pirate, sir. You are, sir. Watering the lawn is great. It's like I'm in a rain cloud.
Captain Plankbird is recruiting. Thanks for letting me know. Macon just gave you 26 happy
points. Oh, this is... you just have to tell them. Oh, there's a door over there. Hold on.
There's a door there and some shit over there. White block. I think I might need a tool to do
that. All right, it's saying pull weeds, so pull these. Can I pull these up? Weeds. Weeds. Oh,
that's why everyone wanted me to pull up the weeds. Jerma, pull the weeds. No,
Jerma, you can pull those weeds up, you know. Jerma, the weeds can be pulled. Did you know?
Cannot and day hot? What does it say? Cannot and today hot. Cannot and today hot. Well,
sunny out. It's been a while since I got any scrap. What does it say?
So, I gotta go out here at night time. That makes sense. Now, what about over here? There's a little
garden here. Can I plant the nectar flower here? Yes, I can. No, I can't. Plant the weed?
I'm not gonna plant in weeds. All right, let's come back here at night.
Got it. I got it immediately. I'll come back here at night. Oh, wait, there is a bird up there.
What does a bird eat? Bird seed? Do I have any food for the bird? Weeds, twigs, cookie crumbs,
bones, a cookie, the nectar? Nectar! Will the bird eat the nectar? Gunpowder. No, that's not
gonna happen. All right, yeah, let's feed the bird nectar. Gotcha. This game is so fun. I'm so glad
I got this game. This is great. This is really great. I like this. Sure, we'll save it. You got
not bought. That's where you're wrong. Start with the pirate emote. I did buy. I did bought.
I do own. The ISO cost 100 bucks. No, I have the physical, video, game, disc, original,
in circulation. I have it. I own it, and it's mine. In 30 years, I'm gonna sell it for five grand.
I showed it yesterday. It's in the Wii right now. Did it come with a case? Yep. This is original.
It's got the manual. It's got the case, and it's got the disc, and the disc is in liquid pristine
condition. It is like crystal. No marks, no nothing. It is pristine. I'm gonna shrink wrap
this fucking thing. When I'm done completing this game, it's going back in the case and getting
shrink wrapped. Let's give nectar to the bird. You're scamming, scammering. No, I'm not gonna
tell. That's not to... Hold on. What do you got? Ooh, chirp, chirp, chirp. Do I have to have a bird
costume to speak bird? Chirp, chirp. Okay. I think he's half asleep. Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
Yikes, I overslept. Chirp. You look at the time. I almost missed my date.
Holly will peck my eyes out if I'm late. Last time she plucked all of my feathers. I had goosebumps
for a week. Thanks for waking me up. Chirp. You seem grateful. Way to go, Chibi-Robo. Now we can
keep going. We can get on the roof. We can get on the roof. It's roof time. Careful. Demon door.
Oh yeah. All right. Anything else up here? Wait, let's break this. Two demon doors.
There's a bunch of dirt up here. The bird shit. I'll get the bird shit in a minute too.
Clean. Save the battery. Can I fix this somehow? Um, can I get it? Just jump. Hold on. Can I get
across this? Boy. No! What just happened? What? I was trying to shimmy. What the fuck? The camera
moved a little. The camera moved and it... That was weird. All right. Hold on. Let me charge up
again. So LOL bad. Oh, he's blaming the camera. Fucking the camera's fault. The camera sucks.
Oh, I just... I wasn't expecting it. I was shimmy. Fake gamer. I'm not even a real gamer.
I used to be. I was so good. Did you see my TF2 one live gameplay when I got like 28 kills?
One life. I used to be so good. I had like 37 kills in one life as a demo man. Oh,
you're just old now. That's what happens. Oh, but man, back in the day. Oh, I'm so good.
I'm gonna walk behind him because I don't want that cut scene to trigger again.
Oh, that's what happens when you when you beat Sekiro. When you beat the last boss in Sekiro,
I'm doing that because I just want people to think I still kind of got it.
That's what I thought. What are the purpose? Does that serve? This is how you guys know
that I still kind of got it. And this game is like 100 bucks on eBay. We'll just wait
till you type in, uh, cubivore. Check that one. I don't, I don't have that one. I do not have that
one. You're back? Get out of the way. Oh, you again. I thought you died. I thought you fall
off the roof there. Figured you'd never gonna come back. You got anything to eat? Cookie crumbs.
Oh, get out of the way. That's what I wanted to eat. Mm. Tap you a little one. Uh, and it made
them big. All these crumbs have made me thirsty. This is going to ruin my singing voice. Water's
good, but I much prefer the sweet nectar of a flower. All right, we have that. Just fall off
again. All right, let's not fuck this up again, please. Awful wink. Want a refund. There's no,
there are no refunds. Okay, this is what happened last time. The camera went, here we go. Oh, look
at all these trinkets. 10, 15. Nice. I got to 75k. No way I'm going to use it on a mere blink.
2250. All right, how many more? There's one more door out here. Isn't there one right here?
Wish I could zoom out. Can I zoom out? Kind of, not really. Where is it? It's like on the wall,
right? Right here. Where is it? I remember seeing it. Is it right? Where is it? Oh, cube. White block.
Now where is that other door? There it is. Okay, right there. I'm going to shimmy across the drop
of the dork variety. Yeah, I got all the doors in the backyard. No more. Eight out of eight,
completed. Backyard's pretty much done. Oh, I do want, I want to get the bird nectar. We'll do
that too. Let's close that out. This is a real gaming hours. Yeah, I guess so. Am I going for
100%? Um, yes, but not on the way you think. I'm going for 100% personal fulfillment. When I've had
enough and I'm done and I want to complete, I'm going to complete. That's my 100%. That might
mean do a shitload of side quests. Maybe not all of them, but enough of them. You sound like my
youth pastor. It's the 100% happiness run. That's happened 14 times. Yes, it has. Can I get up there
before the day is over? I'm going to be close. Probably not. Hurry, hurry. Gibi robo, get away
from there. Sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep, sheep. Sheep, sheep, sheep. Go so close. Stop. Go.
Nectar. Hey, look what I got. Yay, nectar. Glug, glug, glug. That really hits the spot.
Nothing beats natural nectar. Chirp. You've been great, but I need one more thing. I've been eating
a lot of junk lately and need some veggies. See any around? Balanced diet is important. If you
don't have your health, you don't have anything. You don't look so good yourself. Try not to work
too hard. I came to this town so that everyone could hear my lovely voice. Weed. Should I give
them weeds? Counting on you to get me my veggie. I have weeds. That's dumb. I have to do it again
tomorrow. Maybe a twig? Maybe. Make them a Sisu salad. Seed? We'll find out. It's either weed,
twig, or some kind of seed. Waiting for the countdown now. Dang. Come up with that connect,
Jerva. I'm going for it. Birds eat sticks? Well, birds eat seeds and, I don't know, leaves?
Bugs? Birds don't eat sticks. Birds do not eat wood. They don't do that.
I'm gonna save my money. There's only one thing I can buy. It's the spaceship. Does the basement
warp? Warps you from place to place. Placed on both ends of the stairs. Yeah, I just get it.
Woodpeckers don't eat wood. Yeah, I know. They're not eating it. They're borrowing.
They're borrowing to eat bugs. They're making a hole so they can eat the bugs out of the hole
that they're borrowing with their nose. They don't eat wood.
The utility bots just gave you a hundred happy points because I did it all. You got the utility
bot sticker. You really are amazing. You've done it all. You're the best. I actually need to look
at the stickers. I haven't seen them. Scrap trade? Exchange rate. One scrap equals one. Oh, so now
I've gotten to a point where I bought everything. The space scrambler and chibi battery. I'm not
gonna buy either one of them. I'm like one sub. All right, it's night time. You know what that
means. Back outside. Do the radar. Is the bird there? The bird's sleeping at night. He's up there.
I'll do that after. Am I calling a UFO? Wait, they're all robots. They look just like me.
I don't speak alien. I need an alien costume. I don't know what they're saying. Oh, what? I don't
know. Alien council. Should I say yes? Yes. I asked you if you liked pineapple on pizza. Well,
was that you chibi robo? What do you mean was that me? You're losing it chibi robo.
I only asked you that to test you. Get a hold of yourself bot. Those were aliens.
I've seen them on tv but this is the first time I've seen them in real life.
They're smaller than I would have thought. They were very shiny but their voices were so quiet
I couldn't make out what they were saying at all. Oh, I know. I'll ask Citrusoft if they have a
chip that can help you hear their voices. Well, they're gone. They've left. Maybe Citrusoft can
give us something. Okay. Now what? I have a bandage. The bone. The weed. Bird. Is he sleeping?
I'll wake him up and feed him. First thing I see in chat is what I'm going to eat tonight for food.
Is it an egg? No. No, I don't think so. It was eggs but I really don't want to eat eggs. Hey,
I'm back. Don't you have a way to speak to animals? Wait, this is the way to talk to all animals.
So why is the frog suit just frog? I need a vegetable that's super duper nutritious. It
might be pretty tough to find one but I'm sure there's one nearby. Okay, anyone that's super
nutritious? I might be pretty tough to find one. I'm sure there's one nearby.
I don't have it. Eggplant? Eggplant? Where's there an eggplant?
What about over here? I'm going to sneeze.
Your head. Nutritious eggplant. There ain't nothing here. Looks not on your thousand dollar mic.
Wait, hold on. There's a spot up here. Remember I was trying to figure out what the hell to do
with it? I mean, this might be a shot in the dark or whatever. It was a little patch somewhere
over here, right? Where is it? Up into the right. There's a little spot. Where is it? Am I crazy?
I think I'm, yeah, I'm crazy. No, I'm not. It's over here, right? It's right there, right there.
Yeah, I know. I'm not crazy. What the hell is this? There's nothing. I really can't get in here.
Oh, maybe not. I guess it's not.
Oh well. This has to be here for a reason though, right? What else will this be here for?
Oh well, okay. I'll just come back later. Let's move. The next order of business is...
What is the next order of business? Go back to the, and get the chip.
I think I didn't spend any money. All right, can I talk to the dog? I can talk to the dog with this
on. Let me go see if there's a new chip. I could hardly believe my eyeballs when I saw those aliens.
Shocking, simply shocking. I couldn't quite figure out what they were saying. They were speaking so
softly. I almost forgot. I think Citrus Soft makes a chip that would allow you to hear soft voices.
I'll contact them right away. I knew they had something like this. It's called an alien ear
chip. But they know. How much is it? Okay, we'll bring it back. All right, let's go.
That can't be more than like 2,000. 2150 alien ear chip. Fine. So let's go back out there and
do it again. Maybe I can actually hear them this time. Maybe if I, uh, maybe the first thing in
chat that's not an egg is a food item. I'm going to eat pizza. Okay. Thanks for playing.
It was pizza. I said hash house at gogo. Yeah. And you are one of the smartest people in this
whole room. You have to be. You have to be one of the smartest people in this whole chat room.
Absolutely. 1000% positive. All right, let's go. I have the chip installed. Let's see if we can do
this again. Oh, so we're stupid. No, I just said that that person was one of the smartest people
in the room. Look, if somebody was in this room right now and had 155 IQ, I'd be like,
you're smarter than me, but I'm smart. Like if I have 140, that doesn't make me stupid. That
doesn't make you the smartest person in the room. Why are the frogs back? Oh, fuck. I have to talk
to them with a frog suit. Thank you so much. Long time no see chibi robo. Can I ask you something
ribbit? It's been so dry here lately. This keeps up our minds and bodies will scribble up like
disgusting prunes. Well, you weren't out here when dad was spraying water making giant puddles
everywhere in mud. This is over the last full day. We need to stay moist the frog way. We used to
bring the rain with a rain ritual. But now there are only two of us and we need three frogs to do
it. Can you help us with our rain? Yes, of course. I would be honored. Let's do it. The rules aren't
easy. Adjust your timing so that you crouch at the same time as us with Z. Watch our movements
carefully and get the timing right. Let's go. We're doing it right now? Wrong. When we crouch
together, press Z at the same time. He's fucking up too. Don't get mad at me. He did it. You did
it before alone. So why are you only mad at me? I love the sounds. They're so good. A healthy snack
and a grow from that garden. Yay rain. Thank you chibi robo. You are so welcome. It's not only
just for frogs. I bet the flowers are happy too. 100 happy points. You got the frog sticker.
Their whole arc has been completed. Frog arc complete. Now I think there might be a healthy
snack over there. Let's go look at the stickers. There's one right here. Frog. What was I doing
here? Oh yeah, this. All right, come back. I'm back so I can actually understand you.
Now it's daytime, isn't it? It's technically the morning. Is it because of the suit?
That's because it wasn't the frog suit on. We're back. Aliens. Wow, wow, wow. This is the first
time I've seen one in real life. We are aliens. We are here to see friend. We made promise to
friend. Must see now. Are you friend of friend? Where is friend now? Are they talking about the
they're talking about gigajad? Chibi robo, let's show them the way to their friend.
Yes, way to go chibi robo. Keep this up and we'll be at the top of the chibi robo rankings. Do your
best. All right, everybody get inside my head for a little bit. You watch ship. We follow you. Thank
you. A little stingy on the happy points. Lo just gave you six. Ganymede just gave you six. They're
all Jupiter moons. Wow, wow, wow. Chibi robo, the aliens gave you happy points. Titan, Titan, Lo,
Lo. Ganymede, Ganymede. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. I know. Wait, I'm bringing them through
the house. Guys, this is not really how this works. Usually how this works is you get inside my head.
All right, we gotta go. What if the dog kills them? All right, follow me. Wait just a minute.
Who decides what is justice and what is evil? What is justice? What is evil? I don't know. You
cannot fool me disguising yourselves as space hunter robo. I know you've come to annihilate this
world, hideous extraterrestrial friends. I must stop you somehow. Space hunter robo, I don't want
to believe that you're an agent of evil. However, if evil exists, justice will defeat it. That is
what justice is all about and I am the hero of justice. All right, push him into the beam.
Space hunter drake redcrest. Not a guess, not a guess. Humiliation is a cruel mistress.
I seem to have run out of gunpowder. I'll let you go. Your day is numbered. Adios. I have that.
What was that? That was cool. Alien is amigo. I want to meet amigo. Let's go. Drake redcringe.
All right, we need to go to the basement. Basement. Basement. The quickest way to the
basement is foyer. We got to watch out for the dog. Follow me. And if you see any trash, pick it
up. That's what we do over here. That's what we do on earth. It looks so happy when I pick it up.
They do a jumping jack. It's me and the boys. Shadow clones. Okay, foyer. What about the...
Are we going to get attacked by the eggs? Let's go. Come this way. Let's avoid a conflict here.
I wanted to pick this up, but I was going to hang out for a minute. Come take a seat.
Come see your friend. Hey, wait. Can you... Does your ship have 4,000 power by any chance?
I just went to the kitchen. Oh, you sure don't? I thought you knew where you were going.
GP robot, why is the GPS turned on? You've been down this road 2,000 times. I know. I know. Shut
up. Just fucking have it on it, right? Oh, look. Wait, don't touch that. Look who I got. Okay, so
you ain't the fighting kind of alien. Okay, good. You're the exploration aliens. I couldn't have
gotten to one group of fighting aliens. Friend, pal, buddy. Uh, he's dead. I forgot to mention
that. He died like 30 years ago. Did I tell them that before we came down here? Thank you. Thank
you. 33, 33, 99 points. Your achievements are already on a universal scale. We came to fulfill
our promise. What did you do to our friend friend? Yeah, I'm working on that. I'm working on putting
them back together. It's been slow going. You see that there's like a divorce going on. I know
there's like intergalactic shit going, but like there's a frog girl up there I had to give rings
for. It's been a long process. I paid off the rockets. Ally immobile. Is savior sick? Is mate
cold? Yeah, shut your core colors for a second. Are you asking about Giga Robo? Hey, he's as stiff
as me beard. Friend has stopped. Friend does not move. Friend has died. We promised. Friend,
we are too late. We are sorry, friend. No good. Sad. Are you all grieving for me shipmate Giga
Robo? What a kindly bunch of critters you be. I can't stop me tears. Tears are all tiny oceans
of sorrow. Tears from a poem I penned once. I forget I said that. Pirates don't write poems.
Just another part of the pirate's code. I'm sorry. I'm okay. We leave the part. Withdraw.
I hate your fucking vacation. I'm crying. You're crying. Well, we just have to bring him. We have
to charge him and then bring it. Okay. I'm not here. How much money do I have? We just have to
charge him back up, bring him back to life, and then bring the aliens back down. It's that simple.
It's so it's a very easy simple equation. Go gamble for 4k. What's going on over here? Help
instructor. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. How do I like the game up to this point? I think it's a
so like I think it's a solid it's 6.1 6.2. No, this game's fucking awesome. It's so good.
It's amazing. It's like, I don't know. It's very good. Come on, bunch up. All army K.O.
Tao training cleared. I think it's fantastic. I love it. Thanks to you, my men are ready for
the worst. They're prepared to face the great furry evil. I think I've upgraded. Our training
is over. We gotta come up with a plan to save Memphis. Once we've drawn up our battle plan,
we'll be ready to take on the great hairy threat. We'll need you when the time comes.
It's time we take the fight to the enemy. It's time we Romnibus Romnibus, whatever that means.
Help us take down the tyrannical Tao. Let's talk to the dog. I think we need the dog side of the
story. I don't have time to do anything else. Centrist. What a centrist. You, I remember you.
Go join the pirates. They're looking for people. Hey, yeah, word is you got a hot rod.
How about a little game of chicken? Game of chicken. But you want me to drive and you want
to drive into each other. Why would we do this? Whoever stops closest to the edge wins. Press B
to slam on the brakes. What? I'm not driving the car. Okay, the brakes take a little while.
Oh, GV Robo. Take this, you crazy robot. Let's do it again. Yes. All right. I thought it was
going to be hit and stop immediately, but you have to, okay, I get it. This really is a great,
this really is a great Wii game that came out 500 times. Oh, come on. He's giving me 50 bucks.
Can I just grind this 50 dollars every time? I stopped that pretty quick. I stopped that.
Almond or wifi. Does this work? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond
or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Almond or? Good work. I had to have done it. Not
terrible. Pretty close. Let's see. Oh, you did. D. How did I get a D? That was so good.
Give it a rest, man. Come back later. How was that a D? That was, that was, that was so good. That was
so, well, that's kind of not fair. I got really close to the edge. I was almost over the edge.
I'm pissed off. Let's go into mom's room while I have some minutes here. Here this game is three
games and then a final grade. Oh, there's something here. Later. Is this the Almond or wifi streamer?
Mom, wake up. You have something for me. Give me the cool costume. You were knitting me a sweater.
No, thank you. I can't. House of fun. Who am I? Who am I? House of fun. House of fun.
No, thank you. I can't eat anymore. I just tried to bark and it didn't do anything.
Good house. Jenga. Who are you? Who are you? House of fun. Hey you.
Hound dog. I saw him trying to bite off his own tail once. He was a sweet little puppy though.
All he needed was his doggy bone to make him happy. The suit... i don't think i can get up
any higher. You know, it's easier to forget that the point of this game is picking up candy wrappers.
that's what i'm saying people give me shit for cleaning that's on the front cover of the box
i'm with a vacuum cleaner no it's not it's him carrying his plug on his head i don't know i
thought i was with a vacuum cleaner but i can't do it's too i can't do anything in here all right
we need a game plan game plan during the day talk to the dog find out the dog side of the story
remove the suit and talk to the dino okay game plan why would i say that when i have it here
almond or it's right here i don't even say it anymore oh t.v robo just look at that will ya
moss anderson's trapped in there and he hasn't had any food or water for three days
he's always been neglected as criminal there ain't no two ways about it look at how young
and strong he's he's the picture of gallantry oh if only i could open them blinds that ain't
nothing but wishful thinking though if i were prone to melodrama i might phrase it like this
um
dumb dumb dumb the old dino can't open the blinds will funky phil ever know freedom again
yep i reckon that's what i'd say pretty sad ain't it if only somebody could open them for him
how do i open it i don't get any new items to open this i mean i tried doing this before
wait hold on i was just up here when i did come on baby come on girl don't be like that come on
over here please i'm on my funky knees here okay so i don't have knees but give me some funky
fresh love wait what i'll never get my funky self out of here work with me just a little bit
huh hey funky robo my corny friend here is a child we only love just let me in a very unfuncular
line could you open this funky robo word that's what i'm talking about wait a minute i'll give it
a little push you catch it and save me uh there we are you the robot funky phil just gave you
35 happy points look at the t-rex down there crazy mrs sanderson he just has to shut the blinds
it's not like anyone's peeping in her window but now i'll be able to kick my funk into high gear
and practice my moves oh yeah funky robo yeah funky robo as a reward you get to howdy funky
oh wait long time no see let me tell you this old gal wanted over the blinds for you but
as any fool can see these tiny arms of mine aren't fit to stir upon a chili
you about startled me out of my skin chibi robo you handled them blinds like a pro
oh thanks 80 points now listen up here funky phil let's say you shake off some of that
dust and show me some bootstool how about it for all time's sake well i'm well um um ain't
no kind of answer you've been skipping meals again partner men need to be manly manly here
are you gonna find yourself a good little missus if you ain't got no spunk
if worse comes to worse i know a certain dinosaur who'd bite the bullet and marry you oh stop you
wilted you dang fool i'm just pulling your leg there's a joke it's a j-o-l-k-e being stuck
inside all the time is maybe you're maybe insane are you gonna get ahead in life you ain't got a
sense of humor come on let's get a move on hold everything hey i got a riddle for you
do you know what kind of race a t-rex can never win answers right in front of you an arms race
that is arms race oh god it's a little gag little like my arms i got a million of them fellas
oh hey i ain't done yet all night funky nice just like i remembered funky bill
is funky if i was 10 years younger that boy'd be mine for sure mom's just mom is just depressed
sleeping in the background this is this is too many emotions going on here ain't no two ways
about it right chibi robo sure darn tootin you're brighter and you look partner what entire nation
funky phil something something fell off of you it's a darn gold seed why why am i blushing it's
only a seed snap out of it dina go get that scene see what it is no time left what is this
funky seed funky seed if it's a seed should you plant it um um what is all over the ground here
it's just like radioactive liquid i'm gonna plant this uh right now where's a good planter
i need a planter is there a good planter somewhere day over
over
happy point total i'm gonna level up definitely rank like seven or six six six
we're making into the top six more battery that's a big increase 30 are we gonna go to 40 after this
so
i should have sucked up that liquid do it again okay we are
putting uh we're putting a dent in a lot of these arcs not many more story arcs left but
now there is a do i think i have a frog ring meaning game first frog suit i already talked
to her in the frog suit i already talked to her in the frog suit eight nine all right well
i'm gonna what's gonna be the radar anything new here there's one uh hidden one somewhere
uh-huh follow it interesting up on the tv above the tv give me this thing give me the bridge do it
again uh hold on i will i'm just gonna do this push it tv frog champ okay where is this final
door in the living room final thing in the living room it's probably gonna be right behind the tv
right here let's see interesting where is it in the tv it it's the it's the cap on the tv
wait a minute what i don't get it nozzle i mean i've i've already turned the nozzle i've already
i've already switched the channel shovel maybe
understand it doesn't doesn't do anything
is it maybe underneath no no way right i can't change the channel when using the radar
huh weird i cannot interact with the radar it doesn't do anything there it doesn't makes the
radar do the radar again underneath that'd be something weird right let's try first of all
plug in before i die i don't think you can plug it in oh shit i guess i'll die something can i can
i go in the back of the tv is there anything else behind this doesn't look like there's anything
behind the tv there is nothing behind the tv well i have no idea oh well where's the dog in the
kitchen change the channel a bunch keep changing the channel keep changing the channel this is
actually nothing right and she'll hunt well i'm i'm running out of time you're a great cook chibi
we're best friends he's still if you're still burping and having loud burps and indigestion
five days after eating the hamburger i think it's time to go to the doctor all right kitchen dog
just burped in his face kind of i'm at 4 000 i need to go to the kitchen kitchen kitchen his way
i did find mr prongs i did he was very strange very strange man
in revive giga chad i will only do 4 000 more to do that i'll have enough soon
i just want to complete a couple more of these things dogs not in the kitchen
hey you oh all right there's a new crew member hold on where's the dog where's the dog outside
maybe let me go tell this guy to go join the pirate group that was a gold it was worth it
all right i want to fly i'm gonna probably just use the bridge huh can i get to the table
from here uh i should get to get it okay let me try and go for it
perfect hey go for drawing the pirate group goodbye i'm sensei i want to be a pirate
captain plank bird is recruiting pirates go oh get out of here go seven out of nine
did i miss any uh i'm gonna go yeah i'm gonna mom is probably awake now i'm gonna go to mom
get the sweater feed the bird i don't have the food for the bird bird wants something
super nutritious i don't have anything i'm gonna have to go maybe the sip funky seed will do it
once the seed grows into a plant oh let's go upstairs let's go get the costume still
don't i gotta find the dog too no no no stop stop stop stop is there any more of those pirate i
think i saw a pirate person in here right what is redblock there's two up there oh those are not
pirates they're they're spacemen oh go talk to mom fuck out of here i can just turn this into
money now right there's really no reason me to be collecting this anymore all right give me my new
costume okay mom do i have to meet the aliens oh i i have to bring the giga robo back to life
i just need to plant this seed
somewhere i need four thousand dollars to bring giga robo back to life how much do i have right now
like 1200 i have a theory that that's if the game is needs to load that's a load extra assets all
right mom give me my costume oh you're dressing up like tau can you talk like him too i just
remembered a dream i had you were picking up garbage around the house
but if i have that dream the house seems to sparkle in the morning thank you
costume i wanted to make you something but there aren't any old clothes really
i can't make anything without any material what should i do
i'll hunt around a bit for something so just wait a little longer make sure you tell me if
you find anything we can use you're like why this is underwear um can you use old boxers
did you find any old fabric i did a dirty pair of underwear that'll work nicely you know i'm
pretty sure there are three pieces of old clothing this material is fine let's get your measurements
you know chivo for a little fellow you sure are a hard worker if only my lazy husband had some of
your go your get up and go i wonder how long this will drag on no let's forget about that for now
why don't we get you all measured up turn around and raise your arm don't move that's right stay
still you're almost as tall as one pack of cigarettes your height and shoulder width are
you're a small one aren't you i bet it's hard to find your size at the store
i can't imagine trying to shop for chivi pants all right the rest is a surprise just you wait and
see i think it'll be done by tomorrow so go play with papa for the time being okay thanks mom
briefcase code mom briefcase code by the way mom help me get up here look at how much i'm
struggling helping just a minute yeah get over thank you all right i need to go back into here
do i have enough time there was another pirate in here wasn't there in the jenny's room okay
where is pirate there you are can i climb this from here no i can't shit oh does it how do i
get up there gotta go from there we gotta go all the way up don't we you got anything new
for me to say or do anything who's been bringing me flowers it must be a secret admirer i'm sure
he's just a wonderful person bear and the honey have we got that lug lug lug miyam miyam back
lug lug lug lug excuse me that's a little scary smack smack plug
lug these evil noises oh
sorry to interrupt your meal huh
how long have you been standing there oh not very long at all you should have at least said
something we did you did but what is something wrong what is nothing i'm sorry my name is sunshine
nice to meet you it's the first time we've met isn't it and you are it's chibi robo and i'm
telly's manager chibi robo and telly oh yes i see what nice names nice to meet you nice to meet you
too uh well we should get going
nectar nectar something wrong i'm hungry i'm hungry for nectar bring me some nectar nectar
from a flower bring it now don't make me hurt you holy shit douse me with it i want to roll
around this sweetie bear needs nectar now i can't help it okay blog i've got something right here
come here come here where'd it go where'd it go you're enabling him what
i'm just trying to get a happy point you're carrying a syringe around look i'm just trying
to get a happy point curious come here look what i got hey hey you have some nectar my sweetest
i'm full of warmth and happiness now thanks chibi robo there's some more there's some more
yay it's nectar my favorite i'm covered in nectar yay i'm so full of joy okay i think you've had
enough the rest of this is mine doesn't doesn't mine i'm nutso for nectar i'm cuckoo for coco
i know what to do i have to scare her with the ghost costume and then he comes out and saves her
all right good good plan you don't have time to do it hey look what's behind you stop it chibi
robo please stop it i can't stand the horror of it all do i have to do this a few times
do it at night maybe at night yeah you almost killed her it's all right let's come back at night
i got a lot of shit to do what money do i have wait wait wait wait
ha ha i got it off all right i can do another uh you can do a thousand kilowatts
do giga robo and i need three thousand more to activate giga robo
giga battery has six thousand kilowatts i do let's put it on a thousand
mega giga ultra chat we're almost there
three thousand more the pop for anybody else yeah his voice in here only in here really is pops
and some music does i'm not exactly sure why uh i'm gonna convert these uh actually i have almost a
thousand
emulator issues well however the we is emulating the game cubes audio has a problem there stop
reading what i say i'm gonna all right let's go uh back up to the foyer and scare her at night
this is the kitchen oh this is original hardware well it's on a we we is an original we've already
how many times we have to have this conversation the we is the game cube with a couple bells and
whistles uh this way two game cubes duct taped together it's mostly the same hardware with the
cpu running at a higher speed that's correct all right time to scare you come here look at this
oh shit stop it please stop it wait so where what's going on mort mort the plan didn't work
mort where's mort where is he not over here there he is okay well mort i need to go up there
mort wait this is d battery no i don't care about who cares about batteries
we're gonna talk to mort mort i got a great plan it's gonna work trust me
mort trust me first let me get these snacks out of the way oh the friendship man that was pretty
close yeah okay mort i'm ready for the plan you rattled the very depths of my soul
a hero and a princess a time-worn cliche isn't it yes we all know that story don't we
but i'm sure princess pits would rather have lovely fresh flowers instead of my withered
stems whenever i touch a flower it dies a lovely nectar flower would bloom here
i'm sure princess kids would be very happy hey excuse me chibi robo is always prepared
what do you think about that well see you in a couple days while you stare at a plant growing
i mean you're just gonna pick up this trash
water it uh you don't you can't water anything in the game there is no water there's no watering
have you guys been paying attention to anything going on in this video game there's no watering
this plant has anybody even been paying attention what are you guys been playing
scrabble together use a plunger okay i gotta get up to the pirate how do i do that
yay i'm covered in nectar okay good now uh i can go up there can i not get any higher than this up
on the bed i don't think i have the capabilities to do this yet i have to though right if i get up
there can i go from here to the this painting over here maybe the other side of the bed oh
fuck let me check inside and do something over here
get up there no you fucking idiot all right nice oh there's a door up here
oh fuck i'm all the way up hold on hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait get this first
apologize for being mean to chibi i'm talking about me i'm the one in control of chibi robo i'm
i'm talking about me all right there's a lot more doors up here she's sleeping um okay i can climb
that all the way up shit i think i need to get a snack i think i need a snack everybody else need
a snack i could use a snack right now i go like this squeeze apple thing no something a little
more substantial the train over here maybe like beef jerky yeah i got i got one how close might
at the end of the game am i getting close i mean i'm still having fun i'm not gonna stop the stream
right now but i feel like i'm getting kind of close what was the train i do something with the
train that's kind of cool look at this it's so cute i don't even need to use the box still fun
to ride can i do anything with the flower oh a box green block it is go up here oh shit okay um hold
on let me do something right here that actually hurt now it's in the very corner of the room okay
all right i can't i gotta get out of here i gotta i can't fuck around i have i'm gonna run out of
battery oh snorkel i knew it oh um good okay let's go back i'm getting that door same deal
the family know that this is a sentient being probably not all right we got two things to do
here first of all we're gonna do pirate first uh uh fuck door there is a door oh shit move it you
don't think i can knock this over are you kidding me one charge shot it's gone nice a lot of money
i almost have enough to power up a giga robo i might have it i might have it what the hell is
this yellow crayon power up again and then i'm gonna get that other door still to find his leg
oh yeah that's right shit i do have to find his leg what the hell is his leg
all right good morning
uh there are three more doors two more if you count the one i'm about to open
that's tame it is isn't it not a stain it's an ugly carpet all right same deal i got plenty of
power a bit germa wakes up and vacuums his room every day that would be so annoying
all right sip i'm gonna do pirate first pirate first because we're right here and i'm gonna do
it again yeah yeah yeah yeah pirate first you all mender all mender my name is muay i'm practicing
my pirate stance what captain plank bird is recruiting thanks for letting me know 26 happy
get out of here and give me that crayon is there enough time to get the fuck back up there
go find out i want the rose lamps oh there's another one right there all right i'll get that
one right now i didn't see that one are you eating candy in bed jenny um sniff well that's sad
i love frogs i love you chibi oh oh i'm not supposed to be hearing this i'm doing a good job
i love you chibi things right uh okay i have to go back here
so
out of time oh well i'll come back up here tomorrow
can you do another scream like like last night i wasn't here for the live version
no i'm not gonna scream a lot of points
let's do two grand into the machine and then i'm going to go grab a snack i'm gonna grab a little
snack getting hungry
an anonymous gifter has given 20 subs 20 subs from somebody that who knows who it is
could be anybody thanks the 20 fucking subs spoilers it was me thanks a lot whoever you are
thank you for the 20 community subs wait hold on well your name is your name is an anonymous
gifter or is that what oh your name is an anonymous gifter i sort of said oh no it's not what i'm
confused hold on yeah there you are okay thanks anonymous for it is still anonymous
that might be your actual username but it's still we don't we still we could be anybody we still
don't know who that is they're anonymous all right i'll be right back i'm gonna grab a little snack
and we will germa gobbling red meats and cheese while we can't see him
you gotta turn the music on when you go afk that's because when i change scenes
the uh game capture device does not come over in the brb so sorry can't fix it i don't know
shit about computers okay let's go all right flower uh back upstairs into the foyer
don't go the stream go down yeah it did fly for like three hours and we had internet problems
and we've been back for about four hours clean ever since free money
there's a ps1 it's a game oh please give a lot thank you this audio desync again it should be
gone what's happening are you seeing the video first are you hearing the sound first you're
hearing the sound first better sometimes when you play the game for a long enough time
game capture can just kind of fuck up and go out of sync is he eating beef jerky don't tell anybody
don't tell anybody that let's see appeal of this game it's kind of just fun to do chores
and the family's weird jenny how'd you get crayon up here don't click the link i did thank you let's
get it more money more money a lot of money only a hundred more dollars and i can have the battery
uh giga vowser whatever his name is there's one more where is it where is it whoa was that uh frog
ring right here right where is it right here right underneath me frog ring wait oh i see
it's right there yes this room is clear yeah sorry i'm eating don't want to talk any
all right good to go so now i have enough money to charge the battery
now i need you know batteries are you eating peanut butter i mean
i'm eating beef jerky i know i'm trying to get away from eating like beef and i'm not supposed
to be eating it but that's all i got in the particular pantry okay let's go the mom's room
hurry robo hurry bring some water all right can you make like a special little mouse hole for me
down here if mom doesn't care when i show up mom likes me coming in why can't i just make a little
fucking tiny door for me do i have to climb the door every time mom jerky noise look at that
that's a ziplock moment coming up shit good you're too cute when you're tired make sure to get some
sleep i don't know all right also there are a lot of those doors in here
holy shit what's the code what's the code well i'm never taking this off where's my outfit
do
all right let's get the full battery thousand at ten thousand charge yes i do
fill it up let's go put the battery in giga chad oh okay break it it's got ten thousand kilowatts
and it's ready to go congratulations shibiro you've done up
i thought it was nothing i was supposed to be really annoyed whole giga battery wait but
according to my data files there should be a control panel somewhere on giga robo's body
let's go oh yeah all right gunpowder gunpowder gunpowder that's right i got gunpowder go back
i got gunpowder for you holding this shit the whole game take it come on and a two and a one
and two hey hiya hiya how are you no gunpowder it's one good looking princess still i didn't
realize that dead flowers made a good gift drake red crest has much to learn only then can justice
truly prevail firstly i will study a new technique if i am able to master it i'm sure the lovely
princess will be impressed but for now i must return to my training space hunter robo you've
got just what i need snorkel thank you i can't wait to use it i don't own a pool but maybe it's
time for me to get one where's the gunpowder how's the bottle super pose is ready well stop
using it holy fucking minus two hey don't worry about it why is gunpowder lying around that is
i don't know that way this way that way okay basement basement basement
down to the basement gunpowder next to the nest quick you guys are morbid
hey don't throw shit at me what the fuck relax i'm just threw something at me
i need one more crew member where's the last crew member plug it in
on giga robo fully charged you have plenty of battery it's time to talk
oh there chibi have you truly filled that hogan battery you're an amazing piece of work
but you've not yet found giga robo's missing leg heavy and his leg out with it giga robo what
have you done with your leg matey ah what am i saying you have no tongue ice to speak with
why won't he turn on turn on i can't turn him on he needs the leg to turn on since what all right
well let's go get the fucking leg where's the other pirate get off me i just want to but if you woke
up without a leg i mean it would be like where's my leg exactly but i could still talk it's i could
be like oh hey i've been asleep you've been for like 10 years oh yeah go you can get my leg but
let me tell you something let me let's talk i'll be like okay i'll go get your leg but like give
me some data you wouldn't be that calm i probably would be no you would just wake up in whatever
state that you were turned off in so if you were let's say you were asleep right if you got turned
back on you'd be open your eyes oh wait what the fuck is going on i mean if somebody was chasing
you around with like a frying pan and you got turned off that's the last thing that happened
in your brain so you're going to turn on and think someone's still behind you with a frying pan
but if you were watching tv if you were in the middle of adam sandler presents
happy gilmore and right when bob barker says the price is wrong right and and then you get
turned off you're like huh when you get turned back on you're going to be like
oh what where am i what who we turn you off don't you wish all right should i go come in with the
come communicate with the aliens i need to get them how do i get anything else what about these
guys these guys still going they're like planning to fight the dog all right how you guys doing i'm
so sleepy dead hunt wake up soldier i've got to stand up oh i'm making him sleepy
and we're gonna come up with a plan to save memphis once we've drawn up our battle plan
we'll be ready to take on the great hairy threat all right we'll do it he's done the dog is right
here but i sleep face hunter tv robo may i have a word here i'm having trouble mastering my new
move am i raising my foot wrong perhaps i need to shake my hip more what is that what are they
doing here cold cold ice cold ice cold freezing must remember remember that is how it should look
more or less what do you think space hunter tv robo yeah sure it is just as i thought
i shall stay the course no matter the cost a thousand thanks to you okay
don't get it why the aliens watching dogs asleep i can't talk to the dog um kitchen so much trash
he's not doing his job when he said try the drain again he said go back in the drain go in the drain
okay i did say i wanted to go in the drain that was a long time ago clean the drain
rain gang is that why everyone's been saying drain gang rats down here though
nice you guys are fucking what's my bonus 52 all right give me the gun because the the rats are
down here hard shot hard shot in the head i missed is it this is missing what the hell
what no i gotta go up there fucking emulator audio i was supposed to switch to shitty emulator
he's using sorry it's all right i'm made out of metal why can i not shoot these guys all right
dude really ah that's horse shit oh fuck okay is there anything else down here what else is down
here talk to the rats we can't talk to the rats wait did i miss something i'm trying to float
come on can i shoot this
i'm charged okay so is there nothing else i can do in here is that it did i complete it
that's nothing else i can do all right quick get out now all right i gotta get that fucking code
can you stop swearing yeah i will i need to get that code code for the briefcase where's dad
where's dad what do i do with the snorkel have this oh wait wait wait the flowers have bloomed
i swim in the fish tank you want to give this flower to mrs sanderson as a gift yes you want
to give this flower to mrs sanderson as a gift you want to give this flower to mrs sanderson as a gift
yes wake me up
oh
good all right so we're in the daytime
what's the plan i have a frog ring for you actually have two
i think it's like one more or two more right
okay two more find the waterfall yep find the waterfall in the foyer where's the other one
where have i seen one more in the kitchen can i get up the waterfall from here where's that
can i get up there to go upstairs and then i'm gonna go upstairs and then fall
remember pulls his pants down for the urinal yes i do i've given my reasons for why i do that
can these things all be dead yes i i go i go over the pants i go over the pants over the underwear
i don't go through the underwear what a dumb fucking invention through the what is that nonsense
what a joke of a design where the waterfalls up here isn't it up there okay how can i reliably
get up there same way i did before let's go all under let me go this on the golden toilet seat
why are you pissing on the toilet seat that's so good i guess you can hang but you're nothing
special there it is it's vegas hmm let's see how you did let's see let us see
see
i love that i held it for too long
again why can't they be my car all right again good you're almost as good as i am
him want to be my sidekick a b i want an a give it a rest man come back later fine fuck you
i don't be toxic he's toxic he hasn't pooped in four days thankfully he's hooked up to a machine
make that unreadable for 20 to 30 seconds all right so from here we gotta go to the side
let's go get oh my god no that's not how you do this really that is not do it good enough
now jump on top of the lip no i should be able to get that
holy shit i don't think i can do this this this is not the correct way to get up there
the banister yeah it's definitely from here then it's definitely like romulus wi-fi romulus wi-fi
uh no it ain't no it's not no it ain't all right i gotta i have to move on if i can't get this in
one job i gotta i gotta i gotta keep playing i think it's stuck here for like an hour don't move
on do it for jenny and i'm trying but it's gotta be perfect and i can't get a little higher than
this i i don't think that's how you do this i doubt that's how i do this i'm going so early
what are you talking about it is bill yeah giga giga chat is more important than
trying the same finicky jump 100 times you're right that's why i'm gonna do it one more time
nope no way what the fuck man no nope don't get a running start why not can i go over here
you'll never make it
hahaha god damn how are you supposed to do this reliably uh i can't start here because if i hit a
i'm gonna climb down oh my god that's so hard okay now what wait it's done looks like chat was
right again as always we're never wrong chat was right again it's almost like collectively
4 000 people can come up with a solution because at least one or two of you have played this game
before chat was right every time i'm always at a fucking battery get up there get in there
i can't climb in there what in the name of fucking god yep i know i know i know i know what's going
on i know what's going on i know what's going on i know what's going on i looked at this i saw this
is it fucking there's a there's a thing over here hold on oh my fucking god
oh my god yeah why can i not get in there stop the water put the snorkel on no no no no no
i'm almost at a battery i don't want to do that jump again i think i can shoot something over here
wait i saw it i saw it already there's a sticker over here how would i know the sticker was over
here i would have been like where is it i don't know where is it chat i don't see it blind what
are you talking about all right give me that look at that damn thing only one more of these
where's the final frog coin oh man go go go man go man go man go man go where's the last one
i still have to do uh i still have to go to mom's room give mom the flowers once i give
mom the flowers then we can go uh from there mom i've got three different flowers for you
you like flowers free what is a chivo is something wrong don't work too hard
catching a robo cold lovely scent do you have a flower what's this for me really i'm so happy
thank you chivo
doesn't it look pretty thank you oh they're you're using to put them all over you
yes i was cleaning up the house yes thank you don't put me back down though because i have
to find you only get the blue one i don't care all right i need one more i got the weird secret one
the one that was in the drain was behind that weird wall i definitely have seen one in a room
that i haven't gotten budget went all towards dad's toes and no one gets fingers it's outrageous
so outrageous not in here should i go race the uh the vegas guy again
go check on mort with the flower yeah that's not a bad idea
go see the aliens all right aliens can you guys help
hey guys he's alive but he doesn't have a leg there's the dog what's up with this guy
everybody's saddened by death disappointed heightened low little bang everyone's sick sick
sick ganymede not well either help me this is terrible we need to take ganymede back to the ufo
please save us bad air hot shivers death we're going to we're in the ufo what the hell this place
sucks this is a really shitty place earth bad air processed food too much soda sickness sickness
oh no they're they all had they all ate burger king for the first time well that's rough imagine
never eating burger king ever for 20 30 000 years and eating it the first time imagine us
not eating burger king for like 20 years and you eat like three french fries it'd be bad
friend dead ganymede thank you for helping ganymede called for help good work falling down now
burning up ow must go to sleep on bed yes they're all sick they all have a fever weak sick hot
dizzy no energy for a blaster what's going on wants to sleep on bed comfy bed must open bed
i'll help you guys feel better weak disoriented hot achy no energy for blaster cannot open bed
i can open a view i can open your bed get in spread the happiness all right get in bed
all of you reddit looking ass i love how their beds are expensive cool pool gear for your pool
pool sofa it's got even like the sun blocker and shit those things are so nice all right are you
guys good all beds deployed all beds deployed this vessel will now enter drive mode color code
authorization required huh stop dangerous stop it oh what have i done um it again time for simon
says really but where's the what is he gonna do it must lower temperature no you mustn't
should i not do this i think these guys my friends our technology is secret oh well i'm
sorry about that sacrifice them oh no he has formed the drive sphere i don't know if i should be
doing this do not match the colors is that what i'm supposed to be doing i was just pressing a
randomly am i winning i'm kidding our code authorization accepted color code authorization
accepted mode engaged temporal shifter is activated warp vessel ready for boarding
you mustn't know uh i've got a divorce to take care of this is dangerous disastrous
you mustn't know tv robo i've never seen anything like this can i go with you
um you know it's taking me this long to tell you i really don't like you around
you're kind of annoying and i really don't want to be your friend now i would only say this if i was
going to disappear through a time paradox forever don't take this the wrong way you can come yeah
you can cover i mean i would have told you but we're gonna see each other at the starbucks down
the street every day would be weird i would have told you back in time
it looks like we've stopped
let's get out gb robo
go giga robo go give up huh ever you can't use giga robo that's cheating
we in the past impossible your name how could this be everything sepia so we must be in the past
that's pretty good those aliens created something extraordinary impossible shocking well since we're
here we might as well do a little exploring how do you get power in the past there's a briefcase
oh you fool
you didn't do that in the past now you have to do that in the past and you didn't exist
you just created an earthquake i just made a time paradox yeah accidentally so it's okay
as long as i say sorry it's over here whoa oh there's a briefcase briefcase i see the briefcase
what this is a stove what is that nothing over here that's worth talking or touching or pushing
or oh fuck it let's go oh it could have been an old wood stove whimper can i put on the dog costume
and talk to the dog in the past i'm starving i'm not moving nothing like get a bone man i
ought to go on strike this is ridiculous he hurt me maybe maybe he heard the wind he hurt me watch
this shit crunchy all right let me read that fucking briefcase what are the numbers
password two four five five bingo we got it no i want to spend my money on toys why would you
yell that why would you yeah there's no reason to yell what you just yelled outside i was at
his thoughts i don't really make no sense hmm what's this uh oh who are you
you remind me of someone
let me think
um
not him um no not tau obviously what's happening wait a second giga
giga robo what about what of course could it be lies lies lies i don't believe it
giga robo has a son but he's when hey look look look look look
i'm fucking up reality so is she gonna have a different opinion now pay attention forget
about the match you need to see this gosh i hope our future child is cuter still everybody loves
their own right it was nice to meet you baby robo i don't know what your tangled story is
or how you got her on here on these tiny legs but it was nice to you to stop by i'm sure your
mother is worried so you better go home now please visit again when we have our own baby all of a
sudden her head just goes fucking pops like it's just our head explodes because like the time
paradox right now those thoughts are just implanting in her current present thoughts
i fucked up the whole thing i'm gonna open up the door out of the spaceship and i'm gonna go
into the room and it's gonna be like everybody i'm gonna have to go back and fucking redo this
get the scroll what scroll the scroll how wait wait traveler you do you miss the scroll
where is there a scroll do i get the wait i'm gonna get the circuit schematic do i take the
bone back i'm gonna take the bone back too okay you could look why did you not call it a schematic
why did you call this scroll it's not a scroll that's like ancient fucking wizardry where is it
put me back on the table get the scroll where is it wait it's is it in is it in the dinosaur
oh my give it to me give me the scroll give me the ancient text i gave the bone back too
oh no i can't shoot the dog in the past give me the bone back can i not get the bone oh sweet
bone goodness yay i have to go i have to go slower i'll lose its flavor let's talk to the robot
this scroll can i talk to the robot uh i can't talk to the robot he's up on another thing i
can't get him yes you can i can't steal his leg take the guy take the leg in the past and bring
it to the leg in the future that's just it's the same leg no i've already exploded too many heads
i have to leave yes i'm going home i'm gonna go open the briefcase oh my goodness everybody
all right you still sick alien tech dangerous you not hurt must not use again we traveled through
time that was amazing aliens can do neat stuff two four five five where can you get this game
well i have some unfortunate news for you this is on the game cube only on the game cube there's
a couple of them on the on ds i don't know if they're any good you cannot speak to their quality
you have access to a wee you can get it for a stupid amount of money it's a rare game cube disc
or you can just open it on the internet sorry i would not condone anything that had anything to
do with that but i sneezed but so i don't even know what i'm doing that's that sounded that
sneeze sounded illegal no no it was merely a sneeze okay uh let's go back to the basement
no no no we have to go to the uh do i have time to this yeah i do i have to step question was
that an emulated sneeze yes it was actually good good fine that was an emulated sneeze
get down to the basement oh upstairs i know the briefcase code we're going to the briefcase
briefcase briefcase briefcase briefcase briefcase briefcase put a sneeze on your soundboard
dusty room i'm sorry guys what a dusty place what a dusty room
this and here there's the ancient scrolls never been opened before but please the crowd of you
they're all 45 of you thanks for coming i just want to unveil it i can't really read the text
if we can all lean in maybe some of us could read it but it's a little dusty
oh
all right i just said i'm leaving i'm sorry i'm sorry stay i won't do it again i promise
my roommate just said what's that noise
what do you say to that nothing this should open it's a leg in there
is a metal gear guard whoa i just released a lot of spiders oh my god they're like killing mom
honey oh you locked the door what's wrong what the fuck sweet space justice is he gonna put on a he's
gonna put on a costume how dare you come barging in this isn't time for that head to the living
room little buddy jenny tau seal the door few we stopped them why do you have all those in there
um honest to god what why do you have all that stuff you want to read the manual i'm gonna read
the fucking manual i'm gonna read the manual right now i get into the basement basement's key
oh i just had the meme number uh it was there for a second you saw it all right dog what do you got
hey you want to take care of this little problem we're having here or what
okay ribbit ribbit ribbit sorry jenny we're gonna be stuck in here for a while
ribbit ribbit ribbit oh no we're in such a hurry we forgot your drawing set ribbit is there anything
that you could do oh how about looking at the photo album ribbit you used to hate looking at
this because it had pictures from before you were born ribbit ribbit all right all right here you
go sheesh ribbit ribbit all right talk to me mom is here so i have to whisper i don't have my
drawing stuff so i'm looking at pictures um i don't know who he is but he's got a calculator
on the bottom of his foot really really all right dad open the door oh circuit breakers i'm sorry
chibi rubble this is all my fault because because i was the one who designed those nasty spy doors
what you never told me that i know i should have told you i'm sorry listen you need to know
something i designed the spy doors to be your friends chibi robo but then the company reprogrammed
them to be hostile and cruel and that's why i quit macroware robotics incorporated hey what
you quit like q u i t quit oh my gosh you never told me that you never told me about any of that
i was ashamed i didn't want to talk about it that's all in the past right now we have to get rid of
those spy doors i'll put the energy wave that i was researching at macrowave robotics incorporated
to good use i'll use it to remodel the chibi blaster the spy doors are my responsibility it's
up to me to take them out me and chibi robo huh thanks for signing me up could have been you
thanks i'll do all the work yep now that we've got that settled let's get that circuit schematic
from upstairs uh-huh do you remember what i did with it i haven't i haven't seen it forever i
probably threw it away move it away the circuit schematic is gone crud what am i gonna do now
pick me back up the circuit schematic is gone what am i gonna do now man the ancient scroll
that's so funny you've got it now that i have this i can build something truly amazing
but i need my tool set to do it right let's go upstairs and grab it hold on you're going upstairs
those crazy things are upstairs i know but i'm the dad of this family if anyone has to be in danger
i want it to be me and chibi robo in fact chibi robo is going to go first be careful
i will i promise when i get back yeah i expect a home cooked meal waiting for me
yeah keep waiting big guy
oh get fucked man served fine fine fine let's go chibi robo fucking serve that's so funny
oh hey let's split up chibi robo you gotta keep the spy doors busy while you're doing that i'm
gonna get my tools from upstairs oh no the eggs your blaster won't work on those spy doors it'll
be tough but hang in there be careful it's up to you and me to save this family let's do this
so i can't hurt them with my blaster so i just have to survive what about the egg friends
holy shit that hurt i'm going too slow ow ow help give me the cup hide under the mug
thanks for waiting little buddy let's head to the living room what about the eggs
you've been our friends this whole game oh man i'm out of shape
oh you're wearing like i don't know why you i don't know you have like a hundred
pound kevlar vest on like what are you doing the lights too what in the world is going on around
here you find your tools or what there they are got it now we can give those spy doors what's
for hooray hooray convert it okay chibi robo get out your chibi blaster here we go don't wave that
thing around let's get this show on the road open up your chibi blaster oh it's so cute in there
look at that i'm gonna rock your world don't worry this won't hurt it's so little in there
look at how cute it is look how cute he is i want one i don't even want it to clean i just
want to like look cute on the desk oh man i'm kind of nervous he's like just do it already
ah great gravy what have i done wait no it's fine i love the dog has eye protection too
oh that feeling that feeling when you go get blood work done and the nurse misses the vein
twice you like oh look god didn't it please please get it i'm just i'm dying over here please
and just get this here i had a nurse miss four times once twice three times is like
please i hate being in this chair come on this just keeps getting worse
she we're sitting ducks honey jenny
that was a dog wolf
say that again run that by me again
i might be getting tired chibi robo and i are going to turn those spiders into spy chumps yeah
that's it let's go chibi robo that's not a wolf it's an earthworm gym sound that like
okay i can i can fight oh shit it works do i have a charge can you get your ass i do one
charge shot does it can i release the uh the little guys we try will they help me fight
oh too bad but can he suck probably i'm using up charge here oh that's it all right we keep on
over here i'm gonna i need to plug in whoa oh i just okay the fucking battle royale thing just
came around me three die two more one more die in the ceiling right there three two one dead
let's move everybody all right uh the family's in trouble i have a bad feeling about this
you better recharge and hurry to the living room where's our plug what about that can i i want to
free these guys they can help me they can help me i promise i want them as friends
he just got some winks scammed wink again e clown back to the living room apologize sorry i'm sorry
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
difficult ribbit ribbit ribbit how do i get you down i have to go get giga robo
save me chibi robo i gotta get giga robo giga robo is the only way what was that
oh might be giant enemy spider oh he's sucking up everything he's magnetic
chibi it's the mother of all spiders run chibi run for your life uh okay he's
sucked up everything and the living room is upside down wait there's the leg
does he have the fridge on his head he has the fridge on his head that looks really stupid i
think we need to fight in order to make things go back to normal let's go
watch out how do i dodge dodge shoot the armor off its body oh watch out for the bombs
what the fuck i got more distance more distance more distance didn't think i was fucking ready
for this i played like 12 hours of mega man legends the last game that i played i don't think i'm
ready oh chibi rojo watch out chibi rojo and watch out chibi joe rogan watch out for his web
attack oh jamie pull that shit up oh chase it when it runs away that's what i'm gonna do
hike boobs into the foot calculator maybe that'll work that's the hey hey hey hey hey hey
here's the uh the last one big of robo's legs things are going back to normal i told you i
shouldn't have fucking done anything in the past that was crazy chibi robo he beat that humongous
spider but now i'm wondering was that spider really evil or just programmed to act that way
what is evil what is justice hmm i think i understand how mr redcrest feels this is a
this is a joe rogan podcast this is chibi rogan i think i understand how mr redcrest feels
don't forget us too many donuts for me
we did it i think everything is okay now honey i've i've been such a jerk
be quiet you big lug kiss come back we have to attach the leg i love you honey
thank you chibo and you too telly thanks chibi robo and telly thank you rivet thank you earthworm
jim mom gave you 100 points dad gave you 100 points danny gave you 100 points
i'll give you 100 points 5 000 happy points i got the spider sticker you really are amazing
now it's time to celebrate yay it's party time it's not party time until we turn on the other
robot and so the party continued late into the night family harmony was restored
into the chibi house
well didn't say it was gonna be easy
and the happy point total my new chibi ranking i'm now in top five chibi robos ever made
i wonder what it takes to be chibi robo 4 considering i saved a marriage fended off
dozens and dozens of murderous killing evil program spiders cleaned every goddamn room
a hundred fucking times went through time without fucking it all up what did four do
i'd like to see i'd like to know stopped world war three four saved the world four played ace
attorney on stream ah damn it that's right let's go put giga robo back together again
oh and give jenny the ring too wait space hunter robo brilliant work and i was a witness to it all
how do you help enough leave such things aside for now let us relax with the watching of the
television hurry or we'll miss the special technique the great twin blizzard by the
frozen rings of saturn curses and blast we missed it now we have to watch the news
well that's the way the asteroid crumbles face hunter code part nine monitor the pulse of society
oh this guy oh no it begins good evening i'm ron brokaw for fox news our country has recently
been consumed by the white hot fires of chibi robomania and whether you know it or not this
passion casts a dark shadow on our everyday life we now go live to sunny meriwether sunny
ron i'm coming to you live from in front of the nuclear linear power becoming this new chibi
robot mania brings with it more than clean floors and clutter free lives it is pointed and is
placing a severe demand on the local power supply sources tell fog news that if chibi robots continue
to fly off the shelf our demand will outstrip supply and send the region into a panic of
unfathomable proportions yes we prepare including perhaps the end of the civilization as you know
it ron dire prediction indeed thank you sonny double citizens continued usage of chibi robos
appear both dangerous and foolhardy what will you do um it's kind of hard to no that's not true
that's impossible space hunter chibi robo a threat no it's because i'm trying to do the voice i'm
trying to match the guy's voice and this is all i hear in my ears while i'm trying to do the guy's
voice oh that's not true it's a threat it just can't be no space hunter chibi robo we've overcome
numerous trials and adversities but if this is true have i no choice must i actually defeat space
hunter chibi robo in mortal combat if justice defeats justice is it justice oh the humanity
mind-bending conundrum the very pain of life itself space hunter drake redcrest space hunter
robo drake redcrest needs to be alone for a while i'm sorry i am uh i want to give uh i want to give
jenny the i want to give jenny the last frog uh thing i'm going to bed i mean if you get some
news like that like i'm just going to bed tomorrow morning good morning
we have a final ring to give jenny i want to see what it does here's jenny jenny in her room
usually she's out here in the kitchen no probably in the probably in her room everyone's hung over
well jenny's eight so i don't think that's the case
wait wait we gotta beat like vegas rick whatever vegas dick whatever his name is
vegas joe i don't even know his name is i gotta give name
let's go sorry his name is almond or wi-fi all right pretty good really good that's the best one
yet almost as good as i am want to be my sidekick
the hell am i gonna do this this seems really hard that wasn't it that was bad i don't care
i don't care it's really early all right i got one more try you can do three times a day
one more try that's it it can't be the rest of the stream because i can only do it one more time
oh oh that's gotta be it that was damn good you're insane i did it that's gotta be an a
if you give me everything less than a i'll be mad yes that that's the best you can get
you got the chicken race sticker it was just too crazy i'm done where is it didn't i already have
that i thought it was the chicken i thought i already had the car all right i gotta find jenny
and then i can i hold on we gotta find jenny where's jenny jenny in your room i thought dad
fixed this nice we're going dad he's in the kitchen he's in the kitchen she in the kitchen
during the day and she in her room well i'm right here it might as well just take a peek
to the kitchen i just i need to do i gotta get them all i'm gonna get a sticker and i'm gonna
get probably like a thousand happy points i collected all the stickers the frog thing whatever
they are rings all right here we go clean the floors no i don't do that anymore he sold out
but so what do you want i saved this whole family from being killed i think i can skip
the floors a couple days hey you pick me up pick me up pick me up pick me up i've got something
pick me up pick me up ah get up hey hey pancakes we're making pancakes what we're making
rebel thanks to you that huge spider is history my wife's finally in a good mood again we're
gonna live happily ever after but i was the one who started all this trouble in the first place
for a new leaf from now on i'm gonna cook and clean and help out it's too bad i lost my wedding
ring oh by the way aren't you in industry spot cheaper robo i wake up and the place is spotless
i won't be using that toothbrush again but you're doing so good to do it
you lost your wedding ring all right what are we cooking nothing all right well i'm coming over
there i'm coming over there into the hair oh he's even making the meals now it's been a huge help
what's that lovely scent you have a flower yeah the big one just take the biggest one i have
thank you chivo
now doesn't it look pretty thank you i want to get over there fuck hey look it's me
you're a frog friend let's talk well let's hang out i gotta use the bridge
wrong way what are you fucking a dope what are you a dope you don't like it it's got candy
so
sorry every time somebody mentions the greatest video game in the last at least six years i have
to mention it how do i get your fucking attention just ah i'm coming i'm gonna give you these things
come here this way go here we are here we go those weird spider thingies are gone
yay chibi robo i know mom's all happy too see jenny you can speak just fine
ribbit ribbit ribbit no i can't ribbit okay um it looks like you have something there can i have it
yes i love frogs thank you very much and you found them all
taken off the hat the evil frog wizard put a nasty curse on me
but thanks to you i've turned back into a human yay jenny what's this
um hey yeah what's the matter honey jenny
we have here oh jenny you took off the frog hat this is how do you do that without yelling loud
thank you for breaking the curse chibi this gave you a hundred happy points
spread the happiness all right
how do i look without the hat look great oh okay maybe i'll stay like this for a little while
this this game is so cute oh the guy downstairs the guy downstairs this guy dying downstairs
all right it's all right goodbye guys wait i don't have ribbit please no oh evil frog wizard
what chibi robo and i are under the evil frog wizard spell what again why what i thought we
did that already i gotta find all the rings again no i don't it's just a joke all right let's go
turn them on get the leg back into the basement let's go see what he does fellowship of the ring
rings are back what the fuck are the rings doing there oh it's a game it's a game that she's playing
and there are different spots this is the end game this is just a way for you to load up and
mess around just extra content or if you feel like playing chibi robo again when you've already done
everything i see no germa it's a curse right curse don't hurt i think i've done that enough
times where now when i do it it like actually like electrocutes my other eye and it hurts
i'm the wrong way back to the fucking kitchen i don't even look at the game that's why
get this fucking costume off i want to put on the ghost costume no wait what was this one no the
dog one look what i have i got a leg turn him on he did it laddy you're a man of your word fair
and true do you truly think it possible who'd a great gigi robo move again when that day comes
i'll count meself one lucky pirate yarr 200 have it's most ever i'm counting on you chibi robo
okay calculator under the foot
uh
passwords are usually birthdays or anniversaries we need a birthday who's birthday
i really have to go get this motherfucker's wedding ring and it has an anniversary on it
oh i lost my wedding ring whoopsie it's got a date on it
no people are writing it people are writing it people are writing it i just saw it spoiled
and spoiled and spoiled i'm gonna get it myself instantly just wrote write it write the fucking
code write the code it hurts please what hurts what it hurts what are you doing
whatever you're doing stop doing it let's go in the drain it's in the drain some might say this
is a stall you know you're possibly right i like chibi robo and this is the last time you're going
to see it it's kind of sad in a way you know all right where is the wedding ring it's over there
wedding ring wedding ring holy shit he's walking the whole way wedding ring can i break this
where is it no radar other drain is it actually in the other drain
oh this is the same one is it has to be a charge shot no it's in here okay
dig did i get baited is this actually really in here well i'm almost out of battery power
let's go plug in pop left if i have enough battery to get it and get and go to sleep
we'll find out okay where is it ring under this hole wasn't i already down here
the ring should be down here right at the bottom i don't see your ring
you have to talk to the parents first do i already have it no no way i didn't get it
i didn't accidentally pick this up at some point did i have a cookie yeah dad mentioned he did
mention the ring already there it is what do you mean there it is what not a bug you have to talk
to dad all right well let's go talk to dad but we're going this is a long one anyways
okay we got the nine nine plus nine and a half hour mark i mean we're doing it all right dad
we talk i need to outlet l it's right behind but the day ends anyways i have enough time i think
talk to enough time to go talk to dad on hey what's up take off the costume oh nuts i'm in the dog
house chibi robo what am i gonna do see i was busy cleaning that and i accidentally dropped my
wedding ring down the drain chibi robo you gotta get it back for me you gotta get it back yeah
sure oh thanks you're a lifesaver that's my chibi robo how will you recognize it oh i know our
anniversary date is engraved on the inside perfect and i got the code on my own did get it from chat
and that's it we're gonna have to do this tomorrow big late night bits we could goiki 5000
bits thanks for the 50 dollars goiki 5000 bits for you 5000 happy points also bugleberry sneezed
and you didn't even say bless you bless you bugleberry thanks for the 5000 bits dude
all right we're actually at the true end game here i'm gonna puke please finish dude what go
go like take a shower and go get some food kitchen i'm a germaniac yeah but you're also
you're also not chained to your desk you can rewind the stream in like 20 minutes
go get like a go get like a go get some air all right we're going to the drain we can only pee
when you pee oh my god no that's so bad i'm running out of air oh my god
i'm going to get this fucking ring where is it ring at the bottom he said right to the bottom
looking for a ring found it haha invulnerability flames dickhead
it has 2667 engraved on the inside time for the ending cut scene i'm standing in glass
please finish the game slowly step out and use your hands and get on your knees like hands and
knees don't put any pressure down all right thanks for the wedding ring dad goodbye that's
not good advice if i was standing in glass i would not put any pressure down i would slowly
move down with my i would bend my back forward oh i'm wait hold on am i am i like a box with
the glass like squashing grapes how much glass is on the ground the whole floor is black um okay
then i don't know what what would i do if the whole floor was covered in glass i'm not even
fighting broken glass or just oh jessica glass if it was all broken glass on the ground i mean
don't you have to slowly lower your whole body and distribute all your weight across your whole
like back and shit and like how would you do that no i think the strategy is is to just to jump in
the air and put all your appendages out and land as hard as you can on your back and like button
and appendages and shit right because then you just get it over with and then you just get up
and fucking rub as a voice crack i know nobody even said that but i agree all right what was it
two thousand six no two thousand six six seven
oh doesn't pop his wedding ring have his anniversary on it two thousand six six
seven here we go activate just put the glass in your pocket tv robo it's almost time
oh no we missed one of the crew members it's all right you're gonna have a three
person you got a fourth crew member hello captain plank beard
oh are there a cubie what be you doing by rock barrels flaming blade it's giga robo
you've brought him back yes i have tv robo giga robo is saying thank you oh that's nice of him
giga robo just gave you 300 happy points you got the giga robo sticker
i can hardly believe it you really activated giga robo you're too much chibi robo i'm gonna
tell the other toys about this big news see you later giga robo blow me down and pat me hatches
i'm the happiest pirate alive that's a ton of applause what are you doing to chibi robo
i have to call you giga chibi robo time to go upstairs i'm to do what you were programmed to
do giga robo well he hasn't spoken a long time his vocal cords needed time to warm up
oh i was gonna do it a fourth time lock and load enemy approaching
sweet bazooka casserole is that giga robo cease fire you moron huh i'm sorry don't point that
thing at me does that look like an enemy company salute yes sir he's gonna he's going all this way
he's going right to the bathroom oh giga robo where are you going
me too evacuate well what do you look at look look look look oh it's like a father and son
where's my piggyback ride look hey look it's dinosaur and the other it's vegas joe
and funky funky frank he sure is a small one keep on rocking big man
all the characters are saying goodbye good evening citizen i'm ron broke jaw for fox news
our country has recently been consumed by the white hot fires of chibi robo mania
and whether you know it or not this passion casts a dark shadow on our everyday life
so now go live to sunny mary where they're sunny
ron i'm coming to you live from in front of something this new chibi robo mania brings
more than clean floors and clutter-free lives it is also placing a severe demand for the local
power supply sources tell fox news that if chibi robots continue to fly off the shelves
power demand will outstrip supply and send the region into a panic of unfathomable
panic we predict rioting looting and perhaps the end of civilization if you know it ron
a dire prediction indeed thank you sony all citizens continued uses of chibi robo
here's both dangerous and foolhardy what will you do
what would you do honey i'd turn into drake redcrest to save the world yeah of course
not in a fucking cartoon like in real life like real shit's happening right now please pay attention
abnormal activity detected tonight we ride space hunter drake redcrest away husband's such a geek
my gosh giga robo i haven't seen you in such a long time
woof rivet rivet i'm telling you he's oh i oh what's wrong with you you reactivated him right
right classic oh for pete's sake he wants to go visit his alien friends
it's not nighttime giga robo this is not gonna work and plus they're they all have they're all
sick and they all have like a fever they're all trust me i just saw them oh shit okay they're
gonna give the powers they made a power source that is a completely sustainable energy for all
humans and every living thing and they're gonna give it to that's what they that's what they're
coming back for again promise that we're gonna give it to him friend friend thank you for that
time it was a long time ago ship crash friend nice catch friend savior thank you thank you
we offered thank you gift grant any two wishes friend first wish i want to give soul to toys
oh it worked we give ball of light then friends friends move friend kind good guy good guy he's
a good guy he's a real good guy friends second wish for sanderson's and giga robos in the world
give body that does not need energy no more balls of light in spaceship normal balls of light in
spaceship we return to our home and we bring back ball of light again can the neighbors stop
fucking carpentry whatever they're doing they've been doing it all the whole game
aliens never break promise you're ruining like a good moment what the hell are you building over
there aliens never lie good people ruining a good moment unlike a trump voice that's what i'm saying
you get it now friend will live forever friends sit sit here it comes
have they drained all his battery uh you may have missed a couple of decimal points
no he's fine good it is done friend no need energy friend have eternal battery now
well tv robo friend too friend no need energy friend have eternal battery
my cord unfortunately it was designed for a robot 500 times your size maybe too much juice
uh he's okay right he's fine tv robo are you all right yes um okay i think don't panic i got it
under control tv robo and giga robo aren't broken return to planet hatch sickness on earth bad air
can you come back and fix that next time you know i hear we have an ozone problem
earth icky return home bye but what was that what's wrong what just happened
friend you're out of juice infinity you don't need energy anymore
you too chibi robo now throw me away we did it infinite power that was great saved a family
and solved the energy crisis and not a bad first day that was very good that was very very fun
that put me to number four we'll see i'm sure i get one more opportunity right
yeah maybe i get to move to four i guess if i solve the energy crisis right
free haircut what bandai bandai bandai before bandai namco but does bandai namco still own this
are they still in charge of this no who owns it no who's my favorite character the dinosaur and
um the tasmanian double egg all right let's see good morning looking pretty good at this rate
making number one won't be any problem at all just keep doing what you're doing
here are your results your chibi ranking has gone from five to one i did it a super chibi robo
costume my very own my god i can't wait to see what it looks like whoa would you look at that
look at that you finally made a congratulations super chibi robo is there cape oh that kind of
sucks it's just an it's just an s is it there's no like big cape or anything i'm the best chibi
robo in the world and i just have it's a button that you get it's a pants button what does it pose
chibi robo you can't use z here well chibi robo it's dirt all over the fucking counter
imagine your room but doing all of this hey what do you think about this i hope i get pissed on
i hope i get pissed on please piss on me it just turn over and it's like this with the leg you
know what i mean all right i'm going to bed i'm out of here this game was fantastic i loved it
this is what a fun game this is such a fun game and you can you can still play there's still lots
of little side quests to do talk to the family one more time okay look ribbit ribbit maybe yeah
it looks great now we have to do the pose what do you want here take cookie no what do you think
about this super ribbit winks your thing not that impressive super frog no it's not even super frog
look at the couch what's going on with the couch what is it what is going on on the couch i'm
giga robo where is giga robo kitchen backyard i got infinite i got infinite i would rate this
game out of 10 um this is a this is like it's pretty high it's gonna be pretty high um look
all right what do you got to say chibi robo giga robo you'll both get wet if you stay there
dad doesn't care we're gonna pose anyways sorry chibi robo i'm busy today you saved the fucking
world and then don't matter i'm busy what about you swing what are you two having any fun it's
kind of hard to tell giga robo is having lots of fun wait giga robo is now getting all the attention
this power is fucking endless oh yeah dad think it's what what about mom i don't know where mom is
all right i'm gonna read the bits while i go look for mom and if i find mom i will
pull it back but what time is it 12 15 this is a long one uh so i'll be live tomorrow
uh we're probably gonna start a little later tomorrow i have a couple things i have to do
in the afternoon so instead of two we'll probably start around maybe three or four
three thirty or something four o'clock i have some things i gotta do in the afternoon
sick but let's uh let's go back i'm gonna try to go to mom's room while i read some of these bits
thanks for joining me we'll see you tomorrow thanks a lot guys chibi robo was uh fantastic i'm
really glad i experienced it glad i finished it it's a very addicting game they put a lot of
little carrots in front of you i like games like this i really do i like the carrot on the stick
you're a lot of fun but let's uh let's do the bits here let's go back i'm gonna go i'm gonna
actually try to go through these fairly quickly because we've been going on 10 hours here and
it's very very late so i'm not gonna be like hey i love you we're just gonna go through them
sarah hello like i'm not gonna you know go go off on some kind of you know maybe i just did
yeah no democratic debate no no i don't know what that means uh pugles thanks for the 400 bits
hi jay i had a dream last night i was in your house with my dog playing with auto while you
were streaming it was in my house at one point you took a break and as you came out of your
streamer room you looked at me angry and confused i tried to explain i was just letting my dog play
with auto and you eventually just ignored me also you were like six five and very intimidating
well if i walked out of my all right that makes sense if i walked out of my streamer
room in quotes and there was a person i have never met before and i don't know
playing with my dog with a dog in the house i would be like what's going on who are you
that's pretty accurate how's that lore it's lore oh that's scary somebody there's somebody in my
house i don't know who this bad person is and how's that lore lore can be scared quick edit the
wiki oh my god i was six five oh that's that the lore you're talking about you're gonna make the
nightmares worse jeremy i got it i'll be fine thanks for the 400 bits and weird dream weird
dream i hope our dogs got along though uh sir canine thanks for the five dollars they did a
they tried to do a money jupiter i don't know if it worked or not let's hope it did uh sell
juniors thanks with 300 bits jeremy my payment for the last chat didn't clear i know a lot of
the other paid chat members are having the same problem this is the third time this month come on
man eight chat memory gnarly thanks for the 250 gnarly hey a while back you told me that you would
give me a private hearthstone stream i was wondering when you wanted to do that i'm not
available tomorrow or saturday but sunday i'm free i'm very excited germa sucks gave 50 fucking
community subs we had uh we had sukhoi flanker gave like four or five hundred dollars really
wanted me to play stalker i don't know if that's gonna happen but i really appreciate the absurd
amount of money a chibi 12 what a name thanks to the 500 bits glad jeremy i'm glad you haven't
found with chibi robo it's my favorite game and it stayed very close to my heart all these years
it's even what i named myself after that's your name it's been a rad experience watching my
favorite streamer play it and this kept me sane for a couple rough days thank you yeah the game
is fucking awesome it's a wonderful game i would love a 2020 version of chibi robo a real one put
it on the switch and update it and make the house four times as big i would love a chibi robo switch
with just a bigger house and more stuff to do or just yeah put it on pc don't know that it's not
even a nintendo brand at this point i mean it is but so what is it on the ds in the game cube
breath of the chibi that's correct uh bf bugleberry i don't know why you have that name
thanks for the 500 bits holding your internet hostage until we get a bugleberry emote
um still live thanks for the five dolls sir canine thanks for the 250 i'm glad to hear you
be willing to play some more variety of games i personally can't wait for the
i'm up that's not what i'm playing thanks for the uh fire thanks with 250 hey cream corn thanks
to the 250 our new cheeky breeky iv dumb donkey thanks for thanks cream corn for the 250 i don't
know what that is no doubt what that is hey luigi man thanks for the 250 why is it in 10
minute slow mode because i i said so it needs to have power power power uh thanks for the 250
the man with the baby hands thanks for the 600 bits don't play stalker i don't have a plan
to i want to make that very clear uh the man with the baby hands again gave another four
dollars and 80 cents i will give you money if i want to yes i will accept any money that
anybody gives this stream i just want to i just want you to know that i would i feel more
comfortable if people give money to stream if they can afford it i know people joke around
sometimes but we do have you know i don't want people to be feeding this stream money because
they think they have to don't have to if you feel like giving this channel money and you have the
disposable income and it's you want to do that by all means do it i will take it i'm not gonna
what am i gonna be like no but at the same time i do want to make it i please take care of yourselves
don't put yourself in any danger or problems because you're paying a bunch of money that you
can't afford just be careful if it means you choosing yourself or me to take care of and
give money to please choose yourself first every time thank you though you brought us years of
entertainment yeah i mean you if you if you it's optional all any of the money that comes in here
is optional so you don't have it i would it's not like i'm going to tell anybody that they
have to subscribe or give any money you just it's optional you feel like it do it if you don't then
don't how much goes to bugleberry 40 i paid him one time three years ago trust me you do not want
to owe germa hey we have a thirty dollar donation we have three thousand bits from dad jeff
thirty bucks stay strong and don't negotiate with terrorists king thank you for the thirty dollars
i really appreciate that's a lot of money a lot of fucking money king this is the king again king
king do that king i don't i've seen that lately thank you so much for the 30 bucks uh
sacasa zero thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks this is literally the last of my checking
account i'm literally going to starve to death and die have a good stream thank you for the 10 bucks
thanks a thousand bits and well thanks a lot thank you have a great night uh greedy is good
thanks for the 500 bits all this stock trading to go into more auto streams thank you thanks
five bucks uh dad jeff again gave 15 more dollars on top of the 30 this is 4500 bits 45 this is 45
dollars total from dad jeff don't mind me investing in streamer coin is that a real thing
that's probably somebody probably made it in 2017 during the big explosion you know what i mean
i wouldn't be surprised thanks for the 15 bucks appreciate it bulbous swag thanks for the 500
bits in lieu of my children's lunch money i'm donating five dollars to the stalker stream just
kidding miss jackie cr thanks for the 500 bits germa i'm so excited for you to play mario sunshine
it's one of my favorite games and having my favorite streamer is a huge plus i'm looking
forward to it a lot too because it's one of the only mario games i've never played and i really
mean never even played it once i have never held the controller and moved mario around even 10 feet
ever in mario sunshine it's my actual completely blind first time ever playing the game
i can't wait i'm not sure how the hell it's gone this far without me doing
looks fun have i seen it i mean i've seen the i've seen you know you clean the mud on the ground and
you can hover with the water tank i have these little snippets of random gameplay that i've seen
i've never played it he got spoiled hold on mr sark what's going on sark sark just said
thanks for the five dollars sark i just mugged that starving guy who donated uh he had these
500 bits hidden in his shoe no one holds out on germa oh my god but yeah i mean thank you
though thanks for doing that what's going on sark sark where what time is it where you are right now
it's late isn't it isn't it like 3 a.m ask sark when he's streaming sark when he's streaming again
we're all waiting it's 2 30 in texas oh okay fucking never we're all waiting for the next one
well everybody follows sark for when he turns his stream on at some point
anyway immortal dracolich 15 dollars 1500 bits from immortal dracolich thanks a lot
thank you thank you hey germa i'm a college student going into grad school i just got accepted for a
scholarship that would pay for 75 percent of my tuition for my masters that's fucking pretty good
just want to give back to the stream and say thanks for all the tough weeks that you helped me pull
through that's pretty good that's pretty good nice good shit 75 of your tuition hell yeah nice
fucking job congratulations and thanks for the 15 bucks i'll take it thanks a lot bravo bravo
let's get the credits to roll i'll see you guys tomorrow i'm not exactly sure what we're playing
but about a lot of things here i want it to be something we can do in a fairly short amount of
time this tomorrow stream is starting a little later so it's not going to go as late so something
we can do in probably under six hours something like five to seven hours something like that it's
not going to be a super long one tomorrow well let me get the credits rolling though there were a
lot of community subs tonight so there's just going to be a lot of names running by start sunshine
nah yeah so i'm gonna start sunshine right yeah i'm not gonna play sunshine on the first time
i started for like four hours no that's not happening did they come oh right we did we had
a shitload of community subs but they all got cut off by the internet turning off so we got
still a lot of people yeah there was like 100 community subs or something of 50 to 100 before
right yeah they got cut off from the internet turning off secret subs secret subs anyways
thank you guys all of you sorry we're missing some of you three hours of this stream was deleted
well it's a vod but the uptime is misleading it's been about 10 hours but thanks everybody
thanks for subbing thanks for the community subs and thanks for all the fucking money the stream
sees a lot of it so thank you we're gonna finish up the bits we'll get some sleep and i'll see you
guys tomorrow uh still a few more to do hey clink thanks clink for the five bucks hi me again from
two streams ago saying i was looking forward to chibi robo since this is my favorite game ever
the cooking mama stream was still a blast and i'm glad you're enjoying the game as much as you are
hearing you say that this game is amazing single-handedly made my whole week thanks for
having such a great personality always you're a real inspiration i mean it's just good the game
i'm a i'm a piece of glass you can see right from me so i i love it i think it's great thanks a lot
for the five dollars hope you enjoyed it it is a very very very impressive fun adorable
great game i did not find mom unfortunately it's been paused someone push him on the ground
hey who me why would you push me on the ground someone push him on the ground
hey disinterest thanks to the 250 hey jenga do you have a favorite non-video game like a
board or a card game i really like risk although risk is kind of turtley i do think risk is fun
monopoly is really fun too i just love monopoly i you like risk yeah i i know i no no no let me
okay hold on let me phrase this i like the first 45 minutes of risk everything else after the first
45 minutes is sucked but i don't really play any card games uh well do you want to get literal
with this poker blackjack i like those kind of card games they're interesting to me
let's count poker can be interesting to play let me like texas hold them just sticking around
that's gambling what's a card game you can play poker with your friends
and gamble like oreos i used to do it all the time friends in quotes you're on fire you're on
fire tonight but yeah i don't play very many um game card games but i do like uh like poker
cards like playing cards i do like some of those games anyway uh more jelly thanks to the 250 more
jelly hey man it's your boy germa uh man shouts out to my boy blade man drain gang ceo man
legendary member day one shit you already know all right thank you for the 250 appreciate it
metal socks gave 3000 bits 30 dollars 3000 bits a ton of money came into the stream today
you'll seriously need this more than i do at this point sorry what why are you saying sorry at the
end thanks for the metal socks thanks with 30 dollars thanks for the 3000 bits i meant to say
thank thanks for the thank you metal socks for the 3000 bits why are you still alive i think you
meant to say do you meant to say you put you put an a in there germa why are you still live
right because it's been like 10 hours that's what you meant to do i hope you correct it
otherwise why are we alive oh no mocha s are you eating in or out like burger boy laughing my ass
off it is late fuck um that's a great question find out in a second alex just asked for that
uh we'll see in about 10 minutes germa's gambling our bits away as we speak
not put my phone down what are you talking about you didn't hear what what are you talking about
can i can i hold that for a second the river's coming hold on
bless me bless you bugleberry i didn't know you're still in the room
hey dubsky dude thanks for the 250 thanks for the 250 dubsky you forgot about usura's rap dlc
but for the love of god don't pass up on rain world it's a fantastic game and you barely scratch
the surface due to your terminal case of boomer bones hope you give it another chance also the
chat lied last time the big gate rooms with symbols are how you progress to new areas
why would they lie to me why would they lie to me dare they we'll see tomorrow might just
be a stream where i do a few things that i should probably clean up i can't say for sure we'll see
princess maker 2 um i don't have that i don't have that game hey michael thanks for the five
dollars michael 500 bits i just want to say i was sound asleep when the sneezing joke started the
sneezes woke me up and i was really fucking confused clink thanks for the 500 bits five
dollars from clink fun fact about the serpent the sergeant the sergeant of the egg heads voice
sample it's actually from monty python's the meaning of life you can hear it right here in
this clip no shit this is a rick roll on turning the stream off it's not okay good
is it really is it what the fuck it is just random weird samples you can hear words and then they
cut it off weird interesting tidbit though thank you hey rooster pigeon thanks for the 500 bits
thanks so much for playing chibi robo germa i run a chibi robo twitter and discord and you
playing is bringing a lot of new fans means a lot thanks so much i mean the game should have a lot
of fans i'm a fan now i'm gonna go get a pot from downstairs and put it on my head and walk around
and like plug my ass into outlets i'm gonna pretend i'm not gonna do that last part though
that's dangerous but thank you for the 500 bits and finally at the end of the night
we'll see you tomorrow have a good night galactus gave 500 bits thanks germa for evenings full of
laughter these past few months without you there wouldn't have been much of it keep up the good
work as always and i can't wait to see what you play next we'll see what we do tomorrow
i'm open to suggestions tomorrow because i want to just chill we'll see have a great rest of your
night get some sleep i know we went pretty late tonight kind of a long one but you know it happens
sometimes see you guys tomorrow good night goodbye take care