Hello, hello. Oh shit, Vinny raided. Hello, uh, Vinesauce viewers. Just got back. How you doing?
We are moving on. It's always fun to play with Vinny. Good to see Vinny again. We are going to play
a couple more horror games, and this one is apparently a doozy, from what I've been told.
This is At Dead of Night. This apparently has really, really bad scares, and I'm... you know me.
There's no settings in this game, so I imagine just an FMV. We'll find out right now, won't we?
I need to change the game because the title can be the same. At Dead of Night. All right, coming back.
Let's see if you can see me, which I think you should be able to. Oh, not quite. There we are.
There's that, and then here am I. Okay, I can't really turn the lights off because it's still day here.
It doesn't work. Turn this on. I don't know how loud this game is, but it's apparently,
I would imagine it's probably very loud. Let's find out. Okay, Q&W is audio loudness.
I should probably watch the to- okay, I'm gonna watch- let's watch the intro. Is that too loud?
Watch full tutorial. Watch the- what should I do? Do it louder? This is loud, man. Just I'm making
sure you understand that. Should I just watch the tutorial? Way too loud. I- what the- it's at zero!
Hold on. Okay, you have to stop her. The chase. He hides whenever he can. Oh my god, this is gonna
suck. I'm not looking forward to this. He can't hide on the stairs, or on the ground floor,
or in the basement. So, okay. What's my strategy? Move out of line of sight if he sees you.
Got any unlocked room you can hide? If he comes in, just- okay, so hide in the bathroom?
Hide, okay. Use the spy glass? You can call out. Of course, the game where the monster or the bad
person is chasing you, lock him in. All right, I forgot everything. Is this spoilers? Spoilers,
idiot? It's the tutorial of the game! It's the game's tutorial! Hey, what do you mean,
spoilers? Okay, all right. So, let's watch the prologue. Two FPS Andy?
Why am I at two FPS Andy?
Why are all FMV games British? Are they?
Yeah, how come the FPS are bad? There's no video settings I could do.
I'm not dropping frames. I don't know.
Very nice friends. Very nice. And there's quite a few of you I see as well. Nice to see so many
fresh young faces for a change. You're here for the music festival in town, I presume?
Yeah, we were supposed to be camping that night. Somebody said, why is she not talking?
She is now. Will you be staying for breakfast?
I don't think so. We'll probably just get going. That's fine. And if you don't mind me asking,
Maya, would you be interested in the entertainment tonight? Tonight? Starts around
midnight, usually. It's me doing it. Actually, comedy. Ooh, okay. I do this comedy character
called Hugo Punch. He's sort of this comedic sociopath, says things that you're not supposed
to say and that sort of thing. It's quite popular with students. I don't think so.
That's not me. You're all just going to bed, I think.
This is really familiar. Oh, stop it. Twist your arm on this.
It's okay. I'd rather just go to bed. Sorry. Fine, fine, fine.
Which way are the rooms? Just take the lift. You're on the first
floor. Okay, thanks. Oh shit, wait a minute. It is midnight in England right now.
Drop your key off in the box, if you will, Maya, please, tomorrow.
It's midnight in England right now. Best show in town and no takers.
Who needs proper entertainment when you've got YouTube and my face or whatever? Stupid, uncultured.
Why is it running like this? Don't start this again.
I feel like the menu is doing this, but when I, I don't know.
I don't want to hear it, okay? Not tonight. Go to the settings. There aren't any settings.
No to children of bad eggs. They need to be taught a lesson.
Uh-oh. Shut up. Just shut up.
You always do this. They're paying customers. Wait, they haven't done anything to you.
I don't think so. Just leave them alone.
Bad eggs need cracking. Whack them hard and crack the shell. Kick them down the stairs to hell.
You know what you need to do, Jimmy. Show them who's boss. That's the way to do it.
Okay. I want to fix this. What the fuck is going on?
Disable G-Sync. I don't think I've ever turned.
Press alt to enter. It'll toggle full screen. I think it is in full screen.
We'll see. If I actually start playing, see what happens.
Breaking bad intro. It actually is. I think it's the same sound. It's the same drum beat.
All right. If I hit escape, is again, can I maybe?
Sea View Hotel has a dark past. Its ghosts have a story to tell.
Find them. Use the ghost and spirit receiver to talk to them.
They'll tell you Jimmy's secrets.
Jimmy! Jimmy! Okay. Let me see if the FPS is still bad.
It's back to normal now. Okay. So, all right. Start new game. The story of Jimmy Hall.
Okay. Choose standard game or extreme game. When playing the extreme game,
if Jimmy attacks you, he will take almost everything every time.
Your current game will be lost when you begin a new one and your achievements will be...
Oh, we're just doing standard. We're not doing extreme.
Oh, we're going. We're going. This is the device you found. Select this to switch it on.
It can detect spirits voices if you're near enough to them.
They're going to turn it up a little. Okay. If you haven't seen it,
go to the main menu and watch the tutorial. Okay.
Oh, yeah. This game hates my computer. What should I do?
Is it weird? Yeah. GPU settings enable or disable G-Sync.
Restart it. It looks fine. It looks fine in the menu here.
Yeah. It's when I'm in the actual game. It's in the Nvidia Control Panel.
Okay. Nvidia Control Panel. Opening that now. All right.
So now manage 3D settings. Monitor technology G-Sync, right?
It's under display. Monitor just G-Sync. G-Sync can call. All right.
So I'm going to turn... I'm turning off G-Sync. Windows G is enable.
I don't think I have that set up. Windows G enable. Windows G? Is this real?
Don't fuck with me. Is this real? Is it going to crash my computer?
That's a meme. God damn it. All right. I'm in...
I'm in the Nvidia Control Panel. So go to monitor... I'm at manage 3D settings.
I can't turn G-Sync off. I can only make it something else.
What the fuck did I just do? It's in Windows settings.
What do I need to... Okay. I can do fixed refresh under monitor technology.
Should I do fixed refresh or ULMB? Fixed refresh. Is this going to help?
Okay. I just did fixed refresh. Apply. Oh fuck. What happened?
Oh my God. What just happened? Are we okay? Did that fix it?
I think we're good. I think that fixed it. Is my cam fine?
Oh my God. You guys are absolute heroes. Yeah. You fixed it. We're good.
We're good. Looks perfect. I thought you guys were making that whole thing up.
Like, oh dude, turn off G-Sync. It's like, huh?
All right. So I can turn it on. If you haven't seen it. Yeah. Yeah. We did.
So turn the device on. I can talk. Try to make contact with a spirit.
There's no reply. There are no spirits around. A loud noise means there's a
spirit in a high energy state near. All right. When you meet spirits, you can
ask them questions. Pair their replies to make connections. When you're alone,
you can review spirits' replies here. Okay. Is anyone there? Is anyone there?
Okay. All right. All right. Let's get out of here. Where should I go?
You need a compass and a scrying mirror. Okay. I'm going up.
Is someone there? I fucking hate this already.
Okay. Room 301. Anybody in here? Is someone there?
There's nothing in here. Okay. Oh, it's loud.
302. This is fucking dark in here. How do I turn the light on?
How do I turn the light on in this room? It's too dark. How do I turn the light on?
Is someone there? Who's there? What room? Is this 301?
Hey, hey, hey. Hey. No. Hello. Hello.
The wind got higher. Okay. I don't think there's anything here.
Blocked. Room 9. Anybody in here? I need to find a compass.
I think I have to go back downstairs. Is someone there?
Haunted Google Maps. Oh, you found a handwritten note which reads goodbye.
I'm sorry for everything. What does that mean? What does that do?
Okay. I've got a note. Is someone there? Is anyone there?
I'm going to go right across. Wait. I can open the other. Wait.
You can open both drawers. That is just one. You found dead lock key to room 309.
Doors can be locked or unlocked. Oh, I can. So I can hide in here?
Okay. So I can hide in here now and lock the door. Okay. Good to know.
I'm going right across. Okay. What's in here? Another. Okay. Another key to bolt the door.
Copper wire. What's that do? Copper wire. All right. Anybody in here?
Is anyone there? It's been 15 minutes.
You haven't even done the first objective. Yeah. So what? To find a where would a compass be?
Okay. I'm going to go down. Okay. I'm going down.
Where should I go? Second floor or first floor? I'm going to go second floor.
Dark. What's in here? Really? This got to be like a compass in here, right?
Is anyone there? Remove the motion blur.
There are guys. There are no video settings in this game. I think it's supposed to hide.
Let me try that way. No, it's locked. Why is this locked too? First floor?
I'm going around. You have G motion blur on.
Is someone here? What's that fucking noise? Get it. Hide, hide, hide, hide in the locker.
Hide in the hide somewhere. Can I hide in this locker? What the fuck is that?
Spirit. I'm here. Stupid. Idiot.
Is someone there? Is someone there? Where are you?
Is someone there? He's there. What? Really? Where'd you go?
Locked. Oh, I can. It's the most loud here. Look at how loud this is.
What should I do about this? Is someone there?
Near the lockers? No, it's off there. Is someone there?
I don't think I can do anything here. You need to get the compass in the mirror.
Yeah, I don't. The game, the game did not say, hey, you need to get the compass in the mirror.
By the way, they're in 104 and in the garage. It did. Yes, it did. What are you talking about?
It's, it did. The game said to get them. It didn't say where they were.
Huh? You need to find a compass in scrying mirror. It doesn't say where it is.
I'm going to go to my room. My room is 101. I'm going to 101. Don't go that fucking far.
106. Let's just go in here. See?
Found some childish, violent drawings. OK. Is anyone there?
Nothing in here. Why is the music getting louder? I know, but I don't know where it is.
Got to go to 101. I'm so concerned. He's going to be here. It's so quiet.
Where's 101? 107. I'm in the wrong fucking way.
101. 108. Fuck. All right. I'm just going in here.
Oh, hurry up. He's looking for me right now.
Where is he? OK. Check these. Does this one even work?
Oh my fucking God. Oh, that's very bad. Dude, I got a sword.
All right. Can I hit him with the sword?
Is anyone there? I have all this shit.
I can't talk to anybody. It's down the hall somewhere.
You found everything but the compass. Oh, I don't know where it is.
I have to get to 101. Oh, fuck. I went the wrong way.
107. All right. 106. Dude, where the fuck is 101?
101. Let's go. Let's go. All right. I'm in. Lock the door.
All right. What's in here? This is my stuff. All right. Key.
Bottle of turpentine and a lighter. You found a chef's hat.
Is someone there? I found every single item in the game.
Besides the one I need. That sounds far away.
I'm going to try to get to the elevator.
I got really high. I got really high and went to sleep last night.
I had a dream. All right. Hold on.
At one point, Jerma was stealing a spaceship.
As he flies around, he just makes some insane incoherent noises.
I was speaking of being high. So Holly and I were high the other night.
And you're going to laugh. So Holly and I are high.
We're, you know, whatever. We're just doing a little bit of recreational marijuana.
Whatever. And we started, it started, we started getting really, really high.
So it's like, all right, fuck, man, we need a palate cleanser.
Because like we were on YouTube and it was like we were watching videos and shit.
And it was like, okay, we need some kind of palate cleanser.
So we went to this video specifically titled.
It was called cute animals from when you, for when you are stressed.
Cute animals for when you are stressed. It's like, okay, let's put that on.
There was a pre-roll ad on this video and it went exactly like this.
Crime is skyrocketing. Your, your life could potentially be
changed dramatically in the future. That's why you need to vote.
It was a political ad talking about how crime was skyrocketing.
We're going to go to like a dystopian future.
And we were just sitting there like, what are the cute animals? What's happening?
Crime is skyrocketing, honey. Did you know that?
It was fucked. It caused way more stress.
Anyways, let's keep going. Okay.
I need to get back to the elevator and go to the basement again.
I can't open that. Go back.
Check every single room. Did we go in 107?
Uh-oh. I've given up trying to help.
I'm sorry. If I look over here and this 10,000 messages a second.
I'm sorry. I can't read what you said.
Okay. I didn't look in here yet.
There's nothing in here. Did I go in 109?
I did. No, I've been in here. I've been, I've been in pretty much.
I got to go to the other side.
Yeah. This is where the, this is where the, the sword was.
I have to go to like one, like 12 to like 115 or something, right?
Because I can't open these with this key.
So I have to go to the other side. What was that?
Okay. That's me running. I did 107.
Did I go over here? It's okay. 112.
There's nothing in here.
You don't have a storage unit or something here?
There you go. Okay.
I found the compass. Finally.
You told me to go to the basement. Yeah. Okay.
Okay. I'm making progress.
You need to find a scrying mirror. I bet it's down here.
Where's this compass? How do I, can I pick up the compass?
All right. I'm going to keep going down this way because this other,
I'm going to go right across, open up that one.
To point towards spirits.
It's too dark. I get a flashlight, I guess, eventually probably, right?
114. Too dark. Scrying mirror.
Come on. Trophies and awards.
That's not a scrying mirror.
Turn the lights off, dude. This isn't even scary.
It's, it's the middle of the day.
Uh-oh. This is open. Jesus.
Okay. I don't think there's anything I can do here.
Oh, wooden paddle and another key.
Where is this mirror? Wait, can I look in there?
It's too dark. Too dark.
It's pointing this way.
Why is it, what's going on? Why is it, why is, why is, what's behind me?
He's literally behind me right now.
Oh, fuck. Get in here.
He doesn't actually come in here, right? I just scratched my nose.
Wait, lock the old suitcases.
Okay. I'm going to go down.
I feel like he's right here.
Where are you?
Oh my God.
All right. How do I get the fuck out of here?
Elevator, elevator, elevator. Right here.
Go. Quickly, please. Okay.
Go on. Hurry, please.
Garage.
All right. I'm good.
I haven't looked down here.
They're going like the back office.
He's not here.
No, I can't do anything in here.
Is someone there?
Where the fuck I'm going, but I'm going.
Can I not interact with anything in here?
Jesus.
Okay. I guess I'm going to go down again.
Ghostless run.
Lower ground.
I'm going to complete the game without seeing him once.
I was already down here.
Remember? I already did this.
There was that little girl down here.
I can talk to the spirit now.
I don't think so.
Is someone there?
Hello.
What's your name?
Who are you?
Amy Bell.
I'm 10.
Okay.
I saw a girl in the basement crying.
Is that you?
Who was she?
Hey.
Who drew those violent pictures?
Okay.
Who wrote the note that says goodbye?
What do you know about the sword?
Who does the sword belong to?
Okay.
What was the coil of wire used for?
What is turpentine?
I found a bottle of turpentine in a lighter.
What were they for?
I don't know what that is.
I'm 10.
Who did the chef's hat belong to?
Who are the whiskey bottles?
Is there a collection of whiskey bottles in one of the rooms?
Okay.
Yep.
I found some trophies.
Who won them?
I don't know.
Where did the wooden paddle come from?
I saw some suitcases in a chest.
Who did they belong to?
I don't know.
Okay.
So we've learned absolutely nothing.
All we learned...
What?
All right.
Where is this mirror?
I need the mirror.
I don't know where the fuck it is.
It's not down here.
I missed a few rooms.
Third floor.
Ground floor.
I feel like I didn't explore everything.
We learned that Jimmy was a fucked up boy who had a sword in turpentine.
Yeah.
See, I've seen a lot of G's.
You can backseat.
This game's...
It's one of those games where you need to...
I don't know what you're doing.
I don't mind it.
Ground floor.
I already went down here.
All right.
Where are the rooms on the ground floor?
No help.
The compass will bring you to the mirror.
You have a key for floor one stairs.
I do?
All right.
Let's go to one.
Where did I not go in one though?
I feel like I opened everything.
I feel like I went in 107.
You did.
This one here?
Where is it pointing?
Where is this compass pointing?
Dude, this compass is pointing in such...
What is this?
Where's it pointing?
This compass is just going in a circle.
What's this?
This door room.
It's pointing nowhere because it's in another floor.
Oh.
102 to 105.
121.
Uh-oh.
122.
123.
None of these are probably going to work.
The next one does.
All right.
123.
Give me the mirror.
Dang.
Ah.
I thought it was a mirror.
I'm going to go straight across to 122.
What?
Wait, I have a...
There's more than one compass?
You've done a syringe?
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Hide, hide, hide, hide.
I've never seen it.
I don't even know what the guy does.
I don't even know what he does.
I found every other item in the whole game.
He's on the floor.
He's on your floor, but you're safe.
All right.
What am I...
No.
I have to go to 102 to 105.
I don't even know how to get there from here.
I think I'm just going to go for it, right?
Holy shit.
No way.
What?
Get...
Get out of here.
Why could he not see me?
Did he leave the room?
Holy God.
This guy sucks.
He heard me say that.
Jesus.
What did that say?
What happened?
Look, my whole body hurts.
I heard the door close,
but that was not the front door closing.
That was the bathroom door closing.
My shoulder hurts.
Oh, my God.
I just...
There was no...
There was no road in my brain
that led to that guy was still in the room.
He takes things.
Oh, he took my radio.
All right.
So it said, look...
There was a thing that popped up.
What did it say?
Look in the first floor near the stairs.
Okay.
Where am I?
107...
Oh, I'm in 107.
I need to get to one...
No, other way.
I need like 102.
108.
Look in the first floor store near the stairs.
I need like 102.
Is it right here?
Why is it so dark?
Where are you?
Did I get so turned around?
106.
All right.
Is it in here?
This is not it.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Can I run?
What if I just run?
Is he doing that on purpose?
He's fucking me on purpose.
Should I talk shit?
I'm gonna scream.
I can't...
I can't lock the door.
I think I have to go this way.
All right.
I'm gonna go for it.
One, two, three.
Hey, I need...
Is he behind me?
Oh, come on.
Bathroom.
What are you doing?
He's right here.
And I'm sorry.
I have a lot of trouble with hotels.
And maybe some of you can relate to this.
It doesn't matter how many times I go to my hotel room.
When I come off the elevator,
I have no fucking idea where I'm going.
Is it left, right?
I don't...
Okay.
No, there is 102 to like 110.
I have to go that way.
I'm not gonna be able to find my way around here.
He's right outside the door.
I can't get...
I can't leave right now.
Should I just go for it?
I'm gonna go back up to three.
Should I go to three?
I don't know.
I don't know, dude.
I'm going.
Which way is he?
106.
Dude.
My god.
Oh my god.
I'd somewhere right now.
Not here.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm fucking dead.
I just don't know even...
I...
There's no signs.
I feel like I'm walking around a casino floor.
Like I just don't even know what direction I need to go in.
There's no signs.
There's one sign in front of the elevator.
That's it.
108.
Should I go in 108?
109.
I went in here, I think.
But he's coming.
This is where the sword is.
Okay, dude.
Dude, I can't think of a worse thing that I could be doing
than try to find your way around a hotel room.
If I go hotel...
You got three floors of this shit?
Every hallway is the same hallway in my brain.
It just is.
I can't open these.
I'm gonna try to go up to three.
And where is the storeroom that's apparently near the elevator?
All this shit looks the same!
All right.
What are you doing?
I just went down the same fucking hallway.
It's literally concrete all over again.
I'm better off just using the sword and swinging at the guy.
Seriously.
You've been in the same three halls over and over again.
Dude, I can't...
I can't navigate this in real life, let alone in a video game,
where somebody's chasing me with a baseball bat.
Go down the stairs.
The stairs were locked last time.
Like, where...
I gotta...
I keep, like, going in a circle.
This is one...
All right.
Where the fuck am I going?
This is one...
I haven't gone on 114.
It's fucking dark.
Never mind.
Ask for directions.
Dude, I...
I'm being honest.
I have no idea where the fuck I'm supposed to go.
Every single room is the same room.
Every hallway is the same hallway.
Is this it right here?
It's the storeroom, right?
It's not in this one.
19...
Fuck is he?
I don't know which way to go.
118...
I just have to go in a room.
I have to go in something.
Whatever.
Go...
Run to the exit sign.
Jesus.
Get out of here.
I'm going not...
I'm not going anywhere.
He's probably just sitting here.
Like, last time.
See, this shit happens.
And then I come out here and my brain has reset.
It's like, oh, this is just another nondescript hotel hallway again.
But here we are.
Nondescript hotel hallway.
There's no map.
Like, I don't know where the fuck to go.
If I can press M and see where the fuck I'm supposed to go.
I'm just running around till I find the fucking elevator.
I'll just outrun him.
121...
122...
123...
The skips.
I'm done.
This game sucks.
The skips.
I hate this game.
It's stupid.
I'm done.
This guy sucks.
Uh-huh.
All right.
Now, what else did you take?
Can I please find a way to get to the fucking elevator?
It's not even the fucking scary bad guy that's a problem for me.
It's walking in a circle in a nondescript hotel room.
107.
All right.
Where do I go?
How do I get the fuck out of here?
Not this way.
All right.
What about the other way?
108.
How did I end up here again?
Where's the one hallway that leads back to the fucking lobby?
Where is the fucking elevator?
Where's the exit signs?
I'm going to fucking alt F4 this game.
Yay!
I found it.
Oh my god.
Why does this take me so fucking long?
All right.
Where is the storeroom?
They just looked on the security camera.
A guy just going in the same circle.
Give me this fucking thing back.
Now we get to play the game called
go try to find where the fucking scrying mirror is.
I'm going to third floor.
101 to 115 is that way.
Good luck.
I'm going to get lost.
101 to 115.
Okay.
So where's 101 is this way, right?
I need to remember this thing.
All right.
So 101 is here.
This is 106.
What?
Wait.
Huh?
Where's 101?
This hotel sucks.
It's so confusing.
Huh?
Okay.
101.
103 is dark.
Please don't yell.
You're going to lose your voice.
All right.
You're right.
There it is.
This floor has a dead end.
Okay.
Either by in the door in rooms or in the ground floor kitchen.
Either by the door in rooms or.
Okay.
So I can use the mirror to see clues about where to go.
It will also help you locate lost keys.
Okay.
I got some items.
Use the mirror in the dark rooms.
Okay.
And I already do that though.
That was the little girl, right?
I already did that one.
This is hallway that I haven't gone through over here.
I might have some more stuff now.
Yeah.
Let me just finish exploring out here.
104.
Use it again.
Oh, shit.
Wait.
Don't use it too much.
Why is it bad?
There's one more that I haven't done.
Use it in a dark room.
Sorry.
Is he actually coming?
Oh, this is crying.
I can't believe I'm bald here.
Okay.
So I think I've seen everything in the first floor except for the dark rooms.
It's not right here, right?
Oh, don't open the door.
How do I bolt the door?
What's the button I do?
What room am I even in?
What room am I in?
How do I use the key?
105.
Can I press 105?
Did you press the talk button to do it?
105.
Oh, my God.
What a pain.
Do I even have it?
I don't even have the key to this room.
Okay.
Well, I'm leaving.
Let's go.
Okay.
Now I'm going back down.
Don't be here.
No.
Could be no.
Show the girl the new stuff.
That's the plan.
But wasn't there a dark room over here?
I don't care.
Let's just get me out of here.
My God.
Oh, my God.
Wait, I can lock this one.
Okay.
You can't get in now.
Fuck you.
You can't get in.
I'm safe.
Now I just like taunt him.
Wouldn't he have a key?
He's like a weird guy.
Wouldn't he have like a...
I don't know.
I feel like he would have like a hotel key.
He like owns the hotel.
All right.
I think I'm getting out.
I'm not calling him out.
No.
Okay.
I just have to get to the elevator
and I'm going to go down.
Okay.
Let's go.
Unlock the door first.
Oh.
Okay.
I gotta...
Where are you?
No.
Why are you in the same exact spot, man?
You're in the exact same spot.
Oh, my God.
Get in.
I don't know.
I didn't want to click on that.
I swear to God.
He's camping the elevator.
Oh, this is bad.
Oh, my God.
You've got to be kidding me.
No, not this.
I just came out.
Click.
Oh, my God.
I wish I could have a solution to this issue.
Do I have the key for 107?
I don't.
I don't know.
Just fucking hide in the bathroom.
I'm dead.
I'm just dead.
There's no way he doesn't know I'm in here.
He's going to just...
I'm dead.
It's over.
Yeah.
I know.
You know I'm in here.
Of course you do.
There's no way you don't open this door.
Bullshit.
He's not...
He's still there.
And now, again,
every time I see this guy,
my memory wipes the entire floor plan of this hotel.
Get me to the fucking elevator.
Where is the elevator from here?
Okay, this is 107.
It's like...
I got to go around here.
No, this is wrong.
It's...
There's like a little tiny entryway that I go down,
which is right here.
Right?
No.
Is it?
Is this correct?
No, it's not correct.
There's one hallway that leads to the elevator,
and I still fucking find where it is.
There's literally one hallway that goes there.
It's this one right here.
Is it this one?
No, this is the fucking suit of armor.
I don't care!
Fucking come face me!
It's literally...
I'm following the exit signs.
There's one hallway I have to find.
The exit signs are the green sign of the guy going like this, right?
It's the arrows.
I know, but then I go that way,
and that's the only sign there is,
and then I just go walking around in a circle.
I don't know where I am.
It's a concrete level.
Why would I play the game with the hotel rooms?
Fuck you, guy.
Okay, let's talk.
Who's there?
Okay, I have new things to show you.
What do you think about this?
Is it Amy?
Who did the Charles Perth belong to?
Where did the bottle of diazepam come from?
Why is there a blood-stained cloth in one of the drawers?
Okay, so now...
Okay, it said blood-stained cloth.
All right, so you can only select two things at once.
Okay, I don't think we learned anything new.
Select two things.
You have to pair things.
Okay, so this is yours?
Is it Amy?
The blood-stained cloth and the purse?
All right, I mean that's...
Match two replies you think connect to work out the spirit story.
I mean, is that...
Okay.
Pair sighting replies with item replies for faster progress.
Sighting replies and...
Amy doesn't have an answer.
And the sword?
Cloth could have been mine.
Had the sword.
I didn't like it.
Like that?
How do I like say yes to this?
Pair sighting...
Okay, the sword and the purse and Jimmy stealing.
The purse was mine.
It was my birthday, but it was stolen.
Okay.
But pair that with what?
Cloth could have been mine.
How do we know that?
Showing keys.
Showing everything.
Settings, not items.
Okay.
Boy called Jimmy locked me in the basement.
Then he started stealing things from me.
And the purse was mine and it was stolen from me.
When you said Jimmy stole things from you.
Okay.
Is that connected with what you said about the purse?
So now go to the ground floor.
Hello.
Okay, Jimmy wouldn't listen.
Okay.
We're going up to the ground floor.
And then we're going to follow the...
Campus.
What is going on?
Jimmy, give it back.
That's mine.
Stop stealing on this.
Should we talk?
Is it Amy?
All right.
So stealing...
I saw you shouting to Jimmy to give your toy back.
Why did he take it?
That doesn't help.
That was funny.
Okay.
Stealing my toy.
Is there anything else I can need to do?
I'm gonna find the toy.
Wait, scrying machine.
You know, I haven't been up to the third floor
in a long time.
Let's go to the third floor.
Third floor is the only one that I really...
Have not really looked around.
Let's go 309, 308.
That one...
I feel like these were...
One of these was dark.
Right?
Did I get everything from here?
Yeah, this is where the goodbye was.
One of these was dark.
Which one was dark?
I just came out of this one.
Yeah.
All right.
You know why it's confusing?
Okay.
Yeah.
Because I'm turning...
All right.
My brain wants to open the door.
This is what's causing all these issues for me.
When I open the door,
I'm imagining that 308 will be in front of me,
but I keep turning and putting my back
and the door that I just came out of is in front of me.
You know what I mean?
Like when I open 309, it's like, all right, 308.
But you turn your body.
That's what keeps happening to me.
I figured it out.
Now I know why I'm so fucking lost.
All right.
None of these were dark.
I already got that.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I did everything here.
Crime is skyrocketing.
Okay.
So now let me check these.
302.
All right.
302 is dark.
Do I have the key to 302?
Why would I?
No.
Scry.
Is that water?
Found G.
Okay.
G again.
Well, isn't that where...
We're on like the little girl's quest, right?
We need to find a toy.
It's turpentine.
Shit.
Okay.
Do I have enough to know what happened?
Do I just have to go down and put the right stuff
when I talk to Amy?
I think I already have everything, don't I?
I need a toy though.
I need to find the toy.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
He's coming.
I will have explored the entire third floor after this.
Should I just get out here and run?
Where is he?
Why is he just standing here?
Whatever.
I'm just gonna go.
Okay.
So don't get turned around.
So this is very dark.
I'm not going to scream again for the rest of the night.
I promise.
What did you take?
Did you take something?
I don't even know what you took.
Fucking radio again.
First floor store near the stairs.
I knew he was behind me too.
I just didn't want to turn and have it hit me in the head.
Okay.
So have I...
Where am I now?
I'm on the first floor right now.
Okay.
I need a sign to tell me where I'm going.
Where's the exit sign?
You know what?
It's this floor here.
This is the problem for my head.
This place.
It's like fucking nine paths.
No, I need to get the thing from here.
It's right here.
What is this?
This is open now.
Can I touch this?
Give that back.
No.
What's in here?
There's nothing here.
Is someone there?
No, there's nothing.
Okay.
I'm going to go to...
Two?
I have the key to the stairs.
Go to G.
I feel like I was already there like three times.
Do I have the key to the stairs?
So, I mean, should I...
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
He can't be in there, right?
I'm going to G, I guess.
Stairs are safe.
Yeah.
Going back to that room.
Talk to her again.
See if I can't.
Right?
I mean...
Wait, hold on.
I can't go in here?
Come on.
What about this room?
Can I do anything in here?
Hold on.
All right.
Perpentine on the bear.
That's a bear, right?
I don't have a bear though.
Okay.
So, not that way.
What's right here?
Okay.
So, can I talk to you about this?
Is anyone there?
Okay.
So, the turpentine...
Is it Amy?
I don't have a bear though.
I probably need to find a bear.
Stealing?
Like that?
Does that make sense?
What you said about Jimmy stealing your toy.
Does that have something to do with what you said about the turpentine and lighter?
Yeah.
Right.
The one.
All right.
Let's go.
Now.
Okay.
Floor one.
Is there anything else I can do here?
Probably not.
Let's just get to floor one.
I have to complete at least one quest in this game.
It's your favorite floor.
All right.
We're gonna drop the...
I mean, it's getting to be a little darker.
Let's go ahead and drop this.
It's time for lights off by the way.
Adjust this.
That work?
Kind of.
Okay.
There we go.
Scary.
This is too...
This is like way too bright.
Hold on.
Now I'm immersed.
Dorito.
Yeah.
I know.
I've only done seven percent of the game.
I've only...
Seven percent?
What?
You've got to be shitting me.
Okay.
Where is this pointing to?
Is anyone there?
Floor one.
Where's the...
Where's this...
I don't...
This way.
But it keeps going.
Stairs?
Play the Ghostbusters game.
Ah.
Or the mirror.
Let's head first floor.
Can Jerma see us?
Yeah, I can.
Follow the arrow.
Yeah, the arrow just is spinning in a circle.
It's like here?
In this room?
Are you in like in 106 or something?
I don't think so.
Is anyone there?
Fuck you, man.
Seriously.
No.
I want to turn.
I...
I wish I could just do WASD.
I'm gonna die.
Okay.
Here he comes.
Is he gone?
He's not gone.
All right.
Come on up next to play and stay out of the house.
The puppet combo game.
Be aware.
Probably loud as fuck.
I want to at least complete this mission with the little girl.
I think I'm going out.
Yeah, I'm just gonna go out.
He hasn't done it yet.
He's seriously coming back.
Bro, when I unlock the door, you're coming over.
I mean, if he's just gonna sit here, then I need to...
What am I gonna do?
I have to leave at some point.
All right.
You know what?
Fuck this guy.
I'm just going.
Like he's gonna stand here this whole time.
Compass is pointing over there, but there's no way to go over there.
Huh?
Why is it doing that?
109?
Are you in here or something?
What's in here?
This is where the sword is, right?
Yep.
Um.
Is someone there?
It's loud in here.
I don't think there's anything in here.
All right.
I'm gonna give this game five more minutes.
And then I'm playing the other one.
Pointing this way?
No.
Where is this arrow pointing?
It is pointing in here.
I couldn't do anything in there.
Why does it want me to go in here?
Not like right here, right?
There's something there.
Should I do the mirror in here?
Let's try it.
There's nothing in this room.
Just the sword.
Um.
I'll do the...
I'll do the mirror?
109.
Isn't that where I am?
That's where I'm standing.
Look around.
I mean, this...
I can literally only look in two directions.
Ah!
I fucked this game.
I'm playing something else.
I'm playing a different game.
Why did that not happen the first time I...
Okay.
Why did that not happen when I walked in here two minutes ago?
Is it Amy?
Yeah.
It's me, Amy.
Okay.
I saw you holding a toy on fire.
What happened?
The cloth and the sword.
Okay.
Sword, blood...
What was that?
Who's this guy?
Sword and bloody cloth?
Sword and cloth, right?
Who's there?
Hello?
It's gone.
Okay.
All right.
This game's scary.
This game's fucked up.
This game is very long.
I want me to go to floor two.
This game's scary.
It still said floor one, though.
Where are you?
It still wanted me on floor one.
Uh-oh.
I'm done with it.
This is...
This is scary.
This is awful.
It was an awful experience.
I recommend it.
That was a horrible experience.
Would recommend.
Down here.
This way.
Jimmy?
All right.
Let's play the next one.
In just a second.
Where is she?
Where are you?
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm telling you, Jimmy.
You can't do that.
You're home.
Oh, I don't have my...
I don't have my thing.
I can't communicate.
All right.
This game was scary.
This was...
All right.
That was cool.
That was...
That was confusing for me.
But it was a good game.
We're gonna move on to the puppet combo game.
That was intense.
Give me one sec.
Only 7% of the game completed, too.
Holy shit.