You're my iPad, Mayo, and Wine THG tensed stream featuring Krabby Patty and Fortnite Mobile.
That's me. I'm that guy. I'm your guy. Somebody wrote that. I didn't just say that.
No one said that. Yeah, like 30 people did. Hey, destroy dude. Thanks for the five. Give me 30 subs.
Right off the bat here. Welcome back, everybody. We're going to continue our trek through VR.
We are not going to play Half-Life Alex today. That is reserved for tomorrow and Tuesday.
I'm hoping to get through Half-Life Alex either tomorrow or Tuesday. I've heard it's about a 10
to 15 hour long experience thinking maybe three streams will do it. Maybe. One of the scary games.
I have like at least five scary VR games downloaded. We'll get to them. Wait till...
It's not Halloween yet. Wait till at least like the week of Halloween. I don't do like October
every day is a scary day. When is Chubby Bunny? That's going to happen next week.
Fucking Chubby Bunny. Patience is a virtue. Yeah. Hey, the Fooly. Thanks for the five.
Give me 30 subs. He's a liar, liar, liar. I'm not a liar. Look, you... I'm not... And by the way,
people think I'm going to die if I do Chubby Bunny. I'm not going to do Chubby Bunny until I die.
I don't know why you think that's going to happen. I'm going to do like seven marshmallows and then
we're going to call it a day. I'm not going to die. Chubby Bunny is going to put him in a wheelchair.
That's not going to happen, dude. But for now, we have a few games I want to go through.
Very importantly, the main thing today is The Room VR. I made a video like seven years ago
about The Room. It's one of my favorite series. And I'm not even kidding. It's an iPad series.
Hold on. Don't be such a dick yet. It's on Steam. They ported it to Steam like three or four years
ago. It's this like box inside of a box inside of a box puzzle game. It's so much fun. They made a
VR version of it. And it's not just a VR version of the first game. Or, oh yeah, we like slapped
some goggles on you and we gave you hands. No, it's a completely from the ground up VR game
experience. So fuck yeah, that's what we're doing today. But before that,
I think that's at least a couple hours. We're going to do some just VR fucking bacon wrapped cheese,
bacon wrapped scallops. Fucking Resident Sleevers. It's been four minutes, dude.
You can't show up to the concert. And they're like just before the concert music is playing.
All right, what's the lineup today? Oh, we got Blink-182. We got Kanye. And the main event
is Skrillex. And it's like, oh nice. Okay, I can't wait. I'm at the concert now.
Oh, this is boring. Turn off this like before the concert music. Where's Skrillex? That's what I'm
here for. I don't want to sit here for four hours and wait for Skrillex. Get them on now.
That's true. You don't resident sleeper at a concert. If you resident sleeper at a concert,
you may have the wrong choice of music. Start the stream. I need my crack.
This guy sucks. This music sucks. Song sucks. Honey, how much were these seats?
They were $180 a piece. Oh, you like this music? No, you do. I'm just humoring you by coming to a
concert that you wanted to go to. But don't you think this guy sucks? Yeah, actually I do.
But you're the one that listens to it in the car every day. Yeah, but I mean, I mean, this concert
sucks. All right, let's go. That's wrong. This is a true story. He's projecting. He didn't think
you're going to see me show up right now, did you? Oh shit, hold on. And I got the VR guys on camera
shirt and I got one of these. We ain't fucking around today, boys and girls. I ain't fucking
around today. I am protecting my hair today. He's got a dirty shirt. You know, okay, you guys know
that time has passed since the last stream, right? This is not like 12 hours after the last stream,
just because the last stream happened. I've washed this by hand. How do they even take this off?
And dude, you know something weird about headbands? I feel like that blood is being
constricted to my brain. I hate these. I feel like it takes longer for me to say sentences right now.
Is that weird? It kind of feels weird. All right, let's go. First up is Taphouse VR. This is just a
meme game we're going to play for like a half an hour. Why am I holding this like I'm videotaping
you at like a wedding? Okay, okay, now go in and kiss, go in and kiss each other. Yep, yep, yep,
oh my god. Yeah, that looks great. I'll be back about 40 or 50 more times during the course of
the wedding to annoy the fuck out of you. Stop harassing the bridesmaids. I'm going in. Can you
guys hear this? No, you can't. Isn't that what you did? I was paid to be there. They paid me to be
annoying. And look, all right, I know, I know. Look, I gotta address this. Yes, we are getting into like
fat germa arc. I know, I know, I know you can see this because I can see it. You know, I know you
can. I've gained like fucking 20 pounds since the last time you saw me on camera. I'm strong and I
can like rest shit on there now. My iPad, like when I'm lying down, my iPad can just sit right there
and I just go like this and I like I just sit there and I like I play Hearthstone, right? I play
Hearthstone and then in a little window in the corner is like preparing and playing Hearthstone.
It's awesome. I can't even see what the fuck he's doing. I just like having it on. I got the picture
in picture. Stonebod. Here comes the bad boy arc. Why would that be a bad boy arc? Wait, are we
talking like bad boy? Like I took cookies out of the jar and it was like, get away from there.
Or like I ride a motorcycle. Which one? Both. All right, let's go. This is Taphouse VR.
Why am I already wicked hot? It shouldn't be like this, dude. Dude, they need like an AC unit in here.
You know when like a mascot has a fucking costume on? Valve, get on that. Now the headband's in the
fucking way. All right, I'm good. At least it's protecting the hair. I don't want to lose that
shit because I will. All right, I'm in a good place. There you are. All right, how do I play?
How do you play? Oh, okay. Normal, bold, collected, drink serve, drink accuracy,
dead customers. I thought that was somebody coming in my actual room. Dead customers.
Wait, there's a slot machine? I don't even know how to play. Are these like triplets?
What does he want? He wants gnarly juice, cranberry flavor. Can I punch him in the face? No,
don't do that yet. Cranberry juice. Oh, here we go. Okay, that was a monitor. That was a monitor.
All right, cranberry juice. You got it. Here you go. How much do you want?
You get to take the whole thing. What's that? What's that? Why is he like doing like,
do you want a beer? Everyone else notice that every VR game is based around like pouring
drinks into glasses and then throwing the glass at the guy's face. All right, you want 50%
Spropa bar. Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Do I have this shit? What's Spropa bar? It's just make
a mess. VR. Make a fucking mess. And you don't have to clean it up. That's the big selling point.
Okay, Spropa bar energy drink. Okay, we got gnarly juice. Got it. The right one. No, it's the wrong
one. Here we go. And then milk. Oh, all right. What do you want? You want one in the curved glass.
Okay, I got it. Gnarly juice. 60% gnarly juice. You got it. That's like 60, right? And then you want
20% rum, 20% milk. All right, it's my first day. 10% milk, 20% milk, and then 20% rum with some rum.
Okay, that's it. Here you go. Let me move that for you, sir. We're at 100%. Yeah, that's good.
How do I take these? I want to play the slot machine. Hey, I can't. I can't get that one.
Can you hand that to me, please? You want a lazy schmo? What? Lazy schmo? You want a bucket of
lazy schmo? What the fuck is? Okay, here you go. Good, right? Holy shit, that was a lot of money.
Fuck, what was that? Give me this fucking money. Excuse me. He just wants rum.
Didn't I just give you a drink? All right, you want just you want rum in a martini glass?
Where are the martini glass? Oh, shit. Hold on a minute. Let me in here, man. Let me in here.
Where are the martini? Where are their glasses? The martini glass? I don't know. We don't have
any. We don't have any martini glasses. Fuck off, dude. This is the wrong bar. All right. What do
you want? Want 80%? Beer and vodka? That's fucking kind of gross. Vodka. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. This beer is never ending. They all leave together? Not good.
Customers. Here we go. Clean. There we go. All right. Where's the martini glass?
What do you want? Go fast. Tap water. That's it. Oh, what do you want? Did that get his attention?
What do you want? I want one of these. One what? Okay. And what? 20%? Oh, so vodka. Here you go.
What do you want? Order up. Martini. Fuck. Martini. Milk in a martini glass? What's wrong with you?
Milk in a martini. I don't have any. Where are they? Guys, help me. Up left. Oh my god. I'm
fucking oblivious. Milk in a martini glass. Here you go. Wake up. That'll be $12, please.
Break it. What the fuck are you doing? Break it. What the fuck am I hitting?
Do you want? One second. Why do I have my own slot machine here? This is the stupidest thing ever.
All right. Hey, switch those machines. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Superbar. There we go.
You pay the big bucks for that. I want to play. Give me this. I mean, if you own this place,
this employee is just paying you back. You don't even have to pay this guy. This money is just
going right back into the restaurant. Oh my god. It's going to go over, isn't it? Okay. Seriously.
Is it tipping over? Is it falling? I don't know. I'm a diamond. Bring the shelf down. No.
All right. 20%. I got two minutes. I'm good. How does somebody die in here? I don't know. How
do you die? Can you imagine leaving a bar? All right. What do you want? I don't know what the
dead customer thing is supposed to mean. All right. What do you want? That's your thing.
You know what? Just take it. Just take it. Take the bottle. Take it. Here. How's that for a beer?
It's MaxBit. All right. Watch out. Watch out. I don't want to hit anything.
Okay. I'm already hitting something, but I'm busy, sir. Oh yeah. Do you want? Here. I got you, dude.
All right. You want the Superbar. Is there anything else happen in this game?
Oh, I don't understand. Like how somebody's a dead angry customer.
They got power. Yes. All right. So now I got a D plus again. How? Inbox. I'll play Saw 2.
No, I got an action packed game coming up next. I'm trying to see what happens if I...
Wait a minute. Hold on. I can't do anything. Next game.
Give them the wrong order. Okay. Here. Here. Here. Here. Here. Here. Take it. Here. Here.
Okay. Yeah. Let's get around a fireball. Yeah. Oh, I love doing this shit. I love when 30 of you
come in and ask for fucking around a fireball. Yeah. Make sure I get all of you. You in the back
too. Fireball for you too. Sure thing. Sure thing. Now I gotta go in the back and I gotta
get another bottle of this shit so that I can make you fucking idiots happy. Yeah. Sure thing.
Oh, what's that? Oh, half of you didn't even come get it because half of you didn't even
fucking want it in the first place. Two of you wanted this. 12 of you didn't. Okay. That's a lot
of fun. Being a bartender with a bunch of dickheads. Oh, we all love that, don't we?
Real world experience. It's... It's zingy. I feel like I'm in an airplane bathroom. Where am I? Why
am I so... Why am I hitting the same wall so many times? They've got Skrillex. Okay. I'm gonna go
to the next one. That was kind of fun. That was pretty fun. That was fun. Wasn't it? I thought
it was pretty cool. Come on for a sec. Oh, this is... Why the fuck did I get over here?
Skrillex waiting room. I already won the slots. All right. Give me one sec. That was fun. Okay. I
forget the next game. What was it? Oh, right, right. It was Hell... Hell... Hell Road VR. Right. Now I
remember. No. Okay. Hold on. Let me get it up. A long drive. It's called Hell Road. You ride a
motorcycle. It looks intense as hell. I missed some subs here. We had a five from Donut. Thank
you, Donut. And then $50 from Zurich Da. 5,000 bits to say love you, big man. Thanks a lot, dude.
That's a shitload of money. That's an extreme amount of money. I'll take it and I will spend it
the worst possible way. Okay. Let's get this up. And here we go. Should be able to see now.
There you go. Okay. What does it want me to do? Re-center. Hold on. Re-center your view until the
windows are in the correct position. Press R to reload. Press enter to finish calibration.
Holy shit. Dude. I got, you know... I haven't even done it in VR. When you sit on a couch and you
have a pretend like 5,000 foot screen, that's what this is. I'm at like a movie theater right now.
This is a seated experience. What? Okay. Press R to reload window positions. I'm gonna press R.
Does it really matter? Good. Press enter to finish or toggle edit mode with VR controllers.
Sit. Seat comfortably. Please seat comfortable in the chair and activate both VR controllers.
Oh, this is good. This is fine. So, but how do I get the... I press enter.
I'm ready. You ready? I can stand up on the bike. I'll be fine. Both controllers are activated.
How am I going home? Oh, how do we go home? It crashed? Game crashed? How did it crash?
How does a game like that crash? Why does it want me to host a Minecraft room?
Because I wasn't sitting down. Well, what the... All right. I am now.
Try this again. I'm clearly sitting now. Okay. Okay. That's good. See. Here we go.
All right. I'm sitting. This is a seated experience. I think it crashed again.
All right. Well, we're not playing that one, I guess. That was... That one looked fucking really
cool too. That's unfortunate. Well, we've got a whole shitload, so it doesn't really matter.
Oh. Oh, fuck yeah. You ready for this shit? Are you ready for me to prove to you guys once
and for all what I fucking can do? I hope so. Let's go. Oh yeah. Time to show you how to play
the drums. Everybody thought I was a liar. I'm about to prove to everybody that I can fucking
play the drums for real. We'll see you. Ah, that crashed too, didn't it? Fuck. How did that crash?
VR is just... VR was just never ready for us. All right. Here we go. He's got a virus? No, I've
reinstalled my entire fucking operating system. I don't have a virus. Okay. That's better. What the
fuck happened to you guys? Why? Okay. Why did fucking a stupid motorcycle game fuck this all up?
Fucking uninstall that piece of shit. Whatever. I'm only gonna play this for like 10 minutes
anyways and we're moving on to the next one. Okay. Let's go. All right. I lost chat now.
Bunch of horse shit. Uh, we're gonna do rocket. Oh, I can't wait for this shit. Don't even tell me
you crashed. Okay. Can you guys hear this? Where's the audio? What the fuck did that game do to my
computer? I gotta... Hold on. No, no. Wait, wait, wait. I gotta reboot SteamVR. Fucking pile of shit.
Virus stream. Yeah, it's called... It took over SteamVR, broke my whole computer, and then deleted
my audio. How much was that fucking game? Hold on. Give me a second. Let's... Searching. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. I know, I know, I know. Reboot this shit. Write a negative review on Steam. No. I didn't
get a chance to play it. Okay. Here we go. Everybody relax. I'm gonna calm down. Not gonna be upset
about this. We don't get upset about things that we don't. We have no control over. Right, Jeremy?
Okay. Very nice. I can... Why can't you guys hear this? What the fuck? Yeah, it says... It's the
Vive. It should be coming through the Vive right now. There we go. All right. I got it, I got it,
I got it. Fucking VR. Drum Beats VR. There it is. Let's fucking go, man. Killing me here.
There we are. Fucking killing me. Okay, can you see me? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Fuck. Such like a production to do this shit. You gotta have like eight programs open for VR to be
streamable. No, just have like four windows open and download like six fucking mods. It's easy.
It's easy. All right. I better be able to see you guys. I'm not gonna be fucking mad as hell.
Oh, this whole, this whole thing is fucking broken. Now I can't even see the goddamn chat.
That's fucking, that's phenomenal. Oh, what is this? Would 0.2% of people own this shit?
Whatever. I have to, I'm gonna play. Why are you not showing up? I'll fix this later. I don't even
need to see chat right now. All right. There it is. Wait, I don't have a foot. I don't have a foot.
How do I do that? Oh, this is weird without a foot. This is weird without a foot. This is weird
without, I can't do, I have to do with my fingers. I can't do it. I can't, I thought I'd be seating.
You know, do you know how fucking weird it is to have to do the foot pedal with your
finger? In the fucking rim. What the fuck was that? I wish I had a fucking foot pedal.
My VR just crashed. Why was I just on a, why was I just on a fucking iceberg? In high school,
that like is so ready to show the family reunion him play the drums. And he's kind of nervous
because he's like, I've never played in front of a crowd before. And then the whole family sit there
while he does that. And it's like, oh, it's like kind of fucking bad junior, but like it was good
enough for us to like clap and be like, okay, now let's wait. Where's the fucking carved turkey?
I need a foot pedal and I need real. That's doesn't even fucking work when I press the button.
Why? Can I like put that on my toe? I can't even see you guys. You got a fucking motorcycle game.
Fucked it all up. All right. That's good enough. I don't care. That's good enough. I don't care.
That's good enough. That's good enough. That's good enough. I clapped at my high school fucking
party. I don't care. Wait, was it small this whole time? God damn it. Why the fuck is this
happening? Why can't I see you two? You two? What do you mean you two? There are more than two of
you here. All right. We're going to move on to, oh dear. I don't even know if I can play this one
right now. I did want to check out Blade and Sorcery's new content. I heard there was new
shit in here. So give me one second while I fix the chat. I'll be right back. Fucking motorcycle
game. I swear to God. Fucking motorcycles. Fuck. Oh my fucking God. Fuck. Fucking motorcycle game
sucks. I'm going to fucking piss my pants. Okay. We're good. You guys ready for some more fucking
VR? No. God damn it, man. I heard you playing. Yeah, I mean, I was trying to fix the chat.
Every like, every like 25 seconds probably was said like, fucking stupid fucking thing sucks.
I just was trying to get the chat on. He was rehearsing secretly. Okay. Well, that sure was
a fucking blast now, wasn't it? I want to play the Blade and Sorcery update. Oh God, what the fuck
have I done now? We're good. It only took like fucking 20 years. It only took 20 fucking years.
Don't ever fucking buy that motorcycle game. Donate your money to charity instead.
All right, let's go. He grew in size. All right, so what's the update? All right, let's go.
There's an update apparently. Magic. What's that? I think I've got to play the game. All right,
let's go. There's armor now? Is there really? Who's the destination? All right, so is this
new destinations too? We've got arena, canyon. I've seen the canyon. Ruins. Zinado? First they're on
screen. Virtual reality. Virtual reality. Settle down. All right, we're okay. Fucking okay. What
have we not seen? No. And he's new. He's going mental. I'll just try one. Whatever.
Actually losing it. I was fine until I opened up a game and it deleted my whole computer. Why
does my arm feel like bigger? You know, I feel like my head is too close to my hands. Does that
make sense? I feel like I'm like this. All right, I want to see. I need any new weapons.
Yes. What's wrong with my hair? I do this, right? I lift it up and then how do you throw it, right?
How do you throw things? Stop. I'm getting sad. What are you talking about, dude? Wow. What?
Oh my God. Oh, the wind tunnel was sure was fun.
Fucking Mars attacks alien. Hold on a minute. Fuck man. Can I just get a break for a second?
What good fucking that fucking motorcycle came. Fuck that motorcycle came. Fucked up everything.
Count Dracula. All right, get me in here please. Get me please in here so I can start streaming
the fucking video game. That's a literal Vegeta hair. Fuck. Dude, I can't. I can't right now. I
can't do that right now. We can't talk like this right now. Where are the weapons, dude?
What do you mean fight in progress? I need something. I don't have any fucking weapons.
I'm just being chased by a lady with a knife. Shit. What do I just activate?
Stay away from me. Stay away from me. I'm a psycho. My computer can't handle this.
My computer is lagging. I fucking had a computer lag. Wait, I know what to do. I know how to fix
that. I know how to fix that. I got it. Trust me. Don't worry. I'll fix it in a second. I know
what to do. Why did you hold this like this? I got you. I need to pause the game. I'm going to
pause the game. Pause the game for a second. I got to win. Don't do it. Don't do it.
Don't do it. Don't do it. That's a mistake. Must destroy the humans. I'm going to fix the lag now.
Check this shit out. Ready? Lag's going to be gone in three, two, one. Check this out.
Look at that. Lag is gone. Told you I was fucking capable of it. Fuck. Why am I so stupid? Okay.
How do I do the magic? It was a magic update? I thought I cut my finger off.
I was like, oh, that's great. Whatever. Hold down A button. They added a kick.
Look at me. There's a kick. I need to get a person here to fight. I want to just sit down here and
just be like, come on and get me. Can I activate this stuff? I got to get this down. It's been a
while. Do you flick it, right? Or do you just push? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right. Let's activate the next one. Die? I mean, that's really fucking far.
All right. Respawn. How do I respawn? Oh, why don't I? Didn't there a lightsaber mod?
Can you do pogo like last time? I don't know. Oh, the storage. Wait, what's this? Oh, Jesus.
Oh, yeah. Where they at? Where they go? Didn't they run by me? Holy shit. He was waiting for me.
Can I take that? Hello, come get me. Where the hell is everybody? All right. Let's wily
coyote this guy. Oh, no. Oh, shit. Wait, did I get wily coyoted? Oh, no. This is when the thing
falls and I go. Give me this. Oh, get him. Wait, can I like strangle people? Get him. Fuck.
I hate you motherfucker. Where'd that guy go? Oh, here's somebody. Give me the fucking sword.
Holy shit. She's fall down the stairs. They pull the fucking bows and arrows.
Why is it lagging? And why can't I keep this in my ear? It's lagging so bad. Shoot. Come here.
Come here. Listen. Listen to me. You got to stay in school. You got to study every day. Look at me.
You don't want to end up like this. You don't want to end up in constant fucking war.
Look at me. You can't even look at your dear old dad anymore. You got to fight for how many
voice cracks are going to happen here in the next 20 seconds. Don't look. Don't look at him. Don't.
Let me tell you one last thing before I go.
Reef case with all the money in it. You'll never fucking know.
Ow. Oh, shit. It's coming in grease. Where's Kevin McAllister? He greased up the ladder.
Honey, what's the kick button? What's the kick button?
Get away from me. Get away. I'm going on the slide. No. Mom. Mom. Get out of here. It's my turn.
Get away from me. I want to kick him in the face so bad.
Oh, my God. I can't, dude. Go up here. Go up. Go up. Go up. Go up. What is this? I don't know
what this is. Where am I? How did I get behind the ladder? What? They left. Oh, my God. My fucking
stomach hurts. Hear that? Hello? My computer's lagging so bad. Ow. Come here. Put that down.
Put that down. Put that down. Put that down. Oops. Give me that. Give me that. Holy shit.
No arrow. Yeah. It didn't work. Ew. Yucky. Why is my game lagging? What's with all the lag, man?
Any bodies? Turn the graphics down? I can't. I turned down some of the lighting. Did that help?
Oh, man. That was fucking so funny. F4. What do we got? Okay. Camera stabilization. I don't know.
Motion blur off. What was that? Alt F4. That's not going to do anything. Change the map. Okay.
Change it in the game. Oh. I forgot how much fun this game actually was. Game is a joy. All right.
From... Oh, shit. That's my powers. This is the update. This is the update, isn't it?
Use magic and slow motion. All right. So, I have fire activated. How do I use the fire? Trigger.
What? Oh, my God. That's so cool. That's unbelievable. All right. I got to change
the graphics. How do I get it? Let me change the graphics. Get the hell out of here. Handbook.
Button on the controller. The menu button. Wait. Oh, shit. Here we go. Custom resolution multiplier.
Motion smoothing. What is all this? Under resolution. Motion smoothing. Off. On. Oh,
I lost you guys. That's not it. Wrong in-game book. Another in-game book? It'll write touchpad.
The menu button opens this. Menu button. The raid? Oh, shit. Who came in?
Incredible Orb is playing Basmophobia. I thought it was Incredible Orb raiding. I was like,
how did that know? I can hold the camera of the right touchpad. I've hit every single button.
What the fuck is that? Menu. Oh, fuck. That scared the shit out of me. Who raided? Who raided?
Touchpad. Touchpad. Touchpad. Touchpad. I've hit every single button. Menu on left hand middle
trackpad? I can't leave the fucking game. Right touchpad and left menu button. What the fuck is
that kind of combo? It's right trackpad and left menu button? Oh, god damn it. All right. Let's go
to the... I'm going to use these new powers. Who raided though? Who raided actually? The raid song?
Okay. Craig. Thanks, Craig. For the raid. Wherever you guys are, I can't really see you.
How about the raid song? Oh, yeah, of course. Everybody get to the battlements. We've got to
raid. We've got to... Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Where are we going? How about the canyon?
Sandler? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Thanks for the raid though. Seriously. Welcome, everybody.
We're going to play some VR today. I had a little bit of technical problems because I opened up a
fucking motorcycle game and it derailed the whole stream. I want... Yeah. You're going to... Oh,
okay. Let's go. You can do that. That's awesome. Unlimited power. Let me show you the true
power of the dark side. Oh, that's not supposed to happen. Oh, that's not supposed to happen at all.
Oh, I'm just an old fucking man without electricity. What? Why did that not work?
Oh, I'm in trouble now. I can barely cross the fucking road on my own. Oh, shoot. Oh, shoot.
This is really not good, is it? Usually I laugh and they get scared.
I lost my... Give me that fucking shield. Give me that shield. That shield, you bastard.
I'm so scared I'm going to fucking hit something in my room.
Okay. Oh, I'm running out of juice. Oh, I can't do it for much longer. Oh, boy. Anybody have an
iPhone charger? Dude, where do I get... Where do I get the fucking lightsabers? Is that just on
Steam Workshop? Is that easy to get? Oh, it's not? Fuck. All right. I don't know. I'm breathing on
this. That's embarrassing. All right. Where's these graphics? Where's the graphics book? Okay.
Here we go. Graphics. Render scale. I'm going to turn that down. Shadows. Mom. Character. Fast
Gen. Character quality. Player. Whatever. NPC. I don't know. Impressions. Yeah. What was that?
Head drop. 0.75. Okay. Cool. All right, man. Let's go. Go to the market. Use magic on a weapon?
You can enchant a weapon? That's so cool. This might be the best VR game. It really might be.
All right. What about like electricity on a weapon? An electricity mug? I'm playing the best one.
Yeah. We're going to get to Alex tomorrow. Actually, I want to see this. Let me look through this.
Onyx? Oh, dude. That's... Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I got to be Wolverine from you too. Just give me
a weapon. Come on, bub. Okay. I like it so far. Let's go. Turn the trigger to pull.
Uh, fuck. Okay. Why can't I pick hard mode? T-Max alive. Totally. Oh. Oh, what the...
Circle of Death? Circle of Death. I don't know. More people playing games than I know, apparently.
Not allowed. Circle of Death. Where'd it go? Who's going to come in first?
It's right in the fucking kidney. Is it alive? Right in both of his ears. Hear that? All right.
Get the... Get this off. Get this... What the fuck? Uh... Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Um, come here. Why did I just... You're an idiot. He slid his own
throat. Now what? Back away. This exploded brain? Why is it so laggy? Which one would you like to die
by? Electricity, fire, or the force-exploded brain move? Which one? Yeah, I would have fixed
fire too. I would have fixed fire too. I'm an avid evil guy in an anime, aren't I? What? Too much
power. Too much power. Wow. Hey. You shut it off, you dick. Hey. Come here. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
How dare you? You get out of here. He's so... He's not dead.
He's just in a scoop for wine. Listen, Jampa. You'll get it, okay? He's... When he comes in the
ring, you don't start swinging, all right? Don't just go right in after the bell. What, are you
out of your mind? Come on, kid. You got this. I know you got this. Come on. Remember. Step, slide,
punch. Step, slide, punch. Stay with me. Step, slide, punch. That's right. Get out. Get in there.
Get in there and get him. How the fuck do you know what's going on? Okay, listen. Oh,
shit. What did I do? Is he all right? Back away. You're away. I got the champ here.
Grab their body parts with that spell. The garbage cards suck so bad.
Does my computer suck? Combine spells? No, you cannot combine. That's just a shitty magic trick.
I gotta drop the graphics even more. Oh, that looks so bad. Get the 3090 already? I would've
got the 3090, but they made like 15 of them. All right, what about this canyon? Find the purple one.
What the fuck was that? It's nothing. Oh, fuck. What happened? I have my own. It's a gigantic.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Don't look into it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha. He's alive? I'm shooting. You just run on them.
You really good shot there.
Next. Well, I got you. Get out. Get out. Ow. Can I get some help? Somebody can help me.
Wait, I know what to do. I need leverage. There we are.
I hit my fucking head right here. Real tragedy. I don't think you guys can even see that.
Am I okay? I think so. Actual blood. No, this is this. We heard it. I want to see it. I want to
see it. Get play space boundaries. Ah, well, here, let me, I'm going to come in close for you
here. The reason why I don't have play space boundaries is because, um, well, I have it at
standing room only, but I still move around like I'm a fucking dickhead. I have to move around. I
can't not move around in VR. Oh, how long? Let me go take a piss and make sure that I didn't like
scuff up the front of my head. I'll be right back. It's a dent.
All right, let's see. I'm fine. Look, look at this hair. No, that's not a mark from, that's a mark.
Goodness. That's a mark from the headband. Where is the, where is the headband? Hey,
where's the headband? I don't know. I'll be right back. I gotta find it. Battle for glory.
You're leading the way to victory. Fight among your people and the Empire.
All right. You, you and me. All right. Fine, buddy. Oh shit there. What do we want to win?
I missed. Don't move. Don't you move. You listen to me. You and I are going to team up.
You're going to team up. We're going to kill those guys over there. You understand?
I'll do it. Hey, fuck. All right. Get out of my way. Wait a minute. I can grab his hand.
Wait a second. Look, I can grab his hand. Let's go. It's time to go home. Get in the car.
Come on. Come here. Let's go. Let's go. Come on. You're ruining my fucking joke. It's so laggy.
I can't even fling. Come on. I can't even see what I'm doing. I'm about to crash this fucking
computer, man. Okay. Okay. Okay. I've had, I've had just about enough of you. Give me the axe.
Killed me. He was just behind me the whole time. Oh my God. It's so laggy. Punk. No honor among
thieves. No honor among thieves. There ain't no honor among thieves anymore. Okay, let's go.
Update fucked up performance by a lot. Really? This feels like really bad. Even when we come,
usually it gets back to like 80, 60, 70, 80 frames a second. You know what I mean? It's like
memory leak or something. I don't know. What does that mean? Post-processing? NES resolution.
That feels the same. Next game. What am I doing next? Enable motion smoothing? Projection in
Steam VR. 1v1 game mode using more processing power than the graphics card. We'll play the room.
It's time to relax. It's time for the relaxing portion of this room. Saw 2. I'm going to download
the lightsaber thing. This game is fucking hilarious though. It's so much fun. It just
kind of runs like shit lately, like I would know. All right. Let's play the room. It's time to chill
out. I'm looking forward to this. I've actually been waiting for this. When I heard this came out,
I was ecstatic. This is going to be the ultimate in Pog video games. You guys are going to be so
happy about this. Okay. Where is it? The room. All right. Here we go. I hope this is what I think it
is. It's going to be awesome. It's going to be fucking fantastic. I can't wait. No, not the room.
Like Tommy Wiseau. We got free center in the windows. Yeah, this just looks good. That brings
me back. Yeah. And look, we have actual frames. Are you already disappointed? Time that person
out for 30 seconds. I have no idea. The room VR dark matter supports multiple profiles. I'm sure
it does. This is a game about, okay, let me, let me give you an example. This is a game about,
it's a game about and about and you don't understand soon enough. I need hints sometimes.
It can be kind of fucking hard. Standing. Please calibrate your standing height for the most
comfortable gameplay experience. Stand still in the center of your play area and press calibrate.
Boomsbury police station. Getting dark. I should get back to work. I can't wait to open up like
three boxes. Oh, sick. We're at the projector handle with dozens of disappearances in just
a few weeks, but this is one of the strangest. Bird area of the British Institute of Archeology
where the professor was last seen. How can someone disappear from this? Dr. Montgomery
specialized in priceless Egyptian relics. He told colleagues he was on the verge of some great
discovery. There you are. This is the piece the professor was studying when he disappeared.
Nothing else was missing. No evidence of a struggle or break in. It doesn't make sense.
I should check my desk in case the sergeant has left a report. The gentleman was asking
after you. He gave me a parcel, said it would help with the disappearances. The damn thing was
making the strangest noise. The constable told me he was hearing things. I put it in your wall safe.
You want whatever. Pick up the key. Excellent. Let it go to put it in your inventory. Okay,
what's this? Can I open the inventory? I mean, it's just so intuitive. That's an intuitive
inventory. To get this open, there's something in evidence storage. I gotta go to evidence storage.
I cannot wait to fucking play this game. Evidence storage. I wonder if we confiscated something
that can help me crack a safe that'll be listed on the blackboard. Oh, safe cracking. William
Crack. He cracks saves. William Clark. Safe cracking. Box number. I don't know. Please file
evidence with the correct case number for me. The filing system isn't that complicated. Your
detectives work it out. John E. Assault. E3. Aldem Wright. WW2. William Crack. C6.
Wilco Streamer. Loves game. Hates chat. Oh, the hints only show up if you can't figure anything.
Look, do you see all these little gears and shit? I can't wait. This is gonna be so
fun. Clipboard. This thing. A wine opener. Back to the safe. Where do I put this?
D-crack is safe? Oh, you mean, you mean me turn around? Don't you like put it, how do I put it
somewhere? Mic is fucked. The mic is fucked up? Why is the mic fucked up? Mic is fucked up? What
did I do to it? I don't know. I don't know. Was it when I bumped into it? When I smashed into it?
Maybe when I hit it. Sounds the same. I don't know.
Alright, how do I put this? How do I get this on here? No, no, no, no, no, no, it's okay.
This should not, I, there's a hint available to pull the tip. Now that I have the safe cracker,
I can get to work on the safe. Yeah, I, what do you, what? Oh, it's so satisfying. Oh, I love it.
Alright, we're gonna turn some dials here. Shit, almost. Yeah. Loves it. I do love it.
Forgive my unorthodox approach detective, but I have vital information relating to a case
you're investigating. We have questions, so please take these lenses and let me show you
what I can explain. This is the only, the beginning. Craftsman. Take the lenses? I got,
wait, wait, wait, wait. First box. I mean, usually it's like a box with a box and then a box inside
of a box. Open the inventory and pull the highlighted tab to put on the eyepiece.
Alright, this is the real first box. You don't have any idea how happy I am to be playing this.
Alright, so what do we got? We got, let's examine the box. Got that. Got this. Moon,
moon with a star on it. I don't know, any of these move? Yup, there you go. Look at that. Okay,
here we go. Then pull that tab. Tabs. Hey, looking good. You want tabs? Right here, look at this.
Thank you. Okay, now what? Whoa, project anything? Wait a minute. Yes. Boom, this is the VR made
of room. Welcome detective to the hidden realm of the Gnoll. The disappearances you are investigating
are part of something more sinister than you can imagine. Show you what happened to these people
and perhaps together we can avert any further loss. This document is no ordinary letter. The
Gnoll connects it to me. This author used the eyepiece to reveal the connection. Find the others,
discover their fates. The Craftsman. Oh, the British Institute of Archaeology. This is the room Dr.
Montgomery was working when he disappeared. How did I get back here? So many toys to play with
in here. I can't. This is the arm made. What does it do? I don't know yet. We gotta do, we gotta do
it one by one here. I gotta get something over here. I can't do this yet. What about over here?
What's this? All right, we need a piece for this. Something goes right there. It's like a lady's
face. Whatever it is. Hey, check chat. Gonna take him five hours? Hey, I am a veteran of the room.
Okay, I'll have you know. I'm not just some scrub that does not play. All right, what is this?
The poster pulled the sarcophagus from the storage room. Take through. Take to a practice of taking
about followers with them throughout their life. They believe this rite could rapid contain their
souls, but the hieroglyphics don't follow any known lexicon. Does it make any sense?
All right, well, I don't, I wanna, I can figure this. Let's do this. What do we got here?
Touch this yet? That, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, what's going on here?
A piece? Yeah, that means something. What does that mean? Grab the mic sensitivity?
Why are people talking about the mic? I must have fucked something up when I punched it and
ripped out a cord or something. It's the wrong mic? Oh, when I turn around, you can't hear me.
I get you. All right. Well, we can't, we, we gotta get something that fits in here.
I can't grab this, right? No, can't do this yet. What about this guy? No, can't open that.
Oh shit. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, whoa. All right. I got that open.
Now. Yeah, almost. That not it? That, I got it, right? No, it's blocked up there. It's blocked
up top. How do I release that shit? Oh, excuse me. Behind you. What the fuck, dude? You're a
warp has a face. This is to open the door, right? Probably over there.
Uh, I don't have any face words, dude. What am I missing? I'm missing something here.
Like open that, but I can't. I don't get this all the way. That's open. Not even in the cameras.
Fuck. I thought that was a one real wall. Hey, I'm back. How are you? I can't pick that up.
What did I miss here? Something something's here that I missed. I guess I could just travel with
this thing. We'd go somewhere else. You have to go somewhere else. Oh, what was that? That's a
sarcophagus. Nice beer gut. The door is unlocked, but too heavy to open by hand. There's a rope
attached to it that leads to a set of pulleys though. Yeah, I know. Beer gut. It's not a beer
gut. It's a, it has to be something with this by hand. So I need to do this thing. I open this
coming out, but it can't just Nancy. This is way better than Nancy Drew. Hey, yo, got mesh. Shut up
and Turkey peanut oil diet for the right side of the door. But can I, I can't really go over here.
Like this is connected to that. How do I get this to move? How do I get this to like,
how do I get this to turn? Get the fuck out of the goddamn way here. What's a punch? Whatever's in
front of me. Can I, can I, can I pull? Oh shit. Look at that. Let's go get this shit out. Oh yeah.
That's a big guy right there. Porter was back asking about my progress. A curious fellow. He
seemed almost confused that I couldn't crack the code. He gave me a parcel, said it had been left
for me in the post room. Inside was an odd looking lens along with a note that said the lens would
help me in my work. Goodness knows that it was going to help me. What do you got? I hit him in
the head with a, with a crowbar. Oh shit. Brass. Wait, wait, wait. Wasn't there a circle somewhere
that needed a circle? Something needed a circle here. Where did this need to go? Cursor for
cursor. Mouse on the screen. You guys call the, did I get it? Did I get it? Over here? Right there,
right? Shit. Where'd this fucking go? Head? Want it back. Doesn't know shapes. In the book.
Oh, that just spawned something in there. We gotta spawn. Yep. The eyepiece. Oh yeah.
Fuck is that? He'll do, okay. We got a lot of shit going on here. That's new. What did I just do?
Did I win? What? I just pressed, did I press it, did I do it? Everybody understand what just happened?
I had to unlock. Yeah, I did. But how do I open? Should be unlocked then, right?
That easy? Or am I doing something wrong? I feel like you have to like move this.
Please smash the reddit shelf. I'm, I don't want that to happen. That'd be something I'm doing wrong
here. Need something to put in there. Oh, that AC feels so fucking good right now. I'm such a
degenerate. I thought this was a slot machine. That we need a triangle pointing up. I just won
accidentally. And now what? Okay. That's going to go this way. This one, right? What, rabbit?
20 to here. And what animal? What's the animal? Uh, where does that go? That's, that'll fit this.
Oh shit. I've got a tool. Okay. All right. It's getting more, we're getting more interesting here.
Animal. Generate gambler. Generate gambler. What is it? What's the shape? Like a little claw.
Wait, can I do that? It's vibrating like I can. Oh shit. There's even more of this crap.
No mouse on the screen. Wait a minute. Come on. Really? That's not like the tool to like break
into his head. I see this now. Nothing new from that. Touch him. Find him at the beginning.
Oh, tool, tool, tool, tool, tool, tool, tool. Tool, tool, tool. Check it out. Oh yeah. Sick.
Nice. Open up. Oh, the distinctively shaped head. I need to turn that. Brave stone disc. It's a
that goes over there. How do I move this? Okay. Wait, wait, wait. We got, um, uh, eagle and
flamingo and stop. Flamingo and, uh, bee. Wasp. Flamingo, wasp. What do we got here? Flamingo,
wasp. Ow. Where's the, where is it? Flamingo, wasp. We're over here. Read chat for a second.
I'm here. Actually on screen. Saved. Saved. All right. We're good. I got flamingo selected.
So now I got that tool. Right? Yeah. All right. Let's go back over here. The reason why this game
is so much fun. All right. Let me fucking actually talk to you guys. The reason why this game is fun
is because one thing leads to another thing. Another thing leads to this. That opens that,
that opens that box and then that box opens on its own. Wait, I got a match. Okay. Hold on. Give me
a minute. Got to be green or is it going to be green? Red and blue and wait, did they? Oh fuck.
Okay. I, uh, they all have to be red. Rubik's cube. I mean, does it have to be red, green and
that's it. That's it. I got it. I did it. Let's go. Open up. What the hell does that do? Stuck his
tongue out at me. I can't even look at it now. You guys have ruined this for me. I can't, I can't.
Somebody said one thing and that's all it took. Okay. Well, now what do I do? These were instructions
on how to do the first part. I'm such an idiot. Wait, it came out of all four places. Wait,
not over here, right? What else did I not do? Over here? We got, I don't understand this part.
I'm looking for an animal. I guess we could, it's one of the four chance. Of course we could
just guess. What is this? Uh, yep. Another one of those. Okay. Flamingo. It's another, it's a one
out of four chance. Okay. I'm going to get from that box. I am going to get a flamingo. Oh,
why, why does the cursor keep coming back? I'm not doing that. You're clear. I'm clearly across
the whole room. All right. Think. Think for a second. Think. Can't move this. This is the
tool that I'm going to be able to slide in here and then pull this out. Press her again? No.
Pulley system can lift up the mummy. Can it? Goodness. Look at you. Look at what you just said.
Quite a different pulley now. Is there a dog? Oh shit. Look at this. I'm pretty strong in this.
I knew that was going to happen. Pull it back up.
Okay. It is a dog. All right. It's Otto. Um, he can't really come in here right now.
What am I going to do about that? He can't come in here right now. I'll be like, Oh, Otto,
where is he? I don't want to step on him. Let me see what he wants. Let him in. No, that's dangerous.
I don't want to, I could, I could like hurt him. All right. Let me, hold on. Let me go see what he
wants. Hold on. All right. Let me see what he wants. I think he might, maybe he wants to go.
Give me one sec. I'll be right back. He's here. He's in the room. I just wanted to come in. He's
all the way in the corner over there. So he's, he's not in any, uh, play area. There's no reason
why I would ever go all the way over there. Oh him? I don't know what I'm doing. Right over here.
He just wanted to come and lie down on a blanket. He is, he is like all I've, there's no reason why
I would go over there. He just wanted to come in and hang out. You said that's all you wanted?
We did it boys. Hey, you having fun in the room? I'm looking forward to this game for like a
hundred years and half like, half like, half, uh, like, you know, like half like, uh, half
like Alex, like doing that tomorrow. And that's what we're doing the whole stream. So that's why
I want to play a few of the games that I had lined up that are not half life Alex. That's
what we're doing all stream tomorrow. Fucking motorcycle game. It looked fun too. That's the
worst part about it. The game is this. This is called the room VR a dark matter. Come out on
screen. No, I don't have, I don't have a feed. I don't know what happened here, but we can get
back to normal. That'd be good. All right. So thanks for the one guy. That was a really good
advice to lift up the sarcophagus with the other thing. Pretty sick. Well, I need my team of
assistants to play VR. It'll be like three people in the room. One to make sure I don't hit a wall.
One to make sure I can hear the audio until I take care of my dog. I got that ball. I could sense
the shelf. I could smell it. Whoa. I got his beard. I can't like take his beard off. What is
this for? I put like a walnut in here. Oh, no, no, no. I got the, what's the globe for
and a little circle. What the fuck are you talking about? I need an animal. We got it. Look at it.
We got, Oh, you're close. All right. You guys see an animal? Oh, this is probably important.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I don't know what that does. I have that glove though. Let's
show. Can I put the globe in here? Mayo stomach. Damn it. Damn it. Ah, ah. What about in here?
Let's put it in his mouth. Add munkah. Hmm. What's munkah? Hmm. How do I do with this thing? Oh,
well, it looks like I got myself a sword, ceremonial dagger. That goes in his mouth,
right? You open the mouth and you slip it in. It goes there. No, this is not what you do.
I got a sword. Can it go over there? What the fuck was that? I just gave it to him. What does
it want me to do there though? Okay. It's a symbol. I don't swear in front of Otto. He's mean
something, but I don't know what they mean. Okay. Found it. It's dog pot. What the fuck does that
mean? Dog pot. Oh, that's just the solution to the thing that I guessed. Egger? Egger here? Oh,
yes. Okay. Now what? Faved cylinder. Here? I think this goes over here. It looks like it matches,
doesn't it? Going inside of his body somewhere? He missed four holes, man. I don't know which hole
it goes in. Look at that little indentation right there. Up your chair, up your ass. No,
no thanks. I think I'm okay. I think I'm going to be good. I do with you. It's a puzzle. It's a
puzzle. It's a puzzle. It's a puzzle. It's a puzzle. You're going to be in the right part of
the room. It's a puzzle. I have to be standing in the right part of the room. Oh shit. That's so
cool. That's so cool. Now what? Now what? Oh, let's get. Oh. Hellas. Let's go. It feels so good.
There? Open up. Bingo. Oh shit. Stone tile. And another thing. And I got the, what's the Harry
Potter thing that they all chase? What is that? Oh Lord. I got to rebuild like Stonehenge.
All right. Wait, that's not right. Okay. Oh, hold on. Bingo. There's the piece. The piece that we
need. And there's a bowl in there. Dude. Okay. Cool. Looking good. Sound design is really good.
Yeah. No, this would be their fifth game or sixth game in this series. I am begging you to go play
the room. At least the first one and the second one. If you like just like playing with little
trinkets and toys and clicking and boxes and shit. It's unbelievable. It's one of the most fun
series on steam right now. I don't know how much it is. It's less than like 15 bucks in it.
It's an ADHD game. Yeah. I mean, call it whatever you want. Okay. I have the other piece here.
Here we go. Definitely flamingo. Metal handle. Oh, where does this go? Oh, a decorated amulet.
Oh, wait. Oh, now they have a stone tile with a metal token in it. Now I got two tokens.
Uh, I thought that was going to be right. Tokens in his mouth. Not a bad idea. I mean,
it wasn't, it actually kind of was a bad idea. It really, it really was a bad idea.
Three tokens. Did I miss anything over here? This is done, right? This box is done. Yeah. Here we go.
Ooh, that makes a good clicking sound. Oh, fuck. Come on. Let's go. Okay. Let's bust in the box.
Find out. Here we go. Oh, wow. He's go in there. That's right. No, let's go put it inside of him.
So does it matter the order? Oh, this look, this is organs. This is a lungs. Heart. This is
intestine. I don't know. Kidneys. Brain. Heart. Uh, that's a heart, right? No, is this, this is a
liver? No, that's a stomach. That looks like a brain. This looks like a brain. Okay. Got it.
Thank you. Congratulations. You have completed my quest. Now please take the riches inside of my
chest. Yes. Whoa. It actually is a heart. Have to take his heart? Dude, guys, this is, I don't know
about it. All right, we got to go back to this. Not the string. I supposed to do that? Is he going
to be alive behind me? He's going to be alive behind me, isn't he? Oh, ice. Holy shit. Okay.
Oh, he's been here. He's always been here since the beginning, waiting, waiting at the beginning
at the temple. They all wait at the beginning. I see them. They aren't blind like me. Trump, right?
This, where are we going? Oh, the beginning. I feel like I'm at Disney world right now.
Let's do a Disney ride. It's a good one though. Oh, but this is the, how do I put this? Oh, hey,
loading that. I have two more of those to do. Oh, the note. Long one. Welcome back detective.
Perhaps now you can understand the danger we face. I mean, I don't really, I don't really know what
the danger is, but I guess it's scary. The artifact you collected now holds the very essence, the soul,
if you will, of the professor. Sacrifice will help further my work and bring these arcane forces
safely under my control. Onward to another of those lost unfortunates, a servant of God this time.
He was searching for some long forgotten relic. You must uncover what he found. A crack head.
Oh, we're in a church. Church, perhaps this reverend will have some answers for me.
We don't, let's go. Let's start our search. A box. And there's just a big ass key in here. You got
it. Cool. Okay, we got a door in front. Thing on the left. Go left. Oh, this is the podium. Okay.
Here. Six, one, five, eight, seven, three, nine, eight, one, four. Or it's probably going to be
some Sudoku math problem, right? The puzzle was fucking easy. The puzzle was just pretty good.
Oh, this door. It just opens. I got the key. I got the key, man. Oh, shit. All right, lots of
levers here. Maybe we should have done that. Where's Obi-Wan Kenobi here? An old man I've
not seen before approached me after Evan saw the legend of this chapel and the relic hidden
somewhere within these stone walls. He gave me a small box that it contained something that would
help me, something which would unlock truth. The well. Wait, wait, wait. We saw those, didn't we?
Yep. All right. N plus W thing. Plus E thing. There it is. Zoomers Maulding. Why do we have
Zoomers Maulding? All right, well, something obviously goes in there. I don't know what.
Goes in here, obviously. I don't know what. Oh, there's tons of places you can go through.
Miles the Templar's carried the cargo. An hour before midnight, the attack began.
That's a clock. How do I change the clock? There's a lot of space here. That's a plate
for the well, right? Mirror fragments set in stone? All right, whatever. It's a process, right?
Look at these books. Books? Wait, put the night vision on. Make sure there's nothing in there.
All right, I got the well. I'm good to go. That go in here. No, place to go behind me.
I mean, absolutely no disrespect. I mean, no disrespect in here, okay? I just say that all
the time. I say that all the time. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I really am sorry. Check auto. Oh,
he's okay. He's right over here. Auto is gone. He's right over here. We're concerned. He's right
there. He's okay. He's just chilling over there. He's lined up. Man out the window.
Okay, let's go. Is this for the clock? Well, I can't move that now. It's not. It's going to be.
There's going to be a whole thing here. Turn around. I have this bowl. What do I do with the
bowl? Can I get in here? What do I do with that bowl? I'm not going to steal auto's way over there.
Get a real job, German. Nine to five. How do we even respond to the get a job comment?
Hey, get a job. All right, dad. I'll do it. I got to get that to 11 o'clock.
Oh, hold on. Right there. First. Hold on a sec. Am I changing the clock? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that doing anything? I don't know. I can't tell if this is doing anything.
Lock. I'm not doing shit. What are you talking about? I'm doing anything.
Well, I can go down there though with this. Oh, nice. Okay. Move it. Grab it.
I felt pretty good. Oh, this is telling somebody screenshot this. This is telling me something.
You'd like blue, black, yellow, white, blue, black, yellow, yellow, blue. Okay. Somebody
screenshot that. We're going to need it in like 10 minutes. Oh, that was completely wrong.
screenshot that now. I don't know why. I really don't know. I don't know why. I swear to God,
this is going to sound really weird. I just felt like for one second that my dick was out.
I'm weird. I just, I don't know. I just, I got a weird panic where I'm just like,
holy shit. I think, I think my dick is out. I don't know why that's getting to him.
All right. What else? What? I got that bowl back here with the numbers are over here.
There's numbers over here. Those two, wait a minute. Two, six, one, six, one, four, five,
eight. I need the four, four, five, eight, seven. Yeah. I need a four. What do we get the four?
Four over there, right? Let me do this bowl. How do I do that bowl? Oh, fuck. This one already,
right? Yeah. I did that one. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's go. Something appeared over there.
But yeah, yeah, yeah. The box, you got it. Yep. Yep.
The crystals look unusual. Perhaps I should use the new lens to examine them.
Strange. It feels like I'm being pulled towards them. Oh my God. This is terrifying.
He just went up. He just went up. He just went to actual height. You see, with the actual size.
Should I jump around? Whoa. I'm inside of this thing. Oh, I guess I'm turning it. Oh goodness.
Okay. And then, whoa, there it is. What do I get? Glass decanter. Hey, that will fit.
Where's that going to, I know where that goes. That goes somewhere interesting.
Goblet of fire. Break it. Orb. Orb. Eat the orb. Eat the orb. Orb. Goblet of fire. No.
Oh, this decanter fits here, but it doesn't do anything. I must have missed something.
Oh, that makes me wicked thirsty. That just made me so thirsty. That makes me so thirsty.
I want to drink this so bad. This is just blue powerade, right? The way that it came into,
it was just blue powerade going in. I want a blue powerade right now, if anybody has any.
We get anything? Oh, the star. And you can go inside. Root forced it. I didn't root force
anything. There we go. This is my favorite part so far. I love that. I'm going to get a screenshot,
right? Oh, it's right there already. Thanks. Thank you. I'll upload that. Okay. There it is.
I got it. I had it. I did? I did. I just did it. I just did it. Did I do it? Blue, red, blue, red,
yellow, orange. Yeah, I got it. Yeah, I just did it, didn't I? That's correct. That's not just
correct. That was correct already. Wait a second. This isn't colorblind. I'm not colorblind. It's
going to spin it up. I'm going to spin it. Okay. Then we flip that around. It's right there. That's
it. I did it, but give it to me. I win. What am I doing wrong here? Do I have to like lock it in?
Like, yes, lock it in. Does it have to be the opposite? Except the one outside.
Isn't it right? In his own world. Yeah, but it's right, isn't it? Don't read chat. They're
just shaking it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I can't wait until you get timed out for fucking five minutes.
I can't wait until you're gone for at least five minutes. Stop reading chat.
A little shaking. Oh, man. That person is right. That person's right.
Got to match that in here. Right. All right. So we need yellow, green.
I got to get the blue there. The wooden box. There's a large lever and two pulleys. I can
use it to change the pattern of light. A hint will be available when the timer has ended.
I can't cheat fast enough. And it more. That's not, that's wrong. I found on the stone door,
I could use the wooden box to shine a matching symbol at the door. So that's correct.
I already did it. That little guy right there. A chess. Oh, man. I just love that bullshit thing.
Um, Stormwind, who's the Stormwind guy? Like the shield of Stormwind, right?
I'll go check. Over there. Take that. Thank you.
Gonna make that. Somebody screenshot that. Hello, blue, pink, yellow, blue. Got it.
Oh, let's make that thing pink, yellow, blue. Sorry. That was okay. We're good.
Okay. We're not good. I'm getting tangled. Right. Well, shit. What was it? Pink, pink, yellow,
blue. But those were different. And I can't, I wouldn't purple. Uh, what is this? I think one
of these, this was flipped around. This one was up the other way. Like that. Right. I'll let you.
What the fuck are you doing, man? Like that. Right. And it was pink, yellow, blue. Is that it?
Did I get it? I think I got it. Why is the camera facing,
how come the camera's not facing the other person? Why is the camera facing you? That's it right
there. That's the one right there. All right. I got to face the camera at the right guy.
Um, I put a mirror over there. I sure do. That's something else on your back. Um, that's a mirror,
a mirror, um, hanging on his utility belt. I need something to go here. Um, this, some Tetris
piece has to go right here. Uh, it, it does not, does not suck or burst your bubble there, but
nope, I think you're very incorrect. How does this go? Our piece. Spin it. Up here?
There? Possible. Right here. Oh, I haven't been in here in a while. Was there anything in here I
could do? Uh, ha ha ha ha ha. Remember with the Victory Royale in room four.
Got another box, ladies and gentlemen. It's a big one. Not going there yet. Block picking tool,
Can I reach in here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Probably have to go in there first.
Oh, right.
I'm inside the vault.
I know I'm getting closer. I can feel it.
I hear it. Worlds within worlds.
The old man can't have known what this
lens revealed. Why would he give me something
this valuable?
Why would he do that?
Alright, let's see.
I need to pick this lock.
Being tiny.
I got that.
I have to go open the other side?
How do I get on the other side? How do I get over there?
How do I get over there?
How do I get over there? What the fuck?
Alright, I'm done. I'll see you guys
in like a week.
I'm going to get the fuck out of here. Fucking stupid.
How do I get over there?
Unlock this side?
Okay.
I can't go in the other side.
I can't go in this side.
I can only walk in there.
Brain, ha ha ha.
Up on the right.
Come on, I'll get it.
My nose is so itchy. It bugs all of my eyes.
It bugs all of me.
Shit. I had it too.
Alright, it's done.
It's fleas.
Not fucking fleas, folks.
Right in the AC.
I've been streaming for three and a half hours?
Really?
Any medallion?
What's with this box?
I can't go up or down with this.
I can't drag it down.
Play Left 4 Dead 2 for a minute.
Probe! Oh, this is going to be hell.
I know I'm not going to do very well on this.
I think this is going to be horrible.
Slug Pug.
Should I delete? Where are you?
Should I delete Slug Pug?
I added it for like an hour one day and I just was like,
you know what? Fuck it. I'm going to get rid of it.
Should I get rid of Slug Pug or no?
That's medallion number two?
Yeah, fucking kill it.
Please do. It sucks.
I can't even see it. This isn't a VTTV.
Probably one more.
I don't. I don't like this one.
This is the Impossible Staircase thing.
I'm getting Super Monkey Ball flashbacks right now.
I feel like I'm playing Monkey Ball.
It's freaking me out.
I've got to turn this all over.
How do I even manipulate this?
Probably all screaming right now.
Like, dude, just pull the fucking rope, dude.
Good. Come in.
That's one of them.
I'm going to get the second one.
Yo, Jerma, that's a nice ass you got there.
It's supposed to just like,
fake comment.
Alright, so in here,
where's the second one? Up there.
We're going to go up the stairs.
Here we go. We've got to end up here.
That's where we have to end up.
We're going to go that way, around,
that way, that way, across.
Oh, we go over here,
through there. We go up these stairs.
We go around. He's got it.
Bingo. Let's end this place.
Let's go, skip to the top.
Told you I was going to get it.
That would be number three.
Stream is making me feel like I drank too much Nyquil.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Is that an off-handed,
boring stream comment?
That was pretty good.
If so, that was pretty clever.
I'm having fun
in my puzzle game, okay?
Under the stars of Taurus,
the boomer fell.
The Templars lay defeated, yet the cargo
was saved. Why does everyone
love me?
You're talking about me.
End of this. This is fun. Yeah, it's fun.
I've been looking forward to this game.
Yo, chubby bunny.
How fast do you think I can move?
Under the stairs of Taurus,
the banner fell.
Templars lay defeated, yet the cargo was saved.
Under the stars of Taurus, the banner did
fall.
Under the stars of Taurus,
the banner did fall.
Now, here's the question.
I know that that's
Gemini.
I don't know if that is Taurus.
That's Taurus, right? No, that's the goat.
What's the goat? The ram?
Ares. Ares the ram.
Binding of Isaac. That's the one that
destroys the whole room when you use it.
Bacon. Bacon.
Pisces is the fish.
Question mark. What's the Taurus?
Taurus is the horn. Taurus is the horns.
That's not the goat. That's not the goat.
The sheep, whatever it is. Ares the goat.
One with the horns.
Taurus is under one. What are the two M's?
Taurus is ten.
Okay, so we gotta get ten.
We gotta get this ten o'clock.
What about doing these medallions?
I know.
I know where they go, right over here.
On screen? Yeah, man.
Look, we've been doing all kinds of
crazy shit in VR. I wanna do a puzzle game.
Where do these go?
Look at this. Slug storm.
They're on coke.
I am not on
coke. I am sorry to do.
I guess like, uh, that unfortunately
for you, I don't know what.
You want me to be on coke?
Ooh, how about you just relax?
If we're gonna do some working
practice, we can find a way to fix it. Of course it's not working.
Hammer? I have a hammer.
Copper? Wait, we gotta
go upstairs now.
Remember I told you that we needed
that shit? Big thing
that was upstairs.
What was that though? What actually?
More fun than Skyrim.
There are clumps of hair
falling out.
Imagine that turn.
It looks like a big fucking clump of hair
just falls. I turn over here.
Huge clump of hair.
I'm just bald in fucking five
places.
I will tell you this though.
Do not fuck around in VR for this long
because man, your hair is
changed for a year.
You wanna know why I do all the
VR streams in a row?
And we don't take any breaks?
And it's like five, six, or seven
VR streams in a row? Because this shit goes back
in the closet because my hair
is ruined for like two years.
Until new hair
grows back, it's ruined.
Mallet, I got the mallet.
Hey, Templar, I fell in a fierce battle. The horror was
laid bare by the light of a full moon.
Alright, is that like
Uncle Fester machine that you hold
and it just vibrates your hands?
By the way, I can
do that shit on the highest setting and not let
go. I actually did it recently.
The thing that just goes
and the thing laughs at you, I held it the entire
time. You want? Ask
R.T. Gamecrub. He was literally
in the room. Literally in the room
while I'm sitting there just going, yeah,
this don't even fucking hurt. And they all
called me a psycho. Everybody was like, you're a psycho.
You're a fucking weirdo. And I'm
just like, good. Play
Jump King. Alright, actually time that person out
for five minutes. You are a weirdo.
I'm not, why am I such a weirdo?
Alright, let's go. Alright, because I
can do the Uncle Fester machine thing?
Old people use that machine.
Guys, okay.
You try it. You try it on easy when you see it
next time. Next time you see that machine,
I want you to do it on easy and then I want you to go,
oh my god, Jerma's
so much stronger than I am. That machine
fucking scared me.
Oh wow. Boom!
What do I do? Am I looking at this shit
here? Am I paying attention to the banners?
Oh, it was under the banner.
It did fall. Under
Taurus it called.
Under Taurus it did
call the banner that would show them all.
Right? Whatever it is, the one banner
to rule them all, Taurus is here
to stall.
This one? That one.
Pumps of hair. You know what?
Ah, quiet.
I want you to, alright, the next like, I'm gonna
I mean tomorrow we're doing VR but I don't know if I can
do it by then. I'm gonna get like a bunch of
fucking hair, like just like a wig and cut a bunch
of hair out of the wig.
Like the Halloween store and like
get it in here and like have it be coming out
and shit on stream. I don't
know what this even means but apparently it's like under
one of these banners. But I don't know
what that mean.
Somebody will get a good screenshot.
Upside down, okay. I know what to do.
Let's go. Banner that it would fall
or whatever. That was important.
Although we don't have a disc or anything over there.
There's no disc.
Bugpug. Full stream.
And this is gonna put me in trouble. Cog
goes where? Nice.
Gonna have a huge indent on my
face. It hurts. Oh, okay.
Taurus at ten o'clock.
It did fall.
And ten o'clock
to save us all.
Or something. Whatever.
No, it was eleven o'clock.
And it was a full moon.
Full moon.
Taurus at ten.
Oh, I gotta... What does that do, man?
Let me get a close up
view of this.
That's... Okay.
Oh, don't know where that
goes. Oh, auto check. Auto.
Right.
Look at the other one. That's not gonna bounce.
Bounce off that
one. I don't have that one.
Oh, the piano.
The organ.
Oh, okay. Here we go.
So why is it so dark in here?
Hold on. It's dark as hell in here.
You guys get out. I'm just a silhouette in the
room. Better.
Wait. That's the question.
Wait, wait, wait. What is this?
Germa, frankly, I...
Germa, frankly, I find your avoidance of an answer to the
question of slug poggins problematic.
I've been an avid viewer of the channel for fifteen years
and as such I can clearly see the great value of slug
pog is brought to this channel. Please don't
kill the slug pog. It holds us together. It's a sticky
slug slime. It's being removed at the end
of the stream. Like, I'm just gonna get rid of it. It's ugly.
And it annoys everybody.
It's being removed in about
thirty to forty minutes.
Or is it? Stay tuned. Find out. Or is it?
Find out. I'm so scared to take
this headband off. I really am.
I'm scared that I'm gonna take this off
and there's not gonna be anything underneath
her. Oh!
You know in the movie
where the guy puts his hand on the
ball in the class?
In the science class?
It's not even a movie. It's just in class.
That's not
coming back for a while.
I'm in a lot of trouble now.
Oh my
fucking
God!
Oh!
Ray man!
It looks like it hurts. And it does.
Trust me when I say it fucking hurts.
You can't do VR. It's not possible.
This is why it's never gonna take off.
One point eight percent of people on
Steam have VR.
Do you want this to happen to you?
No you don't. You don't want to look like this.
You don't want to like
lose the top fucking part of your
hair? You're using the five
year old outdated
I can't even take myself seriously.
You can see the scalp.
I've ruined my fucking
head. This is gonna take
years for this to come back normally.
This is gonna take a decade. And by
a decade by the way I'll be 45
and it'll just be gone anyways.
Brush it? No! I'm not
brushing it. I'm not brushing it.
I'm gonna go in the bath and I'm gonna hold my head underwater
and put a conditioner in my hair. This is a
chaotic stream.
Okay, ready?
Would you swipe right?
That's the
guy that you accidentally super like.
And you go
Oh fuck.
Are you super like
me? What was it?
You like me a lot apparently.
Do you like to go on a date?
No, Rayman.
Rayman was the best.
Rayman is the best description.
I really like this
view. I feel
pretty confident right now.
Remember me? German985.
Good to meet you.
That's me. Welcome to the stream.
I'm pretty handsome. I'm a pretty handsome guy.
Don't you think?
I made it
worse. It's dead.
It's actually all dead hair.
It's a bird's nest. Let the
light hit it. Somebody fucking electrocuted
me. Take the shirt off.
Like that'll help.
I don't even want to touch it. It's gonna all fall off.
Imagine if I actually
pulled a clump.
Upside down. Hey, show feet.
Is that really what you're asking
right now? After this?
That's what you're asking.
I gotta cut it all off.
In VR.
Alright, let's get in here and do the organ.
You gonna do the castanza?
I thought the headband was gonna help. The headband
might have actually made it worse.
Get down. Your hair is fine.
Let's go.
Where the heck am I?
Where the heck am I? I can't see anything.
This is fucking really immersive.
Today I hit the fucking thing.
It didn't even work. I was trying to...
Are those glued to the wall?
It's been baby-proofed.
What the hell are we doing before I
panicked about my appearance?
Like how my hair is gone?
I'm gonna leave conditioner in my hair.
I'm going to play Half-Life Alex tomorrow.
I'll be lucky if there's anything left.
Bald. Bald. Wear a wig.
Why not try a beanie?
I tried a beanie before and my head was sweating
so much that I got
zits all over my forehead.
All over my face.
I had zits in my hair.
I remember being like, ow, fucking
zits.
VR sucks.
Okay?
It's just do a cool thing
and torture yourself.
VR fucking sucks.
It's so cool.
It's so much fun.
But holy shit, you lose like
three months of your life every time you play it.
Alright, let's do this.
Oh, up the stairs, right? Yeah.
How do we get back up there? Anybody
remember?
Okay. Popper?
Thank you. Popper? Thank you.
Oh. Oh, nice.
Oh. Oh, shit.
I think it is.
What the heck?
Bull.
How do I get over there? Bice is over there. How do I get over there?
Okay. Um.
Do I get out? Bro, what the heck?
I don't know what I just did. Wait a minute.
The hell did I just do? What is this doing?
Whoa. What's going on over there?
Uh.
Hat. Hat with a hat?
What are you talking about? Rat Pog. Rat Pog.
Did all of them just face the same direction like that?
Yeah, did they just face the same
direction like that? Rat in the hat.
Where's the rat in the hat?
Do you not see the rat in the hat?
Oh, dude. What are you guys talking about?
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Hold on.
That's where I'm standing, right?
Um. Did I get one that can
turn? I have no idea.
I don't know. At behind you.
I think Xanax feels like
the game audio is muted?
No, it's not.
Wait. Like that?
That's not right. This is not right.
I don't know. We're going back in.
What am I doing? Oh, that's the shell.
Ooh. Holy shit.
Okay, cool. I got it. I figured it out.
No, I didn't. Fuck. It's gotta be a shorter one.
Okay. It's gotta be a short
one. This one is correct.
Kind of. So it's this
whatever one is right here, that's correct.
But that one isn't. It's gotta be this one
there. Let's go.
Oh, that's correct.
Another one of those. That one right
there. Put that one right there.
How about that one?
How about that one, folks?
That was wrong. Poor hair.
I'm so sad about it.
Why is this... I can't...
Why can I not spin it anymore?
Exit right there.
Exit right there? I can't...
I don't know. I'm there.
I need a lip. Is there an even shorter one?
Wait, is that not it? Open it!
Spin them back around. Yeah, I
can't. I can't touch the wheel.
Walked in place. It's probably just one of these
weird ones here. But I got an idea.
That one. That'd be this one here.
Hey, any of these?
It's none of them! It's none of them!
The wreck pipe is missing? Whose pipe
over here? Give me it.
How do I get it? Give me the pipe.
Give me that pipe. Hey, please.
Come on, this is starting to run a little thin.
Also, already...
Your other left?
Okay. This is...
If I'm looking at it like this is the right
side...
Dude, this is starting to get a little
thin.
Which one? Where is it?
That one here? Or is it one more?
Hey, dude, German, this is like
starting to get a little thin.
God damn it.
Give me this.
You know, this joke is kind of
running a little thin.
Okay. Very cool.
Very fun. Awesome.
Sick.
It's done. Stop saying that, please.
What the fuck did you say?
Nice. That's so cool.
Well, that's the bellows, and then this is another bellows.
The two bellows, and that should turn it back
on.
Play the piano.
He said it. He finally said it.
He did it.
He finally said the thing.
Said Munkah S.
Is this a dumb thing?
Play it. Piano time.
Come to my opera.
Wait, wait, wait! There's not enough keys!
I can't play it.
Hey, hey! Remember this one, guys?
Summer lovin'.
Had me a blast.
Happened so fast.
I met a girl. Cutest could be.
Met a fo-
Cutest could be.
Summer!
Fucking hate it. Okay, let's go.
Look at this shit.
This is a really, really weird way to teach you how to
play the piano. Oh, I lost the ball.
Hey, wait, wait, wait! Okay, now
it's gotta go down there. Shit!
This is fucking hard. Okay, I need one
hand. It's fucking high!
The black keys?
What? Oh, shit.
Get this off. Get it off the screen.
I have a new ball. Alright, it's gotta
go down. I need it to line up
right. No, fuck! I didn't wanna do that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I wanna see at least one
pogchamp. I need- I want at least one
pogchamp for that one. One more. All the way
over here. Hey, hold on.
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it!
What do you guys have to say about that?
Ooh, we can't do it.
That shit. I'll take it and
that's the completion of that fucking room right there,
folks. Here we go.
Now we just gotta line that up. That's red,
blue, and green.
Funko viewers? What?
The Funko
viewers. Okay, red, blue, and
green. Here we go.
Red, blue, and green. Oh.
Red, blue, and green.
How about Abadoo
right there, I think.
Red, blue, and green.
Green. Green.
What's wrong with it?
Hey, this looks super cool. This is
this is
for my fucking loyal viewers,
this is the Room
VR. Now,
the Room VR is an offshoot
of the Room the Video
Game series. The series of
puzzle boxes. One of
the most fun iPad games
that they ported to Steam. I know you
know that. You're my guy.
Check it out. This is called the Room.
It's on Steam. I don't know
okay, I was just gonna throw this against the wall
and this thing's like, this thing's worth like
fucking 60 bucks. Does it have like a
price tag on it?
That was tricky. It paid
$50, but it's worth $40.
Okay, so how's this wrong?
That looks real, that looks correct.
Am I, if she was shining
at the wrong person? That looks
right to me.
What's the deal? I just did that.
Alright, now we're gonna do one more. This one is
in there, what? Upside down.
And red. And then we got
a little bit of
and red. Dine it.
Oh, it's burning the shield.
Rat in the hat chat. There's no rat in the hat.
Aha.
Fuck does this mean? All gonna be facing the same
direction kind of? Okay.
It's gotta be, did I fuck it up already?
Bingo. That's it.
Okay, now, oh shit.
Is this listed somewhere?
Do we have a list of this somewhere?
Yeah, okay.
Top right is hourglass.
Right there is
uh, pizza.
Already there. Then we got
a blade. It's already there.
And then we got, then we got
infinity. Finally,
illuminati. Oh.
Final one.
Yellow, yellow, white,
blue. We have to be in night vision
for this one. Freak mode, whatever
it's called. What was it again?
Yellow, green, blue.
I don't remember. Yellow, blue
and green. Yellow, yellow,
white and blue. White
and blue. Dine it. Right up
into the ceiling. Oh, it's a staircase.
Guys, it's a staircase.
It's a staircase.
Okay, a what?
Oh, cobwebs.
I hear it in the walls, the floor, the ceiling. It crawls all over this place.
Through it, under it. They are waiting.
I hear them. Spider's a boss or something?
Boss fight?
I don't wanna go in there.
That dude's in there. Say it?
Say it. No, I'm not gonna say it.
Only one more remains.
I hope the reverend found his
piece in the end. One more artifact to recover
before I have all I need to bring these forces
to heal. One more and I will release you
from your task. The last
soul thinks her twigs and roots will let her
dabble in worlds beyond her own.
She has no idea what she is meddling
with. Who is it?
Lady from Resi- uh...
Grandma from Resident Evil.
I said this was the- actually, this is the Resident Evil
fucking seven house.
This is actually the Resident Evil seven house.
Same layout.
Sure!
It's all okay. I'm sorry I made a shitty joke
and I punched you right in the face.
Oh, we get to make something!
Turkey! Okay, we gotta make
food. Ingredients, we get ingredients in
there. What else is in here?
Herd? What is this?
I'm gonna make a potion, eventually
here. Now, what else?
Also- oh.
Ayo.
The butcher arrives. When blind
to their master's shadow, even as the rod of
deceit rises off them, they
like a thousand burning embers.
He deceives them with- uh...
go to me.
Uh, I- I have to stop.
I have to stop. I have to.
I'm sorry. It's too- it's
my vibe- look at me.
Look at me.
I look like I have a sunburn!
Like, I was- I got too much sun!
I have a burn on my-
I have a burn on my face.
I have to- I gotta replace
this fucking thing. It's- it's horrible.
Take off the headband.
Mmm.
Radiation.
Yeah, man, VR is really fucking
cool. But- ah
God, I just wish there wasn't so much
radiation. It really does
look like a radiation burn.
Wha- how much radiation
is in a VR headset?
Did we know? Does anybody know what-
how much radiation evitst from here?
Alright, everybody wants it.
Sure, I'll- okay.
Get this in HD.
Here comes a headband reveal.
My- my career is over.
My- my looks are over. It's over.
It's over.
It's- my poor hair.
Oh, my poor hair.
Mmm.
It was already so damaged
from the last few VRs.
Save it. Save it! I can- I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try.
Ah. It'll bounce.
I'm not gonna bleach it. Look at how-
look at how fucking crazy this looks.
Wear a hat.
I- this is what I did this for!
So it would be, like, out of my head.
I'll wear a hat in VR?
I'll die in there.
I'll die in there if I wear a hat.
I'm not gonna shave my head.
No, I don't even shave it.
It's just- it's just all
dead. Look, my hairline's really
not that bad. It really isn't. You know, I had
a person at the salon told me,
Jeremy, you got another seven to ten years of that
hair. Alright.
That's it? I mean, that's it.
I'm thirty-five. You mean I get
to keep my hair till I'm, like, forty-five years old?
That's pretty sick, actually.
Seven to ten hours.
Oh, it's so- it's so beat up.
Oh, man.
No. No.
It's okay. I'm gonna go- okay, I'm
gonna go condition my hair right now.
I'm gonna go just condition my hair and leave it in for, like,
an hour. And I'm gonna play Half-Life
Alex tomorrow with, like-
Can I do, like, a- can I-
Can I have, like, a VR, like, surrogate- like,
can somebody be in the machine for me and I'll just
do commentary? Alright, I gotta
get out of here. Uh, I really
wanted to finish the room, too, but
no. No, it's time
to stop.
Sorry for the technical problems in the first
hour or so. It wasn't my
fault. We played, we were good.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a good rest of your night.
I forgot about Otto. He's right here. He's just lying down.
I fucking- it hurts up
there. I- what should I do?
Salt?
Put, like, sea salt on it or something to make it so
it, like, calms the hair follicles down up there?
What should I do? I'm not gonna put bleach
in my hair. Oil?
Maybe some olive oil? Alright, I'm gonna- yeah, yeah,
I'm gonna do olive oil. Yeah.
I'm gonna do an olive oil treatment tonight.
Yep. I'm gonna do EVOO
with a little bit of tea tree oil.
I'm gonna fight this,
because I've, uh,
that looks real bad. Oh, man.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna replace
the face mask, too. Get a scalp massage.
Alright, I'll do that.
Thanks for watching, everybody. Thanks for the subs, too.
You know, if you're new to the channel, these are the credits
here. Everybody that's subbed, I do not read
subs on stream, because I am an
ungrateful fucking asshole streamer.
Nah, but seriously, thanks for the subs, everybody.
Thanks for the bits. Thanks for everything.
I actually think that- let me see. Take a look.
Oh, Jesus, we had- speaking of subs.
Wait, Mr. Sark gave
twenty community subs earlier?
No way. I missed that.
I was too in- into the headset.
Thanks, Sark, for those twenty subs.
Appreciate it. Uh, KaiStraw
thanks for the five community subs.
Malcolm thanks for the five subs.
Radshly thanks for the five subs.
Balls4brains five subs.
TexanToaster gave sixty
community subs. Thank you for the
insane amount of money. That's insane.
Sixty community subs.
That's more money than I could ever ask anyone to ever give a stranger
on the internet. That's a lot of money.
Thank you. And then InkCat
with five community subs as well.
Rounding us out there at the end. You can smell your
stinky gamer juices.
What the fuck even is- what's a gamer juice?
What does a game- what does that mean?
I really- I- dude, I'm
losing my mind. I really thought that
my, like, penis came out on stream today.
And I, like, freaked out about it.
That's completely impossible.
I have no idea why I thought that.
But it did.
Uh.
Uh, let's raid Joel.
Let's go say hello to Varg Skeletor.
And I will see you guys tomorrow with Half-Life
Alex. Okay, if I wake up
tomorrow and I look in the mirror, and I'm
just like, this looks horrible.
What do I do?
I'm gonna have to, like, put oil on my- I'm gonna have to oil
my hair back. I think that's what's
gonna happen. I'm gonna put, like,
just oil in my hair
so it slicks all the way back so that it does not touch
the coconut oil. Yeah.
Don't use a headband.
A swimming cap. Use olive oil.
I'm gonna put oil all over
my head tomorrow. That's the only way this is gonna
help. Thanks for watching, guys.
I'll see you soon. See you tomorrow. Take care.
Good night. And goodbye.