Hey, what's happening, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight, gonna be playing as the Chain Uber Medic tonight.
Haven't done a Medic video in quite a long time, so I figured why not just come out with
a fun video if you don't know what this is.
Essentially, it's infinite invincibility. It's having an Uber charge for more than
15 seconds, sometimes even as long as two minutes with an Uber.
It's definitely a whole lot of fun, but I recommend you don't do this all the time,
because it totally is just trolling. You're pretty much just trolling the other team hardcore.
And as you will see later on in this video, it's actually pretty easy to break up. You
just need a pretty good Pyro to kind of blast you around, but you'll see that later on.
So how do you actually pull this off? You need two Medics, obviously. Both of you need
to be in some type of chat program, at least in direct communication with each other. You
both need the Uber saw, and you both need the regular default Medigun.
So what you end up doing is hitting somebody on the enemy team four times with an Uber
saw, because that's all it takes. Then you Uber your friend. Your friend is gonna get
four hits, transfer it back to you, you're gonna get four hits, transfer it back to him,
so on and so forth, and you just keep going until you can't go anymore. And it's actually
quite surprising that Valve hasn't done anything about this. You would think that they would
do some type of patch or something like that that didn't allow more than four or five
Ubers to go in a row from the same Medic within a minute or so. I have no idea. There's probably
some way to fix this. So as you can tell on the screen, we are absolutely
spawn trapping them right now, which I felt kind of bad about. You always feel bad about
this type of thing, but it's pretty funny at the same time. So I'm playing with MLC
Stealth right now. MLC Stealth is a big Call of Duty guy, good friend of mine. We were
just messing around in the chat, we decided to do this, and the next clip is actually
very, very funny. Me and Stealth end up going as Medic Spies. That doesn't make any sense
right now, but it will in a few minutes, I promise. So I get myself killed right here.
Probably shouldn't be doing this. I had like 70% Uber, I could have just ran backwards,
found Stealth, and we could have done it all over again, but I didn't do that, got myself
killed. But here is the second clip. This is actually pretty funny. They Uber at the
same time, so we go, oh, okay, let's just keep going. We make our way through the tunnel
here, see an Engineer on the left, I start smashing him in the face. I always feel bad
about stuff like this, because I think he might have been free to play, and he probably
had no idea what was going on right there. Just like, oh, let me drop my sentry. What
the hell is this? What is that? And then he's just dead, and it's like, I'm sorry, there
was some crazy guy in blue goo attacking you. So this is where it gets a little interesting,
I say over chat, I'm going, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, sit right here for a second. Let's
be medic spies, and watch this, backstab, backstab, backstab. We end up killing two
people being medic spies, and we still stick around, and we're still alive. Get this sniper
as well, and then it's time to start the chain again. Probably shouldn't have done
that right there, because it was just one sniper, and now look, Stealth is just smacking
at the gate. So remember in the beginning when I said a good Pyro can really ruin this
for you, take a look right here, I get the charge, and every time I go for it, I just
keep getting compressed backwards. This is what you have to do to stop this from happening.
And it works out pretty well for him, because we have to retreat back into the tunnel, and
I end up getting the kill on him with the Blutsauger, because that tunnel is really
small, you can't really dodge or weave or anything like that. So it works out pretty
well in our favor that time, and we end up staying alive. Kill that engineer, that was
pretty gruesome. We were just both sticking on knives into his face. So now we're back
at square one, playing as Medic Spies again. And take a look, that same Pyro comes out
and it's like, nope, not going to go for him, I'm not going to go after that guy. Just
chilling out here waiting for someone that's not a Pyro to open that door, and eventually
a Medic comes out, and I get him with the Medic Backstab. One, two, three backstabs
is all it takes. So we just barely get the charge off on that Heavy, get the kill on
him, and now we're looking for somebody else. No one else is really around, so he runs down
this way towards the cart. And look who shows up to ruin the fun, the Pyro again. He does
his job, but we had some miraculous rescue from another Pyro. I don't even know how
that guy got back here. But he ends up saving the day nonetheless. So anyways, this is going
to be the end of the video. We end up getting ourselves killed by a Pyro. Thank you all
so much for watching, I really do appreciate it. Just wanted to put this video together,
showing some quick, goofy little shenanigans as the Chain Uber Medic. But yeah, thanks
guys, I will see you all next time, and take care everybody.