Hi guys, welcome. Welcome to a stream that is gonna be a little all over the place, I think.
This is gonna be interesting. You probably saw the title already. This is 700,000 games. No,
it is not 700,000 games from a couple years back, or a year and a half, or whatever it was.
This is the sequel. This is 700,000 games 2. I'm not just playing the old one. They did it
again. They did it again. They packed 700,000 more games into this teeny tiny little disc.
How do they even get it in there? So they, over the two versions, have 1.4 million games.
Oh, that coffee is very hot. I'm gonna let it sit there for a minute. But yeah, this is version
2. I've already gone through and looked at a few things and will touch upon them in just a
matter of mere minutes. So give me one second. I want to, I want to grab another
coaster. So give me one second. Be right back. Okay, so if we take a look at the box,
I'm going to show the box now because I want to be able to trickle in because this stream
is a fairly special stream. We're not going to be doing this that often, so. And by
often, I mean, we're going until this is done. I'm going to play every single one.
Like last time, if there's 700,000 games and I play each one for five minutes, that's
seven, 1.4 million, two, three, four. I got, that's, you're talking about probably three or
four years of the stream is going to be. So this is probably going to be three year, 20,
a 24 hour, three year long stream. So I'll see you guys when I'm like 40
and we get to the last one. So without further ado, why don't we go like this
and why don't we go like this? Hi. So here it is. 700,000 games version 2.0. One of the things
you're probably noticing right off the bat is the fact that the, the price tag has been
scratched off. I didn't do that. That came like this. And as we all know, there are only two
reasons why you do that. Either one, the gift was so cheap that you desperately don't want
the person to know that it was a piece of shit or you're embarrassed because the gift
was too expensive. And I wonder which one this is. Scratch off that price tag. It's a gift. I don't
want you to know how much this was. Both. Now, can you, I don't know. Maybe the company is
embarrassed that this was like $11 on Amazon, wherever the hell it is. But yeah, here you go.
I'll give you a close up. That's, you see pyramid escape up there. Can't wait for that one.
Uh, Mini Golf 3D Mania. Something interesting to know about 3D Golf Mini Mania.
Uh, there's a thousand and one Mini Golf Mania levels, which is included in a game. So that's
a thousand and one different games. They're using a weird semantic literal definition.
And oddly enough, that took about 40 minutes to install. Something else that's kind of
funny about this, before we get started, is I did open some of these and why don't we just,
I'll just show you. Uh, this is the same exact thing as the last one. Here's the difference.
Take a look at the, here, here, all of them. So you see those of you that watched the last
video that I did on the first version, I had a lot of problems not being able to open
a lot of these. So what this actually is, this is not 700,000 games too. This is 700,000
games. But this time, a bunch of them work. This is a patch. They patched in the ability to open
half the games you couldn't open last time. Sounds pretty good, doesn't it? Take a look.
We got hidden objects, arcade games, brickbuster games, time management games, marble popper,
card sports, match three, puzzles. Look at all these boring, terrible games that make up
699,990 of everything that's included on the one disc. So yeah, that, that's pretty much the long
and short of it. So what we're going to do is we're going to, we're going to do a little system
here. So I'm going to change this to this. I thought about turning on smart click. Uh,
there is no way smart click is going to work. You guys are going to have to, like,
pick a quadrant if I turn on smart click. There's no way. We will never choose a game. So
we're just going to start. We'll do smart click for like an encore at the end. Pick a quadrant,
then game. Smart click. I'm just curious of how awful this would be. So hold on,
give me one second. Let me change to this. I gotta get, where is it right there? It's copy.
So I can make sure I have that on over here. I'm, I'm just curious of how awful this would
be if I tried this. Okay. So without further ado, if, if we'd like to see how this is
going to work, uh, first I have to turn it on. You're going to have to refresh your page,
I think. Okay. It is now active and now I just have to go to it and turn it on.
So you're going to have to probably, if your extension is not there,
let's just see what happens. All right. That I super frog is where everybody,
it's actually working fairly well. This is not working terribly. This works actually pretty
well. I thought it was going to be a disaster. So we're starting with super frog.
Is that what this is? I'm surprised this works as well as does well. I'm shocked.
So it looks like we're going to start with a classic video game by the name of,
by the name of super frog. Thank you for your participation in this,
by the way, uh, need to make one more thing very clear. Uh, RIP to the whole stream.
I'll rip the VOD because we're going to be playing landmines.
Some of these are going to crash the entire computer and I'm going to have to restart my PC.
So good luck. Please don't, let's not click on the landmine
just through opening and closing certain ones. Oh, this is going to be a disaster.
Hope you, uh, welcome to the spring. Here we go. Let's go ahead and open super frog.
Let's get some nostalgia here. So I'm going to, I'm going to go away because I don't want
my face on the screen here, but what I do want is super frog. Yes. That's my desktop
background. And by the way, I have lowered the volume by like 50% and it's still going to be
awful. And when you might not even be able to see anything super frog here.
All right. This is important. I don't think I should do that. That, that, that might,
that's a, that's a, that's a risky click. You know what I mean? Whoa,
hold on a minute here. Risky click. Oh, come on. Come on. Oh, all right. Here it comes.
Look at how small this is. I have to make this better. Hold on. I knew I was going to
have to do this like a shit load of times and it's so loud. How does it know my name?
How does it know my name? I didn't click this. I promise. I didn't open this.
I want, I fucking promise. I did not open this game. It's a window. Hold on. Can you hear
me? All right. Throw bubble up joke. Okay. We're good. I can't wait. I'm so ready for
super frog. What a developer Easter egg. Yeah. Okay. Here we go. Time to play super frog.
You only got a taste last time of what this game was like. I had to,
I had to play through at least 20 minutes. There it is. Version two. Wait,
you can't even see this part. Yeah. We're going to have a lot of fun called every game is
going to open in a strange window and I'm going to have to resize them because I can't
resize them on the desktop. That's, there we go. All right. Collect all the flowers. Use the left
and right arrow keys to move in the appropriate direction to jump. Press the up arrow key to
collect the flowers in the middle of the screen. Reach the highest platform and then jump off of
it to the lower platforms using the arrow keys. Desktop background. What is that? I got
500 candies. Hey, welcome to the reference stream where I'm just going to make a bunch
of fucking references the whole time. Is this a different level? I thought, I thought it was
candies, not flowers. What the hell was that thing? This is the best song. You know, people
are like, oh put it on OST. This is the one that I want to listen to. I had to get the
banana. There's no double jump just in case you're curious. Just in case you're curious.
To enclose a monster in a bubble to trap it and then press the space bar to send it
flying. So it's like bubble bubble. How long should I spend on each one of these? There's
700,000 of these guys, remember. What just happened? I thought I put them in the bubble.
I have to pop the bubble. Oh, right. What if I only played Super Frogs? Would you guys be mad?
No, you guys wouldn't be mad if I only did Super Frog. I did it, right? Oh wait,
the flowers regrow. Oh, that's fucking new. Oh, here are the candies. Wait, is that?
Cockroach up. Oh, fuck. I'm beating the whole game. Restart. No, I'll get them again. Don't
worry. I'll say the line. Don't worry. You know what, I'm not going to say the line.
Say the line. Say the line. Oh, I should probably turn off the desktop background. Just
make it like a black screen, right? That's pretty quick. How many more do I have to do?
Hold on, let's see if I can get it how fast I can get this.
Frog tech. Don't you wish this guy had his own Nintendo video game? Well, he already did.
It's called Gex. Enter the gecko, right? Am I not doing it fast enough?
I want it in Smash. Monster cleaner. What's going on? How do I beat this level?
The fucking flowers. Because they're eating the flowers. I get it. That's a mechanic. Guys,
I've only played this game for like fucking four minutes. How? I don't know that. Oh,
hold on a minute. Quick zoom in. How could you not? I didn't. Hold on. How could you not like
it? It's got candy. See? Reference. That's the line that made me famous. That's where all of
my fame comes from. I said that one time. Now I tour college campuses. I've written
a couple of books. So what point do I give up on this one? You never finished that book. Yeah,
but I still read it. I don't get all these right now. I'm putting a hole in my monitor.
What's going on? Okay, I did it. It's the same thing over and over.
What are these? Missiles? Why didn't missiles drop?
Okay, that strange reference. This is a reference stream. That's just the
papers please noise that the guy makes when you click on the thing.
T for teen. Actually, there's blood in this game. Not this one, but in this package.
All right, that's it. I've been on Super Frog for like 10 straight minutes.
We have a long way to go. We had to open it up strong. Very strong.
More keep going. No, I'm sorry. We're getting out of Super Frog in about 15 minutes.
I'll Frog tech these guys one more time. But if you want, okay, hold on. We talk a lot of shit
about this game and this product, but I really can't think of anything better. That's more
just completely benign than this game giving it to like a third grader. You know what I'm
saying? This is just the same level over and over again, where you just collect candies and you
shoot bubbles out of your mouth. This is so, there's no content here. None. So this is the
best thing for like a, okay, little Tim, you get 10 minutes on the computer to play Super Frog
and they're going to be like, oh, Super Frog. They don't give a shit. They don't even know
what they're doing. They can barely talk. That's worth its weight in gold as a parent.
You don't even have to, oh wait, if you're a good boy, then you get Captain Crunch. No,
no, no. If you're a good boy, you get 10 minutes of Super Frog and then you pretend
like it's the greatest thing in the world. Make sure you get him catching you playing it
like I am right now. Comes into the room. Dad, yeah, what's up? Hey son,
just playing some Super Frog and then they don't even understand. All right,
that's enough Super Frog. Oh yeah, there, there are two new emotes by the way.
There's Germa Old and then I turned Germa Expensive into Germa One, guys.
There will be a new Germa Expensive emote. Everyone, papers please, papers, papers, papers,
papers please. Ready? Holy shit. He's going to teach her this is F. What a terrible
character design, but that makes it so good. I thought my computer just crashed.
Let me, okay, let me change the desktop background to black. So this, like I see
Game of Thrones shit in the background. This is not a Game of Thrones background,
just in case you were curious. It's not. Let's just change it, personalize,
change it to just a solid color. Oh, look at that. Can you see? This is going to,
everyone, this is going to freak everybody out so much. Check this out. This is live right
now. This is happening. All right, we need to cross off. So here, let's go back to that list.
Oh god, we can't do that again. We can't sit there and play Super Frog for 10 minutes.
You know what I mean? This, we got to make this clear. So I need to add,
I need to add an X and just put it over that because we are not going back to it.
It's done. Super Frog, I almost put it on the wrong thing. Super Frog is done. All right,
shall we pick another one? Let's pick another one. If you'd like to click, we're going to,
just we're going to do this for the first little bit here. Click on where you'd like us
to go next. I'm not going to fucking Super Frog again. I am actually really surprised
at how well this is working. We're going to go from Super Frog to Super Fox.
What did I expect? Yeah, all right. Super Fox, thank you for participating. If you
want to participate, all you have to do is click the screen. Super Fox, it is. Good luck.
Oh, this is a full screen game. Uh oh, I have no control. This is in the other one too.
Is there any, can you guys even see this? Oh shit. Uh oh, hold on. Let's see if this works.
Can you guys see this? Because this, I can't change this. Is it still just,
just a black screen? Can you see this? What does it look like? It's small. I can't fix it.
This is how it has to be. I can't fix it because there's no, I can't put this into a window.
Zoom it out again. Oh Lord, hold on. Some of these games are just going to open.
Let's see if that helps. Yeah, it's, it's going to be like this. There's nothing I
can do about it. Can you see? Just like look real close into your screen because what's
happening is it's changing my resolution across every screen. This is great. Close it up.
So you can ride the alligator. You're going to get chased by, I thought he had a dick for a
second. I really did. It was like, holy shit, what the hell are they thinking? Here we go.
Choose if you want to play single or with a friend. We're going to play single. Pick two.
Choose the level pick you'd want to play. Pick two, pick one. Uh, pick seven. You must
reach the gate by jumping through the holes. You can run through the edges of the screen
by using to move, escape to in-game pause. All right. But again, I thought,
I hope you guys can see this. All right. So where, where am I? I just killed myself.
How? I'm smashing my skull on the bottom. So this one has presents and cheese and gummy
bears. Does that click? There's fall damage. Is that killing me? Okay. I'm running out of
lives. I just fucking smashed. How would, why would you make a super Mario game
where you can hurt your head? No, I ain't typing that in. It's going to go up to like some server
somewhere and they're going to know me. Okay. That's out. That's it. Thanks for playing.
That's it for super Fox. I'm not doing that one again. That's just, that's not going to
happen. Where's, where the fuck is it? So many on here. Okay. I'm not, no more super. Oh
damn it. Super. We've only done two. Oh God. I'm going to be here. This the first 24 hour stream.
Is it going to be this one? No, no, no, it's not. No way. All right. Let's do it again.
Where would you like to go? Oh, you fucking pranksters. Super frog to super Fox to super
Fox two. Okay. How much I might as well just go through and do all the supers.
I just, I'll just do them because they're just going to win every single thing.
All right. Let's play super Fox two. Thank you for participating. What the hell even is this?
Which collection is this in? I knew this was going to happen. Okay. I think it's color is
collection three. Yeah. Okay. Super Fox two. Tell me if you can see this. Oh God. It's doing
it again. It's loading up the it's fucking up the back. It's what, what's the difference?
They just made it. They gave him a different shirt. Look at how fucking small this is.
This is like one of, I got a lot of them have actually this one is different.
I wonder how closely you guys have to look right now. Chess or Trest hot air balloons
because I can't make it window and I can't get out. It's right now my monitor,
my actual, all of the monitors are in like 640 by 480. All right. Look closely because
I got a fucked up screen too. I thought the deck tiger was really, really happy that he
killed like a bunch of people. I thought these were all like dead bodies lying around. I don't
know why I went to that immediately, right? That's what I thought it was. I thought he was like
looking happy. Check the Nvidia control panel settings. Uh, well what's happening is it's,
right? That's the same problem happened last time I played this.
Whereas some of them just force. It doesn't matter what you do. The game physically cannot
turn on unless the monitor is at 640 by 480. Remember these games are, these games
were made in like fucking two hours each. What happened? And there's your case in point.
This game took 42 minutes to make. And after that we're out. Okay. Well that was fun. And
I'm just, I'm just gonna get it out of the way because, oh Jesus, it's still on. We're
gonna, I'm gonna open up Super Mole right now. Yes, I know, I know, I know, I know. I know
that the mole is the next one that you want to see. I'm certain of it. How is this one?
Oh God. All the ones that are Super Mole and Super Fox, they all do the same thing.
Damn it. You don't have no options to. It's not bad? It's not that bad? What the fuck is this?
What am I supposed to do? What? Mole movement. Use current weapon. Switch weapons.
This is not like the other Super games. I don't like this. It's different. I don't like this.
The developers decided to go into like a gem hunting spelunky way. I don't like it. I
want the old Super games. All right. It's weapon hotkeys. Get rid of panels. Suicide.
Didn't even give himself a chance. Where are you getting those grenades?
This game already exists. What's it called? Uh, Dig Dug. Oh, there's a grenade. Smell the,
smell it. Wait, wait, wait. They're gonna crush me. Okay. Watch out. Don't get crushed.
Uh-oh. I just check mated myself. Did I? Fucking 900 million IQ. I like this one.
I just, what? I just got like a nuke. What the fuck? Oh shit. I have, oh yeah. I have like
bombs. TNT. What is this one? Is it a mine? Poison. Drink poison. I just drank poison.
Holy shit. I can go. Okay. It's like a Pac-Man power cube. I like this one. This one's actually
kind of fun. Cool. Enemies. There's no enemies left to destroy. It's not exciting, but this
is a good game. Yeah. You don't die from that. Good. Oh, I have a health meter. Sick.
There's actual thought in this one. That was fun. All right. This is where it derails.
How long has it been? Because that's the first one that I think is still open in the
task manager. And if I close it, it might kill the whole computer. Why?
Why? No, I think we're fine. No, we're good. No, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're
good. Everything's fine, right? I can still change scenes. Oh, we're golden. Let's go ahead and
get that over Super Mole. And then we had Super Fox 2, right? Super Fox 2 was down here
and we've played four games. Maybe this wasn't such a good idea. All right. So
where would you like to go next? Oh, wonderful, lovely audience of mine. We're in this together.
Oh, yes, we are. I'm seeing a lot of, uh, it's more so now that there's no more
Super in the title seem to be pretty evenly split except for fish food, which is the
next one we're going to play. So let's go ahead and open up fish food. Hopefully this one
has even a full screen graphic option. That would be very nice. Now I get to do the fun
task of finding where the fuck that game is. Okay. Found it. Fish food. Let's go.
If you think this is going to be even remotely close to insane aquarium, you are,
you are so wrong that it's actually making me angry. Let's do it. Yes. Yes. Thank God.
What? Why would you have a maximized window if it doesn't do anything?
Oh my fucking God. It just increases the window.
When did this come out? I'm, so hold on a minute. Let's be fucking serious for one second.
When did this come out? Two. Okay. This is designed for windows seven and windows eight.
Okay. Why would you have a six 40 by four 80 window in like 2013?
Did you just hit the pinnacle of where you are able to design a video game and you just
don't even attempt to go any further. This game came out probably in like,
did this come up this year? What's the copyright on it? 2014.
And you're still making fucking six 40 by four 80 windows. You can't like fix this.
Well, I, I'll try. What the hell is muse on? What's this fucked up weird, like
out of the scene in Adobe flash Easter egg affiliate link. All right. Fuck it. Let's go.
How to play meet Sonny is small. See that you guys have it, have it easy. I got it hard
because I have to look at the fucking screen that is under a microscope.
Fast ocean. Use your mouse to help Sonny survive in these dangerous waters. Follow
these rules. Eat the fish smaller than yourself. Avoid the fish bigger than yourself.
Eat enough fish to grow up. That's an overworld. Meet Sonny. Look at this.
All right. Fish frenzy has more levels than Donkey Kong country.
Something's wrong there. Did I already eat something? And you get the mouse on the screen
too. You got me so far. I can eat these guys. I'm going to get gnomed. No,
I'm not going to get gnomed. This was so easy. This is level one though.
What I get gnomed in this. The gnome didn't even exist until like 16 months ago. I don't
know why I'm referring to the gnome in baby years. Like how old a baby is golden fish.
Wow. I just got gnomed. It just happened. You just saw it on the screen. I just got fucking
gnomed. All right. Let's speed run this. I wonder how far I can get before fucking raging.
Oh, he's going to rage. Hey, place your bets guys. What's it going to rage?
This is not what I thought the game was going to be like. I kind of need to see.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. What's with all this stuff?
Uh, toxic waste dump. What's with the, what's with the bomb over here? Am I going to get to choose
two different paths? Going through toxic waste, die by a whale or like nuclear explosion.
This is important. Oh wow. We got big guys. We got big guys. He can, he can grow too.
God, this just reminds me of BBB so much. You know what I mean?
I'm getting some real, like it's itchy. I'm getting those real BBB vibes. Uh-oh.
Gnome me. Don't gnome me. We're going with first death. Game over. Hope you guys are aware of
that. Can I beat this whole game in one setting in about nine months? This is going to be so
long. I want to see what happens when we get to the nuke, but the difficulty is going
to ramp up. They don't want anyone completing the game because guess what?
There is no completing the game. After level 16, there's nothing there. It's that's just
there. It'll be a liar. I didn't count. I'm 11. They didn't develop past like level 12.
That map is not going to work after 12 levels. I guarantee it. Guaranteed. You see that needle
threat right there? Nobody, none of you, nobody in this chat could do that. I'm surprised
nobody's made the joke in this chat yet. It's pretty easy. First game that Jeremy's been
able to get S ranking on. Where is that? I haven't seen that yet. Go. You just got,
okay, I'm gonna, I'm gonna speed this process up. Come on, I can do this quick.
He ate them all. That's not fair. Get out of here. Ah, GDQ run. Doesn't matter. Yeah,
it does. I'm about to escape. This game, this actually, I don't know why that hurt my back,
but it did. Just don't touch a whale and I'm good. Oh, what a perfect use of that
emo. Yeah, after God. I'm losing growth is what's happening. All right, that's enough. I'm done.
We're gonna be sitting here for so long. Get to the toxic waste or riot. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. That's 11 more levels. Yeah, that is actually kind of
funny. There's two endings to the game. One where I become a gigantic fish and I win and
the other one where a nuke goes off. Very interesting stuff. I'm not gonna win. I'm
gonna lose here. That just, that was the button to click to add like two minutes to this game.
Thank God, because that music was gonna be the reason to hit escape.
No, that's it. I'm done. I can't leave again. How do I leave? I think I have to just click
the X. No escape. This, I probably have to beat the level to go to the menu.
It's not even gonna be toxic waste. It's just a thing on the map that somebody drew and put
there. Haven't you ever played a game? Haven't you guys ever played a game before? Haven't
you guys ever played a game with as an overworld? Yeah, it's a phone game. In Candy Crush,
you do the same thing over and over and over again and then you walk by the clown with
the funny pink hair and he doesn't, like, there's no clown. There's mines here though.
Well, this was fun. This was a fun one. What am I talking about? Look, these are mines.
You're already halfway to the waste. They're the same four enemies. We're not going to
even get to see a new enemy type. It's the same spongebob fish. It's over. Say, I was
trying to circle that guy and I forgot. It was that one. That was a super fish. What the
fuck was that one even called? I don't know. That one was called fish food and it is now over.
Where are we going? See, now it's split. I'm gonna have to sit here for a minute or two
because this shit is locked down. All you fucking guys clicking on feeding frenzy
that want to see the same game again, but this time the fish is green instead of yellow.
Spy chaser. This one's probably... I think I remember this one. This one's 3D. We're going
spy chaser. Yeah, this is a 3D game which means it's probably gonna fucking crash the computer.
This might be the first landmine of the evening, so I'll be right back if it crashes.
Thanks for voting. And where is it? Spy chasers. It's pack two, I believe. Spy chasers. Okay.
Is that not it? No, it is. What the fuck is it? Spy chasers. There it is. All right,
here we go. Good luck. See you. See you maybe in like a minute when my computer blue screens.
Huh? Are we good? Is it open? That was spy chaser. Pretty good. Pretty fun. Where are we going
next? I thought they fixed all these. All right. Somebody keep... Somebody jot it down.
Somebody keep a mental note somewhere of the ones that didn't work. I guess I could just do
that. I have a monitor right here. So, because I want to see if I can go into like
the fucking game like I and I files or something and try to like force that to open.
Okay, spy chaser was one of them. Just write it on the monitor.
I could just do that, right? Just half like... But no, I like... I can't...
No, there's no reason for that. I can just write it here. All right,
looks like we're going feeding frenzy. Let me click on monster doors. Is it too far over?
Hahaha. Let me click monster doors. What are you doing? What the fuck? Fuck. File Arter.
It's cool. I told you Dutch made that cool again to like be able to like
voice crack. It used to be not cool. All right, we're going to feeding frenzy.
You can't wait. Looking forward to it. Yes, I'm sure. I'm sure I want you to open this.
It's like, are you sure you want to open that file? I guess. Here we go. Well, this
one opens. That's a Harley Quinn without any makeup on. Options. Wait, what? This is the one
this is the fast one, but it's so small in the corner. Wait, wait, wait. I might be able to fix
this a little bit. Let me see if I can fix this. If I go like this and then move it down like
that, you guys are going to tell me if this helps at all because there's no way I'm going
to be able to know. It kind of did. It kind of did, right? All right. So game speed. Yeah,
it's as fast as possible. And here's the thing that I did this on a different computer that
time. Is this supposed to be ash? All right, here we go. Go fishing. Oh God, it's going to
do it. I know it, but I'm at like probably 3000 frames a second. Oh my God. It just
crashed. What the fuck is happening? No, why? Oh my God. What the hell was that for?
There's no reason for that. No, it's doing it. I get Jesus. This collection came out in 2014.
That was not like three decades ago. Oh my God. Why? My head hurts. This is supposed
to be version two. How is that version two? Somebody just dragged and dropped a folder into
a new folder and named it two and then sneezed in the thumb drive. My God. Okay.
Um, I'm going to write that one down too. So, uh, feeding frenzy also didn't fucking
do anything. Well, it did do something. It, it turned on a Halloween strobe light
into almost 6,000 people's faces. Can you imagine how fucked up that is?
What I've just done on the stream. I did, there is a stadium here full of people
that I just flashed and then I walked off the stage. All right. I think, I think people
are trying to click down on monster doors, but maybe they can't.
Is everybody like, all right, I'm actually concerned about that.
How would I ever know that opening feeding frenzy was going on?
What the fuck is this big frenzy from now on here on out, I'm just going to flash myself.
Okay. So I'm not going to change over to the game until I'm certain that like it looks all
right. Well, wait a minute. Hold on. Now we've got, okay. Big frenzy. So big frenzy's looks
like it's going to be the one that wins 50%. Thank you for voting. Okay. Big frenzy. This
one is in best video game hits four. Big frenzy. I'm not changing this over yet. Well,
I am actually for a second because I need to. So hold on. I feel like we, I like the
camera being on like, I feel like takes us into another dimension. Like we're already in
like a fucked up dimension and bringing it back to reality for a second. So just hold on.
I'm still in pain from that flash. That's the fucking worst thing I've ever seen.
All right. Let's make sure this is actually going to be captured.
Okay. Big frenzy. Please, please just spare us. Spare me because I'm the one that's
looking at it right now. All right. Okay. This has, this has video options.
It's, I can't make the screen bigger. Brightness medium. That should make it a little better.
Come on back to me. Bug, bug man. What about bug frenzy? It's a little better. Holy shit.
This is fucked up. This is not right. This is not right. Oh, I don't know why this
happened. I just, it just reached into the fucking computer screen through and like
choked me. It fucking crashed. I just actually got strangled by that game.
Okay. It looks a little better. Could be better though. That's as good as it's going to get.
Start. It was nighttime. The firefly flew around the garden collecting glowing eggs.
Why is this written in shitty chalk? Okay. Is that what, is that what the bug did?
Am I dead? Oh, that was actually kind of brutal.
Okay. We'll try it again. I'm going to try to get every single crunch berry.
That's a song. What popular song is that?
What is it? Oh my God. It's going to, it's, it just strangled me.
It's tonight's going to be a good night. No, no, this is not the top
one most embarrassing spring. I'm so quirky, right?
I did it. So we do it again. I'm not stopping until somebody puts in the chat what this song
is and what interlude this is. No, it's not again and again. It's for you and then you
and for you and for you and for you and for, is this wrong? What am I doing? Is that wrong?
I got a feeling that tonight's going to be a good night. No, it's not.
What's this thing do? Oh, I have another life. I was going to,
how many more is this? Last one? Only like one more little quadrant up here
and then we can finally get this shit going.
All right, get me the fuck out of this.
That was, I don't even know what that was. I forget what that was already. That was
Bug Frenzy? Where the hell is it? There it is. It's been an hour. That was Bug Fuck?
I don't think the title of that game was Bug Fuck. I'm pretty sure it was Bug Frenzy.
All right. Where are we going now? I know you can't click on the bottom of the screen,
but I'm sorry. There's not much I can do about it. These are like five separate
images that I had to staple together. Never has no one ever. It's never have no one ever by the
Smiths. All right. I don't know if this is Gerbil Quest or Monster Doors, so I'm going
to say it's Gerbil Quest. Let's open up Gerbil Quest. Again, all these fucking things.
I just wish, here's the worst part. Going through this the first time,
like I could like set up the capture again. I could change the window. I'm going to burp
real loud. No, I'm not. Okay. Here we go. No, I'm going to turn it off because I don't want you
to see this because what if it's a fucking flash? Oh, did Gerbil Quest not open?
Trying to. Write it down. Gerbil Quest does not open. So that's why Chaser Feeding Frenzy
Gerbil Quest. See if we can get this to open later for the encore part of the stream.
Uh, looks like everyone wants Monster Doors because you can't go any lower.
Monster Doors or we riot. You're going to get your Monster Door or it might be a land mine.
Monster Door. Incoming. Let's try it. Monster Door. We're good. No, we're not. It's a land
mine. Fuck. It's a land mine. It's up. No, it's not. Thank goodness. I'm scared to do that.
No, we ain't doing that. No way. Do you think I'm going to full screen that game?
Dad, talk about a door I don't want to open. That one. All right. It's off center. Someone's
going to be like, it's off center-ree. It's off center-ree. Right? Someone's going to do
that. I know someone's going to write that. Okay. We're good.
That's an exponential increase. All right. You ready? Monster Doors. Classic original puzzle
with one figure to collect. Two by two. Every fourth level you'll get a new figure to collect.
I don't know what that means. Level one. Points to pass a level 160.
Collect figures. Monsters. This jester's bonus figure. I don't understand what's going on.
So they come out of the barn floppy disk doors. What's the goal? This is Hotel Mario.
But what the number muncher is monsters. I don't have a score yet. Score yet. So they have
to... that's not a score? Wait. Hold on. I think I get it. That's a four in a row, right?
Jackpot. I need a green down here. Got it. Five in a row. Jackpot. Nope. I need a green right
here. Got it. Watch this shit. Bingo. Oh no. That's not going to happen. Uh. How am I
supposed to set this up? I need one. There's too many greens. Too many green figures.
Just make a square. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. I get it. Okay. But I'm looking at the bonus game.
Oh I get it now. Watch this. I'll fucking run through this shit.
This is fun. I like this one. That's what I was trying to do right there. I get a double.
I did it. I beat the level. I win. All right. Now that I know what's going on. Watch this.
Yeah. Oh wait. Look out. Oh shit. It's uh. It's the birdie from Five Nights at Freddy's.
Why is nobody clicking on the screen? That's you.
VeggieTales? Where's the VeggieTales one? You want me to play 100,000 Mahjong games.
Okay. That looks like the place we're going. I click. Wait. Am I saying it wrong?
It's. It's Mahjong, right? Mahjong? Mahjong. It's correct, isn't it? Am I doing it wrong?
All right. Let's open it. 100,000 Mahjong games. Let's see what happens here. Let's get it open.
All right. Look at this. Oh wow. So interesting to note about this one in particular. This is
very important. This is the Windows 95 logo. It might even be Windows 3.1. They just don't
give a shit, do they? I have no idea how to play this. I don't know what any of this
means. I've never done it before. I think maybe I think one time I watched my brother play it
and you have to match symbols or something, right? Match tiles because and they're layered.
So I gotta find this. I gotta find these two. I'm gonna wait for it
until somebody figures out what I'm doing. Just gonna hang out here for a second.
Oh yeah. I was right. You have to match them. Okay. So get out of here. Get off
the screen. Get out of here. I don't need that. I'll figure it out. It's just here we go.
What on earth are you guys clicking right now? All right. Hold on. I can do it.
No one's on here. I'm just being silent right now. I'm being so quiet. It has to be on the edge.
Got it. Sometimes you just figure out that you're really good at something.
What? That's on the edge. It's a nice interesting game. So where are the 100...
Okay. Are there 100,000 pieces? 3D? Wait. What? This is so much easier to see this.
This is 3D. This is 2D apparently. What did I just do? Let me like use my finger.
Hold on. I gotta use my finger. Like I sometimes I need to use my hands
because I got a top screen here. So I'm gonna make sure you guys can see what I'm doing.
I used to be pretty good at this. One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, five, six.
These two. Those two. These two. Right there. Those two. Those two. These two. Six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen. Okay. I'm kind of stuck here though
because there's a couple of different ways to sit in eight, nine. Okay. Now I can do really
quick math in my head. So green into green and then the red into red and then the black
frame into the green and then... Okay. Okay. That was kind of hard. It was like
touching the screen is like hard to do. But I got it. That was fun. What a god of a game. I mean,
stop. Let's say that. Not really. Kind of. I mean, you know, sometimes. I mean, you know,
whatever. Thanks for the compliment. That was a hundred thousand mahjong games. Computer loadup
celery man. What? You lost 300 viewers playing mahjong. Well, let's be honest here.
If you clicked on a live stream and a guy was playing mahjong on it and it was on the screen
for more than 10 seconds, you'd probably be like, ah, I don't know if I want to watch a
guy play mahjong and you'd probably just leave. All right. Where are we going now? What do you
guys think? Oh, are we, are we considering another 3D game that's guaranteed to either
not work or crash OBS? I'm looking forward to it. Why does nobody like Adam Ball?
Adam Ball. There's the Pac-Man clone. That one's from the last one, too. One vote is currently
on. One vote is currently on. All right, let's open it. This is, uh, what the heck is this one?
Which one are you clicking on? Mystery World War II aerial dogfight. I remember this one
was in the other one, too. It has really loud music and impossible to control. Welcome
to the reference. Here comes a reference. Thank you for voting. Let's just redo the video.
All right. I'm going to make sure the screen is not, uh, going to be terrible here.
What the hell is OBS? Where did OBS go? Oh my, that was kind of scary. All right. Let's,
I'm not going to change it yet just in case it's all fucked up. And we have video
options. So resolution, field of view, big. This mic. Okay. You take a look at this and
you tell me if you think this is going to crash the whole fucking game in the whole
stream. Not me, not my face. This. I mean, resolution, scene detail, shadow reflection,
cool effect if enabled, if special effects is enabled, 3D sound, hardware sound. This is
just all these boxes are ways to crash my computer. Think of the amount of troubleshooting
it would take to potentially have to deal with all these checkboxes. Good luck. I just
clicked it. Oh, it worked. Yeah. This is the same one. I remember this one,
the loud ass music. All right, hold on. I can make it look better. That's as good as
it's going to get. Oh no. No, wait, didn't this happen before? This happened last time.
It cracked. This happened in the video. It crashed the computer. I remember. And
I finally got it to work. It's over. It's done. This happened in the last fucking,
in the video. No. Oh my God. I can't fucking believe it. That just relived it. Oh, you gotta
be kidding me. God damn it. Go pull up that video. Watch this part. This exact same thing
happened. I had to restart the computer. I think. Fuck. Hold on. Oh shit. I think I
can get it. Can I just kill it from here? It might kill OBS. No. Oh no. No. Don't
kill OBS. Good luck. I'll see you guys soon. Hopefully. If it doesn't. Hello? Where's the
webcam? Am I still here? Uh, what? I didn't do that. I didn't do that. What happened
to the camera? Can you see this? Okay. So this time we're going to hold on. Oh,
that was wild. I can't. This, here we go. Ready? Hands up. I clicked it. I'm not touching
anything. Oh, you can feel it. Feel it. Do you see that? Do you feel it? I'm like fucking
melting. I can't do anything about this. Just fucking campaign. Who cares? Yep. This
is the, I remember you can't control the plane. What happened? Oh, end. All right. Let's go.
Leave your left hand on the keyboard. Okay. Is it, is it, is it going to sense it?
You could hit the broad side of a bond. Why am I doing this? Repeat fucking emo face. That
guy's making. Got it. No, no. Exit. Exit the game. Oh shit. Quickly. Hold on. No,
this might be it. Oh, fuck. It's over. I can't. I'm the task manager is on the
other monitor. Oh shit. I did it accidentally. Oh my fucking God.
That was a 3d game that I should never open ever again. What are you clicking on now?
I'm so upset that this is just the same fucking game. There's almost no differences. It's
probably all DigiPen student games for a shell company. Honest to God though, why is this a
second version? I'm going to, okay, at some point here, I want to open up the screenshot that I took
of the last one and actually see if they just put two in front of the game and release it again.
Looks like we're going to, uh, atom ball, atom ball. What a joke. What an absolute joke.
700,000 games to nothing is the same games have the same problems. We just put a two in
front. That's it. I'd like to know what the two what it actually is. So we're going atom atom ball.
All right. Hold on to your, uh, hold on to your hats because here comes atom ball.
Where the hell is it? I actually don't even know where it is. Atom ball. Oh, okay. It's
down this one. This one. All right. Here we go. Good luck. I'm going to have to do a full
clean install of windows after this. Let me just make sure it works. Same problems as last
time. I'm just reliving the making of that last video. Does that one didn't open? What is the two
for? What is the two for? You've misread. It's 700,000 games to meaning also means it's just
again. Oh my God. This one doesn't open either. Adam. What's it called?
Adam ball. Put an X on it. We also need to see if the same games didn't open
because I thought some of them did. Holy shit. I can't even fucking believe this.
Well, let's see what else there is to try and attempt. What's the original 700,000 games like?
It's this. It's this. It's the same thing. I think I think we may have actually been baited
on me making the video again. That's what happened. So it looks like we're doing, uh,
the ancient Mayan empire. All those are the same exact game. All right. Just in case anyone's
wondering, there's no difference in those games. There's no differences. They are all the same
game. So we, I can just delete all of these. Oh my God. This is going to take 20,000 hours.
Secret empires of Maya open it. Holy shit. This actually takes up the whole screen.
What a miracle. That's an actual miracle. Is this the first? This is the first one that's actually
1920 by 1080. Why is this all off? Okay. Hey, remember that video? Ow, my ears.
Hey, what's this one? Let's try this one. Now I know why they had it all turned down.
Uh, secret empire of the ancient world. Inca. Good. All right. What are we looking for?
Looking for chain crowbar, sunglasses, domino tires, seagull, seagull, Russian doll, maps,
sapphire, sapphires. Got it. Oh my God. Why? It just reset. It's the same. There's no difference.
It's the same background. It's just a desktop background with a bunch of random blurry bitmap
images. This is the same thing as it was before. There's not one single difference.
We're looking for brooch, wheel, belt, oil can, skull, scrub brush, owl, lunchbox.
That's not, that's not correct. Good work. You found one. Lunchbox. What is this? A piece
of bread? All right. I got that one. I only need the owl and that's it. Where's the owl?
Find it. Found it. I did it. Done. Oh no, I didn't. Brooch, wheel, and belt. Wheel,
with sunglasses. Why are you clicking on the sun? There's the brooch.
And then we need a belt. There's the belt. Congratulations. You have won the game. Thank
you for playing. What the fuck? Why is there a piece of bread on the goat's ass?
All right. Help me out here. Let's speed run this. Everybody clicked right here.
There's no goat. The goat's not here. Thank you. No, it's a cat again. The same like 10 people
clicked on the cat. Okay, that looks good. Are you guys even trying? Somebody is. Come on,
we need to get to the third level. We need to find the brush. Where's the, where's the
toothbrush? Whatever kind of brush that is. Found it. Congratulations. You've done it.
All right, here's it. I gotta, listen. If you guys can get all nine of these
in nine separate circles, you win. Can you do it? You guys will win. Collectively Chat
will win the prize. And the prize is you get to see my face on the face cam and I'll wink.
What a great prize that is. Okay, we got mouse. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. There's no crow on this list.
You guys are so close. What's that? That's not even anything either. You guys got that wrong
too. Two. Holy shit, you guys got a lot wrong. Wow. Oh no, that is right. That's correct.
Oh, that's correct too. Yeah, you guys didn't, you guys didn't get it. Sorry.
You wanna try it one more time? Think you have what it takes? I'll give you minutes to look.
Okay. I want one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight circles. And they only need
to be on the right thing. And I'm gonna wink at you. Think how cool that reaction gift would
be. You know, like you're talking to somebody on Twitter and it's like, oh yeah, like that's
sure. That's definitely my favorite game. I just did it. Get a minute here. Imagine the audacity
that you would have to put these four in a row on each other. To release it twice.
Secret Empires, Secret Empires, Aztec, Inca, Maya, and you click the send to Amazon
purchasing button. Balls. It's actually almost like, that's like almost commendable at that point.
Okay, here we go. I want nine circles. And if you guys, nine circles, I'll give you a sneeze.
You can get it. It's coming. Did you get it? Let's try. Oh, I wanted to come up so bad.
Did you get it? Let's see. All right, we got one, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Who fucking did this? It's a wasp. That's why. Let's see if you got it. You didn't say they had
to be correct. What did you think I meant? Just put nine circles? Oh, we have to beat this
one. Did this last time. Goldfish. I'm gonna give you guys one last chance to get a sneeze.
I actually don't know where they are. I actually don't know where the fuck they are.
All right, let's see what happens. Let's see what happens first. Can you guys find the remaining
four? No, no, no, no, no, not yet. Not yet. We're gonna do this for next time.
We're gonna have a contest. There's the pipe. Find it. Good work. Where's the moon?
Find it. Where's the moon? That's a cat. Oh, I could have just looked at that. Where's the
moon? Holy shit, that was hidden. All right, you guys ready? The next, the goal here for you
guys is can you find all of these? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight before I
get to negative 100,000 points. Ready? Go. My hand, my hand is fucking killing me. What did
I get to? All right, when I get to negative 10,000 points for that, I clicked it. All right,
did you do it? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. You didn't do it.
Bird. Mouse. What have you guys done? It's not even correct. Candles.
Circle. I don't know if that was, but I already clicked it.
Uh, hook. Water jug. You missed. Uh, I don't know if these are heart and I don't know what that is.
You missed them. Sorry. I win. Yeah, that's not it. That's not correct. All right,
if I can find it before you guys, I win. Ready? Go. Got it. I fucking lose.
All right, that was fun. We're out. This is seriously just dump whatever is in grandma's
closet after she's owned the house for a hundred years into the living room and figure out what
you're going to sell and what you're going to, who's going to take what. Well, you know,
like that, like the four kids, who the fuck is taking the penguin statue? What are we going
to do with that? That's enough of that. I'm not going to click the other one. You already
know what it is. Is this again? It's literally the exact same game. They just put a two on
it. Uh, this game has one review on Amazon. It is a one star review. The person just wrote,
I can't get it to work. That's the only review on the entire website. So got baited pretty hard
here, but you know, you got to commit. All right. Uh, what are you, where are we going now?
No, really? Why do you guys want to do that of all the things to do? Oh my God.
Somebody just gave a lot of money. Hold on while we sit here for a moment. Uh, thank you to just
that guy for the $70, $60 right now. And then $10 a few minutes ago. Holy shit, man. Thank you
for the 70 fucking dollars. Thank you. You say, Jeremy, you legendary shit poster. Of course
you would do this again, but I would recommend if you really want the chat to make bad
decisions, you should send them to cool math games. We tried that before and it was a
disaster. And then you say, try the worst game here and make the chat pay for you to change it.
That's so terrible. Why would I want to do that? Make, make you pay. Um, if I just,
okay, first of all, thank you for the $70, but let's go over this for a second here.
If I sat here like this, right? If I'm sitting here like this and I say, okay guys,
uh, sorry, but, um, for us to play, uh, another game, you're going to have to give me 50 bucks.
You just leave. You'd be like, okay, X, I got some laundry. I could probably fucking do.
I would just sit here and watch the view count drop at like four or 5,000.
Some of you guys would stay just to see like what would happen, but you just leave. I don't
know if I don't know. That's a good idea. What the oh. All right. So we're going, uh,
I can't fucking believe I'm pressing this button, but I am. I just have to press it, right?
Oh my God. The, the, the ball of koala, thanks to the $50.
All right, here you go. So that means I have to get off of this.
He, he's get $50 to get off of this one. It actually worked.
No, no, you can't pay. You can't pay. What's going on with the camera? You can't, you can't pay
money to influence what I do on this stream. You understand? If you want to give money,
thanks, but I can't put that as a precedent because we've got super frog two to play
everybody X out of the window. No, stay, stay here. Click on your favorite fucking toy.
Click your favorite toy on here and I'll be able to judge you guys.
Fox. Cool. That's pretty cool toy. Forget about what, uh, the, the onk. That's the onk, right?
Okay. Cool. Uh, bottle of wine. That's pretty nice. Gekko. Nice little pet. Uh, bird crow.
There's a monkey of some sort skull. And I'm surprised no one has clicked on the
cockroach or the spider or the snail. I would have clicked on the snail
or the turtle or the sun. Nice work guys. That's it. That's the end of that one.
So now let's actually get the next one going here because that one was banned,
but I got paid $50 to do it. What's next? Do I have, do I have time to eat like a
bowl of spaghetti? I'm going to eat a bowl of spaghetti really fast. Okay. No.
What's this one? The gorge. What is it? I can't see it. This is, I can't see what this
is. Baby bird care. Sure. Let's try it. Social eating. No, I'm going to eat it as fast as I can
downstairs and like get indigestion. Okay. Here we go. Baby bird care is opening and it's
already having a problem here. I'm not going to switch until I'm certain. Hmm. Maybe. Okay.
It did open. I don't know if you can see this, but here we go. Wait a minute. Hold on.
Is this Diablo 2? Honest to God. 800 by 600 and 640 by 480. What an excellent fucking game.
All right. Here we go. Baby bird care for the baby bird. Change player. Welcome bird.
He thinks I'm a bird. Okay. That's interesting. Help. Wait for a visitor.
Drag a baby bird to an empty nest. Release the baby bird to set it down.
Wait for a visitor. The baby bird wants to sleep. Click on it to sing a song. The baby bird will
fall asleep. The baby bird awakens. The baby bird wants its parent. Click on it and take the baby
bird to its parent. The babies have wishes to eat, to drink, to play. To fulfill a wish,
you should take food from table, water, ball, pickup item and take it to the baby bird.
There's a kitchen. To prepare food, click on the kitchen to place an order and a bird in a nest.
The hummingbirds will prepare the food and place it on the table. They have tables.
To place more orders, click on the kitchen several times. Prepare a drink. Musical instrument.
Drop items you don't need in it. You can use a musical instrument to put all the babies to
sleep. And there are bonuses. Mood. Cook. This is the most elaborate one so far.
2007. We're gonna go on medium level 1-1. No, tutorial. Medium tutorial. I need to know
what I'm going on. This is first day working in... Today will be my first day working in
the kindergarten. If I don't do well, I'll be mopping floors the rest of my life.
So I better listen to my boss. Fuck. Ding dong. This is the first visitor drag a baby
bird to an empty nest. Wait for the baby bird's wish to appear. It's a food wish.
You need to arrange some food. Click on the kitchen to place an order. Right. The hummingbirds
are preparing food now. This is just Diner Dash. But with a Warcraft 3 custom map. Okay,
it's ready. Click on the table to pick it up. Take the food of the baby. Give it some time
to eat. Perfect music to do this one. Remember this thing? Remember from Banjo Kazooie? Hold
on. Remember that one? Takes time to sing a baby to fall asleep. I'm done with this one.
My fucking ears. Oh, wait. It's a bird daycare. The happier the bird are, the more points you
earn. Now you're ready for your next visitor. All right. Give me the hardest level in the
game. Place two orders in the kitchen. There's a... Well, I don't know where the
doorbell is here, but that's fine. Wait for the wishes to appear.
Let's fucking go. Eat. Come on. Already got you. Thrash. Are you hungry again? Food? Sleep?
Same? It was so easy. I was right there. Ready to go. Give it up. Good. Where's the...
How do I buy things? Food? Got it. We got two now. Ooh, getting tricky. This is getting
tricky for me. I can't wait to eat that spaghetti. Look, that looks like spaghetti
to me. That looks like, well, looks like somebody chewed up a bunch of spaghetti and
then spit it all out. But it still looks like spaghetti. You know what I'm saying?
Hurry up. Somebody just wrote, why are people not leaving? Why are people not leaving? I mean,
that is a question. Is it a good question? I don't know. Because people want to see all
700,000 of them. I got a silver extra level. That's fun. 700,000 games remastered. All right,
where the hell was that? There's so much more. What happened? Did everybody just change their
mind immediately? Motorbike. I will never give up. Motorbike. I will never give up.
It's going to get interesting here. Let me get a bowl of spaghetti. No, not yet. Chess.
Do you really? Can this be the one that just gets an X? Can you guys vote for the one that
gets the X? Because chess. Okay, now there's a reason to leave if I open up chess. Who the
fuck wants to see chess? Apparently half of the people in this chat. You want a rematch?
Fine. You get your rematch. We're doing this one time. Well, that's all over the place. Well,
okay. Did I even get to? All right, whatever. It's going to just sit like that.
Got to get this off the screen. Here's your rematch.
Okay, so I'm going to, I don't even know what, who am I playing? Are we players?
Oh, whoops. Okay. Setup. Control. File. Okay. No, no, no. All right, all right, all right.
Hold on. Let's make this better. Yeah, we already did this and I destroyed chat. It was
actually really embarrassing. Okay. Here. This is going to take forever.
This guy is selected. Now where? We already did this. All right. Good move. My turn.
Do I have to like clock out or something? Oh, what the hell just happened? It's making
it smaller. What? God. That's not happening. That's not happening. Sorry. I surrender. You
win. I surrender. Mystery, mystery museum. No, hold on. This looks kind of split between
mini golf mania and mystery museum. This is a great stream to trim. I'm not going to read
the rest of that. Now, mystery museum. I just saw it. I think mystery museum is going to
win. People are still clicking on. No, this is another chess game. No, that's not chess.
That's checkers. Yeah, I saw it. It was mystery museum. All right, let's open it.
Mystery museum. Thank you for voting. Let us click on your face. Okay. A little bit later.
Not right now. All right. What's your runner? This that this actually opens.
It did. Wow. Holy shit. That was so painless. Oh, he is just all hidden object games.
That's when you see it. I need to know if okay, if they're all all of them are
fucking hidden object games. I remember this. Watch this. This is the one right next to it.
This is haunted house. Yeah. Oh, scary. It's the same thing with like a mummy this time.
A really small mummy. A mummy that is not even like three feet tall. That's scary.
It sure is. All right. Let's just get this over with. This is the next one. It's cryptic
castle. Oh, I wonder what it's going to be. Yes. Oh, okay. Cool. There's like 15 hidden
object games in the same. Look at that badass up there. Surfing on a broom.
That's a T pose. Surfing on a broomstick. Witch. And it was what we needed to click on.
That's all I needed to see. That was cryptic castle. This is ghostly garden. It's the
same fucking game. There's no difference. In fact, there's the tiny mummy again.
Same music too. See, I wasn't bullshitting. Those of you guys that watched the video on
the first 700,000. This is the second, part two, second game. I wasn't lying. It's the
witch again. Is it weird that I want that as an emote? Is that illegal? It might be illegal,
but I want this. It's probably, honestly, this whole game is probably ripped off from
Google images anyways. I wonder if I can find this image. Some of you guys that use the internet,
that know exactly what the fuck you're doing. See if you can track this down,
see where it's actually from. Okay. So that was, I can't, I cannot believe it's the same
fucking game. That's unfucking believable. Selling a sequel. There's no sequel. Did
somebody already find it? You did not. That's not it. That's not the right one.
I'm not, I'm not clicking until I'm certain, because these are going to be gnomes.
Crazy witch surfing on her broomstick. I'm not clicking on a gnome and I'm not
clicking on porn. All right. Can one of the mods, let me know if any of these are real
before I gnome myself on stream for like the 30th time. By the way, where are we going?
What happened? Checkers. 700,000 games too. I'll never, I can't get over this.
You want to play checkers? All right. It looks like we're playing checkers,
but no, I don't even, why do I want to play checkers? Checkers? Don't worry. Don't worry.
Everyone that's concerned about checkers, it don't even open. It doesn't even open.
No, it don't open. So scratch that off the list. 3D checkers doesn't open. Sorry,
I know everyone's really disappointed. Liar. I'm not a liar. That, I can't open it.
Just restart your computer and try again. Oh my god. It works on my PC. You don't own that
game. Nobody does. Me and the one guy that bought the game that gave it a one-star rating
own this game. All right. Looks like we're going to mania. Golf mania, which is down here.
Mini golf mania 3D. Will you open? So interesting enough, all the games,
look, we'll do this in real time. Any game that has the word 3D in it.
You ready? Here we are. If it has 3D in the title, it does not open. I wonder why that is.
Hmm. Interesting. Update your graphics card.
You clicked on an image. Yeah, I gotta, I'm sorry guys. It's, but I gotta update my graphics card.
Go again, try again. The same issues from the last one. No, I can't click that one. Do it
again. It does, I, that one doesn't work. No, no, the one, this, okay, fine. Back game in 3D.
What do you know? Hey, look backgammon 3D. You see? Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Which has been found?
Is my computer lagging? I don't even know how to play backgammon. No, wait, wait, wait. You
found the image. No fucking way. Oh, unbelievable. I can't fucking believe you found it. Hold on.
How did you find this that quickly?
Unbelievable. But where did that come from? And did they have permission to put it in their game?
No way. Guaranteed no. Guaranteed no. Is it the right witch? Hold on. That, who,
nobody plays backgammon. No one. Who cares about backgammon? It doesn't make any sense.
Bye. See you later. All right. Let's, and this is very important, actually. Let's see.
Okay. For a second, I was like freaking out. Yeah. I saved it to the desktop.
So there it is. This file is 27 kilobytes. All right. Hold on. Hold on. This is important.
I need to open up this way. We need to see if it's the right witch.
That's actually pretty important. That is the right witch. I don't even know why we're doing
this. You know how much time, there's so much that we still have to go through.
And I'm doing this shit right now. She's not here. We have to beat this level. Edit the
snort over her face. Why is that so funny? I got to get rid of the white.
Where's the witch? So we can compare the image. I don't see the witch anywhere.
I just need to like, just skip everything. It's the castle game. Wrong game. Middle left of
screen. I don't see the witch anywhere. What are you talking about? It's there at all. It's
not, guys, everyone that's saying that I'm an idiot. You have to remember these are all the
same fucking video game. The assets are the same across the entire five game catalog.
Just scorpion. Where's this? We're just gonna get to the next level. Scorpion found the bread.
One more. Crossbones and scorpion. Scorpion. Crossbones. Got it. Okay, here we go.
Is it? It's not the same image. This is not the same image. That's impossible. I don't
believe it. No fucking way. It's a different. It's a different witch. Another one. No fucking
way. I refuse to believe there's another one. There's no way. Oh my god. There's another one.
Oh my god. But it's not the right one. That's not correct. Guys, that's not correct.
It's not the right one. Look, it's not correct. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Hold on a second. Are you guys ready for this shit? It's a different witch.
I need to flip. We need to transform it. It's not the same.
We need to get it out there. Exactly. I need to transform it. Oh, get this out of the way.
Is it the same image? How do I rotate this? How can these be different images though?
That's the thing I don't fucking understand. It has edits on it so they didn't get fucking sued.
Is this the same person? I can't. I don't know if this is even the same. The broom is
a different direction. It's been photoshopped and it's blurry. Hold on. I need to fucking
fix this. No, I can't. I can't do it. The hat is different. It's so fucking pixelated
it's almost impossible to tell. But look at the hat though. I think they just like smeared it
in Photoshop. It's a mix of the two images. Did her mouth just move?
The one on the right's mouth just moved. What the fuck? I'm scared by itself.
Okay, I need to get out of this. Turn these off. That's actually unfucking believable though.
My god. Wait a minute. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. No, don't do this to me. No,
don't do this to me. Somebody just cropped this from this stream. It's a screenshot of
this stream. Where the fuck are we going? We are a fucking ton of money came in. Hold on a
second. Frillity. Frillity. Thanks for the $50. I love this witch game. I don't know how
you guys found that that quickly. Was it as easy as just... Wait, no. Okay, hold on.
Thank you so much for the $50. It's time for slime. Thank you for the $50.
There's another image here. At this point, I don't know which one is fake and which one
is real. Thank you for the $50. It's time for slime and for litty and just that guy gave
$40, $50 on top of like $100 plus $130, $140. Jesus Christ. That's an absolute insane amount
of money. Thank you guys. How do I vote? Just click the screen. This is how you vote.
Yeah, that was fun. Thank you. Thank you so much. Oh, look what we got here. Right.
Probably should take that off. All right. Thank you for the dick that was on the screen.
That's very, very appropriate. So what was that? I don't remember where we even were.
I don't know what that was. What was that? What's the last thing we did?
It was back in 3D. Okay. So are you guys going to behave? Can I turn it back on?
Please. There's another one. I can't tell if this is... I mean, there's another one.
There's another witch image here. There's another one? This is crazy. Hold on. Let me
just like show this on stream for a second. This is like kind of wild here. You know what
I'm saying? Hold on. You guys are still finding these images. It's actually pretty...
This one is pretty shocking. That's kind of ridiculous. I mean, there's so many of these.
Wow. Where did you find that one? There's so many. Is there some website? Is there
gotta be some website that you're going to to be able to create these, to see these?
Witch on broom with scary face. That's the number one result.
Interesting. All right. What are we playing? Amph... Amphric, thanks for the five community subs.
You tried to make another deck and you failed. I don't even know where you guys are going with
this. So I'm going to pick one that's in the middle. I see air ball and mystic demon
between the two nuts is the shaft of the penis. And I'm going to pick one that's in
there because the, you know, you've read what you sell. So we're going to go with,
uh, we're going to go with air ball, air ball. Here we go. Thanks for voting.
Let's see if this one works. It does. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Maybe it doesn't. No,
it does. What is, what is this on the screen? Oh, it's because I can't even turn it off.
I can't even get out of this. All right. Get off. It's because this capture is all
fucked up. Oh my goodness. Reset it. There we go. Okay. Okay. I'm ready.
Why did the music just drastically fucking change? Oh, the music is so bad and loud.
What happened? I'm not even going to attempt to fix the,
I'm not going to even attempt to fix the fucking screen here. I can't even leave the
window. Look at what does that do? Okay. Logan, log in, new game, save game, new game.
Choose your pad. Whoa. One, one. That's my desktop background and it's just a mirror.
How lazy do you have to be? That's the ultimate in laziness. You just mirrored one image to make a
giant screen. Why wouldn't you just get a picture that was big enough to fit? Why? What am I,
I'm a penguin? No, I'm not the penguin. Oh, it's just brick breaker. This one's really fun
actually. Oops. Sorry. It's kind of hard to control though. Ah, I thought I could make it.
Oh, somebody here thought that was funny. I can't even hear anything.
There we go. Kill the penguin. I'm about to. The penguin's about to be dead.
Gotta maximize the shot. Beautiful. What? It's not a real penguin, guys. It's a digital,
it's a digital copy. Well, that's a perfect copy. It's not a real penguin.
This is just, in bowling, this is the worst thing you can possibly do.
Excellent. Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it. I'm the bat.
That one's fucking dumb. It was fun though. It was okay. So that brings us to where, where
the heck was that? Air ball. It was just holding you back. Yeah, I agree. Oh, I'm
gonna get spaghetti. All right, we're almost at the three hour mark and we're, we're, you
know, we're almost like 30% to 40% of the way there. So I'm gonna just, I'm gonna eat
spaghetti. I'll be back in probably 45. I'm just kidding. Motorbike Racing is the one.
Motorbike Racing. Is it the one? Yeah, it looks like it. Extreme Motorbike Racing.
I think this one was also in, all of them were. I'm just, I'm watching one of my
favorite movies that I haven't seen in a long time. That's what's happening right now.
Extreme Motorbike Racing, prepare for the crash. That's inevitable. Let's see what happens.
I can't tell you, I don't know how loud this is.
We're good. Can you see it? By the way, I just came to this realization. Turn the music off.
You just contendo, Nintendo, contendo. Okay. Can you guys, I don't even know if you guys can see.
I have no idea. Every other monitor is black. This is apparently 1920 by 1080.
Okay. I don't think I agree. Okay, here we go. Start game. Yes, I remember this one. Race
two. Race three. Fruising. No entrance fee. Race three. Yeah, I remember this one. This one sucks.
Automatic transmission. Let's go. Holy shit. It is, it is 1920 by 1080.
Yeah, this is one where I just drove into the wall. What? That's my favorite movie.
Look at how you do that though. How do you do that? How do you make that happen?
This is just a taxi driver coming. Yeah, it probably is.
How did I get on one wheel? Oh my god. I, oh no. Space nitro is control. Handbrake is space
nitro control. Horn H toggle lights. Nice desktop. All right, so we're gonna have to do,
we need C L H N control. Control. There it is. Remember this? Remember this part of the video?
I do. Let me actually like, I'm dropping in game currency. I lost. Fruising. He, I, he did
the thing, but from the video? So this is just cruising around. I think I tried to go like
5,000 miles per hour last time. Well, it's still going. Let's try it again. You have nitro,
you can pin a nitro on it, but you can do it straight away. This is not really a good
straight away. It's the mountains. Handbrake. Come on. Then I can do the joke. Yeah. I would
call this one the most complete video game though. Don't you think? That didn't happen.
That, that's patched version two. The one thing that they fixed in the game.
The loudest water sound ever heard. It's turning. I'm going to hit it again.
I need to hit five hundred miles per hour. Oh my fucking god. This is actually starting
to aggravate me. Wheelie on slopes. That's probably a good idea. Straight away? I can't
from this far away. No, no, not yet. Don't punch it yet. I got to get a complete straight away,
which is no, not yet. He's being back seated on 700,000 games.
Punch it. Okay. Stop. Slow down. This hurts my fucking head.
How is second gear 200 miles per hour? It's straight away. I just wish it wouldn't be this
long. Oh shit. It's so hard to control when you're going that fast. Last attempt.
Are they more than two gears? I don't know. They might be straight away.
Really? I don't fucking believe that for a second. How could you not have the gas
station blow up? Still going? Yeah, it's just going down the street. Can I open the map?
I mean, I know I shouldn't care this much about this, but I do. I need to do the joke.
Otherwise this is a different movie. Reverse? I probably, yeah, I can go in reverse. Here we go.
Straight away. This is it. You ready for the joke? That wasn't as good as the first movie.
First movie was better. There's a jump here though. Why would you put a jump there and
not let me go over it? It's the same shot. I know, right? What happened? What? I last drive
into a wall. LOL moment. Nerdy. Here it comes. Whatever. It's done. Stream motorbike racing sucks.
Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Right back where we left it off.
Wait, this is a new movie. This movie's new. I haven't seen this movie before.
We've got a sequel. What the fuck is overhead right now?
It's a casual zeppelin flying overhead. There you go. That was it. Thanks for playing.
I don't even know what that was. What the fuck is it? I don't know where it is.
Where is it? Extreme motor. There it is. Okay. All right. Well, you guys vote for the next one.
I'm going to go grab some spaghetti. I'll be right back. I'm not doing that one again.
Restart. Sorry. I'll be back in like two minutes. I'm not going to do BRB.
Hey, that's pretty nice caterpillar or car. So it looks like I get it. Hey, it's streamers choice.
You know what that means? I get to go anywhere in there and I think we're going to do
parking lot parking lot maze. Thanks for voting. Parking lot maze. Welcome back.
I'm like, I just ran up the stairs. I ate spaghetti with my hands and then came up and
ran up the stairs. All right. What do we got here? Actually, I can drag the bottom.
It's the first one I've been able to do that with. This music sucks.
Turn it down. I don't know what the point was to do that. I'm sorry. All right. Start here.
Monopoly. It's Fortnite Monopoly. Welcome to parking lot maze. Parking lot maze is a,
come on. That's not even. Did you even try? I would see that and change that and fix that.
Highly addictive puzzle game where your goal is to untangle the vehicles and restore traffic
within the streets of Strestropolis. Strestropolis. Move the vehicles by clicking
on them and clicking on an empty tile. I don't know what that says. However,
you cannot move. I played this. It's just this thing. What? Yeah, I did it. The stress
meter. Don't let stress meter fill up or you will lose a life. That's okay. Don't get stressed
out and lose your life in traffic. Oh my God. That's fucking horrible. Okay. I got out.
Got out of traffic. Solve. If you can't get it, you can just solve. I'm pretty,
I'm pretty good at this shit. Multiple goals. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I get you.
I know what I'm doing here, guys.
Oh, he's so good. He's so fast at everything he does. I like this. This is fun. What a
fucking terrible game. No. Yeah. You guys fucked it up. Hold on. Just my face. That's
got to be bigger so you guys can actually click on it. Where am I? You do, you do a dick on my
face one more time and I'll play chess again for the next six hours. Is that what you want? Holy
shit. Wow. You're actually listening. All right. Let's get one more time. Nice and close.
Yeah. Now you lose privileges for the next 10 years. What? I turned it off. Oh, it's because
it's on the other scene. I get it. Okay. Where are we going? That was a car in the lot.
Bust out 3D world. It's either, well, bust out 3D world or alchemy drop. Okay. Looks like
alchemy drop. Let's play alchemy drop. Sure. Alchemy drop. Why am I, can I say that in a
different tone or is it the same audio clip? Alchemy drop, alchemy drop, alchemy drop,
alchemy drop. I can't do it. Alchemy drop, alchemy drop. There we go. Finally. Jesus.
Alchemy drop. It's going to, I know this is going to be a match three game. We're
going to be quitting it in two seconds. I'm reliving the nightmare I had last time
in real time, live on camera. Fuck. I can't believe I'm doing this shit again.
If you had told me three years ago that fast forward a couple of years and there was going
to be another edition of this game that was supposed to be different and it was the same
thing and I'm doing it again. Bust out world. All right. It's time to, it's time to start
picking on myself for the next couple of rounds. Everybody wants to put a little dinky
on the screen. All right. Let's go. Bust out 3D world. It's a 3D game. That means it's
not going to work. You can try it though. It doesn't work. Hey, at least we're going
through it quicker because the ones that, I wonder if it's the same ones that don't work.
That would be hilarious actually. I need to go watch that video after this.
Farmer crates is 3D and it works and it's from the video.
Let's take us back. Oh, Jerma, you really cashed in on that video you made. All right.
We're going to play Farmer, Farmer crates. Did I get this game for one cent? I got this
game for, I think it was $11. Farmer crates did work in the last timeline. So let's see
if it works in this one. Of course it does because this is the exact same collection
and why is it opening on my other monitor? I am so confused. It's opening on my right
monitor right now. This is not correct. So I'm going to put it into windowed.
There's, there it is. It's another song. I don't know what it is. I don't want to play this again.
Can I skip? Can I veto this one? I've already done it. I already know what this one is.
I've already played this one. Remember? Oh, wow. Look at that face that guy has. It's a
really scary face. He looks like a character from the Dark Crystal. I don't know whatever
I said. Some reference. Joe, that's fine. I've done it. You've played all of them. Not all of
them. Some of these didn't work. Some of these actually did not open. A lot of them didn't.
Deja vu. No, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Good reference. Right.
What is it? Three, two, one. And what is going on with this guy's work outfit? What?
This guy puts on overalls and shoes to go to work and he's naked. Three, two, one. I mean,
three, two, one. I mean, like, this guy belongs in a different video game. You know,
he belongs in, he belongs in the Dark Crystal from the Muppets. I don't have any, I don't
know what else to say. Oh, I fucked that up. Oh, Dobby. Dobby. Harry. Harry Potter.
Did I do that one? Jeez. I thought, I thought this was going to be like a big deal.
It was going to be a different thing, but it's just, no, no, no. It is a big deal. It is a big
deal. And you guys thought that was it. You guys thought that there wasn't more. I thought
there is more. Vegas Slot. This 4500 Vegas Slot. Oh, I'm doing that right now. This is
streamers choice, guys. Sorry. Virtual Vegas Slot. So name guest player, name Bank Robert.
No, not Bank Robber. Bank Roll. Bank Roll. Whatever. Who cares? It's a fucking, this
game isn't stupid. Choose game and almost, it's coming. No, it was going to sneeze.
All right. $100 super bets. I get $5,000. If you go hard, you fucking just go home.
I'm going to go five real and we're going to do, I don't know, Dinosaur Dollars.
Dinosaur Dollars blast him up. $100 bets. Deposit money into the machine.
Where's my bankroll? What happened? All right, let's do it again. Let's do $100. And we're
going to go to Chocolate Lover. Oh, I don't know. Okay. Deposit money. $5,000. Deposit.
Choose how many lines I want. All of, all lines. Every line. All lines. 20 lines.
20 lines. It's $100 per line. That's how much is that for one spin?
That's, how much is that? That's 20. That's $2,000.
I lost like 1400 bucks.
Some Y outs. Give me some Y outs. I got like 10 grand on this credit card. This is it.
Multi-millionaire tower of cash. Super sports. Do it. Those machines are stupid.
Everybody knows the best machine at the casino is Betty White's fairy tales.
Or the Ellen DeGeneres dance machine. Everybody knows that. They don't even fucking have those.
So worst slot machine ever. Cheddar, Cheddar Fool. I don't, uh, looks like everyone wants
me to play Cheddar Fool. Circular Pool. Okay, that's what that says. Right. I've
waited three hours for Circular Pool. Well, I really hate to tell you this,
but there is like a 40% chance that it doesn't work. Let's have some faith.
Oh, you just have to have a little bit of faith. Cheddar Fool. Let's open it. Let's go.
Balls are shmeez. And there's coins. You guys see this shit? Blue surface.
Boxcar Bob. Boxcar Bob is going to break. Move the window. I can't,
I physically can't do it. Yeah. I, if I'm, I'm going to side to side of the screen here
and this is a crash computer game. I'll try it. I'm going to try it. Let me know how this looks.
Better? All right. Boxcar Bob. This is cool. It's like a breakup with pool.
This is really cool. Oh, you just have to like curling. You just got to get it out of
the way. It's like sumo wrestling. All right. So what, what is he? Which one am I?
Does it matter? How do I control the ball? The ball is just stuck on the,
I can't move the ball into the center. It's always going to go off the side of the screen.
Um, arrow keys. No, it's not the arrow keys. I'm moving the mouse.
Okay. There we go. Oh, wait a minute. I get it. So it's up and down and left and right.
The one thing that I really, you know, chat sometimes it's just so
fucking irritating. Oh, you've just hit me. You struck me. Bully. All right. I'm going to get
this one. Watch this one in the corner pocket. Uh, I think this is going to work. We got to
go again, right? This music's making me depressed. Why? What an idiot. That's a free
ball. Nice one, Bob. Is that the AI helping me? That's it. I won the game. He knocked in the,
the eight ball. I win. Get out of here. See you later. Thanks for the free victory.
That's it. It's time for me. Yeah. Oh, I can do that better. Oh, you want to fight?
You want to fuck fight? Don't fuck come at me. Don't. Oh, I went too far. I was,
I was looking at the camera. I actually fucked that one up and that's all right.
Oh no, I need to see that. I have to see that. I was, that was a mistake.
You didn't mean to do that one. My hand went too far and I didn't react fast enough.
Did that actually just- No, that wasn't the right one. Don't fuck come at me.
Holy shit. That, oh my God. That actually just happened. Wow. Oh, you want to fight?
Don't fuck come at me. Holy shit. Yeah, I did not actually mean to do that.
I was trying to time it with the kid. That was me actually doing that. Well, that was fun.
I can't fucking believe that just happened. I was trying to do this joke where my hand
comes all the way across and I turn and I turned it. I didn't turn at the right time.
Well, that was, that was the worst part about that is the noise still happens.
The fake joke noise still plays on top of it. Where the fuck is that? Unbelievable. I haven't
even been drinking. I've had like coffee and food. I'll never live that one down.
That'll be a clip that's posted forever. God damn it. Unbelievable.
What the fuck am I going to do about that one? You want to fight? Don't fuck come at me.
Oh my God. That's this so much regret here right now. I can't fucking believe that that happened.
Oh, no. God.
Of all the things to accidentally do, I would have rather shit my pants on stream
because at least like I got a stomach ache and I shit my pants and there's gonna be so
many people that think that that was on purpose and like how why would you not think
that? But why would I do that? Like there's so many layers to how awful that just was.
Fucking unbelievable. I can imagine the people that are already typing it right now like
he just did that on purpose. What a fucking idiot. Like trying to get views. I know.
I'm just, I'm just stupid. God damn it. What have I done?
All right, vote on the next one. How am I going to explain that one to mom?
Yeah, Jeremy, I was watching a clip on Twitch of you slapping yourself in the face.
Why did you do that? Mom, I, I don't know how it happened but it did.
That's people gonna edit that in places and it's gonna, oh my God. What the fuck.
You can hear the embarrassment in my voice. Where's this going? 3D fucking circle pool.
What did I do? Because I was pretending to miss the person in front of me and go around like
a fucking three stooges video and I actually did the three stooges thing in real life.
So it looks like we're going to classic, classic Pac-Man.
Don't take it seriously. I mean, how can I at this point? All right, here we go.
We're gonna go to classic Pac-Man. Ow, my ears. Okay, this is advertising a website.
Oh yeah, I forgot. Yeah, this is the one with the monsters. Remember I'm like, oh,
there's cars instead of ghosts. It's the same game. Well, I can fix that. Classic.
Watch out for the monster. Yeah, it's the same. It's just Pac-Man and it's,
don't go to that website. There's no reason for you to go to that website.
Although Pac-Man, seriously, the fact that if you remove Pac-Man's eyes,
he really is just fucking terrifying. What a scary fucking monster he really is with no eyes.
Pac-Man didn't have eyes? Didn't have a little, little like eye? Well, that's
like a clay version. Maybe, did he not have eyes? No, he didn't. What was it? Was it 1995
when they gave him eyes? Yeah, don't go to that website. Why, I just told you not to go. Why
would you go? Hey, I just went to that website and I fucked up my computer. Don't do that.
If these games are free, why would they be put in this box? Whatever, game's fucking not even,
it's pretty good. Get that off the screen. All right, what we got? That was Pac-Man.
That was, oh sorry, let me rephrase that. That was illegal Pac-Man.
Illegal Pac-Man is now done. Where are we going now? Are you trying to click, what are you
trying to click down there? Are you trying to trick a jail runner or strike bowling?
I'm not sure which one you're trying to click on. That looks like you're trying
to go to bowling. I'm not sure. It could be anything. Strike bowling? Let's see if it opens.
Strike bowling it is. And uh, or maybe you click it on jail. It could be anything. Strike. Call you mom,
she's crying. That's it. Blurry.
Ali, Ali, haunted Ali. Let's see this. Can you still not hear me? Screams? My game was fucking
terrible anyways. There's a creepy pasta behind that game. Well, what's left? Actually, we took a
huge trunk out. Jail? Set this as the desktop background. You want the witch as the desktop
background? That's actually, I can't, that's too bright. That's horrible. No, that's too
bright. No. Hey, remember this? No, the witch can't be the background because that's fine.
Where are we going? Hey, this is your mother. Is everything all right? Mom, everything's fine.
Jail runner? You got it. Excuse me, did I miss something? Uh, no, you didn't miss anything.
This is Mac's escape. All right, so we got, uh, volume is fine. Start. Jail runner. Jalil
runner. All right, how do I start it? Uh, Mac grew up in 1960s when love, peace, freedom
were the ideals of youth. At school, Mac was abused for everything, even for the love
to, even for love to teacher Brown's daughter. You're good for nothing. Having finished school,
Mac became an artist, but no one bought his paintings. In spite of bad luck, Mac decided to
propose to Mary Brown, the teacher's daughter, if you forgot. And what a proposal without a
ring, but here we, here were no ways to get money. One day, a man in a Mac offered Mac
money for making some copies for him, but the stranger sold the Mac's copies as the originals.
The painter was sent to jail. Mary's parents wanted her to marry another man. So Mac escaped
from jail. How do I play? All right. All right. So go now. Can I press that?
What the hell? I can't jump. Oh, I did it. Now I need a key.
Is that it? Can I get this? I got that key. I have a shovel. Ah, the shovel knocks down. I get it.
I get it. I get it. I walked over the rat as a bridge somehow. How do I get over there? I have
to fall down? How the fuck am I supposed to do this? How do I get up there? Top left. Climb on
the pipe. I thought that was part of the background. I don't think I can climb it.
Not the big pipe? Like, it's done with this pipe. All right. What is that sound?
Oh, whoa! Ah! Jail little rat. I'm just gonna go through the middle. X level, you made it.
Well, that was fun. We got, we saw pretty much everything we needed to see.
How about that play? How's that for a play? That is a warden now.
Assuming he just follows you around. Oh, fuck. Okay. Watch out. Why are there ladders in a prison?
Is that a camera? What happens if I go near it? All right. Okay. Nice work.
Wait till them to cross. And then there it is. And then I'm going to go out on that one.
Whoa! All right. That's it. I win. That was a good game. That was another guy.
What else we got? That was Jail Break. Hidden Object Mania. That's not really what you want.
Hidden Object Mania. Or Texas Hold'em. I don't know where you guys are going. Looks like we're
doing Texas Hold'em. It's got 3D in the title. I don't think it's going to work. I will give
it an attempt. Oh, it is. It's opening. This is the same one as the video. Hey! Hey!
Another reference! You ready for more references? How do I start? Random people, random all.
Starting cash. Fucking trillion dollars or 9999999. Me? All right. Whatever.
Everybody gets that money. I thought that was just me. Fold. Fold. Call. Fold. Call. Fold.
Raise. Fold. Call. Call. Fold. Call. King seven. Check. Bet. Fold. Raise. Raise. Fold.
Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Check that bet. Raise. Raise. I wonder what you got. Raise. Raise.
Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Call. Bet.
Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise.
Call. Bet. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise.
Raise. Raise. Call. What is it? You got a nine? I got a oh.
How much money did you just win? Eight hundred and forty-seven dollars?
How can I change the bet? Fold. Ace jack. Fold. Fold. Fold. Fold. Oh no. There goes 0.9%
of your cash. Fold. Call. Call. Fold. Bet. Raise. Raise. Raise. Raise. Call. Call. Bet.
Raise. Raise. Raise. I'm gonna have 5,500 people watching this. Raise. Call. Call. Bet.
I was about to fold. Raise. All right. Come on. I got a pair of jacks. Oh well. Where?
And I'm still, I'm gonna be real honest with you guys. My mind is still struggling with that
slap. It is. It's still fighting in my brain. Like the left and right hemispheres of your brain,
the left one is streaming, the right one is going. Man, that slap. Where are we going?
Oh, you want to go to hidden object mania? You barely touched yourself, you big baby. No,
I know I didn't do it that hard, but the fact that it happened is worse than shit in my pants
on stream. All right. Hidden object mania. Let's open it. I remember this one. This is the same
one. Same shit. You have to find. Dragon attack. It's just the, it's the, which one is
the difference? It's find the differences. Start. Is it starting? Why is there another window
here? I'm so confused. Did they just take screenshots? Hidden object mania bunny play.
It's not interactive, but it wasn't at all. It was interactive. Here you guys have, you guys
play. Start. What do you think I'm doing? Click the stuff. Click the X. This is what
you get for not folding. All right. So did you guys find it? Yeah. Okay. I see the,
the red cheek here. Again, I thought it was a slap again. They're just, you got,
it's just, just trying to remind me of things. The starfish is different over here.
The pens, the eyes are different color. Good work. The pencil is in the middle. Pencil,
pencil. What about the pencil? This is flash player eight. Enter. You guys did a pretty
good job. I think you found, you found most of the things. Nice work guys. My God. So
there are, there are, there are over 1200 clips of this stream. That's like double or triple
what it normally is. All right. We're going, uh, boker drop or mystery Moscow.
He didn't play cubic frenzy. Not yet. All right. It looks like it's split between,
uh, boker drop and mystery Moscow. Let's go ahead and open it. Okay. I'm going to do all
the mystery cities in a row because they're, they're the same game. Mystery New York,
mystery Paris, mystery Moscow. They're all the same. So let's just get them over with.
Here we go. In three, two, one action. Same company, same game, same volume, same thing.
No witch this time. What's the point of the voting if it's just anarchy?
Well, I mean, the consensus usually is about 20, 30% every time. Usually toaster. No bat
tire bunny. This is Moscow, right? I don't know how an apartment building is just Moscow. It's
just a apartment. Mystery Paris. I really hope we see a witch. That would be so funny.
Here's New York. We got to get through these quickly.
I'm looking for a witch. I don't want it so bad.
Jerma witch and emote and Jerma slap. But what, how would I even make the slap and emote?
It would have to be right on contact. Well, that was fun. Those, there's a lobster there.
What are you linking here? See, everything's fine. I'm good.
Bruise? There's no bruise. Look, my face is just like that. I have like a redder face
right now because it's hot in here. Got a black eye. I don't have a black eye. I'm just tired.
Set as wallpaper. Fuck me. Fine. Which one am I going to put as the wallpaper?
Where we going? Oh, that's right. The mystery, all the mystery cities. I have,
oh, what have I done? Mystery Paris, mystery, mystery New York, mystery. What the hell is
the other one here? Mystery Moscow. And then next to that, Poker Drop. Let's give it a try.
Gamesoft. 2000 Sweet Leaf Studios. Windows NT. This is Tetris? Cards? What the fuck?
What's, what's happening right now? Oh, I can choose. Wouldn't a pair work if it was poker?
How does that make any sense? That's three. That's three of a kind.
Does it mean next to each other? Read them and weep.
Read them and weep. Well, that was fun. Special thanks. What are you, what are you clicking
on? What were you clicking? Nothing. Nice background. Thanks. I may as well own it.
Poker Drop. Tetris with poker, but I don't know. I have no idea what it was.
He lacks the knowledge of what occurred. Do I though? I looked at you making a triangle.
We got it. No. Tank Battle is currently winning. Goddamn Tank Battle. Let me see
what you're doing. Oh, let me see. This is the clip. Holy shit. This is,
a pair of work. How could you even see anything? It's like,
this is unwatchable. Oh, unwatchable. We're going to Tank Battle. Let's see if it opens.
Nope. It doesn't open. No Tank Battle for us. Might as well put the X on it.
Hey, you got any other ideas? 100%. What the fuck? What is it? The number is being,
it's covering everything. What is that? Aquarium Shop. Let's give it a go. This one opens.
That's a good sign. Just kind of is in the corner like all these other dumb games.
It was London? Well, are you sure? I feel like I'm going to like this one. This one might
give me at least 10 minutes. All right, options. Let's get the music a little bit lower because
I mean you can't even hear a damn thing. Star Game. How does it work? Same company
that made the other one probably. What's she holding? Since my parents worked as lifeguards,
I spent my childhood by the sea. I discovered the beauty hidden beneath the surface of the
ocean during my first visit to the aquarium. Enchanted. I decided to work in an aquarium
when I grew up. Sealand. Now it's time to make my dreams come true to get started. I
bought an old house by the sea. The previous owner didn't take good care of it, but I plan
on making some improvements. Is that supposed to be the house? With my help, these baby fish
will grow to be beautiful adult specimens. This is the house you bought. Hello, Jenny's
fish shop. At last, my first order. Select a pet to keep you company during the game.
Sharky will help you take care of fish and Taz will lend you a hand if time is running out.
Taz. Yeah, I agree. Big fish. Helicopter pad. Play. It's my first day. I'm going to be
receiving orders to raise fish. I should get familiar with my equipment.
Now it's another one of these. So they bring fish to my store. Why is he locked in here?
Oh, okay. All right. Get him out. Box him up. What's that money? 32 bucks sold.
No, is that right? I think I got it. What's wrong?
Hold on. I got him. He's fine. Turtle saved everybody. Let me make that money.
Is this a real game? Yeah. Taz is supposed to be in here. He's not drowning. He's a
turtle. They live in the ocean. He gives more time. I get it. Pet shop or daycare.
Yeah, they pretty much come to your place for you to feed. Can't do anything else.
Turtles can't breathe underwater. We'll blame people that made this game. I didn't make it.
I had nothing to do with this. You did? Well, then you should have known better.
$259. Three minutes of work. Pretty sick. Why did it take that long for that to pop up?
All right. Let's have a little chat. Let's see where we are right now.
We are at... where is this one? Okay. I'm not opening that one. I don't care. All right. So
we have... we're pretty much at the 50 to 60. We're at like 60 percentile. No, I'm not doing
that one. It's already covered. Mystery London is Mystery New York. See? Look, I opened it.
All right. Now what? Picks up notes. That was a nice speed run.
Did he already play Farmer Crates? Oh yeah. If it's got an X on it means we already did it.
We seem to be very split. 16% are clicking on one that has already been shown on screen.
16% want. Oh, it's close. Taxi? Yeah. Looks... no, hold on. But these are already done. Why
are you guys clicking over here? Should I even ask that question? Stone Age Taxi. There it is.
All right. Let's go. That isn't the first pack. Stone Age Taxi. No, it's not the first pack.
What fucking pack is this in? This one. We've played this one already. No. Got him. Got him.
Got that guy. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. We in trouble? Not good. Not good. Don't do it to us.
Wow. Why is it the click? I can't even... no, what is this like doing? Get off! Get...
what are you doing? It took over my whole computer again. Leaked. Yeah, I leaked out like
the menu. Oh, there's this... there's nothing there. This might... maybe you might have seen
my recycling bin. What's going on back here? I hate that I have to do this. What a crock of
shit. All right. Here we go. Played this one. Kid mode. This one. I do. You can run the
people over and shit. I remember it. What reference can I make? Oh, in kid mode you can't kill the
cavemen. You can kill them in the adult mode. You're welcome. How's this for kid mode? Nope.
Want to see the difference? Here's the difference.
There's the difference. They were really concerned about kids running people over,
apparently. Damn it. These all suck so bad. Oh, what about the kids? We have to take care
of the kids. It's down here. Hmm. Tennis champion. Penguin push. Uh, looks like we're
going to do... oh, it's kind of... I don't know. Tennis? Is this big head tennis?
Yeah, this is probably big head tennis, from what I remember. This is what you waited for,
ladies and gentlemen. That's right. Big head tennis. You guys always try to find a way to
slip in that thing. All right, let's put it on. Tennis championship. Uh, no. No, I don't know
what this means, so I'm not going to do that. I don't know. Why does it need that? Direct play.
It's safe? Skip installation. No, it's going to sit there for fucking 10 minutes and install it.
Why did I just teleport? Skip. That's just... that's not a monster. Side burns? They're
fine. They're fine. They're correct. The closet opened on its own. Oh, it did it now. Did the
closet open on its own? They're not two different lengths. It did. The closet opened on its own.
Show me a clip. They actually are uneven. Bullshit. No, they're not. That's just the way
that my face is shaped. See, there's just less hair here. I have to get my haircut. Look.
Look at the ear. Right here on the ear. Right there. Look at the ear. Right there. See?
They're even. He's so bald. How could you call this so bald? I mean, it's... I'm receding, but it's not...
Don't let him get to you. Don't let him get to you. I'll do two hands this time and go around
and hit both cheeks. I almost did it again. And here's how that happened. I figured it out.
So I'm looking at the preview right now because... well, I'm looking at the preview.
I was gauging how far... I almost did it again because I can't gauge the distance by
looking at the preview on the screen. Can you imagine if I fucking just smashed both
sides of my face right there? For the love of God. All right. Anyways, uneven bald spots.
That's fine. Who just gave bits? Who are you? The guy on the tennis championship icon is just
you when you were doing the green screen walk, but someone has edited a tennis racket into
your hand. That's fucking funny. Well, tennis doesn't work. Okay, why is it? Because
the window's 10. And I did all this shit to... whatever. Tennis walk doesn't work. Where are
we heading? Might be penguin push. Possible. That might be air strike. Maybe the doctor lab.
It's gonna be penguin push. If it's... oh, when we do jewel wizardry, I'm gonna do the line.
Oh fuck. Did I just... no, it's gonna... it's penguin push. No, it's not. What the fuck?
Well, we might as well get it out of the way. I feel like I'm doing stand up. Remember I told
you how I have a tour of the country with my... my popular video? I just get up on the stage and
I'm just like, ladies and gentlemen. Yeah, I got the mic in my hand. I'm just like,
so you know, how are you guys doing? Are you guys doing good? Yeah! Jewel wizardry!
That's what I'm doing right now. This is like the fifth or sixth town I've been to. I wonder
if I can get the whole thing correct. In fact, let's see. Let's see if I can get it. Jewel
wizardry. Give me a moment though. I need to queue this up. All right, where is it?
See? Look! Remember this part? I can't stop it. See? The same thing happened.
My computer. So, you know, when I... this is real. We're just doing the video again.
All right, where... where's jewel wizardry? Where is... there it is. See if I can get this.
Here we go. Okay, I'm gonna try. Make sure you can hear it. I haven't seen this video in a
long time. I think I know what I said though. Incoming jewel wizardry. You're gonna do it?
What the fuck are you doing? You're telling me jewel wizardry is not even gonna open.
You gotta be kidding me. I... where is it? I don't see it anywhere.
What is this? What are you linking here? What are you linking? What is this? I'm not gonna
look at that on camera. I need to make sure you guys can see this. All right, I'm just gonna
go. Here we go. Can I get it? A classic game. A game of jewel wizardry. If you think you're
powerful enough to try to challenge a road in a red dress and a Diablo 2 paladin scepter.
I... I did it kind of good. Oh, I get it. I actually get it. I get it.
That's close enough. He hasn't changed at all. Not quite. Can I like...
Hold on. God damn it. Let's try this again. I'll get the whole thing this time.
I'm gonna wait till it's ready. Okay, let's do it again. No, never mind. We're not doing
that again. Oh, it's a classic. The classic game of jewel wizardry. ASDF. Was it the same
in the video? Because that would be very, very strange. Yes, it was. What? No way. Oh,
that has to be default. Because I'm on a different computer on a different internet.
In a different state. Oh, okay. Oh, I get it. Ready? Oh, okay. Oh, I get it. Oh,
it's kind of cool. Nice. Oh, okay. Oh, I get it. Can't do that one. Oh, okay.
Point. I fucked it up. There's a bonus inside this triangle. I can't get it out.
Oh, okay. I get it. It's actually kind of fun. Nice. Quick, use the Diablo 2
Paladin Scepter. What does this do then? This actually might be the most interesting game
like this whole thing. I think I did say that. Let's just repeat the same video, the same thing.
Come on, Jeremy. Say it. Bonus. Not easy yet. Aquarium shop was the best? I think I'm out of
the disability there. I don't like the time management bullshit.
What about Jail Run? No, that game sucked, too.
Jewel Wizardry is actually pretty great. You know, for its time, I think it was kind of way
ahead of its time. See, they took the game Tetris that they didn't make. Changed it a
little bit. Got it. Come on, hurry up. Hurry up. Nice. Pretty good. Sponsored stream.
That was good. That was Jewel Wizardry. Just like the, remember the last time we did it? It
was so much fun. You're too old. That's why you like mom games. Mom games? I don't even
know what that means. Could have guessed that the next one was going to be Penguin Push.
What games does your mom play? My mom doesn't play any games. Why? Because, I don't know,
she doesn't play video games. She's not a gamer. I'm trying to think the last game. You know
what? The last game that my mother played was Grand Theft Auto 3 because we were like,
Mom, you try. And she's like, I don't know about this. This seems crazy. And then she
smashed into a wall and she got scared. So she never did it again. All right, Penguin Push.
Is direct play safe to enable? Let's see. Is direct play safe now? Is it safe now? What
do you mean now? Badgers, I don't trust this bullshit. I can't host using sockets
because I run ICS as well. You mean that disc erasing effect. I think that was fixed ages ago.
What? Why is that so scary? Is that correct? All right, this is on. Once installed, it won't
cause a VAC BAM when I play other games, right? And somebody writes, direct play is an API inside
of DirectX. It shouldn't cause any issues with other games. I'm going to fucking crash my
goddamn entire PC. Install. It's installing right now. Did it work? Oh, fuck. What
happened? Are we good? Penguin Popper. It's too much. Playing is easy. You and a friend play
penguins who have to escape the nasty Eskimos and their pets. You move through the levels by
squashing all the Eskimos and their pets. You do this by pushing blocks. There are four
different enemies to watch out for. Pushing the ice blocks. This is just, I'm at a concert
and the guy on the piano got way too into it. Oh, what happened? Let's delete it. Come on,
let's see those hands. I think I broke something. Nope, I'm not doing that. That would have been
really bad. I have shorts on. I am having another slap moment on this stream. End tutorial.
I was going to go like this with my feet like dun dun dun. No fucking way. Not right
now. What happened? 80 levels. 80 games in this one. Watch this. Watch this.
Up! Oh, I get it. It's Kenny himself. I'm trying to get the mouse off the screen.
Fuck. Wait, I can go through. I'm so glad I didn't just show like my fucking legs.
Somebody would have freeze framed and it would have been, I would have gotten
banned from Twitch forever. All it takes is one guy to like, one guy just has to freeze
frame the exact second that I like turn my legs over with shorts on and all of a sudden you're
gone. I can't have that. We live in the fucking digital age. Wait, what's this? Yeah, I know,
one guy. Diner Drop. Uh, I veto that one. It's going to be Diner Dash, but a different name.
What's this? Oh, okay. We're going to put a penis. Hey, hey, what do you think we should do?
Hey, hey, hey, chat. Hey, what do you want to do? Hey, shh, don't tell him. Hey,
don't tell him. We're going to put a penis. Hey, don't tell him. Alright, I'm turning on
Diner Drop. Wrong and it's free. Refused to say the website.com. That's not it. That's my face.
There it is. Do you really give a shit if this is not on the right spot? I don't think anybody
does. Yeah, come on. This is a, you're running a stream here. Well, what? Simple moves. Get three
or more identical food items in a row and they will disappear. You may swap adjacent elements
if you swap the elements, but the elements don't appear. They will return back to their
original place in less surprise. The objective of this game is to clear the entire field of time.
If you gather four or five identical food items, then you'll be ready with money. Okay,
he doubled up. That's so much information that I don't, who's going to read this?
That's so much. It's still going. It's a lot of tutorials here. Cool. It's one of these
games. So we've got cheese danishes, cheese hot dogs, three ice cream cones. These look,
it's rotten. That's a rotten bun. There's no such thing as a sesame seed hot dog bun.
Is there? I don't think there is. Is there a sesame seed hot dog bun?
There is? I've never seen it in my 38 years of life.
I'll tell you guys the story of how I spent probably 37 or 38 dollars of my life
on one of these games. I played one of these and I spent like 38 bucks. I played it for like
a year. I forget what it's called. It was like mystery gem drop or something and it was this
fake stupid where you solve mysteries but you don't just a match three game and I
don't know why I did it. There's no reason to.
No, it wasn't bejeweled. No, it wasn't. It wasn't. It was not that.
Got it. Only one more tile to clear. Order and pick up text is outside the box.
You just don't care at that point. You don't care.
How could you care? It's just that's just so
you just don't you don't even mind that that's there.
Come on. Come on. Oh wow. Why would I play that game? In fact, why am I playing this one?
That was that was uh commander crunch. Diner drop. Airstrike. I guarantee this one doesn't work.
I'm gonna I mean it's pretty unanimous right now. I 100% guarantee. I'll try it. I have 699,000
games left to play. I gotta pick up the pace. Well what needs to happen is I gotta pick up
the pace. You're right. I'm gonna just close it for now just in case it flashes on the screen.
No. I'm ready. How to play. The year 19XX. So fill in the blank there.
Third Reich has cloned thousands of zombie pilots in secret labs to support the plan
of conquering the world. To bring the world down and to stop the Nazi and the figure and
to just build an allied commander has called up three pilots in order to destroy the anime
at any cost. Skyfire. Ray, Annie, or Wolf. I won't speed. How do you play? Not like that.
It's just it's just Raiden. I'm sorry Raiden 2. Raiden 2. Yeah it's a shmup. Not really
because it's running at about 22 frames a second. It's hard to have a shmup
when the game runs like this. This shit in serial anymore. Is there a reason they stop doing that?
Just contact this company. Fucking Frosted Flakes. And replace this with Tony the Tiger.
How easy that would be and how cool everyone would think that was.
How about that be like Snap, Crackle, Pup. There are 25 enemies left. I can get them.
Let's play well. Tony the Tiger against the Nazis.
Yeah. Are you telling me you don't think that that would be worth playing?
It would definitely be. Yeah that's what I'm saying. All right I win. What do I get level?
How did I get to level three? This isn't worth playing. But it is worth playing if it was
for free in a cereal box. This can't be worth more money to make than the same Hot Wheels car
every year. You know how much it was probably to license Frozen from Disney to put in the
fucking Happy Meals? If they had just, well I was going to say put Elsa in here. But now
they didn't need Disney licensing. Forget about the licensing. Just put a piece of cereal here.
You don't have to have a licensed character. If it's cornflakes put the fucking rooster on here.
Who cares? You don't need a licensed Disney character. Put Ronald McDonald on here.
Cornflakes are disgusting. Let me just talk about that real quick.
You know I would rather slap myself in the face than eat cornflakes. They're good. How
could you say something like that? They're not. They just, they smell. Have you ever
smelled cornflakes? Pour some milk on a bowl of cornflakes and smell it.
I guarantee you you're gonna go. That's kind of, that's disgusting. What the hell am I eating?
So you'd rather shit yourself than cornflakes. That's not what I said.
Yeah it smells like sour. Like kind of like cheese. Like rotten cheese. Every time I put
milk on it. I don't know what it is. Something weird. Where we going? Oops. Sorry. Spoiled milk
joke minus 20. Yeah. Yeah I could see that. All right. Doctor lab or tomb raider? Tomb
momer. I think we're going to the doctor lab. Don't tell him we're making penis.
Somebody just leaned in really close. Clicked on the penis button. Went
right into this screen. All right. Doctor's lab. Let's go.
Doctor's lab. This is going to be Doctor Mario. Yeah it's Doctor. Even the, that's a total.
How does Nintendo get away with that? That's very clearly the guy from Doctor Mario. Use
system memory. Funny story. I don't even know how to play Doctor Mario. I have no idea.
Doctor Smith. My laboratory got attacked by malicious viruses. I have no idea how to do
this. Does it sound like we connect the two? We have to connect red to red right? Like jump
in a car. Dude this is just Doctor Mario. This is Doctor Mario. That's just Mario when he's
60. 70. Mario is supposed to be like 70 isn't he? Fuck. It's hard to control.
You gotta give them credit though. They just don't give a shit if they get sued.
Why would it ever happen? Do you think it would ever happen? I'm not sure it would.
Oh just put whatever song you. I can't. I'm trying. It's hard to control. Up is the only
thing that changes it. That's going to be something. There it is. Oh it's so hard. You
don't understand. It's like this input lag trying to move these. Trust me. Oh my god.
I pressed it twice. Oh I feel like I'm playing this underwater. Come on queue it up.
Oh my god it's. There was like a half. There was at least a half second delay when I pressed a
button. At least. Had to have been. Uh Pharaoh's Challenge. No. People have decided to change
their minds. The band's gonna sue me. They're not gonna sue me. They're gonna sue.
I don't even know what company this is. When will we play the 700,000th game?
Stop. Don't. Stop linking this flap. It reminds me every time and it brings me back there.
That's the. That's. That's. You know what that is? That's 2019 Snort. That's definitely
what that is and it's way worse. I am going to click on clips for the next year. It's
gonna be like hey dude I saw this uh funny clip that you should check out. It's gonna
be this lap. Just. Just replace it. Snort. Replace it. All right we're going to
Atom Bomber. Atom Bomber. Thank you for voting. I really appreciate it. Atom Bomber doesn't work.
Thank you for voting. Appreciate it. It's a good attempt. Sorry guys. Where you want to go now?
Pharaoh's Challenge. That's what it looks like. Book of Thanos. Don't eat fish. It's toxic.
What are you talking about? That just. Somebody just bursted through the door and just
screamed. Don't eat it. Uh Book of Thanos has one. Let's head there. Book Tales. Okay.
Fun day today. Does it open? Nope. Sorry it doesn't open. Yes it does. Yes it does.
Don't be so quick to say it doesn't. Bingo. It does. And you can't see shit. All right does
it. You need to be able to see this shit. It says please press me. Enter your name.
There it is. Turn off full screen. Figure out what the fuck this means.
Give me a second. Uh I need to show you the options here because what the fuck does that
mean? There's an option here as you'll see in just a moment. Uh so options. Eye candies.
More eye candies. I guess I'm going to keep them on fairy tale. Modest creators. That's
chapter one. Chapter two. Chapter four. Five. Six. Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten. Eleven. Twelve.
Thirteen. Fourteen. Fifteen. Sixteen. Seventeen. Eighteen. You haven't written anything in this
book. Is this my book? 2020. You want to pass? Do you want to pass tutorial?
Uh does this say I want to skip the tutorial? I should read something. Oh god damn it. It's
one of these. Uh cast. Uh meat. Meat. Meat. So. So. Swoosh. E. Oh okay I got it again.
Uh eehee. That's one of the words. Eeehee. Quick. Queen. What's happening? Quest. Quep. Queen.
Queer. Uh all right that works. That's I guess. Uh king. Queen. Keep. Uh on. On. Uh roar. Voo. Vroom.
Roar. Roar. No it has to be connected. Uh shit. Shy. Okay. Uh oh I get it. It does it. It
that's what it does. It auto does it. That's what's going on. Uh sam. Same. T. Uh now. Shut up.
Oh. I killed him. I died. I'm dead. Wait I can do spaces? Hold on a minute. Now that I know
you can do that. Okay how about Saturn. Saturn. Saturn. Saturn. Shre. Yelling is not going to
help. Town. Town. What's this? Lob. Crew. Rine. Rhinestone. How about rhinestone? I can't do that.
Uh be. Here. Wait. Yay. Yay. I'm getting close. We're almost done. Pharaoh's Challenge is where
we're going. That was a passable game. Here where was the eye candy? That was a fantastic
question. How do you vote? Just click the screen. As long as you have the extension enabled.
It should be enabled by default right? Unless you have to press a button. You might have to
enable the extension. Everybody says play bookworm adventures. Well I already I just did.
All right. Pharaoh's Challenge. Touch my monitor. Why? Pharaoh's Challenge.
Now where? Pharaoh's Challenge. We want tennis. I can't get it to work. Tennis Championship
doesn't open. Touch the monitor or we riot. Relax. Hold on a second. I know you can't
see it. What the hell is it doing? All right. Options. So I gotta see if you can see that now.
Can you see? Oh I gotta bring it down. Damn it. You have oh I have direct play now. I can
play tennis. You're right. Classic mode. Let's go. I already did this one. I don't know what
any of this means. Oh this is fucking fun. Do combos. Let's get a five combo. Check this out.
All going this way. Oh my god. I'm gonna fucking scream here. This is gonna be insane. It's gonna
be insane. Pharaoh's Challenge. And let's try tennis one more time because I have direct play
now. Touch the monitor. What what are you talking about? What are you talking about?
What are you guys even talking about? I can't. It's gonna. It's another one of these stupid
things. I'm stuck here. All right. Let's go to career. I need. Can you guys see it?
I have to make it larger. Somewhere on earth is it go. Why are you going up there?
Why would it go up there? Let's see if I bring it down. What it does this time.
This is Hotline Miami 2 music. Oh that's as good. That's as good as it's gonna get.
Timmy. Male be human. You can be what other species? Gonna be like a dog?
Why would they be something else besides humans? I don't know how to play. Shift.
Alt. Control. Z. X. A. C. B. Space. Space. Cursor up. No. What the fuck is going on?
Oh no. Up. I have to make it random shit. I'm fucking so mad. I don't know what it is about
tennis. Tennis just fucking enrages me. It makes me so angry. I don't know what it is about
it. Got it. Look at how long that hair is. I didn't hit that. Oh my god. Fucking tennis.
Oops. Say the line. Oh I can't do it until I serve. Who coughed? How come she doesn't even need
to move? This is not fair. Everything I do goes right in the middle. She doesn't have to move.
I have to move. I keep hitting it to her. How am I supposed to not hit it?
I'm hitting it straight in the middle. All right listen.
There is no way that I'm going to be told I'm doing something wrong in a serial box tennis
game. And here we go. Big. And here we go. Big head tennis. This is what you came for.
It's not going to work. Big head tennis. This is what you came for ladies and gentlemen.
Big head tennis. See. I did it. I did the line. You cannot stop booing me. There's only space.
I can't aim where this even serves to. It just goes right to her. You're so bad.
You can't. You can't. You can't be bad at tennis championship on 700,000 games.
It's not possible. There's one action. There's swing and there's walk through mud.
There's no such thing as being bad at a game like I just splashed liquid on my face.
You suck at tennis. I'll see me in real tennis. I just fucking kick back
and smash it as hard as I can. It just goes soaring over everybody.
You know they properly throw it and it's just fucking I just hit it as hard as I can
trying to hit it like out of the ballpark. You're gonna be like everybody fucking gasps.
Touch your screen please. Oh my god. Why did I do that? I get it. Come on do it for me.
I know you guys are capable of doing this. So are you are you capable of this?
You guys are not even capable. Really? You're supposed to be touching when I touch so it looks
cool. I'll give you one more chance. I'm done with it. I'm done with it. This is too much
of a delay. It's like a four second delay. There was a 55% click on my mouth so you can't
come on. You can't tell me that I'm bad at tennis when it came from this game.
We're going to space something. Space crusaders. How long is this stream? This is almost five and
a half hours. Oh my god. At least we can say we did this. I've been watching all night for this.
Well I hope it turns on because it might not even work. I hope it works too for your sake.
I really do. I'm so sorry. What's even left? One two three four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve. We've got about 30% left. Twenty five. Maybe like another hour or so.
So it looks as a foosball champ. There's 3D in this one running in compatibility mode.
The whole thing is set for compatibility mode for Windows 7. That's what is recommended.
The whole thing is in compatibility mode already and as administrator. All right.
Foosball 3D. 3D in the title and there is 3D in the title therefore
Foosball Champion does not open. Wait a goddamn second. Wait a second. I need to find out this
once and for all. Hold on. So this is this is game pack volume five and six. Five and six.
And that game was called Foosball Champion 3D. It's in here. So what the hell? I thought
it was gonna be an empty folder. Dest was making sure it was an empty door. The door is yeah the
door is moving. No it's not an empty folder. It just doesn't work. Let's not try again. Foosball
3D. Little Herder will work. The closet. What the fuck? I don't even know what the fuck you
guys are talking about. It's close. This is actually really close. We'll have to see. 24.
Wow that's this close. I can't stop it yet. Damn. 31 to 35. Little Herder. All right looks
like Bob. Bob is the winner. Let's take a look. Thanks for voting everybody. Which one was it?
Heli Quick Bob. Heli Quick Bob. Let's see. Open. Does it work? We're getting so unlucky
in a row. It doesn't work. Helicopter Bob doesn't work. How? Why? Look at how cool this
one looks too. Look it starts to open and then it just damn it. Hold on. Let me go.
We're getting kind of. We're striking out here. Seriously. Let me try a couple things
here because I want to see these. A load of bullshit. Volume 8. What was it called?
Bob? Something with a bob? Heli Quick Bob. Yeah it's in here. Let's try it running it
directly from in here. Yeah run it. Is it going to work? Sorry guys. I'm running as
administrator compatibility mode. It just isn't going to work. That's unfortunate.
Let me get that back on the screen. Try again. We're eliminating a lot of these.
Where the hell is it? 8 right? It's down here. Heli Quick Bob is dead. Take a guess again.
Where are you going here? Down lower left. Seems like it. So 4 up. It's just going to be
Connect 4. You want to play Connect 4? We can play Connect 4. If it opens. And it is. It
finally fucking opened. 4 up. This one can be changed because that looks fine. Let me zoom
in a little bit. You haven't played? This won't take very long. Alright let's go. So game.
New game. Or game settings. View. No. New game. Human versus human. Alright I'll go first.
Your turn. I think I'm going here. Uh maybe not. 34. Oh it took it over right now. That's
it. That's it? No? What the fuck? Hold on. Hold on. The vote got skewed. Try it again. Go.
Enhance. Enhance. Alright hold on let me enhance. Yeah that's enhanced. Let's do it again. Enhanced.
Come on. My grandmother's faster than you guys. My grandmother's even faster than you. Uh that
didn't help. That made it worse somehow. Did that? What are you trying to click on over here?
I need to enhance it more. Well that's where you guys are trying to go I think. Now where?
Okay. 47% down here. You got it? Alright I think I'm gonna go here. What about you guys?
Where are you going now? Okay. Right here. Sounds good. Well um sorry I'm gonna have to
block you there. So you thought I was gonna let you just do that in a row. Right there.
You got it. Okay. My turn? Where are you guys going? Okay. Here? Here? This one here? 33%?
Got it. I mean it's a majority. Almost. 35. I'm gonna go over here. Okay. Alright. That works.
That works for me. Alright. Where are you guys going? Here or here? Which one? Here?
Or down here? This one? 11%? That's a little bit. That's a lot. Here or down here?
Well maybe like over here? Some people look like enough here. Okay. Fine. Oh where do I go from
here? Oh hmm hmm hmm. Right here. Looks good to me. Where are you guys going? Down here?
Over this way I think. Maybe like down this way or this way. I've never seen
a consensus like this and it broke. I just had to say it. You guys might have a good play
down here if you get a couple down here. Because like I'm going diagonal here so you
can get a block right here. Hmm. Let me see where I'm at here.
Right into my twap. Where are you guys going? Right here? Oh that's a good play.
Like oh I get this. I get it. Where you off to? We chat is in trouble. I've got three
separated plays that nobody knows about except for me. And now it seems like you're
splendoring a little here. You don't know. Should we go up here? Down here?
Jebaited! Right? Oh no. The one where he holds his head. Feels like this.
Feels failfish. Feels bad. No. Not like this. Okay. Really not like to be in the
position that you guys are in now. No I would not. Because now you have to. You have to
start to worry about the win that I have here. Now you have to worry about it. And I've got
three victories. You sure? Three lined up victories. Oh boy is this gonna be bad.
Seriously. I mean the look on your face. The look on all of our 4500 faces.
Ah look at how spread out it is over here. Look at all these places I can go.
I've got so many. Just depends on which one I'd like to go to.
This way? This way? Right in the middle here. Oof. Oof. Oof. That's an oof. Okay.
Well. Well. Look at that. You would just love to have that wouldn't you?
You'd just love to have one of these. One of those. Right here.
Yeah. You would. You would like that I think.
I don't know.
I love this. 17 percent. Traitors. Traitor.
Okay. This is. This is. There's a decent play over here for you guys if you can come up.
All right. I wonder. I wonder what I'm gonna do.
83 percent. Mercy kill. Mercy kill. That's not four in a row guys.
Do you surrender? No surrender? Never. Okay. Never surrender. All right fine. You sure?
I mean I could if you wanted to. Eddie you want to go here? Oh boy.
That's actually a pretty smart play. You should do it. Please go there.
Absolutely click that. Do not change your mind. Click right there.
I'm trying to help a little bit. Four up. What are you gonna do? Okay.
That's it. Congratulations chat. You lost.
I would play the rest of this out but is it even really worth it? Should I?
Okay. That was fun to play together.
This is a draw. Rematch? Okay fine. One rematch and that's it. I'll go first.
Say how would you save changes to that? Go for it. No. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Stop.
Okay. In the middle. 62 percent. 49. 40 percent. 49 percent. Okay.
Is chat getting too caught up drawing a dick on the screen that I'm just gonna win in four
moves? You can't just click no mercy. Okay. Good luck. Are you gonna draw your dick to
victory? Is that what this is? That's not even I don't think that's possible. Right here. 47.
What do you say? Okay. Yeah that works for me. No that's good. Good call.
No that's not rigged. That's not rigged. I would I was in the middle of saying that's good for me
and all of a sudden everybody changes their votes. It was 44 to 39 and I was like all right and
then it was like wait no hold on and everybody clicked on over here. Didn't wait long enough.
I waited plenty. That was as long as I waited the last 10 turns. That what? Pull it back.
Let's run it back. Let's see it. Well yeah but you just wanted to win. No it's not the
case. But let's pick another game because we got to move through this shit. That one isn't
canon okay. We'll count the first one as canon. We tied. It was a tie game between the two of us.
Between the one and 4500 of us. What the hell was that game called? Checkers? Connect 4?
I have no idea what the hell that was. Four up. Right over here right? Right there.
All right where we going?
Everyone's linking. Oh why is everyone spam linking this?
Oh it's the god. It makes it so bad because we need to watch this because this is very
important. The the slap in the game makes this fucking so brutal. Do you understand?
The slap in the in the game. I timed it perfectly. Why am I linking this? You've already seen it.
That that is. Oh my. Yeah it was real. I accidentally did it but this game sound
made that so much worse. That wasn't as loud as that actually was. That looks like I fucking
crushed myself. All right where we going? Did it hurt? No because I didn't. I'm not playing.
Connect up again. I'm not. No. Let's. Okay the clip of me cheating. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
I want to get this on stream so we can have a documented evidence of what happened.
Documented proof. One second. We can watch this right now. Look at that. 40. Do you see?
44. Right when I click it. Look take take a look again. Slow it down. Look at this. 43 to 39.
You can hear the click. Listen for it. See? I clicked it right here. Right there. Listen.
Are you listening? See? You guys didn't make up your mind fast enough. There wasn't there was
not a consensus. Bang. You can't call me out on that one. You weren't quick enough.
44, 42, 44, 39. Bang. There it is. I mean what more can I say? That's how the cards fell.
So many games left. And we're getting late too. It's been six hours. All right. If even one
percent click on something else. I'm gonna count it. You understand? That's unbelievable.
I'm gonna let. Okay I'm gonna grab uh I'm gonna grab another soda. I'm. Someone's gonna
click. I know they will. See? See? See? I told you. See? We got like blaster balls in space. We've
got fun maze traitors. I mean you got a significant portion of traitors it seems.
All right. I really am gonna grab another drink. I'll be right back. Probably the last
break of the night. And we will clock out the rest of these. Probably another another couple
hours maybe. Maybe like an hour hour or two. Who knows? We're just gonna go. I'm having
fun. You having fun? You having a good time? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. No. Because you cheated. No.
You cheater. I'll be right back. I'm not. You think I'm gonna leave without turning that off?
This is the chat that cried wolf. I'll be right back. So I just tried to explain to
the people downstairs that I hit myself. That I slapped myself in the face.
And I just got. They couldn't even understand how it was possible.
Ah. Was I on purpose? No, no, no. Were you drinking? No, I wasn't drinking.
It ain't AC being green. As Kermit the fucking frog once said. All right. Uh so what have we
decided to do? Chat. What are we doing? Well. You guys just made like a squished dick.
Why am I talking? Stop talking. This never would have happened if we didn't have to come
back into this game. I'll take that vote kick. Kick me. Get me out of here. I'm gonna give a lot
of time for you guys. More than 10 seconds. It was like 25 seconds. You can't tell me that
it wasn't. Where are you off to? I'm gonna hold on for like 10. I'm gonna do 10 seconds.
Okay. That's pretty. That's unanimous. Do a bad impression and the vote kicks increase.
Look at how torn this chat is now. You can't blame it on time this time guys.
You gotta blame it on the from the 20th. Blame falls here because eeeeek. Okay. Have a nice day.
Trying to build up right. I can see right through you. That's unanimous. I've had to sneeze
for six hours and it just won't fucking happen. This is horrible. Slap yourself. Why? Why does
this have to be happening? GG idiot. What do you mean GG idiot? You haven't won yet.
GG. GG idiot. You haven't won. The game still goes. Okay. Uh. Hmm. Can't go this way.
Can't really go that way. So I guess I'm gonna go this way. You're fucked now. Yellow well.
Go for the bottom. Go for the top. Go for it. Connect four. All the way over here. Seems
like that's what's gonna happen. Good luck with that. Good luck. 100%
GG idiot. GG idiot. Right here. Which which one? I want to get this right so I don't have to
fucking play connect four again. This looks like it's going over here. Do a recount? What
do you mean a recount? I don't get a recount. Let's refresh it. Fine. You get you get you
one phone a friend here. What are you guys doing? Why is it so? What is the consensus
here? Do I have to zoom in? I think this is 40 40. This is 41%. 41%. I don't know what this is.
That it's it's right here. No it's definitely this one. This is it's probably like 40
something 30 something here. All right. Last recount here. If you want it in this slot
click over here. If you want it in this slot click over here. You understand? Action.
What is going on? All right. Okay. Hold on. Wait a minute. What? This is correct. This is correct.
What's going on in the middle? It's definitely left. That's 40%. It's the left one. GG idiot.
Shit. I'm a dog sleeping. 100. Whoa. Stop stop stop. What? I can't believe there's 100
going this way. 100. Cut that one off while we can. We have all the winning moves. Idiot.
Yeah. Oh, what's that? Look at me. All right. I'm going to wait here. I'm going to give you the
time to figure it out. I am going to put my hands up. That's 10 seconds. That's it. I
can't let you guys think about it that much. That's it. That's 10%. What are you going to
do now? You want to go here? Wow. Are you sure? I can't believe you guys want to go there.
Are you done? Are you done now? Can we move on? No. Why would I do that? Again,
we already did it. I'm going to pick one at random. Play the Vincent Price laugh for us.
No. Will you pick something? We've been here for six and a half hours, guys.
Pick something else. There's not much more. There's only like 15 more video games to try.
I'm going to do it again. No, I want to win. Well, that's too bad. We're going to play
the cat in the maze. Good choice. See, there you go. You guys get to have your win.
I beat you last time. I beat, first of all, beat you guys. The first time we played
checkers beat you guys in chess, checkmated you guys in about three seconds.
We're tied right now. Checkers rematch. No, no, no. Why would I do that? You win,
you go out. All right. So we're going to do a cat maze. What the hell was this thing
called? Aqua boat maze. Chess rematch or riot. Aqua boat maze does not work. Oh, yes.
Oh, whoops. Actually, that's kind of good because I can do this. How's the hair?
Not bad. Aqua boat maze from Parker Brothers. Press any key. Where's any key, March?
I don't know. A lot of information. Anchor slows monster down. Extra life gives you
temporary invulnerability. You can eat monsters with the ring, Louis. Collect the dots.
This is just Pac-Man. Yes, it is. And there's a Lego guy here. Oh, you guys want me to play
Lego Island? Well, this is kind of it, isn't it? There's no island. I mean, there technically
is an island. It's me. And objects surrounded by a body of water is an island. We thought
I was going to lose. God, Legos are so much fun. GG, idiot squids. I got to beat the first
level. What's this one? This one does something to monsters. Slows them down. Well, good. I'll
eat them both. Get it. Nice. This game is terrible, but I'm going to complete the first
level. It's just Pac-Man again. Yeah, that's unfortunate. I ate his bones and he died.
Odd. Two, three, four. Done. Press any key. That's one. That one's done. No one wants
to me to sit there and play that for like another five minutes. I don't think one person
does. One person. You're right. There is always one guy. That's true. Well, the 35% on Connect
Up is being deleted, so we're going to go with the next highest one. It is books and
beaks in space. Books lost in space. Where is it? Break ball lost in space. No, I'm
not going to play checkers for an hour and a half with chat. We've got 700,000 games to
get through. This one's going to be a disaster. I'm going to do this one really quick. This
one. Here we go. Okay. Cool. I can't see. I can't see. What do I get? What do I
get? Can you guys see what's going on? Got it. I think we hard pass the ones that
cannot be opened correctly. You know what I'm saying? It's 40% of these. Yeah, guess what?
And 40% of your votes aren't counted because of this. Oh, bowling. I know it says bowling.
Cosmo Alley Bowling. Let's hope this one works. Undemocratic. Well, come on. Cosmo
Alley Bowling. I played this one. Did it open on your computer? That's a start. Run
as admin. I did. I've done it on a bunch of them already. I'll try this one. This whole
thing right now is open in Windows 7 compatibility, which it's supposed to be and in administrator
mode. I've tried to open them from their own respective folders in administrative mode
and it doesn't do anything. I will try this one more time. See if we can get it to work.
It's just a whole lot of bullshit. If you ask me. That one was called Cosmo Alley Bowling.
There it is. Properties. We got to make sure it is compatible. Compatibility. Yes.
And it's as administrator. Try it again. It is, right? Okay. Come on.
Jerma sounds fed up. I just can't believe they released a second one of these.
And it didn't work. The arrogance on releasing a second one. The
insolence. The arrogance of doing a version two. You don't know how scams work. Hold on.
What company is this? What else have they done? This is Viva Media. Wild Tangent. What? No,
it's not. What else have they made? Where have I heard this name before? I swear to God,
I've heard this name somewhere. Oh my God. Stalker. Call of Pripyat. Are you kidding me?
I knew I heard this name of this company before. No way. Who made it? No, that's not the same
company. That's GSC Game World. Why would Viva Media be connected to Stalker? Hold on. Viva
Media Games. Take a look at what pops up in the first thing. Strange. Maybe there's like
a weird keyword in there. It's a publisher. The conspiracy deepens. What the fuck are you
guys doing? No, no, no, no. Don't do that. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I'm not going to condone
that. I'm not going to condone that kind of behavior. No, I'm not even going to say it
because I don't even want to give it attention. I don't want to condone that behavior. So I'm
not going to give it attention. Nope. No. No. Pick the next game. What is this
coffee pasta here? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to fucking, I need to,
I gotta paste this on the screen because I, hold on, that went by too fast.
Users have complained that the company's products have an adverse effect on their PC's
performance or are intrusive to the user's experience. PC Magazine wrote in 2004 that
although the program is not very evil, some privacy complaints were justified as the
program's user manual states that it may collect name, address, phone number, email,
and other contact information and could distribute the collected information with the
user's consent. Where did you get this from? Did one guy make this up? I think one guy may
have made this up. No. Did one guy make this fucking story up? And I gave it administrator.
You know what I think is a great title? I think it's a fun
series of games. 700,000 games is a fun thing. It's fun. I think I just want to make sure
that, oh my God, there's no, what do I, okay, time to play fucking, oh well, we're in too
deep already. Let's fucking keep going. Somebody wrote, it's not fun. Why bother?
But that may have just been a jokey copy pasta. I don't want to like say that that's,
I just want to make sure we're clear. That could just be like a gotcha streamer moment
and whatever. I'm going to just say it is because I don't want to fucking think that
that happened. What? It's, I'm never going to be able to look at this and knock, oh my God.
No, but this isn't wild tangent though. This is, the company name was just listed there.
I'm not going to fucking play. Connect four again. Okay. You have to pick something else.
That's a wild tangent Wikipedia. That's not even the same company.
Can one person collect something else? They know your garage door password.
Is nobody clicking? Am I, is my click fucked up?
I just was through it because of this. I just saw a hundred percent again.
Oh, we have to refresh it because that's not going to work. What are you guys doing?
Oh my God. All right. It looks like we're going to enchanted worlds, enchanted worlds,
13%. 26% of everybody is throwing their vote into the garbage can into the garage door.
Enchanted worlds. That sounds like fun to me. I'm glad people are just clicking
random places on the screen. I genuinely made this. Yeah. It's me slapping myself in the face.
We're picking games like you asked enchanted world. Does it open? I don't know. We'll
find out. It's data including phone numbers, addresses, email addresses. Here it comes.
Are we talking about the face slap? No. Well, all this one did is just made my
screen look fucked up. This one works. It's not the game. All right. Enchanted worlds.
How to play. It's divided into cells. Each cell can contain a letter. To guess a word,
you should select the letters in the order in which they're used by clicking on them and
then press the submit button. Guess a word. How you can hear me. Gotcha. Half-Life 2?
Half-Life scores. Music is too quiet. No, it's in a perfect audible level.
There. All right. Treasure mode. I didn't even start. This removes your previous game.
Continue. What are you talking about? I've never opened this game. This is actually kind
of scaring me. Okay. So we got satir. It's already on the list. Okay. Tyrannosaurus.
The word's already on the list. I just put it there. You have to be connected.
Irui. It's already there. Well, they gotta be connected. What does this do? Oh, you add
letters. What? Oh, man. Just get them all up there. Make this easier. Okay. OBS. The
streaming platform. Ghoul. Ghoul could be one. Nice. That word doesn't exist. The word ghost
does not exist. Are you sure? Bot? I have no idea. I don't have a single clue. Taste. Tasty.
Food. A-S-T. They have to be connected. Ta. Tab. Ghost in closet. Run. R-U. There's no U.
Obo. Why is my acoustic foam on the ground? Because it's falling off the walls for some reason.
Chanted words is done. Snowball. Snowball in. Oh, boy. This is people have kind of lost their
minds here. Snowball bust out is the one. This next one. Okay. The whole top row. Yeah,
we're going. Snowball bust out. We got to pick up the pace. We got to get this done
in the next 30 minutes. Snowball bust out does not open. So call it. Try again. What's this one?
Business boardwalk. Seen a lot of clicks. Board. Business boardwalk. Get it open. It opens.
That's a good sign. You guys can't even fucking see. Speaking of not being able to see.
Hold on. What happened to OBS? It doesn't exist. It's off my monitor. I don't know
where OBS is. You guys are going to have to tell me if you can see this because there's
no way I can. You let me know. You can't even see anything. I'm going to drag the window down.
Try this again. I have to exit the game. So I have to go from, I have to drag it.
So I have to take this and drag this down here. Like that. Probably right. I would assume
something like that. Give it a try. All we can do is try. What the fuck was this game called?
Boardwalk. Can you see? See it? Come on. Did I do it right? All right. Here we go.
New game. Select your card. Red, beige, teal. Teal. Add a human player. No, no, no, no.
Computer player. God damn it. Computer. Add a computer. Add a computer. All right. Start.
Is this going to be, is this Monopoly? Holy shit. This is Monopoly.
What are these gems? Racket? They're taunting me here with the tennis bullshit.
Five. Owning a store entitles you to collect rent from other players.
It's cereal box Monopoly. Let us play Monopoly. Guys, you understand the,
what are you going to click on? There's roll the dice. I can just roll the dice for you.
I got the wheel of death. Place your bet on red and black, high, low. If you win,
your bet will be multiplied by two. When the outcome is zero, your bet will be multiplied by 13.
What the hell was that called? All in? Dear idiot. GG. All right, guys. We're at the point
of the stream where I'm going to start just fucking opening. Maybe one or two more picks
and then I'm just going to blow through them and we're going to try to find a good one.
What happened? What's a little Kirby fucker in the left? I'm getting tired.
That looks like we're doing Kirby. This is called Lil' Herder. It's called head drama.
This is full screen, but is it actually full screen? We'll find out in a minute.
It's possible we win. We may have found the best game.
And it could go in a window. Best game of the night coming up. I know. I know. You
can't see. I know. You can't see. I know. You can't see. I know. You can't see. I know.
You can't see. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Now you can.
All right. Lil' Herder. Welcome, Jeremy. Play. It's like game world and level.
And we found the next piece of copyright infringement as clear as day.
As absolutely clear as the sun shining. That is Kirby's face, but just poorly photoshopped.
Very poorly. I even said little Kirby guy. Look at the circle here. Not even an attempt
to feather the edge. Nope. Just drag it over in Photoshop and press quick export as PNG.
We've kind of, like somebody said, we've kind of just transcended to bootleg.
Let's try it. It's probably going to be really, really fun. Speaking of fun,
resizing this window again is going to be real fun. Oh my goodness. In 2014,
just dumping school projects. You know what? There are school, some of you guys that have made
video games as a school project. Seriously, it's absolutely a thousand times better than this.
Absolutely. World one. Angry Birds. World one is fine. I don't know what's going on.
Click here to place an arrow. You have to guide the wandering sheep to its home to win.
This is fun. It actually is. Who recommended this? Nice.
I was not expecting Chu Chu Rocket or the Zumbinis. Send the wolf into the hole.
Don't need this arrow now. Remove it with the right mouse button.
How you make them run into the... Ah, I get it. They run into each other.
They're just starving them. Real nice. Hey, real nice.
Oh man, we're getting... I gotta perk up, man. We're getting low energy here.
When I was playing the piano, I'm just sitting here like this. Look where I am right now.
I'm all the way back. I gotta get high energy. I got low energy here.
I can't fucking believe this shit. You going to sleep? Have a great night.
I know we're going late. A lot of you guys probably got the fuck out of here a while ago,
but thanks for coming. Tutorial done. Now it's my turn. What happened to my arm?
Okay, that was weird. I'm trying to get high energy again. Let me clean this shit off.
Looks better, right? I just like made my skin... Now don't even mention that because
that's for the ASMR joke video. I almost just mentioned a stellar joke that is hysterical.
Don't want to fuck that up until you see that. Almost. What am I doing here? Is that in the
shape to hell? How many arrows do I get? Oh, well I did it. What? Oh, I lost time.
Oh, I need to... and spin it. He's getting tired. I really am. I'm dropping energy.
It's falling. I'm trying to stay with it. I'll get it. I'll stick with it.
I don't have very many more to go. Don't worry. I only have mahjong. 100,000. I'm going to beat
this level and this actually was kind of fun. Where is this one? Williams. Oh, I waited that
one just go. Oh shit, there it is. That was fun. Little Kirby. There's so many left.
There's too many. There's too many. I didn't... I thought I could get this done in one stream.
How many more are actually left? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven,
twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one,
twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five, twenty-six. There's like
six more hours here. Just... I'm going to start opening them. Jewel mines. Go.
No more voting. Jewel mines. This is from the video. What did I say here?
Five community subs. Thank you for the five community subs skill. Really appreciate it.
Thank you. That was jewel mines. What's left? Jewel mines. We got a monster truck
stunt rally. Here it comes. Someone took a screenshot of the ghosts. What ghosts?
Ghosts. What the hell did I just do? I have no idea. Oh, this is the music. I remember this
one. Oh, great. That's yeah. Good ghost.
That was playing really poorly as if I was playing it. That's as good as it's going to
get. Uh, monster truck rally. Go. Do the tree one next? Yeah, I will. I lost.
I forgot about this. Shit. The same exact thing happened in the video. Remember this
one? I did a James Bond reference here, right? References. References. Press H. Tree.
How do I do this? Change? The fuck? Frames jump. Eight. Dry river bullet. Half ring easy.
Hemispheres. Mixed course. Reverse climb. Simple jump. Spider truck. Spikes. The loop. Bullet.
Bullet. Let's try.
Community made workshop maps. That was very deceiving. I thought that was a
jump that they forgot to put the gray part in. That's not a checkpoint. Where's the
checkpoint then? That's not a checkpoint either. None of these are checkpoints.
Why is this called bullet? The game crashed. It did not. Do the loop?
I definitely did not play this in the video, did I?
I didn't even know how to change courses. I'm not sure I even attempted.
That's... why was it that loud?
Cool. All right, that was those two. Am I going to be able to get this
through these tonight? I'm not sure I'm gonna. What's left? The ghost in the closet.
Is it time to go to bed? It might be time to end this. It's been like almost seven and a half
hours of one of the fucking worst things ever. Do teapot pyre. We're gonna do... here's what
we're gonna do. We're gonna do... oh my god. I did not think this is gonna be this long.
We spent way too much time on checkers. Let's go over what these are gonna be.
And we'll play the ones that are worth playing, okay? Let me see here. So we've got
star cosmic bust out. Uh, yeah. No. That's gonna be a breakout clone. Star cosmic invaders. Uh,
yeah. That's a breakout clone. Seek and find collection two. Hey, how about that? Wait,
wait, wait. I'm gonna mark... We're going straight through part two tomorrow. No,
I can't. We can't do a part two. Part two is only going to be like an hour and 10 minutes.
Part two plus kanji. No, we got... We can do it. It's only... What time is it? 11, 12,
1, 2. It's 2 a.m. Eastern. That's fucking late as hell. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. This is the plan, okay? Tomorrow we are going to do the remaining, uh,
games. And, and, and, and, because it's only going to probably take like an
hour or two, I've wanted to play Lucius 3 for quite a long time. So we're gonna do...
We're gonna do this tomorrow and probably Lucius 3 as well. They made a two. Yeah,
they made a three. It really flew under the radar like crazy,
but it is getting really late. I really thought we were going to blow through this,
but we put a lot of time into checkers. So it's time for bed. Actual end of the stream voice.
We'll do it tomorrow and then we will, depending on, I mean, it depends on how long
that takes. I don't think we'll take that long. Look at all these Xs. We really only
have to probably have like another two, maybe two and a half hours. Take those Xs off. Yeah,
you know, I need to take, like somebody screen cap this shit. There we go. We have
quite a few decent ones to go through tomorrow. He plays one game for 11 hours,
can't play 700,000 for seven hours. Yeah, but that was one. I feel like my brain is
overstimulated. So we'll pick back up tomorrow the way we left off here. Still gonna do the
bits in game. Yeah, let me just pee and we'll come back into the bits. Does it feel wrong
leaving the stream half done? We're more, we are way more than half done. We're like 70%
done. There'll always be a part two, don't worry. So I'll see you tomorrow for this part
two. Lucius three. Depends on how quickly we go through these and I'm gonna go pee.
I'll be right back. See you guys in a second. Did you guys see the ghost? Holy, what the
heck? So probably like three, three thirty tomorrow. We'll get back into it. But for
now, let's go back a ways. Thank you binary man for the six dollars. Appreciate it.
Uh, this is watch the whole thing for the full experience. This file has been scanned
with the binary anti gnome system. Zero gnomes have been detected. Shut your traps. Be brave
shit asses. Be brave assholes. Be brave shock suckers. Be brave. Where did you get this?
How the hell did you find this? Be brave horses asses. Be brave bloody bastards. Be brave son
of a bitches. Keep your shit. Be brave motherfuckers. Be brave fuckers. Don't get on my balls. Be
brave. I can't fucking believe it. I thought that guy was gone forever. Never have I ever
experienced something like that where one video there's an audio file and a voice actor that's
there and the next video he's gone. Here's the link. They replaced him with a bunch of
other random shit. But thank you binary man for 12 total dollars is another message here.
Uh, anti gnome scan. There is zero gnomes here. Sometimes more unexpected sound. Drunk
frog reviews French champagne to grab our attention. French French like this desert
rain frog champagne squeaking viral sensation. Champagne champagne has always been celebrated.
11 million hits and counting. It sounds like a dog toy. But actually this is a sonorous war cry.
Oh my god this is so fucking stupid. Of a very angry frog.
Thank you binary man for the 12 dollars and two great videos.
Sprio thanks for the one dollar show this to chat they might like it. Jerma snort.
What the fuck is this? I guess here. Hey Avangrad thanks for the one dollar. Demonic Cucumber
thanks for one dollar. Mankind has surpassed god. 1.4 million games. 700,000 games did twice.
Hey Divus thanks for the three bucks Divus. Jay Paul thanks for the one dollar show. Original
video for boomers who haven't seen it. Well we gotta watch that after. We gotta watch that
because I gotta see how many I gotta make sure I get all the references correct.
So we need to make sure we gotta go after I'm done we're gonna go back and see how many
references were made. But thank you Jay Paul. Thank you bake me home for the two dollars.
They say money thank you. Mo's cow or moose cow thanks for the 15 dollars.
Oh is Nova streaming? Yeah he is. Well when we get done with the bits we'll go say hello.
Super Mario Deluxe is sounds interesting. You could have finished the games if you ignored
the bits. No but I'm I am like faded right now. I'd rather attack this tomorrow and be able to
have some more energy and have fun. Because like I was just like that last two games was just I
was in the back of my chair slumped over. So don't worry it's like not even 12 24 hours
from now. But thank you for the 15 dollars. Moose cow. Hey Germanists would like to say
that the new year starts that we all really appreciate the effort and dedication to
streaming that you put in. And over the six years I've been watching your videos and some
streams it really has been able to uplift me through some tough times. And I would just
like to say thanks. Absolutely thank you. Thank you so much. New year we're gonna have a
lot of fun. Thank you so much. Moose cow for the 15 dollars. Super seal I wonder if this
chad streamer will read my message if I donate 50 bits twice. I mean you did do it right in a row.
So you did you did send a dollar within like 10 seconds. So your first the first one didn't
have a message. I'll count it. I'll count it. Uh thank you the milkman for the one dollar.
God tier frog trigger finger. I was doing some pretty good spamming. Thank you one
g for the one dollar. They just put a heart there. Thank you. Sprio thanks for the one dollar. Hey
German I would love I would love to suggest you a game you might enjoy playing and chilling
around with. It's called Salmon Max. Save the world. It is it's a comedy point and click.
It's very charmful and funny with dialogue and puzzles. It's kind of hard to solve but
you'll enjoy solving them. Game is a bit slow to start. It's well worth getting deep
into it. Oh it also has rats. Yeah uh Salmon Max has been recommended and talked about before.
Maybe on one of these days where I'm just kind of hanging out. That'll be fun.
Darkstar thanks for the five dollars. Oh sorry Darkstar 700,000 games. Of all the days you
of all the days you could have picked for the sequel to one of my favorite videos you've
ever made. You chose my birthday. Man you really are such a gift and maybe I'll sound
like an obsessive fan when I say this but you're seriously one of my favorite people on God's
green earth. Keep doing funny shit my dude and your name is very relevant today. Thank you for
the five dollars and thanks for the incredibly kind words. Happy birthday Darkstar 700,000
games. My favorite part about this is the is the ultimate bait because this is just the same
pack. I'm reliving this shit again but it is fun. It's always fun. Thank you Flank Tank for
the one dollar. Hey Jerma given the last of my bits before I buy more was watching Incredibles
2 the other day and I gotta say this was my favorite scene. I mean it looks bored. I thought
Vi would want to change a pace from driving. This is a spoiler. This is gonna be like a
am I gonna like play a spoiler on screen? No. Like driving food. Does this mean vegetables?
A balanced diet means vegetables kiddo. Get used to it. Good evening everyone.
Thank you uh Swiggity Swanky for the one dollar. You wonder why I don't show videos
on stream on the camera unless I know what they are. Thank you Flank Tank. Thank you Swiggity
Swanky for the one dollar. Here it is. Here is what? One right after the other really?
You working together? See the logical thanks for the one dollar. They say capo.
Capo. Avon Grad thanks for the one dollar streamer. So good at 700,000 games. He
Integra overflows and becomes bad at every single one. What? DG idiot. What word is that?
Am I saying that word wrong? Thank you P337R for the five dollars. Hey Jerma.
Hey. Thanks a lot P337R. Thank you. See the logical again for the one dollar PogChamp. Thank you.
It's time for slime. Thanks for the three dollars. Is this the song?
Is this the song? I don't think so.
Maybe it is. It might be. Drop that song link.
There you go. By the way there's a gnome in there. Thank you. It's time for slime. I'm not sure if
that's what I was thinking of but it might be. Thank you Concerto for the five dollars. Hey
Jerma you might be thinking of the mob song from Beauty and the Beast. Also the original
700,000 games is one of my favorite videos of yours. So I'm super happy you're doing
this. Thank you.
That's all I know. I don't know anything else in that whole song.
I don't think that's it though. Alec thanks for the one dollar Alec 4x4. Hey cool guy what kind of
Timberland Yeezy Supreme Gucci Jordan AirPods you got. If you're rich enough to afford 700,000
games you have to have all the brands on one product. Where was this during drunk karaoke
night? Drunk karaoke night? When was I drunk doing karaoke? I have Bo's one earphone. Thank
you though Alec. Thank you C4G for the three dollars. How can one streamer afford so many games?
Because they're in a big package. They come in one disc. Now thank you Dr. Clay for the one dollar.
I got no words. Bug frenzy. Windows game 2004. It says it's Minecraft. Is it because
of the textures? That's kind of what like cobblestone looks like. Is it like pulling
the cobblestone algorithm? Might be. FGWGWF thanks for the 30 dollars. Thank you.
So I guess Twitch isn't gonna refund my bits so I might as well give them to you.
You've been a huge comedic inspiration to me and since I started watching back in 2011
you've given me nothing but laughs all these years. Thanks for being yourself no matter what.
It's all I can be. I really appreciate that. I'm really sorry that you can't. Twitch had a
bug that had you buy a shitload of bits but I am humbled that you would want to give them
all to me. So thank you so much and I'm honored to be an inspiration. Thank you. Bezos isn't
sorry. Hans Beats thanks for the two bucks. Yo Jumbo Dumbo. Have you ever considered playing
the original Fable from 2004? One of the best games ever. I do enjoy that game. I think it's
very good. I've played through it probably twice. I played the remastered one and the
original one and The Lost Tales whatever the hell it was. The Lost Levels. It's a great game.
Maybe not on stream though. It's great. Jumbo Dumbo. Banana and Banan- Banan- Bananurism thanks for
the one dollar. I've been super sick the past few days. The stream has been doing a really good
job of cheering me up. Hope you feel better and thank you for the one dollar. Get well.
Get well soon. Thank you to Darkstar 700,000 games again for one dollar.
Germa old. Germa one guy. We got new emotes. This is the best day ever. Yeah there's new emotes.
Well one of them has been here already but I made it a baseline emote. Germa expensive.
We'll be changing to something else. Something more appropriate. Didn't I learn my lesson the
last time that I played this game? Yeah but I thought we were gonna get all new lessons.
I guess the one good thing about this is you guys can see in real time. This is kind
of a behind the scenes video three years later. Because even though I got
baited into thinking this was the second one, you guys get to see in real time how fucking
ridiculous and horrible this is. So live behind the scenes three years later video.
It's called version 2 not 700,000 games 2. Well version 2. Why would they need to release
a whole nother product if not to put different shit in it for money?
700,000 games exists. 700,000 games version 2. You gotta assume that there has to be
a reason for that version to exist. Don't want to seem mean but it's kind of sad to think
about past Germa playing these alone and talking to himself. I mean you're describing
almost every video I've probably ever made. That's like making a video. Yeah thank you too.
Again Bala Koala. Just that guy. You guys gave a shitload of money. Thank you both of you.
Smelly boy thanks for the one dollar. Well if it's for another game,
here's your money greedy streamer. What do you mean greedy streamer? What did I do? Hey
flug boy. Thanks for the five dollars. Jesus I think this stream has given me PTSD to the video.
I just want to say hope you're doing well. Hope your heya is cheering you on all the way
to the end of this shit show of a race tonight. Also looked at the old pax photos
of when I met you and low-key got sad. Sad. You should be happy. It was a fun time.
I hope my donation is on soon. I have to pee so bad. Let me tell you I don't see it
for a little while. But thank you flug boy. Don't be sad. That's like that was a great
experience. I had a lot of fun. I always have fun when I do meet and greets. Stop so he can pee.
Did just that guy give another 20 dollars. How do I join? And don't question my choices on
getting your attention. How do you vote? I think we may have uh hopefully you have to
install the extension maybe or refresh the page. Hopefully you got it. Thank you just that
guy for the huge amount of money. Uh numble or no no it's numb legs not numble. Thanks for the
ten dollars and two cents. Love you Jeremy. Thank you. Stop so I can pee please. All right
go go go now. Right now. Quick read his message. No he can pee. Come right back.
Uh just that guy gave another 40 dollars. This is this is all part of just that guy's
uh spree of a shitload of money. So thank you just that guy. 40 dollars, 50 dollars,
50 dollars, 60 you've given an extreme amount. And they say cool witch will burn down your
village and will still be styling while doing it. I can't fucking believe you guys found that
so quickly. Thank you so much just that guy. You back? Did you pee? You're back. All right
welcome back. Hey frody and weapon thanks for the seven dollars. This stream has been
the highlight of my week. Thanks jerma heart. Which emote should most definitely be a thing?
Which emote? Well let me I need to see the legality of that. But thank you for the seven
dollars. It's time for slime. Gave the 50 dollars earlier showing the witch. For litty
we got you earlier too. 50 fucking dollars. Thank you guys. You guys are unbelievable.
Uh thank you scribble for the one dollar. This is the hardest I've laughed in a while.
Thanks jerma. The surfing witch. Yeah and that was that was ridiculous. Great Canadian fuck club.
Gave 10 community subs. I think I missed it. Amphiric gave five. Thank you both of you.
Solid milk. Thanks for one dollar. Great stream jerma. I just got a fireman shirt today
and your stream to give me something to look forward to. Fireman is one of the best
characters ever created so don't blame you. It's the spy theme from tf2. What's what is
the spy theme? What are you talking about? I think it actually is.
Well it was obvious. He's the red spy. Kill me. Yeah you got it I think.
But thank you solid milk. Thank you clockwork for the one dollar. Jerma our favorite gnome
has a song for you. I paid real money for you to listen to this. So please listen. This
is the guy's website. I'm not clicking on this. This is this is just clicking on a gnome
and knowing that I'm clicking on it. Just pretend I did. I paid money for that.
He paid real money to have me get gnomed. Yeah I'll do it for you. Look let me click it.
All right here it is. Clicked it.
Oh
Shit. Got me. He stopped the stream for me to pee. Now you have to listen to the song.
Well you only get to be the one guy at least once. No I mean you only get to be the one guy
once. You might not be the one guy again. Doesn't mean it won't happen. I stopped the stream
for you to go to the bathroom. As the one guy you clocked in your one guy ticket there.
Now you could another day you could. Like tomorrow the next day. But you can only
exchange one guy ticket once per day. Or maybe once a week. Not a gnome. And do I learn
anything? Thank you clockwork though. I hope you had a good bathroom break. Thank you
demonic cucumber for the one dollar. You never find the witch image. Can't you see?
It was the two images edited together. Chat has failed.
It really might be those two edited together to fuck with infringement.
Hey C Clampus thanks for the ten dollars. Tell Andre I say hi. Uh I don't who's what do
you mean Andre? Andre. All right well hi. Hi. Jess homeboy thanks for the one dollar. You say
how do they have the balls to be so lazy? But it's because people like you give them
eleven dollars for these half broken flash games. But no one else is buying this.
There's not there can't be that many people that purchase this game. They probably make like
three or four hundred dollars a year on these games. Thousands of moms buy for their kids.
I don't think that's even possible. Grandma Christmas presents? Maybe.
Dirtball Drop is a standalone game and it costs about six dollars so it's a great deal
actually. That's awesome. I love how you know that. That's kind of it is worth it. Maybe it is.
Thank you uh Sachari for the five dollars. This is the worst.
All right one okay we're getting to the point where I slapped myself in the face.
Uh thank you five dollars Sachari. Man-dom-rec-man-dom requiem thanks for the one dollar.
Captain Worgen thanks for one dollar. While watching this stream I keep having the
feeling it's going to cut off suddenly and the old Jerma outro is going to play.
Not tonight. Thank you Resolute Rogue for the ten dollars. No message just thanks for ten dollars.
Thank you. Means a lot. Tingy thanks for one dollar. After that slap you're going to be on
live uh mostly lost thanks for the one dollar. It's me slapping myself in face.
For some reason I don't know why but uh one anime review. Oh yeah that's right I forgot.
Huge announcement. I watched One Punch Man. It was it was pretty it was pretty great.
That was my 2019 anime. I'm only allowed to watch one. I thought it was really good.
I like the characters. Interesting concept. See you in 2020. Season two is coming out too.
Yeah I like when he punches people and he doesn't want in one time you know what I mean.
Hey thanks for the emote though. That will maybe one day be an emote. I don't know maybe.
Hey the wombat from hell thanks for the one dollar. I'm almost done with my senior year
but I feel worse than I ever have in my life because of what my doctor believes to be IBS
and OAB. I feel useless vulnerable and like I can't go anywhere without risking pain all the
time. I know you struggle with something similar in your youth and I was wondering
if you had any advice for managing getting through embarrassing medical problems at a young
age. Well first of all sorry that you're going through that because it sucks. Second of
all it is a it's a never-ending process. Sometimes I've actually I've been I felt pretty
good in the kind of IBD department but I've been having some issues recently but you just
got to get a good doctor. Try to get a good doctor that gives a shit and you just got to
try to manage it with medicine. Sometimes you might have to change your diet. That was a big
one for me. Try to keep a positive outlook even though it's hard to do. I had a lot of
fucking problems. I had I missed get togethers, family events. I almost missed my sister's wedding
because of that shit. I almost couldn't go or participate in my sister's goddamn wedding
so I know what it's like. I know how that feels. But a couple years later maybe three
years later four years later I started to feel better. I was on a good program. Started
doing a different medical procedure and I'm still I'm still going and I feel better than
I did absolutely six seven eight years ago. Just keep at it. It's tough. It really it sucks
and I wish there was some magic wand that I could wave to give you the answers and to tell
you that you know I would get rid of it. I wish I could. I love how somebody just wrote
Yeah fuck the Patriots. Honestly what conversation are you having? What?
But yeah that's the best advice I can give. Try to keep it's really easy to be negative
and to fall into the negative trap. Just try to balance your diet out and listen to your
doctor and go from there. Jeremy have you ever thought about that urinome because of how
small that I am? No gnomes are a foot and a half tall. Please please do not put me.
Excuse me. I'm at least I'm at least a high elf okay. At least give me that. At least.
I'm at least an elf and I'm not talking about the Christmas pack your presents elf.
I'm talking about a RPG elf. God I wish that was me. Hey mostly lost thanks for one dollar.
Those hidden object games were just somebody's sophomore project in computer science 210
that they tried to make money off of by copying 20 times. Maybe yeah I don't understand how
I guess you just have to bloat it up. Dark star 700,000 games thanks to the one dollar
you have to watch that slap clip again at half speed. It makes it infinitely funnier.
Where is it? How do I do that? Give me fucking break. Oh you want to fight? You want to
fuck? Fight me? Don't fuck? I don't know if I'm ready for this. Oh you want to fight? You
want to fuck? Fight me? Don't fuck come at me. Hold on. All right here we go. Let's see what
it's like. Oh you want to fight? You want to fuck? Fight me? Don't fuck come at me. Don't.
Oh.
Trunk. This is stone cold sober. This is on this is on caffeine and spaghetti.
You want to fight? Don't fuck come at me. Don't. You can see me trying to pull it back too.
That's the worst part. Fucking moron. It synced so well that it's the game. It is the game
sound because I was... play the other one. The other sound is the same exact sound.
Remember when I did it the first time? Can I fart backwards? What does that even mean?
All right we're almost done. Thank you to mostly lost for the one dollar.
Garfy the monday killer thanks for one dollar. Hold on this is this it?
It's just so fucking irritating. Yeah see. Listen to that sound. That's not that's the first
one. Fucking irritating. Lies. What? Uh but thank you Garfy the swiggity swanky gave me a sub so
I'm gonna give him a swiggity thanky. All the cats in the chat are nuts about your stream
Jerma. Make yourselves known cats and chat. Give us some of those poggers in here. The crowd is
going nuts. Garf is honored to be the honorary feline ambassador to the Jerma brand. Years from
now people are going to look back on these streams and say that's Garf up there up on the
stairs. I don't know why I'm up on the stairs. I probably got shipped off to space. Stars.
GoldenCricket thank you Garfy. Thank you GoldenCricket for the four dollars. Good stream Jerma.
Here is CeleryMan. Now Tain I can get into. Oh yeah I know what CeleryMan is.
Could you kick up the uh 43d 3d 3d 3d? Could you kick up the 4d 3d?
Thank you GoldenCricket. It's a classic. Uh demoniccucumber thanks for one dollar.
The guy on the tennis championship icon is me doing the the walk in quotes. Maybe. Darkstar
thanks for the one dollar. The chat draws a phallus on screen joke. Will never not be funny
because every time you just know that a room of 5,000 people all without words knew what they
would do. Yeah. Sirdub thanks for the one dollar. I've been watching your streams for
about a year. I'm hoping this 2019 goes well for the stream. I also suggest a game called
Infamous. I feel like you might like it. Yeah Infamous. It's cool. It's on the radar.
I actually was thinking about doing it a couple days ago but PS Now doesn't really work that
well for me. So I would probably want to figure out a way to do it without PS Now.
We'll look into it. Thank you Sirdub. Thank you MetalSocks for the ten dollars
super frog or riot. Played it in the is the first one we played. Thank you for the
ten dollars. Appreciate it. Thank you CompactViewer for the ten dollars.
It's been a few years now since my friend introduced me to you. We used to watch your
videos on the way home from school on the bus. Thanks for all the good memories. A fan.
Happy to be there on the bus. Thank you so much for watching for as long as you have.
CompactViewer thanks for the ten dollars. Am I the only one who wants Derma to go
with his Dreamcast promise? He's just been delaying it for so long it makes me sad.
It is just sitting back there. That's what the ghost was guys. Take a look.
The ghost is the Dreamcast. Look. You see? Can you see the Dreamcast? It's right there
on the right side. Top right next to the door. That's what the ghost was all along.
Hey PeacefulHaley thanks for the one dollar. I can't believe you lied about not liking
anime. How can I watch a streamer who watches anime? I'm so disappointed.
Why? It's a TV show. It's a television show. So he's never going to play Dreamcast because
it's a ghost. I don't base what genre of TV show or movie I'm going to watch.
How do people rate it? Is it rated? Has it got like an 89%? 78%? I might watch it.
It was enjoyable. I'm not going to go get a One Punch Man
14-inch figurine to put on my desk. I'm not going to dress up as Saitama for Halloween this year.
I'm not going to order the Blu-rays through Amazon Prime. All of those things are lies and
they're all on the way. Thank you Bonjor. Thank you Bonjor Tristan for the one dollar.
Bonjor Tristan again for the one dollar. Dermot please read this out loud.
What happened to F? It was a sign of respect. I lost two ranks in League. What happened?
I don't get it. This is how you meme kids are repaying me. Thank you Double D for the one
dollar. It's a clip. Oh yeah I'm not gonna help. Thank you Smelly Boy for the one dollar. This
is a fever dream. It sure is. Space Dad thanks for the one dollar. F G W G W F thanks
for the five dollars. All these games that won't open are all going to open at the same time
later tonight and nuke your PC. Oh that would be terrifying. Thank you Zaldi for the one dollar.
Dermot let's be real. The follow through on your pimp hand is godlike.
Thank you Jax for the five dollars. Jax3636. Thank you for five dollars. Appreciate it.
Demonic Cucumber thanks for the one dollar. This Connect Four game isn't fair. You could
literally see the next three moves we were planning from the get-go. If you want it to be
fair bring in a mediator or let us vote on grid references. No you guys can click the screen.
You know what you're doing. Hey Ike Turtle thanks for the one dollar. You ever thought
about doing board games with chat? Like a bunch of stuff. Tonight's stream with the
Connect Four was pretty fun. I think it would be wicked rad to do other games against it as
well. Also we can see how you cheat in other games as well. If there was a system
in place where because it is it's actually really hard to do what we were doing.
Because I have to activate the extension. Let you guys vote. Turn it off and restart it
for every single time you guys could click on the screen. So if there was a more streamlined
way to do that I would love to. It's an interesting idea if there's some extension
or something in the future might be worth trying. But it was fun. I had a blast.
Uh three TS Luke thanks for the five dollars. I haven't donated since you were in Anor Londo
so here's more patronage. Patronage. I just said Patreonage. The internet has destroyed me.
Thank you Fuzzy Muffins for the ten dollars. Thank you for playing with us Jerma. Gigi
idiot. You know you love it. Thank you Fuzzy Muffins for the ten bucks. I do. It's always
Dark Star. 700,000 games thanks for the one dollar. Just thought I'd ruin Connect 4 for you.
All right if neither player makes a mistake during the game the winner will be determined
by where the first piece was placed. If the first piece is placed on either end that player
will lose. If the first piece is placed in the center that player will win. And if the
first piece is placed that in the in between it will result in a draw. Good to know from
when I want to beat my friends. I mean and I already did tonight. You know you know you two
you two beat you guys. You two there. The two of you that were playing. Mostly lost thanks
for the one dollar. The game probably stole your stream key. Let's hope not. Peaceful Haley
thanks for the one dollar. Another good stream Jerma. Hope the Wild Tangent Studio doesn't
have your credit card and charge you 50 times for 50 more 700,000 games. Anyway I
would recommend playing Fallout 1. I just started playing it and the first thought I had
was well Jerma would enjoy this. Anyways again have a good night Jerma and chat. You as well
Peaceful Haley. Fallout 1 is a very very very fun game. It's kind of like Kenshi and I know
that comparison is very very thin but it's in the same house as Kenshi. They live in different
rooms. It's a Kenshi but fun. All right I am not gonna let somebody in the chat
say that Kenshi's not fun okay. Because that I don't believe that that is true. I believe
that that is not true. Okay I believe that that's not true. Done. And now you triggered
them. Space Dad thanks for the one dollar. They just have a heart. Thank you. Thank you
Space Dad. Thank you Tybe? Tib? I'm gonna call you Hovercat because that's the end of your
name and my brain cannot say the first part. Thank you Hovercat for the ten dollars. Hey
Jerma love your streams. A lot of folks in chat look up to you and consider you a positive
role model in their lives. My question to you is who do you look up to and consider to be
positive role models in your life? Thanks for all that you do. Never stop being you.
Um I don't know years ago I would have probably told you. George Washington.
Role models? I don't know about role models. I mean this is I mean this is a young Jeremy
answer and this is gonna people probably gonna put lul in the chat for this one but
I'm probably Hulk Hogan. I Hulk Hulk Hogan when I was in my early teens. Oh man I mean not
anymore. I don't I don't like oh yeah Hulk Hogan. No but in my kind of younger years
probably was Hulk Hogan. Into my late teens and teens probably 20s probably Jim Carrey.
I'm literally one of my favorite comedic actors ever. Jim Carrey has influenced so much in
the world of comedy that it's it's absolutely unbelievable. You go watch that string of Jim
Carrey 90s movies. Holy shit they are they're unmistakably some of the funniest movies you
will ever watch. He's changed a lot right recently but remember he's like he's also
gotten older too. He's gotten old. He's in his like what his 50s almost his 60s now.
It's hard to be to be Jim Carrey. The funny guy. He actually talks about that in that Jim
and Andy Netflix original. It's worth a watch. He's 56. Truman Show is one of my
favorite movies of all time. Oh my god yeah. Truman Show is fantastic. I mean do I agree
with literally everything he said in the last 10 years? No. Is Jim Carrey your dad?
Uh no but that's pretty much it. I would say those two. Thank you Space Dad for the five
dollars. They said uh moi. That's moi with French champagne. Uh chocolate cheese thanks
for the one dollar. Uh a bit of caution for Lucius 3. There's a really graphic
graphic scene. Oh dear. There's some really distasteful steam achievements
that go along with it. Uh well I'm gonna have to check that. The French champagne has always
been celebrated for its excellence. But thank you for the heads up. Thanks for the warning.
Thank you Razzle for the one dollar. Hey Jerm sorry to keep you here longer but I don't.
It's fine we're just hanging out. But I just had a quick question. You are so attentive
plus concerned about the few that don't enjoy your streams. How do you deal with negative
comments on your YouTube videos back in the day? Uh there's a YouTube link. Uh are you linking
to a comment here? Am I gonna feel bad right now? Is this gonna make me sad? Uh it's somebody
vaping. It was muted but it was a vape gnome. It was a gnome vape joke. It was muted so don't
worry. Uh how do I how do I I'm concerned about the few people that don't enjoy the
streams. I mean it's not necessarily. I don't think it's I don't think it's a concern about
people not enjoying the streams. I think it's a it's more of a concern of people thinking that
the thing that they're watching is not worth watching. Like boring.
I mean like enjoying the streams is kind of a hard way to look at it because
you can still enjoy something if it is boring right. There's plenty of things that I enjoy
that are boring. So not enjoying the streams. Yeah but like there's plenty of things that
are boring that you can still enjoy. I'm probably wording this in a in a stupid way but
negative comments you just have to take the opinion and somebody said it for a reason.
Somebody said something. Somebody didn't like something for a particular reason.
I get what you mean kind of. Well good. It's also been eight hours and I I need some
spaghetti so but you just kind of have to end. My internet is like going through a
problem right now. No we're good. But yeah you just have to let negative comments if somebody
wants to be mean or negative actually and not just I know a lot of people joke around we
go back and forth a lot of times for fun but there's a big there's a big difference between
mean and fun right. Like actually angry or like hateful and I don't know I can't change
that person's opinion. I'm not going to be able to. I told you guys this a couple days
ago or even like a couple weeks ago. I will never say like oh fuck the haters.
No because that I'm not going to change that person's mind so why antagonize them why why
why try to tell them that they're wrong. I'm not going to change their mind if they
don't think I'm funny if they don't think the streams are funny. What that's that's
their opinion and they're absolutely entitled and have a right to have that opinion.
I can't tell you that you're that's wrong because I don't know your tastes I don't
know what you think is interesting. I don't think this is I don't think you're very funny.
I don't think your streams are good. Uh well uh no you're you're wrong. I mean am I yeah it's
so subjective so it's I don't want to fight negative opinions because what's the point
just people are going to have different opinions and just that's it.
That's pretty much what I got to say. Hey P337R thanks for the three bucks. Hey again
Jerma will there be a new tier three emote? Yes there will. I want to make it worth
that was worth it before I think. No it wasn't. Make it the witch oh god I have to I don't know
if I can use that image for people to pay to use that image that I don't own.
That's kind of a slippery tricky slope there but we're almost to the end of the bits. Thank
you Darkstar for the one dollar wait if I change my name to reference another one of your
videos will you do a sequel to that one too? All right I guess I'm now dorkcube7000.
Thank you FGW for the one dollar whatever you do don't read this he's he's got a knife he's
uh all right I know I didn't read it. Thank you Darkstar again Darkstar 700,000
games one dollar and ten cents. Is Jerma's slap more or less embarrassing than Jerma Raptor?
That's tough I don't know. No Jerma Raptor is more embarrassing. The slap was an accident.
The Raptor was intentional so absolutely the Raptor is way more embarrassing. Hey Fitty thanks
for the one dollar wow this stream good was the stream good should I watch the VOD just kidding
I watch every single fucking VOD anyways we had fun we had fun I had a great time we're going
to continue it tomorrow Clueless Sniper thanks for the one dollar no message thank you
Clueless Sniper. Fitty thanks for the one dollar did somebody mention connect four that
game is solved if you ever want to beat somebody almost guaranteed here you go
connect four game dot game solver no I don't want to know that information I feel like it
ruins the game hey Jeebus thanks for the one dollar Pat suck go I'm not going to read that
out loud and then you wrote bah ha ha that's it for the bits that's for all the credits
here's all the new subs to shitload every damn day you guys spoil the fuck out of me
seriously thank you how do how do I raid someone I actually don't know how to do this
what do I do you type slash raid with their channel name let me see if it works what's
with the fps here no wait is he is he offline he's not streaming anymore well shit um
did he just did he just turn it he just turned it off uh damn it raid me who's live
right now games done quick is going but everybody knows that already what's what's Joel
doing oh twist okay sending more health yes San Andreas is a great game well yeah let's
let's go say hi to Joel so what happens when I press this button when I hit raid
does my stream turn off it just hosts his channel so end the stream and then do it
how long does it last for so end and then slash raid and make sure I get the name right
so it does a countdown okay so you raid before ending the stream I don't like how do you how
do you do basic twitch function a couple more bits came in but thank you Shawnee noodles for
the five dollars hey what's up guy just wondering if you have any near future plans to collaborate
with criken no plans but I'm always open to it he's a swell guy door cube thanks oh my
god thank you door cube seven thousand for the one dollar he he I did the thing you said I would
derma one guy it's time for it's time for a raid so let me get this straight thank you
everybody I'll see you tomorrow probably around like three three thirty something like that we'll
start again due to the rest of the 700,000 games and so I end stream and then I'm gonna
go and and raid raid Joel okay I'm ready so turn this on end stream then raid raid first
all right here we go so how do I get to like see this happening and we're ready we're ready
to raid we're doing it now what so when I press raid now what does it do it ends the
stream so now I end the stream okay I'm ending the stream now and I'm gonna click raid now
see you later everybody see you tomorrow have a good one