Good afternoon, hi hello everybody. You know how much your turnips are? I know.
Okay, you know what? No, I do know. My turnips every day are worth
12, 10 bells for a stack. So you don't want to, my island sucks. You don't want to come to visit my,
they're worthless. See? And they're worthless every day. 12 bells a stack. Yeah, it's bad.
So now people don't need to know. Don't come to me.
Does that like shove the fucking gold bars under the bed? My turnips are worthless. He's got...
Yo, Jerma. Yo, hey. Is he playing No More Heroes? Yo. Yo. Yes, how are you? I played it yesterday.
Were you here yesterday? I'm probably at like the 40%, 30% point in the game.
The idea is to try to finish this today. And if I don't, then we'll finish it tomorrow
and do something else after it's done. I had to go early yesterday. Is the cat still a fat boy?
Uh, well, you'll see. So here's the plan. Here comes the remainder of the week. I'll give it to you.
No More Heroes 2 tonight. Trying to finish it tonight. If I finish it tonight, then I'm playing
Resident Evil 3 Remake tomorrow. Hopefully finishing that in one stream too. On Thursday,
if that's the case, I beat this today, beat Resident Evil 3 tomorrow. And on Thursday,
we're going to get a special treat of Tiny Toon's Wacky Sports and maybe one other Super Nintendo
game of my choosing. Now this plan falls apart if I do not beat this tonight. If I still have
another two, three, four plus hours of content in No More Heroes 2, then I'm going to play it
tomorrow. And then when it's done, gauge the environment and see if there's enough time for
me to do Tiny Toon's Wacky Sports and then do Resident Evil 3 on Thursday. Or potentially
the start of the next week. I'm not sure yet, but Resident Evil 3 will happen. We'll see.
Don't stall and start. That's been three minutes. We need every moment to make sure you can beat
this. Every single second counts today. Dude, every second counts today. All right. All right.
I'm ready. Oh, he's stalling. I'm not stalling. It's been four minutes. Don't make me put on the
anime. I will. All right. Let's go. He caught us. He hasn't been here since yesterday.
We're No More Heroes 2. This is the sequel. I tried that. Wait, didn't I? Oh, right. I opened
it once and said, no, I'm done. Okay. I remember. I'm going to do, how much money do I have?
I'm ready for the next mission. Love this series, bro. Yeah. I can't wait for the third one.
Oh, I forgot you can press B. Wait, who was that?
I read the tweet and thought it was Neo 2. No, not Neo 2.
Hey, that's true. The paper boy's a genius. Does anybody else feel like if you stood in
one of those, it would just make you shit? Anyway, I'd have to go to the bathroom in five
minutes after that happened. It's just shaking you and vibrating all your intestines and stuff.
Yes, the association resorts to this when there isn't much activity in the rankings
or when there are too many strong fighters or sometimes when we just get bored. If you're like,
Jerma, I'll give you $10,000 if you drink a full coffee and stand in one of those for 12 minutes
and not have to go to the bathroom. I'd probably lose. If you win, you'll jump to the 10th rank.
Damn, that's a twisted way to do things. You agents are becoming as fucked up as the killers
you rep. Oh, we've always been fucked up as you say. We just we like fortnight. You guys
fucked up assassins working with fucked up agents. Doesn't get any better than this.
Mature streamer. I'm just keeping it on permanently. No doubt. I'll kill them all in a flash.
I put that on for the drug stream and then I never took it off and I'm never going to take it off.
Okay, so we got ranking battle. Let's go. Oh, destroy man. Wait, is destroy man in this?
Is he? I don't remember. Is it actually destroy man?
I don't know why. In my brain, she's playing hand simulator. That's like a hand simulator setup
to dial the phone number. Why am I thinking that?
He's trying hard not to talk about. No, I'm fine.
Damn, is it my turn yet? Anybody work here? This is taken forever. Open the gate so I can kick some
ass. What's that meme? Did it work? Connect the legs. Somebody do it. The game is stalling.
What is your sense of suggest carnage? This guy who is my next victim? Question.
Surprise task. You are identified as Travis touchdown.
Luck is an irrational concept, but your presence defies probability. Do you remember me? Question.
I do. He died last game. I don't know who or what the fuck. Wait a second.
Oh, yeah, you're that fifth ranked freak Henry sliced up before I got the chance to.
It's going to happen again, right? It has to. Affirmative. After near fatal decimation,
I had no choice but to take this modified form. Looks to me like you just gained a few pounds.
Hardware was affected, but my pride was not. With determination levels maximum, I thought only of
winning. It was meaningless, futile, illogical. But such is the curse of being run by a human brain.
That brain also makes you talk about desert. Why is that always funny shit? But if you want to
take it out on me, go ahead. All I desire is a duel with you. Desire level 100%. Revenge on primary
target was previously accomplished. So Henry makes a cameo before fighting you. I elected to
defeat formally top ranked assassin as practice sequence. This was same individual on whom I
also desire vengeance. Efficient turn of events. Do you agree? Would you shut up? I just need to
make one thing clear. I'm not going to kill you because of Henry. I'm going to kill you
because your big metal ass is in my way. I love that saver. Activating main engine.
I already know this routine. We actually do have to fight it.
That was quick. Is it going to be a maze? I hope not. Pretty fast for a tin can. Now it's my turn.
Shit, we actually fight it. I thought it was going to be another joke.
Activating engine. Let's go. Half is the floor. Okay, that hurt a lot. That almost instantly
killed me. All right. Oh, this is safe. This is a safe spot. Okay, I get it. The ones that don't move.
Come here. Oh shit. I got to go get on that one. Where are we going? Oh shit, this is not going to
work out, is it? Holy shit, this thing is powerful. Okay, easy, easy, easy. Stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Find a good spot to stand. Where, where, where, where, where?
Oh, wait for him to move. Wait for him to move. What's this? What's that?
Jesus. Okay, I can dodge that, I think.
Oh, it says I don't like this. I don't like the extreme explosive noise that pops up.
Come here. I'm safe right next to him. Yes. All right, this ain't so bad. This ain't so bad.
Don't be an idiot. Okay, easy. Wait. Okay. Oh God. Oh God. It's not safe.
Oh, it hit me in the face. That wasn't safe. It got like the corner of my mouth.
Oh fuck, did I dodge it? I think so. I don't know. It sliced off my nose.
Just move. Just move. Where's he going? Oh God. Oh God. I know, I say it a lot. Okay.
Okay. This is safe here. I need that health. All right, where's the health? There's a health box.
Fine. Oh my God. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm not okay. Shake everything. Shake
everything, right? Okay. How are you missing? What? Okay. I'm fine. Oh, he tried to get me with a
dive. I can't make it. It's so hard to deter me, man. It's so scary. All right. Is he going to move?
All right. I'm good. Bang. Again. Nope. Easy.
I'm too scared. I'm terrified of that. All right. Is he going to fly forward?
Is he going? Nope. He's going to do it right there.
Again. Again. All right. One more time. Don't move. Is he going? This is it. I win.
Okay. I'm fine. Game over. Boss dead. This is a scary one. Scary one for those disgusting sounds.
That was just me opening my mouth and closing it to talk. I just didn't do it.
What is it? Okay. I don't even know the origin of this. I don't even know what this is,
but I've seen it. Hey, it kind of worked, I guess. Master. It's been a long time.
Shinobu. How did, wait, what did you say? Did you call me master? I don't have time for apprentices.
You have any idea how much pro wrestling is backlogged on my VCR? I came to tell you I got
back safely from Asia. You should be happy. I didn't even know you left. It's the lore.
I'm not your master. My only desire was to become strong like you, master. So I trained hard
and I thought to become the champion of Asia. Here's my belt. No way. You won this? That's
pretty badass. When I get married, I'm not getting a ring. I'm getting a championship belt
that you have to wear forever. Me? Overburdened? Who told you that? Sylvia. She said I should come
back and help you. What? Who's that bitch think she is? My nanny? Listen up, Shinobu. This is my
war. I don't need help from anybody. Well, the thing is, it's kind of too late for that.
What are you talking about? But isn't her arm gone yet? I'll explain later, master. But you
should go to the bathroom first. Seriously, it's a long story. We're going to get a lore dump.
But I'm not your goddamn master. We're going to get a lore dump. Oh, we went from 23 to 10.
Looks like we skipped a few. Oh, yes. It's that time again. It's time to activate the one guy
squad and tell them to play God Hand. Did you pay attention? No. Not at all. Sorry. Somebody says
it about God Hand. Yeah, I'll play it. July 30th or something. Something, something. July 30th.
Sorry for interrupting your time abroad, but will you fight for Travis? Sure.
I'm eager to kill, so hurry with the details. Straight to the point. I like that. Can you handle
two of our top ten? Two? Only two? That's nothing. Why don't I just take them all?
You've grown confident. Yeah, but not overconfident. Unlike you, I can see myself
objectively. Easy, vague, never. Don't forget your promise. What are you talking about?
I already gave you a hard date for that. You're not worth the stain on my blade.
That's just bad steel. Staining your blade. You must not have a fucking Kathy Mitchell copper pot.
Wait, that play is her. Jump. Hold A then release. Long range. Press A while jumping.
Jump attack. Press B while jumping. Flying attack. Oh, they've added a jump. That's all it took.
Let's do a long range attack. Well, that was fucking awesome. Can I play with this character
the rest of the game? Whoa. I took cash from the toilet. Small F. Emulated. Small F, that's my fault.
Don't worry. It's always my fault. Blame me for everything.
These quick slashes. Oh, I mean, yeah, I got a VPN. Come on VPN. So
that's to make, you know, it makes sense. Don't worry. It ain't gonna, this, this stream ain't
gonna, it's not gonna like turn off and not gonna fucking lose like 10,000 frames. It's just,
I'm going through a, if you ever heard of the term called a VPN, B E E P I A N VPN.
Designed to help with like traffic flow and where's this other person? Where is this person? Oh,
there you are. Can't go through the window. Damn it. All right. Long range, right? Let's go.
I want to do it. I'll do it. I've, this move is cool.
What is she saying? You have no moe? Are you fucking with me? Moe. Oh, it's moe.
Where's the last guy? Oh, there's a chest over here. Apologize for saying moe. Is that a word
that nobody wants me to say? That added to the banned list of words that streamer can't say.
There you are. Wait, you just were here, but now you're not here.
You just were here, but now you're not here. There you are. Meester. You're not even close
to meester. Holy shit, that was loud. This is like every roommate scenario when they're playing
Counter-Strike and you can hear them through the wall. Like dude, settle down, man. Dude,
he's kicking my ass. Dude. God. Cano wins. This fucking screen. It's like, dude, just,
I know, input lag sucks. That's why I don't play online video games that have precise inputs,
because it's like a quarter of a second delay. That's why I don't play them. People just keep
spawning. I'm going to get some blocks in here. That was sick. Long range. Bingo. Here comes a
bingo. I was listening to your stream when you were playing No More Heroes 2 and you did this
thing where you said bingo, bingo, and I fucking hated it. I couldn't get out of my seat.
See you next week when somebody sends that as a message. What's going on with the voice here?
That was weird. Somebody was in the middle of typing it, I'm sure. Well, this looks fun.
Sneak through. That was easy. She had another weapon. Just one weapon. She got one weapon.
The one-time thing, so no. Fuck it. Fuck it.
Shiva. No, she sent some gifts. That was awesome. There's money in here? Holy shit. That's a lot of
money. All right. Watch it. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. Good. Pizza. Oh, it's a chainsaw guy.
Don't even let him. Oh my god. I tried to dodge. All right. Back up. Stop taunting. She gets up
and goes, you have no moa and I can't control it. Attack. Whoa. She says that every time.
You have no moa. Kill. Apologize. What's it mean? What's it mean? What does that mean when I say that?
What is moe? What's the word mean? It means you're not, it's you're not cute?
The anime term for cuteness. I thought that was kawaii. I thought kawaii was anime cute word. Same
thing. Oh, so what would, what would make somebody say moe over kawaii? What does kawaii have that
moe doesn't or the other way around? I have no idea. Okay. Thanks for the help guys. I could
rely on you in anime terms. Come on, get it. No, this is a Reddit chat. Um, I don't think it is
unless you're all pretending to hate it. Unless you guys really actually love that site and
you're pretending to hate it. Okay. I can't lock onto that. Uh, what can I go over to there?
Oh, that sucked. Is there another way to get up there? Okay. Yeah, I just,
apparently just didn't do it good enough. Just didn't do a good enough job. Just don't,
please. Did somebody learn from Gotcha Force and have the camera be in the right place? Gotcha
Force did it. Why can't everybody else do it? Well, I've, how did you miss? Do I actually have
to make this jump? I'm not going to make it. I told you. Like I wasn't, it's weird. It's
fucking weird. That's like a fucked up weird. I told you it's odd. It does. It's okay. I feel
like I'm crouch jumping in the source engine. That's how this feels. God. Okay. Where's the
last one? Oh, I see it. I see it. I see it. I see it. I can't. Oh, this is going to be in the ass.
I already said anime sucks. Whatever. I'm not even going to address that.
Unbelievable. I'm not even going to fucking address that. If you're going to the bathroom
in the shower, this is like the go to the bathroom save point. Wait, he showers and he shits. How
come he never takes a bath? Hey, thanks Ben for the five community subs. Appreciate it. Five subs
from Ben Eldor. Ben, welcome to the German mites. No, actually I get that. I screw up the way that
I say that usually the first or second time I did it right that first time. I'm going to hate this
fight. Who's there? Sorry, but I got to make this quick. Golden gun. It's a young girl. If you kill
me, you can fight Travis, but that's a huge it. You talk a lot of trash for a child. Let's get to
the fun. Done. Okay. I'm not going to go easy on you just because I fuck you. I'm not going to fuck you.
Come to this.
Where did he go? There he is. Walk it. Walk it. Walk it. Walk it. Walk it. Walk it. Walk it.
Holy shit. Come here. All right. Spring it together. Walk it. Fuck you. Why does everybody say
fuck? Walk up. Walk it. Oh, fuck. Walk. Walk. Walk. How many did he shoot? He shoots one,
two, three, four, five. Why can't I walk up the stairs? Hey.
Hey. This guy's nuts. Oh, fucking platforming. Oh, it's not designed. This game wasn't made for
this. I knew I was going to not like this part. I'm not going to go easy on you. He's freaking me
out. How did I not make that jump? That's just so wary. All right. It's one, two, three, walk.
This fucking thing up, man. Where? I don't even know. Where's the camera? Did he say money? I love
money. Is he below me? Okay, block. I'm not blocking. Oh, that's right. She taunts after
every attack I've got. Good. What are you not going to do? Don't jump over him. Dodge better
than anybody. Why is it not blocking? I'm blocking up. What the fuck are you doing?
Block. Block. Drop him. Kill. Kill. Kill. Kill. Kill. Fuck. Why did I not block the other ones?
Where is he? You don't have anything else but two voice lines. Where even is this dude?
He's down here. It's what? Seven shots? One, two, three, four, five, six. I'm down one, two, three,
four. I don't even have the 50% health, man. It's almost trouble. Try to get in front of it.
Don't even let him shoot. Don't let him shoot. Don't let him shoot. Don't let him shoot a gun.
All right. Don't even let him shoot the gun. Suplex him. But you don't have any moves. She doesn't
watch wrestling. Really? Okay. I know the strategy. It's just don't let him attack.
Yeah. What are you talking about? She won the championship belt. She should know.
Okay. We got this in the bag. Don't let him get any shots off. All right. Get up there quick so I
can... Okay. What? You have to fucking wonder. You have to wonder. You have to take into
consideration the fact that this... Why? No. Don't eat that pizza. I better not get hit.
Oh, my fucking God. You got to be kidding me. Don't let him shoot. Don't let him. Don't let
him. Don't let him. What are you going to do about it? What do you think you're going to do?
He's stuck. He's stuck. He wants to shoot me so bad, but he's not going to ever.
He's not going to... Don't let him shoot you. Don't let him do it. He's so confident.
He's not... I cheese. I cheese. Spread it. You don't know anything about wrestling, I guess.
I broke him out of his spell. Store up. Another Counter-Strike roommate. No more heroes, too.
Desperate Counter-Strike. That was way easier than it would have been. No Moe heroes.
I can't talk. Come on. Oh, he's speaking. That's not how that works. Laughing my ass off.
What? Yeah, that's what I asked. Wait, she doesn't even know what it means?
Says it every five seconds. She doesn't even know what it is. That's so funny.
It's this bishop's grave. Yeah. Who's this? Were you friends? Yes. We never met in person,
but we knew each other well. We exchanged many letters even though our countries and
languages were different. That's like a fucking knife on his back. That's a big, huge sword.
I am very much indebted to him. He gave me courage. Oh, I'm just rambling. Don't mind me.
By any chance... Do you know his best friend, Travis? Of course. Excellent. In that case,
would you please give this to him? It is from Bishop. This? It is a lot of things, I suppose.
Knowing it is your hands, I can have peace of mind.
That looks like a type of shitty luggage you'd buy on Sky Mall trying to save space.
Thanks. I promise to deliver it. It fits under the seat.
Yeah. Shinobu, the next match is ready. On my way. This better be good.
Wait, is this the match? The rocket launcher. I wonder what it is. Oh, outdoor. Outdoor zone.
What you got there? I didn't see the second guy. He thought it was just one guy. Wait.
Secret. Can I get up there? Or is it... Do I eventually get over there?
I think I eventually get over there. Okay. On the ground. Kill now.
Why did he walk like the heavy? What do you mean?
Both of us are having trouble.
Yes. This ridiculously high streamer can't even do a Tetris puzzle.
Fucking yesterday. Everything opened up Tetris. What are you talking about?
I thought I could tell before I got out of the car. Now that would have been epic.
Everybody's so vulgar. Everybody just screams fuck.
When are you going to do a cigarette smoking stream?
What? I just said they're in smoke? What the fuck would the point of that be?
I didn't even know you... There's no reason why he would smoke on stream. Let alone smoke
in real life. Another carload of people.
I'm going to smoke every brand of cigarettes and let us know what the best one is.
A guy that's never smoked cigarettes before in his life. You want to do a cigarette smoking
first time impressions channel. Like guys, I'm not going to... This is not opening Breath of
the Wild for 10 minutes and then writing a review about it. That's not how this is going to work.
Because then I hope I will... I'll get addicted to smoking cigarettes. I don't want to smoke
cigarettes. That's gross. Do it. You got to be cool. No, sorry. The only thing I think is
fucking cool is a McDLT dance. Nothing else is cool. I'm sorry. You're wrong.
Okay, boomer. Wouldn't the boomer be the one that had the cigarette in his mouth right now?
Me having a don't smoke stance. Guys, you would know I was a boomer if I would be smoking in my
house right now. Like cigarettes in the house. Not like, oh no, I'm going to step outside. No,
no, no. I smoke in my office. There's no face game to prove that you aren't smoking. I'm not.
Wait until he stands up. Make it embarrassing. I missed a lot of money.
Can I go over here? Is there the... Look at those chests. Do I eventually get up there?
I don't want to miss the chests. Oh, I think I wrap around in them.
All right, here we go. Over this way.
I'm wearing heels. Stupid. Okay, where are those... I got to go pick up all the junk over here.
Just on top? Where are these two? Where are these two? Oh. What are you going to do about it?
This guy's freaking me the fuck out. I'm just going to go. Wait, no, I got to go down every hall.
Oh, this is going to be a pain in the ass, but I have to do it. There's money in me.
Can't tell if that's faster or slower. It's probably slower. Charge is a... Charge is...
Oh, fuck. That's awesome. Thank God you told me that. Cash. Good.
Who snitched? That makes all of our lives easier because I don't sit here for more than like
more time than I need to. What do you mean who snitched? Can I get there from here?
Please don't have to kill those guys. Do I have to kill those guys?
Yeah, I got to kill those two guys that were standing. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I do.
Don't smoke. Stop. Why would you smoke? Why smoke? Don't do that. What are you talking about? Don't
smoke. Oh, I can go. You smoked CBD oil. No, I didn't. Sorry. The proper use is a tincture.
A tincture? Tincture? Okay, this is where we go. It's getting so bad. Did anybody play this
when they were in the middle of making it? Wait, now I'm back. No, go over here.
Now I'm turned around. Wait, what? Is this the right way? It's all the same fucking car.
Oh my goodness gracious. This is the reason why Legend of Zelda never had a fucking jump.
It would be this awful. Dude, let me walk across the board. It's this camera.
Stuff changing. Holy shit. I can't do an attack because I'll fall off the fucking roof.
Shinobi levels are low key awful. I mean high key. Like, sing it as high to pitch as you can.
Like, see, like, I'm just trying to walk fucking straight. Like, what the fuck?
Where's the stupid trucker I can get up? Oh my fucking god. Like, this is like,
high pitch break the windows high key awful. Not low key. Low key would be, no, this is like,
where the fuck am I going? Why did I go this far? I can't wait till I get the jump deleted
from the game. That happens like immediately after this is over, right? And we never have to
do this again. Like, I mean like instantly. We don't get a jump, right? Ever again?
Okay, let's walk across the bridge. Okay, please. Don't like shift the camera.
Don't go off the edge. I'll be so mad. Don't, Jesus. Turn another bridge.
Don't fucking fall off. Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's, it is, it is
fucking bearable. Holy shit. Oh my god. Can I jump up from here? Where do I go this way, right?
Is it over here? Where the hell is it? I'm on those. It's right fucking here.
Ugh. How do I forget? I'm not forget, I'm just insanely angry. Holy shit. You've got to be
fucking kidding me. This is harder than crouch jumping in the fucking source engine. Dude,
this has been, what a fucking journey to cross, to cross a bridge. Okay. I can't turn the camera
and even in the tiniest little movements make you fucking go frantic in this game.
Like, what the fuck are you doing? They're deliberately trying to make me fall.
Bakitu, get on it. What are you doing? Don't even go over there.
Can we fucking fight somewhere else? Because I see edge. I don't want to fight on the edge.
The edge is guaranteed to fall off the fucking edge. Don't move. Hit that chest. Wait, is that
bridge over here? No, no, no, no. Don't do this again. I got to just jump over here.
I almost didn't make it. I almost didn't make it. Oh my god. I don't want to be facing like this.
It's going to happen. I'm going to be so slow. You have no idea. Let's hug the fucking wall.
Hey, we're good. Holy shit, that sucked. Suda. What the hell was that? Suda. Suda wasn't in on
the Rectus one. Oh, so this is the Dark Souls 2 of the franchise. Oh, well, that's all right.
It's still fun. I still like it. I just don't like this part. I don't like the jump. I don't like it.
Send it back. Send it back. Return it. Dark Souls 2 is good. I didn't say it was bad.
I just said it was the Dark Souls 2 of the game.
The Dark Souls 2 also was not made by the same director, right? He kind of took a little hands
off approach, right? What do I remember? Why does he hate this? Am I supposed to be doing this right
now? I'd love to look down. Press the C button. Yeah, that just spins the camera. Yeah, if I was
doing that on the bridge, that'd be bad. It would rip the camera. Then I would walk the wrong direction
for a tenth of a second to fall off the bridge. Another one here? There's probably another one
right here somewhere. Wait, is this a truck stop bathroom? Why does it look like this?
It's like the nicest random warehouse bathroom ever. All right, let's go. Why doesn't she shit?
I don't know. Why do you want that to happen? Why do you want anybody to shit on a camera?
What do we have here? A young lady? You know, it's dangerous coming to a place like this alone.
You ought to be more careful. Seriously. Terrible things can happen. I see it on the news all the time.
Maybe that's why she came. It's what she wants. Two grown men to keep her company.
Horny slut. My master's got his hands full, so I'm taking his place. Not that it matters.
The results are going to be the same. I don't have time for this. You're taking Travis's place?
Wow. I got to say, I'm feeling pretty disrespected. Just shut up and fight. Listen to this
whore. Acting like she's some kind of femme fatale. Shut up and fight, she says. She's really
kissing me off. Seriously. And she's so rude. Reminds me of my complaining customers. Now,
Travis, he knew how to fight like a gentleman. Slice me in half, sure, but he did it with grace.
Come on. Put her there. Don't do it. You know, let's shake hands. Sportsmanship is paramount
to a fair and clean fight. Hurry up and shake. Dirty nympho. Whatever. But which one? It doesn't
matter. Your choice. The one that's throbbing. I kick, I kick, I kick. Destroy Spark. What the?
What? Was this supposed to spark?
I really have to fight two at the same time. This is going to be terrible.
Enough with your freak show. Now bring it. Oh, boy. And his jumping involved. Oh,
he's already mad about it. Your scoot is dead. Watch it. Watch it. Don't get greedy. Watch out.
What are you doing? Where's the other one? The other one. What's that thing? What's it floating?
I'm just going to focus on one.
Get me out. Destroy Spark. Go hide him. All right, go get the other one.
No, fight this one, I guess. The other guy's just raining hell on me.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Oh, headshot.
Take it. All right, he's about halfway. I got to get out of this corner before I get killed.
Where's the health? There's a health box somewhere. Spark. Watch out. Where is it?
Leave me alone. I need health. Where is it? There's a box. Where is the box?
Where'd he go? What? The other guy can't hit me. Oh, that's unfair. He didn't even do it.
Hey, come on. What's with the fucking turn? All right, watch it. Watch. He's going to do moves.
Destroy Spark. Do it. Whoa. Where did he get me? Spin, spin, spin, spin. I'm doing it. What's
happening? He was shooting at me. I have no idea what happened. I guess I was behind the cardboard
boxes. All right, get back over here. I'll block that. Get behind the boxes. What are you doing?
Dude, it's making me fucking mad. It's making me mad. He's dead. Only one more asshole and I win.
Fuck. What's he doing? Hey, what is this? Did you just revive him? Wait a second.
They both have to die at the same time. Are you kidding me? They have to die at the same time,
but now I have to. That's so unfortunate. There's health up here. If only I could get it.
I'm not going to make it to the pizza.
No. Do I got anyone left in me? No. Oh, goodness. Okay. Well, I don't, I have to,
they both have to die within like the same time. Soybeans? That's not what he's saying.
That's what you deserve. You deserve that. Stop it. That was a wave. He dodged backwards.
I'm trying to get you to stay in the way of all his attacks. All right, hit him right in the fucking
head. What? You're just doing destroy beams the whole time. Get that shit. Get that smash
from this bullshit tactic out of here. Playing in a Hyrule castle. This fucking person playing
Samus just sits there and presses standard B across the map. Let him play the game.
You refresh Twitter more than you've played. Don't let him do it. Can I interrupt this?
Oh my God. Oh my God. I don't think I can. Can I interrupt it?
I need the health. I need health one. You seriously just spin around and hit me with that?
That's next level homing missile dude. Come on. Oh, come on.
I can't even get the fuck out of here. I'm going to die from this.
All right. Where's the, where's it? I don't even think about it. You fucking asshole.
All right. Oh my God. Is it safe back here? Is it safe right here? Hey,
holy shit. It hit him. It hit him. It hit this guy. All right. Kill this guy and then spawn camp his
body. Don't let him do it. All right. What are you going to do? Are you going to land?
I don't think so. Motherfucker. Hey, get out of here. You're not going to revive this guy.
No, you're not. I'm not going to let you do it. Not going to happen. What's that? Don't let him
revive him. No, no, don't do it. Please. No. That thing was homing for like 30 straight seconds.
You need more practice. How long can you have a device follow you the fuck around?
I've got to kill them before they get this off. Dude, I don't know. What the
fuck is happening in this fight? Holy shit. I'm going to fucking cry. This is horrible.
All right. Come here. You shoot a fucking homing bomb out. Why? Why does it take you so long to
finish that animation? Oh my God. I'm almost done with it. I'm almost done with it.
I'm almost done with it. He's directing the third one, right? Are we certain of that? Do we know
that? Do we know that for sure? Are we certain? God, I hope so. What is he doing? This guy's freaking
me the fuck out. Hey. I'm going to go up there to try to fight him. He's going to come revive
this motherfucker and I'm going to scream. Here he comes. That's my chance. Get out of here.
Get out of here. Go ahead. Fly away. I do need that fucking help though.
Where is he? Get out of here. I'm just scaring him away. Okay. I have to make a move.
He wants me to make a move so bad to come down and do this. I got to make a move.
Fuck out of here. This is stupid. This is stupid. Okay. This is stupid. This is stupid.
Don't do this. Don't even think about it. Get out of here. Where is he? Go off.
This is going to take forever. This is going to take forever. I have to get in there and fight
him. I can't just do this. This is dumb. I have to fight him. Holy shit. You let me heal. What a
fucking asshole. Go get him. Okay. I'm ready for him too. He's going. He's going. Go, go, go, go.
Go. Here he comes. Let him come over here and do that again.
Get the fuck out of here. Get away. Get out. All right. Now we play safe. I'm not fucking around.
He's going to hit his head right in the pole. All right. We're good. I'm going to follow him
this time. Oh, he's going to get it. He's going to get it. Settle down. It's all right. Settle
down. Which way is he going? I'm going to get up this way. I don't want to. Now we kill him.
Go this way. One last shot. I win. I don't win. I don't want to ever do this again.
Okay. Holy shit. I can do a better one than that. What do you think? Should I go a little
bit more with the throat? No. There it is. I'm going to get demonetized for saying
MonkaS. Well, that's a MonkaS scenario. And that's how I took them out. Destroy Man came back.
Didn't see that coming. He was an annoying prick though. I'm glad he's dead again. I can kill more
fighters for you. Whatever my master wants. I'll give me the game back. Master. Pesky little cub.
You can't kill me. Eat this. Must be having a nightmare. Hey, over here. I can't. That's how
close you can get with VR helmets on. I'm sorry. You can really count on her. The rest should be
easy now that she has done her part. Yeah. Wait. Something wrong? Nah, it's nothing. I like that
cactus. The next sucker's all mine. Oh, I'm about to be done with it. Let's go, Gene.
Holy shit. That was 171 centimeters. That was insane. What the what? You're so good now.
That's got to do it. Close. Not punching anything. I'm not punching the cat. We're doing squats.
Big junkers. Junkers. Junkers. It's not even like that funny, but it is. It just is.
Big. Oh my God. That's funny. Old record beaten. All right. 14 pounds. Let's play.
That was close. Come here. Nice. That was a whole pound from a bro. Travis Touchin was literally
me. Like LOL. We both have the same bleak nihilistic outlook. It was deleted. Probably
rightfully so. Now we feed the finest quality cat food. 13.9 pounds. Good. Oh, this is the present.
The beam katana is how much that beam katana rose nasty. I don't have to spend any money on it.
Let's go see if we can speak in a money. It's been a while. We did like two or three missions
in a row. Let's go check out what we can do. You know what I mean? Like three pog moment here.
No, no more mini games. Well, I mean, how am I supposed to make money? I need money for the gym
and money for the lab. Look, I'm just going to do some... This is playing. This is how you make money.
I fucked it up. This is going to go like this. Wait, where does this go?
No, don't go like that. I ain't about to sit there. CVD brain. Don't feel bad, son. You're
just bad at the game. I'm definitely older than you. I say, son. That was your fucking dad. What
the fuck? What's this? Sorry, dad. Why did I not go in? Soy cigarette brain. You guys come up with
just new terms every day. What's he today? I don't know. He's a Jolly Rancher horse manure
screamer. I'm glad I see. I see one true in there and it makes me fucking happy.
It is true though. Jolly Rancher Reddit brain.
I did that one pretty cleanly. I didn't get hit by any of the meatballs. Made air. I guess you
could bring them all up here and just let them go, but I don't know if I want to do that.
No, I'll try it. I don't even want to give this attention, but no, I'm not even going to.
What the fuck? Let me out. What was it? I don't know. Maybe you'll figure it out.
It was just a dumb comment. How much money is that? Let's see if I can do it. 28,000. All right.
Let's go see if we can upgrade. What do you got? Man with dumb comment. You have nothing?
Do you ever have anything else? Two items so far the whole game? Not even like parts or anything?
It was just one $300,000 purchase there. That's it. This one's going to be really hard.
This is going to be the second hardest. It's $10,000. I don't want to blow this.
Dude, the game can't even register you pressing it like that. I better have done it. Wait, I can
do a no. Oh no. Back to back. This one's $12,000. Oh, I didn't know that. He has a spam now.
Good enough, right? Come on. Yes. This one more isn't there. Good. Okay. Tell that Wendy's story.
One time I went to Wendy's and I got a fucking big chicken. It was good. The story's over. I
don't have any Wendy's story. Tell us the story. Tell us that story. That was a quick change. Come
on. Don't do that to me. That means it'd be another one for this, right? I'm almost a max. Oh yeah.
There's only is one more level of this. Both of them. At least I spent all my money.
Okay. Here we go. This one's not hard. It's probably going to get real hard soon here.
Whoa. Faster. Don't accidentally run off. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Describe day one with Otto. It was a wonderful thing. Picked him up. He was sitting in my lap.
He put his head in my armpit and it was the cutest thing ever. He just stuffed his head in my armpit.
He was hiding. It was like safe for him. You know, it was so cute. Like, oh, okay. You can do that.
Okay. What about clothes? This is one of our new jacket. Nerd. How is this? Is it pens?
I'll take it. Okay. There's a nerd pants. Wait, why is this nerd? Do they have knee pads?
I need more money. I'll be back. Yeah. I'm going to do the other missions.
Elbow pads too. He's being protected. That's fine.
Kill all enemies within the time limit. This is not the new Sabre though. What's the new Sabre?
Dual Welding. It's a dual welder. Okay. Let's go. Pretty cool. Bam. This corner.
It's aggro everyone. Later. I'm going to be able to do the movement. I'm going to cut all their heads
up. Somebody's health go to zero? No, zero. Peony back out.
The range of this is too small. Let's take out, let's take out a real Sabre.
Maybe I shouldn't have aggroed every enemy.
Why these guys have so much health? He's just default enemies. Holy shit.
Bring it on. I'm going to need that health.
Who has the guns? Who's just spamming? Who has the spam?
Hopefully I do this in the time limit. I have 14 seconds to kill three people.
This is the last person. What? It was the final person. I was trying to target something.
There's nothing there. It was you. Okay. Well this time I'm going to use the actual weapon
I should be using. This is the good one. Three, two, one, zero. Hi.
It's too violent. Sorry.
What's the range? It's the best item in the whole game.
It's just, I saved up. That's what we did all scream yesterday. It was me doing minigames
to make $300,000. So we did yesterday. We went for a spawn or? Oh 15. Use Rose Nasty on the boss.
Yeah, I'll use it. Just for something like this. You got to kill them quick.
How much was that for? Rose Nasty does a lot of stagger, especially if you dark step.
I'll give it a try. I'm going to use it. I'm going to put it on.
The East had a brute strength or deadly weapons or gimmicks. It subdues all enemies with the
sheer force of its will. And fighters who wield this clash, the battle is epic. They see it in
each other and form it becomes test of their souls. Yeah, it's fine. Maybe someday we'll be
the spectators of such a battle. All right. Can I, uh, there's a motorcycle fight.
This, I, I'm going to, I want the whole nerd outfit. We actually are on the motorcycles.
No, we're not. Wait. Yes, we are. Accelerate. Brake. Nitro. Steer.
How far was this gulch? So far. Holy shit. You can see the water. They weren't this high up.
Let's do this. Of course. The obvious fall joke. That's going to happen.
Unironically, a thousand times. What are we supposed to be doing? Is this a race?
Wait, this is smart. It's Mario party. It's a Mario party game where you're going to be
Yoshi. You got to like bump into people until they fall off. Right. All right. I'm ready.
What? The trigger, the event is close. I'm going to fucking watch this. He's going to
go right off the edge. It's going to be perfect. Let's go. Ready? Oh yeah. I was the best at Mario
party. Okay. Follow me. Let's do this. What's wrong? I did the nitrous mixes. You can't turn
very well. It's not funny. You're right. That's not funny. It's not. Look at how huge of a turn
that is. Did I get him? Okay. Here we go. Almost. Hold on. Let's do this. You're making this fight
so lame. Back the fucking car up, dude. He's got a fucking wall. That's not fair. Wait.
Hey, that turn. What the fuck? They've made this in dreams.
You don't drift with a back tire and then fly forward. I'm going right in. Let me just go.
And then get him to turn this way. Oh, come on. I just road-runnered him and it didn't work.
Try to leave? Can you? Can I? Okay. Can I leave? Can I? Nope. I can't.
It's payback time. Okay.
You're not getting trouble from that. He's invulnerable. Don't drive off.
That's what I'm talking about. Back in the action. It feels like it should be at times two speed.
That's seven times. Let's get minus two. I'm not.
I'm using Nitro. I'm holding Z. Let's do this. Veto this game. No, I can't. No.
I can hit him when he's revving. No, I can't. Watch. Hey. Turn. Turn. Turn all the way. Turn.
Oh, okay. Not even fair. Not even fair. I can't. It's payback time.
Okay. How many? I don't know. Nine. I have to gift sub-server. No, that doesn't work. Come on.
Hey. It hurts a lot. I can't even do this. Let's go. It's hard to control. I could give you every
excuse in the book. It's fucking weird, man. I don't know what's going on. Half this game is
just weird shit that they threw it for some reason. This is it. I'm going to get it right here. I just
won. Oh, actual phase is real fire. That's fine. That's a cool saber. If I die, do I have to restart
at the... You see? Oh, I dodged it too. That was so much greed. Not even funny. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
Charge. I'm almost out of battery. All right. Battery time. How far does it go?
Time out. We got him. I should try to dark step that, shouldn't I? That would be sick if I did.
Nope. Whoa. Do I run from that? It's still out. Shit. She's low. Oh, fuck. Here comes that snake
thing. He's just out of reach. Give me this weapon. Give me this thing. Thanks for letting me close.
I don't understand how dark step works. Jesus. Battery. Doing it twice in a row.
Damn it. Come on. Oh, my. You have to do this three times in a row. You mother fucker.
No. Bring back the peony. It's decisive. Look at the boxes. Just give me... Please pick it up.
Dude, I don't think the camera's been facing the right direction since like three days ago.
Do it. Easy. Don't stop. Stop. Stop. Come here. Oh, more. More. More. More. More. Give me more.
More. More. More. Oh, no. He's getting careless. Oh, shit. I'm getting so careless.
Damn it. Oh, I got so careless. This battery in this. Oh, god. This is bad.
Hey, we're good.
I win. I'm trying to skid. No more QTEs.
Oh, my.
Why you beat him? He had nothing left. I know that. Jesus. That was fucked up.
This is not some Pewee Karate tournament, Travis. You do not say bow and go home. You are an assassin.
And killing is how you win. But I thought what? He fought honorably so he'd work a little bit.
So he can come back stronger and cut you in half. You are developing a bad habit.
First, that dumb schoolgirl. Oh, yeah. I'm supposed to pee. Just finish the job,
or we will do it for you. These fights are not a sport. Shit. All right. It's pee time.
I'll be back in two minutes. Unless there's no cut scene. All right. I'll be back after you get
to see this part. I mean, this part. Start the clock. Yeah, that'll take me two minutes.
Get back. Flush first.
Is this guy still in the bed?
What the hell?
Your thoughts? Well, you gave them to me. That doesn't make any sense.
I was hoping you'd wander around some more. Explore. Yes, you. You did not want to go back.
So you reached out to my consciousness instead. Now we are one. Let's go.
Got you fourth. Away with you. I said be gone. You should stay here forever. No way.
We live together. I'll never leave. I'm going back. If you want to go, no choice.
Why don't you come with me? You like it. I have a weapon. I know you're trying to trick me.
Congrats, Jerma. You now have to fight Ayaya. Oh, yeah. He's got the Kylo Ren saber.
Attack. Dash. Hold A, then release for long range.
This is the Bloodborne character? That's a dash. I like it already.
If you don't... Oh, beam. Oh, I missed.
Whoa, I can't even... Where's the beam? I just got... Oh, I got slapped. Oh, come on.
Is there health in a dream? Get in there and slash. What happened? What, I have like a magician ball?
Wait, how many... Whoa, this move is good. He's Sony. I'm probably just scared so much.
That was like you just dropped food on the ground and like an animal went to go get it.
Like, no, no, no, hey, hey. Wait, wait, stop, stop, stop, stop. No, I'm not. What am I chewing?
I'm not chewing anything. I'm getting way too greedy with this bullshit.
Go back to the tried and true arcade missile. Okay, now we have to fight. No, we don't.
All right, going for the kill. Don't chew tobacco. That was not a...
That was like a knight. Oh, that was a knight. That was very clearly a...
Like, I'm a knight and I have a big suit of armor on.
A tournament. That was not what you think it is.
Are you the one who rescued me? I had a fight to win. You were just collateral damage.
Watching the video. So get out when you can manage it.
Until then, I've got some good shit on video.
We'll see about that. I'm watching.
Close my door. I'm watching anime. That's when your mom walks in.
Forgive your big brother who's too much of a shitebag to thank you face to face.
You're the big brother? How do you know I didn't pop out first?
And the point is, there's no honor in getting rescued by my younger, big brother.
So I took it upon myself to proper kill Scott Gardner, Greg Cantrell, and Massimo Bellini.
You've gotta be kidding me. Would you fucking people stop stealing my kills?
This makes us even. As far as the rescue goes, you and I still have a score to box off.
That's another subject entirely.
K-K-S-ing.
Damn it. Irish ass. He could at least have told me more about those assassins.
And in case you were wondering, I took pictures of the three skankers as souvenirs.
How long is this message?
I feel like I could do it. When I do an accent like this, you guys scream at me.
Please come out and I'll sleep.
I'd probably make good wallpaper for you.
I'm fine. Well, I've got a lot of things to say. I'll hang up now.
Long message, isn't it?
Good boy.
You're Irish, though.
Um, gotcha.
Why would I speak with an Irish accent if my ancestors are from Ireland?
I'm not from there.
I was born, like, what?
Dude, this dude's Irish. He can't even do a fucking Irish accent.
Ha ha, is that even possible?
Freddie Dredd.
Freddie Dredd saved $200.
When did you do this? Like two minutes ago?
Holy shit.
That's $220,000 of this.
That's $200 bucks, Freddie.
Freddie, you showered me with money.
It's a lot. Thank you, dude.
And they say it was a very clear night.
Uh-huh. See? Thank you.
Just like how every time I go, ay-yai-yai.
Or like, ay-yai-yai-yai.
It's not like, oh, he's doing that thing. I hate him.
Burn him.
Punch him.
I go like, ay-yai-yai.
I don't have any money.
But Freddie, thanks for the ridiculous amount of money.
Cat, cat. I don't have any money for the cat either.
I need to do side jobs.
Which one is it going to be?
And which one do I want to do?
Coconut Grabber.
Don't play the minigames?
I'm not playing the minigames for fun.
I'm playing the minigames because I want to make money.
I'm not just, like, going to the arcade.
I thought about having fun right now.
It's about how much money can I make?
And look, the dollar signs are going up.
Four.
Oh, I didn't save it.
Oh, you motherfucker.
My fucking finger slipped.
It still worked.
Let's catch it.
And this one's going to explode.
I like this one, though.
This one's fun.
Really?
Got it!
How much time?
Pow.
Pow!
I'm trying to get...
I got 20,000.
I want to see the speedrun for this shit.
It's probably so ridiculous.
That didn't go in.
Come on.
Get in the basket.
I got it.
Okay.
The scorpion was freaking me out.
Faster.
Damn it!
I can't do it.
I tried to get it.
It's redeemed the German Wink.
Oh, shit.
They're almost at 15.
What do I do?
One more bullet.
They got it.
15 out of 15.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, man.
Okay.
I didn't think you guys are going to do that.
You surprise me every day.
I've got to give you your reward.
See that shit?
And go.
Oh.
Out of my way.
Nice.
All right.
What did you guys want me to wink?
Oh, my webcam's not plugged in.
It's not plugged in.
And if I plug it in,
it might break the computer.
That sounds like a lie.
I know.
I know that sounds like the worst lie you've ever heard in your life.
If I can assure you,
if I will break my computer,
if I plug this in,
send a picture to us.
I could do that.
I think I might be able to do that.
I got to get this.
This is $14,000.
I got to get this right.
This is the hard one.
The hardest one in the game.
Got to be it.
It's got to be it.
That's got to be it.
Don't ever doubt me ever again.
That's the last attack power upgrade.
And then we've got the final stamina upgrade.
Wink.
Hold on.
You know, I'm going to be here for another couple hours.
You know that, right?
At least.
I'll be here.
I can do it soon.
You know, I could do it on July 30th.
The next wink will be on July 30th, probably.
Kind of plan this stuff out.
Good job.
Time for the mission to begin.
I did want to get the nerd pants, though, didn't I?
Cat.
Oh, yeah.
I'll get the cat.
What do you get for putting the cat back in shape?
A healthy cat.
Gene.
Good jump.
Let go.
I need a bigger one than that.
Gene.
Yeah.
That was a big one.
That's the biggest one so far.
0.4 pounds.
Stretch.
Enormous weight loss.
You're lifting with your back.
Looks like it.
And our big chunky.
12 pounds.
I'm going for record.
The whistle sounds like someone's trying to stop me.
Like, get my attention.
Like I stepped out of bounds or something.
I'm like, come here.
There's a soccer ref back there.
Being like, that's a foul.
That's a foul.
You know, I don't have enough cards for this.
Premium.
All right.
11.6 pounds.
That's good, right?
I don't want the cat to be too thin.
Wait, I have to look at the shelf to learn these?
Belly to back waist.
Well, I got a lot of moves to learn.
Finally noticed.
Put the cat to negative 25.
I don't know if that makes any sense.
We got a whole game of moves here.
Damn, I really didn't do any of these.
Shown weight to the cat is extra weight that you need to remove,
not the weight of the actual cat.
What?
So you tell me this cat was supposed to be 40 pounds?
45 pounds?
I don't think that's true.
All right, let's save this.
You have to get the cat under 10 pounds.
Okay, do the mission.
8 to 10 pounds is average.
Cat should decide their lifestyle.
Rank four.
Herd pants?
I will after this mission.
Take a seat.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Another rule change?
No, it's about Henry.
I want to clear the air.
Why?
We are divorced now, you know?
I don't remember Snake on those things.
I don't want to hear any of that shit.
The last time when you and Henry fought each other?
Snake was the only game that we could play on our old cell phones.
It was a huge deal who had the best Snake account.
Shoes.
Have.
So what?
You want revenge, right?
Your opponents could not care less about that.
Once I'm number one, these bullshit ranking fights are over.
Got it?
Assassins aren't tools.
As fucked up as we might be.
We're humans too.
Until No More Heroes 3.
Ranking battle.
It's time to go.
Need pants.
I don't deserve the nerd pants until I can be a nerd.
I can beat this without any problems and without any huffing and puffing.
What I mean by that is...
I don't even understand.
What is this?
What the fuck?
This is dumb.
This is stupid.
None of that.
No huffing and puffing.
I don't deserve the nerd pants.
Out of my way.
Get out of my way.
Coming out.
I wanna do a new wrestling move.
For you.
Oh
He was queuing it up
Awesome. This is the best weapon. Why would I take this off? I spent good money on this. Why would I ever remove it?
All right guys who's gonna gun gun guys gotta go you got a gun you gotta go
Oh
Then we get to collect all the trinkets only a few more
That's an instant kill it's so good
There it is no more enemies
30 minutes. Oh, I don't
Know
Rejectile you aim it at Travis
No, this is literally 30 minutes long
I need to get some of these presents
I
Not right now
Old cheese cold cheese cold cheese
Cold cheese, they probably heat it up. They probably I never had one. They discontinued that shit before I got to be
All right, is this a hold on a second I can leave I
Can't you weren't kidding
Yeah quickly
There's no frozen cheese on a mckee LP it was just perfect time to
Then
These cars are still having people come out this fucking clown car scenario here
I know this definitely a tube in the middle of this car
and it goes underground and this
Like 500 people down on the ground, it's not all in this car
Still going
Change my weapon Wow, why I'm clearing
Okay, how many more are there German don't reset the level
Don't reset don't reset don't reset
Levels glitch don't stop don't listen to them
But wait, I don't know what to believe don't listen
It's not bug it really does take this long
I'll try another I'm gonna go back to one of my other weapons. I know you
What should I do I'm gonna give these I want to actually try the dual welding
This does feel like it shouldn't be happening
Reset start over it's common. Oh, no a mod said that this takes
All right, so just get killed
No, no, no, no, what do you mean? No, I gotta look this up
Are you are you actually fucking with me I don't know
I need okay. There's like a thousand pizzas on the ground. I'm gonna have to go get some guys
Restarts if I restart and it was a lie. I'm gonna be so sad
The guy I'm gonna open up a guide
Don't reset I like
I
Just got hit by the fucking car
Okay, I think it's I think it's fucked up. I did now I think it is
Now I know I I think it's messed up now. I think it's screwed up. I
Think it's messed up. It's been too long. There's no way this would be this long
I'm starting
You're gonna have to do this again
No, it's no way
This no ways. Yeah, I know I agree
No, not yes way this no way is that
This is not the way it's supposed to be
It's bugged. I believe it now
No, it's not this just got spawned over here. Oh
My god, I was gonna turn it off. I was gonna reset it. It's shocking to me that that's not
That's shocking to me that this is real. I
Was about to reset the game. I was gonna let him just beat the shit out of me and start it over and do it
All over again you guys so many of you
We're so corrected and so many of you. We're just
gas lighters, oh
Can't believe it. I don't want to do that again. So I want to save it somewhere. Okay, I
Have a question was this made to make you go. Hello. That was too long and
What was that? Is that like supposed to be like that?
Making fun of consumerism. Oh, yeah. No, that's what I thought too
like the over consumption of
Yes, I thought too. I
Get it
other people don't
We do
Reset it's not too late. It's still glitched my favorite comment. I think of the whole night. Oh
Shit, dude, you're right. I should probably get out of it or it's too late. Oh
The combos just keep going. Are we fighting a guy with a peony burn this song up? Okay
There you go
Be one with your force people happy
Get through there
You're bringing a left
Down
That stays up
Everybody just died there
There's a treasure chest over here pain killer collection number seven
Fred whoa
That one cool
It was like a real opening to narrow go
This is what it sounds like
Got the gun
That's exactly exactly what I wanted. That's great
I mean some tiger roar. There it is
One with your force
The world like
How is it
Educatingly, what how is this hurry music?
Going to hear theory
one guy
What's that one guy's theory?
$50 5,000 bits from killer crock-mire. Thanks a lot
5,000 bits
Fuck
Thank you people just give that to me
Thank you regardless
And they say we better see Travis strikes back on steam. Wait a minute. Isn't it Travis strikes again?
It's the suit of love later game and it's the perfect master fun and weird that makes for a good screen game
Also, get your god hands out Jack
Yeah, I was like
Landis play it when but hopefully soon. All right, we got we got the music that was cool
Get this back to normal. You promised a new game today. I
Don't know what stream you watched yesterday
Wait, is this the TF2 thing again? I thought it was Cinco de Mayo. We're that way today is Cinco de Mayo for the pretend
Thing that people were making up
Yeah, it wasn't Cinco de Mayo like the pretend look
Let's make him let's let's make him think he's crazy enough where he said he was gonna do this on Cinco de Mayo
All right, what is this boss who's ranked number four three or whatever the hell it is
Um that moon's real close
That's just gonna crash into the planet like an asteroid. Is that what it would look like?
Holy shit imagine how terrifying that would be no I just looking up one day at night and the moon is that close
It will be funny this will be funny. All right, it's a sniper
Why do you know how when League of Legends makes a new character they do it
Strong
What it sounds like
Broken throw it at her
Can't with the part that goes reaper reaper, my name's reaper. I'm so cool and I will
How do I close the gap here
My name's reaper and I'll
Show me the people right now, you know any people have a problem because
No, it's really the last 30 seconds. Love this game and love this song. They all went like this. No, no, don't stop
Rip the fucking mute button down as hard as you can
I'm gonna wait. I'll be back in like 10 minutes
Going back to default
The drama
Watch her sure. I'd love to let's go. I did it. Oh
Getting hitter. Oh
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You can delete me. You can delete me. I'll accept
Bunker s real boy. Come here. They don't even want to do the lyrics anymore
What happened to the lyrics now, it's just a casio keyboard beat
It's already dead
All right, dude, all right hurry up and fucking log in been at the league title screen the login screen for everybody
You fucking forgot your password
Why are you doing this to me shake
Where okay, I need help now I need help now
Food
Dude community content reaper reaper music riveting melody, isn't it? Catchy as hell
Well, you deserve to win did you memorize the song of course I did 100 percent
Reaper reaper. My name's reaper
Don't stand still she's gonna shoot you her name's margaret
Three to go three more uh people that fight was bittersweet
Was it
Play devil's third. I did I did for about 30 minutes and I I took it out
Yeah, yeah, that was part of one of the uh, we fuck face nights. I played what 20 30 we games
Of course like two or three streams
Yes, i'll take care of the cat
Let's start. Let's start with some jumping
That's 151
Gene
Yeah, one more
That's a new record 10.95 genes looking good
Watching gene slick moves inspired new technique. You learn the step in slice attack
Shake the nunchuck to perform the step in slice attack. Wait, is this how you unlock dark step?
Was close
Uh premium captain stop you're gonna make her underweight
Okay, now that we do it
Close play get you happy and then we feed you premium
Hand food
Starving the cat is that too much? No, that that's okay now we feed tons of food
There we go
All done
Save it and uh, let's see if I can do any upgrades
I wanted to hit yes
And I moved left
But you have to wait until
Fully done loading. It's whatever it wants to be done loading
What was the last boss's name? Uh
Margaret I believe that's the answer. I'll get the nerd pants
There's probably something new to unlock that you guys are gonna want me to do
Be so bullyable right now
Who me?
What we done with the gym?
I feel like there's gonna be one more right get maximum or we add maximum
There is yeah, that's it I am at maximum attack power and maximum stamina
Music oh
What about Naomi?
There you go
How's that?
a little better
There ain't nothing here
No upgrades at all
only two
purchasable blades
One just three hundred thousand dollars
No weapon parts or battery parts or
All right, let's take a look at the uh closed store
All right, well how much are nerd pants
I got fifty nine thousand wait, there's this dude pants though. Hold on
No, I don't want something I can no I don't want the dude outfit
Helps
I got crocs on that's what I thought it was
Get rid of my crocs
I'm ready
Who is number three?
oh
Again with this
How do I do nitro?
Why can I go this way?
There's a jump right there. Look
There's a jump right there. You telling me I'm not supposed I can't do that
That's sad
That's how I got into the level yeah, but I
That was bad
All right. Here we go
On the other side dude, this is just like that battle toads level
Whoa, that was big
Dude, huge air
No, you can't do it. Don't even tell me I can I look you can't see it protects you
It puts bumpers on my bowling alley game. I'm supposed to be doing that
Uh pointless santa destroy is a magnet for the bizarre
There are things I still don't understand
It is a melting pot
not only of cultures and people
But even space I even have that second
You can't lose you can't die. Nothing happens. You just drive on your bike. You could have
Cut the scene to me for 10 seconds, man
Hey, all right here. We uh, it's not oh
It ain't oh
I'm gonna say that was kind of strange
I thought that was a big deer like a moose or an elk
You have to admit that was very elk-like
Oh, that was scripted. Okay
I jumped over and I still hit it. I thought that was the boss. I was like, oh this guy looks ridiculous
He's like a bubblegum guy with funny shoes on
Engage on his chest
He has like a big orbital beam what the hell I gotta fight a whole fucking space program now attack successful
Reacquire a target and eliminate enemy
All right
Right to the point on this one, huh?
I don't think I want this out. Let's try the dual welding
Summons rocks. You gotta go around them
Oh
All right, so he's like loading
You know when the you know when like grass starts getting in the way
When the wheat on the ground starts getting in the way
I think you have a small issue. Please respond
What why does he think please respond?
Oh, it's because he's I see
I think i'm taking out the big guy
Yeah, i'm taking a big guy
More damage. Let's go
I think one good hit
Don't swing more than once twice unnecessary
Do wait, i'm not out of there, but I have that move now watch it. You are so annoying
I missed
All right, i'm kind of already sick of the wall-e guy he don't give a shit
He's just like
That's a rude comment. Oh
This guy's lame as fuck
This is just like sad read receipts guy
I was at a battery
Almost there. I can let me get the super fast one. Hey, he predicted me so well right there
Not even fucking cool
I think they're
I don't know what that is, but it looks like it hurts flying around
It's an instant kill that's an instant kill move you uh
Please respond, please
Be a part of the 2020 census
Why won't you do this?
Please respond to this
Are you alive?
Do you have any friends? Do you have any family members? How big is your house?
Name your top five most influential people
god
I missed
He blocked it. He blocked it with his fucking door shield. Get the fuck out of here
Wrestling can I wrestle him? I don't think so. You're gonna catch me
Yes, you are. Oh
Sorry, he's not paying attention. He got disconnected
Don't get hit by that
Oh fuck is this this do I run?
All right. Do you just run away from that big explosion? Do I have to like dodge through it or I don't just run out
Run away
Run run run run
Run the fuck away. How far do I have to run?
That far he's doing it again
You have to do this at the absolute worst time every single time
Yes, stop
You're annoying me. You bother
I'm not gonna respond. I'm not gonna respond. Leave me alone
Oh shit
This is far enough away
It is thinking I tried to kill him
Oh
All right, this is it
Goodbye, okay
It's over captain this
This is earth
Yeah
Welcome. Holy shit. This dude is so wrinkled. It looks like a piece of wood. I'm finally back after all this time
fresh oxygen
Blue sky
Build glory to the soviet union. He's just trying to get a signal the whole time
Why did what did I what did I do?
You are now ranked third
Just leave him alone
Let him rest in peace
We must dispose of the remains its policy screw your policy. He's back with the earth after who knows how long
You're not gonna suck him up with your damn vacuum
Please respond
Oh
Guess what a response
Well, that was sad. We're coming down to the end of the road here two more battles
And I win
bat jr
I don't have time for guessing games
All the information I have
Damn you
I like the national anthem of santa distroy
It's everywhere. It's on tv. It's on the radio. It's on phone calls and shit. It's everywhere
Oh cat's done
Did everything I can do with cat
All I can see now is I can see there's any more weapons
You've heard about two of the supernatural gateways in santa destroy
The third most fitting mystery of all for a city fixated on the ranks
Sealed from the cacophony of modern life
There lived the last abstaining from all worldly indulgences
The ascetics spent every waking hour in training had become an obsession for this warrior
the end all
the raison d'etre
You know, i've never abstained from anything or in the stream. I can relate
When you're so focused on any goal it can make you do what you truly desire
Everybody said chat is cringe and then somebody said the game is cringe
All right, anything else I can do
All we need is somebody saying that i'm cringe in the middle of that and you've got the perfect
Total spectrum of what people think of the stream
No more moves, okay, that's it
So what's the point of having money now?
There's no weapons. There's no buy clothes
To all of these interesting side jobs, I guess
What's the point of doing them?
Close and Naomi Naomi hasn't had anything new
for like
Seven or six or seven in-game hours
Nothing here
I kind of miss being able to come back and buy upgrades for and new stuff
I have a store if there's going to be two items to buy
Do a revenge mission
Revenge kill the target within the time limit. I think I can maybe handle it
find out
Go get the guy with the gun
Three i'm gonna try it with this one
You got really bad body guards man, in fact big guy take it out
Oh
All right, get up get up
Where'd he go? Wait, where the fuck did he go? Oh, he's right there. He's the same guy
Jesus touch over the guy's blade. How would you even have done that?
Get over here
And it's over this shouldn't complete. Hey, we had fifty dollars five thousand bits
Fifty from goiki and goiki says chat is cringe game is cringe streamers cringe. I'm cringe
Is there any other cringe I should know about?
um
Probably not I think you got it covered
Great job. Jeremy me and your mother are very proud of you
Thanks
Uh that hurt
Like I just got hurt laughing at that
It's what the fuck are you talking about? I it's that's your choice to put that in there and it makes me laugh
Oh
No, he's back here
Hey, hey, what you got there? Hey, what you got there? Hey, what you got there? It's they it's I want to hear new things
Just bring it on
Are you prepared? That's better though. I like are you prepared?
Flows off the tongue better. Are you prepared? Uh, are you prepared? Uh, I love this item. It's so good
All of them I wish I could have saw what just happened that would be nice
I missed a chest. I got one right here. Don't worry
Look at this
All right, I don't know why I thought you were saying
Look at the joke that i'm making right now. Like hey look at this joke is doing
It's not very good
Get some money finally, why is he so sad?
All right, let's see
Oil addicted
Oh, no
He's addicted to cbt oil
I don't even want to know what that that I don't even know what that is
That's one of those things that you don't even want to hear those words
Because then your brain goes what wait, hold on what I guess I could no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, we don't want to think about that
Bring it on okay left right or up. Uh, why the three explanation points? I guess this is the right way
All right, bring it on oh strawberry on the short cake
Or anything nope, that's it people over here though
No
Not really actually
He's getting out of the car you can't hurt him
Oh bad spot for you to be in got them all holy shit nice
Uh, who's left
Do now you were in the car
All right, it's two more of these
Why all four of you sitting in dark cars, it's kind of odd right
I
Do a hot box in the car
All of them
It's like eight people here
Finally I get to be the tiger
forever
Come on more. Hurry quick kill as many
Open your doors
Yes
You're my what do you hot box?
I do not
I do not hot box
That's not something I don't want to do ever for any reason
I heard people
I'm sad. I killed this guy. He had a different voice line
Well, how do you smoke then, um don't have to be sitting in a parked car
To smoke or ingest what do you talk? Why do you have to be in a why do you be sitting in a car?
Sounds like some dangerous shit that I don't want to do
wrestling
The hot boxes with his farts
You're disgusting. In fact, in fact, you know what like you got you got to get timed out for like
Two minutes or something time that person out for two minutes like that was just disgusting
Like you got you come on you're disgusting me that's disgusting. I can't I just do a one minute
That is one of the most disgusting things i've ever heard
I go low really
No, not really
Of course not
I get them
See yes go like
Brains I can't get over. Oh, I want this guy died. He ain't got nothing. Nope. You ain't got nothing
Oh, I can't kill him with that last hit thing and I come with this
How do you do it?
Oh, whoa, I guess these guys were hot boxing their apartments
Yes
Dude, okay, this is gonna be disgusting
But do you guys remember it was uh, there was this movie that was
Uh, he was it was called like
Here comes john or something
Like he was like a two-year-old or something and like whatever it was
No, not bison's anymore
It was like he was reversed aging
He was like reversed aging like when he was like 30. He was like one year old or something, right?
It was accelerated egg. No, that's the curse. That's the that's the curse of benjamin button
But the same fucking movie anyways
so
So in this movie he farts into like a coffee can and like closes the lid
And it's just disgusting and then I got it like a week later somebody opens it and like it smells
Something's happened to the movie
Uh
It was gross, yeah, it's it was horrible that guy over there has a germa stomach
This dude right here when he leans back he gets like a big stomach
Not was it no
Like it's that's I get sticks out
Oh my god, it's real of course it is we think i'm liable the movie jack
You do realize that if I was lying what a dumb thing to lie about you could figure this out in 10 minutes
Hey guys, so I saw this movie jack with robin williams and he farts into a can and then somebody spells it
Oh, it's so funny. I what you all takes is you five seconds to figure out i'm a liar
Like that doesn't happen in the movie
What oh
Link i'm not watching it. I'm not why I don't want to watch it. I'm not watching them right now. You can watch it
That it
No, I've read three chainsaw guys bear from the muffins you guys know what i'm talking about
How do you block that
Fuzzy bear
On that goal is like this, okay, I think I didn't make my exit now
We have our new
Eyes scanner general, what's his name? It's not the fuzzy bear. No, there's more than one bear muppet
No, not rote the dog
It's a big huge bear
Muffins from space. He's like a main character
No, not sweetums. Although sweetums also does do that. They all do
Bobo. Yes. Thank you
We know who it is. Well
Because do this to me
You know, it's easy to make me go fucking nuts
Ready to get your ass kicked
You say you're getting tired of lettuce and tomato hamburgers in this town that don't quite make it it's almost auto queued up
You say that just once you'd like it
I want to hear a manly rip. Show us what you're made of. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Oh just just warming up
Just clear my throat. I feel it down below
Okay, all right i'm done
Yes
I told you I got the coffee can right too
Okay, we're fucking turning that off
I don't I didn't want to even wash it but I did
You guys didn't believe me. I people thought I was a liar. I have to prove it
Ruined your career
Why
That would be the funniest thing ever are you kidding me
If that's the thing that like ruins my career
Like the kids smell the fart coffee can
You'll tell that story for the next 30 years i'll never leave you what the fuck i'll be with you forever
Uh, leave him there he is
No
No, thank you super sonic speed any more chainsaw
Sonic generation
What's the actual last good sonic game? No messing around
No comedy like we're gonna we're gonna step back, you know, no more like just messing around what's actually the last good sonic game
Mania mania, okay. All right, this is wonderwall
Almost was
Yeah, this is a worker no
Yeah, perfect
Where where where where where
Should we face this great does it clean your teeth
often
I would say once or twice at least once or twice a day
Long, huh
Yeah, resident sleeper
How do you clean your teeth what do you guys use
Say that would probably be a very very bad idea if it were me I wouldn't do that
anybody else
Yeah
I use water toothpaste makes my stomach hurt. I use water toothpaste like water-based toothpaste or you use water
All toothpaste water-based toothpaste
Every time I see the word based based based on what
Why do you guys do that?
Do you swallow too much toothpaste? Well, the goal is not to swallow any toothpaste
How much toothpaste are you using
Imagine using half a tube of toothpaste every time you brush your teeth
How much toothpaste is in what is one serving?
Uh, it's a one pea-sized amount, right?
Do like a little a little dollop
That's not me trying to be funny that's actually supposed to use pea-sized
We're ready for the second rank battle now, this was a long one you're thinking of thermal paste
Do you chase your toothpaste?
um
I don't I spit it out
I hate using mouthwash. I really do
It sucks you put it in there and then you just want to get it out as soon as possible
Swish it around you're like I can take this it's not bad. It's been 10 seconds
I'm good
And then and then that's when it starts to really like your brain just starts to scream at you that it hurts
And then you just go now. I don't care spit it up. It hurts a good. It's not a good hurt
it's a
It's like I ate too many sour candies hurt like
I hate it. I hate that feeling travis touchdown, correct?
Yeah, that's me the no more hero
how unfortunate
Right when I am about to reach the top you have to find me
I was hoping we'd fight after I became number one
Sorry to crush your dreams
I hate to do it, but i've got business with that son of a bitch
And I can't let you get to him first
Please don't think of me as a nuisance
But I will make sure your victory isn't easy. It's me the no more heroes to desperate struggle
I've seen a lot in my journey up the ranks an endless cycle of violence now broadcast as a spectator
Everybody else get a shitload of anxiety when popcorn pops like this in the microwave
If we are all going to end up I feel like it's gonna explode every time does it really matter why
To me it does
It matters more than anything
We've all become trapped. Don't you see?
Addicted to the violence to a life in the shadows
Once we join the ranks we can never get out
Don't be stupid if you get tired of the battles just fucking quit
But that's why we all want to fight you to learn your secret. Don't you get it?
Three hundred thousand dollars at naomi. You are the crownless king. They only sell one product
You reach the top can't miss it walked away. Well, i'm back now aren't I?
You are no more heroes show me your passion release me from this cycle free us all in a crimson sea
You asked for it bring it on
And negotiate don't move shit he said the fucking thing
All right, the guy floating around his face was a little a guy floating around his face
It's gonna be better than a fighter lady
For you too
Wouldn't even be at a couple zeros
Those
Yeah, the guy's just looking to fucking get out of read receipts and one of the good cell phone signal is better than you
at full power
Ah shit shouldn't talk shit
Good parry here
I don't know. I think she's fell
All right, I need to charge
Oh
Get down from there
All right. Now she's just corner camping. She's just camping in the corner
She's got like a good item and she's just sitting there. Oh, I can't move
What are you doing stuck in the same move?
Holy shit lady
Your level was really long and this boss fight is just over
Oh, it's just going through the wall
Just going through the wall shit's going through the fuck
Okay, get the hell out of here frank too, by the way
You know nothing happened. We were in the middle of a big fight
And I she got hit in the head way too hard
Right off the bat and it was just slowing her down. It was just over if she couldn't she was all fucked up
Everything I hoped for
Don't matter how good you are you get like big fucking knock on the noggin was an assassin named alice. I won't forget
Number two boy number one
You are now officially ranked second
See that
Now that was a battle
Look at this blood. We humans are alive even if we are assassins
Doesn't matter if it's a video game movie drama anime manga. We're alive
People shed blood and die
This isn't a game
You can't just selfishly use death as your tool. Oh my god. Relax. Okay, you can have a han solo figurine
Sorry, I brought it up
Are you done bitching you could never shut down the association
Fighting to be the best is human nature. It's evolution
Who are we to try and stand in its way? Fuck that
I want to be a hero by my own standards. You need to wake up travis. Take your own goddamn advice
Alice moonlight
Who's number one?
10 hours and 20 minutes
Shave off about 25 of that though
That was spent
Um, that was spent doing the cvd tile game. It's me
Are you ready for your last battle to the death? Yeah
You know where to go
It's close by
Hold on
Someone's at the door
It's my first time here, isn't it?
We fight her a vip just showed up talk to you soon
Sure
Sylvia, I can't figure you out
You don't like me. I didn't say that
But there's a lot of things about you. I don't get
You lie
You're greedy
You're a fucking contradiction in heels. This always freaks me out. You hate me
Well, your personality kind of sucks like this is extra radiation. So you do hate me
I'm crazy about you
What do you mean?
Fuck if I know
You
Earthquake hang on to something
Okay
Play I can't play with the cat anymore. I've exceeded all cat stuff. I want to say I perhaps laughed
Do it anyways, you want to pretend to play with the cat anybody else feel like these these clothes smell like an attic?
That's a shirt you get out of the attic
And it stinks like mothballs and mildew and shit. It's very clearly an attic shirt
All right ranking battle number one, what about Naomi's lab are you gonna give me anything else to buy before the game ends?
It's only two weapons you can buy
No more gym legitimate business
I'm going for it. Let's go
But I unlocked a new jacket
to revenge
Angsten no jacket. I really want no jacket on though
Yo
Dude I don't have that
Whoa
Do revenge I'll go do a revenge
Please wear better clothes. I'm begging you
There are seven revenge missions
Your outfit fucking sucks. Whatever
One action
10 people need to die
Just get it going already
Yeah, I could just hit it at lightning speed
Seven dead eight
There's nine ten
Thank god hand
I told you july 30th
This would be another one revenge six
Under the overpass play it now. No, i'm playing on july 30th kill the target
By july 30th three, I don't know
By any date
I tried to turn them try to turn the tiger thing on it didn't hurt
Oh
Get him he's right there
I had it finally had if I was able to activate the tiger, but it didn't work
Oh
Tell me there's 20 people standing around me in a circle and not one of them gets hit by that
It's the pizza it's the pizza it's the pizza it's over here pizza, this is probably pizza
What the fuck am I supposed to say about that is the other sword I like the sword
I
I'm gonna wrap it on the side. All right, ready? I'm gonna be able to wipe out
All right. Fine. I will use i'll use the default one
I like this one
Who's driving in here?
Go
Well, that guy was ready to blow up that guy his blood pressure was like 600 over like 500
That wasn't even my fault
Oh
Okay, so this one more mission
He isn't using rose nasty despite us. I'll use it. No
I will do this next revenge mission with rose nasty
I 100 promise you
That on july 30th, we'll open this game up and complete this mission
with the rose nasty
kill everybody
Give me the rose nasty
And that was fun these things more often you actually get me with that no, I want to switch weapon
Kill
This is a no head zone kill them both really activate activate it come on finish
Very cool
That is
There's another one
mission eight
From a Pluto. I'm sorry. I lied to you
Did you actually lie?
Was there probably 10?
kill the target
Three you're just trying to pad the stream to make the stream longer. Aren't you?
You know, i'm not supposed to be sitting here for more than
You know that i'm only supposed to be here for six hours
That face when you forget about boomer brace
That's eight
There's another one
Okay comes number nine
I just swore there was seven
Just definitely ten
so all enemies
Three two one
Yes
Yes, yes two more just these two fat guys, holy shit, I killed again one hit
This thing is awesome
So good
This is the last mission coming up
Using the slash move. Yeah, i'm doing the weemo shake
With a nunchuck shake
I'm probably making a lot of money
That means I can buy a bunch of clothes
Mission 10
Hey killed the target within the time limit
Three two one
Don't even fight anybody else that's got to be worth a lot of money, right?
How much money do I even have I haven't even looked
Uh, what was that obtained? No jacket
There you go
I did it
Now we need our final part of the game
outfit
Is it no pants too
Have to do it at the hotel
All right. How about like bell box? I don't um, where's my money 5,800
I just did like a bunch of revenge missions
What?
I gotta make a little bit money
All right. Let me make let me make some money real quick
No, i'm gonna do the meat one
This one's the easiest one to understand
Because I like this song the best
Just listen to it
Well, it takes forever
Medium yeah, here you go. Don't puke
Here's a game called, uh river city ransom
This just reminds me of river city ransom. You would go to this shop. There'd be like a bakery or like a coffee shop
And you'd sit down
And eat food for health and bonuses
You pick up the whole plate and eat the whole plate or you'd eat the cup too if you were buying a cup of tea
They would put the cup of tea in their mouth and crunch it down and eat it
I wonder if that game still holds up
Does that game hold up anybody? No
Jeremy you got good at the steak minigame, uh just to match the picture played on switch
Perfect
Perfect give me the easy ones. Thanks a lot
This is all for the final outfit. We have to make sure we get it correct 24 000. All right, this is it
Perfect
Yeah, you lay the pipe I don't need to
Well, this would be enough money this would be more than enough money
It's very delicious is in a row
Perfect enjoy it. That was a little under all right
It's a little over
Well, not
It's gonna be a lot of money
Okay, now we can go get our clothes succeeded in making about 70 or 80 thousand dollars it's a big payday
54 000 bucks
All right, let's go get the hotel say goodbye to the cat take the jacket off
And then take off the shirt too. Wait, I can just be the graphic tea guy that I wanted to be right?
Perfect take the pants off. Yeah
You can't
Like when you're at the convention and you have a big costume
And after two or three hours of walking around in the big top part that has a bunch of foam and shit
You probably get so this is like i'll walk around in the bottom half. That's fine in my t-shirt
I don't need anything spectacular up here
pursuit
Any suit I anything any
Like it could be a mascot
It should be a guy at disneyworld for all that fucking matters
Cat you idiot
Okay, bye cat. Good. You saw the extent of what I could play with the cat fine
I'll make it a little bit more hard more heartfelt
Bye gene back to suplex
Watch the anime one more time
I mean just the first part the intro part
giant swing kick ass
giant swing learn giant swing
We're gonna get a big dlt
Okay, that's cool. I guess
Howard naomi has new stuff. He's sure
You guys like it that
I treat that anime intro thing the same way that I treat watching ads on youtube
I've seen the same
Bizarre jerry ad on youtube just skip it in five seconds. I'm done. I don't want to see it anymore
You ain't got nothing new stop lying to me
You know the reason why they keep telling you to go see her
I'm not going to address it
Get the final outfit. Okay shirt
It's important
I I kind of like that
go out
space age
b
r m i
u
It could be hold on
A lot. I like the lime shirt
Why what's this weird? Look at that thing. I want that
Peter light my fire
Mmm
Joker dancing cats. That's pretty good. Oh, I don't know
Okay
Why is this $60,000?
I like these ones
Belt new belt i'll take it
It was so expensive
How about these?
How about these how about yeah, I like these I don't have enough money for all of it
How much are those pants I want these
i'll take it
Oh, this is what this is it I ain't gonna go do any more money games
Okay. All right. How about this if I can if I can do the tetris tile in 60 seconds?
and
I I win I guess okay 60. Give me a second one minute if I can do it in one minute. I win
Here we go
So
I win
Okay, double another another 60 seconds double what I get here we go
Okay
Let's go play the hyper dimension series on july 30th fine. I don't remember anything. It'll be a busy day on july 30
Are you expecting?
Why do you listen?
Well, it doesn't matter really expected to know anybody even on that phone you came here almost every day
Paid to hear me ramble that gave me as much happiness as I can hope for
There's nothing left to lose
Every day as joyless as the one before it
Eyes closed continue to endure. Why does the stream have the exact same camera angles when I come back?
after a while of not watching
Uh, because it's like a 20 chance. There's gonna be a close-up
Of a girl's chest on this game. Let me hear what you sound like as your dress
Shut up
And it matches me look
I mean, no, it doesn't i'm my it's matching my belt matches
Well, we don't even see it and it's fine
Keep going more spawns
I want to make this happen
Fast dead rising. It's gonna look like dead rising. You're right
How much of the new uh special move
Special delivery this model hot topic
Are they all
I mean no
Are you gonna make the steak of
When I could show you guys my secret steak of trust, but I don't know if anybody wants to see that
I need to do a steak of live stream. Maybe I will
Maybe I will maybe i'll do maybe i'll make some my world famous fucking steak and sandwiches
Did you do this what are you gonna do on july 30th?
Oh, I don't know what july 30th maybe
Let's see if we got anything else going on. Yeah planned for like somewhere in late july
I'm, not sure if there's anything else going on that day, but i'll um
I feel like late july like july 29 30th
There's stuff going on, you know, like a new game might come out of it
Stake them with the easy bake up, uh, that will probably break and I don't want to break it
Cricket to the chainsaw guys before it runs up
This is very very painful
Wrestling I really hope the easy bake up and turns on
I really need to make sure the thing actually works
I gotta do a trial run to like heat it up a little bit before I even
Be bad
Why do I know exactly what you mean by toontown villains
Guys from the commercial
but these guys that uh
you guys have to have the um
You know, I'll just do the impression
And the goons are gonna take over toontown. They talk like that, right?
Something like that
Is it just one person back here?
There's no voice acting in toontown. I remember the commercial though. It was like a guy looked like goofy
And a pie was gone and he would like shoot pies at people's faces
The voiceover in the background talked like that. It was just like are we gonna save the toons?
You gotta get out there and make an account at toontown.org
Ask your parents permission first
I remember watching it
My mother didn't let me play it
I forgot to see what you guys were talking about. I didn't like how much how violent it was
Where's the last person?
old person
Stick to stick stick to sticks
What is that? What's that coming from?
What is that?
Game breaking bug delete the stream. No, it's just this one person hiding behind a wall
save the toons
Were there any disney characters in that game?
It was it was like goofy and donald duck and mickey and stuff
Okay, this is where we switch switch to your guy's favorite weapon
Go welding would be so bad
I feel like it would be a pain in the ass. You'd accidentally hit yourself and shit. It would be hard to
Oh, just give me a big heavy shield as in a small knife
I just want a huge steel shield that
blocks everything
and then like a paring knife like a cheese knife
and I get in close and just like
Step that step that step in the neck. I'm talking like small like a dagger little one
You mean a shield? That's what i'm saying. I just said shield
Shield with a small paring knife
You weren't always like I would do a two-handed broadsword. No, you wouldn't those things are like fucking 700 pounds. No, you wouldn't
I'd use a a double-sided katana. No, you wouldn't you'd cut your hole. You cut your legs off
No, you'd use a cheese knife with a big shield like the rest of them
You guys don't know it took it took four people to lift up a broadsword
one person to hold the the
shaft
Two people to hold that guy up by the shoulders and then a guy
And I kind of sit on in case you fall down
come here
spawn already
He's not spawned in come on
Yeah, but for most of us that are like man, I would love him. Uh, just like
It's like an old knight like king arthur. I would want a big sword like king arthur
You would pick that thing up do a huge swing with it and throw your back out and put it down and be like
Ah, never mind
You get like a muscle spasm on trying to hold it straight in the air
And then we get started on using a whip
You will swing that whip around and try to get practice it and that thing will come back and crack you in the face
And you're gonna lose the top half of your lip
What's the best weapon, uh, it's very easy take a small cheese knife
Or a spear just a long ass spear with a big pointy really light big pointy thing of the enemy
Walk and stick it for it
spear
big spear with a shield
or a big rock
No, I yeah, I know i could see that like a big stone like a big a big rock to throw at people
We'll like hit him with a headwind
Fear and shield. Yeah
That means people can't come near you and if they do they're gonna hit the shield
And this open the door, oh I have to open it
Yeah, and somebody's got it you do the thing where you you all have a shield and a spear
You stand back to back to back to back to back and you walk like a crab
Just no one will ever touch you
Phalanx phalanx formation. Yeah shit works. It was weak to fire bombs
um
We'll just update it and have like a powder guy
That has like a bunch of water and like powder and shit like jump on if there's a fire
You gotta have a weapon
Or just make a big umbrella
No, okay. Let me improve the balance
Just have a big umbrella made out of shield material that a guy in the middle holds up
So you got five you get six phalanxes that if they're out pacing out with their spears
And you've got a guy with an umbrella in the middle who walks with him who covers everybody with the steel shield umbrella
It don't matter you get arrows could hit the top of it it wouldn't matter you know walking
I mean you might not win any battles or anything. Yeah, eventually we'd have to advance and what are you gonna do?
Only one but for defensive purposes you know, we could touch it
Lose every battle. No, it's called only fight on your own home turf
Everybody does that
And everyone would be practicing the whole time and even like that like the waiters and waitresses and like the cook staff and stuff at restaurants
We're doing too
It's back to back walking backwards. We need to learn it's hard to do
What about tanks yeah, we're talking about not current we're talking about like medieval weapons stuff
Yeah, yes the solution if I had a phalanx right now, oh you what the fuck just snipe me from a mile away
Why are the shortest men the best generals
Uh, I think you're making a reference to napoleon napoleon lost 70 percent of every fighting with him
He's really good at chess
Wait wasn't uh, wouldn't napoleon like so good at what he did
They like shot him out of a cannon on an island or something and he wasn't allowed to come back
He came back and everybody was just cool with him
Why do I okay, hold on a minute i'm gonna be talking about potential
Potential spoilers for the marvel universe, especially a character that's very large and very green
So if you don't ever want to hear anybody like anything to do with the very large green person in marvel
Um, I I want to talk about some stuff that happened in the comic book and have a little comic book session
Uh, so i'm giving enough time for people to not want to listen to this
It's old but it's still you know, what if you're like in the middle of me?
I don't know what if you're in the middle of like reading marvel comics right now
I'm not about to you. You're on the i said the next page
You're on right now
Here we go
Uh, so we're gonna talk about the incredible color
On issue, whatever the fuck it is
For the uh series which was called the civil war series
Did they shoot hulk out of a cannon to like get rid of him like he's like napoleon they did the napoleon
They did this right so
Make sure I got that right
Fuck that was the next page is him getting shot out of the cannon with his hands all the way at his sides
Flying towards the camera with like a
Big speed lines behind him and the cannon in the distance with smoke. Sorry
I ruined it for you
Wait, save the game. There is no save
About oh, sorry
Is there a reason why I just have this every five seconds I like it don't get me wrong beats things up a lot
Uh
What the hell are you you talk too much
Live stream broadcast
Here just stop talking on this live broadcast with a mic in your face. I just want to hear
Your
No commentary playthrough it was less than you watched one of those
From my understanding everybody skips those fucking videos, please tell me more about the data that you have
Next panel urban at 85 firing out of cannon what the fuck hands down by side
screaming into the camera
All the way down zoomed out all the way
Shooter with chat on it laughing
Chat controls the cannon
Yeah
That works too
You talked about the switch does surgery on somebody right the thing that I didn't know if I could do it or not
Where like I am on camera
And I'm like, okay guys I'm looking forward to it you gotta do surgery on
Like I swallowed like a toy car
You guys have to get yeah, I swallowed a toy car
Don't ask me how but I did it just was in my food
You guys have to get the toy car out by doing surgery and I lie down and the camera cuts for a second
It comes back and it's like a
Like a dummy lying there
You guys have access to like a scalpel with like pair of scissors and shit to like get in and it's all
I don't I didn't know if I could do this or not
because
I it would be you could like go in there and it'd be like fucking meat and
Goo and shit you'd have to find the car
And when you were done and you like sealed me up
I just you know, the camera cut away for a second. I got out of the bed and I was like, oh man
I feel pretty good. Nice job jet
IRL surgeon simulator
I say I swallowed a toy car you guys like take the saw up to my head
hire like three
Like actor doctors to be like us to doctor. Are you sure you want to do that?
Hold on. Let me well, the car is in there doctor
Went backwards shit actor doctors
Doctor you supposed this is we're supposed to be going into his stomach to find the toy car
Are you sure you want to be up there on his on his head?
You're going down to his feet
You don't need okay. You don't need to take off his
I feel like there's something I probably couldn't do this some, you know, I feel like
Hey, here we are
final
confrontation
Eat the wheel
The groomer
Did you honestly think you could take so many lives and never suffer retribution have you never even seen a kung-fu movie spy flicker western
I used to have that outfit. I'm glad I didn't walk in here with the same outfit
Not only did you murder my father my two brothers as well
That is why I took your best friend's life
Makes sense travis. It's called poetic justice
Go to hell
Don't ever compare bishop with your shit head family
So naive travis is the shark tanker room
You will lose them eventually
See for yourself
Oh my goodness
Now you're feeling it. That's your life losing all meaning you've got nothing left except this fight
Now I know you'll put all you have into this fake. Yeah, those are cakes. You're gonna fucking very highly detailed cakes
Yes
A fight to the death get angry
So angry you start convulsing
Now draw your katana
I'll relish every moment every second of this kill
May you savor your death as well?
Begin
Our kid
I can't hit him. All right. Uh, there he goes. He did that
Can I pick can I suplex him out of the car?
So you gotta have that beam hit him
Really is the brumer?
All right, hit him. I'll wait for it
All right fire that laser out fire the laser at him fire fire
Damn it
What the fuck yeah, what the fuck
Does that love is that a hundred subs from freddy?
Holy shit
Freddy gave a hundred that's bullshit. I'm sitting here spamming
Wait, it's supposed to happen
Ready to give a hundred community subs
Yeah, so he's not dead
Don't be deceived so easily. They're just replicas
serious
Geez, well, aren't I a gullible idiot?
These are thanks so much freddy
Think I can take one of these home after you kill him. Why not? I'll handle his ring piece goons
Thanks, bro
Oh, I wasn't in the right spot. Is there a uh, i've been waiting for that
Spin spin spin spin spin
Out of battery
Is there any uh healing anywhere over here? I didn't see any
Her box. Yes, there is
What is he doing over there?
Go
No has just begun. Oh, of course he did the injection thing
You gotta be shitting me
This is a fight to the death. Sure it is. Okay
I've locked
That hurt with uh with my friend
Here we go
Dodge move i'm gonna do it the spin finally
Phase two. Oh fuck. I'm almost out of battery
Whoa watch out for that grab. No, I'm trying to get away from it. It's a huge
Oh, that's not that's the name of them as hell. I'm fine
Break down for no reason
That's what i'm talking about back in the action
This is a fight to the death
Fuck you don't get in the window swing can I can I throw him out the window cheater battery
What the fuck just happened
All right get him out throw him out of the window
Do I get help
Back to the window. I mean no back facing
I need that help. Give me that fucking pizza, please
Give it holy shit. Thank god. I wasn't facing a window. Is he bigger?
Damn it
Dude I can't even tell if i'm dodging
Why does the camera keep going back into this fucking corner?
Where the fuck am I?
Oh god, let's do this
This is a fight to the death
Remember this th 20 hot don't go out the window
Get rid of him out the window do it. He's closing up. Don't have me go out the window. That would be bad
Oh, he's right here
Get out of my face
Okay, now we do it again we're not even close
Have us have the tiger bring it on. I have the tiger in two seconds
I have the tiger turn it on quick
I was spamming it
Through the window
No, not yet now that's hideous is even bigger pull the craziest shit
Elmer Fudd
We almost got him. I think that was an episode where elmer fudd did the superhero thing. Wait a second
You're already here might as well keep fighting. It's not happening brother for the lego building
Suit yourself
Now i'm gonna get my revenge once and for all
Come on prez unleash your hate your anger everything i'll take it all and fucking kill you with it
Oh my god
I don't
How do I hit him you gotta hit him right in the stomach
I feel like this is one of those
Let's get a really great angle in our indie fighting film because we don't know how to hit each other
So let's just have crazy fucked up angles
We have no training at all
Is he dead my computer
Oh hit him with the nose. Oh, he's oh hit right in his big nose
Is this supposed to be happening? Is this how you beat this guy?
Holy shit, okay
Yeah
It's lice
Fast for bat jr is dead. Yeah, you still hit the ground nice catch
Now that's paradise
No more heroes too in the bag there are secret boss in this one it might be
I think we're off to the end of the credits. You're gonna play the third game when it comes out. Oh, absolutely
That was the reason to play these this year was because I
Knew that the third one was coming out
I'll play the travis strikes again, too
Let's see how far I get in it. That's a long game though, isn't it? It's much longer than these first two, isn't it?
we'll see
When i'm playing it is the third game going to be on steam. I think it's going to be on switch
exclusively
Right. Yep
Switch is gonna overheat
Nintendo actually funded it
Well, that's good to hear
But uh, we did it. It's over
So that means you know what that means
That means tomorrow we're going to play president evil 3 remake. I'm gonna try to beat that tomorrow
then
Honey tunes wacky sports adventure on thursday
Which speed order?
Oh
No, I think that's a good order
That's a good order. I want tiny tunes tomorrow. No, we're doing tiny things on thursday
and probably uh
Another secret game for the super nintendo
No, not tomorrow. I mean thursday these credits are in the game. They're not pre-rendered
Please play donkey kong country 2
Uh, I played donkey kong country 1 pretty recently on my own time
last year
And I rage quit
at the
I didn't believe it was turn the lights off turn the lights on level
Died like seven or eight times and I was like nah fuck this game. I'm done
Oh, that's deep. That's deep in the game. That's level
That's level probably like 18
doom eventually to yeah
All right. Come on. What's the secret cut scene?
There we go
Yeah, that wasn't a after credits cut scene
Oh, never mind finally here she is
Sylvia
I was looking for you
When I just on our bike
Yeah, it's real. Let's go home santa destroy needs us
That's fun
Rank one
11 hours and 52 minutes 11 hours and 10 minutes a lot of that was
ted talk
It's ted talk sound
Oh, it's okay
But let's let's just ready i'm gonna put it on hard see what happens let's see what it looks like
Well, that's it. I'll see you tomorrow
for resident evil 3 remake
i've heard
Things about it. I'm gonna make my own opinion on it. I've heard it's very short
I've heard it's not as good as the second one remake. I've heard it's
For the first time, you know, i'm going in with some muted, uh dialed back expectations
Raise yourself
Done took one hit not even the same dimension as the resident evil 2 remake
Um, yeah, but i'll play it. We'll see we'll see tomorrow. We'll see tomorrow
But we'll see tomorrow. Thanks for hanging out
I will see you guys
same time
Same place
Have a great night. We're gonna do the bits
You want to stick around you're more than welcome to
See you tomorrow. What the hell is that?
Why is that on
when I pressed outro
on my stream deck
Why is that connected to outro?
Oh because it was the first okay
That makes sense. Doesn't it? It was the image that was blown up
See you tomorrow
Let's go back and do the bits
Shouldn't take us very long
Pugles, thanks for the 300 bits. Hi
I'm looking to hire an e-clown for my son's e-birthday because of the quarantine and I heard you the best around
Could you send me your prices and i'll be in touch
Thanks, uh, jokes aside here's a let epic meme I made
Oh, I this is so this is so bad. I have to show it not that
That's that's just it's uh, it's good
That face friend
Uh happy e-birthday whoever it is
Soup gg. Thanks for the soup if you apologize
The annoying request can you say happy birthday to my brother nick?
We've both been fans since like 2013
Thanks for the years of the funniest content on youtube and twitch. I generally appreciate it. Hey, happy birthday nick
Have a good night. Hope you had a good birthday
Two back-to-back birthdays there. Happy birthday
sing for them
Thank you
Smelly boy. Thanks for 250
Hey germbo, do we still have plans for paper mario? I promise you'll like it eventually. It's not now other things going on first
Opster narwhal. Thanks for the 277
Will you play the remastered edition of spongebob battle for bikini bottom when it comes out?
Did you play the original?
It's a classic with a capital c i've never played battle for bikini bottom
I will play the remaster when it comes out. Yes, absolutely
I never played the original
Hey frito man. Thanks for the 15. Everyone asks. Where are the aliens but no one realizes they are all around us
We travel to other stars and even galaxies. We have to go beyond reaction based propulsion
and manipulate space time itself
The achievement of this feat will then allow us to travel beyond the fourth dimension
We inhibit as gravity the ultimate force in the universe travels through all dimensions
It is through reaching this that aliens will stop hiding and reveal extradimensional existence
Did you just copy and paste the top part of your paper you were doing for your project?
Because I mean it's pretty good writing so far everyone asks
Where are the aliens? That's a great opener for a school paper. Great. I would have done that. I would have done that
Open with a question open with a where the aliens i'm your teacher. I'm now you got my attention
Because then I say where are they? Yeah, they're right educate me school me nobody ever asks
How are the aliens?
No, they don't thanks to the 15 dollars. You're gonna get an a hey yoda 985. Thanks for the 260
Hey, mr. Germa, sir, if you have one, who is your favorite transformer bumblebee? See the next thing you should ask is
Name another transformer optimus prime is the only other one I can think of besides the decepticon
But I think that's a group of evil doing robots. I don't know who
The omega red is that the name of the bad one? What's the bet?
What's the bad guy's name omega lull red?
No, oh man. Hold on. No, that's a that's a x-men character. Never mind. Uh
Megatron that's right. Okay. There you go. That's my favorite. Hey bar broski. Thanks for the 300 bits
Germa, is it true you minored in art?
If so, do you have any work available for us to see i'd honestly love to watch a laid-back stream of you
Just drawing for a couple hours, even if it's just funny little doodles of your characters
Yeah, I idea and when I would go to i'm this bad
In my art classes, I didn't know the hell I was doing and every time there was a project to come in with something
This is not a joke one time. I actually did a full project in crayons
Because I was too lazy to go buy all the art supplies needed to actually do the project and actually do it for real and right
So I did it in crayons and I the best part about art
Anything can be anything anything can be anything
So I went in there after doing a full crayon picture and I I was like, yeah
I did the childlike way that I used the crayons for the medium and it was like, oh shit
What they didn't know is I just didn't buy the supplies yet because people would come up with like this really really awesome shit
Well, that's an amazing like actual detailed full person's face in charcoal. All right, mr
Elbertson, come on up. It's my picture of a house that I did in crayons. I did it on purpose
Oh, you did. Yes. Wow
Excellent work. Mr. Elbertson. Thanks. I did it hard. It was very hard people happy
But there were actually some I love forget about drawing
I can't draw and I've I've refused to try to learn because I've tried a million times
I don't have the patience for it. I have no patience for it. I'm never gonna learn and I it's okay
I like clay. I like molding. I like sculpting. I don't like to do it, but I like I I enjoy it. I enjoy
Clay because it can be mushed around and molded and you can make uh, like statues within stuff
It's cool. And yeah, the bugleberry pottery. Yes physical media crew unite just interesting to me
I like the way it feels. He's never gonna draw a manga probably not
I did I did do it and I learned a lot
There's a lot of things in art history that was interesting
I remember not enough to tell you what they were but that I remember how they interesting they were thanks to the three dollars though
Hey the dinkster, thanks for the five dollars. Haha. Jerma smells. I don't actually I smell pretty good lm man
Thanks for the 250 jerma since you like no more heroes
If you consider playing mad world a disc is right behind me that actually is is it gonna be kind of sad to say
That is one of only I think three or four more games for the wii that I have to play on this stream
The supply is running dry pickman two. No, that's for the game cube
But still I count them both because I play it in the wii mad world what else is back here?
Hold on. Let me see bad world cooking mama world kitchen
And that's it that's it for the game cuban wii era of video games that I have
And then paper mario the thousand year door. I don't have that one
I will probably that doesn't mean we're never gonna play wii ever again, but that's just what I have now
A unpronounceable offspring. Thanks for the ten dollars
Just want to say i've been watching your streams for years through youtube clips
I want to show my appreciation
Have you thought about checking out war of the monsters?
Cheers. Well, thanks for the ten dollars
Uh, I think I think we've talked about this game before this is a fighting game, right?
We've yeah, we talked about this before just have to get it
Did they remake it or something? Why am I seeing stuff from 2015?
Did they put it on psn? They did right? Okay. We'll put it on the list where the monsters was a good ps2 game
I'll give it a try. Let's roll the credits
we will see tomorrow still have a few more bits to do but
Uh, let's run the credits credits are probably gonna be much faster than they were
yesterday
considering the
Hundreds of community subs that came in today
The font looks smaller to you
The font is smaller
Getting more no
This font looks a little smaller
Thanks everybody. Thank there was
Insane sub drops today freddy dread gave a fucking hundred
So thank you freddy
And the hundreds of dollars on top of that freddy
You single-handedly freddy you single-handedly pay my bills
Like just you
Holy shit, man. I really appreciate it
That you give a lot of fucking money to this stream. I can never tell you how much I appreciate it
And how much I gotta say, thanks
Sugar
I mean like hundreds of community subs like thousands of dollars. Thanks freddy. Really appreciate it
Let freddy stream for a day
We love you fred
Where does he get the money?
Well, I mean pretty big deal
Hey, I don't know how much you guys know this
Freddy's a big fucking deal
Hey, go look him up one day. That's songs on spotify. That's how you know. He's supplying you cbt
Why did I read that?
I don't know. I was gonna say cvd
Whatever. Hey
Hey, zigzy zyx zii zigzy. Thanks for the thousand bits peony
mvp. Yes, I agree
Hey goiki. Thanks for the five community subs. That's a five dollars. That's not a five community subs
I just saw the five and I said subs
It's not what it is
It's 500 bits if you had to dress up as someone at like comic con or something
For a whole day, who would you choose to be?
Uh the stay puff marshmallow man
No one would know it was me and I just walk around and get just have a bunch of pictures taken on me and be
In a big air conditions suit
So that's exactly what it would be
All day
Yeah, I get to be in the breeze of the ac unit that's in there filling up the suit with air
Thinking face
Hey rain. Thanks for the 250 jeremy. Can you please measure your foot and show that it's 10.2 inches?
I'm not a freak. I just want to be proven right. Absolutely not
Uh, that's just that's just uh, that's a that's just a no that's an absolutely no
Um, hey just like measure just like uh, show it. Uh, hey like what what kind of sneakers do you have show them?
You know what somebody tells you show them, you know, you probably should know that it's like, uh, no, you know
Hey jeremy, can you please measure your foot and just prove that it's 10.2 inches?
I just want to know jeremy. Can you please measure your foot and show that? Oh, you want to show it?
Okay, see now I know hey, you're just mad at 10 point. What are you talking about rip alex rebec?
Thanks to the 500 bits jeremy great stream
Just want to update you on the status of the custom german 985 funko pops you commissioned from me last stream
Factories pumping them out at max speed and just the payment advance a couple weeks earlier
Also, they use a non-polar paint that causes birth defects. Can't wait to deliver them to you and all tax-free
I'm not reading the rest of this. I'm not reading the message anymore. That's what I actually believe
I actually yeah
I'm not saying that I don't want to say that like I don't want to say that
I don't want to say I like don't want to say those words. No, i'm not going to read it
They say something about them having they don't something about all right. It's the they say the irs they say
Gosh, darn it. I'm paying my taxes
And yeah, we all pay them. We all have to pay them. Welcome to life bug smoke. Thanks for the 250
A few days ago. I donated and talked about my first experiences watching your content
I wrote that I used to hate your videos before being a fan
That seemed to hit you the wrong way
I want to send this to clarify my wording before watching you
I just assume you were a typical tuber and that I would have hated your videos
Okay, that was obviously an incorrect judgment
I've liked all the content i've seen you do even the escape stream keep up the content
You mean the unlock stream? Well, that makes one of you one of us. He's a two. I'm a tuber at heart
All right, I am i'll always be a tuber, you know, yeah, that's not gonna grow out of me
I'll always be a tuber. I'm just a twitch tuber. Thanks to the 250. Glad you don't hate my videos a dream boom
Thanks for the five dollars. Thanks for streaming a series
I love did you check the extended trailer of no more heroes three?
I have by the way killer seven was also made by suda 51 and has a good remaster on steam check that out
Whenever you have the time, i'm sure the chat will love it. Keep up the great work
It's been on the list for a while
But I feel like no more heroes three will come out before I have the before I want to play
Killer seven I feel like that's gonna happen first killer seven's a stoner game. That's all right. Hey, it's boo
Thanks for the three dollars seeing you play some more suda 51 games
I'd like to see you play shadows of the damned for the playstation 3 his production team had a hand in it
Sadly, the sales weren't up to par but it was a very unique experience
And i'm sad to see not a lot of people have played what was the game that was a suda 51 game
Where at the very beginning there was this big frog boss we played it
What was the suda 51 game that we played with the weird frog thing in the beginning never dead. That's what it was
Okay, that was a marvelous entertainment game, right? That's not suda 51
Never dead is not suda 51. This is not never dead. Uh
Director no is no. Hold on. This had nothing to do with suda 51
Oh, I think I just thought it was a suda 51 game and it became fact in my brain. Oh, that's interesting
Well, yeah, i'll check it out
See you tomorrow. Have a good night. It's still two or three more bits. I just want to say good night to you right now
Convo breaker. Thanks to 250
Dear jeremiah, i'm sorry for causing you distress sometimes but I cannot hold back from jumping when all the chat is yelling at you blatant lies
And or misinformation at the same time
It's just too funny kind of like my addiction to picking food above the floor saying when in doubt radish it out and then eating it
I can't stop myself. Please help dear god. Also, I don't know how much people like jrpgs
Xenoblade chronicles is like chrono trigger
Like a chrono trigger tier jrpg in the decade
And I don't know what's real. It's hard to determine what's even real
Never played it. You know blade is a thousand hours long
You probably won't see it on this stream
There's a strong cutoff
On this channel where if a game is going to take more than 40 to 50 hours on paper
That means it's going to be one to two hundred hours on this stream
I don't think I have the
Brain to commit to that
But I will play chrono trigger because I know everything about it
Blueberry juice. Thanks for 250
No, you can't just use the peony for the entire game
uh
unga bunga orc
big pea sword oh
Boom, I respect your commitment to the strength build
Also, it's pronounced wielding not welding you illiterate stacom brained caveman
The other one that said the caveman thing
Stacom and it's fun to say too
Hey drumager. Thanks for the 250 what the fuck happened to resident evil 4 on wii. That was the stream
I was looking forward to the most july 30th
July 30th. I already said it
What happened to it july 30th? It's on my list for july 30th. I have a lot of things for july 30th
The ftk stream is also july 30th
july 30th
Pretty good
See you guys tomorrow for resident evil 3
Goodbye. Good night