Hello, good afternoon. How are you? I'm doing good. I'm doing good.
All right, I need to address something very, very quickly right off the bat. At the very beginning of this stream. I said a while back long time ago, that they would never be at sands would never be an undertale and I guaranteed it.
So now I have to eat a shoe. I don't know what kind of shoe it has to be. I just I know that I said I was going to eat a full shoe on stream if sands was confirmed and shoot he was last yesterday.
I mean smash.
It's Smash Brothers. Yeah. Oh, no, no, sands is an undertale. What a surprise that is.
And I mean like crap. Hey, Jolo. Thanks for the five community subs.
Eat a Jordan. Yeah, someone will find a clip of me saying I will eat a shoe.
Yep. But thanks for the five subs. And so the shoe eating stream will be on March 12 2020. Mark it on your calendar. I ain't gonna eat a fucking shoe on stream. Anyways, how you doing today? Yeah, so sands is from undertale is in Smash Brothers. We actually talked about this last night. And that's okay. Cool. That's really I couldn't I could never imagine.
Wow. Oh, that's pretty interesting. He is although he's a me costume. So I think that means I only have to eat 50% of the shoe. You know what I'm saying? I can cut it in half, right? You just eat a sock instead.
No, I ain't eating any clothes. Imagine like I eat a fucking shoe and I got to have to go to the doctor.
What seems to be the trouble? Jeremy? Um, well, you know, sands from undertale, right?
Oh, it's my favorite. Yeah. Let me guess. You bet that he wouldn't be in Smash. Me too. And he like shows an x-ray of his stomach and he's got a shoe in there too.
And I'm like, Doc, oh, damn, geez, what are you serious? He's like, I know, right? And I'm like, why did you eat the whole shoe? And he's looks at me. He's like, what do you mean? Why do we need to eat the whole shoe? He's a me costume.
Oh shit. And like, then he holds up my x-ray and I got a half a shoe in there. We both laugh. And then I make a lifelong friend. So I'm okay with that.
Anyways, we're gonna do more Mario RPG Legend of the seven stars. The final is the finale is gonna be the last stream of this game because we're probably gonna get to the end.
Now, this stream of Mario might be like, it might be three hours to finish this. It might be six. And I say, Oh, you're right. I do have I do have another story for you. But another another story. But I had a few dreams.
And one of them is really, really weird. And I need some I need some people in the chat to try to explain to me what the fuck this dream meant, because it is outrageous. Okay.
So I fall asleep. And my brain tends to do this thing. When I go to bed, where I if I wake up and let's let's let's back up. I gotta back way the fuck up for this. If I go to sleep for more than three or four hours, and wake up for some reason, whether it's I have to I got a pee or something or like, oh, I just kind of rolled over or you know, any reason.
I will fall back asleep, like six more times. Each one of those times that I fall back asleep, I'll wake up fall back asleep, I wake up, there is a new episode of dream TV on every single time. Number one, why does that happen? It was just boom, boom, boom, new episode TV new episode, you're changing channels.
Anyways, the first dream was terrifying. It was fucking scary as all hell. So I'm in the backyard of some I don't know where I was, some friend's house, somebody said that that that kind of detail don't matter. There was a barbecue. It was me and friends and maybe his family cool. Well, we're in the backyard, it's grills going. And in the distance above, all the way up in the sky.
If something was something was strange about the sky, I'm like, what's going on sky? Something's what you know, when you just know, in a dream that something bad is gonna happen. Nothing happened yet. I'm just like looking at the sky. Oh, something's wrong up there. No, there's not. Why do you know that? Why is your brain giving you a spoiler? Before it happens. Anyways, about five to 10 seconds later, in my dream reality, giant fucking boulders were tiny, tiny, tiny in the sky, like three, four, five, six of them at a time.
And these things have rapidly falling towards Earth. And I'm just like, those, those are really far away, but they're coming in real quick. I think I should probably run. Because those are getting bigger and bigger and bigger and bigger. If they were going like 600,000 miles per hour. And I'm just like fucking I start sprinting, sprinting to my left boulder is flying down just takes up the entire sky at this point and like crash to my right. And I like just
barely Super Mario and out of the way. Two more like blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, like asteroid fucking raining hell. More of them come. I look up I'm safe. No, I'm not. What the wall with this board like seven more like starting to come into picture. I look
forward. Otto is right in front of me. And I'm like, wait, Otto, Otto, and he starts running towards me. And I'm like, and I go to pick him up and I scoop him up and boom. Another
asteroid lands right where I just picked him up. But I'm like, we just barely got away. I'm running around with Otto like this fucking asteroids landing everywhere. I'm doing like all these jumps, like double jumps and shit to get away from them. I ended up lying on my back with Otto. And like QTE cutscene scenario, where it's like, there's one, roll left, left. There's another one roll right. Ow, my hand. There's another one roll right. I'm doing QTE is looking at the sky. It was freaking me the fuck out. I woke up.
That was weird.
Oh, everybody okay? Oh, yeah, I guess. Yeah. Hold on. Let me go. I got some water. I had a drink. Okay.
That was good. That was weird. Good night. Back to bed. I changed channel. I wake up. And there's a device in front of me. This device. We had had two cylinders in the top. And in the middle was some machine some kind of machine. I don't know what the fuck it was.
But it was a machine that processed your piss. And I knew that I knew what the machine was. And what this thing did is it processed your piss not by a computer, but it got sent to my Reddit for them to process and tell me what illnesses I have.
So this device is you're supposed to pee like into it like a pee collector, pour it in. And my red like Reddit will tell me like give me like a spreadsheet of all the fucking illnesses I have. So I'm supposed to I am supposed to be doing this. Oh, I guess I'm this is what I have to do today. Yeah, I'm doing that. I go I need I want to know some things. But I don't want like Reddit to know. Like, but I don't know what but that's like kind of personal.
So, so Otto just peed into the cup, and gave it to me. Like I just took it from him. And I poured Otto's pee in there. Like, hey, guys, coming in my pee. Here's my here it is. And they like Reddit started to decipher all these problems that I had. And they were like comment threads about, man, this is like kind of weird. This doesn't seem like anything that we've ever seen here before on Reddit, like on the German Reddit. And I'm like, Oh, oh, they know it's dog pee. What do I do?
Like, I didn't want them to know that like, it was like this weird social thing where like, it's like a social media thing. And I was trying to like circumvent the me doing this. I have no idea. So then, then I this is where it gets weird. So like, I go, oh, let me try it again. And I don't know why I don't look, you can't explain why you do things in dreams, but you just do.
So this time, because people were starting to get a little like, Oh, what's going on here? This isn't this. I don't think this is your pee. I did like half dog pee. And then I just took I just took peed directly into the tube at the same time. And I like hoping that that was going to solve that problem.
I then I woke up. Oh, I have to pee in the thing was Oh, that was weird. Strange. Oh, okay. Time to look at water. Okay. That's better. Time to go back to bed. Change channel again. This one I don't remember that much. I have no must no memory of this one. All I remember is I was a blacksmith. That's it. I don't know anything else. I don't I don't know what I was doing.
what I was doing, what I was making.
But I had this big, it was like a butcher's,
it was like a butcher's cape.
And it was like all butchery.
And I had like big butcher gloves on.
And I was like making, I was making something for somebody
in my like blacksmithing store.
And then I woke up and the sun was out.
I don't, I, that's three separate TV shows
that I jumped into halfway through the episode.
Like I walked in on a friend or a roommate
watching the end of a movie three times.
Like the culmination, the asteroids are falling.
Here's the big climax of that movie.
Dreams don't make any sense.
No one will ever be able to tell us what they actually are.
Ever.
No one.
I don't care if, you know, if you want to explain it
spiritually or scientifically.
What the fuck?
Why does that happen?
Why can't we like see inside of our own heads
when we're sleeping?
I don't know.
To be a black, to see a blacksmith in your dream
represents inner strength and endurance.
Perhaps the dream is telling you that you need
to strike while the fire is hot
or act while you have the opportunity.
Okay.
What does asteroids falling into earth mean?
Help me out here.
Holy shit, somebody gave a lot of money.
Holy shit.
All right, we had, I was too,
I was too locked into telling my dreams.
But we had, Germa lied about eating a shoe
thanks to five community subs.
Definitely, that's absolutely a lie.
So I'm glad you made that account.
Thanks for the five subs.
And MVM Matt gave a hundred dollars, 10,000 bits.
Thank you MVM Matt for the 10,000 bits, 100 bucks.
Huge amount of fucking money.
Hey, Germa, I've been watching you for five years.
You've gotten me through some tough times in my life.
And you always have been the funniest person
I've seen on the internet.
Never stopped being you.
Thank you for the incredibly kind message, Matt.
And thanks for the hundred bucks.
I only know how to be me.
I don't know how to be anybody else.
So I don't think that'll change.
But thank you.
Really appreciate that.
To see an asteroid in your dream
represents a spiritual message from above.
You're about to be enlightened with some knowledge.
Alternatively, it signifies a brainstorming
of ideas and thoughts.
If the asteroid hits the earth,
then it indicates that your idealistic notions
are deteriorating or being shattered apart.
Which one of those things confirms sans for smash?
All right, what about peeing?
Okay, what about, good luck with this one.
Peeing into a device that Reddit will tell you
what illnesses you have.
Being embarrassed about that
and having your dog pee go in there instead.
And then mixing your pee and your dog's pee
in there to try to throw them off.
What does that one mean?
Another hundred bucks just came in.
This is from Phylactery Lich.
Thank you Phylactery for the hundred bucks back to back.
It's okay, Germa.
I also have weird dream episodes sometimes.
They can be weird.
Dreams, I dream, dreams, I,
you ever get to the point where you have a dream
and you don't want to dream
and you'll do everything possible to get out of the dream?
Wanna know what works for me?
If you really wanna get out of a dream,
this is real knowledge that I'm gonna drop on you here.
This is a secret recipe to get the fuck out of a nightmare.
You wanna know how to do it?
You close your eyes tight and open them.
If you blink, if you make,
if you blink in a dream tightly,
if you go close your eyes tight, tight, tight,
close your eyes, close your eyes tight, you'll get up.
In the dream, if you do that, do that consciously,
close your eyes, blink, blink, blink, you'll get up.
I just tried that, it works.
See, welcome back to reality.
I'm talking to the mods at the speed run academy.
We determined you've broken too many rules for this run
so we cannot use this for the archive.
Oh, thanks.
Thanks for the heads up.
Thank you, though, to the both back to back
hundred dollar donations in 10,000 bits.
By the way, I do have to say it
because I'm a live streamer, okay?
I'm a live streamer, therefore I have to say this.
No, fuck it, I ain't gonna say it.
No, you've already heard it a thousand times.
Why do I need to be the person to tell you this?
Every single live stream, okay, I'll give you a hint.
Every stream you have watched, every single one
in the last like four or five days has said this word
and told you about it.
So this is just redundant information by this point.
Sans isn't smashed yet, that's the last I'm talking about.
I'll give you another hint.
It is partnered up with a failing company
that's closing all their stores.
Take a guess.
No, I can't, he hates this, no, I'm just saying.
When was the last time you went into one?
I haven't been in one, I'm just being real.
I'm being realistic.
Yesterday, I'm just being real a day ago.
Hey, who are you?
You can't just barge in here.
What is he talking about?
What the fuck is he talking about?
All right, everybody settle down for a minute.
I'm about to, here we go.
Over the course of September, if you're a new sub,
your tier one subscription will be 50% off.
Partnering up with Subway to,
I'm actually, I'm not entirely sure what they're doing
and why it's with Subway.
It's only if it's your first time subbing
and I don't think community subs do it either.
Why is it Subway?
Do you get like a Subway sandwich or something?
I don't get it.
Beginning September 3rd at 1 p.m.
In partnership with Subway,
we're offering 50% off new tier one subscription.
But what is Subway doing?
I'm actually curious.
Was it just there?
Are they?
Oh, don't forget those bonus bits.
Subway is throwing in 10% more bits
when you cheer 10 or more.
Thanks to Subway.
Subway will be gifting subscriptions to various channels.
Make sure to tune in of who they gift a sub to
and tune in when Subway launches their own Twitch channel.
Wait, why is, what?
Why is Subway making a Twitch channel?
Is this like the great rebranding
of like 2020?
All right, I gotta play Mario RPG.
Jerma, why don't you get sponsorships?
I don't know.
Rewind fucking five minutes.
All right, so the last thing we did,
we've been told that Mallow
is not a frog
and that Mallow is in fact a giant bird who's in here.
So who's the fucking faker is what I,
I'm in a weird mood today.
I can already tell you that.
So now, what was the actual, okay, I gotta go, let's talk.
I used to work in the castle.
You should see the way she hits poor Dodo.
What a horrible wife he must have.
All right, did I buy anything from here?
Say, you had thought I'm looking for something
to look in your eye.
What can I do for you?
I think I already bought stuff, right?
Yeah, Mega Glove Warfam, he already got it.
What was I doing here?
I forget the next part of this.
Wait, what was the last thing I did?
Used to be so small, now look at him.
How do we get into that castle?
I gotta remember this.
King Nimbus loves statues and birds.
He has scads of them in the castle.
You got, I think we have, yeah, I remember.
We gotta talk to like the sculpture person.
You know about the royal bus?
I do actually.
If you read this, I'll give you $50.
Okay, just did.
Yeah, I thought, doesn't somebody,
I swear that somebody recognizes Mallow here.
Wahoo.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Who's that?
Hey, look, it's me.
Oh, you mean that, that's King Nimbus
when he was young.
Huh?
What the, who are you?
Hello, my name is Mallow, and this is my friend Mario.
Mallow, so it is you.
My boy, it's been so long, my,
you've become a splendid young prince.
I'm a prince?
What?
I'm really a prince?
Mario, you're great at impressions.
Wow, Mario, that was some mystique level shit there.
Yeah, okay, I get it, I guess.
You were raised by Frogfuchsia.
There's no question about it,
you are without a doubt Prince Mallow.
Mario, look at me, I'm a prince.
I knew Valentina was up to something.
I just didn't know what.
That must mean that the king really isn't gravely ill.
Then let's go inside the castle
and save my mother and father, right now.
Hey, who are you?
You can't just barge in here.
Wait, I have an excellent idea.
Get over here.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Just stay still for a little while, okay?
It won't take too long.
There.
Don't move.
You're gonna be a statue for a little while, okay?
Let's get going.
Eternally Gaming just gave $50.
A deal's a deal.
You actually did it.
I can't believe you actually did it.
Well, I guess that, yeah.
That's true, you did.
If you keep, that means I have to eat a shoe.
I don't like people doing the things
they say they're gonna do.
But thank you.
They say a deal's a deal.
Anyway, I gotta say that I think you're a great comedian.
Watching you play games can be painful,
but you're undoubtedly a pioneer in streaming.
Love your creativity and talent as a comedian.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate that, thanks a lot.
If you think that I'm a good comedian,
I hope you have fun.
If you are, then you are.
And if you aren't, then I'm sorry.
Hopefully you do next time.
Painful at video games.
Whatever, I do fine.
I do fine.
I'm doing just fine.
What did you wanna be when you grew up?
A magic wand maker.
Like from magicians and shit when I was in preschool.
Well, thank you, Eternally Gaming, for the $50,
and yeah, you did hold your word.
I'm delivering Valentina's latest order to her.
You may enter.
Here it goes.
Hey, this doesn't look like Valentina at all.
Oh, that's because this is a statue of Valentina's nephew,
Mariota, okay?
All right, proceed.
There it was.
Remember that noise I was waiting for this whole time?
It just happened.
So everyone thought I was crazy.
I got lots of question marks last time.
Oh, phew, that was close.
I didn't think we could just get through that one.
There is no such person named Mariota.
Ha ha.
There it is, I don't even have to do it.
Oh, now this is lovely.
My beauty simply shines forth like the sun.
Only you can make something this stunning.
Thank you, your majesty.
I'll be on my way now.
Halt!
What, may I ask, is this ugly thing?
Oh, shit!
That's my latest masterpiece.
I created it just for you.
It's called a plumber's lament.
Observe the thick mustache,
covering the sad, innocent smile of a simple fool,
and the sideburns conveying his blue-collar roots,
and the legs well-defined, strong,
the legs of the masses.
Is it to your liking?
Hmm.
I consider myself something of an art buff,
and I've got to say, this is spectacular.
Garo, only you could have created sculptures
with such gentle beauty and raw power.
Thank you, your majesty.
I'll be on my way now.
Wink, wink, nudge.
Spectacular.
Dodo, Dodo!
Don't just sit there like a roast.
Hurry and carry these in.
Dodo, ow.
Step on it.
Dodo.
Oh, I remember this part.
This is the pretend-to-be-the-statue part of the game.
Ha-ha!
I love this part, yeah.
This part is just so, it's just, it's so cute.
Dodo, did you display the statues properly?
Fine, now polish them to a fine luster
and make them a tribute to my beauty.
Oh, shit.
Pay attention to me.
Hurry up and don't let me catch you dozing again.
Uh-oh, Dodo's in a pretty bad mood.
Keep up your statue disguise and jump to avoid getting picked.
Get ready.
Are you ready?
Yes, he's coming right now.
Trump the narrator.
He's already, no, I told you the blue is the most.
He missed.
Uh-oh, did he catch me?
I did it!
Picked up a feather.
They believe this is an accessory.
Speed up by 20.
Peach has the EXP booster on.
Now, I'm, I'm, I think, I think
that somebody in the party just has to have this on.
I don't think it has to be somebody in the actual fight.
I'm almost certain of that.
Can somebody confirm with me, please?
Somebody else has played this game five or 600 times
like I have, maybe, fuck you.
All right, well, thanks for the help.
And then, I've never played it, okay.
Yeah, give it to me.
If you read this, yes.
One guy.
I don't even know what this game is.
All right, we're gonna test it.
By the way, why is Malo in the party?
That's just, excuse me.
What are you doing in here?
So, let's test it out.
The feather also is very, very good.
So, Peach can have the feather on.
Trooper pin, yep.
Amulet's still good.
Ghost metal, I think maybe, no, keep the amulet on.
Keep Malo, keep Malo, keep Malo.
Guys, Malo doesn't have any stuff.
I didn't buy his shit.
Look, he's got mega pants on.
Like, he has shitty pants on.
Keep Malo or riot.
Maybe if I get to go back to town, I'll switch him out.
Does that make you happy?
Only the person holding it gets double EXP.
They don't have to be in the party.
That's, yeah, that's what I was thinking.
So, Malo currently is getting double experience.
I'm absolutely exhausted.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
I hate being a guard.
Valentino only gives us the most boring jobs to do.
But I guess this beats Dodo's job.
Dodo has to polish Valentino's statues every single day.
This is how I would do it.
Oh, hey, tell me something.
Do statues move?
No, statues don't move.
Then explain this.
It's one of those high-tech, lifelike, realistic ones.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, here we are.
Actually, let me go.
Yeah, we can go pretty much anywhere.
Got that flower tab, sick.
Let's get a fight.
Boom.
Big Yoshi, big Yoshi, big Yoshi, what are you talking about?
This is an absolute unit.
Absolute unit Koopa.
All right, level 16 Toast Duel.
It's time, we pick, we pick, we pick, we pick, we pick.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta, I didn't even put,
the extension's not even turned on.
All right, you guys can, you guys can now click on it.
Absolute unit.
Imagine being that much of a fucking unit.
By the way, if you don't know how this works,
you enable the extension and click on your screen.
By the way, for the entire month of September,
that's right, if you go outside,
it's gonna be a little cooler than it was last month.
Ball is starting.
Buy a jacket.
Thank you for voting.
Magic attack 72.
All right, what is this, what is this,
what is this, what is this over here?
Oh, that's right, he's a fan.
Let's go this way.
I got the tab, that's what I wanted.
Actually, you know what, I'm gonna go up
because the fan blows and I'm gonna wait
for the fan to turn on.
I think I can actually wrap around this fan.
Oh, get out of here, leave me alone.
Come on, Malo, level up.
I wanna get rid of that.
Geno blast, it just wipes out everybody.
333333, Malo, nope, it's Bowser.
Level 16, 136, 144, no one's at 200 HP yet,
which concerns me.
By the way, if you click on Bowser,
that counts as a middle vote.
So yes, we've made that clear already.
Okay, 127 attack power, that's so much.
That's too much.
Got it, nope, okay, I couldn't block that for some reason.
Okay, that was weird.
Miss, I don't like that.
I don't really think I'm gonna kill it
with the next punch, so I'm gonna defend.
Everyone's okay, I'm gonna try jump.
Thank God, Jesus, that was the hardest
fucking enemy in the game.
I think that actually probably was the hardest thing
I've ever faced in Super Mario.
Look at that dodge.
I was thinking about just getting hit
over and over again and dying,
but then I saved like two long ago.
I didn't wanna do that whole thing again.
No, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Heavy trooper's ready to launch.
If you let the heavy trooper launch,
I believe everybody dies.
That's 62, that's 64 EXP from Malo.
Malo's gonna over-level everybody, magic.
I should just give it to Bowser.
Yeah, okay, after this, I'm gonna switch it over to Bowser.
Because Bowser's gonna be unstoppable.
You guys got all the flowers, nice job.
84, all right, let's give it to Bowser.
We're gonna spread this thing around.
Hey, wait a minute, it's locked.
Ooh, do you like that dodge?
Whoa, he's like right up me.
Jawful sleeping, not for long.
I love this character, by the way.
He's just a fork.
No, oh God.
Jawful sleeping, again.
We just geno-blast everybody
from here till the end of the game.
That's how this works.
Don't run, don't run.
Good, because these guys drop good stuff.
44 coins, grab this, here it is, another tab.
Birdcage is right in the way, it's okay.
You know what I'm gonna do.
Oh no, I ran out of power points.
That's all right.
Lucky.
Jawful's awake.
I'll be honest, that's the face that I make too
when I just wake up.
If somebody just wakes me up abruptly,
you kinda sit there like, wait, is this for real?
Ow, why are you taking so much damage now?
Oh dude, that face went laughing my ass off.
Is this experience?
It is, all right, this is important, follow it.
Pay attention, click over to the new tab.
It's the right one, I think.
Don't take my word for it though.
Am I wrong?
Don't listen to me, use your own judgment.
All right, I'm gonna go with you.
All right, I hope you're right.
How are you guys right every fucking time?
I don't understand.
How can you get that every single time?
You have not been wrong once.
We're gamers, unlike you.
Well, maybe some of you are,
because 15% of you clicked on Peach's face.
So come on, give me a break.
You have to go to the bathroom, can I stop for a second?
Yeah, go on.
You have 30 seconds to compete, whatever.
Go on.
I should just change games before they get back
and just act like nothing happened.
What are you talking about, man?
Like with Super Mario RPG, no.
We're playing Dead Cells.
What are you, are you all right?
What are you talking about?
Go like download a save file from somewhere,
like there's like 7,000 hours in the game
and it's like I have every ability and shit.
Switch to XCOM and name everybody Mario,
Malo, Peach, and Bowser.
Ooh, we've got,
we've got a new,
you're clicking on the top right button.
That's new.
Usually you just click on the right flower,
but I mean today it's different.
You're clicking on the top right button thing.
Look at how low this percentage is to click this.
Look at how low that is.
Does democracy work?
Because like only 14%.
How many people went into the voting booth
and like sneezed on the paper
and like moved their pencil and just left?
How many people went into the voting booth
in the last election and just like
put like a marker on like the letter T?
This is, this is, this is the, okay.
10, 12, 12, 8%, 8%.
They just take the pencil and leave.
But what did you do in the voting booth?
Well, I drew a smiley face
and there was some calligraphy on the voting ballot
and I circled it.
Did you vote for anything
that was supposed to be voted for?
What?
No, a left calligraphy gang.
And then they walk away.
Okay, I guess we're going with power.
No, I gotta pay, go, go, go, go, go, go.
No, I forgot to take my potion.
Now I have to fight them for real.
I can't use my cop out magic move.
Ow, I just, I don't know why I just thought of this.
Like ballots, right?
You go and like, you go whatever the ballot,
whatever you're voting for.
And you kind of, it's like,
but like one, two, three, four, five, right?
I just imagined like some old person
just like speaking like a confessional through the wall.
Hey, who are you voting for?
I don't know what to do.
Can I see your paper?
I didn't study, I didn't study for this test.
Holy shit, there's a lot of coins.
Ooh, and watch.
Click, click, over here, over here, over here.
I know which one of these is the middle thing.
Don't listen to me.
Yeah.
Yoshi and Yoshi are both selected.
Yoshi and Yoshi.
You guys are wrong.
We lost all that experience.
Shouldn't have listened to me.
What's double, can you get double of zero?
No, that's math, Jeremy, that's math.
It doesn't work that way.
No, I'm just gonna do it now
because I just keep, I keep forgetting to do it.
You should have just clicked on Yoshi.
I should have, it's fine.
I know you guys saying, oh, big chunky guy,
big, big, chunky, chewy guy, whatever, right?
No, that's a hamster that has a shell on it
as like a funny little joke.
That's just a hamster, guys.
That's not a Koopa Troopa.
Oh, fuck, is everybody dead?
He didn't do it, okay.
God, I can't even say what you said.
What is wrong with you guys?
I'm laughing, I'm laughing.
I think it's funny, whatever.
I don't have any mushrooms.
No, that's not what I read.
Come on, here we go.
Back to cheating.
That's not what I laughed at.
No, it's not.
A lot of experience though here.
This is pretty cool.
Oh, I found everybody.
I used to be a guard here
until Valentina snapped away all my keys
and gave me the boot.
Guess I won't be needing this master key anymore.
Would you like it?
Please.
All right, here you go.
Just don't tell me what you're gonna do with it, okay?
Do you know that there are hot springs around here?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, you're no fun.
I wanted to be the first to tell you.
Go on, take this.
Flower jar.
A dip in the hot springs
would perk up the king in the jiffy.
Hey, did you know?
Valentina's got a huge egg in the middle room.
It spits out eggs from time to time
and sometimes when you shield yourself,
the eggs will ricochet off of you.
Why do you, how do you know this?
I thought he was an NPC.
Those who don't want Geno in Smash,
after just seeing that.
Okay.
Sans got in before Geno.
I'm just imagining the posts.
Sans from Undertale gets in before Geno,
like a laughing fucking laughing guy.
Geno isn't in Smash, but Sans gets in?
Compilation of celebrities laughing hysterically
in an image.
Hey, you're mad.
It's you and one of them that's mad about Sans.
Holy shit, Bowser's leveled up again.
Whoa.
Why would I be mad about a character
getting put into Smash Bros.?
Really?
Why would I be angry that somebody gets to be happy
that somebody that they like to play as
or have cared about gets to be in one of their favorite games?
Why would that make me angry?
No, I think that's great.
All right, where we going?
He's mad.
He's just...
Ooh, nice.
This is a tough one.
I thank you Wingus Dingus 69 for the 10 community subs.
Thank you for the 10 subs, Wingus Dingus.
Come on, pick one.
Pick one.
You're going back and forth here.
Okay.
You've decided.
Thank you for voting.
We're going HP.
Ooh, HP was not the right choice.
HP, wrong choice.
One.
That's not good.
Stop it.
Leave me alone.
Treasure.
There's the key.
Leave you.
Uh-oh.
Look what I get to do again.
I get to make 150 to 200 people leave the stream.
La dee da.
Here you go, big eggy.
I'll give you plenty of nutrients
so you'll grow up to be big and strong.
Oh, Mario's already here.
He's a fast one, he is.
It won't help him.
It's not.
Let me try.
I'm so lonely.
Would you play with me?
Thanks.
Crack the egg.
Hello, I'm Birdo.
Birdo, you're going to be...
What is my name?
30?
I need 30 jumps, right?
That was like eight.
Well, that hurt.
Thank you.
Again, ultra jump.
Here we go.
Shit.
Teehee.
Ouch, you're hurting me.
Now it's my turn.
Get it while it's hot.
Oh.
Too many subs.
That's 69 subs.
None of those are half off.
I hope you're aware of that.
That's 69 subs from phylactery lich.
69 subs.
Too many subs.
Thank you, phylactery.
That's an absolute shitload.
Again.
Doing it again.
So this one's for you.
Here we go.
Four, seven, 12, 16, 17, 18, and 13 damage.
I'll get it.
But, oh, seriously, phylactery.
That's...
You're encroaching on like 500 fucking subs on the channel.
Something insane like that.
I have to get this, come on.
Damn it, I keep getting stopped at like 19, 20.
You have to beat Kyro Toby.
Well, it's never a competition.
Again.
Fuck.
All right, I've had enough.
Nevermind.
15.
15, I know.
I gotta get 30.
Come on, I'm out of points.
Ow.
All right.
All right, ghetto.
Peach really is incredible.
I used to fill my inventory with junk.
Okay, here we go.
So those of you that don't know,
the timing of the jump changes after 12 to 15 jumps.
What ends up happening is it shrinks
to about like two pixels after 15 or so.
So trying to find the timing is very hard.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, I'm never gonna let you go.
You're just too cute.
Castle key two.
Never gonna give you up.
I'm never gonna give you up.
Just hold the stick.
Hold the stick in your hand, jump, swing.
It's all you need to do, Mario.
Come on.
No.
I forgot.
Oh no.
Gee, I used a pinwheel.
Oh no, I used a pinwheel.
Come on.
Right at that 15, 16, it goes down to like one pixel.
God, didn't get 30 on pinwheel.
I'm an idiot.
Ooh, that was a lot of coins.
Uh-oh, we've got an issue here.
This is locked too.
Mario, look, there's a note.
Let's read it.
King Nimbus is resting in bed.
Absolutely no running in the heart.
From Queen Valentine.
This can only mean that mom and dad are in here.
Oh, but it's locked.
Leave it to me.
Looks like it's up to me to get us out of yet another jam.
Feast your eyes on this show of brains and brawn.
Stand back.
Wait, wait a minute.
If my dad's really bedridden,
we shouldn't make so much noise.
We need another plan.
I guess we should find Valentina
and force the truth out of her.
Uh, Bowser, I don't want to tell you this,
but you know, I'm pointing at my nose.
I'm like looking at you.
I'm looking at you, direct eye contact.
Hey, like touching under my nose,
like wipe, like wipe under your fucking nose, dude.
Like we're like at a party.
But what about the door?
Listen, you never ever talk to the leader
of the Koopa troop like that.
Oh, I hate that.
Ah, I'll ignore it this time,
but don't let that happen again.
Queen Valentina.
Ooh, ooh, Queen Valentina.
It's like someone's reading a book to kids.
No, but the only difference is I would be like
falling asleep halfway through.
That's what my mother used to do.
She would start to pass out,
like fall asleep while reading stories.
Oh, heavy troop is coming in.
Here we go.
Queen Valentina.
This is what my mother would do.
So she'd like do voices and stuff.
That Mario creature who beat up Smilax is here.
Mario?
What does a Mario look like?
Well, it has a bushy mustache,
long sideburns and a pair of mean looking legs.
I have a feeling I've seen this Mario before.
And I'd be like, Mom?
Wait, yes, that was a setch that Gora just delivered.
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do, Valentina?
Well, we certainly aren't going to listen
to your pointless chatter.
Mom, what happens next?
Frankly speaking, I'm not going to worry
without this key.
The king can't go anywhere.
This is real.
This happened.
I'm not telling a joke.
This is reality.
This is what happened.
My mother worked hard, okay?
Give me a break.
Hush.
I said, shut up already.
What?
That isn't a statue.
That's Mario.
Valentina, hand over to me now.
My leg.
How utterly rude.
And who in the blazes are you anyways?
Me, I'm the real Prince, that's who.
Brat.
How dare you listen in on a private conversation.
Private?
Private, everybody in a 10-mile radius could hear you.
Oh, if you're going to be this rude,
I'm simply going to leave.
So long, chumps.
Hey, Valentina ran away.
I shall fly the coop too.
I think we've kind of missed a boat here.
So we better get moving too.
Let's go, get him.
I didn't mean to do that.
Dodo is cute.
Here comes the launch.
Somebody leveled up?
No.
See that nice dodge?
Oh, fuck, I forgot this was here.
I just killed Dodo.
Oh, shit.
Dodo.
No.
Oh, poor Dodo.
I just starred him.
Hot springs are up ahead,
but only really to go there.
You don't look like royalty.
All right.
I, what have I got?
Why do I have to like items?
Max mushroom, max mushroom, honey syrup.
I have way too many honey syrups.
I'm going to do the flower jar though, I'm taking it.
Froggy drink, Carol, Carol, Cola.
Okay.
Shall we?
Queen Valentina.
Queen Valentina, is the king showing
any sign of improvement?
And how is his wife, the old queen?
And Tubby, I mean, Prince Malo,
where is he hiding these days?
You know what I think?
I think, get out of here.
The truth, get out, let me check.
You know what I think?
Ugh!
Pipe down, all of you.
I have better things to do
than listen to your half-wit opinions.
And look, while I've been wasting my time
listening to your endless chatter,
Mario has managed to find me.
Dodo?
Oh, that bird has a permanent brain cramp.
Dodo, do you hear me?
Get over here now.
I need some help entertaining Mario.
So move it.
Come over here now.
He psych killed him.
Dodo?
Where are you?
Don't just sit there, help me.
Uh-oh, one-on-one.
Gino versus Dodo.
Can't do anything besides attack normally.
Toy versus a bird.
Yeah, what an exhilarating fight this will be.
Wait, we're all good.
Valentina kind of looks like, hey, Arnold.
I'm just realizing this is the first time.
It's like Stewie Griffin, or hey, Arnold.
It's Stewie Griffin.
The same like squished head.
All right, here we go.
No, 17 every time.
No, I'm trying to, the timing's so hard.
I'm trying to change it up.
It's after 16 is where it becomes one frame, I believe.
Now, how do I, where's my emulator
where I can slow down time, like how everybody did this?
Dodo, how could you lose already?
Well, come on, get over here.
Uh-oh, drain beam.
All right, Gino still can't do anything.
All right, we're gonna go for,
we're gonna go for Dodo first.
Sorry.
Oh shit, stop hurting him.
He's hurting me.
Somebody's sick of mushroom here.
No, I'll be fine.
It's a max mushroom, why would I do that?
How many was that?
18?
Uh-oh, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Peach is dead.
No, Peach is alive.
This is more important, Gino.
Ow, do it only with sound cues.
That actually might be a better idea.
Oops.
Oh, sick, I just got 18.
It's time, Peach can't do any heals.
I'm gonna try doing it with sound next time.
Should I do Lucky Jewel?
I think it's time.
We're gonna, Lucky Jewel, you ready?
At the end of this, we're gonna,
you guys have to get it right.
It's time for Lucky Jewel.
Lucky, there it is.
We are doubling something here.
You gotta use your shit.
I hold onto these items so much, it's just stupid.
211, see you later.
Lucky Jewel infinite, is it?
I thought it was just one time.
I'm gonna do this only with sound, you ready?
It didn't help.
What was that?
20.
Oh shit, I don't believe this.
The show's over, folks.
Dodo, let's get out of here.
All right, those of you that are not paying attention,
I need you to pay attention now.
So, come back over here,
because this is important.
There we go, this is 200 coins and 40 experience.
So we're gonna get 80 experience.
You ready?
Now this is important.
Here we go.
Which one?
We're gonna, the whole team will level up if we do this.
We, I mean you.
And by you, I mean 3,000 people here.
All of you.
All right, this is pretty unanimous.
It's 80 experience, so that's 100,
that's Bowser's gonna level up at least once.
Bowser's doubling his EXP.
That's 160, Peach level 17.
Nice job, guys, you did it.
You did it, you did it, you did it.
I'm very, very happy, very grateful.
More power.
What stat is good for Peach?
I would say reliably.
Magic, damage, magic, defense, and HP.
There's Malo.
Somebody says, hey, I have a question for you.
Has anyone really been far even as decided to use
even though want to do look more like?
If you could let me know, I'd appreciate it.
Yes.
Magic it is.
Everybody levels up today.
Here comes another one.
Bowser, level 18.
All right, we gotta take this off.
Bowser's gonna be overleveled, but that's good.
We're gonna need it.
Bowser crush.
He has learned 100%.
Wow, that was almost 200 clicks at 100% on the website.
That's pretty remarkable.
And it's not even close, so 139.
Great, they're gone.
Hurry, let's go after her.
I know she has the key.
Ow, ow.
Huh, Mario, look.
I didn't mean to eat that.
That's cute.
That's very cute.
How adorable.
Mom, Dad, I'd like you to meet Mario
and my other travel companions.
What's that?
Oh, wow, did we understand you well.
I'm Bowser's father, King Lindus.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you so much for looking after my dear child.
Allow me to introduce everyone.
This is Princess Toastle from Mushroom Kingdom.
Ah, I haven't heard so much about you.
May I have your autograph?
Don't embarrass Junior, dear.
Oh, never mind.
Who is this gentleman over in the middle here?
This is Super Mario.
He helped me from the start.
Why, sincerely thank you from the bottom of my heart.
You don't mean the Mario, the jumping Mario?
Autograph, please?
That's quite enough, dear.
Okay, all right, well, wait a moment.
Show him just a little jump, a tiny one will do.
Do the thing, Mario.
Make us all happy.
Oh, fantastic.
Show me ever again later.
Ahem, and who do we have over here?
This is Bowser, leader of the Koopa Troop.
Oh, another famous person.
Oh, this is too much for me.
I must have your autograph.
Dear, behave yourself, please.
No, not even a scribble?
Okay, all right, well, fine.
Yes, yes, yes, I'm quite forgetting my manners.
Well, who do we have over here?
This is Gino, who I told you about before.
Oh, yes, the story about Star Street, oh, how awful.
That's Star Road.
By the way, a little before Valentina took over,
a large star fell into the volcano.
Well, the dreaded star dragon inhabits the volcano.
It's going to be tough for getting a star out of there.
Perhaps all of you working together could handle that least.
Why would I, as young, I...
Yes, dear, yeah, okay.
Now, once at the volcano, find Hinopio.
He'll be able to help you.
You be careful, Mellow.
Okay, Mom, but I probably won't come back
until we find the star.
What do you got back here?
Any treasures for me?
Yeah, yeah, mm-hmm, there it is.
Flower tab, I'll take it.
Okay, so now I'm gonna do something
that a lot of people don't know exists,
and even if you do, that's just the way it is.
I ain't gonna use it.
Not yet.
Oh, the bird.
There is a secret that I am about to get,
and there's a debate whether or not
you should actually put it on or not.
The king gave me another job as a guard.
Prince Mellow!
Thank you so much.
We were able to rescue my father with the key you gave us.
Don't mention it.
Besides, it was you who actually rescued him.
Good luck in the future.
You too.
Prince, here, this is from me.
Please take it.
Did you know that there are hot springs?
Yes, I know.
That's a pogchamp moment right there, I would say.
Yeah, all the statues are back to normal.
This is no longer a bad play.
Look at this, look at this.
Everybody.
This statue, it seems so unworldly.
Came to see the king's statue collection.
I tell you, it's remarkable.
It's very cool.
All right, let's go in here.
Go pawn the statues.
Why would I do that?
What happened?
I left, did he eat the shoe?
Uh-huh, he missed it.
I had to delete the clip, though.
I deleted the pod.
All right, everybody, if you don't want to be spoiled
on Super Mario RPG's Secrets of the Seven Stars,
a secret in the game, please do yourself a favor
and you should have played this game 10 years ago.
No, not 20 years ago,
because it was re-released like four times 10 years ago.
I was too young.
Uh-oh, busted.
What do I do, what to do, what to do?
I'll give you this fertilizer if you let me go, okay?
Receive the fertilizer.
He just shit in a bucket and gave it to you.
Well, maybe so.
Ready?
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, do it.
But first, let's go to the hot springs.
Hey, you're the real prince.
Sorry about the misunderstanding before.
There's no way that fat bird could have been a prince.
No big deal.
Anyway, do you think you could let us through?
Of course.
Go right ahead and enjoy yourself.
But be careful not to fall into the volcano.
Let's go relax.
This part of the game, I remember every time I did this,
I always wanted to go take a bath.
Woo, too hot.
Well, you did it wrong, Mario.
You're supposed to go in feet first
and then after two minutes, you put your legs in.
Then you put your butt in.
After five minutes, you put your stomach in.
You don't just go all in.
Danger beyond the cliffs is the volcano.
Yeah, but we're not doing that yet.
I've got some secrets to do.
Here we go.
Have pants for Mallow to buy?
Not yet.
In a moment.
Remember the seed we gave to this guy
like four or five hours ago?
And by that, I mean like stream four or five hours ago.
Here we go.
Hey, guys, do you know what you have there?
That fertilizer comes from the Shia Way clan,
famous for its miraculous feeds of godly.
I looked over at beyond the cliffs
and I tried Bean Valley, but failed.
I traveled around the world and waited.
You have the fertilizer on the...
Oh, short attention span?
Yes, you might say I have fertilizer on the brain.
Will you give it to me?
Sure.
Oh, thank you.
I finally have both the seed and the fertilizer.
I'll try them out right away.
I'll plant the seed, then give it fertilizer.
Nothing's happening.
Whoa.
Oh, what?
This is amazing.
This is unreal.
This is just like winning the lottery
only without the taxes.
I mean, this is like falling out of an airplane
without a parachute and hitting a ground
with geese and a man who'll break you fall.
Wait a minute, my buddies here about Happy Gardner's
one of your mothers.
I'm gonna be famous.
You think I could use a little more fertilizer?
Oops, maybe not, huh?
This will get me in Happy Gardner monthly magazine.
Hmm?
Don't mind if I climb this.
Hey, what do we got here?
Hmm.
Boom, you got the lazy shell
and you got the lazy shell.
Ladies and gentlemen, I hope you're paying attention
because this is the best armor in the game
besides one other item, I believe.
Look at those stat changes.
To give you a little bit of a look at that, 63 defense
and there's also a weapon.
Look at that, 198 damage.
Now, anybody can wear the lazy shell
and essentially what it does is it makes that person
100% unkillable.
Whoever wears the lazy shell will not fucking die.
It is impossible.
It's great, it's really good,
but we're not gonna use it right now.
It's cheating.
I will use the weapon or will I?
Maybe, I don't know.
Should I?
Not this early, not this early.
Look at the magic attack though.
It makes you completely useless.
It drags you down so hard in magic and attack
but it makes the person unable to die.
Should I give it to Peach?
Yeah, I will, I will eventually.
But no, I just have it, I have it.
I have the two essentially best weapons
and the best item in the game.
So, you know, I'll use it when I need to.
Like when I fight Kulex.
Because I'll fucking win.
I will beat Kulex with the lazy shell on
because that's how everybody beats Kulex.
Hey shit, use item, I will.
Hold on, there's more to see.
Not yet, just hold on a minute.
So there are a few more areas left to go.
Use that item or I'm gonna go to sleep.
Have a good night.
I'm going to use it.
You're using hacks on Kulex.
That's not, it's in the game.
It's in the game.
All right, I have to, I gotta pee.
No, I'm gonna hold my pee for a minute.
Let me get to the next town.
All right, I gotta go to the hot springs and then go down.
But I'm gonna buy the pants.
No, I'm not, why would I do that?
I'm about to go to a new area.
Time for the volcano.
I love that.
I also love this song.
Bower tab.
The bass guitar is objectively the best instrument.
I think it's one of the most important instruments.
I think it's one of the most important ones.
Bracer.
I have some of the items I gotta get rid of.
Because we are getting towards the end game here.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, that just kind of creeped off on me.
Mario, leveled up.
Very good, very good, very good.
Where does Mario RPG sit on my favorite all time games list?
There are five probably that are all in the same spot.
Power.
I cannot decide.
Geno flash.
That would have been a really cool final smash.
You'll see it.
I'll show it to you.
All right, super 87 magic attack.
I gotta go this way.
How much money do I have?
Nine, nine, nine?
Almost, six, six, three.
Why don't we take a look at it?
This is Geno flash.
The ultimate move.
He turns into a cannon and he shoots out the sun.
It sucks.
What?
It doesn't suck.
Look, I'll show you again.
That's 440 damage.
It sucks 440 damage?
Have you been counting?
Frog coin, how do I get that?
Oh, you gotta jump.
Ah, come on, I can get it.
I gotta get rid of all these things.
We're gonna have to fight two or three things
back to back to back here.
It's all right, I'm just gonna Geno blast him.
Just gonna do that twice.
Get rid of Peach and use Bowser.
When I get a new weapon for Bowser, yes.
But his current weapon right now hurts everybody's eyes.
That's the sad truth.
All right, didn't get it.
Okay, how are we doing on health?
Not great.
What am I gonna do with stream points?
I'll figure out something.
I don't think I even have access to them right now.
Are they in like beta?
I think I would do something stupid where, you know, some,
okay, you know, remember when Pepsi had the thing
where you could get the jet
for like a hundred million Pepsi points?
But what if like, what if like a hundred million
germ of twitch points?
Like I like flew out to like your neighborhood
and we like went and got lunch.
You need to get like a hundred fucking million.
That's some bullshit.
I come to your house.
That's no, that's some like Nickelodeon shit.
Nickelodeon presents Nicktoons come to your neighborhood.
I think they did something like that before, didn't they?
I think they did.
I think you get 10 points per half hour.
How long is that?
That may be like four to 500 years.
A hundred million coins and then we get to like miss.
Bowser level 19.
Where to?
Pull the coins.
Once again, chat is split on HP.
Well, if Bowser is eventually gonna get the lazy shell,
then I would start focusing on defense.
That's just me and it's you picking.
So, oh, come on.
Frog coin up there.
How do I get that frog coin?
That bingo, 380.
I gotta take a maple syrup.
I know I got a flower jar.
I'll just use that.
Go pee.
Yeah, I will.
Once I get to the new safe point, I will go pee.
I promise.
But I gotta get these frog coins first.
What the hell is this thing?
Where is it?
What plane is this on?
Oh, it was forward.
Come on, I already killed them.
I have to jump from here.
Get that, come on.
Dammit, I can't go that way.
Hey, listen, listen.
Listen, guys, I can't jump from here.
Okay, there was an invisible wall there.
I promise, I swear to God.
I swear on everything.
I do, rewind.
I actually tried to jump.
Did you see it?
I swear to God.
Go back, rewind.
I tried.
I did.
I swear to God.
I wasn't ready for this.
I tried to jump over there.
It didn't work.
I tried.
You can Lucky Jewel every single time.
I bet I haven't used that at every single boss.
I did not know that.
This monster's getting furious.
Get rid of him.
Shit.
Va-va-voom.
Oh, no, wait.
I think that kills somebody.
No, it doesn't.
I have to take a...
No, I don't.
Wait a minute.
Should I summon Yoshi?
9415.
I'm going for it.
This is a bad idea.
Really stupid, but he'll die right now.
Yep, okay.
Once again, defense up.
We're fine.
Just walk it.
I have a flower jar.
I don't want to waste anything.
Lucky, I didn't even need to use it.
Killer Crocomar, I just get $50.
5,000 bits from Killer Crocomar.
Thank you, Crocomar.
Huge money drop.
Big bits.
Sam and Max died for this, and I'm okay with that.
As long as you do all the Paper Mario series.
Also, you better Jex it out on Q-Legs.
Yeah, I do want to finish Sam and Max,
but I didn't really like season three.
The first episode just didn't do it for me.
I will finish it.
Never lied about finishing Sam and Max
season three, episode two through five.
Just make the username now.
All right, let's double the coins.
You paying attention?
We're at one.
I wasn't looking.
Do it again.
I'm going to go with the audience here.
31% says left, let's go, and you got it wrong.
It's okay, you didn't lose anything.
You tried.
It was very close.
I need to use that flower box,
because I have no flower power.
There it is.
81, nice.
All right.
I still have to go back to,
I got to bring this to the guy.
Okay, so that means let me do this.
But am I going to play Paper Mario?
I don't know.
All right, time to pee.
I'll be right back.
Nobody noticed anything weird about Germans pee this time.
Yeah, I guess you tell me.
We're also getting to one of my favorite parts
of the whole game.
And I cannot wait to act it out for you.
Damn it.
And then we have the series of doors
which you guys are going to pick.
Lots of chat participation coming up
in the next 45 minutes or so.
Let's go.
No, I wanted to jump.
I forgot to jump right at the end.
Comes the anger.
Tree stump is furious.
The monster's getting furious.
I forgot to refill my drink.
I'm so focused on peeing.
Peach level 18.
Psych bomb.
I'm not sure I've ever used this move.
Is that the final,
is that Peach's final smash?
All right.
Flower or I wish I could click the flower.
Maybe it would give me something.
Going underneath the frog stone frog.
Can I do it?
Can I go underneath stone frog?
Lift up, stone frog, whatever.
Let's get rid of you.
Can I, you know what?
Psych bomb.
Let's do it.
All right.
Why does Peach have bombs?
Migraine.
I think that does all of their health.
We're gonna have to check in on that.
What are these?
Yeah, damn it.
Special.
Did I land on the thing or,
God damn it.
It's all right, geno blast.
Geno flash, let's go.
Everybody.
In one go.
Let's see it.
Oh, that always feels good.
18 for Mallow.
Star rain.
Mallow's final move.
How close am I to the end?
This is the second to last.
Well, no, this is the,
this is the three,
there's two more areas after this area, technically.
So we're at about the 85 percentile through the game.
We're nearing the end of the game, yes.
We're late, game.
Let me sleep.
The stream just started two hours ago.
Ah, shit.
Do it again.
It's four a.m. here.
Well, it's like 5.30 here, p.m.
Let me sleep.
I'm so tired.
Big bits, more big bits.
More, more.
Five, 50 bucks from Killer Crocomire.
That's 100 bucks from Killer Crocomire.
So far, Crocomire, big money.
Huge cash drop.
Shit, I was trying to do something sneaky.
And they say,
don't act like you didn't evade that Paper Mario question.
Oh, if I was, didn't I say I was,
I was probably not gonna do it?
I think I said that at like a couple of streams ago, maybe?
I don't have any plans to play Paper Mario.
Let's just put it that way.
So, but I didn't have any plans to play this, did I?
Somebody actually said that I said I was gonna,
the only reason why I would stream this game
is if I had like a mental breakdown or something, right?
I never planned on everything and I was gonna do this.
So, I don't know.
Evading the question,
I just said the answer was probably no.
That's me answering the question.
Evading the question would be,
are you gonna play Paper Mario?
And then I say,
well, you know,
it actually is supposed to be raining.
I think it's supposed to rain tomorrow.
And then I just go back to normal.
That's it.
Stop evading the question.
Bario's,
Bario,
oh, good for Bario.
He's now level 20.
They all say, keep up the good content
and hope you do the dunk tank stream
before winter rolls in.
I'm not sure if you've been here,
but September 21st is not just gonna be a dunk tank.
It's gonna be like a six hour carnival
with a shitload of chat controlled carnival games.
September 21st, hope to see you there.
But thank you.
Seriously, Crocmar.
That's a lot of fucking money.
Too much money.
Rose and dunk tank.
No, it'll be too cold to do it then.
Ball weight, nine, 13.
No.
I feel like you guys don't care about this anymore.
Cause once we've gone majority clicking right flower,
I think that I should just start picking these.
Cause like that's majority right flower.
I think the novelty may have worn off.
Hold on, I think Otto is like,
is Otto trying to get in here?
Hold on.
Sorry about that.
I just heard him bark.
He was barking at my bedroom door.
Not here.
Cause the bedroom door was closed
and he wanted to go and lie down
in his bed in the bedroom.
Bowser at 152, 153 attack.
That was pretty good.
You probably could've heard that.
Usually I can get away with a full burp under my breath,
but everything was quiet
and you probably just heard that completely.
I need a, I'm sorry.
It was like cue the music to zero.
Hopefully nobody heard it.
Okay, backfire.
Out.
I want like another coffee.
I'm gonna have to feel like that.
Anybody have to feel like they want two coffees.
Ultra flame, there it is.
I think today it might be a two,
it's like five, it's like six o'clock.
You can't drink coffee after six.
You can't, like that's bad.
That is too late.
I'll go get like a water.
Next break.
All right, if right flower click becomes more than 50%,
I'm gonna start just picking these.
Green tea.
You know what?
That's right, I could just get tea.
What do we have for tea here?
I wonder.
I think I have some green tea.
All right, well, I'm gonna start picking my own stuff then.
I mean, that's just too much.
Hey.
Hey there, I thought I heard footsteps.
For a minute I thought I was nuts.
Hey, that's killer.
I'm Hinopia.
This place is a regular inferno.
Come on, step inside.
Welcome to the item shop.
This here is the inn.
30 coins will get you a room.
Armor shop.
Ooh, fire shirt, fire pants, fire cape, fire shell,
fire dress, fire shirt, fire pants, fire cape,
fire dress, don't need the fire shell, fuzzy shirt,
fire shirt, fuzzy cape, fire cape, fuzzy dress,
fire dress, mega pants, fire pants, the lazy shell,
and the ghost map.
Cheater, not cheating yet, Bowser's not in the game.
30 coins, let's do it.
Hooray, I'll get everything ready for you.
This is a laugh out loud moment.
Morning, now wasn't that a cushy bed?
Thanks, guy.
Welcome to the item shop.
All I have is mid mushrooms, how many do I have?
Five, I'm gonna probably need,
I have so much junk in here.
Royal syrup is like a full pick me up eraser.
Probably use that soon.
Yoshi cookie, I haven't used it.
The bright card, what the hell am I,
I gotta get rid of these three.
I gotta go to the mushroom guy after this.
Pure water, yeah, I'll get rid of this.
I'm not gonna use it, that's why I care.
I got some Maxmo, I'm gonna get a couple mid mushrooms
just in case I don't use peach.
Mid mushroom, maple syrup, but that's all right.
Nah, that's fine, that's good, that's good, we're fine.
All right, we've got a pretty cool collection over here.
If you didn't know,
here's a little bit of a gamer trivia.
Here's the Star Fox, the Star Fox, the Arwing, cool.
Then you got F-Zero, pretty cool.
And I don't know what this is, I have no idea.
What's the one on the way to the right?
Metroid ship, I don't think I've ever seen
what the outside of the Metroid ship looks like.
I didn't really play that much Metroid, I really didn't.
I was a fan of some of it, but not all of it.
What?
I don't know, I just tried to pretend
I cared about that franchise, but I do,
but I don't, but I do, because it's a cool franchise.
All right, here we go, first try.
Uh-oh.
It's Yoshi, it's Fire Yoshi, the Tsar Dragon.
Why do I have two saves?
Because I freaked out.
I did play Metroid Prime,
but I couldn't play very much of it,
or else I didn't dodge that.
All right, here we go,
I'm gonna do Ultra Flame on the Flame Dragon,
that would be a stupid idea.
I'm going for it, 30 jumps right now.
I'm getting close.
Tsar means emperor in Russian.
Oh, 240 damage.
Holy shit, that's a lot.
I'm gonna get it.
Here we go, let's get it.
Oh, Fire-type having a Water-type move, stupid.
Damn it, it's so hard.
Fuck, you're never gonna get between 15 and 20.
It takes this hyper-Zen-like way to focus.
Imagine doing a hundred of those.
I didn't block that again.
All right, come on, please.
I don't understand.
I'm doing it like the second it hits,
like, d-d-d-d-d-d, d-d-d-d-d-d-d, d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d.
What's the most I had?
20?
That was good, I just got that out of the way.
All right.
God damn it, I'm getting so mad about this.
It's so ridiculous.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Okay, I'm gonna take my headphones out.
It can be super jump, too.
All right, headphones coming out.
I'm just doing it by sight only.
That didn't work, that was not good.
That didn't work.
It's all right, I don't care.
No, I just healed myself.
What the fuck?
I can't do it without the,
I gotta put the headphones back in, shit, man.
That's so hard.
It's 15 every fucking time.
One thing I've never achieved in this game is that
I've never been able to do it.
I'm gonna jump, I'm gonna like jump with the motherfucker,
I swear to God.
Get fit with Mario.
Here we go.
No, I can't even do it.
I used all my points.
Desperately trying to achieve it.
374, that's insane.
I did it.
Got the star.
Getting close.
Only one more to go.
I'll be taking that, thank you.
Huh?
We got the star.
Now we're amazing.
We're unbeatable.
We're gorgeous.
You better leave now, chumps.
Get back here.
Hey, Red, look down there.
That's gonna be the ugliest mustache I've ever seen.
Ew, gross.
That guy's worse looking than that Claude Mario.
That is Mario, you idiot.
Listen, everyone.
We gotta get this star to the blade immediately.
We'll deal with Mario later.
Hey, Red, careful with this.
You're all thumbs.
Where's the blade?
He'll be here.
Are you sure?
Relax, people.
Mario's here.
He's too late.
Now where's the blade?
Shut up already.
Wrong voice.
Finally.
We fight for evil.
We live for disorder.
We like what we do.
We struggle for chaos.
We are.
This star piece gives people hope.
It needs to be destroyed.
That was all five of them talking at the same time.
Oh, well, that's funny.
Geno Blast.
All right, who we going for?
Let's go for Green.
Oh, Geno's dead.
Oh shit, a healer.
A healer.
Boom.
I'm back.
My pick me ups are specifically for Peach.
He's dead.
He's going to hit him again.
Don't do it.
All right, I need a group hug.
He's dead again.
Bad.
Very bad.
We're just going to pick me up.
I have to.
I'm going to Geno Blast again.
That would have probably killed him.
All right, let's go.
Geno Flash.
Let's fucking just burn them all up.
Let's take out like two or three.
Sleeping?
It's all right, group hug.
Yo, Red.
What?
I broke my shades.
Served you right.
Hey, Red.
What?
I've got a headache.
You're totally out of shape.
Bad leader.
This insults his team.
This is not good.
It's OK.
Do I have any able juices?
Hey, Lucky Jewel.
No, no, no, no.
Not until I'm almost done.
We can take out a pink.
Just one punch to knock it out.
Because I'm not sure what to do.
Red.
What?
My makeup's running.
Then change brands.
Ultra Flame.
Let's do it on a yellow shit brand.
All right, get out of there, Peach.
Come on.
Mario can't do this on his own.
In fact, Mario can't do this on his own.
So Mario's going to do a mid mushroom.
Body slam.
Now he's done.
Peach, please.
Peach, recover.
Thank you.
Come on back.
The timing on that plant hit there.
Should be it for you.
Hey, yo, Red.
What?
I'm hungry.
Chew on your tongue.
All right, you guys really are in like shambles as a group.
No, zero, good.
And enough.
Now I'm angry.
It's time to finish this.
Formation, halt.
Here we go.
After a transformer here.
God, I fucking psyched myself up.
Force beam energized.
Maximum charge.
Now fire the breaker.
Breaker beam.
I feel like, I think I'm going to miss this step.
I almost won.
He kills everybody.
We got Rupok coming up.
Did I do it?
How many was that?
How many?
Is that what?
Did I do it?
Is that 30?
I did it.
36?
Oh, shit.
All right.
Nice.
Wow.
I did it.
Now get 100.
That's the next step.
You have to just like zone out.
Are we at full health?
I don't know.
This might kill everybody.
Did everybody heal?
All right, that was pretty bad.
Peach may be the best character in the game.
Recharging.
I wonder, let me just do like a genoflash or something.
No, that's probably not going to do much.
Let's keep doing basic attacks.
145 damage each time.
That says really good.
Everyone's at full health.
There it is.
This isn't possible.
We are invincible.
Can this be happening to the Axum Rangers?
What?
17 experience.
Hang in there, Axum Rangers.
Why are you on the backup?
And then those seven combine into one.
And then you need to do that six more times.
Six star pieces have finally been collected.
Where could that last star piece be?
All right.
Now we can do a couple of things.
There's one or two things I need to clean up first
before we continue on to the end game.
All I need to go to, where's the mushroom guy?
Which town was mushroom guy in?
Moleville?
Merrymore?
I don't remember.
Seaside town?
I think it's seaside town.
Am I going to get the lazy shell?
I think it was over here, because it was the other side this way.
Mushroom boy.
You have any mushrooms?
I do.
Hey, you don't have any mushrooms.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Is this the guy?
I could have.
OK.
I guess I don't have mushrooms.
I thought.
Let's see if we can make you look a little more snazzy.
No, let's not.
So I'm just going to get rid of these then.
I thought you could be sitting here.
I know I can do something in Moleville.
I'm right.
I think I can, there's my egg, right?
The mystery egg now I can give to this guy.
I can sell something to him.
Good to see you again.
I'll show you my inventory.
A metal plate.
Don't know what it's used for, but I'll sell it for 300 coins.
I'll take it.
Nice doing business with you.
That's all I got.
I think that is, there it is.
The frying pan.
There's Peach's best weapon, I believe.
PUBG frying pan.
I think that's all I can do here.
This guy doesn't have anything else.
I have no inventory.
Am I going to fight the Final Fantasy boss?
Yes.
The carbo, I remember this is incredibly convoluted.
The carbo cookie.
You actually can get a carbo cookie.
You go through this really annoying process to get a carbo cookie.
It's like trading a bunch of shit and getting rid of money.
You give it to this little kid and nothing interesting happens.
You actually can just, I mean, spoiler alert.
She gets off the bucket and then you can go in the bucket.
And I think it just takes her to the river.
I forget how to even do the carbo cookie.
Would you like a shiny stone?
No.
It means you helped her.
Figure it out.
Hold on.
I've got to keep the game progression going.
If you help her, it sets up fireworks.
Oh yeah, the end credits.
If you do the five secrets right.
All right, let's go up here.
Let's do this.
You're an idiot.
All right, let's sell some stuff.
Let's restock and get on with it, right?
Imagine I sold that.
That's the thing about these old games on old consoles.
If I would have accidentally just pressed A,
I would have to reload and save.
Mega pants.
Get rid of these.
Keep the work pants in case I want to.
Buzzy, buzzy, buzzy.
Where else these can stay?
Mid-mushroom.
Breathe, breathe.
I'll get another maple syrups.
I want at least two pick me ups because you've got to be careful.
Give Peach the lazy shell.
I'm begging you.
How about sell the damn lazy shell if you don't have patience with me?
30 jumps, all right.
I've got to go back to Montreux Town.
You won't do it.
No, I won't because that's the crutch.
If I can't beat Kulex, I just can't seem to find the casino.
I'm so tired.
I've been walking around all day.
Hey, he's holding a leaflet.
Do you want to read it?
Come to Great Guy Casino.
Three jumps and a bright card will get you in.
Sorry, but no chomps allowed.
Three jumps, a bright card, and no chomps.
What is this?
I already know that.
Thanks, Colbert.
Guys, Colbert, bullshit.
Let's go back to Montreux Town and get our item for doing 30 jumps.
And then we have to do 100.
No, I don't want to go in there.
I don't want to go in there.
Don't go in there.
I heard your record for jumping stands at 35 right now.
Wow, you did it.
You made it over 30 jumps.
Here's your prize, a tack scarf.
This thing is insane, by the way.
Look at this thing.
So comfy, it'll make you jump.
Now, feather or, do you know, I like speed on G.
Actually, speed on Peach is better because you can just do more stuff.
Now, the real impossible destructive play here
is a tack scarf, lazy shell.
Where's the lazy shell?
I sold it.
I sold it, and I saved the game.
Oh, my god.
What do you got for a ghost medal?
Maybe I should give the ghost medal to Gino.
Because the ammo is kind of old at this point.
Let's give.
Yeah, let's do it.
Hey, thank you, JermaSucks, for the five community subs.
Appreciate that.
Thanks, and five subs.
Ooh, you know what I can do, though?
Here's what I can do.
It's sensei time.
I think I might be OK.
This might be worth trying again.
Because I've leveled up like four or five times.
You also get another insane item.
Let's try this again.
You wish to challenge me?
Yes.
Let's see if I can do it.
106, good.
That's a good start.
Frying pan.
Zero, that's good.
Oh, fuck.
All right, it didn't instantly kill him.
That's good.
That's certainly not a bad thing.
I have enough to take one hit.
Mario's going to be the one doing all the damage.
I missed it.
Sorry.
Triple kick.
Zero, good.
Perfect blocks.
Perfect.
Let's see how much damage she does.
That's not good at all.
All right, we're going to have to play supportive roles here.
And we're going for 100 jumps right now.
I'm going to get it right now, guaranteed.
I was just talking, and that's why I bumped it up.
We just gave a lot of subs.
Hold on.
Nocturne.
Thank you, Nocturne, Aceturne, for the 20 community subs.
Thank you.
That's a huge sub drop.
Thanks a lot.
Congratulations to all of you that got one.
Really appreciate that, though.
That's a shit load of subs.
A lot of people are fucking subbing.
Even just like tier one.
I know we make the jokes about the whole September thing,
but there's a lot of people that sub today already.
Just straight up.
So thank you, guys.
Guaranteed here it is fucking knocking the fuck around.
Damn it, I fucking had it.
You know what I have to do?
I have to lean back in my fucking chair.
I got to lean back in my chair and just stare at the wall.
I'm going to try it each time.
Let's see if I can get close.
If I can do over 50.
No, there's no way I'm going to do 100.
I'm leaning fucking back.
Nope, not in the zen mode.
That one frame, I got to catch it.
How did I do 30 fucking 5?
It's very hard.
Yeah, it is.
240.
Uh-oh, good thing I had those pick-me-ups,
because that's why I wanted them.
Just get rid of it.
I'm not going to waste the materials.
Simply amazing.
You are stronger, champion.
No doubt about it.
My reputation was staked on this last fight.
So I've lost the title of Sensei.
From today, you are the Sensei of this dojo.
Please take this belt, which only the highest ranking
fighter in the dojo can wear.
Good.
Good for you.
You did it.
You got a jinx belt.
Nice job.
We will rename the dojo Mario Style Dojo
and incorporate your jump technique into the training.
Jacker and I will start our training immediately.
1,000 warm-up jumps.
Ready?
Peek-in!
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun.
That's so cute.
All right, so now we have the jinx belt,
which is a huge amount of attack and defense.
Probably better than both of these.
I wonder if the feather is better than the true feather.
Give her the shell.
No.
Give it to her right now.
I'm not.
Just wait.
We don't need it yet.
You want me to break the game?
I'll break the game eventually, but we're
doing a blind playthrough supported by 500 attempts
where I was a 500 times.
All right, let's get out of here.
I got my jinx belt.
Cleaned up the stuff in the dojo here.
Got the attack scarf, so I am good to go.
OK.
It's time to go to the final arc of the video game.
I'm encroaching on the final probably hour or two.
Depends on how badly I get destroyed by cure.
That's such an ENFP thing to say.
I have no idea what the flying buck you're talking about.
But all right, let's go talk to the king.
ENFP pants.
ENFP pants moment.
And we did it.
What was this voice again?
Mom, Dad, were you able to find the star, dear?
Yeah, the Axe and Rangers took it away from us,
but we got it back again.
Well, that was much wonderful.
Now the star, oh, starting, can be repaired, right?
I guess not, you.
Still missing a piece, I think.
The last star?
Wait, the only place left to look is in Bowser's Keep.
Yeah, we know, but there's no way to get in.
Believe me, we tried.
Yes, yes, even Mario can't jump that far.
All right, I'll let you use.
That's it, dear.
You should use the royal bus.
Yes, well, the time has come for you two to make the bus.
Why, when I was your age.
Really, are you sure it's all right?
Of course, dear, I've ordered the repairman
to have it fixed by the time you leave.
You simply have to help Mario and the others
get that last star.
You bet, mom.
Come on, Mario, let's go.
500 male voices, one female voice.
Yeah, all right, how do I rectify that?
I have, I, it's either this, this, this, this.
Well, I, what do you want me to do?
This, wow, hi, hey, it's me, fucking hey.
I'm apparently doing a female voice right now.
We know what to do.
The bus has finally been repaired.
We can start operating again.
Prince Malo, we want you to go to Bowser's Keep.
Could you give us a little piece?
I've heard the story from King Nimbus.
You'll be there in no time.
Here it comes, here it comes.
How's the engine running?
It's pouring like a kid.
Did you take Prince Malo to the entrance of Bowser's Keep?
Of course.
I can't wait to get this thing running again.
Come, Prince, hop on board.
All aboard.
We're off.
That's just Pac-Man with the mustache on,
and he rips it off, and it goes, ding.
Pac-Man joins the battle.
Are they going to make it?
I'm trying to figure out more voices to do.
You know what I mean?
Ah, the scent of boiling lava.
It's so nice to be home.
Smithy's going to pay for stealing
my splendid castle from me.
Boom.
So pumped up.
Everyone's so leveled up and pumped up, I love it.
Why did you tell Nintendo to put Sans in Smash?
As the last time I used my Twitter,
I was talking about how I dropped my fucking pajama
pants drawstrings in the toilet.
When did I do this?
When did you think I did this?
I'm going to go dodge.
Ooh, find me.
Here comes the launch.
All right, here we go.
Catapult.
How much does it just get locked in?
I don't want to miss any secrets.
Ooh, zero.
Oh, I want to get it so bad, but I've never
been able to do it in my whole life.
I've never been able to do it.
It's so sad that I can't do it.
All right, let me try again.
Damn it.
Every time I get to 16, my finger just goes, do it quicker.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, it's so hard.
Because Mario just starts to blend into your brain
after like 20, 30 times.
37.
All right, I'm going to try it one more time.
Oh, no fucking way.
I can only press a button on one frame.
37 fucking times in row before I lose my mind.
What was that, an item?
What did I get?
I'm just going to throw this shit away in a minute.
Do the sound alone?
I'll try sound alone again.
I actually had the headphones out for that one when I did 37.
Croco.
Uh-oh.
Hey, Mario, did you remember to use a save point?
There's plenty of danger up ahead, so it's best to save now.
You need anything?
I got some items to sell.
The heel turn.
The heel to face turn.
Chat, don't tell them his webcam is on.
That would be fucking funny.
It's just on.
All right, I'm getting rid of these.
Paper syrup.
All right, I'm going to get some testing case.
Yeah, all right.
All right.
The webcam is on.
Your webcam is on.
It's pointed at your mushy feet.
Mushy feet?
What the fuck?
I don't even know what that's supposed to mean.
Welcome to There Are Six Doors.
Do you need an explanation?
Sure, why not for all of you.
Of the six doors, two open into action courses.
You can handle a lot of action, right?
Two others will lead you to battle courses.
And you're good at fighting, right?
The last two open into puzzle courses.
No sweat for a great puzzle solver like you, right?
Good puzzle solver.
Once you choose a course, there's no turning back.
You get only one way.
The only way to know what's behind a door
is to walk through it.
You must pass four of the six courses to move on.
Good luck.
You're going to need it, I know.
Trust me.
Which door do you want me to do?
This is actually going to be harder than I thought.
All right, let's do fuck.
Actually, I don't know if we can do this.
Because I can't really zoom in.
Because this is going to be a pain in the ass,
but I'm going to do it.
There you go.
Where are we going?
Which door?
Choose wisely.
What are you guys clicking?
What are you doing?
All right, looks like we're going five.
Into five we go, but now I have to fix this.
This is what I was afraid of.
Okay, five.
Hey, hey, hey, it's me, the quiz master.
And it's quiz time.
So you need an explanation.
I'll give you 12, count them, 12 questions.
If you're right, the block you're standing on
will move up one.
But if you blow it, you got down two.
You have five seconds.
If you can't answer, you'll move down.
Reach the eighth step within 12 questions, and you've won.
Do you got it?
Johnny loves which beverage?
Curators.
What's the password in the sunken ship?
Pearls.
The man getting his picture taken at Marymoor hates what?
Getting his picture taken.
Where was the third star piece found?
Moleville, Forest Bays, Star Hill, Moleville.
The boy getting his picture taken at Marymoor
can't wait till which season?
Uh-oh, skiing.
Who was the famous composer at Tadpole Pond?
That would be Todoth Skiing.
What technique does Bowser learn at level 15?
Uh, crusher.
What's the chef's name at Marymoor?
Torch.
Well done.
I guess that was just a warm up for you, huh?
All right.
Let's see how well you can count.
I'll give you 10 seconds.
10, tell me the number of barrels in the room.
Close your eyes for a second.
Are you ready?
OK, here we go, here we go, 10 seconds.
Go.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
16, right?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 16, 15.
Correct.
But this is just a warm up.
Next.
Now we'll see if you can really count.
You've got 20 seconds.
Ready?
1, 2, 3, 3, 6, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37,
43, 44, 45, 46, 46, final answer.
Piece of cake.
Now for something completely different.
Boo, Goo, Bones, and Kip completed in a triathlon.
The triathlon included swimming, cycling, and a marathon.
It's up to you to guess which place each person came in.
Listen well, you're only going to hear the story once.
I came in third place for swimming.
So Boo, third place for swimming.
Goo, I out-rode Bones on my bike and Bones was never able to pass me.
Okay.
Boo, third swimming.
Goo passed Bones on cycling.
And Bones was never able to pass.
I fell into fourth place during the bike race,
but finally ended up in the same place as I did in the swimming event.
Okay, so this is third, hold on.
I fell into fourth place during the bike race,
finally ended up in the same, so he was in fourth place,
fourth of the bike race.
Goo was third place in the bike race.
He might have been second though,
just because he didn't pass him doesn't mean anything.
But finally ended up in the same, okay, what about the fish?
I placed the same in the swimming and cycling events,
but two others beat me in the marathon.
I came in third for swimming.
I fell into fourth, okay.
So he's fourth in both.
So he's in fourth place.
He's in third place for swimming.
Oh, Bones is my bike, okay.
What did you do?
So you're first.
No, two others beat me in the marathon.
Are you first?
I fell into fourth place during the bike race,
but finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
But finally ended up in the same place
But what did you put up with the marathon?
I think the fish is first or second.
Two others beat me in the marathon.
So what did you go in the marathon?
What did you do in the marathon?
We only have one piece of evidence for the marathon.
Two others, yeah, two others beat me.
So you're in either third or fourth place.
For the marathon, that's the only information we have.
So who won the marathon?
Hold on, I'm gonna draw this.
I have to draw this.
Give me one second.
I actually do have to like write this out.
I have to put this on another monitor though.
Okay, so let's go back here.
I don't wanna lose this,
because I'll lose and I don't wanna restart it.
Okay, so let's do, let me get this right.
Let's get paint captured so you can see it.
Not as well.
Paint, okay, here.
All right, so we got three events, right?
So we have this marathon, swimming,
marathon and cycling.
Why is this so huge?
Okay, that's fine.
So swimming, so Boo came in third for swimming.
So we're gonna do this.
One, two, two.
Okay, so swimming.
So this is Boo.
Boo came in third place for swimming.
I outrode Bones on my bike
and Bones couldn't pass me in cycling.
Okay, I fell into fourth place during the bike race.
Okay, but finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event, fourth place.
I hate this fucking trick question wording,
but finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
What do I mean as I did in the swimming event?
I was in fourth place during the bike race,
but finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
But where did you place in the swimming event?
We don't know that.
So no, then you're in fourth,
you have to be in second place then.
Just because you fell into fourth place, doesn't,
so Goomba wins, Goomba won the cycling.
There's no other alternative.
It's a trick question bullshit.
And then so you're second place in the swimming event.
So there we go, okay.
So Bones, I placed the same
in the swimming and cycling events.
Hold on, I gotta fucking move these.
These are all fucked up.
I placed the same in the swimming and cycling events.
So you're third place.
So Boo, no, Boo's third place in swimming.
So you'd have to be last place.
So Bones was not last place in the cycling event.
So this is, so the two fish came in the last
in swimming and cycling.
But Bones said he was in last place.
No, I fell into fourth place during the bike race,
but I finally ended up in the same place
that I didn't, so you didn't, you didn't, not in fourth place.
What is, I came in third for swimming, that's it.
We know that.
Okay, I outrode, I placed the same
in the swimming and cycling events, but, okay.
Two others beat me in the marathon.
So you have to, you have to be here.
One of these two places.
Two people beat you.
One of these two.
Baby, I got Bones here.
Bones is second in swimming and cycling.
If he was fourth, who would be the fourth?
So then Bones is down here.
How do I get, I have to delete that.
That's fucking me up.
But then who was fourth in cycling?
Did you win the swimming event?
So we got fish would be last in cycling
because, and then, so you'd be last in swimming too.
Fish won swimming because he's a fish.
That doesn't, that's not how this works.
Fish is definitely gonna be last in swimming.
So here you go, we've deduced it.
So then now, boo, I got cycling done.
Use Excel instead.
I don't even have Excel.
Fish is last in swimming.
I'm telling you, it's correct.
Let me see.
Fish.
I got, let me just look at it.
Fish is, he had that, fish is there.
Is everybody there three times?
He's a fish, he, but that doesn't matter.
All right, I'm gonna, I think I got it.
Call me the master, okay.
In the order they came in.
This is for the, okay.
Let's just fucking guess.
I looked it up and I Googled it and it was wrong.
I Googled it, there was a Reddit thread and I,
it was wrong, the Reddit thread was wrong.
Mario won't get up.
Why won't Mario get up?
Okay, imagine cheating and losing.
Okay, let's do it again.
I gotta do all this shit again.
Cycling was the second event, yeah.
Just get this off the fucking screen.
What's the first monster you see in the pipe vault?
I don't know, I don't remember.
Sparky, I think.
All right, this is, I gotta move this back to normal.
This is why I didn't wanna resize anything.
What is Rainy's husband's name?
Raz, yeah.
Yardovich is what?
A breed of cattle, a boss.
What technique does Bowser learn at level 15?
That would be crusher.
Fit to screen, I don't wanna do that
because it's capturing.
I'll show you what happens if I do that.
Fit to screen does this
because it is a old game being pulled through HDMI.
The wonders of technology.
What the fuck is it doing now?
Okay, what's the name of the sunken ship?
Johnny.
What does Balon really like to turn people into?
Scarecrows.
A man getting his picture taken.
A merry boy hates what?
Getting his picture taken.
Who is the leader of the Axum Rangers?
Red.
Hey.
All right, we gotta do more counting, I think.
Time to count.
Wait, I already did this, right?
Yeah, I know this one.
Oh, I think he's gonna change it up.
Isn't it the same number, though?
13.
Was it 13?
Was it 13 or 14?
Oh, fuck, I think it was 14.
Okay, I didn't count the one under here.
Ha ha ha.
All right, I'm ready.
43.
43, 44.
44?
I think it's 44?
Yeah.
Ha, here we are again.
Oh no, wait, they changed.
I outrode Kip on my bike
and Kip was never able to pass me.
I came in third for swimming.
No, it's the same thing.
It's just different people.
I fell into fourth place during the bike, see?
Oh, the fish is in first place for swimming.
No.
Okay, Kip is the fish.
I fell into fourth place during the bike race
but finally ended up in the same place
I did in the swimming event.
I'm not cheating, you can't cheat.
Just guess, there's a one in four chance.
No, there's not, it's like a one in fucking,
like 32% chance.
I don't have Excel.
I can't use Excel, I don't own it.
Okay, here we go, I'm gonna do this one.
I'm going for it, here we go.
This is where, here we go.
I came in third for swimming.
I'm just gonna write it, it doesn't matter.
It's easy for me to do it like this.
This is goo.
Third for swimming, that's all I need to know right now.
Don't need to care about anything else.
I placed the same in the swimming and cycling events
but two of them beat me in the marathon.
Two people beat you in the marathon.
So that means you have to be in third place
for the marathon, you have to be.
If two people beat you in the marathon, that's two and one.
Bones, you're number three in the marathon.
Got it, locked in.
I mean, no.
Three people would have beat you in the marathon
if you were in fourth place.
What are you talking about?
That's locked in.
Okay, let's get some more info.
I fell into fourth place during the bike race
but I finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
Bike race, so fourth place in the bike race.
Wait, what did Abu do?
I outrode Kip on my bike and Kip could never pass me.
I was in fourth place in the cycling event
but I finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
Where did you end up in the swimming event?
Fourth, third, fourth or second?
Probably second then, right?
You had to be second.
That makes sense.
So now we've got this info.
All right, nice.
Okay, now, what do you mean no?
No, second in the marathon, second in the marathon, right?
Yeah, I wrote it in the wrong place.
Everybody settle down.
I wrote it in the wrong place
but I finally ended in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
Second fucking place, fourth place?
I think he is in second place.
All right, hold on, what about Bones?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, what about Boo?
I outrode Kip on my bike and Kip,
so you're in first place or second place.
Boo has to be in first place, you have to be.
So Boo is in first place in cycling.
That means Kip.
Boo could also be second.
Let's just do that.
So Kip had to get second.
So why is everybody screaming at me?
Kip was fourth in cycling.
What?
We are dumb.
No, what?
Kip was, yeah, Kip was second.
I'm going with this.
Kip is second in everything.
I agree.
So that leaves us, what the hell did Bones do?
I placed the same in the swimming and cycling events.
So fourth place.
He says he's, no, no, look, look, look.
I fell into fourth place.
Don't listen to that bullshit.
That is a trick.
I fell into fourth place during the bike race
but I finally ended up in the same place
as I did in the swimming event.
That is a fake bullshit.
Come on, I'm trying.
Look at it.
That's what it says.
It's a fake out.
Don't believe it.
Now you got me all messed up.
Where am I going?
Bones.
I placed the same in the swimming and cycling events.
What did we have them over here?
Okay.
Two others beat me in the marathon.
So swimming and cycling events.
So you're in last place.
Because then,
Goo, what'd you do, Goo?
I came in third for swimming.
So yeah, you came in third here too.
He can't.
I outrode Kip on my bike.
Okay.
I placed in the same,
I placed the same.
It's a 50-50.
Two others beat me in the marathon.
Yeah.
One, two.
Not one, two, three.
All right.
Who is in first place in the marathon then?
It has to be Boo.
No.
I think it is Boo.
I think it's Boo, Kip, Bones,
and then Goo.
I think that's it.
I think that's correct.
I'm going for it.
Boo, Kip, Bones, Goo.
Yeah!
Correct.
You got a rock candy.
Lame.
All right.
Time for a new door.
We might need that again.
For every percentage that clicks on number five,
one minute is deducted from the final amount
of time I stream tonight.
Just making sure you guys are aware of this.
That's what includes Mario as well.
Here we go.
At least 28 minutes.
50, 60, 70.
Okay.
Again, more than an hour is being removed from the stream.
57 total minutes have been deleted
from the end of the stream.
That means it's been about four hours.
If I was going to stream for like six, six and a half,
I'm only streaming fucking five.
30, 40.
All right.
Okay.
For one time only.
So that was over 50 minutes that you guys just deleted.
If 100% of you click on Mario's nose,
I will negate what just happened.
It has to be 100%.
Some people just want to watch the world burn.
10%.
What a great experiment.
10% of all people clicking.
I mean, you're talking about 10% of people.
Just like, yeah.
Chaos Cartage.
Trolls.
Okay.
Try it again, but this time pick one.
Actually give me a majority here, please.
People were spamming.
Okay.
Well, we're going in number two.
Number two it is.
Thank you for voting.
Two.
Oh, this is a fight one.
You have to fight for everything.
I feel like it's been so long since I've attacked anybody.
Once again, once again, once again.
Do it again.
Let me do a revote.
I accidentally clicked on the follow button.
Well, it's a good thing you accidentally clicked
on the follow button,
because that's how you're able to chat.
So it's good that you did that.
Unfollow.
Hey, 21.
You know what?
I'm just going to save myself for like 30 seconds to do that.
It was going to be that.
It was.
It was just going to be that.
Guys, that has happened 20 times in a row.
Do you really think that this is going to be the one outlier
where they don't, the 21st time.
It's not going to be power.
No way.
26, nothing.
Can't block that.
Once again, the screen's a little cut off.
I'll fix it in a second.
This is why I didn't want to restart.
I'm not, I'm just going to pick next door.
The next door is streamer's choice.
It's upside down.
Mic muted.
Oh, I definitely shouldn't scream into it then.
The four keys are enraptured.
The four keys have come to their senses.
I got to heal after this.
Shall I just do it now?
Peek mic, peek mic, peek mic.
Okay, I'll peek the mic for your birthday.
How's that sound?
It is my birthday.
No, that, the person that said that,
whenever their birthday is.
And I know that, I already know that person's birthday.
Because I remember their comment from July
saying it's my birthday, dude.
And I was like, happy birthday.
So now for next July.
Got to wait until July.
Yeah, I don't want to peek my mic.
I don't like peeking my mic.
It hurts people's ears.
Princess Peach has reached 19.
All right.
Just getting it over with.
So I got a question for you guys.
So if I ever did a stream where I peeked the mic,
like, and it was a full peak for like four seconds.
And then I sampled that peak
and made it four and a half hours long.
How many viewers would that stream have?
Would that stream have more or less than a thousand people
there?
Less than a thousand?
I think that would be at,
I don't think that would have more than 350 people there.
I just sit in there listening to that.
You could just mute.
Yeah, you could, nevermind.
You would come to that,
you would open that stream and it immediately
hit the mute button.
It'd be like, oh, let's go, let's go.
Hey, let me check out,
let me check out German 985, it's a live stream.
That sounds like a cool idea.
Just, I'm just opening the webpage right now.
Ah!
The fuck, man.
That was fucking stupid.
That is how long it would take.
Oh, sorry, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's get this correct.
Hold on.
Oh, let's get a, let's get a good representation of this.
Just give me something.
All right, what?
It's like Samsung phones, right?
What's the current Samsung ad that plays on Twitch?
Everybody has an ad block.
You can't tell me what the current ad is.
Whatever, this will do.
This will do, who cares?
All right, back.
New viewer.
Ah!
Wait, you guys didn't get the joke there?
All ads are broken.
You can't close them,
and half of them are fucking muted or way too loud.
Explain it again.
Okay, so you see, for some reason.
No, no, no, I wanted to super jump, what the fuck?
Explain the joke, Peter.
All right, I'll give you a joke.
Watch this.
God damn it, I'm fucking so mad.
Why are you doing this?
Why is it so hard to do this?
It's so fucking hard to do that.
What, I get 37 one time?
You super, that was super jump.
That wasn't super, I thought that was super jump.
That wasn't super jump?
That's super jump.
Why, why God?
Tell me, I want an answer, God.
God, I'm trying this one more time,
and no, I'm not, nevermind.
What am I trying to do?
I'm trying to jump with super jump
a hundred times on somebody.
The game changes the timings
based on how many times you've done it in a row.
So, for instance,
if, you know, jump one through 10 is the same.
Jump like 12 to 20 is different,
and then like jump like 18 or 20 to like a hundred
is one frame.
11 is tricky.
And the game is 60 FPS.
Yeah, it is.
My God, why is it doing it now?
How do I go from doing 37 of these
to I can't even do more than 10 now?
What?
I'm gonna listen to a fucking tutorial.
I need to do this.
Why is the audio coming out of my dumb,
stupid, shitty BenQ monitor?
That's not fair.
BenQ is like, I like this monitor.
I really like this monitor.
Okay, hold on.
Why, what happened to my sound effects?
Why do I have no sound?
No, that's gonna get, that's gonna,
look, Mario does power.
G-Note, I, what is it doing this for?
Why, I don't understand.
I don't understand what's changed.
This is making me rabidly angry, by the way.
Did you just heal?
I'm gonna turn, I'm gonna hit it as fast as I can.
That's not gonna help it.
I guarantee, it's not gonna help it.
Whatever.
I do have the Lazy Shell, but it's cheating.
I only cheat versus Q-Legs.
Or, you know, whatever.
Maybe I'll just put it on.
I got a lot of health.
Holy shit, I should've done Lucky.
All right, I'm going against, I'm going against it here.
I'm doing Bowser HP.
I'm sorry, it's my turn.
Bingo, we got Drill Claw.
That is Bowser's best weapon.
Bowser, it can now come back into the party.
Bowser has the Lazy Shell.
We're also gonna give Bowser, give Peach the Shell.
I want Bowser to have the most damage.
All right, this is okay, all right.
It's time.
All right, everybody relax, settle down.
Time, Gino's gonna take a break.
Bowser's back.
Bowser has the Drill Claw.
Bowser also is gonna put on the Work Pants.
And I want Bowser to do such an insane amount of damage.
I want the Attack Scarf on Bowser.
Oh, you can't wear it, Bowser, what?
Really?
Ruins my whole plan.
Let's give the XP Booster to, let's give it to Gino.
Oh, Jinx Belt, there we go, yeah.
You can put on the XP Booster, Gino.
There we go.
Bowser's now insane.
Lazy Shell is not going on just yet.
Give her the shell, give her the shell,
give her the shell, give her the shell,
give her the shell.
No, no, I can't.
All right, can you guys click these from here?
Let's find out, hold on.
Can you guys make it from here?
Just try, just try.
Make it pinpoint, be very accurate.
Pretty good accuracy, 17% on six,
but what is it on between three and four?
Well, what is it, what is it?
9% want me to leave.
And it looks like that's a giant circle on four.
That's what I'm gonna have to go with that one.
That's a giant circle on four.
Thank you for voting.
More combat.
All right, we got, do I have any AOE?
Peach has AOE, right?
Yeah, that was terrible.
350 damage.
Oh yeah, Bowser is scaring the monsters.
It's Bowser, run!
Cowards.
Bowser, one hit kill, let's see.
Oh, damn it, it's close.
You have more than 500 HP.
Do you?
Now Bowser's minions aren't very loyal, unfortunately.
How do you miss?
How do you punch a ghost?
You know what, you got me.
You got me, it's true.
What?
Oh, it's the other, it's the wrong one.
Wrong one, Jerry, wrong one.
Let's see, then get them all.
100 coins, whoa.
Again, no, that was so bad.
I can't even fucking believe it.
Is the FPS going up and down like crazy or something?
Well, that's an excuse.
Oh, it absolutely is.
I'm trying to make up excuses as to why
I can't get that frame.
Why did I get this game?
Because this is one of the top five
best games ever created.
You know, changed my mind.
Not gonna happen.
What are the other four?
Maybe I'll tell you one day.
Diablo 2, Mario RPG, Team Fortress 2,
Chrono Trigger, and The Neverhood.
And if you really want to, bump off The Neverhood,
put in Bloodborne.
It's probably more accurate at this stage.
Bloodborne, yeah, but I truly believe
that Bloodborne is one of the best video games ever made.
I truly believe that, I do.
Now, if only they made it run at 60 FPS
and put it everywhere else, then I
think it would probably take that cake.
I would even take a PS4 Pro patch.
What about Super Frog?
Well, Super Frog, no, I'm not gonna go there.
It's the best game that could come out of a cereal box.
No, he's not voting anymore.
No, we're past, we're beyond the voting stage.
Yeah, I got them all.
Star Beep.
Isn't that an emote?
The final fight incoming.
It's against, no, is there another one of these?
No, there isn't, right?
I don't think there is.
Are there three?
Oh, that sucks, I hate that.
Now I have to do it again.
Oh, finally.
Is there another door?
No, it's not.
Star Gun, hey.
Look what I found.
That is Gino's best weapon, the Star Gun.
It goes do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Exactly like that.
All right, there's only one more I have to do.
You don't have very many choices.
You have one, three, or six.
You should be able to click these really fucking easily
because they're so spread out.
Don't want any excuses for this one.
Looks like all the way at the end.
32%.
Okay, number six.
Get, got 10 tries.
Oh, there goes one.
Oh no, and I'm losing money for these too?
Ah, the jump is so far.
Oh no, holy shit, man.
The thing is, there's only one distance you can jump.
Okay, no, okay, I got plenty of coins.
Five chances.
It's all fucking reversed.
Pick me up.
Throw it away.
Am I gonna get camped?
Flower tab.
All right, I gotta bring these guys back here.
Oh, you stupid idiot, come on, what?
Oh, that's bullshit.
What is this?
Max mushroom, get rid of the mid mushroom.
Oh, what is that?
Rock candy.
Getting rid of a mid mushroom.
I'm definitely at 99, 999, 99 coins, right?
Yeah, don't even pick, why would I pick up the coins?
What's the frog coin?
Only frog coins.
Five chances.
Secret.
You missed a secret back in Ancestors.
Nice.
I gotta be a completionist, okay, I got it.
All right, try not to mess this up.
I have five attempts.
Oh, that one's just missed it.
Oh, okay, I gotta be careful,
because god damn it, I knew that was gonna happen.
All right, now the flower tab, good.
All right, this is gonna be tricky.
What's this?
Royal syrup?
Just get rid of a maple syrup.
No, get rid of a mushroom.
Oh, fuck, I hit my head,
and I'm gonna fall all the way down.
It's okay, I gotta get it.
It could be something cool.
Oh my god, fuck you, stupid platforming bullshit.
Oh, okay, what is this?
Ooh, good, get rid of pure water.
These things are worthless.
Sonic symbol.
That is Mallow's greatest weapon.
Sticky glove.
Sonic symbol, nice.
It's time to go.
Save point, nice.
Mallow in.
All right, Mallow in.
Mallow in, Gino in.
Nope, he's fire pants on.
Give him the lazy shell.
I'll give it a try.
This is Smithy's castle.
No trespassers allowed.
That was so much damage.
I wanna see if this does.
I can jump more times with the star
than I came with Mario.
He's dead, stop.
He's violent.
That's my child?
My child?
Uh-oh, he brought a jinx.
Wait, jinx is supposed to be on our team.
That's okay, he's gone.
Come on in, 40.
One more hit, that should be it.
Let's see.
Kamek, raised Bowser.
Hmm, that's, that's meh.
Bajie Koopa.
Huh, where am I?
Bowser, hello.
How have you been?
I made it back here somehow,
but it seems like I've been brainwashed or something.
I can't seem to remember anything.
Have I done something wrong?
Ugh, don't worry about it.
Let's just put it behind us.
It's great running into loyal Koopa Troopa like you.
Oh, I'm glad.
It looks like you've got some tough new troopers now,
but my magic can still help you.
What's this?
This magic treasure books will never run out of coins.
Just keep on hitting it.
I'll be here if you need me.
Come by whenever you need to rejuvenate your HP and magic.
What?
Guys, you'll never know what I found.
You still hanging around?
Oh, you want more items, huh?
Seems I'm in a good mood.
Just remember, I can't always be coming to your rescue,
you know.
If there's anything more you need, best to buy it now.
Well, you certainly have hero shirt, prince pants,
star cape, heel shell, royal dress, get it all.
Hero shirt, bang.
Prince pants, thank you.
Heel shell, star cape, royal dress, lazy shell.
It's time, no it's not, it's time.
You wanna see how crazy this thing is?
Well, you'll see.
We're gonna go with the original three.
What I got for items?
Froggy drink, royal syrup, royal syrup, max mushroom,
max, max, max, I need some more syrups.
I'm getting rid of the braces and the energizer.
And like the pure water and all that crap.
I'm gonna keep this, use it on Culex.
All right, let's get some more royal syrups
or more maple syrups.
That's good.
In fact, I need, I'm probably,
I need the syrups more than I need.
You gotta use Yoshi at some point too.
Yeah, FP is way more important to me.
This is the part of the story where Krakos says, see ya.
Fill me up.
Wait, where's the save point?
I can always, I got plenty of money.
I don't need money for anything anymore.
Oops, there's the lazy shell.
It's just one of those big chunky guys.
Gino level 20.
I'm gonna go.
That's right.
I've selected.
Thank you.
Here we go.
It's time.
We're in Bowser's castle in the throne room.
Ah, so you are the notorious Mario.
I have impressed you made it this far.
I didn't think you could.
Oh, feisty little fellow, aren't we?
But this is the end of the line.
Now you've got to deal with me and God.
This lazy shell, this motherfucker.
Boomer.
Oh, what's that?
You can't even hurt me.
I am unstoppable.
Although I can't hurt you either.
Is this the final boss?
You guessed it.
This is the final encounter of the game.
This is the dastardly villain known as Smithy.
No, the one person.
Okay, good.
That's fine.
Just do the group heal.
Oh shit, that's right.
Her magic is terrible now
because I put the lazy shell on her.
Forgot about that.
Let's do an ultra flame.
Now that you're blue, might as well.
You're blue now.
Oh, another group up.
69.
That's so much damage.
Nice miss.
This is absurd.
I can't be defeated by them.
I won't let this happen.
I will not fall in battle.
Oh, having an attack.
Oh, I don't need your sympathy.
I am a soldier.
I am prepared to go.
Take a dive, Chandelier.
See you later, kids.
Builder.
Oh, poor Builder.
But not to worry.
A little fall isn't gonna hurt you.
All right, Mario.
I'll lead you to the top.
We must hurry to the appointed place.
Hang on tight.
And away we go.
Increasing speed.
Next up, the top floor.
Please fasten your seatbelts.
And wait a second.
There are no seatbelts.
I killed them.
I killed all three of them.
Why didn't they trust me?
I'm a bad guy.
I've been in the castle for fucking the last six months
as a bad person.
Let's go.
The eye is protecting XOR.
One.
They're all so overpowered right now.
I have all the best items in the game.
Well, except for that.
That was painful.
That was very painful.
Yes.
This is the meme boss.
And by meme boss, I mean,
this is the boss that you can kill in less than five seconds.
Gino can kill this boss in less than a second.
I just figured we would,
I don't, you wanna see how,
I wanna play this way.
XOR's protection is gone.
Yes.
You can do 9,999 damage to this boss with Gino.
And everybody knows that.
So, I mean, it's like, that's like a thing.
That's like in every top 10, did you know gaming lists.
It's like number six on every single one of them.
So, I mean, are you really that shocked?
Do you need to see it?
Damn.
That's slow down.
I gotta get rid of the mouth.
All right.
That's bad.
First bad thing that happened.
I mean, you're gonna come back with like 20 health.
Let's do one of Bowser's fun moves.
The crusher.
Oh, that hurts.
Let's do a group hug.
Knock out the, don't, knock the mouth out.
Mouth is annoying.
It does too many moves.
There we go.
You know what, take out the other eye too.
Other eye, come on.
I want the whole thing down.
I wanna shut down his whole computer.
Come on, shut off his whole computer.
You don't stand a chance to me with my best items in the game.
Oh no.
Everyone's fine.
Go for the eye.
Go for the X-Or.
Use Yoshi?
All right.
No.
Let's use Yoshi for the real fight.
You know what I mean?
I'm gonna use, I'm gonna use everything on Kuwait.
I'm gonna use Yoshi now.
Real fight.
Oh shit, I forgot that you guys don't know
you haven't played this game.
I'm sorry.
I just, shit.
Oh shit.
Oh no.
Guys, there's like two more hours in this game.
Uh-oh, gunk ball.
Is everybody alive?
Everybody's fine.
All right, do you want me to reload the save
and kill this boss in one hit?
Sure, why not?
Yeah, that'd be cool.
So, the Gino Whirl timing is like,
I think right when it comes out of his hand, right?
It's like right when the disc comes out of your fingers.
You have to go through boomer and cut scenes again.
Yeah, that's true.
There's a weird timing on it.
It's as it leaves the screen.
So, it's right when it goes boop.
Right when it leaves.
Don't reset?
I won't.
Once I finish the, once I finish everything I wanna do,
maybe I'll, next save that I do
is gonna be a different slot.
And maybe before I end the stream,
we'll just go try and do it.
You know, it'll be one of those after things that we do.
There we go.
I think we're getting to the end of this boss.
Yep.
Sucked up.
Teach level 20.
Swap.
Do you know where this leads to?
It looks like Exor is the contact between the two worlds.
In other words, if we follow this road, we'll find Smithy.
So, what's keeping us?
Hang on.
Hey, I only joined so that I could get my castle back.
I'm not gonna be dragged along on this stupid hunt.
This is as far as I go.
I'm gonna gather my troops and rebuild my castle.
And you, Mario, you're an official member of the Koopa Troop.
It's your duty to help with the repairs.
Bowser, you're completely missing the point.
I ought to rip your stuffin' out.
No, think about it, Bowser.
This sword connects the two worlds, right?
Yeah, so?
Even if we defeat Exor,
there will be other weapon beasts to follow him.
Your castle is at your entrance point to your world.
In short, they'll be back.
Is that what you want?
Uh, well, eh.
More weapon things comin' to take over my castle.
What about my privacy?
Yikes.
This isn't good at all.
In fact, this stinks.
But I can't just be pals with these cretins.
I've got an image to keep up.
Uh, I got it.
No one insults the Koopa Troop and gets away with it.
I've got a bone to pick with this Smithy guy.
Come on, Mario, we'll teach you a lesson.
Bowser needs Nord?
I'm so sly.
It looks like we're together on this one.
Let's-a-go.
VPN.
Oh!
No!
Let's see.
Good thing I have this save,
so we can go from here all the way back to where we were.
ZL, ZR?
What do you mean, ZL, ZR?
Rewind, you're on the classic.
What do you mean, rewind?
I can't rewind.
I didn't mean rewind on the classic.
How do I do that?
Can I rewind on the classic?
Hold Z...
I don't have ZL, ZR.
Hit reset.
What's that?
Save?
Stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hit X.
Rewind?
How far...
Wait, is this for real?
I'm scared.
What does that mean?
Don't listen to one fuck...
If I hit X, what happens?
Don't.
Hit Y, make a save state, just in case.
Okay.
Now, let's rewind.
Is this gonna be fucking bad?
What the hell is happening?
What is going on?
What?
What the fuck?
All right, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, I'm gonna come in.
Here, this...
I'm gonna come in right here.
Right...
You can actually time travel in it.
It records the whole thing.
I didn't know you could do this.
All right, so come in right now.
Wow.
What?
That's insane.
I didn't know you could do that.
That's so cool.
All right, here we are.
I'm good.
You created a time paradox.
No, I didn't.
I came back in the second I was about to create a save,
which therefore would have created a new timeline.
So I came in on the current timeline
and stopped right before a new timeline was created.
Therefore, I'm playing in that last timeline.
I made sure that I did that correct.
The other timeline is doomed.
And we don't care about that one.
We're not in that one.
The other...
You killed the other timeline.
No, that time...
That's scary.
I don't like that.
No, that timeline...
All right, so let me think about this for a second.
So we were walking, we were playing,
and then I needed to go back in time.
So I went back.
So the Mario that was walking forward...
I don't have a PhD.
I'm not gonna be able to do that.
I don't care.
Oh, those of you that are curious,
these little guys here give the most experience
in the whole game.
And there's a place where you can farm them
to get to like the fucking 300 million levels.
Odd.
Rewind every time you miss a jump out of a hundred.
You can't make me do that.
Oh my God.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, 10, 11, 12.
Fuck.
That's too hard to do that.
That's impossible to do that.
No way.
You're creating all bunch of doomed timelines.
Who gives a shit?
One, eight, 10, 11, 12.
It's...
No, no, no.
You fucking idiot.
I'm trying...
Who cares about all these other people?
Can I speed it up?
It's 12, so on 11, I have to come back.
It's gonna work.
This is a lot.
Oh, hold on.
I'm just, I'm connecting timelines.
Three, eight, 12, 13, 14, 15, 18, 19, 20, 22,
25, 26, 27, 28, 29.
I'm coming in.
What was that?
40?
40.
43 jumps.
All right, let's, I gotta count them.
For nine, 40, I'm coming in.
Shit, I lost.
I lost jumps.
Timer in the top, right?
I, yeah, but I did sit here for a second.
Just coming at five seconds.
Okay.
I don't know how many that was.
I don't know, we have to count, right?
I don't know.
That was, I don't know, we have to count, right?
What am I doing?
I gotta get, I have to do this.
I am this far into this?
It's the only way.
Me.
Why can't I just have, why do I have to,
that was 46?
Oh my God.
Just like go make a hamburger or something.
I just come back in five minutes.
Those of you that don't know what's going on,
if you do 100 of these in a row,
you get the best armor in the whole game.
It's like a secret.
Okay, I'm done, I'm done.
I can't, it's impossible.
You're gonna do this shit 100 times in a row.
Create a save state every jump.
Every time I, okay, wait, that's a good idea.
All right, I have to come in and then do what?
Come in and then hit save state the battle part.
Wait, okay, what if I save state right here?
Like I'm gonna hit start, save state.
Oh my God, oh my God.
I'm about to fucking rip the controller out of my hands.
I couldn't do it fast enough.
Save state the battle?
No, I can't do that.
Cause that loses all 46 of these jumps.
Just hold on.
I'm gonna try this.
Did it do it?
It didn't hold.
What happened?
What did I just do?
What just happened?
How do I unlock this?
What?
What the fuck is going on?
I lost 20 jumps.
No, I didn't.
I'm done, I'm done.
I save stated it right here
and I fucking fell off the motherfucker.
No, man, no.
Nope, nope, no.
That's it.
I'm fucking, I'm not doing that.
I don't care if I never see a hundred jumps.
That shit's not, it's fucking impossible.
A hundred frame perfect jumps.
No, uh-uh, I ain't doing it.
I've never done it.
I've never done it once in 15 years.
Ain't gonna do it.
Ah, here's the room by the way.
No, I can't, it's too,
that's too fucking hard to do that.
That's what you said about the fight.
Yeah, but the 5,000 points in the Game Boy game
wasn't coming down from the air,
loading into a save state.
There's Mario's best weapon.
Oh, I do have the lazy shell,
so I don't think it's gonna be,
I don't think it's gonna matter.
No, the ultra hammer.
The lazy shell is better.
Now, that's how everybody does that.
They open up their emulator
and they slow time down to like a 10th of 60 seconds.
And it's just do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
And they can,
it's right when Mario's shoe touches the enemy.
It's Mario.
How did he get in here?
We better do something.
Time is marching on.
Do, reboot.
It's three o'clock, time to recover.
Gotta take out the heads first.
Ah, everyone's good.
Oh, he's destroying every timeline.
Ha ha ha ha.
He's even destroying the clock that controls the time.
I know, I'm a sick fuck, aren't I?
Oh, does Bowser have any other moves?
Fear of roulette.
Oh, it's dinner time.
Don't forget the math puzzles.
What do you mean math puzzles?
Math puzzles?
Time to break.
All right, let's get Peach back.
Doesn't she have the lazy shell?
Yeah, but the lazy shell cannot protect
from instant death, unfortunately.
Come back, Bowser, please.
I can't believe Bowser's fucking dead.
He's dead again.
Oh, by the way, anybody that comes back that says,
oh, did he do the 100 jumps?
Just say yes.
That was gonna take like 34 minutes.
That shit was gonna take the rest of the night to do that.
I had to pull the plug, I had to.
You played the Beetle game for an hour?
Yeah, but the Beetle game, that was like mind destroying,
trying to do that 100 jumps thing in the middle of a jump,
going through different timelines.
The fucking Twitter.
It was the same thing.
No, I can't, I can't.
Level 20, finally, good.
Oh no, look at all these crafted characters.
Maybe at the very end of the stream,
I will lose my fucking mind and try to get it done.
But not right now.
I wanna get through the rest of the game first.
21, when am I gonna do Kulex?
Very soon, actually, very soon.
Nope, good avoiding, good dodging.
Ah, hey, stop, I'm trying to move, stop.
Annoying, time to fight all the bosses again.
Remember these guys, remember this guy?
Wait, he got to 100, I was tabbed out, yeah.
How was your burger?
I think it's 200.
No, I thought I could teach to go.
Speaking of burgers, you know what I had?
Recently, that I actually thought was pretty good.
All right, you ready?
You know what I ate that I thought
was actually pretty damn good?
Hopefully nobody laughs at me for this, the Beyond Burger.
It was pretty good.
Subway, no, it's actually really damn good.
I went in like a total dick.
I didn't believe it all.
I was one of those people, like, okay,
because I'm serious, every fake meat I've ever had sucked.
It was fucking terrible.
I don't know what they do to the Beyond meat,
the Beyond like fake meat,
but it is the closest thing I've ever had.
I'm missing so many, I think ghosts, right?
I'm gonna leave, there's too many sponsorships
and you didn't jump 100 times.
Why can't they please just kill these things?
Die, ah.
Royal Syrup, the Maple Syrup, the Beyond Burger.
I was trying to go.
Oh, wow, that just was bad.
What the fuck?
I was, I panicked because I didn't know
what was going on here.
What's going on here?
Max Mushroom, second boss.
Out of, I was gonna say money, that was extra savory.
Good, just keep hitting them.
How long until the game ends?
Well, the game, the game ends very shortly,
but there's a very specific thing that I'm going to do.
I'm gonna try to beat the Impossible Burger Boss.
And then I'm gonna, no, I'm not,
I'm not gonna try to jump 100 times.
That's like 600 people left during that.
You want me to do that again?
You told them to.
No, I didn't tell them to leave,
I told them to make some food and come back.
I said, come back in five minutes and it'll be done.
It's been 20 minutes and nobody came back.
They found something better to do.
You told them to leave.
No, I didn't.
I said, go, if you don't,
just go make a hamburger and come back.
How long does it take to make a hamburger?
Actually, it depends.
It takes a fucking hour to make.
That's so funny.
It's all been deleted.
You gotta defrost it.
What do you mean, defrost it?
All right, now this is the time of the stream
where I go get Killex because we're getting to end game here.
Is there a way out of here?
I forget if there's a way out of here or not.
I think I actually have to go back.
It's all right.
Yeah, you defrost the ground beef.
You don't get those shitty Costco patties, do you?
No, I just get like,
I just get like grocery store hamburger.
You store it at room temperature?
No, I eat it within like a few days to get it.
Hey, behold, they've taken the bait.
I guess I can spare a few minutes.
Maybe they'd like to play.
Endable.
They throw a bunch of bosses at you at the very end.
This was a RPG trope back in the day.
You kind of had to go through a bunch of shit
before you got to the end.
God, I love it.
I love this game.
What a fun game just to play.
I think there is a way for me to get out still.
Phew, but weaklings.
How shameful if they were to defeat me.
Oh yeah, I forgot about this.
It's clobbering time.
Sued.
Mr. Alphlinton, you're going to jail.
There it is, I did it.
Right before it goes in.
That's much better.
All right, the mad adder or domino.
Let's go for domino.
It's easy for me.
Controlling the device, why not get him to shut it off?
Right?
Everyone's taking a lot of damage.
If you do 100 jumps, I'll give you $100.
I can't do it.
I mean, I will painfully attempt to do it a few times
at the very end of the stream, but not right now.
Don't kill Mario, please.
I have to do it on my first try?
Well, I can guarantee you that's not going to happen.
The highest I got legit was 37.
Or like 39 or something, right?
Inflating the number?
No, it was 37.
It was fine.
Ooh, that was big.
That's 436 damage.
And go.
Yeah, the clock, these two guys.
All the random physics experience.
All right, let's see if I can do this on my own.
All right, what's going on?
I don't find that to be very fair, but that's okay.
Peach 21, I want to do regular defense with Peach, I think.
No, magic.
So we are now at this stage where I believe I can.
All right, yeah, this, I'm at the,
this is the end of the game.
So let's go.
It's time.
I'm going to save it here.
I'm going to go back.
See if I can make it back quickly.
Oh my God.
We're going to try to kill, get rid of,
we're going to try to fight Culex.
It's not time for a hundred jumps.
That's after the game is finished and the credits roll.
And I'm, you know what?
You might, that's not going to happen.
That's going to be a waste of time.
Do it on Culex.
Is it Culex or Culex or Culex?
What's the name of this song?
It's called the March of the Doxans.
At least that's what my mother used to call it.
It's like the doggy, like march song.
Please run away.
All right, we did it.
Oh, my, my neck just ripped up to the ceiling
because I got caught by this.
I made that noise up into the sky.
First try, good.
Come on, fall, do it.
What the fuck?
I didn't do anything.
I'm going to do this quick.
Let's go, God.
I've lost step.
It's just certain at this point.
I wonder what the percentage is to do that.
What's the actual percentage to run away in games like this?
Especially this one.
I don't think I've ever known.
All right, almost done.
Just got to get past this part.
Good.
Actually, that is, that's better, I think.
Cause now I can.
Oh shit, what the fuck is in here?
All right.
I didn't know that was in here.
We're so close to being able to attempt Culex.
Where does this go?
You might be asking, why am I making another one?
Well, because Culex, I'm going to have two timelines.
We're going to have a beat the game timeline
to see the credits.
And then we're going to have a Culex timeline.
That's not what I want to do.
Timeline.
Am I going to get a turn?
All right.
I said, all right, like five times.
Okay.
All right.
Here we go.
The gate.
Let's go back and fight Mr. Culex.
I think we're equipped.
We're leveled up.
Let's just take a look at what we got.
Bowser, Mario, and Toadstool.
Lazy shell.
Ghost metal, jinx metal, tax, scarf.
I think we get to give it a go.
I'm going to save it over here.
See if I can beat him.
Greetings.
I am Culex.
Dark knight of thunder.
I've crossed into this dimension to fight for the dark mage,
but this world is uninhabitable for me of my kind.
I must return to my old world.
Before I go, though,
I would like to challenge your strongest knight.
Will you accept my challenge?
Will you enter combat against me?
Engage.
I am matter.
I am anti-matter.
I can see your past.
I can see your future.
I consume time.
And I will consume you.
So we got Culex, wind crystal, earth, water, and fire.
We're going to go with water.
One of these takes a lot of damage.
We're going to go with, yep, water crystal first.
All right, we got it.
That's not bad.
All of them do like two or three moves each.
This is me from the other timelines.
Oh, didn't even get a chance.
Didn't even get a chance.
That's why we've got, come back,
and I got the timing down correct.
It's right.
It's there.
Come on.
We got to get rid of that water crystal first.
You can't hurt Peach, I'm sorry.
Oh, I, you know what?
What the fuck does this do?
I don't know.
Defense up.
Don't do it to Mario, Peach.
Oh, Mario's going to die here.
Oh, thank God.
Would you look at that?
All right, let's do group hug.
No.
Hmm, yeah.
Pop it, come on.
I can throw up the candies,
the fire bombs, the rock candies and stuff.
Yeah, that's what I bet I do.
I'll do that.
Time for Yoshi.
Well, maybe in a minute.
No, I got to bring back Mario.
Fuck, what happened?
Auto P.
Don't even do this.
Don't start this bullshit again.
60 damage with the lazy shell.
That's fucking insane.
The last time people said,
oh, I auto peed in the house,
and I like ran downstairs and like nothing happened.
Kulex is a genus of mosquitoes.
All right, that's good.
We just need to get rid of the crystals
because they cause all the damage.
Mario, okay, there we go.
Peach is seriously just here
to bring people back and to heal and to stay alive.
I mean, obviously I have to be careful.
That was weird, it took a long time.
Oh, come on.
Ha ha ha ha.
I didn't even know I got attacked.
Pop it.
Ah.
Bro Luck just gave a hundred bucks.
I'm fighting bits.
Yes, I am.
Here, mate, here you are for the 100 jump challenge.
Just paying it forward now since I'll be leaving soon.
Thanks for completing the challenge.
I got some bad news.
I don't know if I will complete the challenge,
but thank you.
Thank you all and congratulations.
And thanks for the 100 fucking dollars.
Now you have to do it.
I will give it a real attempt, I promise you.
God, it's still there.
I almost want psychopaths
to find out how much health they have.
He paid you a hundred fucking dollars for that.
You have to.
I'm gonna try.
Damn, that hurt.
How much health does Peach have?
101.
Just get rid of the blue crystal.
No.
He does it a hundred times.
Oh, you're pathetic, Turbo.
I can do it.
Got it.
One down.
Yeah, I can do it.
Oops.
Sorry, hold on, let me rewind.
Let me read my time for a minute.
This is actually much harder than it looks.
Sorry for making fun of you earlier.
How do you do this without the lazy shell?
You don't.
There's another one, which one of them takes damage?
This one does.
One of them takes, I think they all do.
You have to get a bunch of rock candies.
Yeah.
You just get like 15 rock candies
and just use them all in a row
and heal the fuck out of everybody.
I hope you win.
Speaking of those,
rock candy, let's go ahead and use it.
200.
I'm gonna do it again.
You know what?
Let's get Yoshi out here too.
Come on out, Yoshi.
What are they?
For the first time, let's see what Yoshi does.
Come on out, boy.
Let's do it to, right to Coolix, let's go.
He did it.
He did it, he wins.
Yeah, I think he took a candy or something.
He stole something from Coolix.
Damn, that fucking hurts.
He stole, what'd he take?
Yoshi candy.
Yoshi candy?
We just gonna go for it?
Wait, where's my rock candy, there it is.
Got a freebie, I can do it again.
I was gonna say, this is how you lose the game.
Even with the lazy shell, if Peach gets transformed
and then she gets melee twice, it's over.
That can't happen.
Does group, how do I,
can I, does group pod get rid of status effects?
Yes, it does.
Jesus.
78, what is this bullshit?
34, what is this horseshit?
I have to go for it again.
I think it's magic, you have to do magic damage to it.
But nobody here really has very much magic damage.
Rock candy, yeah, I don't think I have any more rock candy.
I have fire bombs though.
Let's see if I have any more.
Oh no, I just got a freebie, right, yeah.
There it is, all right.
And let's do the fire bomb, go for it.
Just use all my items.
This is the hardest boss in the game.
The actual last boss is not even close to as hard as this.
Now let's heal Mario, did I miss that?
Now what's next, probably earth.
Yeah, that 360, burn this.
Yoshi candy, all right,
I'm gonna use the Yoshi candy on Mario.
Wish me luck, I actually don't even know what this does.
100 HP kills you instantly, that'd be bad.
You know, in all the years that I've played this game,
I don't know what that does.
It doesn't seem to do anything.
The shredder, does it take FP?
Does it, I don't know what it does.
It takes away all your buffs, oh my God.
What is this song called?
This song is probably just called
Kool-X's fight theme, I'm assuming, Kool-X battle.
Final Fantasy IV boss theme, that's fine, it's a Bowser.
And then we didn't have to deal with only Kool-X.
It shouldn't take very long.
It's the crystals that give him all the power.
Did I do lucky?
Just in case I don't remember, did I?
Let's do it.
Shit, I missed the camera.
He thinks Nintendo made this game, right?
Nintendo did not make this game.
This is a square soft game.
Nintendo just said, all right.
This is before the Enix merge.
It's a square from software game.
I don't know why that did that hurt my head
thinking of the thing you just said.
It's a from soft square software.
I have no idea what you said, I said it,
but I'm freaking out now.
Flame crystal going down, and then it's just Kool-X.
And then you get something.
Let's let Peach give it a whirl.
66 damage, not bad.
All right.
Just you and me, Kool-X.
And what do I want?
Let's just whack him.
You don't have any of your cool gadgets anymore.
You just are gonna take damage until you're dead.
Bowser is in trouble.
It's all right.
Just do the group.
Doom this world by breaking the crystals.
Well, maybe his world.
My world's gonna be all right, I think.
We're not in my world right now.
We're very clearly somewhere else.
He rented out an apartment in Monstro Town
and made a big black hole over here.
This is not even Monstro Town.
I missed that.
Won't be long now.
Another two, three rounds should be it.
348, goodbye.
244 EXP, double it.
Pay attention, because this is like 500 experience, so.
Here we go.
Oh shit, that's kind of split.
I don't know, guys.
That's, okay, all right.
That's a majority.
Ooh, no.
21, why does it keep it up?
24, he got so high, because he has this thing on.
22, how is her regular defense?
This is terrible.
I'm gonna go, she has to get a couple of points
in that shit, man.
Not like it matters, the game's over.
I already leveled up from that.
Ah, your spirit is strong.
Thank you, brave knight.
I will treasure this memento of my journey here.
Perhaps in another time, another game,
we may have been mortal enemies,
but as part, as comrades in arms.
Take this, treasure it as a keepsake of our fight.
Kulex decided on his own.
Nobody told him to do it.
He gave a quartz charm to Mario.
Beautiful stuff.
Farewell, champion knight.
It's blue text I got, and plus,
it's fun to make people very angry at me.
All right, so that's Kulex, he closed the door.
There's the quartz charm.
Shining source of power.
Now, it might look like he's not very good.
And in fact, I'm not even entirely sure
exactly what he's done.
Need 205, I'm ready.
Deal 50% more damage and take 50% less damage
and prevents instant death.
Well, that's incredible.
Use Gino, Bowser sucks.
All right, hold on.
For the final, Gino has to be in the party for the final fight.
Okay, here's the final party.
The original three from the very beginning of the game.
Malo, Gino, and Mario.
Plus, I'm gonna have to be fair with my party here.
Peach has been in the party for the last, like,
six or seven straight in-video game hours.
Bowser was in the first.
You know, we have not seen very much Malo in that party.
It's Mario and two nobodies.
Heals, Malo has a heal as well.
Let's go.
You have to make your party
who's currently playable in Smash.
You gonna, you, really?
Really?
That's not a very nice thing to say to me.
You know, I'm a huge Gino fan.
Sans got in Smash before Gino.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
LOL, Gino didn't get in Smash before Sans.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Funny.
He was in Smash as a costume.
No, he's not.
He was in the old one.
And then, why did you make him in the new one
with the costume?
What's going on there?
Why can't they just put the new,
the costume in the new one?
Why?
That doesn't seem right.
Aim square.
That's so much damage.
Okay, this is gonna be like embarrassing
how quickly I beat this last boss here.
This is the final boss of the game
and I'm gonna, I'm gonna steamroll the final boss.
That's a cool looking enemy.
Hold on.
Oh, if you wanna see how the other final moves look like,
this is Gino's final attack move.
Shoot stars out of his hands for five,
I'm gonna beat the boss in like fucking three rounds.
I'm gonna do 1500 damage a turn.
I'm gonna hog.
A lot of experience.
Malo, that's why.
Okay, what do you got?
Let's get you over 150 HP.
Peach would have done more.
Absolutely.
Peach is a better character, but that's the thing.
I need to get some screen time for Malo
because I wanna see his other moves.
Didn't you get like a new super special move?
Oh, come on.
I thought I had it.
Sorry, we'll kill him in two hits.
Why is Malo so bad?
The attack power is not four, a damage, or eight?
That doesn't seem correct.
He's wearing armor, right?
My finger slipped.
Ice bomb, cool.
I can use that.
There we are.
We can get rid of this
because that's just this play through.
I'm kind of confused with the other ones before.
I think one of them is to do the Geno Whirl.
Okay, let's go.
Production is on schedule.
This despite the fact that Mack, Boyer, Yardavich,
and the Axum Rangers were defeated.
At this rate, Smithy will have a new army in no time.
A new army?
You can't be making more weapons.
Haven't you caught enough trouble already?
Oh yeah, who are you?
This is Mario.
Give up now or you still have a chance.
Shut down production now or I'll stomp you.
What did you say, you little puff ball?
Mad Malo, trash him.
All right, let's see what you got.
Easiest final, this is not the final boss.
It's Shovel Knight.
That is, actually Shovel Knight.
He just needs to be blue.
22.
Let's round out, I need this.
Mario's so bad in regards to magic.
Huh, hope you learned your lesson.
We're almost there, Mario.
Come on.
What do you think this does?
Nothing happened.
Huh?
Must be the funny face, Mario.
Oh, I know, you're trying to make me look, aren't you?
I'm not gonna fall for that one.
Wait, help, help me, help me, help me, help me, help me.
Oh, that was scary.
I guess the green switch controls are the cranes.
Mario.
No, Mario.
I had to beat the whole game.
All these things respawn.
I finally made it here.
Let me help you.
Mario, Princess.
Sorry, I snuck out without telling you or the Chancellor.
I just wanted things to get back to normal.
I wanted to do my part to help.
Princess, yeah, that's it.
Any job that lets me help both Mario
and the Princess is worth doing.
My voice won't do it.
I'm trying to do that.
I can't do it.
You're gonna help both of us.
Well, I carried all I could.
Now what can you use?
Maybe a couple of these, maybe a couple of these,
a couple of these.
That's all I need, man.
I told, I really don't wanna say this to you,
but you wasted all week getting here.
I don't need any of this stuff.
I was all right.
I just came from beating Culex.
He's a Final Fantasy IV boss.
I don't need any more mid-mushrooms.
I'm sorry, I like, I'm buying them
because they're gonna feel bad for you.
This is for you.
Oh, rock candy.
Thanks, Toad.
Thank you, Toad.
We're almost there.
Come on, let's go, let's show him.
Toad has joined your party.
Why wouldn't Toad be in the party?
I'm just thinking about this
and this is kind of strange to me.
There are five party,
why wouldn't you get a nice clean rounded six?
Or even seven with Luigi.
Thank you, sir.
Here's the report.
Sir, drill bit will be finished on time.
We're ahead of schedule.
We'll make Smithy proud.
Good work, everyone.
The harder we work, the stronger Smithy will become.
It's me, actual Shovel Knight this time.
The weapons we manufacture here will be just think of it.
When Smithy takes over Mario's world,
we can do anything we want.
Ah, ah, funny.
Someone just did a funny joke.
I can't.
Not so fast.
You sure are a cocky bunch.
I've ruled this world, don't you forget it.
It's Mario.
Mac, too, and the Artemis, too, didn't stop him.
No, no, leave Mario out of this.
I'm the only one you need to worry about,
not him.
Mario, you're about to make the longest jump of your life.
You're ignoring me.
Oh, it's okay.
We'll get it with the Gino Flash.
Shovel Knight got us a smash before Gino did.
Oh, that's right.
I'm gonna start handing out permabans.
Cut it out.
That sucked.
Malo might actually not be very good, huh?
Damn.
I might have to bring back Peach.
Use spell, I just did use a spell.
Oh, well, like the moon over, like the...
Like the moon over the day.
My genius and brawn, I lost on these fools
at the small height point that I wrote.
It had nothing to do with the game.
I just, as the narrator, decided to come in
and give you some knowledge.
Oh, everybody hates that so much,
and like, I can't stop doing it.
You there, are you the one in charge here?
Do you know what your weapons have been doing to our world?
Stop this nonsense at once.
I'm afraid that isn't possible.
Any dissent against Smithy will be dealt with
by immediate meltdown.
Meltdown?
You can't scare me, I've got Mario by my side.
Dissenters will be eliminated.
Production will continue.
Right for the director.
I really, I really hope there's no more blue text
in the game.
I hope that's the last of the, of narrator blue text Trump.
Malo, it was so bad.
Oh, that's right, he does have the lazy shell on,
so that makes him almost 100% useless.
Right, Malo cannot have this.
It makes him almost totally useless.
He only has HP rain, yeah, I gotta bring in Peach.
This is the worst spell.
It's his final move, it's like the best,
it's his final smash.
That was scary.
But we can't run away now.
We've got to kick these lowlifes out of our world.
We're going straight up, just absolute DPS.
Quartz Charm, Jink, Spell, Textar.
Jerma, you're using the wrong spell.
Mario, I'm surprised to see you here.
This is the end of the line for you.
This is the closest you'll ever get to Smithy.
So, save it a moment.
You'll be fodder for my incredible invention.
The Gun Yolk.
I just don't want him to see it, you know?
I don't want him to see us destroying his invention.
This is a DPS, you see what I'm saying?
You see what I'm talking about here?
We're doing pure hundreds of damage each second.
How much DPS is this?
Well, we're down to about 12.
I think we're about five damage per second at this point.
If only Peach could heal.
We're not even gonna need it.
Pure DPS.
All three of them might die right now.
We're good.
Sometimes, that was, you saw how quick that was?
Damage.
The production line has been halted.
Look Mario, this is where the weapons come from.
This must be where Smithy makes his weapons.
Define the last star piece and stop the factory.
We've gotta defeat him first.
Mario, there's no turning back now.
Are you ready?
Our quest is almost over.
And when the time comes, let's get this show on the road.
Here we go, here we go.
Joel, Joel just came in with a raid right now.
Right at the perfect moment.
What's going on, everybody?
Thanks, Joel.
Hope you had a good stream.
We are currently finishing Super Mario RPG.
This is the, by the way, hold on.
Wait, wait, it's up to hot.
If you never played Mario RPG before,
you just walked into the theater in the last 10 seconds
of like Infinity War.
Okay, so this is the last,
this is the final battle of Mario RPG.
Here we go.
Welcome.
You ready?
Turns out it's fucking Santa Claus.
Hey, there's our last star piece.
What, huh?
Already finished your tour of the factory, huh?
All right then.
How about a little demonstration?
Hey, yo, Smithy, stop making those things
and hand over the star piece now.
Yeah.
Huh?
Oh, so you're the Mario.
Looks like we're gonna have a little dispute over this star.
Just hand it over and get out of my castle.
My, my, we're a little touchy today, aren't we?
You know, I'm actually growing rather fond of this place.
Please don't make us go through any more.
Just give us the star now.
Okay, better yet.
Why don't you give me all of your stars?
Why, then I could easily conquer the world.
Then we can get rid of all these wishes
and create a world filled with weapons.
Over here now, I'll crush you all.
Oh, why can't we have five people at the party?
Here we go, best song in the game.
Swear.
That didn't hurt.
That shit, you know what?
Just keep, let's just keep healing.
Let's shut off your weapon fouls, I think.
That's probably a good idea.
First time we've seen that move, it hurts.
Everybody but Peach, obviously.
Uh-oh, that's all you made?
Well, that's kind of, that's kind of shitty,
I'm not gonna lie.
You can make anything.
Hmm, let's see what this does.
Who do you think's been making all these bad guys
for the whole game?
You know, when I was younger,
I truly did not understand that he was like a Smith.
I thought he was like, that was a last name.
Like, oh, it's Smithy.
Like, his name was like Dan Smith.
I did not get it when I was like 12 or 13.
Dan Smithy.
I didn't get it when I was 26.
All right, that's a little different.
Okay, it's shut off now.
Let's get rid of that little guy.
Now we can't make any more.
That's a one hit KO.
Just got it.
Oh, so he's like a black Smith.
Oh, really?
Hold on, wait a minute.
You tell me, you tell me Dan Smith is a black Smith?
That's fucking crazy.
That's crazy.
That was pretty good.
Mega drink.
Let's let Peach get a little fucking shot in there.
Did I already beat the hardest boss?
I did.
No!
Calm down, Smithy.
Your head looks like a geyser.
Don't get so worked up.
Think of your blood pressure.
We just built this yesterday
and the foundation's very weak.
So stop shaking the floor.
How utterly annoying.
What the?
How in the heck?
Fuck, fuck, fuck, shit, fuck.
Oh shit.
Oh, ow, no.
Ooh, I'm burning, I'm seething.
Never have I been so wronged.
It is time.
I will show you my real form.
I will show you my true power.
I will teach you respect and I shall have my revenge.
Oh.
Do it.
Goo, come on, you puny ants.
I can take y'all at the same time.
Now this is actually the best song.
Can't block it.
Let's shut him off.
Yoko Shimomura was pumping out bangers
before King of Hearts.
Oh yeah.
Oh, he's supposed to heal.
Oh, let's go with an ultra jump.
Can't move.
That was so, Peach has the lazy shell.
You know how much damage that is?
In fact, let's, all right.
Well, 582 damage, that was big.
582.
Back to the, oh no, stay there, that's fine.
This thing takes the most damage.
I might kill you before you even get a chance
to go to the end of the phase.
Dude, keep doing over 500 damage each hit.
You specials are no reason to.
They do way more, like Mario does five,
doing like a super jump or an ultra jump or a flame
is only gonna do like 200 damage to this guy.
Same thing with like Gino at this point,
like Gino flash, Gino blast, it is not worth it.
You just do so much more, 446, that's it.
It's over, I just beat the game.
I am burning with power.
No, I'm just kidding, that was a lie.
I thought that was it.
Dark Star.
And I'm gonna change to the mailbox.
Or whatever the hell that is.
Is it treasure chest?
I know, that's a mailbox ever since I was a little kid.
It can't be anything else to me.
Whoa, all right, this is a really weird looking one,
isn't there a fourth one that we haven't seen yet?
There's the mailbox, the tank, the magician head,
and I think there's another one.
Okay, close.
Oh, that's not it, all right, well,
this is at least 2,000, 3,000 damage here.
It's a fruit bucket.
690 damage for one attack.
That might be the, I mean, I'm gonna be real with you,
that might be the single biggest damage attack
I think there's ever been.
With just a standard attack, it was 700 damage.
Oh shit, you're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
I forgot, I still have these.
Ah, karaoke cola.
Quick, use them before the game ends.
738, they are burning.
It's not possible, I don't believe it.
I'm finished, I'm done for, oh no.
Come on Mario, send the last one way up.
His hands look like McDonald's french fries.
Don't ruin this, this is a very emotional part of the game.
All seven pieces.
Thank you everyone, the Star Road is back to normal, and.
Ah, here we go, goodbye.
Take care guys, you'll never fucking see me again,
but I hope, just please, just beg Sakurai
for me to be in the next game.
Put me in something else, please.
Do you see my hand cannon?
Do you see my finger guns and shit?
This is all I got.
Somebody please.
He was a cool guy, wouldn't he?
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
this is important stuff.
Hooray, I am the king now.
Ha ha, yay.
You ain't ever gonna see me again either.
Bye, my story's complete,
there's no reason to keep this going ever again.
Story is complete though, I guess.
Fucking Johnny, Jonathan Jones gets more screen time
in the end than Gino.
They'll put him in Smash.
He'll be a fucking assist trophy next year.
Wait, is that implying that he poisoned Yoshi?
Oh, we didn't complete Todofsky,
there was one more song to do.
Oh, hello.
They're perfect for each other, aren't they?
Thank you for playing.
Hey guys, remember that guy that's in the green shirt?
Brother to the guy we played all game?
There he is, it's Luigi.
He's been running the marching band the whole game.
Let's go, let's go.
Ha ha ha, there's Malo, like get out of here.
Please don't make let's go a thing.
Why would I ever do that again?
It's too late.
Out of the blue pixel character, like Croco.
Bloons.
Is Ooster on the train, and the snippets, and the beetles.
I remember these guys.
What's at the very end of this?
Oh, the bosses?
We're gonna see Mac.
Yes, we are.
There they go, all of them.
Mac Yardovich, Boyer, Smithy, Blade.
John, and there's Gino.
You thought it was over?
You didn't think we were gonna get
a Magic Kingdom Disney night light-up LED parade?
Well, I'm sorry.
You were wrong.
This is adorable, oh, yeah, it's great.
It's wonderful.
Even the toads have glowing hats, yeah.
I just want this to be real.
Why can't it be like a Super Mario then?
It needs to be a Nintendo theme park.
It will be, yeah.
Goodbye, Gino.
Two, three, four.
There's the fireworks, come on, where's the finale?
Did I not do enough secrets?
I didn't do the Carbo Cubby.
I told you, the end.
It became a D.
Why did you do that, Gino?
Why did you turn yourself into a D
and explode when you could've been in like 15 other games?
Was it really worth being the D?
People would've got the picture, they would've understood.
So you panicked right there.
You ran at it like juice, you got to the end,
and you freaked out.
That's the end.
This is gonna make me cry, bro.
Yeah, that was Super Mario RPG.
That's one of my favorite games ever.
I am so happy to be able to play it with all of you.
So thank you for sharing one of my favorite things ever.
I'm gonna go try to do 100 jumps like twice,
and then I'm gonna give up, and then the string.
No, what the fuck did I just do?
Did I just open up Star Fox?
I'm gonna mute all sound.
I'm gonna take this out of my headphones,
and I'm gonna do it just by sight alone.
That's not gonna work.
It should, but it shouldn't.
Don't mute.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I don't even know fucking how many that was.
21, this shit's fucking impossible.
32?
I don't know how, how in the name of God,
does somebody do this 100 times in a row,
reliably every time?
I can't even imagine.
You've got to see the world in fucking,
not only do you probably,
you see the world in 4K,
and everything is slowed down by like 72%.
4D world, all right, hold on.
I'm gonna try a different tactic here.
It's a simple tempo.
It is not.
The timing changes to essentially a single frame
after, I believe, 12 jumps.
It is not a tempo.
It does not have anything to do with the sound.
It has nothing to do with the tempo.
It's about, because it changes.
It's the same window every time,
but that window is so small.
I'm gonna try doing it a little bit after.
Let's see.
No, you can't do it after
because you lose the frame data from,
you can't do it.
Just push Y.
Look up the YouTube tutorial.
I'll look it up after this.
Guys, poor Bowser.
The tutorial is useless, is it?
I wonder, because essentially, from my understanding,
right when you can see Mario's shoe,
right there, there, right there,
that's when you're supposed to press it,
but I feel like I'm doing it,
at least after you get past 15.
The shoe is the key.
Fuck.
I'm gonna try this like two more times.
I feel like the area as well,
like the background image adds to a problem
because I got to 37 against the Axum Rangers.
How?
Oh, I'm out of juice here.
Hold on, let me see something here.
I need to plug this in.
Let me try to get at least a 20
because the timing changes two times.
It's like the middle coming down for the first eight,
and then it shrinks from eight or something to 15,
and then it shrinks to tiny from 18 all the way up.
I remember looking this up years ago.
Make a robot that pushes the button at the exact time.
If I have any leftover cash, maybe.
All right.
I can say there's no chance in hell
I'm gonna do this 100 times on a single frame.
This is not gonna happen.
No, that attitude, oh, not ever.
What if I like spam it?
You know what I mean?
Does that matter?
Let's see what happens.
I'm gonna watch the tutorial.
I wanna see if I have this correct.
I'm gonna make sure I have it correct.
Super jump tutorial.
Okay, let's put it on here.
See it on the screen.
All right, super jumps.
I'm gonna see if I can help out
people having trouble getting the timing right
with these jumps.
Some people are, usually a lot of people
say they can't get up to phrases.
Get an accessory that only Mario can wear
is all of the super jump stats and benefits
as this image will attack own.
As far as you see,
at the earliest time you can press Y to jump
depending on how many jumps you've done so far.
The yellow bar is the first through about the sixth jump.
After the sixth jump, this timing bracket
will shrink down to where the orange bar is
which represents the seventh through about the 15th jump.
The orange bar is the earliest you can hit
the Y button at this point.
The red line represents the final timing change
that messes people up.
You have just a couple frames to make your mark
so you gotta be perfect.
Notice that the bars have lined up with Mario's feet
so the button press is occurring
when Mario is literally on top of enemy
and not right before like with the orange bar.
This is the first jump we're looking at
so I'm gonna continue the footage in slow motion
while counting the jumps
and actively showing you the timing changes.
Fuck, this is a lot of info.
Y button to see where you need to press it
in order to keep the jumps going.
Six, seven, okay, eight, nine, 11.
12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
I'm gonna go to 25 because I don't need to animate 44 jumps.
I feel like that's what I'm doing though, fuck.
All right, so after, let's see.
So it's one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
What the fuck, I didn't change anything.
Six, seven, eight, damn it, man.
I am trying so fucking hard.
This shit is fucking ridiculous.
I also have to take into account like the delay going into,
you know that there, you know what?
That is very possible.
The tiny little delay going from the Super Nintendo
into the Elgato into my monitor.
Uh-oh, that's true.
That makes like a little bit of sense.
That makes sense, it does, as to why it can't be like
super duper ultra hyper hyper hyper perfect
is because of that, maybe.
Don't do it visually, well, you can't do it with audio.
Change your timing.
Yeah, but I'm, just change your timing forehead.
That doesn't work as easy as you think it does.
I'm losing two or three frames.
So that means I'd have to do it
like two or three frames early, right?
That's the theory?
Let me see what happens if I try to like a hair early
instead of trying to do it right when he lands.
Let's try it again.
All right, this is the final attempt.
Is the Elgato fucking screwing me up here?
I'm gonna, hold on, I'm going for a,
I'm gonna delete the game.
I'm gonna turn my webcam so you can see.
I'm going right from, I'm going from the Super Nintendo
right into the monitor and I'm turning my fucking camera
on webcam so you can see.
I wanna see if that helps.
I'm real, I'm actually curious about that
because I'm going, let's go out of here.
All right, hold on a second.
And you know what, the stream's over right now anyways,
right, like the stream's over.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Metallix and I are gonna play Man of Medan tomorrow.
That like horror co-op, choose who lives and choose who dies.
So that should be fun.
But let me go to the bathroom.
Let me come back and I'm gonna switch this up
and we'll do like the after stream party
where we do this and we'll read bits.
So I will see you guys very soon.
Why does this look like such shit?
Oh no, it looks all right.
Okay, you guys can't hear anything.
And neither can I.
What is going on?
Why did it just do that?
Why does it look like this?
No, no, I just, I'm just incapable.
I'm just not, I'm just in fucking capable.
All right, we figured it out.
Just incapable of doing the 100 super jump thing.
Did you sit on the screen?
Why is this boss so fucking hard?
I know, I keep doing my moves to him
but I keep doing zero damage.
No, I can 100, if somebody said, Jeremy,
I will donate to you right now $10,000 fucking dollars
if you do this.
I wouldn't be able to do it.
I feel like I didn't change anything.
I just, it feels like my timings are getting lost somehow.
It's the last attempt and I'm out of here.
Ooh, that was fucking pretty good.
So what I started doing there is I started to press Y
right as I was touching the top of his bulbous head there.
Like right when I started to graze the top of his head
as I'm when I'm pressing Y.
Oh, fuck.
I had to itch my fucking face.
Turn it off.
20, 21, 22, three, 34, five, 36, 37, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34,
35, 36, 37, 38, 39, fuck.
I gotta do this 50 more goddamn times.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna press start like now, you know what I'm saying?
Let's see, if I get up to 75, I'll do it.
I'm gonna stop it at about like three seconds left.
I'm gonna try to get it on the way up, not the way down.
Fuck, no.
How many was that?
Was that 60?
All right, same thing.
I'm gonna stop it about three seconds, four seconds.
Why does this look so fucking stupid?
Why does it look like that?
All right, here we go.
Oh, I'm gonna lose my fucking mind.
I'm gonna lose my fucking mind.
I'm at like 60.
It's the viewing angles on my monitor.
Well, hold on.
Put the webcam on top of my head, but then I can't focus.
That's, it's so hard to fucking do that.
It's so hard to get that like exact frame
like going off, down, go.
Oh my God, I'm gonna scream.
What the hell is this?
Where am I?
No, that doesn't even help.
I can't put this anywhere.
All right, I'm gonna hold it in my fucking mouth after this.
My stream off?
Can you guys hear me?
Why can I see the chat?
What the fuck is going on?
Hello, what the hell was that?
I have to give up.
No, I think everything's up.
Hello, what the fuck is happening?
What is going on right now?
This is going in and out so fast,
but my internet's not turning off.
I think this is like an OBS or a Twitch issue.
Damn it.
I don't even know how much that is.
I think I'm at like 78.
I'm at 78 or something.
Okay, here we go.
It's the second one.
I can get the fucking first one,
but the second one just sucks.
This viewing angle is so bad.
I can't, I'm gonna go into like the camera setting.
I gotta, if I don't get 10 each time I do this,
why, oh, I wasn't paying attention.
I'm done, I'm out of here.
I'm fucking leaving.
I'm not doing this again.
This is too much.
This is too much actual like living pain.
Trying to spring into a hundred of these fucking things.
I'm too close, but it's so, so hard to do,
but the stupid way that I'm trying to do this.
Oh, you can't even see it, nevermind.
I have, if I don't come within like 15,
I don't even know how many I've done.
I can see you shirtless.
No, I'm not shirtless, I got clothes on.
All right, here we go.
Oh my, can you guys not hear me?
Oh shit, I was muted that whole time, I think.
I'm sorry, I've been talking for like
at least a full minute, two minutes.
Wait, was it, I wasn't muted, I was muted?
I'm not still playing.
Oh my God, I was just talking for so long.
All right, so that was Mario RPG.
Thanks for watching, I'm gonna do the bits.
Shouldn't take us too long because we didn't have,
I don't think this will take us more than 20,
30 minutes or so.
I wouldn't tell anyone if you use GameShark, it's all good.
Hey, Sticks Renegade, thanks for the 250.
Here's an update to that sticker car
I showed you a month or two ago.
Oh, your sticker car, Jesus.
What if you even need to repaint the car?
When are you gonna do another jumping session here?
I'll show you.
But thank you for the $5, Sticks Renegade.
We'll show your bumper sticker car.
You got a lot of angles here too.
So what, you added stuff on the front here?
This is like mini NASCAR.
Holy shit, is this too many?
Is this too, I mean, yeah, I think it is.
I think that's too many, never too many.
Where's the German 985 sticker, what the heck man?
Thank you, and good luck with your soon
to be potential polka dot car.
Thank you to Drummage Door for the 250.
Now you might be experiencing RPG fatigue,
but since you enjoyed this so much,
you might wanna check out Barkley Shut Up and Jam.
It's a free humoristic post-apocalyptic basketball RPG.
You can play it even if you don't know much about basketball.
I have heard of that game,
but I think we're gonna be away from RPG games
for a little bit, just for a little while,
because this was three streams in a row.
So I wanna take a break from role playing games
while we do some other stuff.
The old I'll look into it, yeah.
But thank you, hold on, I got some chest burps.
PS, you won't play Lisa RPG, you uncultured brute.
I don't think I will, not on stream.
But thank you to Gunther for the $5.10.
Here's to September, thank you.
Thanks for the $5.10, thanks for your subscription.
Yeah, you did twice, $5.10.
And anonymous cheer, thanks to the 250.
They don't say anything, just anonymous.
And they cheered, $2.50.
Thank you to Halo Softboy for the $2.49.
I'm not supposed to be reading this one.
Excuse me, you're breaking the rule here.
I saw the two and I saw, uh-oh.
But I mean, I'm already here.
Jerma for screenwriting,
I'm interested in alchemy as a visual language.
In the dreams you shared,
the progression of meteors to vials of pee
to blacksmith imagery is neat.
Alchemists believe they could distill the powers
of celestial bodies into liquid tinctures
to be used in forging the philosopher's stone.
So what you're saying is, that was your 500 IQ dream.
You're heading to Vegas tomorrow, I need advice.
Don't spend a lot of money.
Eat at hash house or go on the link.
And don't stay up too late, take it slow.
But thank you Halo Softboy
for that good dream interpretation.
Thank you Zion S-A-W-S-D, Zion Swayze.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Jerma, why are you in the first edition
Dungeons and Dragons Fiend Folo from 1981?
The one on the right even looks like you.
How ancient, how ancient are you?
Oh, this is like a germ.
It's like a goblin or something.
This is the first edition D&D.
The one on the right looks like me.
And it's a germ, a germ lane.
I mean, that is kind of the way my head is shaped.
My ears don't look like that though.
I got better teeth than that.
My nose is a little more crooked.
And I got a nice full, I got a fuller jaw than that.
But I do see what you're saying.
But thank you for the 10 bucks.
Thank you Seven Layer Wario for the five dollars.
Hey, would you say happy birthday to my partner Wes?
Happy birthday Wes, if you get this.
Probably birthday is potentially day after birthday,
but happy birthday yesterday.
Hope you had a good one Wes.
And thank you to Seven Layer Wario for the five dollars.
Hey Garfield, the Monday Killer,
thanks for the 250 Garfield.
Germ, guess whose birthday it is.
It's Garfield's birthday today.
The real one or the yours?
The comics say it's June 19th, but that's just one off.
That's just one of Jim Davis's funny goof ups.
He got it wrong 41 years in a row somehow.
Oh, that's interesting.
Anyway, Germ, as a birthday Garfagraph,
can you sing a rat birthday song?
Germ, a one guy or maybe just a regular birthday song,
maybe an original.
I ain't gonna sing the birthday rat song.
I will say happy birthday to Garfield.
What a swell guy.
Happy birthday to Garfield, whether it's cake or pie.
Happy birthday to Garfield, we owe you much.
Happy birthday to Garfield.
Coming in in the clutch, happy birthday.
Thank you Ryan the Giant for the 10 bucks, thousand bits.
Say they said Oswald Fattenswild from the Gallup Gazette.
Can you tell us how today's stream is going to affect
the rest of your season?
Well, I didn't do the 100 jump.
I didn't do the 100 Mario super jumps.
So I think that's gonna negatively affect me
in the short term.
But in the mid to long term, I think we're gonna be just fine.
Hey, Wiki, this thanks with three bucks.
Oh boy, we're riding the Royal Bus, where we dropping?
I've read that.
Thank you Wolfgang for the $5.
Ex-vacation better be in the next term of Rumbler,
I swear I will cause a massive riot.
Probably.
That's gonna happen before the end of the year.
There were an insane amount of subs tonight.
Insane, insane, insane.
They were probably at least two, three or 400 subs tonight
with community subs involved too.
Is September actually causing a big sub explosion here?
Let's take a look at how many.
Yeah.
Oh, didn't the stream turn off?
The stream did, the stream turned off.
Remember like 20, what an hour ago or so?
Was it an hour, two hours ago?
It went to like zero.
We might have lost a few.
Yeah, cause this is like just the subs
from the current live stream.
Did it stay on?
Oh, okay.
Was that five minutes ago?
Was it five minutes ago?
But still, it's a lot.
And I mean, I can look over and see the subscriptions.
This is a shit load.
But thank you all of you.
Thank you for subscribing.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We're gonna do Man of Badan, the horror game.
It's sort of just a one and done experience.
We'll go.
But thank you snoozingcopter for the 250.
Some streamers just want to watch the chat burn.
No, I want to watch my chat flourish.
Hey Gunther, thanks for the $5.
What is Yardovich 2's favorite flavor of gum?
Double mint.
That's pretty good.
You're coming up with these on the fly here.
Also thank you to Joel for the raid.
I don't know if anybody's still here from that,
but it is very late.
But thanks a lot.
Thanks everybody that was watching Joel's stream
for sticking around for as long as you did.
Maybe we'll see you again.
Also, Phylactery Lich.
50 more dollars from Phylactery Lich.
Loading up a huge amount of money.
Still, weeks later.
Phylactery is still giving insane amounts of money.
They say, what a wholesome stream, Jerma.
Thanks for the adventure.
Now for the love of God, play Paper Mario 1 and 2.
Judging by how many people,
because here's the thing,
this is kind of testing the waters.
I said this the other day.
But I, me, I sometimes think,
oh, is that too slow?
Is doing like a RPG stream too not interesting to people?
Is that, you know, three streams,
four streams of turn-based combat?
And I kind of get in my own head and go,
I don't think people are gonna like that.
It's boring.
Is it boring?
It is boring.
Jeremy, is that boring?
I think it is.
No, it's not.
I think maybe somebody would like it.
So this was a test to see.
And it looks like this went great.
This went really, really well.
So I'm just judging by how many people
were happy with the game
and thought that this was a good string of streams.
My concern was always,
is it gonna get a little too draggy,
a little too boring for people?
But maybe it did for some.
So I probably will continue to do some of these other games,
but not immediately.
There's a lot of things I wanna do in the meantime.
I'm glad that people enjoyed them.
People thought they were fun.
Because I love this game,
except for the 100 jumps.
But I already admitted
that I wasn't gonna be able to do that.
And I tried to time travel and do it.
Still couldn't do it.
You know what?
You have to admit when you're incapable of doing something.
But that's my time.
I will see you guys tomorrow.
And right at the very end,
Sweenex gave $5 right at the very end here.
Thank you, Sweenex.
They say, hey Jeremy,
I just wanted to thank you
because recently I lost my job as an art director.
I've had for some time
due to the department I work for filing for bankruptcy.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
I was watching your Xbox camera green screen stream
when it happened.
Watching you in that fat suit cheered me up in a lot,
cheered me up a lot, as stupid as it sounds.
I can't imagine having a long-term career
that you've had for a while
that because of a company's bankruptcy
or insolvency or something,
it's just kind of, that's it.
I'm really, really sorry to hear that.
Hopefully you can find something else in the field
that you can quickly turn back around.
Seems like if you had that much experience,
it shouldn't be that hard.
Hopefully not.
But seriously, anything that can make you happy
or anything that can cheer you up on these streams is,
that means way more to me than anything else.
Good luck to you.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
To Alex and I are gonna play a man of a damn.
Good night.
Take care, everybody.
See you real soon.
Ta-ta.