Good afternoon. I'm getting this crazy, crazy revelation right now. I'm using,
for the first time, I'm using Streamlabs OBS. This is 500,000 times better than just using standard
OBS. I didn't even know this stuff was going to happen until I pressed live. Let me just go
over it. Let me paint you a picture here. So the chat is here in the program. The live monitor is
here in the program. The recent events, Streamlabs bits and subs and everything's over here. I used
to have like 12 windows out on my monitors. This shit's all in one program? That's unbelievable.
Anyways, hi. How are you? I'm Jeremy. Do I sound louder too? I played around with some audio
settings. This is post carnival germa. I'm all about the production value now. I may have screwed
up a few settings, but I'm all about making productions like this one. Where's the loud
wind? Not across the country anymore. I'm back in Vegas. Not only am I back in Vegas,
I have to get ready. I have to get ready to go to San Diego like tomorrow. Hey, I'm back. Hey,
back after the carnival. Bye. Going to TwitchCon. Post carnival, pre TwitchCon. September was a
busy fucking month. Can I just tell you? Anyways, we can go over a few things here.
We're gonna hang out for a little bit. Just enough time to go over stuff that I couldn't really do
at the end of that other stream because we had to tear that whole thing down. Had to leave. I had
a birthday to celebrate too. This is the exact game I was hoping you would play. I'm gonna try
it. I got a lot of requests to play this. So what's the game? Like two, three hours long or something?
Easy. But if you didn't know, I just saw this the other day. Let me put a link for you.
The goats, the Andy Mark goats. I didn't even know they were gonna do this. They are on sale
right now. The ones that were in the machine. You can buy a goat that was apparently on camera.
I don't know how many of these they have. They might have very few amount of these. I don't know
how many. Copy and paste. There you go. If you read and see these. The goats were special invited
guests to the recent Twitch carnival in partnership with German 95. Together we put on this the first
robotic carnival where viewers at home banded together to control the robots playing games.
You've been asking when there'll be available purchases today is that they each goat in our
inventory was on stream in the claw machine when they're gone they're gone. I don't know how many
were in there. I don't know if this is one per customer. Hopefully, hopefully if you want one
you can get one. Do just chatting. We need to catch up. That's what I plan on doing. We're not
just gonna jump right into goose game. I have to remember how to stream. It's been a while. Hold on.
Speaking of speaking of forgetting how to live stream like from a desk plus I of course I did
the first one. I'm like let me let me set up stream labs OBS. I'll give you one sec. I didn't
even tweet this either. Hold on. Every single one of my USB slots is taken up now. That's not good.
I gotta figure out what the hell is even plugged in down here. How do I have? I have like 15 slots.
That makes no sense. All right. Let me figure out how to add my camera now.
Uh oh. Oh shit. This is harder than I thought. Wait a minute. Hold on. Add. There we go. I think
add a camera. No. This one here. Yeah. Okay. This one looks all right. Is it working? Can you guys
see me? No. Why does it look like this? Why does it look like this? Why does it look like this?
Is this a? Did I fuck this up? Oh from the left. From the last stream. That's right. Hold on.
Hold on. Let me fix my peasant hair. I'm not going to fix my peasant hair. It's not going to happen.
I got a haircut for TwitchCon and I ended up making myself look like a dickhead.
So it looks like we're going with a hat this time. How do I fix this?
Why does this still look wrong? Is it doing anything? I gotta really I gotta learn how to
use this program. That's gonna take a little while. Anyways let me uh kill the audio here.
How do I crop in Streamlabs? Everybody know how to crop in Streamlabs? What do you do?
It's not alt. It should be alt. I've never used it before. How do you crop in Streamlabs?
Show Werelord. Show Werelord. I gotta I got a story for you about Werelord. Okay. Werelord
was a huge pain in the ass to take home. Uh hold on. I let me just hold on. Let me tweet this. I'll
be right back. Okay. Yeah I've got I've got a story to tell you about this guy.
It's not even really a story. It's just a series of annoyances. Even right now. Even now. Even now
he's a pain in the ass. Okay look. I there's no way he can go. He's such an awkward like big sausage
hot dog shape. Uh this was my personal item on the plane. I took a carry-on obviously and this
was my personal item. But there's nowhere for him to go. There's no I was gonna put backpack
straps on this thing. But listen do you know how hard it is to carry this around like this
in an airport? Just like dragging around. I felt like um who's the Charlie Brown character that
has the blanket? I was like dragging him on the ground trying to go to the bathroom with this
thing too. I went into the bathroom and I balanced him stuck him through the the handle of the
suitcase trying to drag him and balance him and we got it. I had to go into a stall. I couldn't
am I gonna hold him like this and piss? People would think I was a fucking weirdo.
I had to go into a stall and slowly like this like balance him on the top of my suitcase
and he like fell on the public bathroom ground like three times. People were commenting on it too.
I told you he was gonna be here. I know that you know where he was. He was in the laundry room
because he needed to be cleaned. He was disgusting and I just put my hands all over him again.
Ah but it was hard to take take it around and there was actually a few times you know when
you're walking by um you're in the airport and you see those big fucking trash cans.
Man after trying to finagle him for like 30-40 straight minutes it got real close for me just
like dropping him in the trash. It was really close. It was so frustrating or I was gonna just be I
was gonna be like find somebody and be like here do you want like this toy? But then I was like
that's fucked up too. That's kind of that's it's weird. Hey hey do you want this toy? And then I
thought they were gonna like cut it open because I'm trying to bring like drugs. That was another
thing that was going racing through my mind. Oh yeah just me with this uh yeah Wailord's my favorite
Pokemon. Don't worry he's just a perfectly perfectly large enough to store like eight
pounds of cocaine. Let me just I'm just taking him with me. Don't worry it's kids toy. That was
a fucking whole lord deal. Drug Wailord. Wail Drug Lord. Anyways I'm back. Uh I had a birthday too.
I saw a lot of wonderful things. I'm not even I'm not in the wrong I'm in the wrong category.
Let me change this to just chatting because that's where I'm supposed to be.
Why is my intro still playing? Get out of here. There we go. No not jump. Jump ultimate stars.
Just chatting. Okay how do I make this bigger? It's just gonna look like this. I'm sorry. You
guys just have to deal with how stupid this looks. No not that. This is fine. It's fine. I don't care.
Anyways uh bits bits just came in. Did they? Hold on. Let me change my streamlabs thing.
Is it like am I too wide? Is that right? What came in? Where? Huge bits. I don't see huge bits.
Where do you see them? Wider. Oh we got them. We debated them. Now let's talk about this.
By the way again if you want Andy Mark Goat there's good luck because you probably they're
gonna sell out in probably 15 minutes. Or they have or there's more that was in there that I
didn't know of. They're already gone. Are they actually already gone? No they're not are they?
I think they're still there. He ignored 500 bucks. There's not 500 dollars here. Did you
donate that of the money to charity? No not yet. I have not been home for more than a day or two so
and I had to celebrate my birthday. This is the first day of like existing that you guys are
seeing. You just got paid for the drugs that you smuggled. Birthday money. Did somebody say I
ignored Joel earlier? Is Joel here? Did I did I miss Joel? Well what's up? No it was it was a
great time and it was an immense success I think. There was a couple of hiccups. The robot you
actually guys you actually really did break the robot like twice. You can always tell when the
robot got broken when they would just hand me a microphone and say hey the robot's uh fucked up
like you gotta kill time and I'm just like sitting there like okay so uh nice we've got uh something
else coming up here uh I was doing a lot of lip licking too because it was so windy I watched like
two or three clips right and I'm just going like what am I doing with my mouth this shit was so
fucking windy it was like blowing into my mouth and I should I should have brought like chapstick
because it's like wind wind okay so uh I was like a fucking old man no more money we talking about
look at the top donator wait wait what where what's it what's going on here check the bits
I'm looking at them right now is this is this inaccurate do I have an inaccurate pulling of
the bits uh-oh stream labs obs I thought you were the best program ever what are you guys talking
about you missed 500 dollars are you fucking serious what are you guys talking about let me
let me let me open up this page I'm looking at it right now all right wait why did this not come
through then all right what the hell is going on here okay so no seriously seriously this is none
of this is over here I okay none of this is on my stream labs right now that's not that's kind of
concerning why uh okay uh but yeah uh phylactery lich gave five hundred dollars holy shit that's
not on here the last thing I have hold on let me see if I what way this is doing this for I have
the one ender for 60 cents I have mega milk for a dollar deva kitty's message is not on after that
is zake for 250 how far down is that what the fuck is going on here quick somebody give another 500
no don't do I'm kidding don't do that uh no uh they say hey jeremy missed the carnival so you missed
the carnival stream but caught the vaude right after easily one of one of if not your best streams
ever I just bought my germa goat you better keep that werelord forever I'm going to um
that's a shitload of money that's you are racking up okay you're at the hotel and you asked the hotel
to bring in seven or eight extra TVs and they wheeled them all in you plugged them all in and
you bought like 40 pawns on every single one of those TVs and just played them well you weren't
even in the room you just left you're like they're just playing in the room hey wait by the way
what do you think I got this t-shirt from does it say you're just streaming pornography to your
hotel room and you got the bill at the end it was like 4800 bucks by the way that by the way
that is the actual size of the pancake that hash house ago go at the link um the strip in las
vacas that's the actual pancake uh but phylactery that I think that's the that's only happened like
once or twice I think ever that somebody's ever actually given it five 50 000 bits that's insane
and and trident jacks gave 50 dollars much love thank thank you all for the werelord but we
not to completely jump past that that's a shitload of money but we brought the wind
brought by my like lip licking because the wind was just we really thought we were going to have
to cancel the event it was so like 10 20 minutes before 30 minutes before that the stream started
we were getting these huge ass gusts and we were just sitting around going oh no no this is not
this is very bad we would have rather had brain because we would have pulled everything
towards uh inside because there was a place inside we could do it wherever I was the most
nervous concerning there's a knot in my stomach is the wind going to knock all these games over
and ruin the whole day it was that was a last second call because there were a couple times
during that stream when I really thought the whole booth was going to blow over
wind is like hitting me in the face it was all over the place uh ignored joel hold on wait a
minute wait a second joel 15 dollars from joel why are you giving me 15 bucks yo germa you're
going to poppin gamer this year we'd love to see you there popping gamer what's popping gamer
oh this was are you going to twitchcon if you're gonna i'll definitely i'll be there for a couple
days are you what do you look like i can imagine just like walking around and all of a sudden just
like hey it's me joel oh hey wait are you are you actually not going am i is this a joke are you
gonna get my hopes up like this that i could meet a fellow fucking video game streamer he doesn't
know he doesn't know how to what do you mean i don't know he actually said what am i going to
go to popping gamer this year what what's so what's wrong with that so joel you're not going to you're
not going to twitchcon it's up dog just in a different way what's popping gamer okay well if
you actually are going to twitchcon maybe i'll uh maybe i'll see you there nice dishwater coffee
it's not a dishwater coffee it is a a pineapple juice that i dumped in a starbucks container
and then filled it with water so it's a pineapple juice concentrate that i turned into a hydrating
liquid it was not dish water soap uh anyways that was some of the most fun i think i've ever had
especially even like on stream that once we got going and after like 45 minutes or so and it was
very clear that the wind wasn't going to destroy everything that was so much fun and something
else that you guys really need to know uh this this ain't ending here we are already already
talking about the next one so that's not oh that was the carnival that was really cool uh
we'll never see anything like that again no you sooner than you think this shit ain't going to
have anything to do with the carnival either we're stepping on the gas here guys i'm just holding
it down and i'm gonna hold the gas pedal down until the car is out of gas and then i'm walking
too and then when i'm done walking when my legs give up from the fucking dehydration i'm gonna
crawl you understand and then when i'm done crawling when i'm out of complete energy and i
am not of dessert anymore as a fucking ghost keep going and no i we're gonna we're going
there's way more to see if you think that's it that's not even close
that was a test and i and i think i passed i think i passed the test i only almost got hurt four
times that's not a big deal it's okay we've got more robotic streams that we've been thinking of
just going back and forth just it was the whole team just clicked all the all the people at
were so awesome they were super super nice had a bunch of great ideas themselves that all that
that wasn't just all me guys like they had to come up with most of that shit because they were the
ones that had to make the fucking robot so i was extreme overlord this is what i want this is how
i want it to work this is the joke that i want to do i want this joke i want that to happen i want
that to happen and these guys just absolutely fucking killed it like it was it was unbelievable
i couldn't have asked for a better team so there was a lot of people that worked on that stuff and
there they were very very very adamant and excited to work together again in the future
so i could not have gotten a better group of people can you share anything that did not make
the stream um i'm trying to think there's anything that that didn't get in there every all like the
weird fucked up shit that i wanted to do got in the stream but that we made sure this but we just
like three or four months in the making so we had lots of time to prepare for it and lots of time
to care about it the feet cam the feet cam was scripted it was not in fact a lot of the things
that i think you guys think were scripted were not at all me getting hit in the face by the frog
that was i could i actually couldn't i could not believe you did i said it hit me in the face and
you guys hit me in the face and it was not just i didn't move to like get hit by it it wasn't like
oh there it is i'm gonna like okay uh three two i can see the timer okay get in the way and like
get hit by it no no i didn't move you guys hit me right in the fucking nose i stood completely
still when you fired that thing it hit me directly in the face uh what are some moments there were
some moments that felt scripted well the clowns were scripted because they they had to be and
they were awesome too oh those those clowns were unbelievable bring them back that's gonna be tough
because they're across the country procedurally generated clown content we gave them an idea of
what we wanted and then they just they just kind of hit the ground running and did whatever they
fucking felt like and it was great those clowns was the clowns were scary move in with the clowns
what would you guys do if i just went come on in and they both just came in and i got up walked
out of the room and they just did a fucking two-hour routine it was i felt uncomfortable
yeah well i'm sorry i'm sorry but it was great give us our prizes uh you got the the workloads
right here but twitchcon is this weekend i know at least a few of the people that were that were
part of the event are going to be there we're going to brainstorm some more stuff we were talking
about and i don't want to give away any spoilers in fact i won't but i want i want the next one
to be somewhere either in january or february of 2020 the next stream like that you will see
it in somewhere i'm hoping between december and february faster i can get done the better
early yeah i want to do this every few months every three or four months i want to do something
like that because that's fun to me that's it just i just that's that's what i care about at this
point and now the team exists there they are ready and they are willing and they were just like
whatever you come up with let's fucking go it's like dude i have i have i have fucking nightmares
and dreams every single night with new scenarios so we're not gonna run out of those but it was
something that was cut nope i wrote up everything you see on that stream i've
written down on a piece of paper you know series of napkins i was at it was at chili's and just
wrote like an crayon a series of things that i wanted to do and you know every bullet point
every piece everything that i wanted and sent it off to the producer producer said can we make
this happen the rest is uh history too many napkins ordered off the kids menu no ordering
off the kids menu at a chili's you honestly may as well just go to the grocery store and just get a
loaf of white bread and just eat it out of the bag this the same nutritional value so that way
we're still sub september isn't like chilies right like we're not gonna do like sub october and it's
chilies right am i gonna get i'm not i gotta stop talking shit about stuff mr luxury streamer
hold on a minute here i am not a luxury streamer i just don't like chilies you can be
non-luxury and not like chilies i don't think that's a very controversial opinion i mean
that being said the southwestern egg rolls are some of the finest they actually are pretty good
he's backtracking oh i gotta test my new my my audio compressor does it work you tell me ready
you should this should not get louder than like it too loud to listen to i'm gonna peek the mic
right now but it's not gonna peak this is a test i couldn't test before the stream started here we
go ah right that was okay that was that was fine right it didn't know it could there's no way it
could peak i have a limiter on now yeah is it distorting when i get this close when i go louder
than that does it distort that's what i need to know somebody just gave that was disgusting
somebody gave five it was uh durnu uh kaiser gave five community subs it did peak it's not possible
for it to peak i have a limiter set up right now let me prove it to you where's my audio where's
my audio monitoring device there it is all right hold on a second here so you tell me that you
said it's still it's still peaking your career is peaking okay see you in december and tell me
the same thing hey see it see in like december or january i want that guy to come back okay so
this is your career peaked at spi no that i there's no it did not oh mega lull true like true true
true just because that's your favorite thing doesn't mean that's where i peaked there is no
there is no peak i already told you i'm fucking i'm going on the gas until i have to walk at that
point the car would be when you peaked because then walking is much slower than driving and
crawling is slower than walking and when and when and when you're a ghost you don't have leg you
can't walk oh fuck this is not good what was i supposed to be doing oh right and i was testing
the limiter here all right i'm i can i can monitor this okay so uh hello i want to monitor this
is it working why is it not working is my computer fucked hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello i can't hear anything why i have lost audio on my computer
hello there we go this one shit's breaking okay uh no i can't peek i'm looking at it right now and
hear it oh no i can't okay not important so let's let's move on that's that was not important i
could have done that without being on camera so all right anyways what are you guys looking
you guys got a picture you want me to look at what is it oh like this what this is some kind
of surprise i guys guys i'm in this photo i i know this picture exists somebody didn't just
like sprint over to me and like make me stand next to that and then take a photo and run away
that's whatever how do i explain that i i mean what do you want me to explain that five six is
is like six six six eight look at the bars up top look that is bigger than a ceiling
or you think someone's who are those bars made for then all right if that's five six who are
the bars made for for children okay so you you think that what children like three feet tall
like how big are the people that are on that five six bars at five six doesn't know how tall kids
are yes i do the sign was incorrect and i was looking at it and then somebody took a picture
of it and they were laughing hysterically like their face was bright red laughing like wheezing
and i just kept going like i don't understand why i don't understand they got the picture and
they put they posted it they said could i just please post that picture and i was like yeah
four four six is like this tall that's like six i think that's like either six six
or that's like over that's almost seven feet tall look at the tree in the background is that tree
six feet tall i know that's a that's perspective i can't that's i can't prove it that way what does
it say stand up and hold a ruler no then i'll break the illusion that i'm some fucking goblin
that hunches over and carries like a backpack of gold around and i don't i don't want to break that
illusion that should have been pretty sick though if you had go that much gold everybody talk shit
about the goblet oh that yeah there goes the goblin with the goldenness in the knapsack
uh yeah that's worth like six or seven hundred million dollars like is that
you want to like talk down to the goblin with the fucking gigantic sack of gold they are they go
into their house like oh they slam it down and then they process it through like bank of america
and they get in their suit and their tie and then they go to fucking dinner the nicest restaurant
in the entire fucking city now he's projecting now he's projecting if you guys think i i you think i
own a suit no i don't you saw me with the only suit jacket i own on december 31st and it was too
small remember my arms were coming out of it i had that i've had that suit jacket since i was like
fucking i don't know 17 or something the new year stream yeah that's the only i know i think i don't
think i'm gonna have that anymore am i gonna play anything yeah yeah we're gonna play um
i'm just people wanted to hang out and talk for a little bit go over the the weekend and then
we're gonna play untitled goose game how do they make contact with andy mark it was a long process
those of you that don't know that stream i wanted to do that stream for about two years
it was so hard to try to find anybody that knew anything about robotics to that extent
because there's been plenty of you know twitch controls stuff on this site before obviously
twitch plays pokemon right that was the big one that was the first one wow this is crazy
the twitch controls this thing twitch moves that thing but never twitch can control a robot to that
size and that weight and that kind of device shooting like a ball out of it a real softball
not just like a little laser or a little um like action figure thing so anybody that
people at twitch i brought it up to people at twitch i had a partner manager at the time
and it was just like hey this is what i want to do i want to do like a little twitch dunk tank i'm
gonna do a carnival maybe and have like clowns and do some jokes and bring in some games and
some rides and stuff and they were like oh that sounds really cool and it was just a process of
trying to find the right person to connect to somebody that knew somebody who then could say
oh that sounds like a great idea and yes i work for a robotics company it was just tricky but
just through bouncing from person to person to person to person it went from my new partner
manager who without uh without my new partner manager this seriously this stream does not happen
they connected me to the first person necessary to be able to start the whole thing so without
that person it does not exist me no not me not you no um it really was a one guy scenario
and then i got linked up with um jk productions which was a production company that knew the
people at andy mark and through um various events and stuff and just somebody that knows
somebody that knows somebody that knows that person uh led to uh andy mark making these robots
and doing this whole thing the stream did the stream did cost a lot of money it did like i'm
i people have been wanting to know and i i'm not going to tell you a number because i don't think
it's necessary i don't think so but it it was some cash it was some it was some money because
there's no way that somebody could make those kind of things without trying to dish out a
little bit of money but i've said this before i said it a thousand times it was at least a dollar
yes it was 500 000 i said it on stream it was like 600 million no um i don't need to i don't
want to give a number because once once you start giving numbers then i don't know you start i don't
want anyone to feel like in this community holy shit oh they gave stuff but we gotta like refill
that i don't want that i don't want to come across like i'm saying oh you guys that was a lot of
money like oh that was a lot of you know i'm saying that was a lot of cash for me um it's
not necessary and i don't want any people it's it's easy to concern people right like hold on how
much money did you spend dude don't fucking do that anymore you don't have to do that don't do
what i actually when i told star star is one of the people that knows how much money this cost
and he he was like what the fuck are you doing he was like you are fucking crazy and i was like no
just don't like to know no i'm fine um remember the time when i muted everyone was like why did
you mute what did you guys talk about it was that but again this channel sees so much money
it does what you want to like pretend like it doesn't like i i don't i want to be completely
fucking see-through you know what i mean i don't want anyone to think you guys give a ton of
fucking money to the stream way more than i think some of you guys think so if i am going to i want
to do this i want to take whatever you guys give to this channel obviously i'm gonna i'm not going
to be like a total you know everything's for the stream obviously i want to try to have like a decent
living and have money for bills and money to put away and to save money and you guys
are doing that shit like you are that's where this comes from but that doesn't fucking matter
if i can take a large portion of this money and have a twitch controlled fucking carnival
that's what's going to happen every single fucking time if i'm able to do it
it's gonna happen every time he's obsessed with spending money stop talking about it you're gonna
regret it no there's no way how could i regret something like that it's not gonna happen
it was everything i wanted it to be so i just i just i can't i have no regrets and speaking of
money rvm thanks for the 5000 bits no yeah no i saw the card we talked i was in the pre-stream
we talked about it oh wait maybe did i didn't know i saw this one didn't i yeah i know that
yeah all the everyone contributing all the artwork and all the wonderful fucking sayings and messages
and everything for my birthday yeah yeah it's it's unfucking believable i i cannot words cannot
describe the feeling that you get when something like that comes in you know i'm saying every
message every piece of artwork it's made it's i'm 34 it's you know i didn't really do too much from
i mean i went out and uh and you know had a couple of drinks and stuff and just kind of chilled
it was a great time but when you get to be over 30 birthdays start to kind of become it's not like oh
i'm 18 i'm 21 i'm 25 i'm 30 it's kind of at this point that the ticker is just continuing to roll
so uh that's an incredibly special feeling to see something like this monkey ass what
what what are you talking about that's just the way it is how long am i i gotta cut these before
twitchcon remind me before the stream ends yeah look at these things these things gotta go
these are that these are kind of how long your nails are these are accidentally scratch your face
long nails but seriously so many people was like signed on this too this was a what i believe from
looking at the reddit thread about it and all the people that were posting stuff i mean this is a
multi-week thing to do so thank you everybody in the community that anything to do with this
it's good shit thank you but going back to what he's having a midlife crisis not till i'm 45
you know as long as i still look like this i mean i might i might get a little droopy i've already
started here if you go back this is interesting if you go back um go back like five or six years to
the youtube channel and go to a facecam video i don't have this it was like that i'm getting
a little droopy around the mouth here so you know it happens quick what did quick what he's turning
into bugleberry slowly grow a beard i can't grow a beard this is this is the extent of what i can
grow for a facial hair before i have to shave it before it looks embarrassing okay tell me if i'm
a weirdo am i weird let me explain let me explain this my i like the way that i look the most
when i've had two to three days of not shaving a fresh close shave i don't like the way that
i look right after it so during events for instance like twitchcon coming up i'm timing
every time about twitchcon the carnival stream oh i'm i've got a big party that i want to go to
oh i have this event that i have planned it oh and it's in it's in three days i time it so i shave
so then within two to three days i'm gonna show up to the twitchcon party and it's gonna be like
it's been two and a half full days exactly timed timed stubble and i'll be like hey what's up it's
me germa95 you know me everyone's gonna go i don't know no who the fuck are you and i'm gonna go
goodbye you know see what i got here i got like time stubble and they're gonna go i don't know
get away from me is that weird to time your stubble no a little a little and then i get really pissed
off and i miss time it by a little bit because it's three days it is like two and a half to the
third day if i miss time it and a fourth day goes by and then i go to the event no no we're all
fucked up now and it looks like shit and then i have to have the awkward conversation with myself
do you want to look a little dirty or do you want to look clean shave in the way that you don't like
oh it's hard okay how do i look right now it's like kind of scraggly i look a little dirty and
shit but i it's still all right just trim it no because i i've tried i have tried to trim when
you trim you end up doing this fuck you end up doing like patchy grass it's like mowing a lawn
you end up missing spaces and you have like scraggly hair and random spots i remember one
time it was so embarrassing i got an electric razor that had the trimmer on it and i was i was
at like five days no i gotta get this down to three so trying to get it down to three days
and it looked okay i got rolling on oh that looks all right right i get to where i was going
and nobody said anything i didn't know there was no hey whoa what the fuck's going on with your
neck no nobody said a damn thing i went to the bathroom and i was checking myself i'll just
making sure everything's going all right you know i've been there for an hour or two and then i went
like this and went like because i had these just spikes just black spikes sticking out of
random places in my neck because i didn't get them all the way it wasn't a beard it was just these
weird gross like hairs that were just poking out of a million different places so for the rest of
the night i was kind of like looking down like this i'm not at not extreme like that but you know
what i mean you end up just thinking and then you get the idea you go all right can i pluck all
these out in the mirror there was probably like 45 of them and i'm just like can i sit here and
pretend i'm taking a dump and just pluck all 45 of these with my bare hands you got i got like
two or three in and i was like that's not going to happen so i i don't do the trimmers anymore
try to take a five day down to a three no i just time it perfectly for instance this is like
embarrassing uh the twitch party is on saturday night so what am i going to do on wednesday night
thursday night friday night saturday night notice how i still haven't shaved see in like
four or five hours when i shave my fucking beard remember you need to chill out with this shit
all right well you you and my mother agree that's good no i i shaven's okay shave on stream
i won't i'll never do that i will never shave on stream you know how scary that is to do
i know guys i have i you know i also wouldn't stand outside on stream in a
field during a thunderstorm i'm not going to get struck by lightning it's not going to happen
it's raining out and this thunder and lightning outside i'm just going to stand outside like in
grass could i get struck by lightning make sure is there like a one zero point one point one percent
chance that it'll happen yeah i don't want to get struck by lightning on stream i don't want to be
shaving on stream and the zero point zero zero one percent chance that the blade is something
wrong with it or it's too dull or i i turn the wrong way and like i get a bad cut on my face like
on stream shaving because i shave with a safety razor i don't shave with like a Gillette like
just no i have i have a real blade i shave with a real blade i ain't gonna get struck by lightning
on stream stop having such a chad jawline it actually sucks because when you look at this
thing look at that's all bone like you can't shave over that look at this bone that's bone
that's bone so when i have a razor i have to i have to i have to like go around this big ass bone
and then you end up having like you your eyes you have to cross your eyes those of you that have like
big ass bones here right i have to go like this let's say you're the mirror i have to go like this
into the mirror i can't fucking see what i can't see i can barely fucking see what's happening
right now i'm just telling you i'm just telling you how it is Jeremy you look real old today
is it a birthday gag thanks but it's true it's true uh but i i used to shave and the reason why
i switched and i'm very careful like i'm not gonna fucking around when i tell you that uh i switched
from the guy to say don't listen to this bullshit all right this is more this is more like shit
talking of companies that will never sponsor me okay we don't do sponsors on this channel anyways
you don't it's time for the the six or seven blades in one day one two three four five six
seven eight nine all right you when you shave your face you shave with the first blade it gets the
big hairs the second blade gets the tiny hairs the third blade gets you don't need five fucking
blades you don't need like eight blades in one of those like and then they have like gel on them
what is this thing what happened to the goose game it's still happening we're still gonna do it
the blades get clogged up yeah you go down once and then you just got this like fucking mess in
there that you have to like dunk and like blow on it and like swish it around in water and they're
expensive do you know how cheap a razor blade is and you know how expensive would you go to cvs
and buy one of those fucking 16 blades with like the like the fucking sea salt gel that's all over
it and the fucking powder on the bottom you know how much money that is and you have to buy a new
one like every month it's really expensive i switched to just a safety razor so just raise it
the thing with the head you screw it on it's just a razor blade it's got two sides it's a one blade
two edges and as long as you're careful and you train yourself and you get tutorials on how to do
it i just kind of started doing it i am actually afraid to use the barber one you know it's what
i'm talking about the one that's like a switchblade it's like no no no i that to me that's like going
into the kitchen and grabbing a knife out of the drunk straight razors i can't do safety razor i
can't it's it's actually it's scary it is and i look i know there's a lot of people that use
straight razors and yeah you know i shave with a straight razor you know i do it's much cleaner
it's much better for you that person is terrified every time they use it internally they can tell
anybody that they use a straight razor they'll be in the mirror just going hope this ain't the
fucking day hope this ain't the day it's funny because even when i use a safety razor i say the
same thing i this is fine this is fine here here no this is very easy once i get down here
hope this ain't what hope this ain't the day okay it's not are you being a stand-up comedian
now is this an irl stream wax it off i actually thought about that before but that shit's
fucked that shit is worse talk more about beards i shaved the wrong way what are you talking about
you you don't shave upside down like this you what you go down wait hold on you go you want
me to go upside down with a safety razor this way what are you talking about you want to turn
the blade upside down and go up my face this way nobody fucking pay attention to the people in the
chat right now that be careful when you use any sharp objects near your face that goes for
that goes for shaving razors that goes for toothpicks those of you that chew on toothpicks
this goes for you too and i know one of you right now has one in there and you're like what fucking
me what what would i do wrong be careful because that you can get stabbed now i've been stabbed in
the mouth by a toothpick before it was like oh i felt like went through the cheek so be careful
i used to be one of those people i used to love the mint coated oh i want one of these right now
if i had one right now i would do it the mint coated toothpicks you just kind of spin them around
like this i always need something to do with my mouth i have the adhd i gotta have something in
my hands i've got to have something in my mouth chewing gum hurts i don't want to you know when
you chew gum oh just chew gum no it's like no go like this 500 000 times every day your jaw hurts
um i need a toothpick i'm you know maybe i'll be like maybe i'll be the guy
maybe i'll be the guy with the toothpick at twitchcon you know what i mean just like sitting back with
like my grape juice my like fucking fruit punch whatever with toothpick but that way i would look
cool right is that still cool it was cool like 50 years ago is it cool to still have a toothpick
no it could be though i'm gonna do it i'm gonna get like a mint toothpick and i'm gonna walk around
with it and be like the toothpick dickhead guess what because then everybody that you come across
hey what's your name hey general nice to meet you toothpick guy's gonna fucking put the toothpick
toothpick in his mouth there's gonna be eight people in an uber on the ride back to the hotel
going do you guys see the guy with the toothpick toothpick yeah i remember toothpick guy yeah he
was fucking cool yeah i like shook his hand he gave me his business card we were gonna talk about
like fucking collaborating yeah the guy with the toothpick he's the only guy with the toothpick
at the whole party and then i have to it has to be a thing if i ever like do irl and like hey oh we
were gonna do like we were gonna be like streaming as a group tomorrow you want to come toothpick
guy that's you toothpick guy then i have to be toothpick guy on their stream and i'm just like
typecasting myself as the toothpick guy and i don't want that to happen there's not somebody
named toothpick guy in chat right now if there is give me that i want that give me that username
it's mine you are a top 500 streamer they just become toothpick guys toothpick guy nine eight
five sometimes twitch is like hey do you want headshots taken of your stream and stuff it's
like yeah i'm gonna do it next time with the fucking toothpick you guys don't understand i
don't care i'm running with this i am gonna have somebody bring me up as the toothpick guy from the
party i don't care if it's here i don't care if it's somebody randomly just like says on their
stream one day and you happen to be watching yeah yeah i remember like somebody bought us all around
and it was really fun and what was i was a guy with the toothpick then just know that was me
except don't no that's actually a bad idea because like yeah this guy the toothpick was walking
around he was a shithead and it's somebody else like now making me look bad because of all that
is is just putting a toothpick in your mouth yeah some guy with a toothpick in his mouth got
thrown out it wasn't me i swear to god i was just doing it to look cool anyways i'm not gonna say
the word i'm not gonna say the toothpick word anymore we're gonna move on tooth tooth prick
okay right i need to write that down because that's seriously that's seriously like a that's a
that's a that's a rumble character it has to be well what are you guys linking here all right
all right we're gonna play we're gonna play a game there's a game i want to play we've been
hanging out for like an hour just wanted to kind of chill over the first time getting back hope
you enjoyed that stream it was a ton of fun expect to see more stuff like that in the future now let
me open up this goose game wait isn't my stream title barking at people uh that's not really
accurate at the moment it will be very soon though uh how do i turn off the camera this is a new
program i don't know how to work it you don't oh there we go hey there we go