I still have the Didalus encounter discs scattered around my desk.
Is this a rare game? Are these worth anything?
Is the Didalus encounter worth any money if it's in the disc with the original packaging or anything?
I mean, it might be. It's a 3DO game with all these raids.
Yeah, all right. It's all right.
Am I crazy to say that, like, you should have to do two-factor authentication with your phone if you're gonna do a one viewer, one person raid?
I mean, come on, Quinn.
Like, I'm looking at my timeline of stream lab stuff, and this just, like, you guys are just breaking the system here.
It's just a bunch of these one, one, well, this was two viewers. Wait a minute.
You guys are just raiding me from your personal Twitch channels. You're already here. Why are you doing that?
What, how does it, wait, hold on a minute. I have a question. If you,
If you raid me from your account, and you're here, are you fucking up my view count?
Yeah? Well, cut it out.
Inflated viewers.
No, like, look, and people wonder, oh, I can't believe you missed that raid today. Wow, there was a raid that came in.
Yeah, it's in the middle of, like, it's like in the middle of 300 one viewer raids.
Imagine if I had a notification that played, like,
Would have raids came in, that's why I don't have sounds to play anymore. He's, what an entitled streamer.
No, okay, if you, look, if you, like, raid this channel, I really appreciate it.
But if you're in pre-stream chat, raiding the channel to just, just get on my stream labs feed,
that's a different story.
Ungrateful, ungrateful.
He hates us.
Can you stop screaming? I have homework to do.
But just lower your volume.
Today, we're gonna play Bugsnax again. We're gonna, might even get to the end of this game, I assume, if we don't, and we don't.
But I'm playing it again. I think it's fun. I think it's cool. I think it's just, it's worth just chilling out and playing.
I like it. I have, oh, I adjusted my seat today to make sure
that I could, I'm, I'm sitting back in my chair right now. Like, almost, like, back. I moved the mic,
so it was like, okay, um, you know in Blade 2, you know, that big, huge beanbag chair, fat, vampire, alien guy?
That's how we're streaming today.
Oh, that's nothing. That's just research. That's just a video game, huh? Hit him with the UV light.
That's what we're doing. Just don't burn me, please.
Are there any essential viewing movies? What do you mean? Oh, I don't know if Blade 2 is an essential required reading movie.
It's just a movie that I watched 15 years ago.
That's like the, what the hell is this? I think one of the only, that's, that's Rodney Dangerfield.
You did like a, you did a face swap thing with Rodney Dangerfield.
I got no respect. I'll tell you what I came up. That's Rodney Dangerfield, right?
We're, we're hooing Rodney Dangerfield. Well, I guess that makes sense considering he, he, none of you,
that's not me. That's a, that is a face
morphing software of me and you put Rodney Dangerfield's face on here, and it's very funny. If you play
Tungless this stream, I'll sub for a whole year. I don't feel like I don't want to type that into Google, so no.
It's a real picture of you off of CBD.
He's been dead for 16 years. Kind of normal for a lot of people to have no idea who he is.
Yeah, sometimes I talk to you guys as if
you're not, you know, in your mid to late 30s. Oh my god, I can't believe you guys, that's Rodney Dangerfield.
Like, I may as well say like Charlie Chaplin for a lot of you guys.
I'm gonna just give 50 bucks. But you guys don't, you, you, everyone knows who Charlie Chaplin is. They teach that in like the first grade.
JPQPlays gave
5,000 bits, 50 bucks right at the beginning of the stream. We haven't even done anything.
You don't even know if this stream is worth 50 dollars.
Haven't done anything yet.
But thanks a lot, JPQ.
They say, hey Jeremy, you're my favorite streamer and extremely inspirational. Also, most of the community is awesome. I agree.
Well, but the second part, not that like I'm like you, well, yeah, thank you.
Most of.
Yes, you can say most of, because that's like going into the grocery store, and at any moment in the grocery store,
you could be surrounded by like murderers.
If there's a hundred people in your grocery store, five of them might be a serial killer. You don't know that.
You can't walk, you can't just scream in the, in the grocery store.
All of you are awesome, and everyone here is so, is awesome.
The guy that like has four people buried hears you say that, and he's like, oh nice. All right. I'm good.
Can't, you can't make a statement like that. Like the dude that has the, his fourth salsa in his pants,
stealing from the grocery store, hears you say that. Oh, all right. I'm in the clear.
Can't make a blanket, there's no blanket statements here. Most of you, because I don't know all of you.
Spike889 just gave five community subs, thanks for the subs dude. It's chunky or smooth. What do you mean smooth salsa?
Smooth salsa is just pizza sauce.
It's restaurant salsa.
Smooth salsa. How do you know that most of us are not serial killers? I don't know that. I have no idea who you are.
Like every president of the United States could be watching this right now. I don't know.
Jimmy Carter could be here right now. I don't know. It's possible. He's just on the toilet with his phone.
I can't wait for bug sacks. That's possible. I don't know. What about George Washington?
Yeah, George Washington in his coffin.
He had, he had an iPad slot built into his coffin, and he could always have German985 on it, on his iPad,
on his coffin iPad.
What a shitty afterlife. What do you mean after life?
I just like implied that there is no afterlife.
Whoops.
Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't, what I meant to say was,
what I meant to say was, oh no, what do I do? What do I do now? How do I get out of here?
How do I, how do I move away from what I just said?
Somebody said, hey German, do you want my paycheck? No. You spend your paycheck on you. You want to throw me a couple of coins?
I will probably catch them.
Play the damn game. Hey, I'm just relaxing, man. I'm lying back like the, like the zombie in Blade 2.
I told you, I'm gonna, I'm gonna relax a mood today.
This is gonna be so chill.
Cognito Hazardous just gave $50. You guys have given me a hundred bucks, and I haven't even showed the game yet.
That's 5,000 more bits. He says,
Wag baba boo boo.
All right. Thank you for the $50. That's based. True. What do you, I don't know what that means.
Play the game. I'm gonna play. Can we just chill?
Eat bug on stream.
Nah. Nah.
No, I can't. No, not today.
Dreamer approves that God is a lie.
Didn't say anything. Just you, we took, guys, we were talking for George Washington watching my stream while he's dead in his coffin.
Guys, we're not like talking reality here. Where do we leave off? I forget.
Ew. Bugs. Turn it off. Blue-pilled. Okay. Stop reading chat. What, what do you mean stop reading?
That's like the whole, that's like, that's like half the deal here.
Bugs and bug-pilled. Okay. All right. Philbo wants to talk to me. Where's Philbo? Oh, wait.
Stop reading.
What is wrong, what's wrong with him?
Why's that dude, that dude's on drugs.
He's sleepwalking?
I'll take a glass of air. No ice, please.
Do you have anything? No. What do you mean? You didn't even serve any.
Apparently not. Apparently you're not going to serve any of these drinks.
Hey, get up. Wait.
Wait, if you wake up people that are sleepwalking, can't you instantly kill them? You sever their spinal cord or something, right?
Isn't that, isn't that possible? Can you like kill somebody if you wake them up like out of a sleepwalk, like sleep like this?
That's a myth.
You sure?
Thanks for waking me. Oh, you're welcome.
Another 50 bucks just came in. What are you guys doing today?
5,000 more bits from DonCad. Thank you DonCad for the 50 fucking dollars.
Hey, Jerma, it's your weed guy. I've been outside for an hour and your phone goes straight to voicemail.
Do you just want me to leave your in quote?
Nug snacks at the door.
You know how weird and awful and embarrassing that would be? If like the delivery, if I ordered food
and the delivery guy got here and like
knew who I was and like heard me scream bug snacks and they have this moment of realization where they're like,
holy shit.
I am outside the door of this motherfucker right now.
You know, imagine like, oh, I'm coming up to this delivery at this place. I'm just at a place just delivering food.
You'd be like, what the fuck are you, what?
Hold on. Like I was just, I was just watching him like
I'm delivering this. No, that just can't be him.
And he like, dude, you like comb your hair a little bit.
Here, I'm at his house. I'm here. I'm here.
Hold on a second guys. The fucking delivery guy's here. I bet he's a fucking loser.
Hey, hey, thanks for the food, man. You're welcome. Yeah, Jerma.
Hey, what? What did you say?
I, uh, Jerma, I, uh, hey, um, I can't believe I, I can't believe I'm here.
All right. Thanks for the food. Slam!
Hey, the delivery guy recognized me. Oh my god, are you fucking kidding me? What's this bug do?
No tip.
No, you tip through the app. You don't, what are you talking about?
Yeah, and what he doesn't understand is he's going to look at that his phone and it's going to be like a
$200 tip and a message that says, hey man, thanks for being a part of the fucking bit. Thanks for playing along.
Take care of yourself. Have a great rest of your night, man. Thanks for coming.
And then it turns out I didn't have any money left in my card.
And I write again.
Hey, dude, I'm wicked sorry, but, uh, like I bought a bunch of fucking shit on Amazon and
I like didn't realize that I didn't have that money in my account. Uh, thanks for, thanks for coming by though.
How do we even, oh, right. Like somebody said they were delivering weed to my house.
I kind of want to turn this down to a pretzel. Is that weird?
Somebody said that was a four out of ten bit.
And we'll just get, it's been 18 minutes, man. There's going to be plenty more. Probably not though. I'm just like lying back in my chair.
It was a five out of ten maybe.
It was four out of ten. All right. Well, look, your favorite publisher comes out with like a five out of ten, six out of ten game
three times a year.
They make one good game like every five years and they're like a AAA company.
All right, cool. What are your thoughts on Bugsnapp?
We rarely get a ten out of ten bit from you.
Whatever. Good. There's no such thing as a ten out of ten.
Voices were ten out of ten.
He's got a lot of that social anxiety.
All right, where's Lisbeth? Lisbeth is top dog, you feel me? She really inspires me to test my limits.
But uh, that's about it.
I'm really tight with Egobel.
Your meatwad is getting better.
Is it?
Egobel's a sweetie.
Your ass is a ten out of ten bit.
That's not even my joke.
That's okay. First of all, here's two parts to this. That's not my joke and I just have a huge ass.
I didn't, that's not like a comedy routine.
I just have a big fucking huge ass.
And somebody
enlarged it a little bit.
That's, I didn't do anything.
I just joined and he's bragging about his ass.
Is it bragging or is it just me saying things about my body?
Look, I didn't say guys, I have a huge fucking ass.
That's not what happened.
I just said I have a huge ass.
I didn't say look at how huge my, I just said I have, all right, we're moving on.
You really slam dunked my questions.
And how am I supposed to drive the conversation away from my fucking giant
bulbous ass?
It's like half the images you guys link over the last two weeks.
I'm just gonna ignore that this is what the community is currently on.
Shit, I was gonna just brag about that.
All right, so let's go talk to Philbo.
Oh, here they are, here are my snacks.
That's my favorite one right there so far.
One thing I don't like about it is it has the stupid in-and-out wrapper on it.
Because look at how old and retro it is.
Get a fucking full wrapper on that and stop putting
all the food in a half wrapper
in the bag at the drive-through.
I, I hate that so much.
It's like,
do you don't, I don't care that it's in a half wrapper in the bottom of the bag. Don't stop doing that.
Wrap it up. If it's, if it's not a to-go order, fine.
But if it's a to-go order,
I don't want my burger out in the open in a
half bag in the bottom of a bag.
I'm sorry. If that's like a unpopular opinion, then I'm glad it is. I don't care. I hate that.
Holy shit, what's going on?
You're talking shit about in-and-out, bro?
Yeah, of course, of course you're the type of guy that would be mad about that fucking chattler.
Oh, I have these, I have these bags.
Nutty snack pod. What should I do with these?
Should I, maybe I should feed one of these to somebody.
All right, look, will you leave me alone if I give you one of these?
Can we give him a nut nose?
All right, we'll donate the other one. Oh, no, he doesn't look okay. He looks like he's kind of messed up.
Somebody lift him up and put him in the corner.
Oh, can I do that?
I can't help him. Somebody help him.
Oh, you guys weren't lying. You can actually pet them.
Oh, where are my other friends?
How come these guys are locked up? They shouldn't be locked up like this.
Where's my favorite one?
There you are. There's my favorite.
I want to go pet my favorite.
You're a good pop dick. You're a good George Washington hair.
Okay, let's go. Let's talk to Philbo.
Forgot how odd this guy looked.
Why do you want me to, why?
Something's wrong, buddy. We better take a look.
That's a he well, what did you wait? What's this? I can open this. Can I I can open that what happened?
Somebody's dead. Somebody got killed.
This creature wearing a crown or perhaps holding some sort of ceremonial dagger
You can't not laugh when you talk to some of these people scattered. How do they not laugh frankly? I find that hard to swallow
Drama zonk off. She just told this guy to zonk off drama
Get some grump and sleep grumble
This is what this is when you make a student film and you don't know how to edit yet
Everyone just do their lines
And I just go like this
It doesn't even matter if they're looking at the camera
All that if what bramble and beffica are saying is true. There's got to be some physical evidence left behind. Yeah
Indeed we should tweak the perimeter and keep watch in case the creature returns
Good idea buddy. Do you think you can scope out the restroom? You know find out what they saw
I didn't even know he was talking. Why do I have to investigate the bathroom every time?
Can you go look at the restroom and find out if I don't want to look at the bathroom anymore?
Wait, I'm also one of these things
What?
I'm one of these things
I am but how come I don't eat anything?
Oh, I found something
Found something a rusty spade discarded near the sign smells like snacks. I have an allergy
Oh, I didn't what I knew I was like a I didn't know I was one of these like mutant muppet people
Oh, what's that?
eggs eggs
rambel knits all of her own eggs
Okay, cool. Um two out of six clues
Oh this clue
footprints
Messy paw like prince lead from one edge of snack burg to the garden
What about what about you? It's you?
It's tiffany tiffany. Oh, no, you're just investigating. Okay
Tiffany get out of the way
Wait, what?
more paw prints
Even more paw prints bug prints bug snack tracks scatter from where the grumpus tracks stop
We need another clue in the toilet
What did I miss?
It's a community shitter. Yeah, that is kind of gross
Oh, I see
No more bug snacks. It's a warning
Bilbo, where are you dude?
Yeah, they all go to the bathroom the same place. I mean I guess wait
That is not what you like your family does that it's not like weird
That is not like that weird if you live in a house with more than like two or three people that you go
You use the same toilets. It's not that weird, but every single one of you guys has a your own toilet in your own room
No, no, what no you don't who has more than like three or four bathrooms
I guess if you have like six bedrooms like four five six bathrooms. That's a lot. That's a lot of bathrooms
All right. There are tracks that aren't quite grumpus
Chat bourgeoisie
Which is more likely that is so far unseen giant bug snack politely left a note on our door
Or that this is some form of coordinated gaslighting by the grump and what's more gaslighting dear?
Is that the word of the day on this stream every day scientific data behind it? What is you haven't even drawn?
Thank you. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. You know what? Let's split the difference. Eh, you're both wrong
He's got those like popsicle feet
Becoming pretty unlivable who okay who who wore it best? All right, who's got the best out who's got the best mutated body snorpy?
You were a lot safer. I know I have my favorite same goes for me and my little ones
We shouldn't split up again. It's probably him
Or it's cooking marshmallow nose
You don't know
Yeah, I feel like I don't want to change him what's wrong with him we don't have lizberg each other maybe if we try
You'd all add up to one of her
What are you implying that?
Like none of us all of us combined are like just barely as interesting or cool as lizbert
That's not putting that much confidence in us if you must according to the tracking device
I placed on them by boiling bay, which is that way the last time I saw shelda
She was meditating in the sizzling sands shelda. Don't forget about egobel if she's not with lizbert
That's just
It's just the germa 985
Quote funny voice. I can't wait to play a legend of sheldon. How does that sound? Let's go get some sleep
Okay, we got to find shelda
Yeah, he does take the cake search for the search the frosted peak
mountain climb
ooh
All right. So let's take a look
We got a few people that we got find shelda find floof d and then climb the mountain
Floof d is in the boiling bay shelda is in the sizzling sands
We just gotta keep going where where we got those are two places that we have not seen
So how do we get to the sizzling sands? Didn't he go that way?
Sizzling sands. That's okay. This is shimmering springs
We go down to shimmering springs and maybe over to sizzling sands
Wait, there's a I want to open though. There's a hut down here. I want to open
That's the d sands
sands
Sands
That's you saying the d is weird sizzling sands sands
The d is silent when you say sands sand
sands
Hey, that's mine
This is that this is just a talk. This isn't tommy boy. Chris farley and david spade do this
Like oh, I love saying word. You know, that's another funny word limit limit
limit limit limit limit
This happens in tommy boy
All right. This is the boiling bay. We got some new things to investigate here
Golden a golden quibble
I feel like that's important. Whatever
I like this place
Oh, what's this?
Another uh a la soda
This bug skims along the ocean floor and sprays water at nearby sauce
He hates all sauce. It's a lacroix
This is apple a green crapple
Loves chocolate and loves
Honey
I love green apples. They're awesome. All right. What else anybody else we can look at?
Weird tree a tree that jumpy bug snacks can
Hide in
Well, I know. Okay, I get it
So we're gonna we're gonna trip them
Let's try it
So this we need to use the trip shot
Set it up right here
And then we're gonna aim it this way
And fire
Wait, I can't do it there
Can't I can't do it there?
Um red banana burr
Loves chocolate jumps from tree to tree. The trip shot could be useful here. Also. It is red
Loves chocolate. All right, but how do I set the trip shot up? I can't get up there
I broke it
Climb the tree
It did while it's in the air
I don't think that's what you do
Trip shot. All right, but hold on. Wait, can I go? All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
We can go from here to here
What the fuck is wrong with this thing?
All right. There we go
now
I'm gonna cover this in chocolate
He's gonna love it
No, get in closer
Get in closer. No, no
Get back here
He you gotta he's gonna come over here and spit at this but he's gonna stand here
I thought he was gonna come over and get mad. I don't know how far his range was
Get over here. There we go. Okay. Good
That's not where I wanted you to
Got a slug got a banana slug
All right. Now, what do you like? I want to get you too. All right, you hate all sauce
You have to destroy sauce. It's like in your it's built into your like bug dna
But i'm out. Okay. I've ketchup still
Hold on i'm gonna put this
Like here and then he's gonna get so pissed off at this sauce over here. He's not gonna be able to stand it
What was that? Here we go. That's your motherfucker
Now what how do I get you you?
Prefers to stay underwater but will serve us to pick up things that catch its eye. He loves chocolate
He'll come to the surface to pick up chocolate
I got no chocolate left
This is what I get for not being prepared
Oh, there's a bobsicle
Did I get another bobsicle just to have?
Yeah, definitely
Was that even a question?
Oh, he didn't hit the wall. Wait, this is like a multi-flavored popsicle
Hold on
This is one of those like rocket ship popsicles
No
It's a pata pawns now, what are you doing here?
Precious time getting here any longer in the way come let's finish our work
All right, you're going back to snack
Now assist me or be gone with you I will assist you if it means you go back to bugberg
Preparations my grand experiment are nearly complete
Soon, we will see if we can amend my ambulation
But for now
You guys hate that why oh no, sorry one person did sorry
Turn floofy's hand into a red banana beer. I already I got one
turn floofy's hand into a
a banana
Which hand doesn't matter a red banana hand
Snacktivator I have updated it. It is now capable of altering no more zonking off process of sonic anamnesis
Uh
My body remembers what I eat
Can change snackified limbs into anything i've ever eaten use it change my arm from bonaparte to straby
What I missed that I missed it I missed it turn floofy's hand into a straby snack experiment a straby
I can't even
I can't even talk it's too much
It's too much
It's too much on my missing leg
So I can just turn people's legs and body parts into whatever I want
You're the sick revitalize the frail
What strain are you smoking I don't smoke weed
Ungodly degenerate degeneracy again, I eat it
All right turn the limbs into cocomites
All right snack experiment
Oh
I need we need to get four cocomites
Or germamites
All right, there's coconuts. Maybe they're open to coconut. That's not a how did I lie down? What happened to me? Oh
What's this?
A sherby it drills beneath the sand waiting to unleash frosty vengeance on its foes
It's such oh
I love this thing
I love sherbert. It's like my favorite thing ever
You're my favorite. I need you. I must have you
No, don't die
No, no, don't die. Don't don't don't don't don't you're alive. You're okay. I'll put you out in a minute
Oh put him on fire. Come on. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out
Into the water into the water. Come here
into the water
Quickly, what do you like? What do you hate? What do you don't like? What do you what are your interests?
What do you have? What do you love your?
I got him
Saved him right when he was on the verge of death
I love sherbert. Oh, there's a clue
You picked up liz's notes on a secret code
I think this is I have oh, this is the second part of the code
I have both these now
Let me see. Hold on a muddy projector tape
Okay, here we go. Looks like I need to weigh down the pressure plates in order first left
Then right then center and after that push down hard on all three
All right
bad link
well
When you've rushed to make an image and you don't even care to save it as anything and it's called unknown dot png
That means that you just you so quickly tried to rush that out
At i'm assuming it's not very high effort
Okay. Well, I know the I know the code now the puzzle
I need to get coconuts. Shut the fuck up you idiot
what
Don't stfu me
I'll it'll take a powerful force to crack this bug snack shell open. How do I?
Okay, so launch rock at it. Can I grab it with the grabber?
I can grab it. Okay
So then now we need to smash it
How do we smash does anybody run at you? Is there a is it hold on?
Is there a bug that's there's a phoenix in there? Hold on. What is that?
Flamin cheese poof. Oh, it's a flaming hot cheeto
That's funny
Is it like a nutcracker in here?
a noodler
Bades and pools of lava. It's hot noodles
Can't be put out while in such a hot climate. Oh, this is like the hot. This is the spicy room
This is so cool. I love this
What are you doing in here? You don't belong here. You don't belong in like the hot spicy climate. You're lost follow me
Oh, come here. Come here. Come here
Come on. Come on. Run run run. I want the big one. I want the big one. I want the big one
Nice
No, you're a bobsicle
Okay, I need to break this
How do I smash this thing? There's got to be a smasher bug here somewhere
Are you a smasher?
Smash that put it in the lava
Um, I don't think
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. All right, how do I put you out?
sauce
Whoa get in there. He's no he's too heavy. I gotta pick him up
How do wait maybe they bump bump? Yo, yo. Hey. Hey
Okay works with its lesser to tackle any threats
Why is he he's he's dry. He's drowning himself
What happened?
What is he doing?
That's got a free soda
All right smash into each other
like the three stooges
Works with its greater to tackle any threats
They work together greater cocoa might lesser cocoa might
Works with its greater to tackle threats
That doesn't get no more info
They love chocolate. I don't have any chocolate though
um
Well, go go fight this thing. I need to go get some chocolate. Can I trip them?
Maybe I can trip them. Oh, you just got tripped get out of the way. I'm trying to trip you
I think that's too tall for you
Get them, please get away from me for a second
It's too tall
I'm just getting bullied right now
Yeah, eat that
Okay. I need two more
Do I do I need full cocoa rights?
cocoa might
all right
you can call me a like
A contrarian if you want you call me a contrarian fine. These are cooler than pokemons
Oh, there's nothing I want to get rid of. All right, one of the sodas
Sodas are easy. Okay, I got four here you go turn floofy's limbs into cocoa mites
Wait, what?
What do you mean? You only need one?
oh
My body has changed into more cocoa. So if okay, can you even comprehend what has happened?
We just deleted two sodas for no reason each one could change it to any other with the right stimulus
And now that is true of me now use this
A stimulant. I don't have time for a stimulant. Okay, my bonobo and strappy all at once
Oh, look at this buddy be
Rape skeeto. Oh, I didn't already know what that was
Yeah
Follow me. Follow me. Follow me. Follow me. Follow me
No
I already have one of you. Never mind. I don't care about you anymore
I there's a grapes guy. I gotta leave
Okay
We need a red banana per
And we need a strappy
All right, I can get you that
Turn floofy into noodler
I need a strappy
You need you only need a noodler. All right, I need a noodler
Where can we find a noodler?
Only noodler she's eaten the other ones. I know but where do I get a noodler?
Oh, it's in here. It's this noodler
spicy spicy spicy spicy spicy
Hot hot hot hot hot
All right, what do you like you love hot sauce?
So why don't we just have you come out of there?
You love hot sauce so much you'll come and get this and we'll just slowly make you go
over here
Out here into the water
Why am I doing this when I have this ball?
Come get it. He just threw it
Quick get back over there and make him happy again. All right, and he's extra spicy now
Good link. Hold on. I'm catching a noodle
He's not interested anymore. Oh shit
How do I get him in the water?
Oh, I know what to do. All right. Come here
Yes, yes, we're gonna go we're gonna go over the lava
Stop throwing him
Follow him
No, don't throw him in the water. Don't
Hey
Look, he's spicy
God damn it
No, what?
All right. All right. Oh, hold on. You guys are spamming. This is spam
um
Snacks are us in his ass
Blur me. Yes, my butt is juicy. Fuck off, baby. Well, I don't I don't I don't know what this is
I don't I don't know. I don't
What do I delete your discord?
I don't understand what this is
True true. I don't
It's me with like a the the popcorn. It's my massive ass
Stop stop. I don't what did I do? What did I do? Did I do something wrong?
I didn't do something wrong. Did I I gotta get you into the water?
Come on almost there
We're gonna let the tide take him the tides are gonna get his ass
Come on
Oh
Fuck get in there
Whoa, I just smashed him
How did I do that?
Oh, i'm sorry. No, he's not get out of here
Wait, i'm not ready. Stop spinning at us
What's it?
I don't even know what happened. He spit at him
Okay, okay, he spit at him
He put him out
We're good
We should be thanking that guy. He was trying to help us the whole time
Okay, so here's a noodler
noodle nose
an egg
You're a noodler now. Let's turn you into a
greater
cockamite
And a red banana
I wanted to have an egg nose
Threshold of crumpusness
When every cell of my body is bug snacks stabbing hand
It's an anti-vampire hand
I must find out
The answers won't come to me without further testing. However, I have exhausted my research
Every stream is a wild stream by the way
I look forward to working with you further
All right. We got uh floofies going back to snack bird
Our work here is done
But not quite because there's still a couple things I want to get
What did I not get here?
Well, it's nighttime now. So there might be some new bugs
to look for
possible
Get the golden snack
Oh, that's right
why
Why is the soda giving me the double middle finger emoji?
What's going on here?
Stop fighting. Stop it
I'll take that bob snack though
You guys all right? Why are you being so mean? Aren't you guys friends?
Why did I get involved?
This guy's getting stomped
Are they falling asleep?
You don't need more of these. All right. All right. I don't need them
I need to get the cheese. I need to get one cheesy poof
Don't follow me in here
Okay, you ever have a bug
In your room or in your house and you really feel like the thing's trying to kill you
This thing is trying to kill me
It's following me around. It's really pissed off
And even when you walk away, it's like i'm coming for you motherfucker
Oh shit
He just he just like scoop slammed him into the lava
Why did you do that?
Is he dead?
Oh shit, he's dead guys. He's completely dead
He's yeah, he froze over in his own coffin
I want that wait. This is the cheesy snacks up there
Can't scan it
fruity snack pod
I'll take it fruit snacks
Okay, what are these things?
These things look like they could be interacted with
Oh left. Wait, wait, wait. What's what is it? It's left
Okay
left first
Then right then center
right
then
Which center?
I mean at least we're gonna say this like does it matter?
Uh, this is not this is wrong puzzle wrong puzzle. Yeah, but I mean how many combinations of four could there possibly be?
64 possible combinations
Got it never have your password be four letters four numbers. Wait, this is how to get the sizzling sands. He's pretending
You must be new here. I'm always pretending always always
Still still still to this day always
We're sizzling sands. I gotta go back to town a buffalo. Cust. It's a spicy buffalo wing
Okay
I don't know why I thought that was I thought
That was waluigi. I was like, why is waluigi in the game?
That was just an egg. Oh dive bomb this it's a sandwich. Is it a cookie or a sandwich? What are these?
a loaded spuddy
a cheeser
It's a little cheese cracker poop breakfast bits. This is wait. Is there like a bacon egg and cheese sandwich?
I hope there's a bacon egg and cheese sandwich. So wait, that's the pizza monster
Looks like it could use a good slicing
There's shelda I found shelda what is that that's a there's a praying mantis over here with a diaper on
I don't care about you right now
I don't care what you have to say
You shelda
I'm missing so much action over here
Questions must cease wisdom can be gained only through experience
Where's shanandorf and shink where's she
Link
Shenandoah
That what you just described you just described like a girl named shannon
That has like a cosplay instagram account and she dresses up as ganondorf
And it's hashtag shanandorf and it's really good
It's very good. You're like, holy shit. That's pretty good. I'll let you get away with the shanandorf
I'm seeking inner peace
Shelder has renounced material temptations
So it is that shelter is really grumping hungry
Seek the yellow sauce within the great maw of stone
On this I shall be sustained
Your viewers just spiraled it down when you said shanandorf
Why no, I didn't. All right. What do I don't get cheese sauce for shelda?
I can't stay. Okay. I'm gonna call I have to call that person something else
That person's name is now shida
I can't say shelda without shanandorf and like
Shink and like the the shriforce of shrurge
What's that?
It's a burrito
As long as it's under the sand it can't be caught but it can't dig through solid rock. Ooh. All right good clue
More importantly though. I want to see the praying mantis
What the hell a large aggressive and destructive a void
This that is insane looking. Hold on
It's like a taco
The Dorito face burrito praying mantis
What is it? He he's afraid of the spuds, right? Okay. He's afraid of these things
I gotta get cheese sauce first and foremost. Hold on. What is that thing?
score pepper
Okay
I want the big pizza moth, too
All right, let's start first of all, let's get let's do this. Let's get the cheese sauce first
But I need to I need to go back to town and get rid of this stuff
I'm not gonna no overwhelming myself. I'm going back to town. I'm gonna donate
After I look at the top of the pyramid
Okay, this is like the pizza pyramid. What is going on over here? These two are just fighting. That's a pancake bug
Okay cheese. Oh, this is hot sauce. Where's the hell? I didn't pay attention. What do I get cheese?
cheese sauce
Delta only eats cheese sauce. I will have to find some for her so that she doesn't waste away get the cheese sauce
Beer cheese. All right, i'm going back to town. It's pancake flap. Wait, there's something in here, too
So a sody d
This liquidy bug lives in the oasis and won't tolerate the presence of sauce
the sunny d
sunny d
Drinking back your own heartburn that you burp up
the flavor
I love that one, too. I want that
Somebody died over here. I can make a case. No, no go go just go
Strawberry sunny d is good. I'm gonna have your paper in my hand and do a red line
through half of your sentence
So there's a red line through
Strawberry there's a red line through is good and in red ink I write next to it is disgusting
And I take there's a minus three points and you get like a 97
Hey, bro, just got done fixing up the old bridge
Would have done it sooner, but crondo wanted me to pay him. Oh, this is where the bridge was. Okay
Whatever that means no need to thank me. Just go find sheldon. All right. No
sheida
shelter
Okay, get cheese sauce. I gotta go back to town
fristol sweetie fly
That seems kind of rare
Why is it like you're all collectively pretending that shannon
Dwarf was not easily the most clever hilarious well-delivered joke the germans ever made on this channel
I didn't make it
You're lying to yourself if you claim that you didn't throw you into a laughing fit lasting 10 minutes
Derma works hard on this channel for us and it definitely showed with the shannon dwarf joke
I didn't that that's not mine
I can barely even see my screen from the laughing tears that blind me as I type this be better
Nobody in chat said that I didn't I just I reacted to it
All right. I'm gonna donate all this
Be better be better but the barbecue
Big beautiful be better burger. All right. Does anybody need I'm gonna feed some. All right
I want to increase some interesting
You look you have a shitty look
We're changing that you're gonna eat one of these and we're gonna change your why can I change your nose there?
The duck that looks even worse
Sherby's getting donated. No one's getting all right. What about uh, okay. No, these are getting donated snack spearmint
This looks like bones. Okay. Yeah, we're gonna we're going to have you be
The unfinished claymation rig puppet
You know, you're not quite done yet
I didn't I did not allow I did not consent to you taking a photo of me delete that
Yeah, you I want you to look interesting. Okay
hmm
Okay, I like the fry legs
fry legs
and bobsicle hands
I can't change you you have to stay that way you on the other hand
You know, you're fine. Everyone has like a quest for me, but it's I gotta focus
same thing
Maybe your whole premise is flawed from the get-go
Snacks aren't like plants
He's got two normie limbs left
Right, it's just um, you keep trying this over and over you can't it can't be like that. It has to be different and weird
If that's how you choose to look at it. All right for asking, but would you that's a great question
The answer I don't know. I can't even answer just all right time that person off
All right, let's deliver. How many more do we have to deliver?
I want okay
They're all going in I only need two more
Arthur how's it going?
Any luck? What does it look like? I'm sorry
I want to okay. Let's mess with his face
He's been he's been like this for a long time. Just give me every sort of bug snack that digs underground
I reckon it might aerate the soil or
something
I must lose one more score
But you don't give up just because things get tough straw isn't a snack nobody else believes in me
I gotta believe in myself
It's that or or nothing aerate the soil
All right. I'm changing. Let's change you a little snack experiment
Uh, let's see
Wait, what about this?
Mr pretzel
Whoa?
oh
French fry nose
Didn't I say I wanted to turn somebody into a pretzel?
Yeah, and then we're gonna do a soda a soda can. Yeah, that's good
Maybe soda can teeth
Ow. All right. You're good. I want to change you but I don't want to change you from
Every four-year-old's drawing. I kind of have to keep you like this
What about you?
Pineapple. All right, definitely pineapple feet pineapple feet popcorn hands
What about cheesy poof hair?
Uh olive head olive hair
What about popcorn ear?
Yeah, hold on. This is good
Ha ha ha
It's grandma
Kind of all right plant a snack world
In the garden. That's not what I want to track. What was I doing?
Okay mountain climb, right
There's still two other snackberg residents that I have not found yet and one of them's here
Okay, eggabelle. We have to go to the frosted peak
cheese sauce cheese
Where do I get cheese sauce from him? Yeah, I could use some practice. They'll be interviewing me every day when i'm a gazillion
Cheese, uh, you know what I could go I it's only been like an hour and a half. I can't talk about this right now
But i'm gonna just fuck it. You know what I mean?
I want right now
a like 12 inch
soft
like white sub roll
And just shaved ribeye
Just slapped in it and I want I want to watch the guy
I want to watch the guy take the big knife
Take the big hot loaf of bread and just slice down the middle with a huge knife
You know i'm talking you guys know what I mean, right?
He's got that long ass knife and he just goes like whoop and he opens it
And then just slap slap slap slap rib eye rib eye just like perfectly cooked rib eye
A little bit onion just like raw onion and then just take the fucking wet cheese sauce the gross stuff from the movie theater
And just pump it on there
Close it wrap it up in foil in foil. It better be in foil or I don't want it wrap it in foil
Put it in a bag and and hit the button thing and give it to me
Business king sales savant future ceo of starbucks the one the only
I will take if you don't have the movie theater cheese sauce. I will absolutely take you taking the sub roll
and using it as a glove
to pick up
the mess of meat cheese and onions that is on the flat top
and like putting it face down and
Closing it and picking it up. You know what i'm talking about
Where it's like the the meat the cheese and all the stuff is on the flat top
And they take the sub roll. It's open
They butterfly it open place it face down on the flat top with the meat and the cheese and everything and they
They like pulled it up scoop it up. I'll take that too
I can tell you lizbert's stank of opportunity
She came on tv talking big about this new super i can't wait
When you get to the end
The end of the roll
You eat the you eat the first ball. It's cut in half. Let's be clear
It's cut in half
You go through the the front part the end of the sub roll has this
bunched up bunch of cheese
In the very end of the roll and there's just a little bit of meat in there and it's the best part
Like vh1 is the best thing I ever ate
What am I doing delicious irresistible marketable they're gonna catapult the food network
Just like super cut me into that show he wants to fuck a sandwich
I don't want to fuck a sandwich if that's what you got from this
You all by the way, by the way, I got a store. I don't care what he's saying
I have a story for you
Remember when I played lego star wars and I told you guys i'm playing lego star wars right now
I have to stop like saying fuck and stuff like that, right? Because like this is like a kid's game
Okay, my nieces and nephews
Love lego star wars. It's like their favorite thing in the world
And I got a text
from my parents
And from my sister
that said
Hey, um
Just want to let you know the kids were watching your stream because they love lego star wars and we had to mute you
Because you kept saying fuck so much
It's like oh my god. Why did you do that?
The kids love lego star wars. It's like their favorite thing in the world right now, apparently
And I would have to I had to been like the only person on twitch playing that game
I was swearing a lot and like I think they were watching during the swamp section
so
oh
You could see my maybe my surprise and my embarrassment when I know that like my family is gathering around the fire
And putting uncle up on the screen while I freak the fuck out
At a children's lego game that they all love that i'm losing my mind over it like you have to yes
Just think about how I may have felt when I was told that I was salvaging. That's a community service pal
and I said on that stream
Maybe actually be careful because
This is a kid's game
Everyone here thinks she's so great
Oh
Man, I I gotta grow up. I gotta grow up a little bit. I think that's the wake up call
It's time to grow up, right? I gotta grow up. I'm like in my 30s. I gotta grow up
So I think that's the catalyst. That's it. That's elizabeth mega fake when push came to shove
Omega little time to grow up
What about peter pan isn't peter pan like 60
How old is peter pan missing you do the math
I bet liz and egg are living large in new grump city by now
like in in the actual lore peter pan was like a
Kid who never grew up and he never grew old and he was peter pan and he could fly
Right. He was like 65 years old
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, i'm not the nicest grumpus around. I learned early on that life is like a box of trash
You always know what you're gonna get
A trash man
Just go check out what a boat was see what you think coming there. I started garbage eat garbage
What a great show
Oh, I got a map at the end of the boiling bay past the shipwreck liz was definitely over there. You'll see
Oh, I did see that. I didn't let me pick it up though. I need to grow up. Also peter pan lore is cool, right?
I never said it was cool. I just said it was a fact
Toys r us don't grow up
No toys r us don't grow up toys r us just go out of business
Hey, they didn't grow up so they failed
Oh, sorry, you kept on distracting me. All right, where are we going? I need cheese sauce
Hello, do you sell cheese sauce?
Hey
Tiffany found some sort of treasure map while she was digging around they say it'll lead to a young
Imagine what a snack that size is worth. It's nolan north. I was thinking of taking that map off
Tell me it's not that's where you come in
Get me a bunk snack so delicious that trippany would die for it and we'll trade
Then we'll split the profits 50 50. Tell me it's not
Was it that was it? Yeah, that was kind of a nolan north yell voice
Uh, did you say 50? I clearly said 50 deal or no deal catch a buffalo cooked
So where do I get cheese sauce?
Where does one?
Get cheese. That's a lot of money somebody just just dumped a huge amount of my 50 community subs you gave you 50
Lag x 65 just dropped
50 community subs
That's a big one. That's a big one
Thanks for the insane sub drop that's insane that's 50 congratulations to all the
jobs
Sing the community sub song
Everything has to have a song on this channel. Oh, you're gonna go brb and go pee. Oh sing the ipeed song
Hey
Is this a children's tv show?
where all the basic functions I just sing you songs about like pooping your diaper and going pee and like
Why you should have good manners at the dinner table and eating fruits and apples is good for you
Why does everything have to have a song?
Should we have should I make a song about how like cleaning up after playing with your toys is a good idea?
All right. I gotta go get the hold on deal or no. All right main I and I got the mountain
on the mountain frosted peak
that is
flavor falls
Or here where is that? I think that's flavor falls. All right
Upgrade your shit
Sugar pine sugar pine woods, which is this way?
Flavor flave I don't even upgrade shit upgrade upgrade. I don't know. What do you mean?
Yeah, but it is it weird that this
Okay, so they watched it muted
But don't you think it's worse?
With this being muted. I don't think you would want to watch this muted
That's makes it strange and scary. It's scary
Okay, we're at flavor I almost said flavor flave peak because you got in my mind we're going to go this way
How do you explain that picture to your parents
Guys I think my parents just like kind of don't pay attention anymore
It's like
Okay after the family dinner stream
It was like, okay, he's like just kind of fucking gonna do this weird shit. All right. Well, hey, that's funny. I guess
Good luck son
It's funny because my mother actually does watch some of the streams
Be like, oh, you know, I saw you doing this the other day and i'm like you did
oh
All right. I'm still in the will right like I still just not i'm not you're gonna like disown me or anything
No, i've removed you from all of those. It's all going to your sister because she's smart. She grew up
I heard you talking about peter pan
All right. We're at the frosted peak
There's new enemies here the mountain dew in here
This bug washes away sauce and somehow stays unfrozen in the cold
No, i'm kidding. My mom my mother my parents are very very supportive. They are
They are
Yeah
Oh creamy patch this melty pile of ice cream and cookies
That is a banana
Sunday that's a banana split
Catches prey in its four legs and freezes them. It loves chocolate
Oh, that's cool. What's on the peak?
I didn't get any sauce. Uh
Ooh, what's this one?
Stoodler this boiling snack is a source of warmth
This is so cool. I love them
This is way cooler than pokemon it is
I'd like fucking like blast like blast punch me in the face some of you
I whatever i'll just rock my head back and go. I still believe it
Butter jam this elusive flyer is looking for its favorite sauce. It wants to be coated in honey
What's this? Free me goo jelly goop. Oh, that's definitely from the from the jelly monster. Okay, where i'm where the
Melty
Are these dipping dots?
These are different dots aren't they?
I didn't why did I not scan it? What's wrong with me? Why did I not scan this? It's dipping dots
I gotta get you
Oh, how would I pick that up? Right?
I think I could get it right here. I could get it. Yeah, I could get it when he turns around free up
Here we go. Ready grapple. Will that work? I think he's it's he
It's it's ooey and gooey. I don't know what was too sticky too sticky. So i'll get it. What are you doing? I fucking hate you
Whatever
Why did I just do that? I just jumped off the cliff. All right, I need
I'm so overwhelmed. All right, stop. Everybody stop. What the fuck is that? It's a chocolate chip cookie. I need sauces
All right, I get out of here do this right I keep on freaking out and just being like oh my god
Look at this. Oh my god. What's that? Did you see that? Look at this
I need to get sauces and get my tools ready and I gotta get sauces
Where am I? I'm gonna I gotta go around and collect sauces. I want a bunch of sauces. I'm gonna be ready for this
No more. Mr. Nice guy. Oh, sorry. No more. Mr. Nice jerma. No more. Mr. Nice guy
Who's the first person to say that?
Where did that come from? There was some movie in like the 40s or something, right? It was alice cooper
Was it it was julius caesar?
All right, what do you love chocolate don't have it it was socrates
Who was all right? Who was the guy back in the day that like drank the poison on purpose?
He was like, I know they're trying to kill me. Let them do it
But you all will see it happen and you'll know the truth
No, not rasputin. No, no, no, no. No, it was it was like some old philosopher
He knew they were trying to kill him and he drank it anyways in front of a bunch of people was like
I'm going to die now and you'll all see the corruption
And it had happened
Maybe that was socrates. It was okay. I need uh, I want chocolate. I want hot sauce. I want all the sauces all of them
20 out of 20. We're going to sauce hunting right now socrates was given the choice between death
And exile and he chose death. Yeah, that's what I mean. And he like did it in front of a bunch of people
Didn't he he was like i'd rather die with the truth than live with the lies
He drank it on stream
Oh fuck
What the fuck? Oh
Have you watched i've not watched anything
a raid from socrates
Yeah, he's he's just in like stunner shades
Playing like fortnight. No, this is peanut butter
I don't want peanut butter. I want chocolate hot sauce ketchup mustard pickles
ketchup mustard olives
Mushrooms ketchup mustard and mayo
Here's my fries. All right, where are we going?
Go to town re it comes like gandhi raid
I go to town re go to town re so where are they? I love you
These guys are always just arguing and fighting
You say
Just want you to know
That i'm on his side. I'm not on your side. I think I find you to be kind of in the wrong right now
I just as a friend if you like like I should let you know
so
Like i'm still you and I is still really cool. I just I just need you. I you kind of beat a dick
That's you got to be honest with you
I'll hit me up tomorrow though. Like we'll we'll let's go get like coffee or something and like just chill out
But like you I think you I think you're kind of a problem
All right. Bye. I'm sir. Dude. I'm sorry, but like i'm all right
Just hit me up tomorrow something man
Jesus dude, I don't fucking know what his problem is. I'm sorry. Like I just like talk to him
I don't know
No, I mean you just like you're doing your thing and he's kind of just like kind of flying off to handle his shit, man
i'm sorry
I don't want anymore peanut butter. Stop planning this
Oh
Psycho after all that i'm the i'm the guy i'm the bad guy
Get the plants i'm getting them look chocolate ketchup
the travis scott burger
Here's my quarter pounder with peanut butter hot sauce ketchup mustard and chocolate
Are you mad that i'm taking all these?
Where's the mustard? How have I not found that yet?
Second they grow they are taken
That's what you eat for dinner. I actually don't like ketchup that much
I like ketchup as a dipper not as something that's on uh food
I'm not i'd rather i'd rather
Be the one that rules the destiny of when and where ketchup is applied. I don't want it pre-applied to anything
I want to be the one to make that choice
I like it, but I don't want it on something
predetermined
Okay, I almost got full
I feel the same way about mustard too
Because it's here's the thing. It's really easy to overpower the hell out of whatever you're eating
If somebody applies ketchup that's too much ketchup than you wanted it's over
And don't tell me just scrape it off that it ruins the whole experience
Because then like the bun or the whatever the thing is already wet and kind of weird and soggy and it has that weird
coating of
No, okay. I've got 20 20 20 20 20
Same thing with salad dressing too. Give me the salad dressing on the side. Don't ever dress my salad for me
I will flip out want something I will flip out and I will fucking slap the thing down to the ground and I will
Throw it behind my shoulder
Okay, it's like omega low privileged
Oh that has salad dressing on it. Get it away from me
That's the ultimate that's the ultimate you spelt my name wrong on the starbucks cup privileged asshole, right?
Like do I really care that much?
Uh, my name is uh, jeremy not uh jeremie
Um, I don't know who the fuck that is
All right. Where am I going? Right back to the peak
Jaron
I don't people. All right
I don't know why people get so bent out of shape about shit, man
Like people get so mad and so annoyed over such little dumb things
Oh like you yeah, like you like you can't beat like a children's puzzle. So you curse out the developers of the video game
Fuck. Oh, that's not the same. That's not the same
You don't like ketchup. You just want to rant about how gross ketchup was and like get it off my fucking bun
Let me do it myself. Yeah, but it's different though. It's different because it's me
right
If it were you I would say that you're an asshole, but if it's me, okay
It's me so who doesn't I don't i'm not any no one can say anything to me. You know, it's really sad
That's like why the world is so fucked up
Who the fuck are you you shouldn't be here
It's not safe
You need to get off this mountain for the sake of your health and well-being
Trust me. I'm a doctor. Why is the dynamite strapped to you? What is that?
If another earthquake strikes
It'll cause an avalanche if you're up here when that happens
You'll be buried in snow and if you don't die from blunt force trauma
You'll asphyxiate
You I know you you're egg bell
Oh, oh you're the reporter the one liz was always talking about yes
You're that character in the germa 985 universe that we brought back to kill
To make sure he would never have to show up ever again in any form of future media. Where's liz what happened to her interview?
We were exploring the mountain there was an earthquake got separated
How can I help back home? Okay
be safe and
Please hope nobody heard that don't tell anybody i'm up here
Oh a real bad place to say that in a giant echoing chasm where I can scream out here and it'll echo everywhere
We follow oh I have to follow you
shit
Come on egg. You can figure this out. Just think like liz
Ha stop sneaking up on me or i'll quarantine you
What?
Well, it's a big mysterious door. How do you walk on that leg? There's some kind of weird lock on it
I feel like that's on there with scotch tape. I don't know what happened to our notes. You kind of just rag that don't you swear
I just need to get into liz's head space
Crack the egg
I oh why look at her. She's like, oh, that's my favorite
Snack
I love those
That's cool
bacon bacon bacon
Find notes on the mountain map
Oh that i've explored every area. All right notes on the mountain map
There's some kind of weird lock on it
Liz figured it out, but i've almost got it. I swear
Find the journal find the note find the notes find the notes on the mountain map shit
I know how to get in one
two
Three I could have just figured this out on my own without any puzzles or anything
I have them
Notes on the mountain map. I don't have the mountain map. I have this which is probably
You just skipped over everything you need
Blind am I actually blind though?
bugsnax file wiggles autograph
boiling bay map
circuit pine woods map the code
the strange device
But what's going on? I didn't pick this up yet. Whatever it was in boiling bay. It's beyond our help
Use the code code
the code
What's happening?
Yep, I just
Yeah, left right and middle, but how do I?
left
I have the code, but how do I weigh these down?
I need three grumpuses. We'll go stand on it. I can't do this right now
Go find the last paper. Yeah, that's what i'm talking about
We're all these all these shit talkers in chat. All these shit talkers don't understand
I need to go get the other note find the notes on the mountain map. What are you talking about?
Look at all these shit talkers
It looks like it might take at least three grumpuses to activate them. I don't have three. We have two
Here's the I lie. Here's the code looks like I need to weigh down the pressure plates. I know that
I don't have three grumpuses and I have not gone to boiling bay to get this last clue
God what about the keys?
I can open the cabinet in liz's hut
Chandler gave me the key to get into egg bell's chest
Where's egg bell's chest?
Bad uncle in the town. All right. Well i'm getting out of here. I can't do this yet
Everybody freaking out the code you have the code you have the code
Idiot you have the code. You're stupid
Yeah, you didn't know we needed three grumpuses, but more importantly i'm catching some of these snack pusses
All right. What do you want?
This bug washes away sauce and somehow stays unfrozen in the cold washes away sauce. It hates everything hates everything
Oh, oh you're hurting me you got me oh
Ah
Oh my god, it hurts. Ooh scary
Fucking stupid ass bug
Oh, okay. It loves chocolate
What the fuck what i'm kidding. It's a it's a choke
Okay, it catches a prey in its legs and what about more info?
Loves chocolate
Okay
Should I trip him? Let's see how I let's get a trip here
Can I attach this too?
About right here
All right. Now let's get some chocolate on me
Pour on the ball
Oh, he's already
Looks kind of sad. I don't i'm i don't want to do this to him. I don't feel bad anymore. This motherfucker's dead
I don't care anymore. He's dead
Fuck this guy. I'm killing him
How do I he's too cold to touch
So is there lava anywhere over here? There's fire over here
I can't pick him up
If you run him into the fire you follow me
No, don't spoopy
Come with me. I don't even need to put sauce on this. This guy's just a dick. He's gonna run into you
It's not funny
Shit
Get up here. Why are you not following me around? This dude turns around and then just goes no never mind
Doesn't he love chocolate? What the hell are you doing then man?
Well, actually keep going that way. Yeah, keep going this way. Perfect
Hey, what the hell was that? Get the hell out of what's this like?
All right, I burnt him now. I need to knock him out
How do I knock him out trip him shit, this is too high
Yes
Scoopy voodoo. Mr. Potter. All right, so I got those two now. What are you?
It's an ice cream sandwich flying and freezing cold thawing. It might bring it down
Okay, so he what did he not he got mad? Oh, he loves chocolate. Let's bring him to the fire
Where's my ball? I'm gonna put the ball over in the fire
I'm out knock him out
You're very far away though go to the other fire can I grab him when he's not cold anymore maybe
Pool ball. Okay, I gotta be ready. So I trip him got him. Nice. I got a I got a chili nilly
Who else is here? This is next gen
Uh, not really
This is not next gen. This is current gen. What other animals are here? Nobody in there who's in there?
Instagram, this is a universal
Shushka bug loves the spotlight. It loves to be on camera really. Okay. Well, you just made this really easy then come on out
Influencer bug. What do you like?
Loves the camera. What if I move the camera over here ready?
Instabug I did get two photos though. So we're good. I already got this creamy patch
I gotta go back to the boiling bay and go pick up that last note anymore
Oh, yep. There's the jelly jam sandwich. I want to get that you have it already. I don't have it already
Throw instabug off a cliff. What about the soup? Oh, yeah, there's a stew in here, too
All right. How do I cool? I gotta cool you off don't I? Okay. I need to cool you off
That's uh, there's a cookie bug over here
Be tripped right off the wall
or
Or forget that
He's kind of freaking out a little bit. That was funny. Apparently. Why can't I get you? Hi
Uh, are you good? Just all right. Just chill out there man. Okay. Um, go up there
Oh shit, he went up too high
Oh, no
no
crap
Stay right there. Don't move go up there and and go up there and get it. Oh look what's up there
Why are you not moving? What's wrong with you? You little fuck?
You fucking idiot. Why did you do that? Why did you fuck us both?
I'll be put out eventually and then i'll be able to pick him up. All right, stay right there chippy
Okay. Now you
You I gotta get you out of here the cold somebody has to freeze you who's going to freeze you
Somebody is you love hot sauce. We're gonna make we're gonna coat you in hot sauce
We're gonna get you out to the lake the cold
cold lake
Follow me. Let's go
This thing's stupid like stupid stupid stupid
Come on studler
It's chilly out here
It's very chilly
Sir, this is a wendy's
I didn't say anything. I haven't like talked in 45 seconds
That makes sense though pull up to the dry through just
Roll the window down
Here we go
No, get him
Get no
You fucking idiot
Get studler
Get him
Squeeze the life out of him. Oh, you look sad
That's my face
Oh
What the fuck?
Holy shit. They're like different days. It's a but just a banana. Hold on a minute. I gotta
What the who are you?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, leave me alone. Stop for a second. This is important. I have to
There's just a solo banana here
All right, it's time for you to die
Scoopy it drills beneath the snow waiting for unleash frosty vengeance
Go on the fire
Come here scoopy
Get over here. What the fuck is that?
Wait a minute. Who are you?
It was like a cherry
Wait, this is overwhelming. I'm overwhelmed overwhelmed overwhelmed
Cherry you got a cherry
All right. Now we want that. I want the banana
It's like three of them
Banana per oh, it's just a regular banana upper. I see. Okay. Ah, I don't really care. Let's get the uh, scoopy
All right scoopy come with me. I'm putting you in a fire this way. Okay. Don't you hate me?
Don't you hate my guts?
All right, you love chocolate. So
Let's go ahead and we know what to do here. Don't you love it you do
Come get some
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Over here who do you think you are spraying him? Where'd he go? Where'd he go? What this way?
Stop doing that you
They all love the chocolate. All right
Kill that thing
Oh, he's pissed. He's like don't try to hit me. No, no, no, no, no, no, no come here. Look, you know what?
Go focus on that
Now you
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Love it. Love it. Love it more more more more love it
Get the fuck out of here. This is the one. This is the one
This is the one no you get so disinterested so quickly
Come on. It's right there
It's right here for you. It's right here for you
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha oh what do I want to get rid of oh you all right deposit
I donate yeah, let's go donate and you do the mitch mcconnell laugh
I got a bug. Okay. Here's the thing though
I kind of want to feed these to people so they can have new cool things to put on their faces
This game looks like ass
You don't really think that right? No, it doesn't this game's cool. I all right
I really really like this member in pre-stream pre-stream channels will know the story here
This game was a 79 as of this morning
It started at 60
But as you all know the market is closed when the stream is offline
So we hit 79 people like dude 79. Fuck you. It's better than that like hold on a second here
Markets closed when the stream is off
We were still going up and it took today. Okay, we started today. Is it we're gonna come down
We're gonna pull back to like 77 75 after that big jump
We're still going up
by neo omega lull
Why oh what?
mega lull
What's the current price right now 83?
It's gone up. Oh, I didn't donate
Neo
What the hell are you talking about like the matrix? That was a donkey sound though. Excuse me. That was not a donkey sound
This is a donkey sound
Oh
That's one of those ducks at the store that you squeeze the dog toy never mind I tried it was a chew toy
All right, rewind it. I'm one of them. I'm a dog toy. I'm a grocery store dog toy or like a pet smart dog toy
Donate yeah, we can donate uh donate all of them size of your heart is grown and so your inventory grows, too
I do think I okay no more donating
I want to feed these two other
No, but then we get to we get to look at them forever
Oh, I should have fed the insta bug to somebody
What do you want? I hate to say it but ambus has a point bigger snacks means more to love
And be a bit smarter
Might respond better to my artless streamer begs chat for donations
Snackiest bug snacks you can find
We've that kind of matched up a little bit but
Begging for donations
I would I would honestly like i'll be real with you. I would I would never do that
What we have here is we have a a stream
Where I am broadcasting to you?
My financial responsibilities are not your financial responsibilities
If I were to ever make my financial responsibilities your financial responsibilities and tell you that you have to pay for them
Would be I find that that would be pretty that would be pretty bad
You're in debt though. I'm i'll be fine. What about the debt?
Like if I okay, like just let's put this way if I like wanted if I wanted like a car like a new car
man, I was really thinking about getting like a new car, but
Oh guys, like if you could like do that help me out here like
Why do you guys like sitting in your dorm like in a dorm room?
Just like uh
The fuck are you talking about jeremy? All right, this is where I need to go. No the boiling bay
Like please please can I have a car?
Like yeah, you can you you have um
You have like
10 000 subs, but please please today. Can you just give me money for a car, please?
You already you already we already do
like 10 cars
But no, no, no, but give me more. I want a car today
Jeremy fuck off
All right, where are we going? We need to go boiling bay shimmering. Oh, you know, it's scorched gorge
To the boiling bay, which we were going the right way
Use the keys
Oh shit, he disconnected
He disconnected from twitch
It's the same exact background
Multiple worse noise contenders. I don't know about that and and another thing where we're going. Oh keys. Whose dead body is this?
You sicko
Well met well
See you around
Hey there. Hey there. What am I doing? I open up doors. I have to open up doors keys
One two three five the finest wearers of the land. You're going to make your biceps explode
No, sorry safe travels safe travels
That was it
I can do this
If you insist i'll go ready some ice packs
Ah, you're a tall one. No, no, no, no, it's my you're a tall one
I love that game even though it sucks
All right. Well, there's a we got we got keys to open up stuff
Seven fresh opponents. Are you ready? All right. Are you ready? Are you ready?
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Leave me alone becca. It's not not everything is mr. Satan. What where's the there it is. I have a key
Ooh, there's notes in here
You picked up a video diary
clue clue clue clue clue
First I thought that was another one. All right, so this wait
Video diary two
Why's the audio so low? I don't care about either of these characters. I'm just being honest
I don't care about anybody in this town
I I kind of like the little donation guy and the funny mayor
Oh and and the and wiggle I like wiggle
Who the hell is that?
That's a that's the is that the bicentennial man? No. No, what's the robot? What's the robot one? I robot
No, no, no robots. It actually was called robots. Yeah, the movie robots
Those you guys that are saying who the fuck is filming this
Don't put it past somebody that lives in this town to be walking around with a fucking camera and pointing it at everything
I've been doing it for the last seven or eight in-game hours every cutscene. I've done this so
Is it really that hard to believe?
All right. Well, that's two films. I have another key
Or something. Oh
Uh-oh isn't we're gonna get the big reveal?
Syringe in here there comes a big reveal. Oh wait, we skipped
All right. I like I like I like the egg lady staged footage. I actually kind of like everybody who I have my hard
Frosty outer shell but my soft guys. I have no idea who would be taking these videos
Who was taking the photos in this town? There's no way nobody does that
I'm using i'm filming the film right now. I don't know why I thought there'd be a better view
You're filming me
Filming the film that somebody else filmed like this. This is piracy. This is like, okay
That's the dvd. I'm I'm like the torrent
And you're you're like the person on the side of the road that sells this
Like you torrented the torrent and you're selling it in like these weird jewel dvd cases on the side of the road
Oh, there's another there's one right here. Which one is this one four?
No, we already saw this movie turn it off. I'll rebuttal you. All right, you want to do it again?
All right, put it down you you take the first shoot me then
Shoot me. You won't do it
Everybody just relax relax relax relax put it down relax
We don't it doesn't have to fucking end like this
I'll put mine down if you put yours down put it down
I'm putting my gun down here. Okay, my camera
All right
Okay
There we go. Now we can be civil
Fucking double kill god damn it. We both had the same idea
Tarantino
Why do they have normal bodies?
There's no cinnamon buns on their noses and like hamburgers on their feet
This is before snacks. Oh
I thought she had the gun up. Why is she just pointing at me? Is it another gun?
Oh, I wasn't prepared for that. What do you want? Hey there bestie a new target
This is her house
Oh
No, it's not this is not her house. This is like the movie theater
Find out what cromdo does at midnight
Okay, I did I used all the keys
I don't care about what cromdo does at midnight. I care about
Opening the secret door
Okay, chandler would like to talk to you about something
Track the code. All right. I need to go to the the sizzling shimmering sizzler or whatever it is
We have to investigate
the
That part that I remember I tried looked at it before
Yeah, we got across the bridge at uh, the
crusty gorge to the sizzling shore
Because all these names are almost identical. They just get open at the source you figure it out. Oh, okay. Here we go
There's a place
That we have not been I glazed over it. I didn't pick up the clue. I'm gonna pick it up right now
What do you care about? What is this? What do you care about then?
You are so negative today germa these bug people are just trying to live their best life and you always put them down
It's pathetic because I wanted to be a bug snatch catcher when I was younger and I just didn't do it
All right, and watching these people do that and I wanted it. I wanted that I have to catch one of these
All right, that's a dangerous one though. That's a rare bug
We are in the right spot, right? Yeah. No, we're not we need to go to boiling bay
How do I get to boiling bay?
How do I get to boiling bay from here? Catch this guy first?
All right, how do I what do I got?
large aggressive and destructive
It's afraid of the potato bugs things
It loves hot sauce and stuff. Okay. So how do we put you out? Is there water anywhere over here?
I don't think there's any water
How do I put you out? Does anybody here have water? Is there? Oh, there we go right here
All right, get off that
I need you over here
hot sauce
Go get it
What do you think about that?
And what do you think about this? I'm in the water now
Okay, now we just I mean i'll take that for free now let's trip them
Did I get him? No, I didn't get over here
Fuck why did you exploded?
What the hell?
What is that?
talk roach
What the way I could I could just pick him up. Why why could I could have just picked him up?
As long as it's under the sand. Oh
I just kicked his ass. All right. This is I gotta get this right. I'm gonna set this up. We're gonna do a
home alone
Trap here
So let's get this in the right place
No, I need a good spot for this. It might be okay
All right, that's gonna be
Never mind. There we go. All right. Now we're gonna get you to follow me over here
with hot sauce
We'll roll the hot sauce
on you
Hey come get me you big alien
Told you that story, right?
how I went to disney world and
There was that scary ride with the alien
It was it was actually a terrifying experience. It was it like epcot
It was called like the alien or something alien encounter
I've told that story before yeah where I put I put my my thumbs in my eyes
No, I put my pinkies on my eyes and my thumbs in my ears
To make sure I didn't see or hear anything the whole ride
And then when it got like it gets like pitch black
before the alien breaks out
And right when it got pitch black my brother said
Come over here you big stupid alien
And I remember just I heard it kind of muffled through my enclosure I had and was like don't say that man
Don't say that he's gonna come over here. Why would you do that?
I'll make a little baby. Yeah, I was eight
I was eight years old
Get off
Get off of this now
last year
Get down
I'm gonna get you
Ouch
Ouch ouch
I wish I could I want to play that so bad
Why won't you get off?
I'll just steal your egg then
Oh, there goes your egg
Okay, I I don't know. He won't come down. I need to launch him off. Hey, look at me. I'm so scary
Oh you dummy. All right now get over here
Right into my trap
Good. Good. Good. Good right in here. Oh, no. I'm in the water
Look out
Where'd he go?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no this way. No, no, no, no, no this way this way
Okay, no, no, no, no, no this way this way this way this way this way
To me to me to me to me to me to me to me
what
It's just like stole that
I got a talk roach
Any more of those or did I fuck the whole thing up? Although, excuse me your favorite sauce is
Hot sauce. We're gonna get you to dive bomb this
What do you think about that?
Something down here bridge handle. Wait, is this done like a shortcut?
I bet I could use the snack grabber on this. I bet you could
Oh
Wait a minute any of the what's that?
Unique rasbee. It will need help escaping the underground
Okay, I can do that
Oh, well, i'll just get you black raspberry. Nice
Is there anything else down here that I haven't gotten?
A hall of scorpions is that that looks like it could be
Broken by something. I don't know what that means
I do know what that means
Where the hell is this?
The hall of scorpions. Oh shit. I'm about to collapse this whole thing
What does that do for me? Oh
Uh, I mean, that's I guess that's kind of cool
Oh
Nobody touched that
Okay you
You follow me got him. I want that thing too. I want to score. I want to I want a scorpion
Okay, so you
lurks invisibly and
I got a free pancake. I want that. That's the ultimate prize the supreme moth pizza. All right. I need to go
Where's the
Go back down here for a second
I feel like I missed a few things down here because I could go this way or I could go that way
Yep. All right. I'm up top
No
Is there anything else to do here?
No, you're desecrating ancient artifacts. It's a long way to save rocks. I want the cheese
I want the cheese puff. They were rocks those that wasn't an artifact. I didn't desecrate the scorpion things
I desecrated the rocks
There was just a bunch of wait. I didn't desecrate anything. Let's be clear. I didn't know there were no desecrations
I'm an opportunist
Oh, what's this? This pyramid is just rocks. No, the pyramid is a pyramid
That was the clearly just rocks in the way then I blew up the rocks. Is there where I need to go?
That's a little shortcut. Okay right here
Remember this I do
Already got these. All right. So now I gotta go to the bottom of this place. There's a little beach
Pick up the clue. It's down here
Love you, by the way. Love you
Down here. All right
Here it is. I already got it
Yeah, we but we told you that an hour ago, but um, we told you it was the other half of the code the paper
Okay, but how do I get a third person up there? I need to interview people. Oh
You must investigate and do interviews didn't I interview everybody already? Who have I not interviewed? I need to get shelda
This lady wants cheese sauce. I don't where am I supposed to get cheese sauce at cheese bay
You know, I have not picked up one of these guys yet
Very elusive. It's literally adjacent to her
Oh, well, I don't have time for that. You get it from chuck-e-cheese
You know chuck-e-cheese is a fun thing to say doesn't when you when you say the word chuck-e-cheese
Don't you think of a gross microwaved pizza? I just think of a pizza like a cheesy gross pizza
chuck-e-cheese
It's the ch
Followed by the ch, you know like chuck-e-cheese
I got lots of donations to give
And who am I who have I not interviewed?
I don't want to do what do you work for you who has not had an interview
These two haven't been interviewed, right? So you slithered back into town up to another grumpy naughty scheme
I'm not participating in your delusions brother. You waste your talented mind for a second. I was like, when did I feed this lady black olives?
Those are just glasses
What did I I don't know your moral compass and stop working for the man
Oh, please don't try to dress up your cowardice. I'm no coward. I you still haven't told the green meathead how you feel
Green meathead don't try to confuse the issue
I thought so lead me to my business and i'll leave you to yours. This is a minion
It is a minion don't have my secrets plastered all over the front page news
Okay
Let's interview one of the last two people we didn't interview
I suppose I can reveal a tad bit so long as my identity is protected
This game is really interesting because I could see where it was
Sort of created
It's like you're in the bath this person was in the bathtub
and they were just like kind of like kind of falling asleep in the bathtub and they're just like
Eating bugs that have food bases and you turn there's muppets with bugs for food. I'm gonna make it. Let's go
I think i'm uh, that's a great idea
That's dangerous
I don't mean like I don't mean sleeping in a bathtub. I mean like
You're just chilling
Redacted he thought I needed some fresh air or something much as I hate the outdoors. I simply can't say no to him
Do I talk like that I feel like I talk like that sometimes I get self-conscious
Do I do that? I probably do sometimes not all the time though
I surmise they are some sort of synthetic life form designed to beguile our taste buds
john oliver
I'm so glad you asked. I believe that maybe no, it's not john. Oliver hit it on this very island hidden somewhere deep underground
I have charts. Let me show you my charts later
I want to do it so bad. I don't I don't I was too exposed
Fluffy tried to wrap me up in their experiments now that lizbert and agabelle weren't around to occupy them
I could see that this was the next step in the grumpin otis plot against me
Stop interviewing this nerd and catch some bugs
I have to interview the nerd so then somebody one of the nerds will follow me up the mountain and stand on a plate
For me so I can open the door to go in one day
Do you really think those are all coincidences? I made that joke twice recently a joke
I don't
John oliver reference foolish bone in her body
She could rival me in wits and chat redacted blow an arm wrestling
We would share secrets now and again
Dreadful and chat interview you sure what do you ask me something?
I'm not telling you the terrible secrets because they are terrible. Who are you?
My name is jeremy elbertson. Why eat ass?
redacted
Excellent interrogation chum so great that you deserve another hugging experience. Why do you why are you pretending to like this game?
This must not go on the record elizabeth mega think discovered something on the island
You're not using the chart correctly
This is important stuff hold on extreme caution I can tell you what to find it but the rest is up to you
There it is
Um, you guys are doing you're reading the german 985 streaming chart incorrectly
If I stream a video game
more than once
That means that I like it if you see a video game that is streamed more than one time
That means I found it to be worth doing again
saw
Well, here's the thing about saw
I was I was like self bullied into playing saw again and beating it because
Um, I got saw two. I I already like bought it. I like heard already ordered it
And halloween was coming up
So I just I had to
And I didn't notice how I didn't do any more of saw two
I did saw one
All right. Let's finish saw one because saw two here comes halloween never playing this fucking game ever again
All right, let's uh, I want to no donations for a little while. I want to feed
I want to do some interesting builds. Who do I want to keep? Okay. I'll keep a so dd. I'll keep a loaded spud
I need the praying mantis for
A reason right? What's the reason?
Somebody wants this don't they okay a ramble right donate a praying pecan tus
Here we go. He's huge
All right. There you go. I did it. No matter what size there's always room for more in my family
He's huge. He needs his own pen
He needs his own pen
Plus two link. What's the context of this? I remember doing this, but I don't remember what the context was
Why is the hat the same?
It's like the same person
This is that's creepy. I don't like that picture
Wrong link
That's not the wrong link. Okay, let's go. I gotta pee really bad
Does it ramble later?
Wait, are we breeding?
insect food
I'll bear it back. I'm gonna sleep in your bed for a minute
Am I leaving?
No, no, you open up the pen. They're all running away
What'd you do?
Like that hat man, it's fucking me up. It's the same hat the same person
And they're gone without so much as saying goodbye bug snacks will be simple
They don't have it in them to be cruel
But cruelest thing you can do is not care at all
Oh, maybe I should pay wiggle a visit
We have to go wrangle all these back again. I hope not
This is are they terrorizing the town? All right, let me go. I gotta go pee
Let me take a quick break. I'll be right back
I think it would be kind of funny
If I were to come back from the break here and unpause the game and the whole place is just being attacked and on fire and shit
All right. Um, is he just locking himself in his house? We don't get it. Oh, we don't need to find
Does he not care anymore?
All the animals escaped
weren't we in the middle of
What's wrong with you? What happened to your teeth? Oh, right foil
Uh, okay. Let's continue what I was doing. I shouldn't even
donation campaign
Oh, but I don't the I can't the
This is open. I'm not gonna donate them. I'd rather eat them
If I look they're gonna run away
Should I he song or riot?
There's no peace on
What's up, bro?
How's it going?
Okay, I have let me see the map near the mountain peak hang left from the trail and take a narrow ledge north
It's the attached map the pressure plates won't activate. I think the ancient grumpuses
Need to be fed first, but what do they like to eat?
Okay near the mountain peak hang left from the trail and take a narrow ledge north
See you later
Riot riot riot riot riot riot. That's fine. You can ride all you want. You're not getting up. You are not getting a
When we use the toilet we no we're not doing that. I am not doing that. That's why I'm drawing the line there for real
I'm not getting any more than that
songs
There's like a company that just makes a variation of the same song with 3d animated characters
It's like baby eats vegetables and it's like peas peas
Baby eats the peas
Yum. Yum. Yum
I eat them up the peas and they replace words and they just kind of change a little bit of the animation and they have
a billion views each
Johnny dude, dude, dude
Johnny
I was real. Okay. I gotta be honest with you during the johnny dude to do arc of like meme ability from like a year or
Two ago. I sat there. I watched dozens and dozens and dozens of like weird children's song videos and they made me laugh
During like the johnny dude to do joke that everybody thought was so funny. I was like, you know, what what else is out there?
I I think some of you guys underestimate just the kind of shit that I do
Last night. I watched a compilation of wood cutting videos
Just people splitting wood and just cutting wood
It's like real
I'm like, yeah, that's nice. I don't know. Just gonna fell like it. Okay, here we go the ledge on north. Here it is
Found it. All right, the gods like to eat food
I haven't figured out anything. Oh my grump. Is it to find this? I know what you mean yesterday. I played
I watched some guy play bug snacks
It's not
Says i'll need to activate these statues
Feeding them the snack they represent
Thanks for the help
I'll take it from here
Okay
You know why I wish I could just say yes, please do that. I don't care do it you catch half
I'll catch the other half and we'll meet back here. So good
Activate three bug statues. All right, what do you represent?
What did I feed you?
I didn't even click anything
Oh, okay you
Represent, uh, this is it looks like a cookie you represent cookies
um
you
Represent
I don't know
You represent marshmallow
Hamburger stuff. I don't know
You're ignoring a raid. Is it what raid came in? Oh master gear
Sing the raid song. I don't even remember what the raid song is
raid
Thank you for the raid
One two three you eat it up you see
peas
Thank you for the peas
It's a raid do do do do do do it's a raid do do do do do
I don't know what to feed these fucking people. You want ice cream sandwiches. You want hamburgers. You want cookies
I don't have any of these
you want
bread
Ice cream. I think I have ice cream. How do I not have any of the things anybody wants? This is definitely you're a cookie
Chippy stat. Oh
Scoopy statue
flutter jam statue
Stoodler statue
a
Soty statue and a chili nilly statue
Do I think I have a soty? Oh, I do I have a soty
But this is a mount soty though
All right
We need to
Somebody remember those we need ice cream. We need a scoopie. We need a chippy. We need a jammy
We need a chili
We need a soty
And we need a stewie that kind of looks like stewie. It looks like stew. I'd say right
Okay, let's go
You only need three. Yes. So whatever I find first
Worst joke 2020. You can't just say everything is the worst joke 2020. Wait, that's a scoopie. No, that's a scoopie banana pee
Not the same thing
Don't wait. Here's a mountain dew
Mountain dew I got you
Come on up
It hates all sauce, right?
You're gonna hate that aren't you?
Wait, cover the sauce
Cover the ball in sauce and get it
What a moron
Moron. Oops. I forgot. I forgot I had to catch you
There's one
All right. Now I need a scoopie a regular scoopie. Not any weird scoopie worst game 2020
All right now actually ban that person for life
for life
You know what triple life sentence?
I need a scoopie this way. There's a stewie up here, too
Whoa
I need oh, it's a chippy
Yeah
Back here
I'm gonna get two in here. All right. Wait, wait, wait. This is it if I get these two it's over
You need a poopie too
No such thing as a poopie. All right. There's the chippy. That's his route
He's coming right at me. Wait, hold on. He's coming. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, okay
Now I gotta get you
stew
You hate you love hot sauce. So we're gonna do the same thing. We go. Here we go the ball
Where's the ball? Oh
Come on. Okay, let's bring you to the cold
Is it weird that i'm jealous that I didn't get to do every single voice in this game?
Yeah, if I could go back in time and do every single character in this game, I would want to
No, not the ones that talk though. No, fuck that. That's I don't do that
I'm talking about the weird animal bugs foods. That's what I want. I don't want to be the people talking
I want to be these things
All right. Where's the uh?
What's that cream cheese bug?
There we go. There's a bobsicle
Now you're in trouble
Yeah, so anyway in the dlc when they have like bagel and lux
Could I be like luxie luxie luxie?
Come on and put like a little filter on that
They can just use that for free
Luxie luxie luxie
That's that's for free. Just use it if you want you can use it if you want to
You don't have to pay me. I don't care
No, let me do it again do over do over
Luxie luxie luxie
Luxie
That's better
That was mortal combat. That wasn't worse. How is that worse?
Fine, i'll do one more. You can use what anyone you want
luxie
Oops, how was that worse?
No, you're distracting me. Stop distracting me all of you leave
Get back here. I need a icicle
All of you leave
Please don't please don't
Will he go in the water?
Well, I know how to get him in the water. What am I doing?
Stoodler move we got it
I say you got it
You're a sellout. Wait, did you not hear what I said? Just use it for free. I don't
That's how is that a sellout?
All right, where's studler? All right studler
That's that's a studler, right? Okay
studler
delicious
this is a
Get mount sodie
This one was a
I don't have a chili nilly
it's
A chippy right here. That's it
You're okay
You are okay, right blood has been spilled drowsiness numbness or missing limbs
Sorry
Uh, don't mind me. I got the rest of the snacks
Oh, you got the other ones. Okay, that helps next she says
She says we need three grumpuses to do the final. No, we don't know any other grumpuses. It's just us
Mountain is unstable. I don't like there's like 10 people back at home. We could pay
Two strawberries to come up here. I can't let anybody else get hurt for my sake
I feel bad enough involving you
Oh, what would lizbert do?
Ask philbo
Liz trust philbo for some reason all right philbo
We're gonna bring phil we're gonna sacrifice philbo watch your step on the way back down, okay
You know, we can't we just put a big rock up here. I don't understand. There's only three plates
You're telling me you can't just pick up this snowman and like put them over there
Why?
Just build a take a bunch of these rocks and put them over there. We need three people
This makes no sense. It's completely unrealistic and this game is just
Really needs to dial back some of the cartoon bullshit
More realism brew brew
That's one of my fish. Okay, my fish is fine. Let's go talk to philbo
You're asking for realism in a game where you eat bugs
See you in a hundred years where that's the number one source of protein for humans. They're saying I will not eat the bugs
You won't even you won't even really think about it. Will you it'll be
It'll be ground up
Turned into a patty at a bunch of sauces and flavorings added to it. You won't even you won't even care
All right, philbo
I need you
I know where lizbert is
Let's go bugs are literally land seafood bugs are literally land seafood
I don't understand
Beyond bugs, yeah
We'll eat too many bugs and then we'll have to make fake bug meat
So 200 years from now people will be so shocked at how much like the real thing beyond bug tastes like
I can't believe it's not bugs
This is not I don't this is not like my typical bug spread I can tell the difference
Get the fuck up grandpa get with the times
Yeah, you really came out of your shell, huh?
Hey, um, so why do you want my help? I thought you would have asked chandlo chandlo's got snorpy to worry about
besides
around for years
I can't sprint
Why can I still hear them fuck they're waiting for me. I want to get in front of them quick
Let me get in front of them by at least a large enough margin where I can launch one of them off the cliff
I've wanted to do it for like the last two hours. Let me get in front of them and go a little bit faster, please
please
Oh
Liz thought it might be some kind of ancient temple to bug snacks
Wait a minute if this door takes three of us to open. How would lizbert get inside by herself?
What makes you think she's behind it? She didn't because she has to be
I looked everywhere her friends came in with her and they had to make a choice
You figure it out
Lizbert still there still alive
With a bunch of red stains around her mouth
You figure it out. This is it
ready
one two
three
Holy shit, that almost crushed his head. That was close. You killed us all. Hey. Hey, it's okay
Agabelle that was kind of scary, but we're fine. We'll just try it again and no i'll try it again
You two are going home. What agabelle? I want to find lizbert just as badly as you do
You don't have to do this alone
Yes, I do
I'm a burden to everybody around me
That's why she's gone
What do you mean?
I was being stupid and I slipped up on the cliffs while I was trying to show off
The earthquake hit and and I was gonna fall but liz saved me
Like she always does
She got swept away and then the ground opened beneath her and
I'm so sorry. It would have been really great for you to tell me this like six hours ago. Please do it
Please just go
I can't stand to see anyone else hurt
You know
When I was looking for lizbert instead of finding little clues and hints on little map markings
So I tried eating this purple flower. She died in an earthquake
And then I went
What the fuck I fell in a hole
And and by the time I dragged myself out of there, I was so tired and hungry. I could barely move
That's when we met buddy
That's awful
it was
because
you know
I can't make it on my own like you and lizbert and it's times like those when I could really use a doctor
All right, I get it
I need some time to think
I still want to figure out what I got wrong. I have a jacket by the way. I do
We've been out here for a long time
And then we'll find liz together
Thank you. Philbo
Stay safe
Oh my god
No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait
I killed him. I killed him. I killed that fucking guy. I killed him. I got him
I got him
I killed the mayor. That means i'm the mayor now
He thought it was fun
Oh shit
He's gonna die down there
Quick remove the evidence. You're right destroy. You should have taken a picture of him. All right. So now what a big story
Oh, I need to all right. I'm missing two interviews. I gotta get cheese for this lady
All right, let's go get cheese for this lady. Sometimes I dream about cheese
Me too. This coffee is garbage. You gotta you gotta get better coffee then man grind your own beans
And like percolate the coffee for like four hours. That's worth it. He's back
All right cheese for the cheese lady now really good coffee is awesome. I agree problem with really good coffee is
It really just it's kind of a pain in the ass
I don't the grinding beans right from the bean factory whatever and then grinding them up getting the hot pour over it
I don't I just want the caffeine and like it's nice to have some
If you go to a restaurant friend like a nice cappuccino at a restaurant or espresso from like a nice coffee place
I love it. I do
But I don't do that shit at my house. All right. Where is the where is she?
Well, if you can make your own cold brew, that's good, too. It's easy
Get the pre ground good shit. Yeah, you can put it in the car. That's fine putting in a cup
But i'm talking about the people that really want to you get the beans out you grind them and you do the slow
pour over type stuff
That's too much for me. Just like just I want to open my mouth and just fucking drink it
All right, where's the cheese lady?
I thought that if this was the cheese I was gonna be so mad. All right. Where's this cheese?
Do you want a cheeser?
Within the great maw of stone
Yellow sauce in the maw of stone
Where's that?
Temple it's right there. How do I get it? Here's your cheese
Oh chance eight eight eight chance one first and and break out of my current shelter
So
That was hard to do my throat hurts after that a crack two egglers
Wait, uh, where are those? What do you want first and break out of my current shelter?
So too must you break?
I don't know what those are
you
Where's the oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I know what those are these crack them open. All right crack these
How do you crack an egg?
Will you crack this?
Crack that
oops
Okay, it worked
uh
Wait, come back
Wait, I need to scan you egglar without a shell. This egg makes for an easy meal. It loves hot sauce
So I need me too on eggs tabasco on eggs is incredible
Hold on. I got you
Yeah, tabasco on eggs is unbelievable
Tabasco on anything is uh tabasco on a tuna sandwich is
I must have based like god damn it. You guys are just fucking inside my head again
um
Tabasco on a tuna sandwich is really good
Tabasco on eggs is really good tabasco on pizza is also very good, too
Hey open this one
Thank you. Almost had it
Yes preach
I too have burst from my shell and so oozes forth my spiritual
This game's edible pokemon. Yes, it is
This edible ain't shit. Yeah, see you in an hour when you've melted into the couch
Removed yet
One still lost in darkness seeking the light
For only in the light of mother natural ray can oh I broke
Break two prior. I already did it
Seek a raspy
Deep below please germ. I worked hard on this
I I wonder if you did how did you do this? This is very fast. This is not even 10 minutes ago
That was like five minutes ago. It's pretty good for five minutes
It's great for five minutes
The detail on the clouds back there that alone would have taken me 10 minutes. It's another one. All right
What is it?
You guys in the make the person fat filter and make the person old filter you guys love these so much
You can't get enough of them. I look like a bird the dark souls character
Yes, and they definitely talk
Like this, how are you? I see your hollow
I'm as well
seek
the key
to the room
Seek it well
Every dark souls character for some reason they just have a wheeze laugh at the end of every sentence fashion one
I'll guide this raspy to one's side
All right guide a black raspy from the under ruins. Oh, I know where that is
We found that earlier. This would have been really really hard if I didn't accidentally find this
Fill up on chocolate
He's over here. There you are. Don't you love chocolate? You love chocolate. You love it
But it's going to be kind of annoying because you're here
You're annoying and nobody wants to oh that looks good. It looks pretty delicious. I'm not gonna lie
Oh you okay. You just like hurt yourself. Okay, i'll just take you
You come over here and you do that too double middle finger already. You're already pissed
Hey, what are you doing?
Come get this
you
Nope. All right, mr. Rasby
It's time for you to follow me
Let's go
Hmm
Get over here. Don't run away. What the fuck did you just do?
pissing me off
Come on rasby
All right, just step over here
Don't be afraid of me
Did I win?
Yeah
Turn the radio back on
I don't want i'm gonna get in trouble
The time has come egress from the sand scape so it is that shelter survives
I don't know what you meant was a metaphor go back to town so I can interview you
To bring such clarity to my followers
Fuck whatever. Okay, you have been delivered
to snack burg
now
There's only one thing left to do
that's interview the two people I have not interviewed
and find
elizabeth
Burt side quest ignored pepe hands. Well, let me go back here and see what's going on. I'm not done
Hold on a minute
Don't look at that. It's gonna make me hungry
Philly cheesesteak. Damn I could go for one extra onions
I think that's the plan tonight boys and girls. I think it's philly cheesesteak with extra onions and cheese sauce on it
And i'm just gonna melt into my couch
This whole game makes you hungry kind of
All right interview
Let's refill on this stuff
You have cheese sauce here
You do you fight? Yeah, every time I find a new thing you get cheese. It's good cheese sauce
That sounds so good. That sounds so good night
Good night
Hey, can you like come over here and just rub your hands in this and then just present them to me so I can bite them
I would really appreciate that
We're gonna plant a burrito and i'm gonna donate. Okay, we've got let's donate an egg
Uh donate them all
I only need one more bill bow wants to talk to you
Uh, where's the party? Hold on not yet. I have interviews to do
Sorry, I am not here to spew gossip for that obnoxious rag you call a newspaper
Very well. If you insist I will educate you
Who are you? I am floofty fizzle bean the world's first
The world's first harry potter wizard school teacher in baby language. I study bug snacks or
Any gnome in world of warcraft to study bug snacks, obviously
A lot of world of warcraft references the last a couple of days and i'm really sorry about that
I'm sorry
I just I don't know what it is today
I don't play it. I haven't played it in years. I don't care about it strange about her arm
She was keeping it hidden, but she displayed early stages of snackification
That peaked to my interest what about shadowland? No interest in it at all. You are asking for opinions instead of facts
I'm not going to discuss my feelings with you
emotional parasite
Hey, that was not nice. I tried to publish my groundbreaking research you journalists instead churn out slander about my
dangerous
That's really into the links today. Huh? You really are i'm i'm into it
What the fuck is this?
What is this is weird?
What how did you do that? You morphed me and taylor swift?
Is that what you did? Somebody said that's what you did
Is it like a british kid?
Why british?
British kid stop editorializing and focus on the science the kid on the corner with a newspaper
All right. Looks like we've got some news today for you a quarter penny, please
That kind of british kid. I simply wanted to continue my work
Agabelle or no, but sheldon blamed me for the disappearances no stranger to witch hunts
I vacated before the pitchforks could come out
cockney orphan
There is no in-between on tv and media you're either cockney orphan or your five thousand dollar dress
Champagne sipping socialite. There's no in-between
Why are you saying that with a voice changer what i keep my suffered leg in the outhouse austin powers
the truth
Elizabeth was an arrogant coward unlike agabelle agabelle truly understood my research. She was hungry to participate in it
Our work together was fruitful even pleasant until somebody interfered
What's wrong with this person?
That mummified fraud stoked elizabeth's fear of my work weaponizing her relationship to agabelle
Scrambling her fragile emotions and fabricating a binary choice between myself and elizabeth
So what happened ultimately agabelle chose sentiment over science?
And I surmise that was the death of her death death kill kill you killed her you killed isabelle. Yes
I have the password to agabelle's personal storage box or it may be of interest to you personal storage box enough of mine
We already opened this leave. I already opened that with another key. This is old news
All right. Let's go to isabelle's house
Hi
isabelle's house
That's
wham bush tiffany's house
Oh, yes one has returned from a great spiritual soldier
So it is one would really like to lie down
Somebody said wow, this link sucks resident sleeper. Well, I don't need to click it then
Strength within strength is the will hog link hog link
If I it I gotta buy it, please
They look toxic. I won't eat them. One is not none of them are good. Okay, you clearly
guidance
I'll bring the others too. You guys are so mean sad champ
Wait, why did you say that?
Now i'm now I want to know what the link is
You guys are mean sad
This is just what every
Okay, you know when you're in like the first second third and fourth grade when the whole class takes a picture together
And there's like three rows of the kids and like one row of them sitting down
This is kid all the way to the left
Standing all right. I ain't clicking any more links
Bury them. All right. Wait, hold on. I need to go uh, dig through somebody's stuff
Somebody has a secret chest
Whose house is it in?
Oh, here we go. Egobel lizbert and egobel's house. Oh already opened that old news
Oh the chest already opened it old news
Oh my god, look at all this secret stuff already did this old news
You gave me a key to something I already owned gave me this key seems to go through a mysterious box
And what do you mean mysterious box?
in egobel's house
Where's this mysterious box?
What are you doing? Stop looking in people's windows?
I don't see a mysterious box in egobel's house
All right, where's shelda?
final interview
This is the final interview
This one one who is was there mortal compact characters did that?
Wasp lady, so it is one maintains balance and purity
Dvorah, yeah
Dvorah
That's before mortal combat
turned into a
80s movie smash brothers. I don't know. Why why did they do that for?
There was a raffle
Am I a hater? I'm not a hater. I'm just saying like it's we've gotten every like 80s movie action and horror movie star
What's left freddy krueger?
Michael meyers
He's in it. No, he's not who's in the other one
He was he was that's right
I don't know like
doc from
I almost said whose lines it anyways doc from back to the future
I'm sure it'll be like great scott and he'll have like devices he can use. I'm sure they'll do it
Doc getting brutalized by the terminator
But I don't know don't put a pass they'll put the care bears in mortal combat 11 at this point
They added the ninja turtles to smite we're starting to get a little weird here
They're in injustice, too
Yeah, why what's with the ninja turtles showing up in other like fighting games
Why is it the ninja turtles it's always the ninja turtles it's like oh man here we go big reveal
We're adding the ninja turtles to our fighting game or our game like it's like at this point
It's been like three or four times now one game
That's not true
Oh, i'm thinking of the hold on i'm mixing my amphibious creatures i'm thinking of the battle toads as well
Because they've they've put the battle toads in a few things, right?
The battle toads and the ninja turtles are essentially they're pretty they're very close
I would say the battle toads are just radical ninja turtles, but ninja turtles are radical battle toads. This is tricky
Take that back
They're in killer instinct and shovel knight
I love the battle toads
I don't think they got done pretty I don't think they were done justice though
May answers be found. It's mystery. This is a locked box. I have oh
I think I I think I beat the game
They just had a new game
But was it I mean, but didn't it wasn't like it was like a wasn't it like kind of tacked on to like game
Pass or something. It wasn't like big deal. Was it?
They also did the same shit with the ninja turtles, too
Remember that and when they remade the like they did a new ninja turtles beat them up game and it was like
This is kind of not good. You're stalling. I'm not what like the game. What the fuck?
I can't what?
Where like that?
Hey
Is the final videotape today?
today
bro, bro
Somebody just wrote it all caps be fucking funny. I'm watching like a cut scene, dude
What do you want me to do right now?
I'm watching the cut scene
What? All right, so we've completed. I don't even know what that was supposed to tell filbo
How's it? Hey channel art chandler. Yeah, dog. What do you want? I'm trying to pull up this stuff
I can build a b-bar court. I'm about as swole as a grumpus can get and I can't move this thing at all
I gotta be stronger than a grumpus
I gotta push my limits. You feel me?
I feel you
I need your help to do the main story main story main story. The main story is almost over
Snacks around eat them. We've got all 12 brompuses. We have all the locations
You go find the biggest buffest bug snacks around
You won't catch aggressive bug stacks. All right, where's um, where's loopy? There he is. Come on loopy
Wow, it's getting crowded around we gotta celebrate big time
This party's gonna change everything buddy
Are you sure you're ready?
Once you start the party, you won't be able to catch bug snacks or complete quests
Be sure you've done everything you won't wait. This is actually the end of the game. I'm not ready. This is actually the finale
What's going on wiggle? All right. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not right. I don't want to do your quest your quest is dumb
What do you have? Not too bad. Actually would you mind helping me finish this? I'm not ready. I'm not ready
I just want to see
end this game, please this game
This I thought we were in agreement that everybody liked what was going on today and yesterday I like what you don't like this
I want to go exploring with trippany
Flavor falls we haven't even explored flavor falls. Let me explore flavor falls first and then we'll do the finale
I like the game from two days ago
We haven't even looked around here we have never even been here before look at it's all new
All new we never even seen this before actually. Yes, we have give me that
I would love like a bird shit just dropped right in her hat
Okay, scan a stone grumpus and report to trippany
Are they gonna catch the sandwich yet?
and a stone grumpus
He loves cheese. Okay. Wait, I want I want to catch. Whoa, what the
That's a pickle
The jar protects it from capture
This ranch dressing in this game. How did I not even see this before? I told you we didn't see this
No, give that back. I got a pickle. I want to get the sandwich too
All right. We're gonna place a trap for the sandwich
Where's the sandwich?
Very important. Very important. Did you know that chandler's names backwards is that's fun? I don't know
You just said that a person's name backwards
All right. Come on sando
Bump it
I got the whole thing
What are you staring at this bush for? Okay scan a stone grumpus and report. All right stone grumpus
Is the one in here?
Uh, it's a stone grumpus
These statues must be hundreds of years old
Very cool. I just scanned with
What is that?
an inch wrap
How do I catch? Oh gross. What's in there? Didn't I scan scan a stone grumpus? That's not what that is
That's a strawberry idiot
It needs to be a stone grumpus
What's in here something's in here?
California it was in there what?
California
California all that
California that's from total distortion
California it's one of the facebook
There would be the work of the ancient stone. When am I gonna stream that? I already did
from over
5,000 years ago
All that's left to them is statuary and some puzzling mechanisms long time ago like the desert grumps
These folks didn't preserve their dead
In fact, I think I did the writer thinks they would sacrifice them to the bug snacks
Like an offering to the gods and whatnot
This means bug snacks may be a more lasting legacy than any of the stuff they built wait
Did I I did stream it didn't I?
I swear to god I did
Gotta gotta have the big squidward pickle nose, right?
You might have noticed pinkle statues scattered around here
These must have been an important food source to the ancient grumps
Okay, well
I was hoping to find a camp of some sort maybe a quarter. You just ruined her. Oh, well
There's plenty more spots to check. I mean ruined her let's head back to snaxford for now
Catch aggressive meaty bug snacks
Oh, i've got the sandwich. I've got three sandwiches for him. I just did two quests in a row
What's that garlic? It's a garlic enemy
Edgy poop that's two quests done
Somebody else wanted the sub too, right? Uh wiggle I get all that
Hold on. I i'm curious. Let me see
I'm missing
I'm still i'm now what is that?
flavor falls
I've seen almost everything but not everything everything
Bag
Still a couple I haven't seen
Still a couple of things I haven't seen
Seen most of it though
missing a lot
Um, not enough where i'm annoyed where I want to continue to find everything
I want to turn these in
I swear if you don't 100% this game, I will shit in your hot sauce
It'll be hard to do the bottle is about three inches tall and like a tenth of a centimeter wide
For the hole so good luck. That's gonna be weird to do
All right wiggle. Where's wiggle wiggle wanted me to bring a sub
I got three quests done immediately need two sandapeds. Uh, oh
Need two. Oh, this is very important sub
sandapeds
Not I gotta okay
Sandwich nose and
sandwiched teeth
That's just onions
This is my favorite character
I'd rather do the uh quest for her
But it's just
It's the creative process
Do you know how I wrote do the wiggle?
Tell me to the studio two hours bacon
I hadn't slept in five days and I was holding a banjo for some reason
I couldn't remember my own name much less what I was gonna say. I love the lean down side to side
That's my favorite animation
While the wiggle is going on lean in wiggle wiggle lean in
And apparently I'd invented banjo pop needless to say it's been a hard act to follow but wait, what else do you need?
Are you ready to help me top the chart? Yes, I want to do whatever you want me to do
Bye
Okay, catch one white cheap hoof
I can do that
You're simping for a muppet
Don't you dare?
Talk about my queen like that again
Uh, where are the white cheap hoofs?
That's a regular cheap hoof. That's a regular cheap hoof. Where's the white one?
You forgot about chanlo. Here's the problem with chanlo. I gave two sandwiches
therefore
Uh, I I he needed three meaty snacks and I got rid of two of them
So I will pick up a meaty snack here while I get a white cheap hoof
I just heard something like crawl across my desk in real life
and
I'm freaking out. Don't know what that was. It was very strange
I hope that's nothing sinister. Okay
white cheap hoof
Um, where does the white cheap hoof spawn?
Don't say centipede. That's the most terrifying animal on earth
It's at night. Oh at night. I need to sleep then centipedes are terrifying. They really are
I I mean people say they're all they're cool. They're cool. They're cool. I
Okay. Oh, I want to have one as a pet
I want to keep one but I I gauge if I want something in my house or not
If I don't want it to hurt me and if I can
interact with it
Like standing across your room while you look at like a giant emperor scorpion with binoculars
Whoa, that's fucking scary and it could kill it could hurt me
No, I don't want that. Oh
That'd be sure horrible if that got out of its cage. I got a dog
I don't want that
If I get a centipede
And you have animals in your house or something. What if it ever got out and like it attacked your dog or something?
If you're into that crazy wild shit, like that's um
Power to you. Really? I that's cool. Not for me at all. Keep them in the ground. You're sleeping
Centipedes aren't aggressive
Until they feel like they are threatened which it could be anything. Yes, they are. Yes, they are
I don't know anything about centipedes
I just know that they're really scary looking and they have like dangerous and poisonous and they hurt
Lots of centipedes in chat tonight
How dare you talk about us like that
We need to show them that we're not aggressive. We're not mean. We're not angry. We need to tell them that we're
Wake up
Drag them to hell cheesy poof leg
Oh we got a sub
You guys don't want me to complete this side quest with her so are you sure
I don't know why I bother
I know I don't have any real talent. Well, that was great
That was really good. I didn't get a chance to say it but what I thought
I need to be alone
No, wait, let me go get you some more bugs
No
Let's wait. Let's give you like a makeover too
Can't do the other leg
She okay cheesy poof nose
for sure
Sub sandwich head. Yep. I just make her total sub
Now sub sandwich head
cheesy poof nose
and yada
ear
pop feet pop hands
And like sugar leg and
What about teeth?
Yeah, sugar ear. I like it. Wait eat this
Eat this too
Okay
I wasn't done or was I maybe I was
I need a meaty bug snack for you
You just ruined her career
Well, I didn't reveal it in the mirror yet for her to go
So just don't ever put her in front of a mirror
You'll never know
Okay, so we need
One more beefy beefy bug and then I don't I don't care about this guy
If anybody would like to talk to you about all right, let's go talk to tiffany. What's wrong with you. What?
What do I do finish the game?
I'm going to finish the game when i'm ready to finish the video game and i'm not ready until I hear the
Finished completed song from wiggle
Wendy well, well, whatever. I don't know what her name is what's shaking baby
You have anything else to do?
I want the full song
I uh, i'm not i'm not ready. I'm not ready
I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. We need meaty burgers
Request a done
There is no more what?
All right, let me get one more meaty bug snack and then i'm gonna complete the game get a burger
Stop rushing him. Yes. What's with the rush?
What's with the rush?
Gotta get a hamburger. There we go hamburger time
Please ram into you gotta get covered the other guy in ketchup or cheese, which one? All right ketchup time
There you are. Come here over here two bungers
Bunger double bunger
Let's go. Don't stop ruining my fun
Stop ruining my fun
What there we go
All right, that's the meat feed the aggressive meaty snacks for chandlo
My mom's making me sleep in 10 minutes
Please finish the game quickly and i'll take her credit card and donate to you. Just go to bed. Let's go to sleep, dude
Get some rest. Come here. I got your I got it. All right feed
Sandwich
Give you a sandwich arm. Should we let's give him a full sandwich arm
Definitely and then let's give him a burger
Burger head
Yeah, you're the new burger head. This is what peak performance looks like. That's a pretty old meme
There's no gaining without training dog. I got a new exercise in mind if you're ready to spot me
Let's go. All right, I get to spot him. I set up these hanging weights all around town
I'm gonna jog around
You use your grappler to knock him down on top of me
Okay, that's not gonna hurt me, but this is what I gotta do to challenge myself
This is a crying screaming and farting reference
That's so stupid
Okay, drop weights on his head
Well, you uh, you're going a little too fast
Can I this?
Hey, I didn't hit him that one fell down on its own
Keep him coming. That's heavy bro. What what how did that fall over here?
Why he sounds like michael from gta 5
I feel swole dog. Let's see what you got stump. Don't do it
He's never gonna lift this stump. It's never gonna happen
But that's okay
I just gotta rest up and keep training
With this bug snack body i'll get there
Because if I don't
Who's gonna have snorpey's back just shit my pants
Wait, this is another one. We are completing his quest line
I wasn't pushing hard enough
Maybe it's the bugs. Oh, I need to go to bed. We went way too small. I have to go to bed. My bum's gonna be mad at me
I've been hearing rumors about this monster snack out in the forest
Wambus said it was so huge
No grumpus alive could lift it
Sounds like the ultimate workout. Let's catch it bro. Let's do it. Yeah
Eat me in flavor town
British orphan, germa needs to go to betty by
Uh, not quite just thinking about that buff snack is getting me pumped
I like him a lot. I like that
Weren't you guys waiting for
A dark twist
That didn't really happen. Did it?
What the hell is this?
oh
My god, it's a giant watermelon
A mama melon this massive snack protects its offspring at all costs try to get the drop on it
What the hell catch a mama mel one?
I need to catch this mama mel one
Or I will be very very mad
Holy shit
Okay. What do I do?
He loves
These toys. What are these? These are wee melons
Bounce the wee melons
Okay. Hold on bounce wee melons
into him
Come here melon
boink
oof
They really like this thing. But what is it maybe light it on fire?
It's rom
Rom the vacuos
Hates that loves these
Get off of it for a second. I'm trying to aim it
breakable statue
Wait, everybody come over here and have fun over this way
Look what I have. It's right here. Come over here and smash this thing
Whoa
What happened? Give me the children. Hey, come over here and play with this. Hey, look what I got
You sure don't like this. Do you all right? He smashed his head into it
and then
How do I capture him try to get the read?
Try to get the drop on it. I he smashes into a statue and then what do I do?
Do I jump on his top of his body?
conveniently built beneath us
Come over here kids. I've got a toy to play with
Shoot the rpg at it. Everybody's silent
Got him
Come over here friends
Don't touch that
All right, break him. I'm gonna do it probably three
If it's like every single super mario enemy, it's three
No, stop hanging
He's broken
broken
Oh, he's mad now though
very
Let's go, let's go. Oh, he just got his ass kicked
What
Oh, it's just a little baby he got plowed he got absolutely steamrolled
Thanks, bro. That bug could have killed me. It was way strong dog
And once I eat it i'll be just I kind of don't I kind of want to donate this
I want to donate this wouldn't it be more interesting eat one of these first
He needs it fine
Just the same chandlo
And chandlo isn't super mario noise. No is my whole life climbing a mountain
Once I got to the peak all I saw was a taller mountain make him full melon
Even if I could rip out that stuff
Full melon with the mario nose. There's always going to be something bigger than me stronger than me
Snorpy's always going to be in danger
Are they all hate themselves?
And it's kind of a general theme here, right?
All right. Let's I want to let's turn them into a full melon though
Full melon chalcomist. I deserve it. Why else would you run away to drug snacks island? Is that the end of his quest line?
I think it is. So what else?
Donation right? I think I can do the donations one more because maybe that'll end his quest line. Yeah
All right. That's it. The size of your heart has grown
It can't get any bigger but donating is still a nice thing to do. All right. Well, that's maxed out
Very very cool. Okay
Uh, who else have I not what's do I care about?
Wait wiggle gets inspired. Oh, you kidding me. I hear music. Wait, where does it come from?
All right, wiggle gets inspired. Let's go to wiggle's house. I heard that you were inspired. Tell me what you need
I will get anything you want
Last is the
Bug snack out in the ocean seen it riding the waves in the morning to be honest. I'm not even sure if it's real
But I'm the big boss bud
Please help me. I can't catch it alone
This is gonna be great
Dance with the dragon
Yeah, every side quest ends up with a legendary bug snack. That's right. My critics. All right, you know
I can't make the magic happen again
I've tried sky diving crystal gorging reverse exorcisms everything
Bug snacks are the only thing that have ever gotten me stayed again. Wait, are you talking about you need to
Take drug snacks
Just sing a good song
Am I enabling this
Yes sing to us
Bobsicle don't give a shit about this. I would laugh so hard if bobsicle rammed her off the stage
That was awesome. So glad we got to see it
We set these lights up. Oh
Oh, that's huge
Come on, let's make some music
uh
Catch the mega maki
Mega maki the head of the beast it can't be caught until it's run out of followers
they follow behind
the head in a perfect form
They're fucking raining down explosives on us. They fall behind the head in perfect formation and panic without its leader
Okay
Time to get tripped up here
Scan the butt. No, it's mini maki and mega maki
All right after they after I trip it. How do I what do I do next?
Holy shit. All right, here we go
Oh god
Get them all
Oh
He's pissed
Hold on. I gotta catch them all
Where's it? Give me that
This shit's flying around now
Uh, does it come back in the water or is it gonna keep flying around?
Did I get to phase two?
Oh shit
Okay. Yep
Oh watch out. I'm over here
Dive bomb dive bomb dive bomb dive bomb dive bomb
No
Not high enough
No, it's gonna blow up this thing
No, it's not we're good
Shit fuck. I gotta get higher
I can't even put it on that high
This way
Here it comes through the hoop. I think I gotta get it over there actually scan the maki again
Hold on. He's not gonna go that way. I'd have to have to be that way
Yeah, it's gotta be like that
Actually my turn
Give me this. Yeah right here. Do not break this don't break it. All right, we're good
Motherfucker
Don't break the tree either, please
I think that's good. Is that in a good spot?
All they all come back. That's good
That's a bit as a better spot over here then
You gotta get so close to put the stupid thing up there. All right
I hate being in the water to do this shit
I'm just standing over here. Fuck it
That'll do it. Here we go
Get back here mini maki
All right, not much left
There it is
and
Only three more to collect and there's no more get back here
Now you're just it's just his head. Oh, it's kind of sad
I want to put him back where he belongs in the water. You're gonna eat this. That's not nice beat him to your queen
Well, this is where I make a choice
This world is indifferent to kindness
This is a ball of yarn
Do the wiggle we're gonna get a final song
That will be my legacy
Can I make it happen one more can't the universe give me one more?
So you just ate a legendary endangered species creature that there's only like three of on earth
Because you thought it was going to give you superpowers to write a song and the other guy thought it was going to give him super strength
Oh, here comes the lesson
Right. Yeah, the lesson's incoming
We're gonna get like a wizard of oz. Hey, you had a heart the whole time. It's in there and you wanted a brain
Of course, you have a brain
Elizabeth's gonna come up or whatever. Lizbert's gonna show up as the wizard of fucking snackberg all coked out too
Very clearly. I never caught one of those that one. All right fail ball once not yet. I'm not ready yet
I'm not done yet. We I want to see maybe I want to see one more mega
Animal not time for party. We were halfway through
Becca's quest line. I did remember I and like yesterday I did a ton of her side stuff
I didn't finish it spy on people. I did that for like an hour last night. I got I might as well at least complete it
Did you do it? Did you write your mapis? Oh, sorry, dear
It's never going to happen
Don't be so down wiggle
Maybe you're overthinking it. Aren't you just from the heart from the heart?
Grambling you sweet summer child. Oh, that's not what I meant. I'm talking about eating the heart of the giant supreme moth
What did you think I meant?
Because I and I've seen time and time again that when I write for myself nobody else wants to hear it
Well, that's a nice sentiment
Celebrities resident sleeper
All right
Where's becca becca
Where's becca?
Main story main story is over
The finale is the thing that I start next. Wait, wasn't he just
Weren't you just over there?
Where did he where's becca? I swear to god. I can't burn these stupid houses into my memory
I'm never gonna know where they are
All the same house. There's a different color stripe like ninja turtle stripe on them. I know they're color-coded. I know
But like I think I've paid attention to what who's who?
You walked past her moron. I'm not a moron. You're a moron. Hey there bestie
Crumdo I know that greedy crumb bag has some juicy dirt. Okay, i'm sure you'll find something good
So what it's crumdo
Find out what crumdo does at midnight. What time is it right now? Oh fuck
What are you doing in here? I'm gonna sleep in his bed until
Okay, what do you do at midnight? Let's find out he sleeps
like most people
All right. This game's really cool because it's sort of a weird
10 to 20 mix
of
animal crossing
pokemon
Almost like like stardew vibes too. Like you can plant stuff and cultivate bug snacks
And like people like each other. They hate each other
Even pinata. Yeah
It's a mix of a bunch of these games
Is somebody there you didn't hear anything pal. You got that not a single wait, that's wiggles big hit. He's drunk
Get me a bug snack so delicious that trippany would die for it and we'll try why people's dying for this
People are gonna you people are gonna be killed over bug snacks
Look, he dances to music. What a shocker
M g that's why he's always so jealous of wiggle
Would he even hide that?
It almost makes him kind of likable
Okay, the big scoop
Got anything else for me?
All right. Well, let's i'm gonna sleep
Okay, wake up for a second
Wake up wake up for a minute
Okay, I there's obviously another part here we go
You're the one keeping secrets you can't touch this
You think i'm the only one who's sick of your gossip girl stick oh peter
Sooner or later, you're gonna be back in your cave all by yourself
At least then I wouldn't have to hear your slimy voice
She sucks are we gonna get some redemption arc from her or she just sucked the whole game
Find three grumpy snack pods on the beach
Fine, that's not the beach. Is that the beach?
Am I insane?
Yeah, it is
You're gonna want 100 percent it
No, i'm gonna 100 get my fill of the game
That doesn't mean 100 the actual video game. That means what i'm done when I feel
Like I have completed the game for me
We'll see when that is
All right. We need grumpy snack pods on the beach
candy patch
The snack pods are just the chip bags, right?
Those are just pasted on random stones
This one right there
grumpy snack pod
Snick food snick food
All right anymore
Hey
snack pod
Excuse me
Mm-hmm
Uh, wait, what about on the other side of this?
Probably on the other side of this, right?
Right, right, right, right
What's that? Oh the villager from minecraft
Right
Yeah close enough
I don't see any others on the beach
Come on. Where are they? I missed one
Is this a scenario where they don't come out in the rain?
Or is this a scenario where they're just always around no matter what i'm just gonna find them. I thought that was one right there
inside log
All right, relax
That's not one
What are you talking about? You're great at pretending. I looked in almost every log
Somebody said to go in the what law that I looked in all the logs
I've seen every log
I've read all the logs
And a lot of you are bullshitters
What about over here?
Yeah, I i've read the logs. I see what you said three days ago versus what you said today
If you reload the area
No, there ain't no there ain't there ain't no this one. Okay. I need one more
All right, reload the zone last one in log
No, there's not i'm gonna reload the area because I do not believe you
I don't trust you
By the way, I want to just I have this to talk about too
So there's a theme song for this game that has this was made by a famous band
And I haven't heard it once the whole playthrough. What's the point of it being a theme song?
Is it a credit song? We'll find out famous in quotes. I don't know. I don't i've never heard of them
Is it just the trailer? It might be becky. Becky's not in her house. Where is she?
Becky, where's becky?
There's becky. Were you just videotaping filbert's bed?
You are fucking what the hell's wrong with you. Why can't I not change her nose that annoys me for some reason?
Uh, thanks bestie
Barely know you and if I did get to know you you'd probably hate me for it
Fuck you. Fuck you. What? Oh my god
What the hell?
All right, wait sleep in a bed and then talk to her again
What's with the hostility? Yeah, I don't know
What's with the hostility?
Nothing new from you
Wait, that's it. You don't have it. You don't want me to do anything
What was the point of doing all that weird shit for you?
Have to wait a bit
All right, i'm gonna sleep again for like three days
All right, what's new? Everybody go
All right, well what the heck sleep till noon
And
All right
Why hey, you don't have anything to tell me here eat one of these
That just looks like somebody cut her nose off in half facing us
What the hell she has nothing for me to do
I already did your stuff. All right, what about um, I gotta go get you
Who am I in the middle of something with other people too deal or no deal? All right, catch a buffalo cust
Buffalo cust is in the sizzling, uh
Uh sands or serpents, whatever
How's it going? This is the thing that dive bombs, right?
I bomb into water
It's in boiler bay across the bridge
Watch the ending on youtube talking to me. I might have an hour to drop off these red box rentals, please
Those are those things exist still it's rented on itunes, dude. Okay. There he is
And there he is the supreme meat lovers pizza. I've never seen you before
Oh, it's a black olive. It loves to eat things that are lick up things that are cheesy
Okay, this spicy
Where is he what happened?
Where what happened?
He's on the ground right here who killed
Fucking on fire. Of course you are why?
I have to have him dive bomb into the water. All right, get over here
I didn't get to read
It loves to dive into its favorite. It loves to dive into ranch dressing
Okay
so
We got to bring you
over here
same
Is there anything cold?
All right, so then we're gonna launch you
Okay
I'm gonna call the ball
Hold the ball and ranch
This is an eric andre skit ranch ball
All right dive. Oh you sprayed him. Thanks, man
Time to deliver a pizza ball. Yeah, that's what it is. Not ranch ball
I haven't seen any of the new season by the way. So don't tell me anything. Let's go deliver this
So you want to hit this ranch?
You know what i'm so happy about
I am so happy that eric andre's show did not get the rick and morty treatment
You know what I mean? Where oh my god like
All the fans like ruined it, right? It was
Very very very possible for that to happen. Stop talking about it. Yeah, you're right. You're right. You're right. Right?
Forget it forget I said anything
TV sucks. I hate tv
Don't ever watch television
All right, we're gonna go back and deliver but I want this cheese sauce
Imagine letting fans ruin something for you. I know i'm just i'm saying
That it was it was possible for okay
It was possible for me to say the word eric andre and people to go. Oh reddit show. Oh, yeah pizza ball
Haha, so funny reddit. It was that's very true. That's possible. Yes, it is
His show is he's very very very funny just throw away this delicious
Hold on now cronto above a locust
Take it
I don't do charity. There is like a sesame street character that looks just like her the way that she is now
Who is it?
What's the deal here i'm not letting a crook like you get a hold of that map you'll just swipe the bug snaps and sell them
Up. Oh, no. No, wait, wait, wait
No, wait, don't touch that you tell are you sure that's not him
Starting timeouts at 10 minutes. Don't spam coffee pasta. You're all fucking you're all in trouble
Okay
Can someone help him
He does this every single day. Can somebody please help him
Can put a lock on his door at night or something like he was just bar him in the house feed him
Wait, what am I doing?
Wait, doesn't he not doesn't he not want to do this. Why did I just do that to this guy?
Wait, take it all take it all. He won't know. Yeah, hold on
Well, you slept on your arm wrong. Oops steal the map. What's that cactus? Yes, it's me cactus
I have your map. I have your map. I have your map
I'm an inside man want something here. Have one of these wake up
What awaken me how can he's not gonna go like what happened? Yeah, I'm gonna sleep and i'm gonna finish grumbos quest
Could you help me with something? See I have it a walking around in my sleep
And uh, it looks like i've been eating in my sleep, too
So if you see me sleepwalking wake me up sure to wake me up. Okay?
Sure, I will
I'm back
All right. Now what else we got?
Becca
Hey bestie
Now that snorpy and chandlo are back. It's toad's snooping time
I never got any dirt on chandlo. He's got to have some deep dark secret, but whatever it is
He's too good. Stop simping for befrica. I i'm talking to someone that doesn't mean i'm simping for them
If I was a cashier at a grocery store or at a mall
And i've rung up a lady
Why are you shipping for that lady?
I'm ringing her up. She's buying things at the store
Anyways, please i'll do anything for you anything
Find out what he does at midnight. Sure thing anything for you literally anything
All right, get this on camera
My belly doesn't okay
Uh find out what chandlo does at midnight. Okay, where's chandlo live? I'm gonna sleep in his bed
Leave me alone. Does he live in the bathroom?
his wiggle
Befica, where's his little green house?
He lives at the gym
Where is his house? I don't see does he not he's does he sleep in the mill?
Why is he sleeping in the mill?
the heck
What's wrong with you, dude?
Where's the stump snorpy? I removed it with my digging device. It took five minutes
Oh
What are you doing with your backside here, man? Anytime chandlo
This motherfucker looks like he's about to lay eggs
Okay, sleep until midnight. Why can't I can't sleep in his bed?
Oh, this is bullshit
I can't sleep in your bed either
What does he do at midnight?
Where's he at?
Uh, what is he doing?
Thing about being chandlo
What you see is what you get
I got nothing to hide
No shame
There's no dirt. You're checking out this beef bro. I don't blame you
He's just a normal weirdo
Uh, sorry becca
There's no dirt on this dude
Sorry
What's up? He's just a regular guy
Nobody is free of dirt
The more innocent somebody looks the nastier the secret. Trust me. I have an idea wake up at noon
Talk to someone go to bed till midnight
Nobody knows chandlo like snorpy. I need you to turn me into green bug snacks
I'll tell you why later green bug snacks
Turn becca's arms into green snacks. I think you already um
That is is the sushi
The maki roll green technically
No, really it's not green what about pickles, uh, I need to feed her a pickle
That looks so strange
This is this is okay
If you would have like
Uber eats sushi shit-faced. Yeah, this sushi's a good idea
Or if it's a uber eats it gets delivered to your house
Oh, yeah, this is what I want
You eat one of them and you just like drop the rest on the fucking couch
In the container and you wake up the next morning and this that's what the that's what it looks like
You ate one piece and the rest just fucking fell all over the place
Or you eat one piece you drop it all over the bed and then you go and like you puke
Sushi is a good idea
Give me I'll take two california rolls or two
spicy tuna rolls
Uber eats
I can't relate to that rich streamer
Sushi uber eats that's by the way, that's already a bad idea
So I I know people look i'm gonna get i'm gonna get shit for this
but
For me look, this is not for you. This is not your friends. It's not your parents. This is me
If I do not eat sushi sitting down at a sushi restaurant
Do I will not eat it?
I do not want it the sushi that's at like the grocery store the sushi that's at the gas station and ordering delivery sushi
I'm
Not into that at all. Sorry. We can't have our own personal sushi chefs. No, that's not what i'm saying
I'm just saying like I don't the the spicy tuna roll that's at the gas station
Something I I don't want to eat you everyone's saying delivery. That's true
You could like uber eats like we said that like, you know that little uh, the little routine there
Here's the problem
Sometimes when you order on those apps
Um, the guy or the girl doesn't fucking show up on time and you might be you might order your your takeaway sushi
and it shows up like
55 minutes later after they did like two or three deliveries before yours
Delivery sushi not gonna happen pick it up pick it up
Hey
Yes, you could pick it up
But i'm i'm just telling you delivery sushi i'm not okay with
Or gas station and grocery store sushi
I want to be at the restaurant want to see them make it because I don't know what I have no idea what from
No, that's reasonable and understandable. I gift that guy some
I'll do it
I don't know. I'm doing it
Somebody do it already. Where is it? What's your name? Too fast. There it is
Sheepish sheepish dialect you're getting a community sub. Did you already get it or am I doing it?
Nepotism here it comes nepotism
Pick me pick me
I am picking out the one person in chat that has pleased me
Did he already get one? He got one already. Wait, did he get one? I think he already has one
Do you have one? I can't hold on. Let me see if they have one
I
Can't even give it to him
Mostly lost already gave it to him. I can't even
Hey, well nice job. That's you deserve that for being a reasonable
Understandable person. Hey, I agree with you happy face. No, that's not how it works. It's only a one-time deal
I'm gonna go get some pickles
This guy sucks. Fuck you gift me a sub instead. You're you're like a you're like an eight year sub
Is this where the pickles are?
No, this is not where the pickles are
That's not a green vegetable
It's in flavor town, right? Yeah, i'm going the right way. When are you gonna do a ps5 raffle?
Uh, I would not hold your breath for that one
All right pickle time
Where is a pickle? There is a pickle
All right green snack. We got it leave
What the fuck what?
I love how I I want to say it so bad
But I can't you guys can all say it and you don't get it to attack each other for it
When I say it I make it real
When you say it apparently it's not real they didn't see what happens that sounds like a threat
I don't think i'm gonna follow up with that
Okay green
arms
Hey, becca
Eat this pickle
There you go
And let's give everybody's pickle, you know, just have everything be just total pickle
Perfect. Thanks bestie. Here's the plan
Snorpy basically can't see without his glasses. I'm pickle beffica them every day at five
So we'll approach him then and if i'm green and I say bro a lot he'll think i'm chandlo
And obviously snorpy isn't going to keep chandlo's secrets from himself
You know it bestie snorpy isn't going to know what hit him that's a lap to hang out until it's time
Hey snorp dog, can I like ask you something
Chandlo, is that you?
I can't see this guy's real glasses real dumb. Oh, there's no time bro. This is important
Oh, uh, well, all right then what is it bro? You remember that deep dark secret we were talking about
You know the really super secret one. Oh, ah
That yes
I suppose it is time we talked about it
Chandlo, it's hard for me to know what he's getting bore at it
I've been afraid of talking about it for so long, but the truth is that was good. I love that was really good
That's not a secret to anybody beffica. What did you get here? How dare you intrude on our private moment?
Bro, she just ran off dog like he's gonna start tucking his pants in stop
Anybody
Hey
I love the marshmallow nose, but I think he deserves a pickle nose
Minion yeah, he looks like a minion, but it doesn't sound like a minion
He didn't go
He didn't do any of that
That's that was stitch. That was less. Uh minion more stitch
The same damn look they sound exactly the same
Hey, i'm sorry, dude. Did I like offend you with that?
I said stitch and the minions are like the exact same
He's very very shocked about that
Yeah, and guess what murlocs and stitch and minions are the same too
And so are the jawas
The jawas the murlocs the stitches they all they're all the same. They all talk the same
To the journal this time we're heading for the boiling bay
They all go like
Yes, they do they all do it's just funny gibberish with a high pitch that's lemmings
Yes, why did somebody say
He's right give me a sub, please
Hashtag kill germo what guys I said jawas and minions talk the same
You're gonna you're gonna roast me over the fire for that
Which was which tell me that was two different audios two different clips
Which was which both of them in first one was minions first one was jawa
Some of you guys can't tell the difference how what if I told you that it was both minions lay them over each other
What was with the music
All right. Well that one's easy because that the unti d the minions don't do that
scan a treasure chest
Oh shit, what about stitch?
I've thought we're not going into the we're not going into the weeds here. All right scan a treasure chest and report feed
Oh, I always know. All right, the jawas and the minions of the stitches they they have very similar dialect
Okay
I I know it for a fact that you can't prove me wrong
And the rabbits too were the raving rabbits. Do should we pull out the raving rabbits?
Stitch is nothing like those two
All right
Over. All right. I need to scan a treasure chest
Where is a treasure chest?
One what about every germa voice is the same voice we're not talking about me right now
We're talking about minions jawas and rabbits. Where's there a treasure chest? All right, let me talk to you again
Maybe you'll tell me where it is
If you don't mind your eyes peeled for a treasure chest and a freezing cold bully of a bug sna-
Mmm treasure chest
Sounds like minions to me
I found a treasure chest
Yeah, I I didn't know that everybody was gonna be so defending the minions
I don't know. We were gonna get some some some real minion defense in here
Oh wait, is it because I said stitch and minions that settles it. I think that's what happened
This ship belonged to grump beard. He disappeared at sea a hundred years ago
But I guess he wound up on snack tooth island
Hard to tell what happened to him after that his bones could be just about anywhere
You're right. You should say it
I'll defend stitch
Well, maybe stitch should have been in there
I haven't heard stitch in a long time
All right. Now we got to feed tiffany a pale toss
That's a backtrack
Whoa
Whoa, I don't like this
You know flutey's got a theory that the bigger a bug snack is we're defending stitch
No telling yet was around in grump beards time
It could have even chased him off the beach
Fun to think about eh
Pickle germa, I can't find anything
She's not gonna wreck them all please
I didn't mean to keep it from you, but that journal it um belonged to my
Some years ago
My grandma chronic a lot of blog decided she was gonna explore something about she lost a lot of blood
Discover its history. Oh, she had she wrote a blog
That's really why i'm out here to find out what became of her
Anywho, that's all for now
Let's head back to town
Catch one scoopy banoopy
Are you listening to that?
You little shit eavesdropper
Don't fucking tell anybody that don't leak that conversation
I'll know who did
Right. It's a golden quibble. I gotta get him. I changed my mind. I'm just gonna take you
What does he like?
Loves chocolate. Okay, cool. I mean, I kind of need the golden quibble, right?
Remember your niece is watching. I don't think so. I don't think they know what this game is
Long time viewer first time watcher. Wait, what?
That doesn't mean that didn't make any sense, right?
Long time watcher first time viewer here. How's it going? I think I've read that wrong
All right. What about uh
Crummy, where is he?
Anything new from crummy?
Hey mind your own beeswax. There is something from crummy. Let's go
Ready to get rich. Yeah
Hope you got your sunglasses pal because we're heading to the sizzling sands
I'm trying to see
I need to know
I need to know please i'm just trying to look something up
Can't there's no info on this
Oh, this is for the pizza, right? We're gonna go we're gonna get the big pizza
Could use a good slicing
Hey check it out an old timey casket an old tomb what if there's treasure in there
You're gonna summon them don't do it. Yeah, whatever onto the real price
Sarcophagus this ancient stone coffin is stuck shut. Perhaps it needs to be cut open
Do we have a cutting tool or something eventually here?
This is the place looks like we got to do something to call the bug snack out
Should be a switch right about
Oh
All right get on it
Whoa, that is something. All right
But it looks like we still got to blow this thing open
See if there's anything good and explosive around here. How about the dive bombing bug snack?
Or the ancient pizza cutter?
Uh, okay, we're gonna use the ancient pizza cutter on the ancient sarcophagus
Bombino when threatened this bug snack becomes an explosive bomb
Okay, what do you like?
You love cheese
Is he oh, I just covered him in cheese. Uh
Right. Oh, I can just pick him up
Oh, that was cool. All right, so now
figure out a summon
mothra supreme
uh
Mysterious altar this altar has a slot on top that perfectly fits the launch pad perhaps the launch
Needs to be placed here, whatever
Come on
All right, defeat mothra supreme
bomb snacks
All right. What do I do?
Why are they all on fire already?
I definitely have to okay. We have to launch the bombs at him
Come here
Stop being on fire. Why are they all on fire?
Why they already all are burnt up and
No
Serve it up
What fell out of him pizza
Pizza sleeve a sleeve of pizza. Um
No, wait, I gotta cut him. I gotta cut him. We gotta cut him
He has to go over here. How do I attract him over here?
Because then i'm gonna i gotta cut through his body
There are more than one
Cutter we didn't unlock the other cutters
All right slice him up
Is that
Where'd he go?
There we go. Ow
Put it out put it out put it out
He's pissed
I want to aim the launcher
All right. Give me back
You're on I don't want that. I want this a final slice. It went over his head
Wait, did it get went over his head?
Why did it fly over him?
I didn't even do anything. I didn't do anything. He fell
Mothra supreme, huh?
Not so supreme anymore
Sad for a week those new bug snacks. I could just buy new lungs
Here you go
That was sad
Oh, the pizza nose is just pepperoni. It's not a full pizza circle
Let's go home and we'll count up the spoils said mom mom
That's really sad. That was kind of fucked up what you said
This game is sad
Yeah, it is
All right. I got two I got one I got becca's quest line to do
And then i'll probably just end i'll finish the game there
I'm so far into becca's quest line that why would I not do it?
This game has been very very fun
How much is wait, how much is this game?
Very important question. How much is this game?
I don't even forgot
This game is 25 was 20 30 bucks
Absolutely worth it 100 percent
24 99
It is 1 million percent worth it
Do I owe the dishonor cut the grump crum dough?
You're gonna give me a piece of that pie
It's a solid 10 to 12 hours of game
And then there's other little secret
Bugs you can collect
To see all these pictures of you stealing trippany stuff
There's a probably 15 to 20 hours of content here if you wanted it right now
And it's fun and it's cute
You win take a bet hand yours over no need. I'd never sell out my bestie
Is he sleepwalking again?
All right, i'm gonna go to bed and i'm gonna look at my log and we'll see who's got something to do
Okay
Here we go
Effica wants to disguise herself as chanlo to get his secrets
This is here. We're out. Well, I think this is the end of her line here
Wait, you got something else too
You don't get it pal. It doesn't matter if i'm honest or dishonest
Either way I lose out in the end
You think I like being a scumbag a grifter a hustler?
It's all miserable
Okay, I think I haven't tried uh, I gave honest living enough chances
But I wasn't born rich and that means I can't afford to be happy
So unless you're gonna buy something one downside. Yeah, the one downside somebody said steam users molding
Yeah, this is like on the epic game store right now. It's just like okay like cool
It'll be on steam in like six months probably right?
That's the only downside it's like, all right, you're gonna get another launcher, but that it's a great game
Doesn't really whatever you have to download like an exe file
Wambus how you doing? I'm not ready to talk to you yet
Boy, I was in the middle of your line, too
I was okay. I was in the middle of her quest line. There's only one more place mentioned in grandma's journal
One more place. All right, we're about to close out her line for the frosted peak finish the game
Well, you understand that once I finish the game the stream is over almost caught up to gram a lot of blood
You know that right about the view from the top means we ought to start climbing
So all you guys calling for me to end the game. You're actually calling for me to end the stream
What the heck is going on here?
That's the point
Yeah, i'm good. I'm still having fun. Now. Look i'm gonna play my video game. You can play your video game
And we can I thought she was on crutches for a second
We gotta let him know to catch the snoopy banoopi here noted i'll get it
You're really really exhausting this aren't you? Come on. Let's go up the top of the mountain keep going
All right. We made it. This is it. All right
This camp had to be one of grandma's and
It'd be a fitting way to go staring out over the land she loved exploring and what's this snack this is
Maybe a last meal or
This is way too happy for what you're looking at right now
Oh, i'm trying to find my long lost grandma. I wonder what happened to her. Oh, she's dead frozen her skeleton's in an ice cube
Oh, I wonder what she ate before she died. What even when I was a kid?
Didn't have too many teeth. This can't be her s
Unless i'm remembering ron or she got spares. It's been so long. I suppose I can't say
If I want to be dead sure I need an expert
So I guess I'll bury your grandmother
You're a lost explorer from relatively modern times
You can't die in this game. Don't worry. All right. I need a snoopy banoopi
Scoopy banoopi
There's a scoopy banoopi
We need fire come with me. What does he hate? He loves chocolate. All right, give me the ball chocolate on that ball
Hey scoopy come over here run run run run run away all of a sudden just not interested in why
What are you doing?
You just ruined everything ball. Good knock him off the cliff
Okay now
um
It's a trip him
What just happened?
What what what?
I was about to quit the game
I don't care. I apologize for dragging you into this mess again
I'll take care of this issue myself if I want so spindly and reclusive
I know what you're thinking
Where am I getting communicated from okay, so
Why are you calling me dude?
Why are you leaving voicemails on my video?
I I did not rage quit bug snack because I was gonna rage quit to the main menu so I could wake up in bug snackville
Okay
Becca
Becca I got here we go
Effica
Where are you?
You're in here. Uh-huh. What's the final? What's the final?
Part of your quest buried his dirt so deep not even snorpy knows about it
I've spent my whole career looking into the good ones and finding out who they really are
And like i'm always the one who suffers for telling the truth
Every friend I ever had dropped me as soon as I told them something they didn't want died to scoopy panoopy omega low
The only upside to complete scoopy panoopy. Yeah, I don't care
I don't know. I like you because we're similar. I'm a leo like that
Can I really trust you?
there's plenty of time to find out but
I'd probably be a lot happier if I didn't know
Okay
Okay, I thought it was a gun. I thought I thought it was a gun
I really did that was a weird way to say the end and that and then like here comes a gum
Here's a gun. Like I don't know why I thought that was like a gun
Okay
God damn it. I'm gonna get the scoopy panoopy right now
Okay, one scoopy panoopy and then we'll turn that in by that point
We'll be able to do the final part of becca's quest line and then whatever the end of this one is too
And then I will do the final party
Where we invite lizbert to the fire?
I'll take turns eating pieces of her body. I'm sure that's how it's gonna end
All right scoopy panoopy round two, let's go. I'm gonna get ready for this
That's the that's the goal. So we go right here. All right scoopy panoopy
Where is he? I don't see a scoopy panoopy anywhere reload you hunted them to extinction speed runners of this game
Must go absolutely nuts when they don't get the spawn of the scoopy panoopy still no scoopy panoopy
No scoopy panoopies. The hell is that?
What the hell is that thing?
What are these things? Wait a minute. I'm gonna free them. I tried there's a stew guy in here
What if I cut what does the stew guy like? What if I cover? All right, i'm gonna cover the ice and hot sauce
Go for it
Um
I don't know what to do set yourself on fire. Holy shit. It worked. What is this one? There you are
It's an egg roll. I just rescued you the box protects its body. Perhaps it can be grappled away
All right easy
I just like broke its neck
I did it. I got a new one. That's i've never seen that one before
What's in here?
Get the stick bug. Uh, I think this is no this is the burrito one. Yeah, we've seen these before
That's the chili nilly. That's the uh burrito mantis
Are they just gonna fight each other?
Oh damn, they are fighting. All right. Well you guys be good get along. Bye. Okay scoopy panoopy
I need one scoopy panoopy, please. Please please please none wrong way wrong way wrong way
I have to sleep
Sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep for how long?
good night
For the rest of your life. Oh my god
All right, scoopy panoopy
There is a scoopy panoopy. I'm ready
I am ready. I was born ready for this moment. Hey scoopy come on over here
Get the fuck over here. You think that's funny turn around. Why does he have so much trouble going down these steps without?
Okay, he's coming he's coming
Come here scoopy
What? All right. Fuck it. Just go follow me
Quickly quickly quickly quickly quickly
Thank you
He was sad
Yeah, it's just kind of sad because he's about to get eaten
Let's go. Yeah, let's go. Let's go. Where's this guy?
Oh the mill i've got your scoopy panoopy. This dude really is just the dessert guy delicious
Thank you. Charm bug snack for no reason
And while we're enjoying frivolous activities, I have another for you. Meet me out back
Mmm
I'm afraid that our success may provoke a counter-attack from the grumpinati. However, I have defenses prepared
Oh, well almost prepared. I've set up flares around town. They should ward away any predator snacks looking to take action against us
Ward away. Okay. I'm so glad you asked. Did you know that my trip shot can do more than well trip?
It can also spread fire. Wow. I'm so excited for this
The element of nature if you will scoopy panoopy you should be able to like the rest of my flares
All right, light all the flares
There's flare one
flare number two
fire fire fire fire
Oh, bro, you're gonna burn down snaxburg with those things. That's the plan. Why are you lighting all this stuff up?
Bro, I saw snorpy set these up
If you don't want to tell me what he's up to i'll respect that but don't treat me like i'm stupid got it
Okay, sorry you scared me
All right. Now, where's this other one?
Fire we need to light right here
Oh, I actually am gonna burn this place
Whoa, dude, you're gonna burn this place down two more
Where
Are you
Where are you?
Up top. Okay. Give me that
Get out of the house
We're good
The dude just runs in screaming on fire
That would not be cool. Okay six. Where's the last one?
Where's the last fire?
Can we see him?
Why in the garden? Oh, it is right there. You're right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Do you run faster? I feel like you do
We're protected for the time being yes, he does that sometimes he's adorably inquisitive
You let me worry about that. I'm very used to worrying for now ease your mind
I think it actually is like five to ten percent faster
Okay
Here we go. I'm afraid we went up to the wrong target. The mountain is now more active than ever
But the good news is i've isolated the source of this seismic activity
The bad news is it's on the frosted peak. This is another boss
What it might be this is definitely another boss on your toes chum. This one could get messy
Cake boss it
I'm sorry. I didn't know that was gonna work
All right frosted peak. Let's do it. It's gonna be a big cake. I'm actually looking forward to this
After this, we're gonna see what if becca has anything to finish
And then i'm gonna do the final celebration
Oh, no 100 I gotta get some food and I gotta get up to i'm breaking my rule
The four to six hour stream rule has been broken
so
God, I have to get up soon
You're stronger now
Not so sure about that catch one daddy cake legs
In here here. We are the source of the seismic readings
Daddy cake
It's a birthday cake, this is a birthday candle. All right, that's what this was. I was wondering what the mound was for
Happy birthday
Holy shit, okay scan it
this behemoth
Doesn't like having its candles lit a flaming trick shot. All right doesn't like having the candles lit
You don't like to have the candles lit
How did you miss that? I don't I didn't even aim that way
Walk over here. Oh, come on. There it is
I didn't light a candle
Okay work, all right got one
Get the other one
Why would you do that? So anyway, I wouldn't even aim it over there
Say what?
That's not just a giant enemy cake. It's not an enemy spider. It's a giant enemy cake
So, all right giant enemy
cake
Did I light the other candle?
What the hell just came out of him
Well, not to worry according to my readings it's still around here somewhere what about those
Find it and finish the job
Do you forget about these things?
baby cake legs
Recently cut from the cake. They seem to be seeking their master. Oh, I think we just well we follow them
Let's off lock it get off of that
He's not following me
I didn't mean to oh I missed a shot over I missed
I missed a shot over
They're not on fire. Why is it on?
Why is it not on fire?
Shit shit shit shit shit
Shit shit
That's two
All right blow up
He went far
I feel like i'm supposed to be doing this
Because he's breaking up into little pieces, right?
Go on kids. There's the fire. Ah right here
Let's go
Oh
What a shot
Oh, what a shot that was
I want to pick up these guys. I think
He's on fire though. I can't touch him. All right, stop being on fire now
Oh, well, then just do this
Stop being on fire
Oh, okay. All right. Where is he? He didn't follow me around. He was stuck on the mountain
Where did where is where'd he go? He's back in town. What about the trap, but they're on fire
I can't get them to not be on fire
Let's go. Whoa
Where is he? Did he actually get glitched and stuck on the side of the mountain?
There he is
Here eat this. I'm sure you'll love it. Wait, try this one first. That's of just an upgraded marshmallow nose
All right, very cool. All right, let's
Finish the game. Let's finish it. I did a lot of fun stuff
If becca does not have a complete my quest thing immediately
And i'm gonna do the final celebration. That's it finish the quest line. I will all right
I'm about to give my no. No, i'm not. I haven't finished yet
I haven't finished yet
I was supposed to give the final rating but I want to see how the game ends. The ending has a very very very very big
influence on how I feel
I'm done playing games dog that died up there and then what would I do? Huh? I'm sorry chandlo
That was not cool
Just gotta chill out go chill figure out when you're ready to talk to me
All right. Now everybody just stop it. No, he hates being in the dark and I hate leaving him there
I want to tell him but you also kept the whole birthday cake for yourself, which that's all kind of a dick move already
And i'm the one that did all the work and you didn't even share it with me
I don't think you'll believe me. But now it seems like I might lose him who eats their entire birthday cake by themselves
A monster that's who? All right. Where's becca? She's sleeping
Wake up. I keep forgetting. She looks like this
Hey, all right. Do you want to talk?
No, no, I gotta go to the bathroom first
All right. Do you have nothing else for me? Let's see. Do you?
No, I think that's it
That's it
Tiffany
So i'm sorry to say oh the grandmother, right? We have to close this out charming specimen are not related
Oh, well, that's all right then
Thanks for the help
May I keep it? I could use a few more skeletons in my closet
Go ahead
It doesn't really matter now. Anyway, are you good?
Yeah, we got nothing from uh from from becca
All right, tiffany, you got anything to close this out? I'm not doing too good
Happened to my grandma froze to death on top of a mountain looking for
Banana splits
In history just like your fate and like my fate here and everybody else in this godforsaken fucking camp
else who came to this island a place where you go to be forgot a place where i'll be forgotten, but you know
Maybe at least the buck snacks will remember me
Well, is that actually the end of your line here later?
Hmm actually that kind of sad, uh
All right
We're not gonna hundred percent
We're gonna i'm gonna sleep and see if there's anything else
And then i'm going to do the final celebration
I can't sleep in these beds. Why is that? I can't sleep in beds
Anybody you got it? You got me
Oh, nobody nobody got anything. Oh, I think I that's it. All right
All right
That's it. Wow
It's getting crowded around here. I can't believe it. We gotta celebrate big time
This party's gonna change everything buddy. That's it. I'm done. Sure. You're ready. It was very fun
Yeah, I know she but she she has a whole quest log. I'm ready to start the party. I had my fun
Let's party
Awesome. Once everybody's on the dance. He finished didal's encounter. Yeah didal's encounter took like four and a half hours to beat
to enlightenment
Is not with them. It is a journey taken with the mind
It felt like 24
You're saying I should chug this snack water upside down
Yeah, it's really coming together
It's nice to see everybody getting along
Listen philbo. I appreciate what you're doing like getting everybody here. It's way less boring now
Actually still pretty boring though friends. They're just making nice because it's better than being alone
Sure, but who wants to be alone?
Pickle beth
But like in a good way, oh they're gonna they're gonna like each other it's gonna be so cute
They're gonna dance together i'm telling you bephiga that like that like peacock schnoz you got going on
It's working. It really works for you. Wait, you're not you're even
Go dance. Okay. You're not you're not weird. I want to give you like pickle face and hamburger legs get everybody to dance
Let's go. If I knew we were throwing parties like this. I'd have come back weeks ago
Go dance, maybe later, bro. I'm busy soaking up shelter's wisdom
Um, oh dance
and all cleaved a snow of paper shards
So this must be before one dances
Get over there and dance
There's a party in my mouth and i'm invited. Don't ever say that out loud again osteoblast says
Looks like the two of us are yeah, trophy. You're such a treasure dance. He's a real hoot. Yeah, let's go
We should go dance
Wouldn't you rather hear about the captivating history of dance?
Yes, tell me didn't expect that did you tell me everything back in like the fucking incan times back when they were
Cavemen were throwing rocks each other and trading teeth. Tell me about the history mighty fine shindig. We got here
Better than the last one. That's for sure
And i'm thinking I should apologize to grumble first
Can't muster up the words
Maybe I could use some of that there
You want booze? How do I get anybody to dance? Okay, how do I turn on change the song?
I get them to do anything. He's kind of nice. Even the ones are I have to go give him alcohol
Now let's work pass out the alcohol
Wait, all right. I give you the bug juice. I'm gonna give it to him. All right. Here you go. Look at this
All right, it's that easy man much obliged stranger. I better talk to grumble before I lose my nerve
Grumble i'm sorry. Is this wait he walks up punches him in the face even worse to your little ones. You're serious
No fooling. I don't tell jokes. Grimble. I am not
creative
Apology accepted now dance, of course. No forgiving is complete. She always is dancing
So that's what one out of 11 is right? I suppose the dance couldn't join them. What a fabulous party
It's no grumble palooza, but we may do let's go darling. I'm always dancing
I'd love to storm the dance floor, but I prefer to sing along and tragically my vocal chords are fried
Booze you got it
Beverage service now I can sing the night away
Good
What about you? Why don't you go over there? All right, what about you two?
Insults were just get them all drunk
they'll finally dance in capturing research samples and I
appreciate that about you
Your apology is as lacking as your ethical standards, but it's a start excellent now that we are reconciled
I have a dozen research papers that could use peer review as you seem to have free time right now
Let us begin
And I take it all back booze
Here give that back if you don't want it
All right, I'll take it you don't want it
What I cracked like the egg above
All right, that worked
Uh, what about you here? How do I get you over there?
I'm gonna show them what a real party looks like get over there. All right, only a few more. What about you here?
Somebody take this man. Somebody drink it
Ttd without snorpy flaming drink bro drink it. I can't burn. Ah soft lock burn
Now it's time. Oh have fun. Look at them all enjoying themselves. I did this. This is my doing i'm god here
I created the fun
The party lights double as a wave inhibitor. This party is secure
I have something important to ask chandler, but being sibling of mine won't leave me be
You're interrupting personal business unless you have something intelligent to say be gone rhythmic gyration has no purpose
Can you leave the party then leave the fucking party turn it up. What about tiffany?
Go dance with you. Just go talk to lou
I bet floofy will want to learn the desert empire's dance of certain death. He's doing gangnam style
He is
He actually is doing god himself
Okay, now we can have you leave so this is perfect
The desert dance mirrors the moves for hand-to-hand combat against bug snacks
Thus the youth were tricked into learning
Fascinating hiding purpose and frivolous waste. Oh, you believe it when she says it
Trippany has convinced me of the historic and cultural value of expressive movement. Perhaps I should experiment
Oh go go go makes me want to shake my tailbone. My chance has arrived. Don't blow it fizzle bean
Go go go go go go go go
Chandlo, I I we've been together for so long and i've always wondered how you feel about me
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
What bro that doesn't make any sense?
Oh
I see
Wait, what?
Forget what I said
Snorpy we've been dating for years
Wait, what?
How is that possible?
Remember that time we made out on that ferris wheel and I said you don't even know that you're like dating this guy
Well, yes, I just thought that we were roommates with benefits. You know, I hate ambiguity
Sorry snorp dog. Is that clear enough for you?
I love you dog now. Let's dance get over there get over there you two
Hey
Forget about hey, what was that lady's name that fucking disappeared and died or something?
Yeah, fucker. Who cares?
Let's go
smile
Oh, look at that. Just absolutely destroying it. I you i'm gonna talk to the mayor
Bilbo we did it. We did it. We did it buddy. We did we're all together again
Oh, well almost all of us. You know, what are you doing up here?
Is out there gives me hope that Liz
I mean none of this would have been possible without you buddy. It's like a dog waiting for a treat
Back for your job eventually, but I'd sure miss you if you left
And did she say something or is he still need to interview lisper, right? So our end is nigh
She was just getting in place for her queue
and
Well, is that a is this the dark twist that everyone was talking about?
I know this looks bad. But as long as we keep calm
Children, it's the queen of bug queen of bug snacks
Machinations are coming to fruition now. Hold on. We're not gonna die because of some cult or monster
That's right. Bigger out what to do now
The volcano that's right. Wait, what? Oh bad timing
Suppose we're gonna end up buried like all the others. Hey, come on death wing
We can survive this as long as we got bugs next we'll be fine my barn collapsed all of my little ones
That was a lot of work for nothing
This funny nose, I can't take it seriously, this is a very dire horrible situation. Wait, where did you come from?
Hey everybody chanlo floofy mr. Trouble ham
Doc glad you made it. Does that mean you figured it out? That's right. Philbo. I know how to get to liz
We gotta go right away
Stop making me laugh. This is scary chance. We get liz is in danger. This disaster is only getting started
Ending quiet you
Doctor you are only subjecting yourself to needless risk
Elizabeth is likely deceased dog. This bird is alive
And we're not gonna leave her behind
I just need philbo and
This game is fucking ridiculous. I can't even what the hell is happening right now
I we need right now. I this is fucked up
This is this is people that have foods for their body parts talking about like a terrible situation, but look at them
But what do we do when the queen comes to devour us
Well, I have a few
Prototype traps that I could put to use
And more practical threats, you know the earthquakes the volcanoes and what have you
It's got a spy kids vibe find a way to get off the ground if the need arises
Well, none of that matters if I starve to death we got my sauce
Yeah, no way pal. I ain't gonna chat out of that nasty plant goop
I stand corrected no more concerns. Great. Let's get to it then
Where are we going open the mysterious mountain door?
Uh, guess we're going. Why is everybody else not coming with us?
guys, uh, when did it become
God damn it this everybody agreed to do something and the three of us are the only ones that decided to do it
Team project. Yeah
He didn't listen to a single thing I was I was the cameraman
I had to concentrate on who was talking not on what they were saying
What if there was a burger inside monka s that's my favorite comment so far what if there was a burger inside
I don't know. What if there was a burger in there?
Do you need a break? Let me check your vitals. Oh, i'm okay besides we're we're almost there
Right
But in the future you could stand to do some exercise or just hang out with chamelo
I'm gonna play nascar with this motherfucker and get it around
Don't do it. I can't have to I have to do it. I have to do it. I have to I have to do it
It doesn't work. Anyways, we're here
Turns out she wrote the order backwards
I guess even the great elizabeth megafit can still make mistakes
Oh, but he's nerfed, right?
Okay, i'm ready when you are
Wait, I stepped on it too early
Here we go the big reveal
Ah
It was a trap
the under snacks
Where'd everybody go?
What the hell was that?
Elbow i'm coming just stay I did see that thing. Remember I didn't I
That thing appeared like four hours ago and I never took a photo of it
You found me pretty quick. I'm sure she's not far. I'm ready with the camera next time
We did
Jelly river carrot i'll take it. Oh shit. Wait
Why
snack swatch
What the hell is this?
You've become wait, wait, wait
What is this like the council of foods?
Excuse me
She's the whole she's the pizza cake monster thing
Oh my what the fuck
Aren't you but we're out of time you have to get out of here
You have to gather up the others and get off the island
Okay, then we can talk on the way back
No filbo I can't go with you like this
Bilbo
Are you not understand like to have you this doesn't not freaking out at all filbo. She's embedded inside of this
Fucking trunk that's put into the cake. That's put into the pizza
That's put into the frog in the bog in the bog in the lake in the bottom of the sea
Are you seriously trying to interview me right now?
Kind of
Great inviting you you came here to interview elizabeth mega fig
fine
Keep it quick
First of all, what is this this?
This is the island's true form. It's bug snacks all the way down. That's kind of amazing
It's disgusting once you understand what bugs snacks. Oh, no, what are they?
What is a bug snack? Here it comes. It's like the soul of a deceased
Child in another reality
They're parasites. Oh never mind inside you they make you want them and before you know it you become it's not that simple
They're
insidious
Patient so they're they're not cute and cuddly and they'll exploit it
What you see parasites? This is what's left of everybody who came before us
Of every living thing that wasn't bug snacks
They always win
Well, why are you like this after I saved eggabelle I fell into this place
Before I knew what was happening. I was swarmed
Bug snacks were crawling down my throat
They tried to erase me to make me into them
that's
Look at how cute they are
But somehow I pushed back I made them into me
So that bug snack golem monster is you that's right
I'm, sorry if I scared you. I just wanted to make everyone leave this awful place
I can't make bug snacks talk
So the bug snacks are under control the bug snacks are in. Why did your nose change? They have been since we came here
They're so ravenous that they're shaking the ground apart
I'm the only thing keeping this island together right now. It actually is the lich king
But it's like fighting a tsunami with a bucket
Didn't we wait didn't we make that reference in that joke?
like
Yesterday afternoon that's actually what is going on there
You have your eyes. It must always be a bug snacks queen. I'm sorry that I put you through so much to get it
Oh
I can't hold them back for much longer
Please go and warn the others
Wait
Okay, i'm just if you're really not coming. All right, hold on. I gotta tell you
What am I supposed to do without you?
What do you mean the price of the game rating is fine with it going up until about a matter of time before one minute
Ago up and ruin everything it's stuff. It hates me, but you
Of you lizbert
Huh?
They love the idea of me the idea of me. I'm sorry. I put so much on your shoulders bilbo
But you you were the one who can bring them together
me
Well, i'm the one who made it all fall apart. What are you saying?
I led you to this terrible island. I filled your bodies with parasites. What I ignored all the warning signs
I didn't understand what any of you really needed
So now i'm taking responsibility for my mistakes
I'll keep the bug snacks at bay long enough for everyone to escape
Is no no must be some other way we can help you
No, I should be the only one to suffer the consequences of my actions. Nobody else needs to get hurt because of me
I've heard that before don't eat those don't touch those
You shouldn't be here. You need to get away
Start eating her. Let's go get up
Agabel stop it. Okay, I could burn her. I got I got a torch back here that I could connect to
Just so you could play martyr. We're getting out of here together
I
I can't my control is already slipping
If I step outside this cave my connection to the bugs actually is and the island will collapse before I make it another step
Huh? All right, then i'll get in there with you. I can't believe that
move over
It's not a car bell
What is going on?
What the fuck is going on? Oh, the price is falling the price isn't a free fall. It's crashing
The price is crashing right now
A lot of people are starting to sell as of right now. I didn't I just got conjunctivitis
At least the eye patch looks cool does make you look a bit worse
So before the island explodes
Oh
I don't know my investment
I bought in when it was a hundred dollars. I bought it when it was 84 rating a share
What is it now? I don't even want to look at it. We've been through worse than this
We both survived so much by ourselves
Imagine what we can do and we're together
Okay
Good luck and i'll see you again someday
You're going to have to take a bit of a shortcut
Hold on. I thought that just said learn the tutorial. I don't know why
Oh, uh, we gotta get out of here. We're gonna warn everybody
You're on your own, dude. You heard what they said
Back to the beginning
It's the beginning
But no, it's not
Put it down
Put down the bug snacks. You don't understand. It's people
It's made out of people
Stop eating it. Can we get back to snagsburg as fast as we can?
We can't let the others eat any more bug snacks if they transform all the way then don't eat the bunker
We feed them so resistant until we're all out of here
I can't believe you just streamed a pump and dump scheme
Escape from stack tooth quick. Let's go
There they are rump's name. Have you two been
I'll explain later the bug snacks are coming to wipe us out off this island now. I suspect it as much
Luckily, the balloon is almost ready to take flight
Great, but where is everybody dead all dead all of them?
Only buy us time
I need you here
Hold steady my love get the minigun. Oh, but somebody needs to finish fueling the balloon
Don't worry snorty. Leave the balloon to me go and help chandler
Splendid as for you. You may need my snack chop
It's much like the snack trap if it were set to uh-huh puree good luck, okay
This looks simple enough. This is get the is a nuke
bend
defend filbo
Okay, so they're oh they're they're evil bugs. They're parasites and they're gonna kill us
I like the better one. We were just dancing around a campfire looking around for the lady that was lost
Help sheldon and flutie
But they were so cute though
One has foreseen the bug snacks will be five feet to the right of where you're aiming
I'm a scientist not an exterminator. Remember when you force fed the sleepwalking guy parasites against his will
Well, first of all, I didn't know
That he was sleepwalking and second of all, I didn't know they were parasites
Come someone with a healthy capacity for violence take this device and clear a path for us, please
go
This just became a dude another so there really is the dark twist you guys weren't fucking around
You weren't supposed to eat that
Bad ending she ate one. She's gonna turn
Doesn't even hurt see you're fine
Everyone seems to be fine
Dude, okay, you wouldn't drink like four bottles of vodka in one sitting. So don't eat like four cases of bug snacks in one sitting
Bug snacks in moderation seems to be okay
Come on snacks. Let's see what you got
Uh chum over here. I've just finished another device the trip drone with this
We can hold off the bug snacks and escape before chandlo collapses. Don't worry snort dog. He just explained that
All day
Oh, oh you beautiful fool. I'll pilot the drone you aim the shot
Unfortunately, you were short on connective surfaces. How about this?
All right, here we go, oh he's not gonna eat it get don't prevent them from going by
Don't trip
Hey, sir. I need a thing to get attached to
Thank you. Finally threw one
We crushed it dog i'm gonna give you the hug of your life don't celebrate too soon
We're not safe until we're off this horrid rock to the balloon
Out out everybody run
Help ephica and cromdo. Oh that two my least favorite characters in the game. Oh, we can't just burn by them. Okay
All this smoke is making my eyes water. There's one thing i'm good at. It's looking for trouble
Speaking up snacks at three o'clock. You got it fire in the hole
Nice shot
You know what it really is a shame is the fact that we stopped eating bug snacks and don't do bug snacks cosmetics
When you look like that
Like oh you wait, I can't eat like one of the cakes and get like a regular cake nose
I mean i've already gotten this far. I think
I can I do another one eat maybe one or two more
Here take this
There you go. Come on. Don't eat that. I should actually maybe you should eat that
Load it up
I don't think you can't lose
You did finish their quests
Yeah. Hey becca, uh, anyone you want with a spy on right now
Great opportunity. We're in the middle of a total panic. I could really find some secrets
Can we stop?
What did she take a picture of me?
Put the camera down
Help wiggle and ramble
So what that means his friend in the ball is evil
Hurt him so why'd snorpy have to go and why sprout? I didn't know you were so punk rock
I'm not a punk or I can't do this
Well, I know who can I have a name i've got them all warmed. It's time for you to bring the house down
All right
Go that way
Whoa grandma hates bug snacks
No
No, I don't oh man, I I bought in right at the top I really did
It's very good. It's a very very good game. I did I loved it
But we are gonna have to take a few points off
or though like
We have to have a twist ending
A few points have to be taken off
and
These games here at the end
This is not this is not fun
Like I wanted to be done with this portion of what i'm doing right now like 10 to 15 minutes ago
Can we do it?
Oh, you love bug snacks name every bug snack
uh
strawberry
carrot bug
watermelon boss
cake
big cake
burger barbecue burger
Potato sweet potato french fry sweet potato fry
Scoopy-poopy I could do them all
I said bonger I said barbecue bonger and I said bonger obstacle. Yeah, there's enough still got my special sauce fresh grown
Okay
Special sauce
All right, get this special sauce them and they'll kill each other
Uh, what happens if there's only one left?
Oh, that's what happens. Okay, we just eat one
Quick to the boat to the flying boat. That's about as big a break as we're gonna get on wamby. It's now or never
I gave it my best
All right, trippy. Let's go home. Where is home?
and on the balloon
They're gonna break the two of them are gonna break up through the ground in their weird
elephant trunk bodies be like
I kill you
Yeah, we're gonna get a t-rex from jurassic park ending where the t-rex actually saves them, right?
Told you
Can I take a picture? I can't use the camera. Yeah, it's been 12 years think back on that time at bug snack island
Think back at the funny faces. I turned your face into a straw. Give you a pretzel for a head
Turned you into a fast food logo. Think about how painful your face probably is right now. I think about your songs
Now they made me laugh
Some of them most of them were terrible you I see a lot of you and me
Especially that hat and you i'll never forget that face
And you wait actually talk to them, oh right well there goes another farm
Me right for building it on top of a size pest. I guess there's no shame in starting fresh
I'll find a place with rich soil
And he talked to the eye
Dude you see that that was kind of like a side. I wait a minute. I don't know about that
I was so close to giving up back there. I get so caught up dwelling on the way lives end
It's not the only thing that matters. Yeah wambus and I we're gonna start the rest of our lives today
What about the tiffany cactus?
Yeah, uh
My friend
I don't think it's appropriate to
Take around like the cactus sex doll of your wife
Still I just like plant it plant it somewhere and like take all this off and let it just grow
You don't you don't find that a little weird like you don't tiffany. That's not a little weird to you
I spent on chasing one new and pink shame andy
No, i'm just saying he's carrying around a doll of you with you around like that's
You're gonna get jealous of the doll. You're gonna be like you got that fucking doll every day
It's me. I'm not good enough. I'm not as good as the doll
Well, I mean, I know that's not what i'm saying. No, I don't
Feel sad when I left all my of course you are of course you are
They tried to murder me also for real. Okay. All right. I have to just not look at the screen while you talk
Hey bestie didn't work. I still think I can see I can see it
Now I know to make new friends and this time I won't ruin it for myself
Gotta remember you
Okay, I know when i'm beat
I draw the line at island full of monsters
All I wanted to do was quit my dead-end job and do what makes me happy
I don't need some big bug snack scam to do that. I don't want to hear everybody's end of their
Check the boat
Why check the boat nothing on the boat? Thanks. Thanks for padding the ending of the game
I'll be very honest
I don't even want to hear your end of your whatever your last four
Dialogue pieces are because I didn't even care about you in the entire game. I didn't do any of your side quests
I don't even know who you are while I regret that all my research was destroyed
I have come away with a revelation cannot improve grumpest kind if I refuse to understand it
It may be a long and frankly annoying endeavor, but it is one worth pursuing
All right, she ate one of the donuts accidentally now you have a donut hand
Same thing with you. I don't know who you are either. I kind of know you wrong being right
I wish I hadn't wasted so much time telling riddles to give good advice
I just need to be me and those who listen will listen
smuggling
shitload
Back back home. Apparently they don't even know i'm taking them back with us
Seems my enemies aren't so all-powerful after all i'm gonna spread this around the world. They're gonna take over real soon
And chandler was always there. We're gonna have to go to customs. I'm gonna get stopped at the border
That was intense
There's no way I ever would have made it out of there by myself
Good thing snorphy had my back. When did he get so strong?
Maybe I hit my personal limit, but that doesn't matter
There's no limit to what we could do together
except for anything that requires
Fingers or toes that's off limits for a lot for now
Hey, buddy. I'm ready to go. All right, everybody or three people
What do you mean three people?
They'll be fine if anybody can survive in that terrible place or smelling
Right because all their noses are like fruits and vegetables
Or hearing or thinking this is like implanted in their brains
You're right. Nobody should ever set foot on snack tooth island again
What do we do about it? I know I can't go wallowing in regret now
We're barely even out of the woods
It's gonna take a while for the bug snacks to wear off on us. I can't go back home like this. So
Is it all right if I stay with you for a while? Absolutely not help you with your story
Maybe figure out which parts to tell or
I've
Absolutely not
I got a one bedroom
one bathroom
No, i'm sorry, but you know what sure great. Let's go
This one was just one over the road release them. No, i'm taking them home with me
You got guts
Tracking down elizabeth inside an erupting volcano. It's compelling dramatic sensational
I'd call it fiction if you didn't have this filibus yahoo along as a witness
It's filbo actually point is you're a regular grumpter s thompson
It's just too bad. Those bug snacks weren't real, huh?
Yeah, too bad
I I hate to think that we went through all that. Hey, would you like a gummy worm clumpy?
I hope you can spread the truth about snack tooth before anybody else gets hurt
Don't worry gnn specializes in painful truths and speaking of you're fired
His story's a page turner and all but you lost your job the second you walked out that door
That's
Oh, thanks. It's not like I expected you to come back
Also, you're legally dead
Might want to clear that up soon
It wasn't ideal but your bad worst days, huh buddy?
so I hear the elections are coming up and uh,
I'd say why'd you say that running for mayor? Why'd you say that? I could use a helping paw. What the hell?
How about it? You just fucked up my whole stream
bug snacks
by kevin zun
christopher stahlman megan vardy
john murphy
rice pulls
kevin geisler devin scott tunken
This is the song
Okay
so
Here's here's the deal
We climbed up i'm gonna give you what I think
we hit
peak
Yesterday afternoon yesterday night 77 78 79
79 by this afternoon 80
81 82 83
84 before we got to that last room
84 I was about to lock in in 84
I was about to lock it in
And then I wasn't a huge fan of the ending. It was I mean they tried to do something interesting
It brought I came down to 83 82 81
79 78 came down 78
Came all the way down to 78 and it's and it evened out there went to actually hit it actually the the candle wicked
At 75 let's be honest
Is all the voice actors?
That's cool
But then we we had a little bit of a bounce
of the 75
76 77 78
And we settled at 78
I think I still think it's a good game. It's very good. It was very very interesting. Very cute. Very different
I really liked it
This is a 78
It hit like 84 somewhere
It was around 79. You know what?
I can't give it an 80 though. I can't I can't I because it's like it's so that's so easy to say 80
Everything's an 8 out of 10. Everything's an 8 at 10 every game's an 8 at 10, right?
So just say 81 that's true
All right. I'm gonna give you a range so i'm between 78 and 81
That's where this game lies for me
It was very it was very good. It was very enjoyable. I liked it a lot
I wouldn't have screamed it for seven and a half hours today and yesterday, too
I loved it
I didn't super love it
It's an 81 done. No, it's not an 80. No, it's not. It's an 81
79.5 to 79.8
I can't tell I can't make my decision. It's a 78. I sent them away
It would be hard to make them disappear at this point 79.4 done
hard to say
Could be they're idiots
Could be they know the truth and they're keeping it quiet 79.5. It just got a blend
Yeah, this is like a weird creepy ending here we're getting a second one 79.5
But jokes aside with the extra, you know with the the score
Uh, the game's 25 bucks
It was that was incredibly enjoyable. It was very very good. It's great
I got what I I got my 25 dollars worth
12 plus hours of cute monsters and funny characters and it was great. I will give a stamp on recommend on this one
Thought it was very good a dollar an hour
You can't get a deal like that at very many places and that's where we're gonna end tonight
Thanks for watching everybody. This is a long one. It kind of broke my rules here, but i'm okay
Uh 50 dollars just came in 5 000 bits
from goiki and he says
This game is great. Fuck you for even as much as insinuating anything different. Anyways, here's 50 dollars. Well, thank you. I get thanks
Uh 79 is is good
Seven, uh, I remember it hit 85 at some point
You can't I don't just rate games based on just here's a flat rating. You guys know this
Resident evil 7 you remember? I will defend my score. I do not give games a rating
I give them a rating based on like where I currently am
The first like four hours of resident evil 7 was a 90
Hour number three through five was like a three
And then like the last two hours was like a 60 70 remember like I
I rate games differently than other people. What is a 95 game half-life 2?
No, that's not even accurate. I think half-life alex is better than half-life 2
Half-life alex is better than half-life 2. I just said it out loud with 10 000 people here. Hope I don't die
I hope i'm not like it
Just I hope I don't like it like incinerated by like the gaming god
Game gamer satan's gonna come out of my ground and electrocute me to death the reddit council monka s
I love half-life. I love it's a great series. I think half-life alex is the most fun i've had in a half-life game though
But it's not really fair because it's this new crazy technology and half-life 2 is like fucking 15 years old not fair
But uh, that's gonna be it. I will see you guys in a few days
Uh, what's today sunday? Let's see. Yeah
monday tuesday
Uh, probably wednesday or thursday. I'll see you guys again on wednesday or thursday
Keep an eye on the sauce over the next day or so give you a good date
bug snacks
delicious
So thursday, right just assume thursday always
We're gonna sell the uh credits here all the community subs all the gifted subs. Thanks guys
It's just
Okay, I open up tabs when I open up images that you guys link
and
They scare the shit out of me. Sometimes I just this was this was just the second tab that I clicked on
i'm blocking the credit
It was very good. I'm happy to have played bugs next they did they did a great job
Who's your favorite character?
Uh bobsicle bobsicle is my favorite character. What about your favorite grumpus?
Uh wiggly we already know that
Did I play the sequel if it came out? Yeah, absolutely
They're the character design and the actual game design with
Just looking at the bug snacks was the most fun part of the whole game
And they obviously this team has enough creative juices to make these awesome
Funny cute little monster food items. So I would love to see more of that
What are they not? Well, yeah, wait, how do you do a second one if you know that they're not cute? That's true
Yeah, how do you do a second one when everyone knows the
the twist
What are you gonna do? Okay, jedi academy
I don't know. Maybe all right. Should I should we start with should we do jedi academy next spring this week?
I think the the book is out on this one people either really really don't want me to do this or they really really really do
No more kitty bullshit
Come this is come on
Come on, dude. What do you mean? No more kitty bullshit
I'll slip your vr. I'm gonna i'm taking a break from vr. I'm taking a break from vr. No vr
Yeah, hey dallas
No more star wars games. All right, but hold on
I have to finish
I have to finish at least lego star wars. Give me that one, please
We can all agree on that right and I will play sly cooper as well. All right, please be honest with me is sly cooper
A ratatouille thing where everyone's just saying that and then when I actually buy this game and set it up and capture it
Everyone's gonna be like fuck this game. This game sucks. Stop playing it
Is this a ratatouille two thing where everyone just says it because it's a meme
No
All right. I'm gonna get it and we're gonna do it next week. You understand i'm gonna get sly cooper sly cooper one
And i'm gonna play it next week
I'll see you later. Let's uh
Let's raid somebody let's raid
Let's raid kraken it's been a long time since we raided kraken. What's he doing gary's mod
Silver squad and the mystery of the broken bunker. That's a mouthful. I wonder what they're doing. What about the emotes?
Oh, yeah, I owe you guys a bunch of emotes. I do owe you guys a bunch of emotes
I bet you'll never see them
No, you will but thanks a lot guys to see in a few days. See you probably on thursday
Have a great rest of your night. Have a great rest of your evening. Have a wonderful day
Thank you so much for watching
We'll see you soon
Good night. Goodbye
Take care