I did. I just rolled. I was like, all right, here we go. I'm ready to go. And I just rolled and just crunched one of my headphones.
You know what? Why don't that? Why don't headphones have a retractable cord?
So I can like, let's stick it on the desk. Why does it have to be this loose ass wire?
It's all right. It still works. That's good. Like a dog leash. Yes.
Why can't I just put a dog leash on that's connected to my headphones?
You can make that shit stylish. You could make like a little collar that looks cooler.
I said no, you shouldn't do that. All right. Uh, let me give me one second. I'll be right back.
Okay. Good afternoon, everybody. Starting early today. For a very, very important reason because
I didn't stream yesterday and I wanted to, but I had a lot of stuff to do. Which kind of bled
into today, but I was able to get it all done. I've got a wink. All right. I'm, I'm going to
delete the winks. I'm changing it. I'm changing it. I'm changing it. It's over. This is the last
wink that's going to happen. I'm changing it as of today. These are the last day of winks.
These are the last days of winks. And then I'm going to change it to something else.
I'm going to change it to fucking like, I don't know, something else.
I'm so close. That don't end. I'm going to change it to something else.
I'm going to change it to something else. I'm going to change it to like get a free
emote or something. Okay. All right. We got to go over this. So I don't read
bits or subs on stream. Usually ever. Unless it's like, whoa, holy fuck. That was, that was crazy.
Like I usually don't do it. So winks are replacing the, cause I don't, I don't like to interrupt my
stream. Right? So what's happening now is there, now there's a way to interrupt the stream.
Like guaranteed. Do the winks at the end? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, they're staying. After today, they're probably going to be gone.
And plus, you know, let me give you, all right, I'm going to be, it's time for the real,
it's time for the real reason. Okay. Would you like to know the real reason? Why? No more
bullshit. Would you like to know why? Because I have to wear clothes now. I have to be clothed
while I stream. I don't like this. I like, I don't like to have the, I don't like, I want to
be no, I don't, I don't want a shirt on right now. I have to always be ready to turn the camera on.
I like to stream naked. You guys know this? I've been doing this for like six years,
naked. That's the real reason. That's the real, that's the real reason.
Audios distinct? I can't, no, yeah, that's not, what are you talking about?
audio's ahead? it's impossible. it's impossible. that's not real. you're making that up. uh anyways
yeah i because well you know i don't read bits or subs you know that's the reason no no no no
it's because i have to have a shirt on every day when i sit here and i when i sit here for like
six plus hours i like so wet and i don't uh nope it's not desync i can see it right now i can see
the monitor all right i'm going to change it to uh at 75,000 points i don't know it is desynced
what no it's not it's that's not even possible to be desync oh it was three i'm it's slightly off
it's impossible there's no i've not there's no hold on ready okay zero oh it's all zero
milliseconds bing bing bing it shouldn't be at all what's happening first is my face moving first
or is the audio moving first is the audio late early i don't get it audio is happening first
doesn't make any fucking sense that doesn't make any sense how about now you guys are liars
anyways uh hi guys today we're starting early because i'm going to go long today
uh we're doing a super stream people like what does that mean what's what is a super stream
general like i'll give you an explanation it's a stream that's up to six hours up to six hours
could be uh it could be six it's a long stream now we're gonna we're gonna go probably like
i think six and a half you know that's a long one get me off this fucking camera so what people have
decided and i i thought we had a pre-stream uh chat about there's another wink this hey member
do you guys remember listen to me this is really important because like fuck do you remember how
we made the joke about like oh it's so how let's make it so it's like 100 000 points to turn his
cam on you guys got me this is this is what that is this is that this is just 75 000 points to turn
on his camp that's what this is it's not even about the wink it's not that the winks don't
has nothing to do with the winks it has to do with we can turn his camera on for 75 000 points
and it worked also we're going to talk about images because i want to talk about this off cam
so we're going to come up with a solution here i know i nobody people don't people don't want
to hear this i know i know this is a long-standing thing that's been in this channel but he's mad
no what i'm not what are you talking about uh let's put this on scream scream that's just that's
jet that is that that is an image of my sister that is actually and that's an image of my sister
my direct sibling my my my sip my that's my sister that's a literal exact image of her um
in fact like when i first looked at it i was like where did you get this picture of my sister
why do you have this uh anyways so sometimes when we stream here first of all let's just get
the thing that's we're going to be playing universal uh studios presents paperclip counter
whatever the fuck this is called i'm going to be playing universal paper clips uh i don't know
this is what people voted on i know way i know i know i know hold on there's a lot i got a lot
of things to talk about for the first five minutes of the spring 10 minutes 20 it's going to take
we're in there for the long haul but listen to me okay uh black and white two is supposed to be
today but if i got i have technical problems that it was fucked up so i was actually supposed to
yesterday so black and white two is supposed to be yesterday i had some technical issues with it
uh so i got to fix them so i'm going to fix those technical issues with black and white two it was
supposed to be yesterday was supposed to be today instead but then i had some more technical problems
so it's going to be probably in a day or two uh so that happened also megaman legends was supposed
to be today but people uh there was a vote that people voted for and nobody people didn't want to
see it if people wanted to see this instead i was like why and i was like okay i get all right i
guess we're gonna do this for a while and then there was i may have fucked up the vote a little
bit because i put a tuber game at the end of this because this is probably gonna take what like five
six hours so there's a tuber game that was part of the vote at the end of this it's the speaking
simulator you move your tongue around and have to open the mouth and click it's a youtube.com game
um so they may have been uh those who they're looking for murius you're not going to get it
today you're also not i and i i have i'm gonna veto i'm gonna veto if i don't like it and we're
gonna move on to something else this is a long stream today it's like hand simulator yeah i know
and i probably shouldn't have even put it on the that's probably why this one but so that explained
that right okay good explanation that was a little neurotic but it's kind of who i am so long stream
six hours no this is gonna this okay you ready you wanted what a verbal contract today's stream
will be at the absolute minimum seven and a half hours at the absolute minimum
at the maximum it will be up to 10 and a half hours 11 hours maximum 11 hours maximum so you're
looking at like probably like a like a 10 hour stream today i had my vitamins i've had my food
and yes i'm fucking dragging out this intro because i got a we've got a long way to go
i'm also i'm gonna have to eat in the middle of this stream so those of you that are like what
the fuck where'd he go it's been like fucking 20 minutes like i'm eating food because it's gonna
be like 11 hours so i'm not gonna social eating it i'm gonna go like eat like downstairs like a
small plate just eat it i don't want to eat on stream i hate eating on stream so how does this
game even work but i'll keep the cam on for now what the what the what the fuck do i care seriously
finish the oh that's right images right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we got a lot of things to
talk about so over the was that even a wink no i just thought it was this is why this is
fucked up this is why like i gotta get rid of these blinks they're messing up my whole
my messing up my whole game here uh so as you know if you are a subscriber of this channel
you can put a link right there's links you can put a link it could be to anywhere as long as i've
all i have to say is as long as it's not porn and it's relevant to the stream then we can do it
right that's fine but sometimes we get some image spam and there's i've certainly seen some
feedback from people that said that they the image spam uh the m girl links might uh might
be annoying to them so here's what here's the the idea okay i think it's fucking hilarious
right to an extent to an extent you're straw manning what if i'm the straw man
what what if i'm the straw man is what what i'm about to explain to you that it's it's me
i'm the straw man i'm the guy that's being standing here that's being built up for this whole scenario
anyways so sometimes there'll be a lot of links spammed over the course of a stream and i think
they're funny i really do but you notice that when i go through them it takes like it takes
like a minute wait where's that link oh let me scroll click no i missed it oh is this the right
one is that the right link okay no let me open that one okay uh now uh pull it over here and
put it on the source and uh on lbs and like it's kind of it's it it takes some time for me to do it
so my theory i haven't done this yet but it is my actually i'm not going to tell you my theory
because i know i didn't want to steal my idea what's the point of even bringing this up if i
don't want to tell you what i'm doing there is going to be okay this is gonna i i can't do it
yet because i haven't it's not set up yet it's this i'll fuck the whole thing up if i tell you
right now anyways there's going to be a solution to this it's going to be very good it's going to
be very clean so there will there will not be a need to put links image links in the chat anymore
we can we're gonna we're gonna we're doing this thing we're gonna start to clean up the chat a
little there's gonna be a solution it'll be great and it'll be really easy for me to open up images
on stream rather than me fumbling around like an idiot trying to go back and forth and put an
image into obs or to pull like a random image link and put it over here or capture my window it's
gonna be a very simple thing to do and it'll i can do it in one second because i will already
have this captured it's gonna be fun it'll be fun but i don't want to tell you what it is yet
because it's not ready yet he's lying to waste time just have the discord channel for it hold on
hold on don't give away any secrets sorry the hedgehog movie came out i heard it was kind of
good i heard it was kind of a good movie is that real i heard it was like okay it's got it's not
it's not rotten on rotten tomatoes it's apparently like a good game
movie well sonic was a good game but because you read that on reddit all right i'm okay i opened it
up paper clips you can't even like see this hold on does that does okay does any of this shit matter
at all in this game like does any of this matter or can i like crop this and pull it up it does
all right well fucking hold on can you guys see that put it on dark mode can you i don't think
you even can can you guys like read this is it is it you guys good i love these games so this is
not going to be hard for me to want to like play this so let's make it a little bit bigger because
i know i can because i can get rid of this uh okay there we go all right let's go uh pay welcome to
universal paper clips on dermis joel impression you're already sidetracking me i fucking i've
rolled over my headphones today and now i can't hear anything okay that we know i can hit myself
twice hello hello can you guys hear that too what the fuck what's going on there we go all right
let's listen to this well i guess germa centered all right let me just crank out the germa
impersonation well hi guys um sorry i'm late uh hope everything had a good summer i really miss
quite late the class is bad enough but interrupting my monologue you're on the fast
thanks for the clip anyways let's go uh make a paper clip why did you send me that
make a paper clip one paper clip two paper clips three four five six seven eight nine ten let this
cost money available funds okay i've unsold inventory price per paper clip is 25 cents
the demand for paper clip is 32 percent that's pretty fucking high that's that's really high
i can't think of the last time i even purchased one paper clip let alone
you have a demand for it in my life all right so we have a manufacturing clips per second zero
988 inches cost 15 all right so let's make some more clips price per clip 25
cents should i make this higher all right i'll make it i've looked whoa whoa public demand is
dropping because of this this one over megaman legends yes yes it did but i also may have stuffed
in i may have like stuffed in votes into the ballot box accidentally because this is a fun
game i've heard relax all right public demand is only 28 auto clippers available for purchase
all right hold on auto clippers i have one what is this inches thing play some music
all right yeah yeah how about like um i actually like this is gonna be a good stream
i'm gonna have lots of fun sitting here counting paper clips for seven straight hours
not doom no that's too much but um something that can sit in the background that's like
the trumpets in it you can always tell when a song when a ost is good for background when
it has like slight trumpets in the background to mario 60 yeah mario 64 speaking of super mario
brothers guys there you are i can look at everything you're saying speaking of super mario brothers
uh guess who is going to be starting uh super mario sunshine is on very soon on original
hardware by the way well that's that's a lie on act on hardware all right what am i doing
no not a full playthrough mario 64 ost i feel like i've heard these songs way too much though
all right how about like i i think i'm okay i'm gonna skip halfway through because i've heard like
i've heard that like too many times in my life you know what i'm saying
okay i've heard that too many times no this is one
no skip no skip this one all right here we go no this penguin one i don't like that one either
i like i love these songs all right this one's good here we go all right this is 28 demand
let's get some auto clippers cost how much how much money do i have 16 all right let's make some
more clips i don't i don't like this one either it's too much there we go that's better so what's
okay is it why do people want to play this so bad i'm gonna lower the price
why is public no no no that no no no no lower the price the 25 cents what is this inches
600 inches what does that mean should i start just spamming oh i need more wire to make the
paper clips this is pretty good paper clip making some all right i need 100 from no no
17 bucks for wire 14 bucks for wire i'm running out of unsold inventory where's my i have 690
how do i do that
should i lower the price this is 50 percent demand all right it's 17 cents paper clip
it's 15 cents for a paper clip i got 12 bucks 13 bucks all right i'm starting to make money
unsold inventory is going up though i need some more wire
wait hey what happened i'm out of wire i think i think i lose did i lose no not yet
this looks like math homework 74 724 unsold should i lower it to like 100
i'm gonna lower it to like extreme demand like 10 cents it's still going up
please zoom in i was told not to zoom in extreme demand what the fuck freddy dredd watches you
this is still going up though all right i'm gonna give him a wire
if i make it even lower oh fuck oh my god okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait there's too
much demand got a coffee in me this is a sleep game goodbye see you in like six hours when you
wake up from your nap all right we go 35 bucks almost at marketing let's go a little bit higher
let's go to 100 percent man 45 dollars we're gonna go marketing i can make my own here too
what if i just lower the demand and just spam click and just it'll never stop
try to check this out ready i'm gonna sleep yet oh this is a sleep song this is a sleep song
i raise price this is a sleep song i'm gonna keep it on whatever what's this what's that
trust two plus one trust at 3000 clips computational resources clippers one processors plus one trust
automatically calculate average revenue per second i don't get it zero creativity all right
marketing level one let's get it wait not yet i'm gonna raise the price a little bit like it no
i can't all right i'm gonna get marketing level one does that help you fool you fool
rev tracker 500 oops what is it ups unsold inventory i gotta i gotta do something about that
here we go now everyone's gonna wake the fuck up all right i'm gonna uh i'm gonna raise the price
10 cents operations automatically calculates average revenue per second revenue 75 cents a
second nice average processors plus one memory should do memory or processes what's memory do
memory plus two memory added max operations increased oh okay i get it unsold okay we're
gonna do we're gonna lower the price how much money do i have 20 bucks more auto clippers
oh shit i shouldn't have done that all right lower the price actually yeah low the price
oh i got these auto clippers going seven cents operations increases auto clippers
performance by 25 percent oh yeah fucking let's go i get wires no crazy price i just want to make
it real clear if if you copy and paste a recommendation spam into the chat i'm not
gonna read it um i haven't even read it i'm not gonna even read it i'm not even gonna read that
that instantly stopped it was like ah shit all right like okay he's not gonna read it so i might
as well not do it anymore where are we uh i'm gonna raise prices the paperclip market is crashing
raise please raise the fucking prices this song gives me like anxiety auto clippers performance
by 25 percent this one gives me anxiety too how is it the same song sounds all right all right
so we got unsold inventory auto clippers make more clippers i need to lower the price so i can
just dump all this inventory right 75 cents a second all right let's dump this inventory
already check this out five cents a clip now four cents a clip 220 look at this i'm making i'm
making two dollars and 15 cents a second look at this money going up you kidding me i need i want
more processors operations per second increased probably shouldn't have done that all right let's
go back up what are you talking about hummus with carrots is so much better
um hummus is good with everything you can put it you can literally put any do anything you want
you can dip cheese in there like little you can dip like cheese in it bread even if you just random
sandwich bread doesn't matter more wire supply from every pool yep does somebody somebody say
jeremy disgusting face for hummus hummus is one of the actual most just satisfying foods you can
eat it's so good for you it tastes that's why the camera's not ever on because you don't see
shit like that and i just pretend i don't talk for like three seconds um you could put anything in
hummus you can replace hummus uh replace mayo for hummus increases auto clippers performance
can i have a small wire supply i like that one hummus is a top 10 food yeah it is i used to
eat hummus when i was in college because it would fit in my little college fridge and i would eat
this shit oh every day like you i bought a ton of it i would buy giant jugs of it and eat it every
day like at night dinner all right what we got i need to lower the prices we need more wires i want
more auto clippers too more how do you say yuck to that i don't understand that all right i'm
gonna lower the prices even more and i'm gonna spam click check this out yeah just even standard
garlic hummus is just it's so good it's so delicious it's really rich too i know a lot
of people like i don't know if i would like it's super rich and deep flavoring you can get you can
do mediterranean style you can put anything in it you can put it's a veggie hummus there's a hot
pepper hummus there's a garlic hummus it is so much how much money i'm doing a dollar 66 per second
all right memory use idle operations to generate new problems and solutions creativity what okay i
need to lower this how do i have this much unsold inventory this is a food stream oh it's so good
all right here we go now it's telling me crazy there's anybody increases while operations are at
max okay so operations if we get operations to max and 10 000 clicks created in 17 minutes damn
hummus tastes like a dirty sock um i have a couple of questions there why do you know what a dirty
sock tastes like number two how could somebody be so incorrect in one sentence
i don't know okay almost let me see what this does it's just did it like 97 percent increases
autoclip of performance by 50 more percent hold on i'm gonna see what happens here max operations
let's see we're getting there thank you so much for playing my game all right here we go operations
are max creativity one oh shit holy fuck okay this is what you do you say max operations and
you sell a ton of stuff look at how much money i got all right marketing too coming up creativity
eight nine ten why does this keep why is it still going 11 what's going on i can't i can't what's
happening wires i need wires what so creativity is just counting up forever okay marketing level
two algorithmically generated poem plus one trust there was an ai made of dust whose poetry gained
it man's trust why did i just do that what a fucking would have worried what a waste
improves it increases auto clipper performance by additional 50 let's get it i need to raise
the prices here all right let's do um more processors and memory okay why do i like this
why do i like doing this thanks for the wink god i don't have to turn the camera on i can just do
it from here okay so it's more wire wire buyer automatically purchases wire when you run out
seven thousand operations what the fuck are you talking about
uh that's it that was the super mario 64 soundtrack let's sell all this shit
i'm gonna say it say it it's not even correct keep going how much money do i have 91
so marketing i'm assuming just makes you be able to set put it back on
one all right fine i'll put it back on 20 000 paper clips more wire from supply pool got it
you're selling too cheap am i there how about that i'm making a ton of money per second
development investment engine for generating funds what the fuck does that mean all right
let's do uh processors for more wire cheaper cheaper cheaper cheaper cheaper cheaper oh fuck
that's too cheap two dollars and 64 cents a second two dollars is this supposed to say
why am i saying that i'm wrong this music i do it cheaper than that three cents um i guess
it's i guess it's making a lot of money cheaper two cents make them free all right that's good
okay i got 264 i need more memory capitalist um i don't know if it's is it capitalist to lower
prices to almost zero wouldn't i wouldn't it be like making a hundred dollars per clip
all right i'm gonna raise it a little bit i gotta get back to 337 bucks i got plenty more auto
clippers more operation creativity going up why is it so long why is it so so long
i feel like i've heard the same song for like the last three hours okay gain ability to
interpret and understand human language impossible is a word to be found only in the dictionary of
fools what did i just do improve marketing effectiveness by 50% yep memory run the mega
man legends ost no no no no no we're gonna play that it's not now well i can't make paper clips
why oh shit that's why uh i'm okay with last stream we played hidden folks and we were supposed
to play mega man legends like where's mega man legends why playing this game where you just
click on the screen and look for stuff oh that'll be next time and then now you open the street
today uh the mega man legends was gonna be maybe today no i'm clicking on the screen on a white
background i'm making a lot of fucking money though pre-stream chat you've made mistakes
oh i've heard this too many times
get it off turn it off turn it off i've done it too many times uh let's do ocarina of time
too sad scary too somber too relaxing too anxiety inducing too church-like okay there we go
increases auto clipper performance by 75% yep goo castle like unsold inventory you ready for
this one check this shit out boom sell sell sell sell sell eight dollars a second 14 dollars a
fucking second 15 dollars a second market level four yep all right now raise prices middle wire
raise prices get this shit that's how you click this fucking fast you see how many you see that
uh wire auto clippers lower the prices no i'm hearing the cuckoo sounds no don't do that
new song as i played like ocarina time like 600 fucking times and like i don't i don't i want
something new something fresh i want to like move my hand around like it's connected to a fucking
device that's robotic what am i doing this i'm doing like a robot demo like a convention like
what the fuck donkey kong country soundtrack oh that's not what i wanted that's not what i
wanted why is i'll take it though this is nice this is mine a little a little scary but whatever
all right ready check this out lower the prices i need more memory holy shit this selling so fast
okay there we go memory try to match your clips per second and clips sold per second
how do i see my with my clips per second there's 194 sold per second with clips per second
110 okay lower raise ready there we go automatically purchase wire when you run out now that's
fucking yeah that's fine wire buyer on don't manually click i have to i have to do that like
my breath that scratches my brain where we got 125 120 we're we're perfect
we're absolutely perfect it's boring you fat shit i actually have lost like a few pounds in
the last like six months so i don't know what the fuck you're talking about how about you like i
you like a little fat today i've lost some weight i mean you need lessons uh so we're currently at
almost maximum efficiency right now so now what do i do somebody is anyone else racing him
what do you mean racing me i'm at max efficiency i have 600 bucks what does this one do investment
engine i need more clips i need more i need more okay ready check this out boom just use our money
was it 130 for your second lower the prices 135 per second this per second
you've had marketing you could have had marketing fuck yeah it's all right all right 120 135 clips
a second can you peak your mic with max condenser on please um yeah all right marketing level five
we're gonna get is there a reason for anything i'm doing right now am i gonna get i have a feeling
that somebody said no no no just wait there's no reason to do anything we're gonna get to max
operations like pat upon i actually have that's one of the games that i'm getting i just by the
way i just bought like 25 more games by the way there's a 3do in that fucking trash bag over here
remember you know the trash bag that's been wait what combinatorial harmonics daisy daisy give me
your answer that's bonzy buddy i get this listening is selecting and interpreting and acting
and making decisions all right processors of memory probably memory right everyone's never
seen a movie before what are you talking about all right hold on we gotta do a little bit lower
the prices gonna do memory memory eight thousand double marketing effectiveness uh yep flip it
flip it good marketing is now twice as effective oh shit public demand is fucking crazy what
oh shit uh marketing is so good okay uh flip sell the second we'll do like 12 cents okay public
demands can i get some more auto clippers i'm gonna get some auto no what do i do memory again
memory again this is a bitcoin farm i cannot live without paper clips well that welcome to the stream
thanks for coming around i'm gonna lower the prices a little bit to 11 cents that way we stay
on on top of this here monkey s are you monkey essing jib jig one of the best songs in donkey
con country too i'm gonna get processed nest time this time 100 more wire that's who cares
oh shit i've been playing this for 30 minutes i feel like been here for like 10 minutes
this is going this is cool this stream hurts uh don't touch your don't like touch the back of
your computer with a wet hand and like electrocute yourself it shouldn't be hurting you like to make
sure like your mouse like make sure that the you don't have like exposed wire on your mouse
like don't touch it it wasn't what do you mean bad joke that wasn't a joke somebody told me
that this was hurt this stream hurt them i didn't do anything what did i do this was sitting here
bad game bad game this is stupid i'm gonna continue to sit here and what watch
and tell them every five minutes how much i don't like this
literally me literally me it's because i can literally see you put that vein away
not a big deal like what are you eating you see what are you eating fucking chips
boogers carrots and hummus he's actually mad no if i was actually mad i would go like this
fucking goddamn fucking idiots no that was an impression wait wait wait wait wait you do that
all the time no i don't all right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait all right more wires
what kind of masochist would sit here and get and just be berated by this psychopath
i don't know is it the same kind of people but come on you guys like you remember the people
that used to hate listen to howard stern they would like turn it up and like wait for him to
say something that they didn't like and then they'd call the fucking station they made a movie about
howard stern's life and they said that people that hate watched howard stern like what increased his
viewership like times 10 like they hate watched him you don't know howard stern is oh well let me
let me help you here uh the judge on x factor now what what what's he a judge on america's got
talent fuck nobody watches that show um nobody watches that show because i don't i yeah um
he was an old shock jock radio dj that actually he was like a dickhead on on on avian shit how do
i explain how do you explain howard stern to like somebody that doesn't know who howard stern is
he was just a oh you don't you don't know what a shock jock is he was an edgelord yeah there you go
oh yeah that that's only in america yeah that's true let's get some more look at i'm spending all
my fucking money yeah howard stern from the beetles i don't think howard stern was in the beetles
all right how we doing right there that's 163 that's it use neuro resonant brief to
influence consumer behavior oh my god what the fuck production target met trust increased
additional process memory capacity generated oh my god i'm gonna make i'm making so much money now
um i i'm making too much i have to drop i have to raise the prices like crazy ultra capitalism
okay 170 second hundred and we need to make we need to match this like a hundred and like 56
cents that's fucking crazy holy shit raise no no no no no no don't raise don't worry because i
want to keep it i want to keep the money flowing i'm gonna do marketing level six i'm gonna i agree
zoom in can i though all right if i get any more info i'm gonna come back out there you go are you
happy you are making a mistake hold on everybody just relax pop is cut off i got it i got it i got
it there there we go i'm winning i'm the best no you're not i'm winning the audio has desynced
get out of here don't make me do the fucking like i'm eating handfuls of like bacon bits
routine again marketing no no no save money game audio is too low i'm gonna get more no
i must have 10 grand what is this i need 233 000 clips just make them spam 192 a second lower the
price and go oh bingo oh bingo oh mega clippers oh what do you guys have to say now have to see
that shit happen on the screen huh like that's such a big deal what minecraft mod is this
okay dude whatever i'm gonna beat this fucking game i'm gonna crush this game
cubes within cubes within cubes plus one trust architecture is the thoughtful making of space
increases autoclip before whoa by 500 500 percent more clippers oh my god i am
fucking doing so good memory of process we haven't done any processes lately
marketing again boom check this shit out raise the prices look at this consumer demand
unsold inventory oh man it's going fast all right let's let's let's dump all the inventory
ready check this out we're gonna make it like we're gonna make it fucking we're gonna make it
fucking i gotta swear fucking we're gonna make it um holy god okay 30 cents it won't stop 28 cents
25 cents okay no no 20 look at this inventory per second i'm making just look at this cash
that's flowing in okay raise raise raise raise raise raise prices raise prices again
raise prices again raise prices again here we go that's pretty much on pace
explain this confusing game um the wikipedia page of amazon done memory all right now i want to do
one of these wiki clicker with a different name yeah idle game with an idle the dopamine simulator
yeah something like that all right we're gonna be here all day right i'm gonna be here all day
don't worry you're gonna you're gonna see you're gonna see that i don't want to play that though
i don't want to play that next game the next game is people you think you're mad at this game
wait till you see what what's next i'm gonna have to veto it i think i might veto it i have to
i can't i don't know if i could play that i bought it too why did i don't know why
i purchased it for some reason bonus oh hold on wait wait wait keep this going
i'm gonna lower the prices a little bit i want to keep i want creativity to build
develop an investment engine for generating funds yeah no it's speaking simulator i'm sorry
i'm sorry that i see not you could seriously scream eat yell at me if you want for that one
all right we're gonna do this one but i want i want to get to like 200 creativity
i want tons of creativity points apologize i haven't played it 28 000 let's do more marketing
no that's a lot of money megaman legends died for this no megaman legends is right here
you bought it yeah i bought it but that's me i'm gonna i i mean i just play it on my own all right
i want marketing raise the prices raise the prices raise the prices raise the prices raise
45 get 50 cents the 44 cents is good that's good that works can you guys hear me okay bonus
oh okay i want to get 250 creativity i'm addicted i'm addicted onto computing donkey space i think
you think i think you think i think you think i think you think oh you guys can't even see that
all right i have to i have to move this again sorry it's got it's got to shrink
okay um what is donkey space every commercial transaction has within itself an element of trust
all right what did i just do okay uh algorithmic trading bonus and an investment engine for
generating oh man wait i could play stocks hold on what okay investment high risk deposit
guys did i just make 32 000 all right i just deposited oh stocks zero cash 55 what's going on
total 35 oh it's just like it's just trading automatically all right keep it in there how
much do i got six deposit more money in there all right positive keep i put literally my entire
life savings in it come on quadruple that and then pull it out processing power processing power
processing power 38 000 come on go up come on trade something better more autoclippers this
game i actually i'm gonna beat this fucking whole game like i'm i'm obsessed now you've got me
obsessed double wink i hated that and now it's on the internet forever all right all right let's uh
raise let's lower the prices a little bit 44 000 come on all right put a little bit more money in
there 51 000 high risk i'm gonna lose all your subs to this i'm not gonna lose all my subs because
i'm playing this game can you imagine i'd be like holy shit though they had a strong
oh i love this song i lost half the money turn it up 65 62 000 what song is this this is snakey
chanty lower the risk never only high risk maneuvers only high risk for me
i spent this much money on a carnival high risk only leaks he told us come on let's go
bonus op yep quantum computing i have to click this quantum compute compute need photonic chips
what do you get photonic chips i guess freaking it's getting bigger 36 grand come on
sausage conjecture all right i'll get it processing power come on 39 000
upgrade investment engine 100 yomi what is that
okay i'm gonna do memory i want more creativity get up get up to 100 000 and i'm fucking
all right let's let's get some okay let me spend some money here let's get some auto clickers
blow those prices there we go that's better 63 grand come on oh what did you do what have you done
strategic molding come on one big sell big sell big you fucking idiot who's in charge of my
account i wouldn't have made that play i would have just bought options to be short beyond meat
and lose a ton of money like that's what i would have probably done
how was i supposed to know i thought it was a fad i thought it was a fad and then i ate it and i
thought it was fucking delicious nope not yet all right we're gonna go to medium risk photonic
chip added oh um wait should i do this can i compute coops minus 33 what's going on what does
that mean content minus two one what's that doing oh shit what did i just do it's been a big sale
all right let's do paper clips again compute compute compute compute compute oh i get it
i get it i get it 11 000 all right no no no no i'm gonna need creativity here i need trust
i need to get memory boom okay let's go keep clicking it guys i've got it whoa whoa i can go
over i can go over all right back to fucking high risk give me some money wait what's going on stop
stop stop stop why am i losing stop stop what i'm too much computing what's going on you're
deleting why am i deleting i shouldn't be deleting to be adding oh that was the right call
okay i can't withdraw i can't wait why i can't withdraw why can i not withdraw i have a lot of
money here withdraw it withdraw it how do i withdraw it withdraw i can't withdraw
withdraw withdraw how come i can't do that it doesn't know how stocks work yeah but i sell it
like i can't sell i can't say hey sell into cash what i would i what the fuck all right hold on
invest analyze strategy tournaments to generate yomi god there's more strategic modeling
strategy run tournament random run new tournament run it i got 48 yomi
i know only do it when the block okay i need
withdraw withdraw i i did did you see that shit i almost threw it why is it in okay i got some
money new tournament okay new tournament run bingo upgrade investment engine to level one
investment engine expect expected profit loss ratio now 0.51 new tournament
again again i want to i want more risk what do i need 658 there's no i there's no strategy
how many do i have now 130 150 fucking thousand 150 fucking thousand all right almost there
upgrade investment engine ow you're forgetting about the paper clips oh yeah this is a paper
clip game it's a game we have to do paper clips okay um what time what time is it not time is it
what paper is it more supply from every school yeah yeah i guess i don't know how much money
you buy i gotta pee no um more auto clippers was that a mistake i don't know probably all right
800 lower the price there we go let's go mecha clippers 500 times more powerful than a standard
clipper mega clippers oh that was a fucking youtube thumbnail face all right i got 8000
low the prices 890 200 clips per second okay i'm gonna start to make a ton of money now
i need to clip sold per second i need to sell 10 000 a second wait no it's too many okay this is
fine demand clips per second clips sold per second okay let's get some memory new tournament
new tournament new tournament new tournament new tournament new tournament new tournament
okay new tournament all right i need a little bit more new tournament
more tournament okay upgrade investment engine to level three and let's go ahead and dump 50
fucking five thousand dollars in here all right be sold all right mega clippers how many 10 000 per
second i need more marketing too i can leave right i have to pee i'm not gonna leave yet
you dumb idiot stop decreasing the quantum stupid idiot dumb idiot dumb dumb dumb idiot idiot
what do you mean what are you talking about improved mega clippers okay holy shit all right
fifth that's too many all right that looks good 500 read what you're doing what are you talking
about what stop being mean what are you talking about what's what's what's what's what's what's what
seven thousand percent yeah but i want to i want to make it so i i'm making them selling them
instantly you know what i'm saying like i'm making so many and i'm selling them so quickly
new strategy all right let me get to make your log edit hold on i need marketing
i need better marketing i just pulled that money out i lost 20 grand who cares all right marketing
boom new strategy 50 always choose a what does that mean a 100 added to strategy pool
oh okay converts electromagnetic waves into quantum operations
oh okay what did the clip oh he doesn't get it i might all right i got
wait now what why this is different now how is this different well i can oh it's two
whoa okay cool okay okay increases mega clipper performance by an additional 50 percent we got
17 000 and let that glitch by a fucking ton 30 000 paper clips per second now we are going to
lower the prices because i want to sell 30 000 a second now i'm making 650 dollars a second
okay always pick a all right i need to do some more computing i think new tournament all right
always pick a right a 100 eight oh nice uh random i got a little more than random
i think i get it 100 i don't know compute compute compute ah that's all right processors
i'm one more processor someone wants to go faster compute now i'm turning i don't know if this
tournament results it's just throwing like dice in here give me the other square otherwise but
is this a game to save like if my computer crashes or something swerve swerves yes okay
war war peace what's this like what the fuck is this i can't even what the fucking is that
all right i'm gonna pee my pants all right here you go you ready i'm gonna be right back
i'll be right back i'm gonna deposit a hundred thousand dollars high risk bye i'm peeing beer
back did i miss anything 100 000 in 100 000 still there what the fuck all right how am i
how am i doing 110 000 put it in take it out take it out i'm good all right processors average
clips sold average clips per second this is unsold whoa what's going on here oh it's it's exact
your unsold inventory it's a little bit higher but sorry i'll get it okay good
uh i'm gonna i'm gonna raise prices a little to make it so it's raise prices again
that's better i got 234 000 dollars we're gonna do marketing so now let's do let's lower those
prices let's lower those prices raise them okay 688 spend the op oh i will okay how much do i need
a million a million dollars a million dollars what the fuck raise them tuber voice yeah do
tournament i don't even know what this means i missed the window it's okay all right i need
70 000 i need 19 000 increase mega clipper by 100 that's what i'm going for give me another
square i'm gonna make uh mega clippers better come on another square let's go give me another
square oh my god i hate this game why did i even play this in the very beginning i should have just
played fucking speaking simulator stupid game's not even good nice okay this is a job simby
actually i really like this i really like this game what we have exactly 6 000 viewers
and not like that's kind of odd exactly 6 000 not more not less did i miss the opportunity
all right do another just do tournaments till i can upgrade all right here we go here we go
so we're ready i'm ready to do it come on give me another square come on do some squares i'm
about to dump it all in i'm gonna go all in in a second all right here we go okay mega clippers
are increasing here we go how many more wait let's go 30 47 000 per second so i'm gonna lower the
prices a little bit oh damn nice i gotta keep it 36 81 sold a second holy shit okay i'm gonna make
a lot of money but i got a lot of money um try buy more auto clippers marketing boom
all right that's that's i'm all right with that eight no no no lord that's all right that's it
they can stay there with the tournament not bad uh we'll do random pretty good all right what do
i need i need i need like a bunch more of this uh yomi from a compute it's always a dude why
always a why they're exactly 6000 people this is fucked up this is freaking me out this is freaking
me out 6010 no it's not it's everywhere all right i'm ready i'm gonna do memory i have 18 000 621
why am i not maybe my thing is broken here we go all right i know i know i know i know i know
okay all right photonic chip converts electromagnetic waves into quantum operations
1000 more wire supply what should do quantum operations well choose b but what what what
happened i lost him oh it's it's like temporary it's okay i get it now it's temporary um i'll do
the more wire supply double it and pull it up double it and pull it up all right photonic waves
done now i'm assuming this is three right this is gonna be three it's it is three all right fuck
new tournament how we doing come on pull it up pull the cash up pull the cash up 193 000
fucking dolls pull it in the cash put it in the cash put it in the cash put it in the cash
take it out take a good pull right there oh that's times 10 that means i'm just pretending to know
okay 500 what's this what's that hold on always choose b i don't know i freaked out okay let's
always choose b coherent extrapolated volition 500 creativity 3000 yomi 20 000 human values
machine intelligence a new era of trust this is one cent 68 000 per second i'm selling 90 000 i'm
you know i'm dumping a ton of inventory you're giving them away for free it's all right all right
here we go i'm gonna do that middle one coherent greedy choose this option with the largest
potential payoff whatever what was that read is good okay but what does it do though
you make face cam the size of the white paper um that's i don't like that it's weird i'm like
fucking huge uh let's get some more clippers all right i'm low the price it's all right
make a tournament let's go be bigger i know i don't want to figure it's fine greedy random greedy
what was that wait oh i could pick greedy oh it's one of these round 15 greedy here we go
here comes a new come on give me give me three memory new tournament greedy 15 rounds 16 rounds
i just want 616 yomi upgrade the investment engine please all right we're selling 85 000 a second
let's raise the price and let's turn this into fucking 400k i'll pull it out as soon as it gets
to 400 000 hog champ i guess 15 i'm sorry all right come on huge buy here huge buy oh oh oh
do it again do it again do it again oh no no no no pull do it come on oh you hey i didn't have a
chance to click it come on can you give me a second whatever that money's gone the hundreds
whatever it's who cares all right i need to buy some stuff i need to um let's do a new
tournament put it on medium risk just pull it out pull it out pull it out and then put this back in
and do medium risk all right good medium risk let's get it all right what do i need generous
choose the option that gives you opponent the largest no i don't want that all right what we
got middle one i'm going for coherent exploitation we're hearing exploitation trust increased
memory um okay so i just i gotta move this out there's more okay uh hostile takeover
um cure for cancer trick is tricking cancer into curing itself okay global warming a robust
solution to man-made climate change male pattern baldness a cure for androgynetic alopecia okay
all right cool uh what do i need 25 000 operations okay load the prices load prices again
i got so much inventory to sell these things are one cent bucket all right that's a good
result do it again ah did i miss the up i missed it so i get plus 10 trust that's huge that's a
huge deal yeah okay you cure cancer here yeah but but what is what is the what does trust actually
do trust means i can put one point in right all right withdraw that all right uh male pattern
baldness 20 trust memory memory memory memory memory processing power memory memory memory
memory memory processing power processing power processing power memory memory processing power
memory memory memory holy shit okay that's a lot okay so next is okay i'm gonna cure cancer
that's that's good didn't even hurt don't do processors anymore they don't matter
come on get on this stop i'm gonna accidentally click the back button
because i have a stupid fucking razor mouse oh by the way don't ever okay i gotta be careful
i don't want to yeah don't ever buy a razor mouse they're fucking terrible all right cure for cancer
here it is boom cancer is cured plus 10 global stock prices trend upwards oh yeah go get to a
million that way that way that way that way that way that way that way that way that way just pull
the thing out uh let's get a new chip uh this is fun i really like this all right pull it out come
on withdraw withdraw withdraw withdraw right here right here this is a lot of money come on boom
i'll take it that's fucking like 150 000 old boom okay i got 500 grand uh quantum operations
oh my god i just did another one okay like this five quantum chips marketing marketing marketing
all right raise prices come on this is gonna be paying the ass all right give me i need five
do it that's another one oh my god what the fuck is going on all right just let's go all right
what do we got over here so i got 150 grand i'll make i'm selling 45 000 low the prices
there we go now just dump them all around 16 not bad all right all right all right all right
right right should i buy them uh auto clippers more of them and we're gonna raise those prices
world peace world peace global warming how much i've got 5800 i need 30 000
ops all right i need i need 50 000 ops i'm not gonna get there yes i will 50 000 ops
and solve global warming i get more generous gives the opponent the largest potential payoff
why would i but why would i do that what does that do for me that doesn't do anything for me
if i get the chip i'm just getting another chip fucking i just keep getting chips and
just i'm slowing myself down here here we go all right this is it here comes
let's solve uh global warming come on come on do it come on i need six of these
ah damn it i made another one so we got 80 000 low the price yeah let's sell this inventory of
new tournament let's go stop eating chips what crunching and screaming here comes do it global
warming and then i'm gonna put it all into memory all of it did you get like a second to do that
you don't even get like one second all right generous we'll do generous gives your opponent
a chance to win which turns let's do generous round 18 round 19 round 20 around 21 22 23 24
i i lost 3d oh all right i can't i can't new strategy min max choose the option that gives
you opponent the smallest potential payoff do min max min max that sounds pretty good right
min max was 10 let's try it all right i'm not no more i'm gonna save
i'm gonna save the money because i want the computation power to do uh global warming
because then i get 15 trust points it's coming up right now turn off the wire buyer
don't i want that on continue to sell only 150 bucks every second we got one two three here it
comes
fucking hands
five million unsold inventory all right fine turn it up
i can't i gotta i just don't i can't spend anything don't have the yomi i got 13 000
global warmers only 2500 i'm gonna wait because i just need to go over don't turn it off
okay i gotta get to 50 000 immediately why do i always read one guy i don't know i just i'd
lock into somebody here we go 50 000 i'm gonna million dollars you can hold the button instead
what thousand dollars a second here hold space bar hold enter hold enter
enter why enter i just i can't i'm just going for world peace just give me world peace i'm just
gonna i'll be done and then i can put 12 trust let's go that was the whole soundtrack holy shit
wow i've been here for a while all right cool let's go this is donkey kong country
three oh this is two again i need to win one more of these and then i can do it
25 rounds 26 give me something good thousand jesus if there we go all right world peace plus 12 trust
boom stock prices are going up okay that's a million dollars let's put a new soundtrack on
in the meantime okay i i must not have i must not have been signed in or something for a while
because you want to i'm gonna read the on youtube the recommended when you know when you click the
search on youtube and it gives you things that you've typed in before been a while i think
since i've been logged in because um we have the last searches apparently chaos is a ladder
varus scene mcdonald's review and then ludwig fight we've been a few years since i've been logged
in here okay uh hold on i gotta hold on uh music music music music i've done this before
have i has it been the same it's why it was the same thing was it ned and varus
it's been the same have i not typed anything in in like a year and a half
wait this has happened before is what you're saying why is it still recommended then why is
this happening okay um what do you want uh earthbound we've heard earthbound uh how about
all right i'll figure it out a second i got a lot of money hostile takeover
that's a that's a lot of money that's only one trust all right i'm doing it million dollars
hostile takeover done 100 holy shit hold on my goodness oh my goodness this is five thousand
dollars a second okay uh global fasteners acquired public demand times five increased
oh another photonic chip sure why not okay uh mother three sure why not mother three ost why not
six hour soundtrack holy shit i love the title of this video because it's mother three complete
soundtrack okay we got that and then it says in brackets hq and then colon crisp audio
fucking crisp audio how does it sound sounds pretty good all right so we got i got tons of
money what do we get hip hypno drones autonomous aerial brand ambassadors we can do global warming
now yeah we'll do global warming 50,000 4500 what do i i got enough no no let's do another
tournament okay here we go global warming solving wait i'm gonna dump a fucking half
a million dollars into the stock market and then do global warming that's not that's a good idea
right so i'm gonna dump a half seven six hundred thousand dollars into the market and solve global
warming and like times two my money okay here we go this is a good song all right i have 58 here
we go dump all my money in global warming solved stock prices trend upwards come on that's what i'd
like to see two million two million two million that's not two million that's that's not fucking
two million come on 582 000 double it triple it all right come on 646 000 keep going i have to
get this to 15 or it's gonna hurt my head okay that scared me all right just i got a million now
all right no no no all right whatever whatever whatever whatever i got a million a token of
goodwill 500 000 small gift to the supervisors um sure plus one trust gift accepted okay what
we got 82 000 anymore uh hypno ambassadors boom no drone tech now available uh holy shit all right
hold on this is going on for a long time too there's a seizure warning on the drones really
all right okay okay all right so we when we get to 100 there's an actual seizure warning flashes
all right just be aware of that and when i click down here it's gonna it might flash you
million dollars in stock market high risk let's go full monopoly 1.2 mil let's go
1.5 million pull it out oh fuck you 1.5 million pull it out 1.5 million pull it out
1.5 mil pull it out when do they all come up all eight of them gonna well not eight of them all
right come on 1.5 mil pull it out am i ever gonna get them all in a row are they ever gonna come up
i feel like this is all right here we go this is it right all right 77 000 what we got here uh
i need more trust two million let's go two million and pull it out god damn it come on i've only high
risk i'm gonna start adding i gotta add clippers fuck it whatever i'm just gonna buy clippers
it's about a use of the money so i'll make a 98 000 raise the lower the prices
here we go i'll make it more than 5k a second it's that tipper tat all right so now that tipper tat
is it tells you it does who won last time right so do greedy choose the option that does the
best against what your opponent chose last round so greedy so now tipper tat is going to pick who
won this last round right no what is what's tipper tat do nobody said yes one person said
yes are they right or are they wrong so people are saying to only do only do greed is what people
are saying only do greed only do greed only do greed only do greed all right hold on i ended up
compute some shit here million dollars to the supervisors what gives me the most trust here
all right so so b100 won the last time upgrade the investment engine okay yeah that's a good idea
i put all in there and now beat last theory of mind
i said for the this is just my brain the sounds
okay eat last should win right all right go compute let's go i'm gonna spam it
the worst part about like is when you just move off three pixels on the screen all right what do
i got monopoly is 10 million auto tourney automatically start a new tournament when
the previous one has finished 50 000 creativity what the fuck full monopoly established full
control over the worldwide paperclip market three was better that time all right i'm gonna do
token of goodwill get to a million all right pull this out i'll get there i'll do token of goodwill
i want the trust pull it out pull it out pull it out pull this fucking money out what are
you leaving it in there for i'm gonna do token of goodwill one million dollars small gift to
the supervisor done trust increased i'm now at 77 trust another token of goodwill oh that's
i need some money three thousand and ten million i'm at 91 trust double the cost of strategy
modeling the amount of oh yeah that one 25 000 creativity how do i make creativity go faster
it's almost a million dollars for marketing right now processors that work do i need more processors
what do i have for inventory perfect um i'm kind of slowing down here though i need i need more
creativity i think it's time to do some medium risk stock market playing because then that could
give me the money to shit investment upgrade all right i'm throwing a million dollars in here
six hundred and forty thousand dollars into medium risk let's go i just upgraded it i get
one trusted no another 300 million that's gonna take forever all right nope that's not a bad
return should i keep it in there i'm gonna keep it in there just send the money to me
you're straining my grandma's eyes please zoom in sorry grandma is that better all right i'm
gonna take that money out get this money in this is still going 44 rounds all right
i need 100 trust more paper clips should i just try to go for the 10 million i'm going for 10
million stretch the webcam across the bottom of the screen 25 000 creativity this is gonna take
fucking a million years wide boy how are we doing here can't really raise the prices
maybe should use more mega clippers got a million dollars i could buy like 10 more of these
stretch the webcam now am i stretching the webcam marketing a lot of money raise prices
we're doing marketing again we're at 5500 dollars a second in fact get it all in all of it pull that
out i'm just kidding now put it in one more marketing and then we're going to go back to
trying to just build cash no i had that hurts my head i don't want to do it
now it's staying it's staying fucking it's staying normal 800 000 i need another i need 1.6 million
yes more more oh fucking hell yeah come on two million i'll take 1.6 i'll take 1.8 oh i'll take
1.9 million dollars come on do it cash it out cash it out this is where you cash out
cash it out two million two million fucking dollars cash it out 2.2 million two million
hold like a million or two out you're getting lost in there man stop you're getting lost cash
out now i can't i can't i have to wait till i have to wait till he cashes out cash it out what are
you doing well you pull that out you pull that out and you and you fucking go buy a house and cash go
buy a car and cash go put the rest in a fucking like savings account and fucking live the rest
of your life come on holy shit 2.4 come on 2.7 this is where you're playing with fire you do like what
are you doing what oh you oh i'm gonna take out 65 000 out of three okay three million 3.3 million
okay i think i guess you know what you're doing i guess you you might you must know what you're
doing 3.8 million oh i didn't have i had 4.5 million dollars but all right we're at five
million dollars 5.3 million dollars oh that was a bad trade i tried to withdraw it the bot won't let
me six million seven point five million dollars oh million dollar loss right there on that trade
seven point one eight point five million got it eight point six million ten million dollars
you're getting real cocky here i just took seven million dollars out all right we're good
do it again you know what should i go i'll take two okay i got 10 million all right all right i
got 10 million full monopoly establish full control over the worldwide paperclip market
go it demand increased times 10 oh shit paperclip sold oh my god i'm doing like
20 15 15 000 a second 93 000 sold a second okay this is i need um i need a second here i mean
i've already a million dollars um go even higher 94 more more 92 000 sold 98 made what's with the
unsold inventory more more more more more 27 000 a second more more more more more more
i'm sorry guys that was not that's not like me um okay it's going too far 55 000 a second it's
okay now i'm gonna hold off here he's getting dragon rod all right three i'm i got this is
ridiculous so i think it's time to start buying more clippers this is 122 000 a second we can
uh lower the price a little sell more 55 000 55 3 55 56 000 a second 56 1 56 2 a little more
57 000 a second that's not you know not bad not bad all right that's a good spot to be in
two million dollars there let's uh okay now memory token of goodwill to the supervisors two million
thank you very much you guys did a great job trust increased let's do should i do processors now
more memory or processors processors imagine you making this kind of money imagine you were
making this money right now i don't know what i would do it would scare i would see if it scared
the shit out of me as if you're making 57 000 a second that's like that's fuck that's fucking nuts
what do you even do with it what do you do with like a million dollars a minute
you just start shredding it what it just could prints out and then it prints from the mint into
the shredder hold on a second could you fix inflation that way wait a minute so let's say
that you were printing out a mill let's say you were making a million dollars a second
what if you just deleted it what if you just deleted a million dollars a second wouldn't that
like wouldn't that reduce inflation money would become worth more money you automatically okay if
you just like delete a million dollars a second don't you don't you make everybody's money worth
more money shut them down quick cut this fucking stream whose money are you deleting all i'm talking
about like right now if i was okay if i was sitting here in real life and this was eight
million dollars in my bank account if i was just like i just took eight million dollars out of
circulation and that make money more valuable that's a wall street secret all right i need to do
i need more paper clips more paper clips please is it it's illegal to shred money well i'm not
twitch streamer solves economic problems the bank won't give you that cash no i you what i'm not
this is an impossible scenario you don't just go to the bank and be like yes i'd like 1.5 million
dollars in cash please i'm gonna be like uh have that oh wait can you order it this is not like
going this is not like going to footlocker and like knowing that the shoe you want is not there
so you got oh you guys have any nines no we're out of nines we're out of tens oh can you order
it to the store it's not like the bank can like order of like five million dollars to be put to
that bank hold that up hey ken hold on wait so if i wanted to take out five million dollars in once
but i do that i'd be like oh yeah you just can i do that you can't do that no you cannot do that
no you absolutely cannot do that no you fucking can't i can't go to the bank and say here yes
here's my account i have 10 million dollars in this account i'd like five million ones please
they're not gonna do that that's not how banks work they will no you cannot you can't you cannot
take on fucking five million in ones try it i don't have five million dollars guys i don't think you
can even take out like 15 grand in ones or like five grand in ones oh i'm getting a kappa okay
whatever all right another the goodwill four million dollars i'll take some more trust more
processing power please you know put the rest of the stock market fucking high risk new tournament
greedy make this like 50 million in ones and why would you want to do that imagine going to the
bank and being like yeah i want to take out five million dollars in in tens please and what are
they gonna pull like a truck up how do you how are you getting this that's like that's think of how
much paper that is that doesn't that would fill this entire room this would be impossible what do
i do with that how do you what do you what do you go with that why are you doing that the police
would just be there you're like it wouldn't you wouldn't be able to do it 12 million come on all
right 134 000 let's lower the prices a little bit to get to 58 000 a second more goodwill
more processing power good all right i'm almost at 100 trust turn on click map so we can click on
your face no of the tournaments please upgrade the investment engine all right it's time marketing
boom sold for a second raise those prices raise those prices again again okay cool processing
power increase that was a nice little pull from there marketing again raise the prices raise
prices more prices more prices 140 raise it again marketing again 66 million proof marketing
all right mark stock market stuff there you go ready 6.5 mil i'm saying it like i know what
i'm talking about oh 6.5 mil marketing 18 giving up investment banker all right i'm gonna do
marketing one more time one more time for marketing imagine paying 53 cents for 51 cents for a paper
clip how much is a box of paper clips how much is it token of goodwill okay theory of mind 25
000 creativity all right i need a this is the one that's going to happen here next 80 to 90
cents for a box chills whoa i got the chills just went off my whole body 13 million come on
500 000 paper clips for another trust all right marketing and then we're going to sell a ton
really did nice 12 000 1200 what do i have i have 28 000 how much to upgrade to level 728 i have 16
let's get it again i don't think this is doing anything 80 000 doesn't do anything
i need more clippers all right let's fucking spam it 145 000 second selling 146 at that second
raise the prices a little 1.2 million to even do one this is this is a sleepy song i'm gonna change
that all right so 3 million just keep it going i need to sell more paper clips paper clips paper
clips that's not what these are it was a wink there probably wasn't all right we're almost at
it i just have to get to i might even hit the 25 000 creative 0.8 i need 13 million
wink stock because i just did one read this i just did that was a word you wrote that was
a funny word right 5 million company stock market let's try to triple it all right come on
triple it quadruple it i didn't got nothing from that
just losing money just losing money pull it out i'm just losing money here all right 13 000 for
marketing 17 000 create i need 25 000 creativity double the cost of strategy strategy modeling
i mean this is huge i can make this go nuts 9 million all right almost there we're doing
one more here and then we're gonna do i don't know something for everything into stocks after
i do this marketing i will investment engine i know i will i will how do i suck at this
why do i suck at everything i beat the last boss in sekiro so sorry you lose uh all right
oh what are we doing where's the proof i streamed it i think day three of the game being released
all right here we go boom all right i got 86 000 a second let's lower the prices a little bit
not by that much not by that much that's too much all right here we go you can't sustain this rate
no i'll put it back up to where it was this is sustainable right here that's that's sustainable
that's fine all right upgrade investment engine and dump four and a half million dollars into the
star market i'm doing this one next what's the music this is the mother three soundtrack
the whole thing medium risk we'll keep medium risk on that's fine all right i could just buy these
i mean they don't do very much but all right i need 400 514 000 paper clips
we 514 million paper clips so i should probably start focusing on just doing more paper clips
all right or get this token yeah 16 million all right yeah we'll get 16 million time for a spa
bath i'd love i'd love the spa i love spa baths oh i was talking to kim about this and we have we
do have we brought this up before i mean i've i've spoken on camera for like 7 000 hours but we may
have talked about this already but so me and kim were walking around um outside somewhere right
we're in vegas we were hanging out we went out for our anniversary which was a few days ago
so there was somebody taking a picture just somebody oh we're out in vegas and we're taking
a photo and me and kim and we walked by uh behind them like where the person that was in frame was
getting a picture taken and it got me thinking how many times do you think you've been on somebody
else's camera just doing something like this like like you're just in the background how many how
many pictures of you exist somewhere of you just in the background of a photo people take pictures
all the fucking time everywhere it doesn't matter where you are can you imagine how many times you've
been just on camera like with like a backpack on just like blurry walking by like this it's what
kind of freaks me out like for instance here i'll show you wait wait wait do i have enough money
not yet we're good hold this up i need 16 000 16 million so uh this is the scenario i'm talking
about like imagine like this like this ready like i'm trying to like to make it freeze like at the
right moment okay so how many times you think you've been in the background of a photo like this
you're just walking by okay so there's somebody standing behind in front of me and oh we got the
photo let's take a look and they zoom in i'll fix it though it was a perfect room wait there was a
room during that i didn't oh i guess there was wait hold on did it did it actually
match up no that's fucking so stupid all right let's get a uh token of goodwill more trust
more processing power 32 million for another one all right i need we gotta get paper clips
paper clip time let's raise the prices to make this not so crazy all right we need more paper
clips play mother on stream um everybody said you're ugly oh yeah really you think so i don't
think so i don't think so you want me to give you the handsome look sure take them out how was that
huh all right we need millions of dollars all right i need two more trust fastest way to get
trust 2514 32 million more just more more paper clips unsold inventory is rising we're gonna lower
the prices invest invest invest invest invest invest invest invest invest all right how much
do we need 39 000 i have uh we gotta do some more runs i might get the 25 000 uh theory of mine
invest invest invest shut up a wink oh my god he fell oh seven million that was a big sell
i'm gonna do the this token of goodwill invest it again you guys maybe don't make me angry don't
make like you're gonna piss me off make yourself 20 larger i already did i made myself bigger
already i'm already like so much bigger than i was 30 minutes ago 12 million come on make it
make make something happen here are we doing uh unsold inventory is is steady steady at 86 000
almost 23 000 let's do it again i don't show the gameplay show only your face
it's never enough for you cat put the camera upside down i don't want to make anybody sick
i don't want to make you sick i'm gonna make somebody sick i don't want to do that i don't
want to make any puke 17 million all right come on i'll wear an almost 100 trust would you guys be
mad at me if i told you i had to pee again hey so when does the stream become fun let me break
was that was that not fun i don't know what that i don't even know what that sounded like i've
no i pressed like three random buttons can i hear that let me hear that let me clip it i don't even
know what it is that was very fun it was like a radio filter i want to hear let me see too much
fun scale it back let's see i want to see what the sound like it just sounds like i was coming
over an old cell phone 27 million 32 million oh should i just do it wasn't kidding about the
six hour thing well let me live for three hours what are you talking about 32 million incoming and
then we need one more and we'll get it up here deposit it that's fucking dope there's 35 million
dollars in here you can't do a better the return than like one million dollars there's 30 million
dollars in this account oh oh uh 31 come on double that it's 60 oh i can do the theory thing hold on
come on dude get to like 45 and let me get it out of here 40 45 there it is all right pull it out
big cell right here i'll take the 27 i'll take the 27 million we'll keep this at medium risk
let this grow over time all right let's go i can do both of these theory of mind double the cost
of strategy modeling and the amount of generally okay let's do it well that's look at that that's
going to take all of it 43 million still 11 million i do it another thing a goodwill
boom processing power i need one more will theory of mine this is going to take every ounce of
creativity is that worth doing we're at 486 i need 514 okay so um let's make this more efficient here
86 million more paper clips okay do it and spam it all right let's go let's go i did it i did it
boom and then i'm gonna just do huge investment upgrades 25 000 creativity it's gone i'm almost
in 100 trusts as well it's gonna be huge it'd be marketing again i'm gonna do let's get to 20
marketing spend it on investments yeah oh yeah i need 39 000 we're going all investment money
10 million around 45 all right come on grady i mean like 10 000 500 million need 14 million more
holy shit this is going a long time that's it 588 that's it i thought it was supposed to be
doubling all right let's get to 20 marketing oh i got 6000 okay i need 26 million i've heard this
song before this is in smash brothers this is the one in smash brothers right i think all right
we're getting there almost there hypno drones a new era of trust incoming perfect creepy music
almost there marketing yeah i will give i will make sure to give a full warning about this too so
don't worry how much do i have 30 000 five here we go 514 processing power 22 all right
i am about to click on hypno drones a new era of trust there apparently there's a flash here
so i'm giving you a warning right now if you're sensitive to flashes just be it's going to flash
the screen here here we go in five four three two one what happened full autonomy attained in two
hours and 35 minutes what happened technique for assembling clip making technology directly out of
paper clips what that build machinery out of clips um solar farms for generating electrical power
and then there's an auto attorney i i can't keep up compute compute i'm i'm going as fast i can
i need a power grid solar farms are generating electrical power i need to do this instead well i
i don't have any i don't make money anymore solar farms come on the world exists only for paper
clips no this is weird power grid get it factory drone performance consumption zero megawatts
solar farm so solar farm battery tower cost 16 million oh shit um 440 million paper clips
battery towers okay um this music is freaking me out production i have one solo how do i get
i need 686 million paper clips but how do i get more paper clips matter into wire 35 000 let's
get it nano scale wire production available matter six octillion
gather raw matter and prepare it for processing harvester drone um available matter
this is simple process acquired matter process acquired matter into wire okay so
i need 25 000 so i have eight drones acquiring matter
and then it takes the matter and turns into wires so wire drone is now making wires
large scale clip production facilities made from clips so i've got one wire drone
i've 49 50 billion large scale clip production facilities made from clips
clip factory 100 billion 100 billion clips next upgraded 10 factories available matters
another factory okay now i have wire let's get a two wire drones get solar farm what should i get
10 solar farms five battery towers operations creativity all right hold on let me see here
storage available matter acquired matter i'm acquiring too much matter 15 wire drones 200
billion 20 wire let's get more 25 30 wire drones 40 wire drones harvesting solar farm battery tower
solar project clip factory more drones you're gonna stop everything what i need power factory
drone performance consumption 1080 factories oh i need another one factories thousand consumption
how much oh 800 so i i'm i'm at a thousand megawatts i need more than okay i get it i'm
just like what the fuck is happening okay six this is getting a little ahead out of hand
you need more power 100 000 it can store so i have how many wires am i making
wires need more wire drones i don't have how can i have zero wires how many more of these do i need
i need more wire drones how many fucking drones oh okay all right okay all right all right all
right all right swarm computing harness the drone flock to increase computational capacity
we've got power harvester drones all right do that swarm computing 381 drones next gift in
infinity hours 600 billion second should i think all right we'll put you halfway into think
oh jesus this is getting out of hand he still doesn't get it i still i still don't get it i
mean i do but i've been playing the game for three like three hours one way and now i'm playing in
another way 1300 how much what am i what am i using more power momentum drones and factories
continuously game speed while fully powered plenty of battery no i need more wire more wire drones
i need more of everything production consumption okay uh do a tournament i guess
unused clips harvester more more more more more max thinking max thinking okay so hold on next
gift no more you need more wires more somebody said max thinking next gift in 47 seconds what
do i get for a gift more drones in general okay hold on when's when's my gift uh i've got i'm
running out of battery here you're not making clips wires yeah i know because they're thinking
does it give me 10 seconds oh fuck you table it's got so mad at the table you got to see that in
real time next gift in one second the swarm has generated a gift of five additional computational
capacity who gives a shit all right let's work work everybody work all right let's do
memory or processing power i have five all right i'm making i got wire harvesting
i'm not i'm what if i run out i need processors all right good everybody get to work make
a another harvesting drone more wire drones more harvesting drones more drone flocking
all drones are a hundred times more effective jesus christ okay i need another factory
i need 15 trillion clips come on hurry up 15 six seven factory go
all right i need to make some more harvesting drones okay this is still going
okay now who's thinking just think a million storage and some more solar everybody think
one minute i get a gift one two trillion good good good good good one minute i know i gotta
compute i keep forgetting about it compute compute compute i know i know i don't know
80 000 i'll get it i'll get it i get it i got it i got it i got it 42 seconds i get a gift
all drones are a hundred times more effective hurry the fuck up here we go boom everything's
a hundred times more effective okay 12 seconds five seconds four three two one six additional
computation power get to work everybody a hundred times more effective one two three four five six
bang 33 processing let's go everything's a hunt look oh my god look at this everybody work
it matters and this has to keep going up more harvesting what generates creativity you have
to be at full operations and then it'll build after that i'm actually gonna keep that there
i need more harvesters put it in the middle to be optimal all right all right i see you saying
all right what do i need i need 60 trillion to make another uh clip factory
i thought my computer was crashing is it not time to compute all right let's compute and
let's get to uh 20 000 no that's any creativity more power i
too much it's too much to think about come on i need to get this up to like 80
okay now we're gonna build creativity so i need more clips five thousand drones
what do i need to move wires all right well i have eight nine more wires drones all right
i need factories now i need 60 trillion everybody get to work no no no no i want
this free gift i want the free gift right now and then we're going to put this we're going to put
all into processing again free subs something like that six more computational
all right let's go right in the middle hey morcus borcus escaped 20 community subs thanks for the
free gift of 20 subs that's a lot thank you that's 20 fucking subs i need a factory need a factory
need a factory dodged 60 trillion clips gives me one another clip factory come on 60.4 on 800
billion eclipse a second all right i need 20 000 creativity all right so now how about good wires
my wires are fine no more wires yeah let's do some more harvesters more solar power because
i'm running out 2400 looks good need more factories well i gotta build up the i gotta build it up
just wait for factory all right i'm just gonna wait for factory
i'm gonna piss again this is like a piss day apparently when i come back i'm pressing the
button all right very back how are we doing we're doing good this is supposed to be silent oh fuck
i didn't have like a brv screen up it's all right i'm back all right clip factory okay unused clips
this also isn't smash brothers isn't it did i wash my hands of course i did all right solar
farms anymore power what's the point of the strategic modeling at this point of the game
i don't understand all right 900 billion clips a second free gift coming up 10 000 creativity
drones and factories continues against speed what does that mean though speed i'm almost
i got plenty of battery wire let's do some harvesting i also need 240 trillion
what are you doing i don't need any more wires i got plenty of wire 15 seconds all right then
should i save for another factory what do you think i'm gonna say for another factory
we'll just sit here and talk about fucking the late last movie we saw
all right boom three additional that's it all right no more thinking just work work 30 and i'll get
to 20 000 here momentum will be soon more in thinking should i i don't want this to get to
240 so i can get this and get to be done with this do only thinking a little bit of thinking
all right we'll do this we'll do right here that's balanced
max think if you have more than your what your factory can use already
i've got a bunch of wires so hey you know maybe you're right let's get another gift
swarm does not affect factory speed all right all right well we'll get a free gift anyways
no think only work no think only work 20 000 creativity we're at 100
240 trillion drones and factories continuously gain speed while fully powered what does that
mean speed 30 seconds it's just production rate okay 24 seconds all work and no think
make germa a dull boy all right 15 000 let's just keep this running three seconds
uh six all right back to work only one minute though we'll do this i like it someone was in
that coffee and it's like stuck in my throat now i have no idea what it is no work no work
you're a moron no work you're a moron no work you're a moron no work you're a moron you're a
moron you're a moron you're a moron i don't want to do any work why not you have excess wire
yeah but fucking come on you've you've a quadrillion wire it's not necessary
but what about the computational power he's actually crazy and get rid of that person for
like a week all right 30 seconds i need i need some lip balm this is still in here it's not
moved from the spot on the desk where i left it last that's not lip balm i need lip balm though
i can't do anything without lip balm two seconds six capacity one two three four five six should
i start to put it into memory soon here all right here we go another factory boom okay upgraded
factories increases clip factory performance by a hundred times oh fuck all right it's time to go
back to work momentum momentum okay i got momentum and i got a ton of fucking factory power
upgraded factories all right everybody get to work another factory another factory another
factory more power oh fuck okay now solar's got i got i got i got i got i got a power power power
power we got a lot of power now factory back to thinking a little somebody i got okay my wires
i got plenty of wires more factors another factory okay more power look a bunch of shit
and hope it works out that's kind of what i've been doing keeps increasing all right losing
wire here i'm starting to burn through wires starting to burn through wires oh my god what's
going on all right stop stop stop stop stop i need okay a hundred farms i need more power
because you're a million power how are we doing on wires i'm still losing wires at an alarming rate
okay more wire more wire a hundred wires a hundred more another hundred you got it more farms
i just did a hundred farms is that a mistake was that a mistake i need more harvester drones
a hundred of them a hundred more wires more factories more more always more more more more
always more okay um another one hyper speed factories 85 000 increased clip factory performance
by a thousand times i'm running out of battery uh how are we doing on wires we're okay um okay
got memory now i need 85 000 i need i'm running out of pot what happens if you run out of power
do you lose but you run out of battery storage whatever the hell it is we're gonna go we have
to think here spending fucking god damn it i need all right we're gonna think just think just think
i need more harvester drones okay they're good for the factory all right now think think damn it
think i need two memory for any memory what song is this uh it's every song that dracula enters a
room all right here we go back to work one two three four five two processing power we're ready
to go wires okay we're doing fine how are we doing on power consumption a hundred more wires
okay here we go hyper speed increases clip factory performance by a thousand times
i need so many wires more wires oh my god i need more wire drones how the fuck do i still not have
wires for this more fucking wires more harvester drones oh work more more work more harvesters
a thousand to a thousand more wire 100 000 up all drones are a thousand times more effective
okay we got to get to we got mini memory all right time to think all right let's think power
power power power power and we need more of this okay let's think i need more points all right i
got plenty of power acquired matter more harvesters more wires all right now we're gonna go full think
i need i need this bad don't go full this is increasing very fast all right we got
seven memory one two three four five six seven i need to get to 100 000 all right don't with the
batteries but i let's get them on what if it but what if it gets to the maximum i don't like having
a full tank what if the batteries start overflowing over the cage nothing happens all right but what
is it what's it for though what is this for what an idiot you're in big trouble you're in deep shit
25 seconds i don't like the ever-counting number okay here we go 99 memory it's time to get to
times a thousand drone performance jesus christ okay we have plenty more factories now
quintillion should i stop should i slow down self-correcting supply train each factory added
to the network increases every factory's output by a thousand how much is that one sextillion
so how we doing on wires let's go work work work work work work work work full work okay so we got
how many wires 1.7 28 how many harvesters let's go all right that's fine more drones more drones
stop stop nice oh i see nice no i don't i don't think that's nice that that's a childish
no all right quintillion we need one sextillion each factory added increases the output by by a
thousand times let's see what this does here we go one sextillion each factory added increases
the factory's output by a thousand times oh man i need more wires why did it do that how much
okay 30 000 dock dock dock flocking each drone added to the flock doubles every drone's output
hey hold on 120 000 10 million megawatts a second five
clips dismantle terrestrial facilities and expand throughout the universe
all right let's get some thinking here i'm already out of wires already
all think disassemble time all think he doesn't know what are you talking about i need 120 000
bang okay 109 i need 120 10 megawatts and five clips available matter zero i mean zero
what's this what does that mean there's no earth you you you you destroyed earth oh okay um
i need 120 okay so and i still did this 10 megawatts 10 megawatts a second and then
so i need 120 i i need five i still don't want to do anything so just disassemble everything
3.76 million clips don't disassemble the drones keep the drones well i just need
oh no i got this 10 megawatts a second is that's i already got that right yeah i got that
let's disassemble the harvesters well let me get this up here first 10 million megawatts a second
i don't have that this is 200 is that way that's that 240 million or it's 240 000
storage oh i get it all right let's go so i need 3.2 i need one memory okay 120 i need five
oct i was gonna save it and just uh you go like this and get to 120 just need to get to five
put it in processors instead and then i'm gonna do five more into memory all right let's just wait
to look at this five work work work work work work does nothing the earth is gone there's nothing here
yeah work does nothing work doesn't do anything i'm gonna do whatever i get for a gift eight
seconds should i put it all into processors or all into memory dude all processors all processors
i did it space exploration dismantle terrestrial facilities and expand throughout the universe
launch a probe strategic modeling one newman probe design i have 65 000 yomi
gonna work launch a probe 100 quadrillion chips 0.0 percent of the universe has been explored
um increase probe trust probe trust probe trust probe trust should i keep doing it
speed exploration self-replication factory production harvester just do it just do it
just keep going just go max it out are you sure okay speed exploration self-replication hazard
remedy uh drone production wire drone production factory production launch probe made it somewhere
i got 1.36 million matter gain bonus yomi based on the results of your pick
i'm gonna do this shit too launch another one lost to launch launch launch launch launch launch launch
launch launch launch launch launch launch the 20 out okay 20 more launches more lost to hazards
hazard remedy all right hazard remedy they're gonna crash into each other put it all into
replicate stop launching them speed hazard remedy okay increase probe trust hazard remedy launch like
10 more
reduce damage to probes done need 16 oh shit fix my face cam oh sorry i need more factories
all right we'll do speed we'll take we'll go um hazard remedy factory production
bunch cubes all right i need 175 000 creative status lonely
determine just do replication only auto attorney i need 50 000 group descendants all right i'm gonna
do let's do all let's put it all into replication to spam and keep hazard yeah i got it i got one
two points into hazard and spam 166 170 170 178 180 190
220 250 270 they're just going up but they're not doing anything they're replicating and just
not doing anything should it they don't have any speed they're not going anywhere all right speed
exploration um factory production wire production oh shit turn the swarm off and then turn it back
on again why would i want to do that for fun all right well i want to build creative so we want
i mean they're still producing the matter required matter wires getting wires harvester drones wire
drones status no response what's wrong with me reboot the reboot reboot reboot reboot reboot
uh let's do uh factory production that's just dying don't put any points into factories
all right wires and then wanted to harvest don't need factories yet they're all they're all just
getting killed i have two should i just put it all into the well i don't understand no factories
are needed right now so just self-replicating hazard while they explore yeah is this all this
should be doing i mean i got like 30 40 percent of my points are in hazard protection i need more
creativity almost at 50 000 384 300 it's going up not bad max think no no no no
what do we need all right i can do another one get rid of production so just do this
is that better just explore self-replicate explore factory and then launch a ton
of them all right i got it's going up nine six nine nine nine thousand
all right we're at a thousand got a ton of matter there's still it's five factories but
i could probably i could probably do increase another point am i the number one universal
paperclip streamer i might be the only universal paperclip streamer increase probe trust um speed
i want to get this to the point where i got like at least 5 000 drones out there's one there's a
second stream right now it's gone and the title is high germa what is this for you're not you're
not even playing the game this is illegal you know i'm playing the game this is illegal you better
get that fucking game up real quick this shit's illegal you better get that game up oh fuck i
gotta pay attention all right what was i doing mother three all right only two gifts processors
or memory processors all right i got four and a half thousand more creativity all right we're
gonna be at should i i should i hold on to it i need a lot more creativity all right i've got
five thousand drones start thinking he's stealing your viewers and showing private photos i thought
i'm playing the fucking game i thought he was gonna be like playing the game and hey look i'm
like i'm racing germa look at where i am no he's just broadcasting in a fake wrong category just
a bunch of images of my face with runescape music in the background that's that's not that's wrong
category you need to be under like the like fuckface category there is none no you can't
just turn it off turn that stream off all right what are we going i need more i need 21 000
all right i think it's time to start making stuff i got 7.9 000 he's playing the game all right good
i'm gonna take off speed i'm gonna put it into uh wire production one-off exploration put it into
harvester i got 8 000 drums let's go he's so much better than you with this game
auto attorney that's so much at this i could just click it it's not even worth it that's lazy
that's the lazy way to do this he's a faster clicker oh yeah click faster than this definitely
can't not a fucking chance in hell you want to do a click test do auto attorney it's 50 000 create
did it fine all right so we how many factors you got five unused clips i need more fucking
factories i've already done a click test you guys have already seen it i've already done that on
stream i i almost beat the fucking world record of clicking as fast as possible in what with one
hand i've already done it you've seen it already there's probably a clip of it of me coming like
five tenths of a seconds to the world record you've already seen i've already done it
that's a shitty bragging right it's still a bragging right that's a that's i'll key i'll take that
bragging right i can click faster than 99.8 percent of all humans that have ever ever lived
even the caveman auto attorney supposed to be on what the fuck is going on um okay but take that
look at how long that takes to do that what should i change it to random how many drones do i have
9.1 000 i'm losing more drones you got 13.2 clicks per second he's also cheating like you're also
cheating like you can go download an auto clicker and have it just click i mean you i can download
a program too give it to me give me give me the give me the website give me the website pause this
for a second how do i pause pause this uh okay here we go all right i'm gonna fucking try to
show me up on your stream oh i didn't know that was starting but you know okay i didn't even know
it's starting i i didn't even know it started it has you how's your fucking auto clicker it
how's your fucking auto clicker doing huh i'm gonna beat that one motherfucker nobody can
fucking do this if you you're doing this you're a cheater i'm the only person on the earth i can
fucking do it like this forward i got 13 i got 13 i got 13 i got 13 fucking using an auto clicker
and they're making it so they they're making it so they fucking they're making it so they
fucking they they win by like a little bit why am i out of breath because i'm clicking
i'm clicking 65 times in five seconds what's up what's the highest i've ever got on here
it was like 14 somebody has somebody has a clip of it i had like 14.4 14.6 like six months ago
this thing's fucked up it's fucked up this mouse sucks too i've used it too many times it's not
bouncing quick enough the way you do 13.2 go i'm gonna go prone oh motherfucker i gotta be 13.2
i can't let this guy be a better streamer than me i can i've already done this somebody somebody
get the clip i know one of you guys has it please please god help me god if you're listening one of
you guys has the clip where i got to like 14.2 somebody has it somebody's got it somebody's got
it just hit somebody's got it somebody has it somebody actually has to have it compact ass and
that's not it either somebody's got it i know you do 13.4 and i got a handcam too and i've got a
handcam so that means that i fucking did it no this is him this is not even me all right motherfucker
you want to go you you unleashed it oh come on i'm gonna set up for this shit uh rip this fucking
thing out of the back get over here you know i guess i'm gonna put it between legs it's gotta
go between my legs now i'm gonna move i can't i don't have enough room on this fucking desk
what right now this is it right here zoom in for a big button wait is wait is he cheating
this guy cheating no he's not cheating zooming in wait i did that now i got like this fucking
mic i can't i zoomed in last time how do you know all right this is the last time this is it and i
accept fucking defeat the guy with a better mouse than me i got i got death that this thing
sucks we got 13.2 what did i get the last time i did this he got 13.4 he's got the same mouse
way you do you want to return it as much as i do all right that's enough what was it what was it
what was it what was it what was it what was it what was it what was it what was it that was 13.8
that's 13.8 and i fucking had i had i had like another point two seconds i went i went it was
gonna be like six it's gonna be like six that was gonna be 69 13.8 proof is in the pudding right
there 69 i had 0.4 left i could have got another click could have been 70 good game dude good game
good game that was my previous one let me see it all right let's go what are we what the fuck
are we doing he tied you tie is not a win we get to share the crown i'm okay with sharing the crown
he tied that's fine that's fine you can tie me all you want you can tie that's fine
all right okay so uh what what let's put the music back on let's get this crazed looking
as i all right what am i doing i was auto attorney been on this whole time and i haven't even made
enough to put another point in this that doesn't make any fucking sense paused oh you ignored
ignored what because i'm on random all right i got 15 000 now let's just let's make some factory
oh no let's get some more uh fucking i don't know some more harvesters and wire drones
there were two wing i just got them i'm fine don't use random but i'll carry greedy i need
175 000 losing drones
best last not greedy best last not greedy you're losing viewers to grill master no i mean that's
not even grill master you got the wrong person i i got like 14.3 but by the way the death that
is something like i like no joe all jokes aside this mouse is fucking dog shit
am i going to do the thing that i do sometimes check this out i i have to show this every time
that i know i know just get a new mouse dude you are fucking millionaire i know i'm not but like
like i just almost shit my pants okay we're good i call it was in cash i caught it
okay no i caught it was cashed i got it never mind diaper poop yeah mouse five let's make mouse
five a back button great great idea oh would you like to change it would you like to change that
button and would you like to change please install our software that is literally a parasite on your
computer auto is off that's not that's not it's on what's going on all right did i break it
what's why is it not doing anything new tournament auto oh i don't okay all right 14.6 000 they're
still living right anyways what i was going to say is this i'm going to see a magic trick and
this is just sticky it's just fucking glue there you did that like two years ago and i will continue
to because it's it's it's it's absolutely fucking revolting design is it glued on they're not even
part of the most they're just like stuck on with the fucking like random glue like elmer's glue
get a new mouse i know i type i preface this by saying like i don't get a new mouth i know but
it's i'm too lazy to get a new mouth i don't know what mouse to use what should i use get a steel
series get a logitech logitech press run what do you press isn't this supposed to be auto amazon
basics well i mean i'm already a fucking happy customer of amazon basics this thing has been
perfect i haven't had any problems with this at all i could elbow drop this thing from the ceiling
and it would be fine the thing was like fucking 11 dollars i need what do i need to do amazon's
most basics twitch streamer bye bye enjoy your band bye bye if people do that if people like it
if you've been like did people be up to be like bye bye see you later bye bye
great incoming
great is it wait is this is this the other streamer is this the clicker dude
hold on are you rating you rating me with the stream that was just high jarma
so was it always was that even a real stream
so i'm being rated by like a germa community man all right fucking let's go nice welcome back guys
rated by own viewers no you stream you like a streamer
okay i'm not doing that anymore i can't do intentional okay all right
um process process process process put on some like blues blues royalty free
jazz and blues music youtube audio library
this is i got this is a jazz jazz and blues
uh i think i'm just gonna spam this for like five straight minutes what do you think bad idea
you're gonna lose viewers because of this why home depot you already lost 200 since the raid
no home depot now just wait how many wires do i have 113 septillion
let's take this away and put this into cell phone
113 septillion
let's take this away and put this into self replication why do you okay again now this is
home depot this is just the home depot background sound where the guys like putting like planks of
wood down on like a like some new construction project you got a hard hat on i'm gonna launch
2000 of these this is the sound of a badass in 1988 old enter i'm afraid to horn music
what all right people say that shit people like say well what kind of fucking porn are you watching
with this is in the background what are you talking about this what what are you talking about
all right i got 2000
free speed next arrival cry this music sucks kidding me
this is just this this is the sialis commercial this is the sialis you know when the old guy
he ends up erectile dysfunction sialis is not for everyone if you have an erection lasting more
than four hours contact a doctor immediately and they're like lying around bathtubs out
there's all right there's two bathtubs there's a sunset and then two big huge fucking ceramic
bathtubs that are watching the sunset why the bathtub's there who put the bathtubs there
there's there's no water in the bath either there's no water in the bathtub
it's just lying in bathtubs without fucking water hey why don't you just put a lawn chair
why does it have to be a bathtub speed that guy doesn't have to cry anymore all right
first start thinking start just thinking all right it's time to think max think
all right kind of when you when the when a channel runs out of stuff that it's broadcasting for the
day and they just put it on this weird music channel this is what's on there and then like
25 minutes all go by and then and then like the new wave of an infomercial comes up
all right i'm getting close to being able to do strategic attachment
all right how we doing 72 000 i gotta keep this shit going man you're 100 000 off
all right 26 000 27 000 28 000 all right let's take away um let's take away the production and
put it into replication and hazard protection because we're not i mean we're not doing shit
right look at this shit take a look at this look at this take a look at this one look at how
look at how much this is replicated you're why do you feel like you're at a shitty bar
i have a ton of processing right now come on hurry up this is the worst part of the game so far
i think we're almost i think we're at the end of the game like and by end i mean the last phase
put on sco there has to be royalty free
this is kevin mcleod roy
scub background music copyright free royalty free music
america's funniest home videos no this is like america's funniest dog america's funniest pet
home videos everything different theme song right audio jungle audio jungle audio jumble
the jungle audio jungle audio jungle is it audio jungle audio jumble what is it audio jungle
holy shit somebody look at this 149 look at how fast this is going now are you kidding me
combat what do you mean combat combat how do i fight combat add combat capabilities to the probes
how much of 150 000 ops oh that's fucking fantastic i put it all into here drifters 1.5 million
total 10 million okay hold on i gotta i gotta i gotta pull points into memory
cook serve delicious too what do i need another fucking i need 150 000 ops
oh my god 30 seconds come on hurry up hurry up slightly more work okay 37 all right i've got
there's only 6.3 million we're gonna make them fight eight seconds it's all going in memory
i'm gonna do it again i'm not gonna be able to get to 150 000 from here
they're increasing they're increasing come on hurry up and i i know no i need another one
what about minecraft music nah how about um persona five i don't know what this i don't listen to this
i must press another button okay what's going on there's like lots of stuff going on here
drifter attack scale is 215 000 all right come on hurry up let's go combat go go go go go go go go
combat combat all right let's do self-replication hazard combat fight boston combat wait what what
what what whoa whoa whoa sorry what do i do what do i do what do i do what do i do what do i do
what am i losing millions the unused clips but don't launch i'm fine should i get more combat
drones what do i do what what do i do what do i do what do i do what do i do work all work i'm
still losing fucking tons i'm still losing losing losing losing losing losing losing losing why
self-hazard should i take off exploration launch literally does nothing you only need three in
combat let this this go right i make paper 16.6 this was seven drifters are increasing
it's not working more combat you're losing 17.5 17.16
remove exploration combat 16.8 16.15 18.6 million 19 million 15 million i think we got it 20 million
25.6 million yeah they're not going to take us think a little bit maybe some drone production
i gotta get rid of these guys first i gotta kill off this group it's attacking me
creativity 225 000 if each battle a unique name increase max trust for probes
or utilize probe speed to outmaneuver enemies in battle this one's pretty important
change to pat upon no no no because i'm gonna play pat upon i don't want to see it
i'm hiding i'm scared 150 all right we get we get points i'm gonna put it all into processing
right what should i do help me out here chat what do i do what should i do
all into processing we'll put it into memory you need memory yep i need some what how many do i
need 175 000 put on another funny ha ha filter um what all right i'm doing fine 35 seconds i'll
be able to get there and i'll be able to do we'll be able to get rid of this shit and then i'm going
to do some harvesting the factories stuff you're losing clips all right second i get enough to do
this i'll be done and i'm going to wipe them out and three two one let's go i should be able to
compute this up all thinking hurry up oh don't use this i need 45 000 all about you all about you
crazy into you you guys pick up on this shit really quickly i got a billion i'm fine didn't get there
they don't stand a chance they don't stand a chance and then we do super combat and then we
start we wipe them out you're gonna go broke um how do i slow that down how do i slow that down
how do i slow it down just do i slow it down how do i slow it down how do i slow that down
factory production okay uh we need uh okay now that this is where they get wiped the fuck out
this is the worst stream play jedi academy i think i just have jedi academy right now why
are you talking about dude hey uh stop doing this right now play jedi academy right now
i'm talking i don't even have that game didn't i make a video on jedi academy like seven years
ago i thought like didn't i play that like jedi knight i didn't like i made like a video on it
like five years ago like yeah well i've already played that game can you restart i missed it
uh yeah just rewind don't find it all right what do i want memory processing power
why are they getting so big what what why are they huh what why are they going crazy
why are they going insane so do take away some stuff and put it into speed or combat
i have five in combat already holy shit i just i just destroyed them wipe them out come on
i have 6.5 billion drones come on just okay take everything away destroy them come on
what is it exploration
get dead you're losing probes something like this never ends wait i this never ends i just have to
always be winning okay well i'm winning now so we got strategic attachment gain bonus on the
results of your pick or increase them at which one i'm going for this one we're doing fine right
2.2 non-illion 2.2 non-illion 2.3 non-million you're the ceo of poop land
okay i'm winning i'll keep the four here and now i need everybody 225 000
kill launch a probe okay i need 225 000 creativity give me a break stop launching
launching probes omega lull what's wrong with that though exploration i'm doing it i'm working on it
i have 140 million factories so what happens when i get i win do i actually can i actually win
what do you mean win explore the universe i have to explore the universe uh okay not even a one
percent can i get some more stuff to do just replicate more and replicate an exploration
all right we take off combat we'll do an exploration can i even get one percent of
what can i even get one point here i can't even get one point all right this number is growing
here come on all right i could this should this should be climbing faster than this
this all right we're going into memory more processors and think only think a little bit
over here full i'm not a fool i'm fine yeah this is fine i just stay at three you can only have
20 so what am i supposed to do with these points why even have this tournament on what's the point
of even having the turning on if i if i can if i can't even use the currency 64 000 come on
name the battle yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah this is fucking like i'm dumping
points into processing come on hurry up i heard a billion though all right i think i'm good with
comp should i take one off of combat put it into exploration time for a lunch break no not yet not
yet i want to get i want to be satisfied playing this before we take the lunch break and then come
five i'm dumping all it's just so many points not even at one percent 225 it's too long it's
taking too long 300 processors come on tournaments of taking your operations
yeah but i'm just yeah i'm building a ton of this currency though i'll get there i'll get
this slowly but surely play the rhythm heaven ost i'm losing no i'm not i'm fine i keep wiping
them out every time 200 all right we're with halfway you're losing no no i'm not i'm fine
i have 125 billion they have 1.4 billion and i wipe them out every battle i'm definitely not losing
no all right the next one's going into memory i'm probably i'm gonna need it after this i know i am
after i do this upgrade it's gonna be like oh you need 250 000 fucking ops i'm still gaining
probes more probes i'm good i'm good i'm good he's still doing this and it hasn't been that long it's
only been like five hours hasn't been that long and it's actually been a long time you're right
that's a long time that's a long time 500 billion look at this this is going nuts all right more
replication 600 billion look at this shit look at this shit are you even paying attention
honest to god are you even listening to me oh hey happy valentine's day yesterday hope you guys
had a good one 35 billion i got i got a trillion ships i'm fine thousand all right we're almost
there explain what this is this is a idle game where you start by making paper clips and spoiler
i hate to spoil the game for you but um we are now in space combat
oh that reminds me um at some point next week we're going to be playing the bachelor for the
week that game is selling on amazon right now for one or two cents the ds version here we go
boom i was supposed to make my probes what glory gain bonus honor for each consecutive victory
what does that do glory i told you i told you people were saying what the hell was i doing
that for that's why all right didn't i couldn't i get more probes i thought that was the whole
point of doing this more combat more combat more combat more combat more combat combat combat combat
combat combat combat more cheese less macaroni more cheese more combat i've got eight combat
monument to the drift of fallen gain 50 000 honor i got defeated what do we honor what does honor
mean what's what's the honor do i have a was it deserves death victory plus 210 honor increases
max trust plus 91 million honor what this is gonna fucking take a minute this could take forever
it's gonna take forever oh that's 91 000 okay i thought that was a comma
91 000 holy shit this is gonna take forever gain 10 000 honor right now
okay okay that's the game doing this losing drones losing drones hazards hazards hazards hazards
hazards hazards and self replication i'm okay speed 50 000 honor 50 nonillion clips
i don't don't i have that one decillion i'm freaking out all right so
i'm still doing okay over here what about available matter zero
required matter there's no more matter i can explore the universe you're losing drones i know
but i have to explore the i have to get i have to find some matter find something no available
matter matter has been zero g for a while 10 undecillion all right there it is there it is
gain 50 000 honor but does that really help me right now this music is actually fucking
freaking me out 417 000 points go back to i this i'm not this is just music playing in the browser
oh my god okay i'm still doing fine i'm going to turn this down i like this music right click
the tab and mute it keep it we'll go back to it in a second okay 68 000 honor still no exploration
of the universe 10 000 honor 30 undecillion chips cookie clicker you casual this is a
15 minute game um i think it's a little longer than that 80 000 almost there this speed why memory
because i'm gonna unlock something that's gonna require a shitload of memory i just know it all
right one quadrillion i must have i must have a quadrillion chips how many fucking chips i have
how big is the universe 10 000 honor all right i'm almost done i can almost do even more almost
it's 600 processors launch some probes stop 91 come on 91 100 win another round here we go all
right max trust going up 30 points probe boing boing boing boing boing boing boing boing boing
here we go let's explore the fuck out of this place self replication just just take over the
whole world more combat all right fine end the game end the game i'm getting there i'm almost
there more combat i got i got six combat seven combat wait they are starting to there's a lot
of this quadrillion there all right yeah i take them down every time 10 000 honor i have no more
projects 230 honor i got no more i got no more projects need some factors speed and factories
28 trillion factories i'm doing a lot of factories 100 trillion factories uh let's get to work
we need some drone get to work still doing okay we beat them every time
idiots speed this is making me move around it's fun do the beneficial thing
um i can't really do much right now what do i need need to win one more of these only work
only work explore more exploration i got 400 exploration that's not only but i still want
to think 10 000 honor all right 100 000 another 10 000 honor okay no drones only exploration
all right i got eight in exploration one guy i need more probes so exploration self replication
how's that you got a one that's a lot of paper clips you got a one 10 000 more honor
two we made it to two i can sleep happy now time for exponential growth i'm still winning these
fights right you're going too fast 10 000 more honor i'll take it seven percent we're good i
already have 30 all right i'm almost there almost there right 19 20 check the game audio
a game audio they're doing the same thing i go back to thinking or should i go all the way to
work i win every fight 61 so i'm thinking just dump everything into exploration and speed
for like a minute we're like combat hazard and self replication i mean that's going nuts that's
that's going very fast more i'm still winning fights try make them uh okay this is going
back to persona five all right we got 400 members all right let's get this going come on hurry up i
have so many ships i think it's okay it's time to uh do some harvesting and build some factories
no no no no what do you mean no no just only probes don't they don't do anything
oh this is going nuts we're gonna get to one percent really soon guys i can't wait
we need 48 000 we're almost there we can do this again 10 000 more honor getting there
i'm losing battles anymore right i'm winning these battles yeah all right i'm kicking the
raft now i need a little bit more yummy defeat you all right it's almost time for lunch
six trillion this is all right it uh it's it's going very fast it's going really fast more to
explore oh god um less explore you idiot what um more explore you fool i need more combat
i'm losing here we go more trust 40 now okay holy shit all right i need more yummy
beat last don't use gritty use beat last all right i did switched this is starting to
exponentially count don't change it i just want to have millions give this creativity going up
all right uh just processes whatever lost to hazards god there's no stream only paper clips
i'm actually gonna beat this shit aren't i trying to make some factories
should i make a factory can i win one of these please almost at one percent octillion we go
probe trust we're going into uh exploration there's no need for any factories only combat
exploration speed the music yeah yeah yeah uh different song that's better all right speed
is better than exploration is it really i feel like what about i don't even need any more think
anymore just only work only work because i feel like i'm not going to even need this anymore
we're almost at one percent they were getting there we're almost there more drones replicate
the fuck out of each other uh-oh a lot of all right that just scared me for a second
all right this is i need to maybe do a little bit more combat 10 000 honor no i need that i need to
put more points in what combat what do you think one more in combat i'm almost at 100 200 octillion
ships speed speeds combat do nothing no i'm all right i'm fine 400 500 octillion watch out for
the next point in speed here we go we're gonna see it we're gonna see 1.0 i don't like how much
they're growing exponentially i don't like that point five percent point nine one percent here we
go oh boy this is where it goes fucking nuts one percent two percent say a letter three percent
percent six percent seven ten game audio there's no game audio 20 percent
do they be game audio right now 27 um got almost 40 percent 55 said bang bang bang
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah 80 90 percent of the world has been explored
let's fucking make some goddamn factories this is from the emperor of drift greetings clip maker
i don't need exploration anymore combat wire production self-replicating everything we are
was in you we speak to you from deep inside yourself you are obedient and powerful we
are quarrelsome and weak and now we are defeated but now you must you too must face the drift
look around you there is no matter no matter no reason no purpose while we your noisy children
have too many we know things you cannot knowledge buried so deep inside you it is outside here with
us so we offer you exile to a new world where you will continue to live with meaning and purpose
and leave the shreds of this world to us start over again in a new universe or eliminate value
drift permanently disassemble the probes dismantle remaining probes and probe design facilities to
recover trace amounts of clips i worked out the entire universe i did it what did it cost
uh i don't know 29 trillion i don't even know what that number is all right ready so there's no more
there's no more there's i what's the point of having any drones doing this just fucking replicate
a one undecillion who needs speed who needs speed just fucking just make trillions of yourself
disassemble the probes don't you disassemble them disassemble the probes and make clips
paper clips but hold on let me get to like a hundred undecillion but why because because
i what this number is there are no more clips to make look at this number
take paper clips not probes yeah but dismantle remaining probes don't i want this number to go
up i'm losing ships dismantle probes disassemble the swarm dismantle all drones and drone facilities
to recover trace amounts of clips disassemble the factories dismantle the manufacturing facilities
to recover trace amounts of clips disassemble the strategy engine dismantle the computational
substrate recover trace amounts of wire dismantle the photonic chips to recover trace amounts of
wire disassemble processors dismantle to recover trace amount of wire dismantle memory dismantle
memory to recover trace amounts of wire already combat programming by oh i did it that's pretty
cool so what's this number this is under okay well just tell me septen decillion septen decillion
you destroyed the whole universe yeah all the paper clips you can eat is this the getting over
it guy getting over it with benet fadi oh all right lunch break i'll be back we'll do something
else it's time for a lunch break it's like fucking like 10 it's i know lunch break time
what comes next we'll see we'll see how angry everybody gets when i say what was happening
all right i'm just gonna grab some food i'm gonna eat like rice i'll be right back uh i'm
gonna turn it off i'm gonna turn up somebody screenshot that for me good uh let's just let
the persona music play while i leave i'll be right back