Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here, and I'm here to introduce that I am the wizard, the pinball wizard. What are you gonna do now, wizard?
Welcome to Pinball Arcade, guys. It's free. Let's just season one tables. Let's go.
Oh, Attack from Mars. Big Shot. Black Hole. Black Knight. Look, there's a million of these.
I remember this one. I remember playing this in the arcade, the Elvira one.
Well, you like had to hit her in the boobs or something. Let's go.
I don't know. I don't want to buy any...
It was a smash. One would say it was a monster bash. It was a smash.
It was a... Can I...
Welcome to Star Trek, the next generation. Play. Captain Picard and John Luke.
Motherfucking...
Welcome to the fun house.
Is everything... I have to pay for everything. It's supposed to be free.
Okay, so there are plenty of tables in this game. There's a lot of them. You have to buy them all, I guess, to like play them all.
This is what you get for free. You get Tales of the Arabian Nights. This is the only thing you get to play in this game, if you just download it for free.
Okay, let's go. Whatever. I'll deal with that.
Shoot, the lamp. There it is, there it is. Go up, come on. Don't let it go down the middle. Got to do the old technique.
Shit. The old technique is... Let me just show you. I want to get a chance.
The old technique is you hold the ball inside like the thing here. You'll see.
And it lets you take your time and figure out what you want your next shot to be. See? Ready?
What the fuck? Why can I not do this? I will get it. I'm going to get it. Just hold tight.
I'm going to get the super technique. Maybe I'll try it like this. No, that didn't work either. Am I out of balls? No.
I'm not out of balls. I got infinite balls.
No, please! I'm looking really embarrassingly bad right now, but that's... I'm trying to... Here we go, here we go, here we go.
Secret technique. There it is. See, now I get like as much time as I want to figure out what I want to do.
So I want to hit the big jello fat guy in the back. Here we go. Missed, but it's okay. I got the secret technique again.
Jello fat guy. Blueberry jello. See? Hit him right in his butt. Hit him right in his butt cheek.
So another technique you can use in pinball games. This is an old secret tried and true technique.
Back in the arcades we used to do something called the burger boy technique. And what the burger boy technique is, is this.
You just mash intermittently on the keys and just hope to fucking God something good happens.
And half the time it usually works. See? I almost just lost right there. But no, I got like a super secret goal.
Hole four complete. I don't even know what I did. Look at this. I got this. I'm doing like sick right now because of the burger boy technique.
I wonder how long this is going to last. I'm not going to make a cut. I'm not going to make an edit until I lose.
I've like lasted longer than any other round. Oh my God. I keep hitting the genie. Shit!
Alright, this is going to be take two of the burger boy technique. I'm just, like I said, I'm not going to do an edit, not going to cut.
We're just going to do the mash the keys burger boy technique until we...
Okay, this is take three of the burger boy technique. Well, let's just go.
Take three of burger boy technique. Not going to make any edits, not any cuts. We're just going to hope to God this works.
There we go. That's like the fourth time I hit the genie and I got fucked.
That wasn't even my fault. It went behind like it sometimes does because these games are a ripoff.
25 goddamn cents? You want me to pay 25 goddamn cents to play a goddamn pinball game?
Well, I made that wrong. It's actually the line from The Hobbit is yellowed his teeth and addled his brain and I messed it up.
I'm sorry. I'm real sorry. They've yellowed his brain. They've addled his teeth and yellowed his brain.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Hit the lamp. Come on. Give me this.
Let me like get the high score in this one stupid free to play level I can play with.
Oh, you want all the tables? You got to spend like 150 fucking dollars.
He wields the foe hammer, the beta, brightest daylight, but the dawn take you all.
I'm just doing like Lord of the Rings stuff right now.
I'm not even paying attention to the game. Can this please stop?
Jerma, please stop it. Okay, fine.
I'm going to try really hard this time to rack up a good score right here.
No more talking. No more like Hobbit references.
Hey, can you guess what movie I just like recently watched as to why I'm like saying all the quotes over and over again?
I wonder if it was The Hobbit.
Hey, well, the new The Hobbit movie is coming out in like a week or two, right?
So I mean, come on. Can you really blame me?
I can't wait. I can't wait for the Desolation of Smaug.
It's going to be cool. How have I not lost yet?
Ooh, ball two is locked. Oh, no.
How many points am I racking up right now?
How am I supposed to banish the genie? I don't know how to do that.
Is there something secret?
Did I just get two and a half million points right there?
I think I did. I'll take that. Oh, I'll take that.
I'll take 1.7 million points.
Oh, back ends.
I've never been so happy to see a Hobbit in all my life.
That was like Sean Connery. Whoops. Wrong movie.