That title could be better, couldn't it? That's as literal as you can get.
And that's not even Red Dead 2. That's Red Dead Multiplayer. What if people don't know I'm playing
the new one? How about, uh, Rootin' Tootin' Cowboy 2. Let's see, uh, Red Dead. There's no redemption
in there. That's the first one. That's the one that was for PlayStation 2. Red Dead...
I don't know, how do you... Multiplayer. Rootin' Tootin' 2 Multiplayer. Cowboys using the
internet. No, but that's not even in the game though. How about this? All right, give me a sec.
One sec. There. I made it an IGN article. Is that better? The lawless land of Red Dead
Redemption 2 Online. And then in brackets it's going to say, watch out for gnomes.
This stream is known to gnome. But anyway, hi guys. I didn't even... I gotta make a fucking
tweet. I gotta see... I gotta make a tweet first. Is this sponsored? I don't think you could even
get a Rockstar game sponsorship. I don't think that exists. I'm not sure it's a good thing.
They're gnome... they're gnome to gnome. Why am I... I'm saying this right now. I don't even
like that thing. All right, let's, uh, let's move this over here so we can actually see the
game. I'd say that's a good idea, isn't it? I have to sign my life away though. That's the
thing. This doesn't have, like, online policies. Just want to make sure everyone's aware on this
channel. Well, I just want to make people trickle in so I can talk about it. Give me
one second. What if I don't? What's all that... there's like fucking people smoking motorcycles
by. Just like... I can hear... I can still hear that guy. All right, so for those of you that
are fairly new to the channel or those of you that, you know, whatever, I want to make sure
that what I'm doing... because I come from a law background. Before Twitch,
uh, I was a... I was in a law firm. My parents owned... there was... they were a dual...
uh, they were husband and wife law team and I was the son and they were gonna bring me up as
like the law prince. So I need to read this shit and I'm gonna read it the whole time.
So I need to know what I'm getting myself into. So what we do is...
My mom and dad aren't gonna like me anymore! Hey, welcome to Red Dead 2 Online. I'm excited.
You just woke my dad up. Hey dad! It's me, the law prince!
All right, so how does this work? Am I gonna have fun? Should I turn off voice chat already?
Is there a story here? I'm so excited. I can't wait for the first person that right when I
fucking spawn puts me into a hogtie. I can't wait. I gotta make my character
choose a character. Okay, we're gonna go with this guy.
How much different is there, uh, is there a character creator? What's that, 6-1?
All right, we gotta get a good name. Good name. Hmm, I don't know what he looks like quite yet, so...
No, it can't be just a beer. It's gotta be something better than that.
No, I'm not even gonna look at chat. I'm not even looking at chat right now. I'm gonna come
up with my own name. No, no, what the fuck? No, not Prawn. Why? Prawny. Prawny Phil. Prawny PM.
Prawny Phil. Prawny Philadelphia. Prawny philosophy. Prawny Philip. Prawny Philip. Prawny
Philip is better. Why though? Because just wait till I make his hands.
No, no, Prawny Philip G. That's his name. Prawny Philip. Prawny Philip.
Prawny. That's an old west name. Prawny Phil. Oh fuck, I know why I named him that. I don't
know. I was thinking of Bill Murray last night. That's Punxsutawney Phil from Groundhog Day. Oh
well. Punxsutawney Prawny Phil. Okay, let's see. Oh, dude, I took a picture of my face
every day for five years. That looks good. Dude, I took a picture of my body every day
for three days. This is what happened. This is what my body did. Should it be like
18? This guy's 18. That's a lie. Does it actually change your face? No, this doesn't change
anything. 60. No, he's gonna be 18. Dude, I took a picture of my birth certificate of my
birthday cards every year since I was 18. He had a heart attack, fortunately. Prawny Build.
Prawny Skinny. Athletic. He's gonna, I mean, I have to make a Prawny guy. I can't just
not make a guy Prawny, right? Carefree. Broad. Narrow. The closer they are to the bridge of my
nose, the better. That's just the way it is. That looks pretty good. How do I change his
name? Wait, can I go even further than this? Customize, though. Oh, damn, you can. High
brow. Deep brows. Eye color. Green. Eye redness. We get red eyes. All right, this is the
seventh, this is the eighth dwarf. Looks smoky. This is a gnome. No, it's not a gnome. I said
dwarf. Like the seven dwarfs. It's not the seven, it's not the seven gnomes, guys.
That looks good. All right, I position up. Yeah, actually down. Down and in. All right, looks
good. Nose. Neutral. How do I customize? It's gotta be low and wide and it's gonna be long.
Long and long into the, let's see, long into the left, baby. Ha ha, it's a funny character.
I haven't even made him yet. I haven't even made the guy. What? You can't say that yet. I
haven't even made him. Just wait till I get to his hands. Smoocher. What the fuck does that mean?
Mouth position. Up is fine. I'm not gonna, I don't think I'm gonna have this beard.
Thin and narrow on the upper lip and then like a, like a big,
like he's got like, he's got like fucking chew in his mouth. Yeah, that looks good.
Keep the beard. Well, the beard is still there.
Ha ha, it's just Jerva Pluto. No, from the side. Look at him from the side. He looks like that
henchman from the Looney Tunes. Tilt high and wide. Go deep. Deep chin depth. Okay, all right.
So, is it a whistle? He's like a bird. Clarity? So what if it's not clear?
No, it's really breathy. It's going through his teeth. Teeth ready.
I like the really high pitched one. That means anybody can hear me from a mile away.
Nice style. Ow. Ugh. Jesus. These are not whistles. This is, I just turned on the TV
at grandma's house. All right, that one's fine. All right, attributes. Health. Oh,
is where we're gonna be. Careful. Two points left. I can't, can I not pull points away?
I'm gonna probably say health. Health is probably the most important thing. Health and stamina.
Forget about Deadeye. You can use Deadeye online. Well, how does that work on the internet?
You turn off everybody's game for five seconds? Am I, are you able to actually do that to
other players? It's gonna make them really burly. Health is most important. I want to be
able to run around and like punch people and stuff. I like all funny. Okay, attributes. How
do I change his fronty philip? Turn based. Appearance. Scroll down. Oh, okay. This is
the only complaint I ever had about Red Dead Redemption 2 is you have all this room below
this. Like I know the number is there, but I wish they would just extend that menu down
like three slots. All right, so we got mouth and lips. Did that. Ears. Cheeks. Here we go.
Goofy. Large. You can click on them. I don't have my, I got a controller in my hand.
Neutral. No, we're not doing the comedy ears. I could make another Snow White reference here
though. These are all the dwarves. Small. Droopy. Goofy. Hold on a minute. Goofy.
Neutral. Large. Small. Droopy. Yeah, and there's only like four, like five gnomes.
Never mind. Keep that one. Cheeks. Let's take off. I need to take this off. Wide.
Uh, gaunt. Looks good. Teeth. Chompers. Plum. Warout. I need to take off the
hair for a second here. I mean, this one is pretty good. I'm not going to do this one.
This one's too easy to just be the fucking weirdo online.
No, I can't, I like this one. This one is just weird enough.
And the guy's 18. Blonde hair. Yeah, that's fine. Facial hair. Okay. 18 with a full,
like gray beard. Like dirty. That's fine. No, I don't like that. No, actually that's okay.
Lifestyle. What is it? What's, what's going on? Complexion. Get rid of the facial hair.
What is, what are they talking about? Oh. Oh, I see. Okay. He's 18. I mean, he could be,
right? Like, couldn't he be 18? This is just Chris Griffin. I accidentally made Chris Griffin.
Chris Griffin does look like this. Chris Griffin is 18. Or like 14 or something, right?
No, I'm not going to name him Chris Griffin. Why the fuck would I do that?
It's not going to be Chris Griffin. No. No. Do it. Do it.
Looks like Owen Wilson. Chris Griffin. No, I'm going to keep the facial hair off,
but his name is Prani Phil. Okay. I'm going to keep the fucking stupid hair.
I'm going to keep his fucked up face, but I'm not changing his name to Chris
Griffin. Okay. Attributes. We already did it. Appearance. That's Prani Phil. Get his beard
back. I kind of like it like this. No, that's it. What? What's with the background there?
No, guys, this is not all these. This is, this is Prani Phil.
Dumb and dumber. It really does look like, what's not Lloyd? Harry. No, it is,
it's Harry, right? It's just Harry from Dumb and Dumber.
I can't wait to get a shotgun shot directly into the back of my head when I spawn at the
at the newbie level one. Welcome to Goldshire.
So I'm in jail. They're going to come across me.
Hey, uh, hey, Lloyd. You with the hammer and you, you'll do. We need to perform a work
detail out in roads. Come on, get in. Open the gate. You guys think I'm out of place
and you don't think that guy is, you don't think saber tooth from X-Men is out of place,
but fucking Harry from Dumb and Dumber apparently is. Red Dead Online. Yeah,
I can't, I can't have a voice like this. I tell you what, I can't talk like that.
I'm going to keep this one and I'm going to be a Barney from.
And it's still Harry. Barney Rubble is Harry.
Education. So how does this all start? How does this start? How does this all start? I don't know.
Good day, gentlemen. Oh, don't do anything stupid. Nobody gets shot. Act like fools
and the pair of you will be dead within a minute. Now, what are your names? Jenkins
and Millican. Well, Mr. Jenkins and Mr. Millican throw your guns to the ground and
get on down here. They break me up. There's Arthur. Very glad to meet you. It's not worth
being rash. I found Arthur. What's going on? You get that salary whether these people escape
or not. Your wives presumably want you alive. Let them out now. Please. Okay. Okay. You all
run away. Aside from you. Try to stay out of trouble. This is a stroke of good fortune
for all of you. Use it. Okay. Now, Mr. Jenkins and Mr. Millican, be so kind as to
you in the back. You're the ugliest person in the whole carriage. You're coming with us.
Go on. Don't look back. Mr. Wynn, I believe it was $50 we agreed on. It was? Here's 50 each.
Each? Yes. Now get out of here, both of you. My employer and I appreciate your professionalism.
All we did was stand there and look tough. And you did it fantastically well.
I'm gonna be some storied criminal. How about you pick up these guns and we move out.
My mistress is waiting for us. Follow the string. You better get on this horse.
Now. Well, this is different. You can do anything in Red Dead Online too, right?
I haven't got far to ride. I can ride a horse? Ready?
Holy shit. I hope you'll. How does the controls work?
My employer. Okay. My name is Mr. Horley, by the way. Six months.
Well, hold X while riding to match the speed. This is fucking crazy.
If I tilt the stick left or right, I turn left or right.
How's that even possible? Like I'm not doing that in real life.
I'm going to strangle you. Hey, whoa. Easy, man.
I hope you mean in Red Dead Redemption 2 Online.
That's Horley. Okay, Horley. I'm ready to start my adventure on
Red Dead. There's a post right here. All right, let's do it. Let's do it.
See how good they're getting 3D in these things here.
Hello. Jessica, the clerk. How do you do? What did you tell him?
Nothing, as we discussed. Thank you, Horley. I do hope we have an
inconvenience to you dreadfully, but seeing as you would do to be hanged in a week,
I'm sure you don't object too strongly. That's very interesting to us.
I know you're innocent. Well, not perhaps exactly innocent, but not guilty of what
you were accused. I know you and those who were with you that died were little more than
patsies and that you were set up by one of three men or a woman, possibly by all of them.
Every time he makes a reaction, I feel like this is going to come out of his mouth.
And one of these people also made Mrs. LeClerc a widow.
And I will avenge my husband's death, so help me, God. But I will not avenge it upon them who did
not cause it or caused it unwillingly. Anyway, I'm sure this is all a touch confusing and
melodramatic. Where are my manners? Horley, please show our guests to their tent and
give them some fresh clothes to put on. Very good, madam.
Then serve us both a little refreshment. Certainly, madam.
This way. You'll find a change of clothes in there.
Hey, look, it's a camp just like in the regular main game.
Also a few other items you might need. A lasso, a knife, and a lantern, I believe.
Wardrobe, here we go. This is where we stand out from the rest of the crowd
in GTA Online because we purchased, we got the $70 hat pack, so we get to wear this instead.
All right, well, I just turned him into Ebeneezer Scrooge, so that's fine too.
Now vest, and no, he's gonna have a shirt on. He's turning, what does he, what does he look
like? He's turning into something. Oh man, this character from a movie.
I don't know who he's turning into. It's like a Muppet or something, I forget.
Who's the Muppet that looks like this? I think, well, no, that's,
just everyday shirt is fine. Yeah, that's good. All right, suspenders. Yeah, that looks good.
I don't like that color though, there we go. Dante from Devil May Cry. I don't,
I already told you, just wait till I get to his hands. Nevermind. All right, so we got gloves,
item up, weapon equipment. I don't have any equipment. I can't modify, I have a collar.
Open, full sleeves, boots. Yeah, I like that. Okay, pants. Level up to rank 24 to unlock
this item. What? Don't I already have it? Well, whatever. No, not bare feet, he'll step on a
fucking log and die. Guys, this is, this is like, this is like 19, like 24 or something.
I don't want to step on a log and die. So George Washington died. He got a splinter
and they fucking bled him to death. All right, exit the wardrobe when you're ready.
I'm ready. Exiting the wardrobe will finalize your starting clothes. Are you sure you want
to leave? Yes. Why am I so small? Oh, nevermind, she was up on the thing. Okay. I know what
that's like to have a photo that's manipulated. Standing on a hill in San Francisco, which should
be 2142 in italics. And I was at the bottom of the hill. And it was literally in out in some
restaurant San Francisco with a fucking sidewalks are like 75 degrees. And I'm all the way to the
end. I know what that's like. different bullets to those you possessed when you were arrested.
These fucking photo manipulation mistake. You were rounded up and sentenced to death
all because you came to town and didn't talk too much and seemed like you were nasty. Anyway,
cool story. The people who run Blackwater, Mr. Jeremiah Shaw, banker, real estate speculator,
and crook, Mr. Amos Lansing, ranch owner, these are the players and crook. Mrs. Grace,
when you get to the top of when you get to rank 10 in GTA online,
lover of the arts, you become this cutscene for all the new players
and have a bounty on your head. Why didn't they do that? A disgraced brother,
outlaw, wanted man and still in contact with them. All I ask of you is your help in finding
out quite what happened. This is the clerk would like to help you get back on your feet.
I do consulting work. Whatever your work may be. I don't judge. You want to rob?
Looks like that looks good. You want to save innocent folk? Do that as well. But you need me
just as much as I need you. I think we all understand each other. I hope we do. I kind
of missed the silent protagonist. Good. I look forward to rewarding you for killing.
Nobody ever seems to mention it. It's just accepted that you never speak.
You just listen in this country in the West. He was killed for greed. Foul greed when there's
quite enough for everybody. I don't care what your scruples are as to killing.
I will take the full burden. It feels really weird.
You know, on a second thought, no, I don't miss it. I don't, I don't really miss it.
Crips well enough. He's long past his prime, of course. I do miss it in some games, though.
Entirely crazy just yet. And he will help you better than most of his ilk. Crips.
Get up. Hello, partner. Horley. This is your new boss. Oh, pleased to meet you, partner.
JB Crips at your service. Was that a sign of respect back then? Camp established. Mrs.
Leclerc is a generous. That's a complete reverse now. Where are we headed?
All right. Where are we headed? I get to pick my select location for your camp.
Crips will set this up for you. A fee can be paid to move your camp again when you enter free
room. Okay. Camp. View and change camp settings. Set camp location. Okay. So I just
small camp. Daily fee is charged for camp maintenance. A small camp can hold between one
to four posse members. I can't do the larger. Well, large is $2. We're going to go to the Bayou.
I think that's the only thing we can do. Yeah. Here comes level one. This is where we're going
to go. Oh, sir. While Crips is establishing your camp, perhaps you can go to the station
and see the clerk, then head to see Clay Davies. He's a horse thief and not a terribly nice
one. Then meet Crips back at your camp. See you shortly, boss. Okay. Good luck. Pressing up
can be used to whistle for your horse. Yes. Just like in the other game. My horse is...
If you don't have any horses, this is your horse. Somebody just get five community subs.
Lightning Rider, thank you for the five community subs. Very generous of you.
Thank you so much. I got resubbed. Oh, there you go. You can thank Lightning Rider for that one.
Is this online? Oh, yeah. This is kind of like in GTA Online, where there was that initial...
You do the first couple of little missions and it teaches you how to play again,
sort of, and then the world opens up. So this is the... I got just a kind of shitty
horse. Got to go to the post office and find a new horse. I forgot how to play. So last night
we played this for like a couple hours just so I could familiarize myself with Red Dead again
because I hadn't played it in a couple weeks. I didn't need to do that. The game just teaches
you how to play again in the first like 40 minutes of this. So am I in my own instance
right now? Or are there other players? Like is it possible that I'm going to see a guy with
like a bear head on just like walking down the road throwing fucking grenades at people
and stuff? You're on your own. Okay. Well, that's interesting. So it is just like the first
time they tried this in GTA Online. Red Dead 2. Find a train as soon as possible.
No, let me get out of this tutorial. I don't want to... I'm not going to go train myself.
Free roam mission givers can be found across the map. The closest mission giver
will be shown on the radar when you enter free roam. So that is a free roam mission.
Okay. There's a rocket powered stage coach. Well, that sounds fucking fun.
Everyone you see is a person. So this person is just doing a fantastic RP job.
You might want to earn a little money. Well, some gentlemen have been robbing our stages and
they are not part of the club. If you catch my meaning, if you can make them go away,
I'm sure they will have something of interest to you. They're up at blue water marsh.
I need to see what you can do. Okay. Here, by the way, a catalog, the latest issue just
came into this armpit from a land more civilized. And if all works out, well,
my colleagues and I move around these stations as needed. And all of us are very discouraged.
We will all help a fellow sufferer with pertinent information. Good afternoon, sir.
Muppet with scally cap. God, I need to know this. It's the same person.
I think I, I'm pretty certain it was just a one-off Muppet from one of the random movies.
No, it's not beaker. It's like, it was like a one-off Muppet. All right. So let's go to the
volume. I'll find it. I think this Muppet was only in like three scenes in the whole
movie. And that's the only time he was ever used. And I think he did talk like this too.
I think it just was that we made, I don't know. I'm subconsciously making characters
that are in my brain. Great Muppet caper. Oh, yeah. I think the person got it.
Did you get it? I think it was. Is it the taxi driver? Yes.
You got him. You got him. All right. We have to watch this right now.
Yes, you got it. Wow. You found him. It's the taxi driver from the Great Muppet caper.
Hold on.
Where is it? Where is it? Nice eyes. Sturdy legs. And it might have been my imagination,
but I think she found me. Here he comes. Here he comes. Taxi. Where is he?
Runs in the family. Taxi. Taxi. I don't know why the cabs won't stop. Just leave it to me.
He's gonna, there he comes. Gonzo's gonna get him. Taxi. There he is. That's very effective.
That's it. That's it. It's the only time he was ever used.
How and why do, I don't know. I just, I remembered, but the best part about it is
who said that? That person deserves an accolade right now.
Oh, I did. Oh no. I forgot. I can't say that. Oh, that's so funny. That was,
guys, I'm gonna be completely honest with you. That was going to drive me
fucking crazy. I was going to sit here for probably, even after the stream is over,
in bed, lying down, at dinner. It would not have left me. Nobody help him next time. What,
you want me to like suffer? Streamer lies down at dinner. Moses, his name was the meme goblin.
So that was his name? All right. Search for the hideout. All right. Search, where is it?
Gang hideouts may appear across free roam. Enemies at these hideouts can be looted for cash
and other items. Okay. Something about this music is, something about this music is weirding
me out. Let's try to be a little bit stealthy about this. He dropped his gun to pull a different
one out. He was holding a toy. Oh, a guy's here. I'm going to pick up a real gun.
I'm doing pretty good. A whole squad. These guys are all in a party together.
Look at that. I, what do I get for doing that? 1800s Stormtroopers.
Oh, got another RP here. Our role player.
All right. The world will be influenced by your honor. Spare the banner in order to increase
your honor or kill them to lower it. I don't have my mic plugged in. So I am just like
the silent protagonist. No, I'm going to spare him. The Muppet taxi driver is a good guy.
Okay. Yes, I did try to punch him in the face. So you've just received a treasure map.
Hold, uh, to open your satchel and select the treasure map.
You're gonna go, are we going on a treasure hunt? Okay. Now install your rifle. I got
my rifle. I'm fine. Search this area here. Okay. For the treasure. I'm going to assume
this is how you make money in this game. That would make some sense, right? I'm online
now, man. So money is valuable. Items are valuable. Where did this guy go? Down here?
That was a real person. All right. Sure. Sierra for the treasure. Let's get back on the
horse. I have to go up here. Oh, by the way, it's been nearly 50 minutes so far streaming
and I have not fallen off the horse once. So that's a new record. It actually might be.
Anybody know if that's like actually a new record of not smashing into a tree or a rock
after 30, 40, 50 straight minutes? Emote. Emote wheel. Oh my God. Search the area. So
when does this actually come out? It's currently in beta, right? When does this actually release?
For real? Not like, oh, open the beta up. Is this closing in a couple of days? And then
coming back a month later or something? It's always going to be a beta. Wait,
I want to emote on this guy. I'm going to emote all up in this guy's face. I can't go. Oops.
I didn't fall off the horse. That doesn't count. So that's a west range. No, come on, man.
That is a really weird way to do that. So it's, you have to lock onto somebody.
R2, L, L, R1, R1 again for the wheel. Wave. No, he's not listening. R1, R2, square,
R1, then press R2. Kind of running out of buttons on the controller it seems.
Yeah, it's L2, R1, and then R1 if you want to change something. So it's L2, L2, R1, triangle.
Let's find that treasure. It's an eagle eye. Let's get off the horse. Well, I don't even,
why would I need to use eagle eye? Here it is. There's going to be money in here, right?
There's a brick. Ability card voucher. What? Gold bars can be used to purchase or unlock certain
items early. Once you own a hundred gold nuggets, these will automatically turn to a gold bar.
Shop items become unlocked as your rank increases. You can see your rank unlocks and
cash can be used to purchase a range of products and services.
So there's a current, there's a, there's an in-game currency and then a currency.
So there's money and then like MOBA gems. You've discovered an ability card.
Coupons can be redeemed to acquire your first ability card. They can be purchased and equipped
to offer certain boosts in combat situations. The triangle is the ability loadout. Select to
equip an active ability card in this slot. Okay, so this is, this is my dead eye,
these are my dead eye abilities. While dead eye is active, you slowly regenerate health.
Okay. While dead eye is active, you and your team members deal a little bit more damage. If more
than one member of your team has an, has this ability active, the effects do not stack.
You can paint targets onto enemies. I mean that's, that's pretty good. Yeah, taking
this one. Paint it black. You can upgrade it. It has its own experience. That's odd. Okay,
that's just normal dead eye. I mean I, I like the normal dead eye.
You now have a dead eye card. When aiming, press R3 to enter dead eye and use the card's
effects. Some cards require a weapon to be equipped. Yeah, now that would make sense.
Almost fell, but it didn't. Opens treasure chest. Cool. Four dollars.
Story mission. So what's considered a lot of money in Red Dead Online? 100 bucks, 50 bucks,
50 dollars? No, no, no. Forget about the guy that already broke into the game's data files
and gave himself like 50 trillion dollars. I'm talking about like for real,
for real video game, in-game currency-wise. Is it the cost of the game? 59.99? Now that would
be fun. If it was 60 bucks and that was like expensive. Some of the horses go for 60
gold bars, which is that's 600 or six. What's the nugget to bar conversion? Is it 101 or
a thousand to one? Is it 101? Don't. We're good. Four dollars is probably a steak dinner.
Clay Davies is far away, ain't he? Jesus, Jerma, if you don't know the nugget to bar
conversion, you will never make it to the finals. I'll make it to the finals just based
on my pure skill shot. I don't need to, look, I don't need to understand. I just need to do,
right? I don't, okay, if you want to take the the basketball or baseball sports thing,
right? I don't even need to know how the game works. The goal is put that ball into
the basket and just don't cross this line when you do it. Okay, if I can get a swish every
single fucking time, no matter what happens, that's all I need to know. And I could get
that 50 million dollar contract just based on getting the ball in the hoop, even if I don't
know how to play the game. Start matchmaking for other players. I guess, I guess we're going
to find players. Is this the same streamer that made kids toys while eating pizza? Yep.
Game start. Players one out of one. Harley suggested that you go to see Clay Davies,
a horse thief, to learn the ins and outs of the horse rustling trade. All right,
I guess I'm just gonna ready up. Weapon loadout. All right. Honor among horse thieves.
Clive and Clay. Somebody already wanted to skip it. What? Skip the cutscene?
I want to see. I want to know what happens. Somebody in the party is just like, I don't
give a shit about any of this. I just want to drop dynamite in the middle of the team
right when we start the mission.
Oh, one out of four. Red dead players have ADHD. Sorry. It's probably three out of four.
Because guess what? I have it. And if you think that that guy has it, that's at least two out
of four. At least. All right, so go to the mill. Take it back to the horse thieves at
Rhodes and bring it to him at St. Dennis. So this is the squad, huh? This already feels
like a ju- wait, what? I can- is this gonna hurt him? Can I- I can jump on his horse. Okay.
That's interesting. All right, that was actually kind of cool. I want to know how fast you
can go and do that. All right, speed up. Get us up there so I can- I want to get
to the first place. I want to live vicariously through the person in first place by jumping
on their horse. How do I emote? All right, we need to steal a horse. Am I slowing the
horse down? I probably am. All right, so we get to steal the horse. Uh, this guy- this
guy is just kind of running in. How did that- what? How did that horse- no- oh god,
you just already did that, really? Oh my god. No, I want to shoot this guy. Give him cover.
It's exactly what I thought it was gonna be. This is the first mission, too. All right,
we gotta get a horse. Did I shoot the horse? All right, and he's- wait, which horse am I?
Wait, I'm in here first. Red. No. Blue. No, no, no, no. Which one do I want?
This one. Let's go. I already didn't get one. How did he- did he not get a- who didn't
get a horse yet? Which one of my crew members? Why are we not together?
Somebody died. Who died? What is- this guy didn't have a horse yet. Go get a horse!
No, I don't want that person- I have to help because that- somebody needs to go get their
horse. Oh well. What the fuck was that? All right, take the horse in the stable.
All right, I gotta get real close. Whoa! Are we waiting for the last person? Um,
excuse me. Excuse me. What? Where's our last guy? What's he doing all the way over there?
That guy- we- everyone shot that guy. Four hats came out of that guy.
He disappeared and he turned to the hats. Um, why are we standing here? Is there a reason
for this? Why can I not shoot? Okay, that was really weird. Leave him. Don't we have to
finish the mission together? You fucking asshole! You dick! That doesn't count. I was
intentionally sabotaged. I ran into him. He stopped- no, he stopped in the middle of the
road. He just went- he did that on purpose. He was trying to- he was making like a
compilation video. Now I'm in it. I get to be in it now. The funniest part about this,
is this still a guy that just rode down there to the west? I don't think that- that
guy- I don't think that guy knows what's going on. Did that person's horse die? Don't stop short
again. I got a horse. Mets. Some kind of suicide squad. I got to rank three.
The good thing about this, I'm happy that we all don't have to complete it. Just, we can't have two
people die. That guy just took off into the wilderness and started hunting.
I call him boy because I'm older. 30 minutes, he went black. Let's give our friend here back the
horse. Hey, thanks. It's yours. A sign of faith and future business. If you want to buy any
extras or sundries for the animal, head inside. Sundry? They've got a lot available. What's a
sundry? See you soon. Dude's face. What the fuck? All right, so services.
Rename the horse. I can't. Horse insurance. I guess just get it. Rename horse. How about-
uh, it can't be Phil. It's got to be something better than that. How about- I just used all my
money. That was seven dollars and fifty cents. I forgot I was online. I- I- this is just something
I just do in the regular game. I just buy it every time because I haven't bought a ton of
money. All right, whatever. Empty slot. I guess this is just free. Improved. Um, it's just
stock. Saddle voucher. All right, saddle bags. This is going to cost money, isn't it?
That's 80 bucks. Look at this shit. 22 dollars. Not enough. Buy now with one gold.
This shit ain't even worth it. Drain rate. It's- you just- you're paying- all you're paying for
is to get that 10% drain rate. The- the- you're not even- you can't even see that
from more than three or four feet away. So if you want to pay for a drain rate decrease,
buy a hundred gold packs on the- no. Absolutely not. Uh, we're just gonna do- just gonna do
default. Just buy the super horse. 21. No, that's too much money. Core drain. Oh, whatever.
I don't think I can do anything about the- this is probably gonna cost money too. Yep.
No, I have to keep- I just do default. I can't do anything interesting
because I need to buy a gun or something. Which version of the game is this? This is
the special edition. I didn't buy the ultimate edition because I didn't think it was worth it.
I didn't think it was- oh, whatever. I'll just get the- I'll get the one that you shouldn't
buy. The one in the middle. And I couldn't play yesterday. And I got like a cool horse
in the main game. All right, that's good. So am I in the open world now? You've
bonded with your horse after purchasing a saddle for it. Your horse is indicated by- yep,
yep, yep. V at the camp. See, I got the cool one. Knowing Rockstar, they'll be flying
horses soon. Yeah, if you want- look, if you want to play Red Dead Redemption,
and you want to play it at its very pure core, you gotta play within the next- I would say
within the next couple months. Because after a year of content updates, it's gonna feel like
steampunk in this game. It'll be like astronaut helmets, there'll be spaceships and shit.
Extra stalls can be purchased in the stables, these allow you to buy and manage
additional horses, right? If you want the real Red Dead Redemption 2 online experience,
I would- I would get involved in the next couple months. Before the guy that has $500,000
that just sends horses with like C4 attached to like blow up everybody standing in free
realm. That's not- that doesn't exist right now. It will. It's gonna happen.
Once people are able to battlefield people in this game, now I'm just shilling for Red Dead
On- no, no! I'm telling you, play it now. Don't play it later. Guess I am telling you
to buy it, am I? Yeah, I guess I am saying that. All right. Well, okay, for a second,
I was like, who the fuck is Sean and why are they in my game? Do you really need me to tell
you to buy Red Dead Redemption 2? Do I have to say that? Isn't it very obvious that this game
is worth playing? I gotta be careful with what I say about one of the best open world games
probably to come out in five to ten years. No, I gotta be careful!
Not really.
Think you did a good job for you? I'll earn my keep. When you get too old to fight,
what choice have you got? It's either work or beg. I'd rather work.
Now, he wants you to come down and meet him in Blackwater when you get a chance.
I think he might have some work for you. And while you're out on your travels,
you may see some folk with employment opportunities. Good folk, bad folk. Well,
should I? Hey, you decide if you want to purchase something or not.
Up to you if you listen to them. I will always tell you what I don't like.
This guy's beard is just frozen boogers. That's all it is. He's never wiped it off.
In probably two or three decades. General stores and tailors with supplies and clothing.
Here you go. Welcome to GTA Red Dead Online.
Find and accept free row missions from various characters like this guy.
Or this guy.
Or counter a rival player's mission for your own reward.
No. Really? Hold on. What?
Did they just say please grief everybody that's playing the game?
Hahaha. Hey, if somebody's trying to do a mission, fuck them up intentionally
by flying a fucking flying horse into the train in front of their mission.
You'll get rewarded for it.
I guess the whole game is about being like an outlaw.
So that doesn't go out of the ordinary.
Player many is used to this and receive invites.
Okay, I can either quick join. Ooh, I got a trophy.
You join or invite players.
Oh, MLC still is not playing this game.
Let's see. He has friends. Yeah, like one.
So I guess just join, view and invite. Quick join.
Join a series or story. Wait, wait, wait. Not yet. Wait a minute.
Camp's white flag is raised protecting you from other players.
Focus on the flag or use the player menu to lower it.
The camp's white flag is raised.
So that means nobody can come in here.
So this is where you're safe. As long as I have the flag raised.
Oh, they're okay over here.
Lower the flag. Lower the flag.
Let them come.
Some items can be purchased through the catalog.
You have a new person.
That is uh-oh.
All right, let's open the handheld menu.
Hunting and fishing horses. So this is just the web.
Okay, so you can buy. I can just buy this from here.
That's cool. How much is a bow?
124 dollars.
724 dollars? Why is it so- how much higher than that?
900 dollars.
Okay. Well, I used to do this when I was a kid.
I was never going to get any of it.
But this is the equivalent of what I used to do.
I used to- okay, there used to be a-
like a Macy's catalog or like a JCPenney catalog would come in.
And there'd be a huge toy section.
And I would just go through
and I would just circle all the toys that I ever wanted.
And that's all I can do.
Oh god damn it. Hold on.
How do I like turn that off?
This is not going to stop.
Notification settings.
That's just- it's just going.
I thought I already had that set.
Notifications.
Notification settings.
I thought I already had it off.
Yeah, pop up notifications.
No, no. Just disable.
No notifications. Absolutely none of them at all.
I think I got it.
Are we good?
I think so.
We're good.
All right, we're back.
Okay, so let's just- just take a look.
I should probably put this back up, shouldn't I?
Just hit- that's the wrong button.
And I don't want to run the ammo in this game.
Raise it. Raise it.
So I can't wait to get chased by somebody
and then stand behind here and just point and be like,
you can't get me.
Like the guy that drives over the Mexican border
at the end of the action movie.
And there's a- there's a confrontation between the-
like the cop and the bad guy.
And like I can't do anything about you.
I can't wait to have one of those scenarios.
One more.
Give me one more.
Continue playing to access your bonus content.
You made that joke.
When?
What was the scenario?
You already made- but when?
When did I make the reference?
Does anyone remember what game it was?
50- 50,000.
Oh, okay.
All right.
First- I thought somebody just gave $50,000 to the stream.
And I was like, no, they didn't.
I was like, no, fucking what?
Everybody freaked the fuck out.
I see 50k.
50k.
I'm like, no, what happened to 50,000?
What happened?
Do I have to- what happened to it?
No, it's just fucking seagulls.
It's just a bot that was there.
All right, let's go do a mission.
Let's go.
I'm gonna- wait.
Don't dream so high, man.
I'm not- no.
I just freaked out for a second.
Okay.
There are almost 4,000 people here, right?
When, like, the chat blows up like that, and I just see 50k.
50k.
And a ton of, like, fucking pog champs.
Is this a player?
I mean, I- what am I supposed to think?
I'm like, 50,000 what?
And then my brain said, wait, 50- everyone's freaking out.
You didn't think I was gonna do it!
You didn't think I was gonna be able to get it,
but I got it.
This is gonna impede me.
I need to just get into, like, a lobby.
Have I used any microtransactions?
No, not yet.
I just want to jump over this.
No.
No, I didn't do it.
Do I- did I do it?
I did.
Yeah, I did.
Oops.
No, we're fine.
Not yet.
Well, no.
Not yet as in no.
Not ever.
I should have been more clear.
I'm not gonna buy gold bars.
If I was gonna spend $100 in this game and buy gold bars,
I would- no.
I would just- I would go take that money to the casino
and just put it on double zero.
Because, hey, guess what?
There's a small chance that I just made, like, 35 fucking hundred dollars.
Oh, there are players here.
Really?
Okay.
I see the little blips on the map.
Where are they?
Are they only on the minimap or are they on the large map?
Ooh, okay, hold on.
There's a person here.
Okay.
Kill them.
No.
I'm not gonna start the never-ending cycle of Rockstar
online game insanity.
If I shoot this guy, it will never end because even if I leave,
I'm gonna shoot this guy and then I'm gonna leave.
This guy's gonna be angry and he's gonna shoot the guy that's next to him down there.
That guy's gonna get angry and shoot the guy that spawns next to him.
It's never going to end the cycle.
It stops here.
I'm not doing it.
What was that?
How do I do the mission?
I just started the cycle and now the cycle is never gonna break.
Where's this mission?
And you see, I shot that guy.
That guy shot somebody else and then that person went into another game.
Fuck this and shot somebody else and then eventually it kept going
and eventually they got to a point where somebody shot the server.
Uh, all right, just go to free room if I can even get in.
Yeah, somebody in game ran around and they found the box
that's plugged in.
That's the way that they get to have all the servers open.
That guy just shot the fucking router in the game.
This dead worked, but what if I did just get banned?
Imagine that.
That's a fault on Rockstar for putting the router in the game.
True talk, is this really good?
I don't, I don't know.
I didn't really get to play it.
Oh God, really?
Due to a fault on Rockstar game services.
What does that code mean?
Hold on, is it just off?
Banned?
Banned.
No, I'm not banned.
The server, somebody fucking unplug the server in Rhodes Ranch.
Uh, let's see.
Oh, we got a fix for it apparently.
There's an easy fix for this problem.
Uh, back out of the menu by pressing the button and attempt to relaunch Red Dead Online.
Quit out of Red Dead and reboot the game.
Okay, so I have to reboot the game.
Hopefully that fixes it.
Wait an hour or two.
No, I'm not going to wait an hour or two.
See, I fucking told you that I shot that guy and it started a cycle of hatred.
And that's the, and eventually it got disconnected.
I got disconnected somehow.
All right, I'm going to restart the game, see if it works.
Somebody tries to find the root of the problem and I was the root of the problem.
That guy was the server.
You guys don't understand.
When I say, oh, somebody must have shot the server in the game.
That's like, that's what I did.
NPCs in this game are, it's a network.
Certain NPCs need to be left completely untouched.
Because they're the ones that are directly, they're making the whole thing work.
Let's try it again.
Here we go.
Are we going to get the same error?
That was the test you failed.
Damn it.
And I said it too.
I said, no, it's going to cause a cycle of bullshit and hatred
and it's going to disconnect people.
People are going to get angry, disconnect from the game.
And then, no, fuck this game.
I'm not playing this game ever again.
Do I like these loading screens more compared to GTA V?
Yeah, probably.
Mainly because the GTA V one was a static image that just changed to,
it was like the same three images.
I mean, these are also the same few images, but it's a little more muted.
And I don't know if this is going to work.
Ooh.
Mmm.
Server booting back up.
Initiate it.
Come on.
Let me back in.
Can you continue playing?
Got it.
Eat.
Where the hell am I?
See, I think you're good.
A rockstar dev definitely just was like, the cycle ends here and is disconnected.
He ripped out all the cords and then everybody now has to start fresh.
There's my horse.
I want to go back over to that mission.
Where the hell am I?
Eats grass.
Well, what if I was hungry?
All right, Sean.
Let's go.
What was that?
Oh, I thought it was a player.
It was a player.
I just saw a name.
There was a name there.
That's the crocodile.
The fuck is talking?
Oh, that's me going.
Yeah.
All right, so I'm gonna be a good guy.
Why am I having, I'm an unintentional bully.
I don't mean to do that.
I don't, I didn't want to do that.
No, this is nice.
I like how this town is lit up at night.
All right, so we got, we got the barbershop.
Uh, what do you think?
I'll tell you what I think.
Let's see.
Nice haircut.
Is this your horse?
What is your horse?
Don't crash the server.
You're gonna crash the server.
The cycle, the cycle never ends.
I told you guys, that person did the same thing I did.
The same exact thing.
And it starts over again.
Rockstar, unplug it again.
We need to start over.
And I will continue to restart and reimagine and originate the human species until you learn.
Get along.
That's what we don't, we're in like a fucking weird post-apocalyptic movie.
Where's my horse?
Can my horse be stolen or taken or killed or something?
I think they're coming after me.
This person, look, this person's just murdering people.
See, I did it once and broke the server.
But now it's time to get a little bit of revenge here, I think.
The cycle repeats, the cycle repeats, the cycle repeats.
All right, I got my revenge.
I gotta get out of here.
It's time to go do a mission with a bunch of friends.
Okay, so this guy right here.
Except caravan escort.
Thinks he's some criminal mastermind these days.
This is the last thing I need right now.
Voice chat, how do I turn off voice chat?
I'm guessing this ain't just a social call.
Showdown.
What are you ringing a bell?
It's in the player menu.
Who's ringing the thing?
That's not the player menu.
So am I right in thinking you're here for more of all the little masters?
Online options, voice chat.
No one.
Friends only.
Walk styles.
Crazy.
All right, now we're good.
Another one here for some money under the table, I assume.
I'll take it.
Nope, got nothing for you, sunshine.
No, what?
Oh, I'm so bored.
It's like being trapped in a picture frame.
Increase your chance at success by accepting free roam missions.
They dropped off a note.
Some job that needs doing.
Whoever they are, not that I give a damn anymore.
Oh, I'm so bored.
It's like being trapped in a picture frame.
So I'm not allowed to do this?
I'm not cool enough?
I don't have a big enough...
They dropped off a note.
Some job that needs doing.
Whoever they are, not that I give a damn anymore.
I need some people online.
Accept Supply Wagon.
What is he doing?
Oh, okay.
I'm not big enough.
All right.
Does this mean that other people are going to be in this game?
Deliver the supplies to Rhodes General Store.
Take the supplies to the drop-off within the time limit to earn the full reward.
So people are going to sabotage me here.
I just got to go.
Maybe people aren't paying that much attention.
I just got to bring the wagon.
And if anybody comes near me, rival players can attack the supplies.
Right.
No, this is great.
Okay.
Well, I know what you're doing down there.
You just got the little pop-up window.
Jerma is delivering supplies.
You should probably stomp him.
Maybe they're too preoccupied.
Maybe I'll just get this without any issue at all and I'll get the full one gold bar reward.
Hey, this is great.
Look at this.
I just get to drive it for free.
No one's going to stop me.
No one can stop me.
I've won.
Am I even in a game with anybody anymore?
What?
What can I shoot?
Shoot him.
Shoot the gun.
What are you fucking doing?
What?
I can't shoot that way.
I can't shoot the gun that way.
This is not a player.
Yeah, it's because they probably all get disconnected.
I need to run.
I am running.
There ain't nobody here to stop me.
I just get whatever I get from completing this.
I think maybe the servers went down to get it.
Now I just get all the spoils.
What's against this camera angle?
Are the servers really that dead?
They shouldn't be.
I'm in an empty server.
Well, I'll go to a new one.
After I get the full reward.
Uh-oh, somebody's coming in.
Wait, am I about to drive right into somebody?
I gotta be ready for this.
Are they going to come straight down the road?
How far away are they?
I got it.
It's right here.
Enemies can't interact with me when I'm in the drop-off area.
All right, we'll get over there.
Red Dead Redemption online.
It's awesome.
It's like a one cent.
Wow, that was exhilarating.
Well, here's my experience of the Red Dead 2 online so far.
Hello?
Anybody here?
What's going on here?
Somebody plug?
All right, how do I join again?
I want to join like a different game.
All right, join free roam.
Be sure you want to join Red Dead online.
Yes.
Just get me in a different session.
Hopping dimensions.
I could do the story mission.
At least matchmaking would probably pull people in, right?
Remember when Next was an emote?
Oh yeah, I do.
Boy, that was a mistake.
Next.
God.
Immediately after uploading that, I was going...
I don't know if I should actually put this on.
And then I left it there for like a year.
Are we going to get the error code again?
No, we're not.
All right, so here we are.
There we go.
All right, we're good.
We're good.
We're...
They're here.
But where are they?
Okay, a lot of people are...
I'm just in like the shitty place.
There we go.
All right, let's just go.
We're going to go on a...
Now I'm excited.
Okay, let's do...
This is like Stranger's Fortnite.
German with a train.
Oh my God, he has headphones on.
He can't hear me.
The train.
Oh my God, he has headphones on.
I already did this one.
I don't want to do that one again.
Play horseshoes?
I could play horseshoes, couldn't I?
I want to be clear with other people.
Is this another one of those...
And you know somebody stops me missions.
Can you open your house?
All right, well, let's actually then...
Let's go here then.
Where is that yellow marker?
Over here.
Well, I just...
I think I'm going...
Does it tell you if you've been marked?
Another player has marked your direct location.
It might.
It probably does.
NPCs, don't worry about them.
Just leave them be.
Hey, Jeremy.
Your title says you're playing Red Dead 2 online.
Can you update the title?
I don't want people getting confused.
Do I have any items for the horse?
Here, eat an apple.
Mod that guy.
No, nobody's getting modded.
Is this...
Whose place is this?
Is this somebody's camp?
Whose camp is this?
I need to investigate.
Who's here?
Who lives here?
Can I do anything in this person's camp?
Well, the white flag is up, so I can't do anything.
Let's go.
Smash the guy's toilet.
Poop in his tent.
No, he has the white flag up.
I can't go to the bathroom on his fucking clothes.
It's far away.
Can I get there by going around the river bank?
Or do I have to actually go all the way back up here?
Put ants in his sleeping bag.
You guys are fucking cruel!
Ants in his sleeping bag!
I have to go all the way around.
This horse sucks.
They really want you to pay.
I'm so used to having my $20 horse from the main game.
I can't believe I actually have to go all the way around.
God damn it.
Shit.
I'm not even near his camp anymore.
Take the train.
Join a death match.
Is the train even actually available to take?
Oh, it is.
Fast travel.
Holy shit, it is.
All right, so I need to go from here to...
I need to go to Blackwater.
All right.
Well, I didn't even know you could do that.
I don't think that fast travel wouldn't really exist in a game like this,
but I guess you could take the subway in GTA Online, couldn't you?
Any plans of doing online with friends?
Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
Definitely, definitely, definitely.
But not everybody can play yet.
I did just want to check it out because it's currently only allowed.
What is that?
What is this?
Hideout.
Hideout?
Who's hideout?
What?
Like another player hideout?
Or is this just a random, hey look, a hideout and kill the enemies?
There's a lot of people here.
Place is on fire.
Oh my god, what is that?
What is that?
What is this?
What is that thing?
No, no!
Get away from me!
I don't have any gu-
Boss in there?
That's apparently the boss.
Oh, fuck.
Where is he?
Where, where, where, where, where, where, where?
He's over here.
They give you these little fucking BB guns to start the game.
I gotta get in there closer.
I gotta move up.
I'm gonna go down.
On this rock.
That guy, uh, in the front door.
That guy died somehow.
That guy killed himself somehow.
All right, let's get this up.
There's like one guy left up here.
And this is the guy with the big hat on inside.
How are you still alive after I blew up all those tanks?
Nice dodge.
All right, just show your head again, please.
This looks like a pretty good time waster.
I mean, it depends on how-
What the hell?
I gotta kill these guys too.
You're still alive.
All right.
Um, hideout clear.
Now I have to pick up everybody's body.
Red Dead Redemption 76.
Okay, I got rank five.
I unlocked, uh, I unlocked like a-
The spleen or a kidney or something.
Pump action shotgun.
And a military jacket.
Zero percent on story missions.
Leave the bodies as a warning.
I gotta loot at least some of these.
Speaking of loot.
I mean, there has to be something in here, right?
Why have a giant hideout boat if you're not gonna have anything there?
Now I'm looking for a ladder.
Can I climb this?
Loot the dog.
What do you think the dog has on him?
Nothing up here at all.
It's to lure in the ADHD streamers.
That's a nice hat.
Oh, there's a catapult.
If I pull that thing, it'll shoot a rock directly into that pole,
destroying the boat and killing me and anyone else that's on board.
It's okay.
Like a hundred more years, uh, they'll figure it out.
Well, a hundred years in the past, they figured it out.
I don't know why we'd screw it up like this.
Nothing here.
I'm gonna be honest, uh, what the hell was that all about?
Can you give me a cool boat to explore?
And it's just the shitty catapult that doesn't work.
We spoke so soon.
Here it is.
No, never mind.
This is just explosives.
Come on, there's nothing in the red Acme chest.
Like the Road Runner chest.
There's nothing over here.
There's not a backpack that has a propeller on it that I can use.
Fuck it.
Let's just keep going.
I mean, that was kind of cool.
All right, back to the mission we were doing.
I don't know what my horse is.
I think I'm being followed.
I'm being followed.
There they are.
They're there.
They're on the horse.
Are you following me?
What are you doing?
They're riding around in circles over there.
I'm ready.
I'm prepared.
Hey, how about, hey, I don't know if you can hear me.
How about, uh, server's just high noon to me.
Oh, he heard me.
All right.
Yeah, you were saying.
See, stop killing each other.
Don't you understand?
The guy at Rockstar that's ripping it out.
The like Thanos Rockstar guy.
No, somebody in town.
Screamed a bunch of swears
and then threw a grenade into the barbershop.
Rip it out.
Start over.
Okay, I'm back.
And, well, you gave up.
All right, so let, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Well, we're going here.
I mean, let's give Rockstar a little bit of slack.
There are probably two to three hundred million people
all trying to connect at the same time.
Two to three hundred, you mean.
Did I say million?
Did I add the million?
I think I added the million.
I meant, I meant, I meant that in yen.
Two to three hundred million yen people.
Which is like, what, two thousand?
All right, let's fast travel over there.
And are we actually in a game with people?
Let me make sure.
Yes, we are.
Two hundred million yen is 1.7 million.
Yeah, so that's 1.7 million people
probably trying to play at the same time.
Fast travel.
Let's see.
How much does it cost?
Oh, man, that's, that's, that's like 30 percent,
33 percent of my entire savings.
I just dumped my 401k out
to be able to take a taxi.
Start riding.
Let's try these for now.
Beat against up to 32 players
across large maps in a series of thrilling game types.
Walk straight into a race and kick up some dust on horseback.
Yeah, I want to try a race.
And then we'll go, we'll try.
Maybe they're just doing Thanos maintenance to it.
It's not a 2018 multiplayer game without Battle Royale.
Why don't I ever juggle on stream anymore?
I don't know how to juggle.
Same.
Yeah, I don't know how to show.
I don't know how to juggle.
But why don't I do it anymore?
Because I don't know how.
What am I looking at here?
Do you wish to spectate this session?
Um, okay.
Oh, this is a really bad race we're watching.
Oh, they crashed.
A wagon just crashed.
What's the next one?
Okay.
Oh, there's the other two people.
You have to pick up Donkey Kong barrels.
This guy's shooting.
Isn't that illegal?
I thought, I thought that was illegal.
I thought you couldn't use weapons.
Who's on the other list?
Somebody in the train?
That's a quick way to win a race is to drive the train there.
38 people to start this.
Well, this guy is, I want the person in like, first place.
Oh god, he's got headphones on.
So this is the person in second place.
Here's the guy in first place.
Okay.
Let's see how he does.
Good luck.
I hope you, no, you're in sixth.
Why can I, wait, this guy's not in first place.
I just went backwards.
Did you just win?
That person just won.
They were so hell bent on shooting the other person that they lost.
Yeah, here comes Sam.
All right, let's go.
My turn.
So is this just like in GTA online where
in the first one second of it going three, two, one,
14 people crash into each other and fall off the horses
and then somebody accidentally gets in first place
and they stay in first place the rest of the time.
This guy's not even doing the race anymore.
First place.
I'll take my reward, please.
Thank you.
What?
Okay, uh, proceed.
Stable.
I'll be riding with Sean who sucks.
Game details.
Yep, I'm, I'm ready.
Ready up.
Change outfit.
I don't have any outfits.
What a wind down different if I didn't get-
Hey, oh, I turned off.
I turned this off.
Didn't I do that?
Did I turn that off?
All right, we just gotta just pretend we're not here.
All right, let's do it.
Bards crossing, point to point, race across, bards crossing.
I'm ready.
Now, heated gaming moment inbound.
Yep.
Three, two, one, go.
That's me.
Three, two, one.
Why am I all the way in the back?
That's not fair.
I'm gonna get in that first place position.
I'm at least gonna start in like the top.
I gotta finish in the-
It really is Mario Kart.
I just got a gun.
In the first place.
How do I punch?
What?
Oh my god, you have so much health.
That's not what I thought it was gonna be.
My horse, I gotta be careful.
Slow down.
Let the horse breathe.
Why did I die?
Whose horse is that?
Why is it in the way?
What?
What's the fucking spawning horse?
Was that my horse?
This is wild horses running around.
Okay, I need something.
I don't know what it is.
God, nothing.
I'm in the last place right now.
But that wasn't my fault.
I got a horse spawn.
Somebody dropped a horse banana peel on me.
That wasn't fair.
Oh, you gotta collect a barrel to replenish the stamina.
What?
Does he like tap my foot and I died?
Three green shells.
All right, this is where I'm gonna get the lightning bolt.
See, it really is the lightning bolt.
I actually just picked up a lightning bolt.
All right, now I got a shotgun.
I just shrunk everybody by like 60%.
I'm good.
Not in the last place anymore.
That person's gone.
That person's off the track completely.
I gotta get in eighth place here.
What?
Is he phased in?
I don't understand.
He just phased in.
How come he doesn't go off?
Why does he not go off?
Why does he?
Why does he not get affected by that?
That was ridiculous.
I get fucking tapped on the toe and I flip off and die.
My horse spins around in a circle a hundred miles per hour.
And what the fuck is happening?
Hey, I didn't come in last.
You can just finish line.
I can't come in last place.
It's all right.
The guy that isn't last place right now gave up.
What was that?
That was absolute dog shit.
The NF is worse than last place.
No, it's not.
That means that I still tried.
That guy killed me so I couldn't finish.
What a dick.
Yeah, that's also the guy that ran through
mud, concrete, and like four explosions.
And he was completely fine.
Scratch on him.
Purchases.
All ammo.
Arrows.
I don't want this.
We've got 14 people.
Let's try this again.
I have to try this again.
I have to.
What the hell?
Mario Kart guns.
How do you turn off GTA mode?
I'm not sure you can.
You're just going to get angry like a hitman.
No, no.
Is there actually a battle royale mode in the game?
We'll do it after this.
Yes, there is.
Okay.
One dollar horse versus a thousand dollar horse.
That's okay.
Ride through all the signal fires around Valentine in any order.
So that's odd.
You have to just touch every single one.
Am I enjoying it so far?
It's fun.
I can't really give you a true assessment of it though
because I feel like I have to try to do everything.
It still has the same annoying flaws from GTA Online
that have somehow poured it over here.
Huge loading screens between every single thing you do.
But besides that.
All right.
Here we go.
Melee combat is disabled.
So you can go in any order.
Why am I instantly losing?
Is my character suck?
I think my character just sucks.
What did I do that was so wrong there?
I like touched him.
Is it my horse?
He's too top heavy.
He's just killing me.
I have weights on my character.
I have extra pounds on.
It's not fair.
Why does it happen to me but not him?
I'm gonna freak out.
Why does it happen to me?
Why does it only happen to me?
It's not, that's not fair.
Why?
I'm gonna calm down.
I have to calm down.
You have more momentum?
What?
You can't just drive into somebody and not get hurt.
I can't fucking believe it.
That is absolute bullshit.
I wonder if he's gonna touch me
and I'm going to springboard off of the horse.
Everybody's Donkey Kong
and I get to be fucking Toad or Koopa Troopa.
If that were me, I would have exploded.
I would have spun a hundred times.
I'm an NPC.
I've come to terms with it.
Everybody's playing the fun game
and I get to be the guy that's here.
The AI bot that just falls down.
Didn't fall off that time.
I only got three more.
Everyone's not paying attention though
so I might have a chance to at least score some points.
I'm gonna, I'm not gonna finish.
I'm not gonna finish.
The reason why I'm not finishing is because I,
I keep getting fucking destroyed on the horse.
People will run full blast into me
and just drive right through me like, like a ghost.
Their horses are better in heavier weight classes.
I really look like such a fucking imbecile.
I'm just such easy prey.
I'm, I'm the fucking kid that got this for Christmas.
All right, I'm, I'm out of here.
I'm out of here, but I can't quit.
Yes, I'm sure I want to exit.
You're a Christmas noob.
Guy comes in, not even leveling up his horse.
No armor and no nothing.
It just gets bullied.
All right, what were the other things?
What's the Battle Royale mode?
Is it Showdown series?
Which one is it?
Victory Royale.
That's so stupid.
He's doing Battle Royale with the P-shooters.
I just want to try.
Red Dead Mario Kart, Red Dead Fortnite.
Just abuse the auto aim.
I don't, auto aim is not really that apparent
in online to other players.
32 player Battle Royale.
Yeah, I'm gonna get, I'm gonna get a steak dinner,
whatever they call it.
I'm gonna get the fried chicken.
All right, let's go.
What's the mode?
What's the briefing?
Let's see.
Name your weapon.
Brief roll where the trickier weapons
earn more points per kill.
What?
Tomahawks will kill players in a single hit.
Okay, kill every, dispatch opponents.
Are they on the minimap or is it just random people?
I hear noises.
There we go.
He doesn't know I'm behind him.
All right, whoa, whoa, guy up there.
Anybody Tomahawks?
There he is, somebody up on the rock.
Oh, there's an item up here.
There's a weapon up here.
This is probably gonna be, yep.
Give me that item.
Where's the, where's the, where's the sniper rifle?
Put it on, put it on.
Oh, you know how fast I can tap circle, buddy?
Oh, how do I use it?
R1, oh, I'm just a target up here.
Oh, Tomahawk, battery's low.
It's all right.
Don't you dare, don't you dare.
Oh, come on.
Oh, that's actually pissing me off.
That actually pisses me off.
I was doing really well.
Oh, come on.
I was doing, I was, I was had to a bit
in either first or second place.
Come on.
That was fun.
I was so proud of you.
Disconnected, charged a bit.
What are you talking about?
I just plugged it in.
That's not plugged in?
How am I not connected?
What are you talking about?
Why does this not understand
that my controller's plugged in?
Okay.
Am I connected?
All right, I am.
There we go.
I have to charge my charger.
I don't think I've been able to stay connected
for more than, what, 30 minutes?
Sometimes less.
Well, the people that are asking how the game is
and if it's any fun in multiplayer.
It, I mean, it seems like it is.
I sure would love to play it uninterrupted
for more than 30 minutes.
Kill all the players to rise up the leaderboard.
The higher you get, the more points you're worth.
That's cool.
Did I just join in a random game here?
Chest down there.
Why is this not just, what is this, a nuke?
I think I did it.
I think I got, I shot him in the head like five times.
That's probably so scary.
PS4 aim.
Well, I mean, it's, I wish this was on PC.
Fistful of Rags is one of my favorite shooters,
like ever.
And having this on PC and actually control it
with a mouse and keyboard at like 60 FPS,
I would, I would play this every day.
Yeah, um, okay, sweet.
Is that guy talking to me?
It's like, I feel like you guys in chat
have said that before.
Like, okay, yeah, whatever you say, dude.
I can't turn this off either.
Can I?
I can't turn it up.
It's only on every, why?
Rockstar, why?
Of all the things.
So hold on, I can actually use it in multiplayer?
That seems so odd.
Oh, you can't be doing this.
Can turn it off.
Okay.
Interesting.
Sorry, brother.
How'd you do you like that?
How do I turn it off?
I'm getting nasty.
Open voice chat is seriously just like,
it's such a distracting, annoying thing
in every video game.
It's like, welcome to the wild west.
You play as Arthur Morgan and his band of misfits.
What time is it?
Where are we?
Shut up, mom.
I think I lost.
It's going to explode.
Don't be rude to mom.
I died five times.
What?
All right, let's go.
MVP.
You're a band of outlaws,
fighting over a treasure chest on the train tracks.
Toot toot.
Oh, be careful.
Huh?
No, I love Cheez-Its.
I'm going to do the mission.
He has headphones.
I only have one headphone in.
Look at all these players.
Where?
I need to go from here to there.
So I need to take the, didn't I already?
No, wait, does this take money from me?
How much money did I have before the game crashed?
If it took money from me when I did this,
I'm just bleeding money for no reason.
Go to the options menu to turn off voice chat.
I already did.
I mean, I already did that.
Honestly, you saw me do it.
You saw me do it.
I did it.
You watched me do it.
You saw me do it.
Right here.
But what, what?
Okay.
What is this here for then?
That menu.
Why don't, why not just put off there?
That's only for the instance.
Oh, oh, all right.
Give me the stagecoach.
Right here.
Same for GTA.
Yeah, what the heck?
All right.
I need to go to, where was it?
Blackwater.
We got to go there.
And I'm going to do the story mission with some online friends.
And by the way, it did take the money from me.
It processed the transaction.
And it may have just did it again.
And it may have just crashed it again.
It's taking more money from me.
I put in the dollar 50 and I pressed Mountain Dew.
That didn't fucking work.
And then I put another dollar in.
It's a dollar 50.
Didn't fucking work again.
What am I supposed to do?
Go get a manager?
They don't even operate these things.
I got to call the number on the back of the vending machine?
No, you're just going to leave.
Why did you do it two times?
Because you were really thirsty and there was your only option.
You thought maybe you could put a little bit more money and it would work.
Oh, I wonder what just happened.
You've been disconnected from Reddit and I'll do to a fault on the services.
And now it's never ending.
It's going to put me somewhere that I was before.
So I'm going to never endingly try.
I'm just going to fucking walk there.
I'm just going to walk there.
I'm going to get on the horse and I'm just going to walk there myself.
Every time I try to get there quicker, it just deletes me from the game.
For real.
Stop purchasing from the broken vending machine.
Play something else.
I mean, I could, I want to play this though.
This would be really fun if I could just play it.
And I have been able to in small snippets.
I want to play this.
I want to play this game.
I want a Mountain Dew from this machine.
I don't want to see Yara Mist from the other machine.
Even if that machine works.
I want a Mountain Dew.
How far away am I?
Let's see.
No.
All right.
Would you look at that?
Okay.
Please go across the entire video game again.
Is there a boat here?
I'm getting on a boat.
Give me a boat.
I will paddle across the whole ocean.
You can just choose where to log in.
Really?
Well, let me just do something bad here.
Boat through the rain.
Let's see if I can get a boat.
This is really cool.
Mountain Dew tastes like pee and marijuana.
I don't think...
Why do you know what those two things combined taste like?
I mean, I can understand knowing what they both taste like.
Right?
But why do you know what they taste like together?
All right.
So I'm just going across...
I'm just going across the whole Atlantic Ocean.
Why would you know what marijuana tastes like?
You can eat it.
Well, you don't eat the leaf.
Leaf.
Boil it down.
Smash it up.
Put it in a food processor.
And bake it.
And you add like corn syrup and sprinkle like cinnamon on it.
And then put like gelatin in it and mold it up into little shapes.
And then you have an edible.
All right.
I need a boat.
There's got to be a boat lined up here for some random idiot like me.
Yep.
All right.
That was the first one.
I'll take that loss there.
That's two hours and 40 minutes, by the way.
That's how long it took.
That's a record.
And there's no boat here.
Wildly unfortunate.
But what is that?
It's a bucket.
God damn it.
Give me...
There's got to be a boat somewhere here.
There's no just canoe or rowboat just on the shore.
So I can just do this.
There's another hideout over here.
Do you have a boat?
That's all I care about.
Just swim, forehead.
How far is it?
I'm not even crossing the right...
Right place.
I'm going across...
I'm swimming.
Let's just go across the English Channel rather than the Atlantic.
Hey, this is the way to build stamina.
That's for sure.
It's going to take longer to swim than ride your horse.
I know.
But...
And I didn't...
What did I even do here?
I just...
I would have already been there if I didn't get the stop blue screen error code X0X00021.
What the hell it was.
Options.
Press the options button.
Select online and go to free room.
And then West Elizabeth.
How do I select where I want to go?
Free room.
I'm right where it is.
Where it is.
There it is.
Thank you.
Just jump on each water droplet until you get there.
Wouldn't that mean that the rain is solid to a point where you can stand on it?
Which means it can carry and hold enough weight for you to stand on it.
Therefore, all life is wiped out because you're essentially dropping tiny little concrete
bricks on everything.
On every person.
On everything.
And every animal.
Every tree.
I guess so, yeah.
Like hail.
But you can't stand on hail.
If it was two pounds per pebble and hundreds of millions of them were falling at the
same time.
You would just turn everybody into a giant food processor.
We'd be inside the stomach of a turkey.
Turkeys eat rocks to digest all the food.
That's what would happen.
Well, we're already here.
We made it.
Finally.
We're in Blackwater.
What's this mean?
Why is he chasing after the wagon?
How do I whistle to him?
A rival posse has started the mission.
Eliminate the target!
Hey, slow down!
Is that, no, that's, that, this is me from the past.
Can I actually get him in this?
Oh my god.
What?
That was fucking funny.
Who the fuck are you?
Oh shit, it's you!
I got him!
It was lag.
A little bit of lag there.
So if you get somebody in the last oak,
and I like to hide them out, actually, like hog-tie them?
No.
So that's why, because that's what I've always taken so long to do.
What?
It's not fair.
There's like three people there as friends.
Where are my friends?
I'm just a random fucking farmer from down the road that heard noise outside of his house.
What's all that racket out here, you little bastards?
It's a four-band party.
One, two, three, four.
Me and my shitty horse.
And then this guy.
Sean is not a shitty horse.
All right, fuck this.
You want to see the real Red Dead Redemption?
Called Farmer Joe was going full speed into the fucking party of four.
That wasn't even one of them.
And they, I fell off my horse, but they didn't.
Fucking typical.
My horse is dead.
Thank god for horse insurance.
Rockstar Online.
Just get in a party of four and bully the farmer that's level five.
I gotta like do something.
Fuck it.
I gotta fuck something up here.
Who the fuck is that?
We are friends.
We're friends, right?
We're friends.
You and I are friends.
Let me get on your horse.
We have to work together.
Don't you stand?
Hi, Sean.
Good luck doing anything with your old man hands.
All right, I don't want to go that way, but they're in the town too.
At least maybe the lawmen will come out.
Who is hanging out over here?
Oh god, he's on the road.
I got my revenge.
I don't even care.
I was trying to run him over.
Wait, that wasn't them?
That was the guy that had the star on his name, right?
What is this guy doing?
Are you friendly?
All right, hold on.
What's the emote?
How do you emote?
I'm trying to prove.
No, put the knife away.
Okay.
He doesn't want to kill me.
Good.
It seems to start with the absolute most, the worst possible moments, right?
Oh, look, there's a guy there.
Are you going to maybe make a friend and go do some stuff?
Oh, you're doing really well in this online session where you're probably for...
No, no, no.
Yeah, only when I get fucking bullied is when they want to keep the servers on.
I've played 14 hours and have never gotten kicked.
I wonder why it's...
I mean, is this happening to anybody else?
Or is this just a...
Is this just a me problem?
Yeah, it's happening to you.
Yeah, me, me, me.
Rock it.
All right, come on.
I want to play this.
I just got two in a row.
I got the one with the two and now I got one with the nine.
Now it won't even let me exit the game.
I'm gonna...
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Let me go take a piss.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna exit, restart.
We'll try it one more time.
I want to play this.
This is what I want to play, but I can't do it.
Well, I can, but just for not very long.
Give me one second.
I'm gonna grab another water and take a piss.
See you soon.
I can't open it.
I'm not strong enough to open this.
What the fuck?
God damn it.
Okay, I got it.
Mountain Dew.
Let's go back into this.
Try it again.
All right.
I'm gonna restart it.
I shouldn't have to do this.
Rock star.
I'll fuck some people up online.
I'm trying.
I'm trying to get it done.
Please drink verification.
What?
All right, here we go.
Let's go.
Oh, it's from...
It's from meme.
I see.
I get it.
Well, actually, I don't get it.
I don't know what you mean by that.
But I get that it's a reference to something.
Do I still drink Dr. Pepper?
I don't really drink soda that much anymore.
Except when it's an ice cold,
frothy Mountain Dew.
That's a Coke, by the way.
That's a Coke Coke.
And yeah, I drink probably like a soda.
Maybe like two sodas a week.
Once a week, maybe.
I drink a lot more water than anything else.
Nowadays.
No, not diet.
I don't drink diet soda.
Imagine drinking water?
What is gross?
What's wrong with water?
What, you guys don't like water?
I mean, water is boring, but you have to drink it.
Otherwise, you'll turn into...
You'll shrivel up into dust.
All right, where the hell am I?
Didn't I...
Didn't I select black water?
Why am I all the way over here?
No, I'm going to just...
I'm going to take what I can get at this point.
I want to do this mission.
I'm going to get on the horse and I'm going to walk to that mission.
I'm going to stand in the circle and go to the mission.
That's what I'm going to do.
Water is not boring?
Well, boring in the sense that it doesn't...
That water doesn't have like a taste.
It is just tasteless.
Tasteless, colorless, no additives.
It's just nothing.
It's just there and you need it.
You know, you have no horses.
What happened to my other horse?
It got deleted?
Well, why is that?
Come here, you little shit.
Why can I not...
Whatever.
All right, let's go.
I'm not going to shoot it.
I don't need it right now.
I need to just stay focused and go straight on the GPS.
Get to the mission and hope that I can do it.
And enjoy myself in RDR2-O.
RDR2-O.
I hate that title now.
That title was just a stupid reference I was making with like
100 people in the chat.
I'm changing it to that.
Yeah, that was like an IGN Plays Red Dead Online reference.
Yeah, that's better.
The lawless land of RDR2-Online.
Don't run into him, please.
Shut up.
What?
Why did you tell me to shut up?
Why did you say that, you?
Why did you say that?
Yeah, shut up.
I gotta be careful.
I'm almost there.
Just let the Rockstar servers stay online
for me to play another mission with people.
Almost there.
I'm going to go very slow too.
I'm going to get off the horse.
I'm going to walk into the marker
because maybe I'm just going too fast
and the game is trying to transition me
to another instance or another server
and it's just kicking me out.
Where are all the random events?
That's a good question.
I think they're the peach markers on the screen, right?
Aren't those the new random kind of stranger events?
I'm almost there.
Come on, just get me over there
and I'm going to walk off the horse.
Okay, slowly.
Let it load what I want to do.
Compete with other players in free roam events.
Dispatch rider.
No, no.
No!
I should have just done it.
I should have just walked into the circle.
I had an opportunity to do it
and I didn't do it.
Small indie company.
We are testing the servers
so hopefully they're getting all the data that they need.
This is a QA data.
Data beta test stream.
You're watching live QA is what you're...
I'm not broadcasting Red Dead,
I'm broadcasting testing.
I guess that is what I'm doing.
And why am I playing just to suffer?
Because I feel like when it works,
it's going to be fun and it has
and when it does work, it's interesting.
And now I'm back here again.
I'm going to go...
No, I don't want to do that.
Just go to the map.
Where am I?
I'm so much further away now than I was before.
This is just unbelievable.
This really is turning into suffering at this point.
But I want to do it.
I want to play it.
Here comes a bad review.
Just buy a plane.
Just reload until I spawn there.
I could probably get there faster
than reloading the game one time.
Okay.
Don't do anything.
Just get there.
Don't say anything.
I was fucking reading the chat
because I was seeing...
Don't do it.
Just forget them.
I couldn't even control it.
I couldn't turn.
Pull it back.
I want you to pull it back.
Give me a clip of that.
I'm not fucking around.
Clip that because you can hear me
press right on the stick.
Clip it and show it to me right now.
Listen to this.
I want you to listen to the click of the analog.
Fucking reading the chat
because I was seeing...
Let's hear the click.
Don't do it.
Just forget them.
Do you hear that?
Do you hear the click?
Listen to it one more time.
Right with the...
I couldn't even control it.
I couldn't control it.
This is a slight click.
No, I swear to God.
I've done dumb things before.
I've fallen off fucking cliffs.
You see, I'm laughing because, okay, I felt that...
I told you, I fucking am absent-minded.
Some dumb shit happens.
But that was not the case that time.
Just get me to the mission.
This would not have happened
if I could just play the game
that I wanted to play like 40 minutes ago.
Okay, I think it's time to stop.
Superior Vegas internet.
That's not my internet.
That's not me.
I'm losing the connection to...
Their server's a drop,
but that didn't do anything.
Try again another day.
What is here is probably fun.
I mean, I really wanted to...
I really wanted to save Jackbox for Friday
because we could do it the whole time
and we could spend like five, six, seven hours in it.
Because, I mean, it's not like I have a time limit
for the streams, but I usually start to get pretty tired
after like five or six hours streaming.
And then at about six to eight
is where I usually call it a night.
And I really don't want to...
I want to give it the time it deserves.
That's what we're doing on Friday.
Stick to the plan.
I'm there, I'm there, I'm there, I'm there.
Hold on.
Didn't have time to kick me out.
I just got in.
It's like currently beeping.
It's currently beeping to get me...
I got it, I got it, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Didn't have time to kick me out.
I just connected.
Oh, whoops.
Oh, it's a strange one, Horley.
We're good.
How is this little clerk?
How bad is you'd expect?
I expect a lot.
The clerk was a good man and a fine man.
That he was.
And this fella?
Well, that's their business.
Sorry, it's my first time streaming, yeah.
The world's business is kindness and gentleness and evil and brutality.
What else is there, mister?
Well, there's a whole lot else besides like lust and greed and stupidity.
Oh, mister Jones is stupid.
Oh, Jones is old.
Oh, Jones has cooked himself in the sun.
I know, I know.
Get yourself something to eat.
There's fellas need help.
Maybe this fella can help them.
Maybe.
They're on the run.
Did they beat the game?
I did not.
I had about the 43, 44% time.
My business is what they do hereafter.
That's my business.
Well, they certainly need money.
There's always money.
Money for them is as good and money for them is not so good.
By the way, make sure everyone is aware because this is the last time I'm going to be able
to talk about it.
If you have a, did I just make money?
Did somebody just take money from me?
You might as well try the sheriff at Blackwater.
He needs help.
That was weird.
I'm not streaming tomorrow so this is the last time I'm going to be able
to talk about it before Saturday or Friday, and at that point it's too late.
So as of tomorrow, midnight tomorrow, midnight tomorrow, Pacific or Eastern, I'm not sure.
But tomorrow night late is your last opportunity to put a submission in for the movie night.
Thursday, tomorrow night.
Meet me back here after you've seen them.
If you do not have a submission in, then you are not eligible for Sunday's movie night.
Now, I've seen some people say, hey, my submission is is two minutes and 40 seconds.
My submissions is three minutes.
Can you show this?
It's like three and a half minutes.
Not for not for Sunday.
Sunday is strictly for these submissions in that channel.
If you go to the Discord and the movie night channel,
follow the very specific rules that are pinned there in that channel.
I don't have a horse so we have to what do I have to go all is there anybody
even doing this with me?
I mean at this point I can't I can't load into free room.
I have to I have to just like go to single player or something,
but that's not what I wanted to do.
It's such annoying.
Uh, yeah, I can't just keep trying.
I'm going to try tomorrow the next night.
No, not tomorrow.
I can't not stream tomorrow.
Um, load in a different place.
Not West Elizabeth.
Yeah, but even when I was in these, I was dumping out on these two.
Remember I was doing exceptionally well.
I got disconnected.
Load in New Austin.
Well, for the purposes of can I change my region?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think there's any way to do that.
All right.
I'm here's what is going to happen.
Uh, I'm going to load.
I'm going to try one more time in a different place.
And if it doesn't work, then I'm just going to go play fucking Peggle 2.
For like an hour or two or something.
God damn it.
That's so the load of story mode or I don't know.
Let's try it again.
You gotta have faith.
Well, sorry to all those people watching that.
We're expecting to see Red Dead Redemption 2 multiplayer.
And what exclusivity we got here exclusively.
Hey, if you, if you, if you bought this game day one and you supported rock star
and got in and played a bunch on the first day, you got rewarded.
When you get to play the beta, you get to play the beta early.
There it is.
Doesn't quite work.
And when it does, it's seems like a fucking lot of fun.
But the beta has just seemed like a gigantic network stress test,
which makes sense.
Okay, that's fine.
But not really, uh, not really completely playable yet.
And we can't even do it anymore.
Oh, well, fault.
There's a fault on rock star's game services.
Well, Peggle time.
Damn it.
If, okay, if the stream had been going for like five hours,
maybe like Peggle 2.
Okay.
That's funny for like 40 minutes.
Just played Red.
I, I, I'm sorry, guys.
It's kind of completely out of my hands at this point.
So, um, I mean, I could, here's, here's what's going to happen.
All right.
Let's be real.
Uh, I have to install Peggle 2 and it's going to take like six hours.
I'm going to move to Red Dead single player.
I still am like halfway through the game.
And then after like an hour or so, like another hour, two hours or something,
we'll try the multiplayer again.
We'll just do the, we'll just stay in Red Dead
because that's what I wanted to do.
I wanted to play Red Dead.
And it's, once we go off the rails and it's like, oh, Peggle and then Bloodborne.
And then, um, um, uh, what else do I have on PS4?
Flash games.
I'd rather just stay fairly, uh, fairly in the same, uh, same realm.