I like this comment. Where is this fucking guy? I'm right here. How are you doing? Time to start
meowing. I'm good. I'm good. That's the quickest way to be like, no, no, I'm not doing that.
I'm good. Let me tweet. So you probably saw the title. Maybe you were here in the pre stream,
but we're going to go over very briefly what happened in the chat because I know that there
are like 15 games in this series and I'm starting with Devil May Cry 3. The big debate in pre stream
council has chosen. They actually chose five, but I vetoed it. Turned out that starting with three
was considered by most people the right call. The smart thing to do. Three and five are one
storyline and then one, two, one and two are the same story or one, two, four and then three,
five. Is it, is it work like Star Wars? Like how does this work? It's four and five. It goes three,
one, two, four, five. Oh, okay. Well, yeah, I was thinking, do I start with one or do I start with
three? I was told start with three. I don't know how to do this shit anymore.
It's like, if you've never seen Star Wars, like how would you, how about, okay, wait, wait, wait,
wait, this is a better idea. How would you tell people to start Resident Evil? We're going to
talk about this. Resident Evil, Resident Evil. Do you have people start with the new ones?
Do you start with seven, eight, do the whole Ethan story? Do you start at one? I don't know
if I would recommend starting at one. Do, are you even into that? Would you do seven, eight,
then one, two, remake two or one, two normally? There's a couple of remakes in Devil May Cry,
right? And do you even put the other Resident Evil games on that list? It's like, it's Code
Veronica on that list, for instance, in like the play one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Yes or no. That's why it gets tricky. There are five games in this series and there's multiple
timelines and storylines. So I get it. It's tough. So we're starting with three. You guys
ready? Devil May Cry, I didn't even do my tweet. Today's going to be a chill stream.
Just want to hang out and play, relax and have a nice evening together. Is this game hard?
When this game's hard, are they just like fun? Not really. The gameplay is the real content.
Yeah, let's just hang out. Somebody said wait, Code Veronica is shit. Resident Evil, I am
and look, I am a Resident Evil streamer. I am. I played, I've played all the Resident Evil games,
all of them. But I will agree that the Resident Evil is an interesting franchise because
they're one of the only franchises that has that main series, which is phenomenal. And then a ton
of kind of bargain bin straight to DVD movies that they also have. I swear I see a Resident
Evil property come out every couple of years and I just feel like it's go, it's right into
the bargain bin. Is that accurate? And then they got Resident Evil 4 remake comes out.
One of the best games I've played. I mean, that's absolutely one of the best games I've played this
year without a doubt. Resident Evil 2's remake. Favorite game of the fucking whole year when it
came out. Resident Evil 7 and 8. I really liked those. I thought they were good. Why are you
stalling? There's no stalling. I'm just hanging out. You've played like four games this year.
No, how many games have I played this year? I want to know. How many games have I played this year
on stream? All right, let me, I'm going to give you guys a little bit of a bet.
Do you think I have played more than 15 games this year? Yes, I have. Do you think it's all right?
We need to, nobody look yet. We need to vote first. A one minute poll. Quick before people,
it's going to take like five minutes to do this research. So we need to poll right now.
Have I played more than 20 games this year? Have I played more than 20 games this year? Yes or no?
It's literally one minute poll going up right now. Have I played more than 20 games since January
1st, 2023? 20 different individual games. No shot. 15 yes, 20 no. Well, let's find out.
All right. So there's a lot of people that don't think I've, how many, are you serious? How many
times have I streamed this year? Shut the fuck up. BNAF trailer. What? All right. All right. All
right. So 70% of you think I have not played 20 different video games this year. How many is it?
Somebody's doing it right now. Somebody was already on it. Jesus. Sorry. This is not the
Switch version. This is, this is the PC version on Steam or the HD collection. You've played 19
games this year. No, that's not true. And do we count the Xbox and PlayStation nights where I've
played like 40 games in three nights? Those, do those count? Those, I don't think those count.
I think those are all part of one collective kind of group of game, right? I don't think those count.
I'm talking like it's a stream. It's a, it's an individual stream of this game that I'm playing
regardless of if I play it more than once. Like how many actual individual games have come out
that we're not part of a, I'm going to play this Xbox game for 15 minutes and move on.
Is it actually 19? It says 31. 31. Let's go. Yeah. 31. I've played 31 games in 2023.
Is this the fifth month? What is that per month? That's a lot. That's a lot. 31 divided by,
Hey, that's five games a month. I've played, I've played five games a month on average,
five different games a month. It's six games a month. Whatever. That's fake one per week. Yeah.
What's wrong with that? Generous math. I'm good. Watch the FNAF trailer. I'll tell you,
I already know what happens in the FNAF trailer. It's going to start on a close-up of a phone.
It's going to be pitch black and you're going to hear a phone ringing and it's going to go like,
and then it's going to cut. It's going to fade to black and then,
and then white text is going to show up. You remember taking the first call
back on the phone. And we're very close by the way, we're literally zoomed in on the receiver
and then it fades out again, white text, but will you be there for the last call?
And then it fades in. We're in an office and it's,
it's some fucking A-list celebrity is on the phone and they're doing the,
hello. Oh, hello. Hello. And we're talking like an S tier celebrity. I don't know who it would be
like, Oh, Wally, are you kidding me? It's, it's Chris Pratt. He's the hello guy, right? It's
going to be an A-list celebrity. None of this happens. I don't, I don't want to watch the FNAF
trailer. All right. I will, I will privately right now watch the first 10 seconds of the
FNAF trailer and I'll let you know my thoughts. All right. Here we go. I'm privately going to
watch it on my own right here. Five nights at Freddy's. Here it comes. Okay. Here we go.
All right. You're tired of having the same old backyard birthday party for your child every year.
So I was wrong. I was very wrong. It should have been zoom in on the phone pitch black.
You were there for the first phone call. I would have hit so much harder.
Fake trailer. Wait, that's not even the real trailer. Wait, what? This is the official one.
All right. Show it. I have to press like two extra buttons to show it.
Yeah. All right. Fine. We'll watch it. I can, I can, I can, no, I can watch this, right? It's a
fucking trailer. All right. Let's watch it. All right. Let's watch it. Let's watch it. Spoilers.
It's the trailer for the movie. We're going to watch the trailer for five nights at Freddy's
right now. Okay. Cause we care so much about this apparently. Five nights at Freddy's. All right.
I'll give you my thoughts. Show your face. No, I can't. I don't, I just can't today. I just can't
today. All right. Holland, you just messed with me. All right. Let's see how this is.
It's like 40 seconds long. Welcome to Freddy Fazbear's Pizzeria. Yeah. Where fantasy and fun
come to life. Hit it guys. If you're watching this video means you've been selected as Freddy's
newest security guard. Hello. We're going to have so much fun together.
I mean, it's just, I don't know. I mean, if it's a 40 second trailer, I don't know what I can't tell
from what's going on here. I mean, is it, is it, is it going to, is it, I don't know. Is it like a
good movie? I don't know. I haven't seen it. They didn't do the trailer that I wanted though.
You're stalling so bad. I'm not even stalling. It's been 15 minutes.
We just watched the Five Nights at Freddy's theatrical trailer. Is that stalling or is that
wow, current thing to talk about? We just installed this. Okay. No more stalling. I'm ready.
You couldn't give a rat's ass about Five Nights at Freddy's. I mean, okay, there's going to be,
I feel like we already know the whole thing. Five Nights at Freddy's has a pretty,
very elaborate lore. I'm not concerned about runtime. Why am I even giving you my thoughts
on this? All right. Time to play Devil May Cry. Turn this up. All right. I said Five Nights at
Freddy's three. That's what we're doing tonight. Let's go. What a centrist take. I'm not going to
see that movie. Can I tell you, I can tell you that, right? I'm not going to see Five Nights at
Freddy's. I'm not going to see it. I won't watch it ever. This is never happening. I'm just telling
you that I'm not going to see the movie. Is it going to be fine? Maybe it'll be cool. Maybe
you'll like it. I'm not, I probably won't watch it because I still haven't even seen the Mario movie.
Do you think I'm going to be rushing to the theater to go see Five Nights at Freddy's?
I still have to, what do you, what does this mean? That's where it's fucked up, dude.
You're a lazy movie watcher. All right. Wait, what's, what does this mean? Gold or yellow?
What does it mean? Gold is continue. Yellow is restart level. Uh, I'm going to go with this one
then. I like that a lot. I'm a big fan of that. Go on. You've heard of it, haven't you? The legend
of Sparta. When I was young, my father would tell me stories about it. In ancient times,
a demon rebelled against his own kind for the sake of the human race. With his sword, he shut
the portal to the demonic realm and sealed the evil entities off from our human world. But since
he was a demon himself, his power was also trapped on the other side. I keep thinking of some
celebrity doing that. Hello. Oh, and, and, uh, it's gotta be a soundtrack by Danny Elfman. You
know what I mean? You were there for the first call. Give me the reins. I'll fucking make it
happen. Yeah. See, they get it. They know. Look at this. They knew what they were doing. They know
how to make fucking media close up on the fucking phone. Black pitch black coming up from black.
We're on the same wavelength. Sorry for business yet. It's a little quiet. I'll turn it up in a
minute. I haven't even picked a name for this joint and I'm already you a customer too.
Well, if you want to use the bathroom, help yourself. The toilets in the back is your name.
Dante, son of Sparta. What did you hear that from your brother? He's got a small head.
Yeah, whatever. Who cares? Accept it. I don't think you want to mess with me, man. I can
X, X, X, X, X, X, Y, Y, Y, Y, B, B, X, X, X, X, X, Y, Y, Y, Y, B, B better than anybody you know.
What is going on? He's got stuff sticking out of him. Okay.
Man, it is really quiet. I'll turn it up. I'm sorry. Oh, now it's not quiet. What was that?
Why is he doing like, all right, tutorial time. This is okay. Select
from four basic styles. Use your select style action to show the enemies just how crazy this
party can get. So you pick from gunslinger, royal guard, trickster, or sword master and B
is your style attack. Okay. You feed enough enemies and eventually your style will level up
and you knew in wonderful style actions. So you have to play with a style to be able to level up
that style. Or do I actually do I have to pick one of these? I've seen a lot of people in chat here.
Okay. Hold on. You will master a new style action every time your style advances. Okay.
Gain experience points by defeating enemies. Change styles mid game via the mission start
screen. Okay. So you got to stick with something for a little while. You will begin the game with
the trickster style pre-selected. Okay. Mission one, crazy party. Customize. Whoa. I did not know
there was all this. So these are my weapons. I think I only have these. That's it. All right.
Style. Let me read these information. Uh, allows player to avoid enemy attacks using special.
Okay. So this is probably a dodge role, which is, I think I'm probably going to pick that one.
Master different melee weapons and maximize each weapon's power. I like that too. I'm not going to
look at chat right now because I know you're telling me the meta. You're probably saying,
Hey dude, royal guard is literally don't do anything else, but I want to ruin my playthrough
before I look over here. So let's do it. Gunslinger. They're going to master different
guns. I like that. I like that. Royal guard minimizing the damage of an enemy attack.
All right. So this is defense, defense, ranged DPS, melee DPS and sort of like rogue kind of
survivability. So do I want to be like quick, quick, quick, quick fight, fight, shoot, shoot
or defend? I feel like I want to pick this one because I, I didn't, when I think of devil may
cry, and this might be a different, I'm thinking of a different game. Maybe when I think of devil
may cry, I've never played it, but I think of two pistols or blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Then holding them behind my head. Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang. Then one forward and one behind
my head. Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang spinning around. Both those guns are behind my head.
I'm not looking bang, bang, bang, bang. That's kind of, and that's what I'm thinking of.
That's Bayonetta. Well, why am I playing this? I'll try it. Go for it. All right. Master the true
power of Dante. So that's lock on, melee, style action, examine, shoot. All right. These two,
this is a special move and then jump. Character move is a taunt. Old right bumper, then press
left stick to change lock on targets. All right. Good to know. Yeah, that this is what I'm thinking
of. Okay. Red orb, a magic red stone of crystallized demon blood offered to the gods to earn new power.
And is this just, can I mash? No, no, not good enough. Try mash as fast as I can.
Act different depending on the time. Oh, here we go. This is explaining to me. No, so why, why, why,
why, why, why, repeatedly press X to rapidly fire press X while jumping. Okay. So it's like, why,
why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why. I got an A. All right. I get it.
Is that it? Good job. I just got S. Oh, I need to lock on. Oh, it's hold lock on. Okay. Okay.
I feel like I'm going to like this game. I feel like I'm going to like it. Current enemy you are
locked on to will be displayed with a cursor and change the target with left stick. Taunting
increases the meter. Ooh, that's what I figured. So if you hold, okay. So that's to get to the
closest enemy. Okay. I was seeing how long I could do that. So what's wrong with Devil May Cry 2?
Why does everybody hate it? Oh, wait, that's like a style move. Ooh. All right. I'm trying to figure
out the lock on. So if I lock on to somebody, how do I, do I, oh, I have to click the stick in. Okay.
I get it. And it just goes to the nearest. I got it. Okay. Magic green stone of crystallized
demon essence. It require, it returns lost life. I'll take a C. That's fine. I didn't turn it up.
Sorry. It's terrible gameplay and story. The characters are all fucked. Oh, you ruined it.
Yeah. All right. All right. I didn't even know about the style points.
That's a B. B-A-B. B-A-B. B-A-B-I-B-O-O-B-I-B-I. Isn't that the three stooges?
Okay. I did not turn it up yet. I will right now. I promise. Did the graphics get better
after leaving that house? My shop, you're going to pay for that.
I almost wish he took an extra like five seconds to put that on her. 10 seconds.
Turn it up. I'm sorry. I got it. Okay. Blast the enemy into the air. Hold right bumper and press
Y while holding the left stick back. So this certain does different moves. It's not just Y,
Y, Y, Y, Y, B, B, B, B, B, B. You have to do certain combos. It's like playing Street Fighter.
Okay. Is that better? That's better, right? Are we happy with this? So hold Y. How come it doesn't
work? I'm holding Y. Hold Y. Oh, and you have to hit back. Oh, shit. Right. Ah, there it is.
Ooh. All right. Ooh, that was cool. Oops.
I don't know why I just thought this was funny. I don't know why my brain just thought that I
was going to uninstall the game. Imagine uninstall the game was in the menu and it was one down from
resume game. Oh, thank God. All right. There is a dodge roll. I was going to say I've been,
I'm missing it. What the fuck are you saying, bro? I don't know. I think that'd be humorous.
All right. So there is a dodge roll. Thank goodness. I was going to say I didn't,
there wasn't one. I was going to be very, very unhappy about it.
Get this thing out of here. Am I doing bad? Yeah. A little. Am I doing, I,
ooh, boss fight versus death. Wow. What is that? Ooh. Oh shit. All right. Let's go.
I gotta get used to the game. I gotta get used to the controls.
I just, I just downloaded it 15 minutes ago. It's better. This is going better. I'll tell you one
thing that's kind of crossing me up is having to hold right bumper to dodge. I'm not used to that
and my brain pressing B or A dodges always. That's going to take at least an hour or five
to get used to. Nope. All right. Let's go. Okay. I'm going to fight death again. We're still alive.
Oh, this idiot. Is it healing? Fuck. I'm not going to be able to beat this guy.
Do I get any gunslinger moves? I have no help. Yeah. Click left to change lock on.
Hi guys. I'm a from software Andy. You know, like I, every video game has to be played like
from software games or I can't play them. Like B is not dodge. I lose. I mean, there's no
estus flask. I can do with X. I can't play it. It's over. This game's not for old people. I got it
right here. Let me just open your inventory. How do I do that? How do I open my inventory?
How do I open my inventory? It's E? No, I'm on a controller. Oh my God. I'm dead. This gets hard.
All right. This is a hard game. Oh, it's down on the D pad. All right. Okay. This is a hard game.
Is everybody laughing? Cause I picked gunslinger. Is that what, is that what I did wrong?
Well, all right. I'll try it one more time with gunslinger. Starting out with gunslinger is hard.
All right. Well, I'll try it one more time. Level one gunslinger is bad. Okay. All right. I'll
change it if I, if I can't do it this time, you should be jumping way more neutral. Trump has
more iframes than your dodge roll. And where are the iframes? Are they at the very beginning or
the end of the middle? Where they at? Fuck. All right. I got half health. Is there a sprint?
How do I run? How do I move faster? Use trickster please. All right. This is my last try with this
All right. I got it. God damn it. That was quick. Oh my God. He's going to kill me again. I'm in
the tutorial. Is this game really? Okay. Wait, can I ask a question? Is this game really, really
fucking hard? Is it supposed to be this hard? He's going to go, dude. People got rocked by this boss
back in the day. I mean, this guy's, this guy's no joke. This game is, don't put that on screen.
Don't put that on stream and ruin my life. It's already there. Okay. Don't put that on. Okay.
Damn, this is hard. Okay. All right. Let me, how do I, how do I make it so I can, what's my style?
I'm not doing anything flashy. I'm just going to try to stay alive. I don't care if I get a D.
I just, I want to just beat it. Shit. I had to, I almost want to remap the dodge to just be like A.
That's the thing that's causing me the most problems right now. What did I just do?
Is there a way to move the camera quickly so I can actually see who I'm fighting?
This has got to be like a camera, like three position, right? All right. That didn't go as bad.
I'm learning. All right. I'm back at full hope. Oh, that's how you do that. All right. That's fun.
I got it immediately to see. All right. Bosses. Here's the boss. Let's go.
Enemies off camera. Won't. Oh, this guy's still alive. All right. Let's go. This is the one. This
is the one right here. Rickster literally has a dodge on B. Please. I gotta, I gotta beat this
guy. Dives and then jump. Oh my God. I'm like kind of parrying somehow. Oh, fuck that. Come on, man.
Shit. What? I'm missing something here. I definitely tell you, if I got this game,
I would have cried and returned it. I would have cried. I would have cried. And you're like,
Hey, don't get it. Wait, is this game M? What is this rated? What is the game rated? Is this M?
I probably still would have cried and returned it. Yeah. Cry. Hit. Hit. Hit. Hold on. Wait, I'm
getting some tips here. You can ride enemies. My worst fears of how a DMC stream would go are
coming true. They'll switch to Mario in no time. This is much harder than I thought it was going
to be. Well, okay. Hard is not necessarily the answer to the question. It's needing to have the
controls mastered in the first five minutes. Come on, Gwen. What's going on here? This is
probably the hardest Devil May Cry game. I'm all for it. I know I'm all for it. I'm,
I just got to learn how to play the game. Well, I beat millennia. That doesn't matter.
I win every argument, but you use teach. You use teach. It doesn't matter. I don't care. All
right, let's go. I'm going to be the tutorial boss. I promise. I'll be the tutorial. I will.
The original version is considered the hardest. I mean, I like a challenge. Let's go put it on
easy mode. No, I got it right here. Watch this. I got it. Where are the iframes? Where are the
iframes? How do I fucking dodge? Where are the iframes? God damn it. This is so fucking hard.
Okay, we're going to, I'm going to, can I, can I do it from the menu? How do I do this? How do I
pick the one that's not horrible? Which one is it? Gunslinger. I picked gunslinger and I was
getting fucking destroyed. Can I do it from here? Do I have to do a new game? You can't rely on
iframes. I can from here? Oh, here we go. Okay. So normal to, wait, what's going on?
Demo digest? I'm confused. What is this menu? All right. So this didn't work out that well.
Trickster. I'll try trickster. Well, wait, wait, wait, wait. Vital Star S. Is this a heal?
I should buy this, right? Don't buy these. Okay. All right. I'm ready. Let's go. Trickster.
So what can trickster do? We, I learned that. Oh my God. Way better. I, I, the movement is so
much more fluid and there's no longer an input delay on every single button. I was pressing
Y and it would be Y and then the movement happened about two to three seconds later.
Holy shit. This is way better. Yeah. I would hit Y to swing in three seconds with the Y. What an
input delay that was. That is hard mode. Thanks for letting me know. I love that move. Very cool.
Oh, there is a dodge roll. Yeah. It's so much better. This is way better. This is way more how
I want to actually play this video game. We're good. There it is. So this is a side roll and
then a jump back. I know that. And now I have this. All right. How much copium is it going to take
for me to get killed in the first 10 seconds of the tutorial bus? I wonder. Oh, come on. All
right. I just got this. That's a heal. All right. Come on. Let's go. No more fucking around. All
right. That's so much better. What was the eye frames? Oh, what's my menu? How do I take that
heal? Where's my heal up on the D pad? Got it. OK. I'm good. I'm good. I get it now. The dodge
roll changes the whole game. Why is everybody calling me DMC to Andy? What's that? DMC to is
all about your guns. Should have started with that one. DMC to sucks, dude. All right. That was
cool. I get it. Nearly a year since we last met. Where does the time go dressed like Dante for
Halloween? You could always tell, you know, who's been going to the gym lately by their Halloween
costume. Dante from Devil May Cry is like I've been going to the gym lately. I can fill out this
shirt. It's all right. Hey, I think that's fine. I'm super bad with time management.
I'm really good with my orbs. I'm not that stylish, but not super bad. I mean, the clothes I wear
fine. I don't do very much damage, but I will eat all of your food. I'll use all the stuff in your
house. I mean, that's like, I think that's pretty accurate to me. I don't know what orbs is. Is that
my brain? That's like how good, how strong my brain power is. That's the big orb in the middle
of my skull. Orbs is collectibles. Oh, OK. Orbs is money. Doesn't it excite you that Timon and
Negru once ruled this earth as the medium between the human world? Isn't it a magnificent view?
Greatest minds of their time, those who revered evil constructed this glorious edifice.
Now, after two millenniums of confinement, it can at last fulfill the purpose for which it was
intended. That's none of my concern, did he? Of course, he's taking good care of it. After all,
I don't know who this is. It is the only memento left from him. He has no idea if it's true.
Oh, I got an unbelievable video idea. And I don't want to say it because I don't want anyone to
steal it. I'm telling you, you guys are going to like this a lot. I might just put it on the
main channel because I don't know. I feel like it's going to it's going to annoy a lot of people
because this would be the first video I've uploaded. But I feel like it would be funny.
Cool. All right. But trickster is going fine. There's no way I can take it off trickster
because it's just not going to happen. Royal guard gets a block. That sounds awesome. I
might check it out. I'm all about defense and not taking damage when I play games like this.
I'm two times as high as normal by pushing off of certain surfaces so you can wall jump.
That's kind of cool. Oh, and you can jump off. My goodness. Oh, okay. I got it. I got it. It's
fine. I'm sorry. I'm getting too caught up in trying to do like combos and not surviving.
Just survive. Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do. Do attack, wait, attack, attack. That right.
Because it's boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. I didn't learn that. They didn't teach me
that. That's cool. That was a cool move. Okay. Any secrets or anything I should know about? New
gun. There are two types of sealed doors, red and blue. Release the door sealed by solving a puzzle
located in that room or defeat all the enemies. So red and blue. Blue is puzzle, red is. Okay.
Devil may cry three. Dante's Inferno. Yep. Things are breakable. What is this? I can remember
everybody saying scorn. I've been trying to figure that out for like the last year. Shotgun. Cool.
I definitely want that. Forget about the two pistols. Switch guns with left trigger in real
time. I'm going to like this way more. You're a fucking liar. What? Don't accuse me of that.
Lying to somebody. I've never done that before in my life. Oh shit. Oh, I got, I got to bring
something up. This is really funny. I don't know why I thought about this. Holly and I were talking
about this. And do you want to, we were talking about what the ultimate Reddit test is. Like the
ultimate, the ultimate Redditor test. And you guys ready to take it? The ultimate Redditor test.
Like if you use Reddit, are you ready? Have you seen the Christopher Lee Lord of the Rings
backstab video? Yes. If the answer is yes. You know, the one where he's like, Oh, what happened
is the air. If you've seen that video, I've seen that video probably 10 different times on Reddit
across like a decade. I had to, we were sitting to think about it. I was like, you know what?
I've seen that video every like a year or two. That video makes the rounds. It's been like a
decade. He admitted it. He's a Redditor. What about it, bro? What are you doing? I'm talking
and walking back and forth in the same room. Okay. All right. Stylish rank. I know what that
means. It means to be better at the game. So don't get, Hey, well, thanks for letting me know.
All right. Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap. How come I'm not doing the thing with the swords in front of me
anymore? One, one, two, tap. What the heck? Dude, just fucking lock in and mash already.
Good advice. Actually just hit me in the door. I don't know how I did that before. Honestly.
All right. When no one's looking, why can I do it? Is there a move list somewhere? How do I get to
it? Library devil arms. Okay. Rebellion combo one. I know that rebellion combo too. I know that
helm breaker. I know this one. Yeah. I haven't, it hasn't taught me these. Okay. And I've been
doing that one. Here it is repeatedly press Y while executing a type two combo. So I have to
mash Y like this. It didn't work. Uh, you have to do it during the second. Okay. I think I got it.
Let me try it again. Nice. Okay. Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh. Starting to understand the game.
You know, I have to collect every, I'm, I'm, I, I'm, I'm an orb person, right? I always get a on
orbs. That's my thing. Your thing could, that's fine. Your thing could be gameplay and can be
getting S style and shit like that. I get S on orbs. I collect stuff. What's this thing?
Do I have to do something with this? This is a DPS check. Oh, I got two of those fragments.
What does this mean? Statue of the omniscient god of time and space. By offering a demon blood,
one can attain the power of the ancient magic plans. Power up. Exchange orbs for items like
vital stars. Exchange orbs to learn new moves or power up your guns. Oh, all right. Shit. What is
this going to do? High speed lunge attack skewers them through the center.
So you have to be running while you do it. Is this one lightning quick sword swing that
sends a powerful shock wave. I like that. $10,000. Okay. So this one is I can upgrade it.
So hold that and forward and then press Y. I feel like I should get some of these.
I could buy a blue orb. Okay. What do four of these do? I'm going to get a couple of these.
Is that dumb? I don't know. My new move seems pretty good. Can I combo it?
Kind of. Ice guardian's chamber. This thing. I think this is probably going to be a boss fight.
I think how many viewers did you have when you started? Um, it was 70,000 people here.
I lost like a lot though. People with it. I took, I took a long time with the tutorial,
so that's all right. All right. Do you mean ever? Cause that's not correct.
Do you mean like when I first turned the screen on ever? I don't know.
I came from a different position in the. Hold on.
Thank you for a walk. Come on, puppy. Let's go. Is there enough silence? Worm. Incident.
What are you doing? What's that move? Okay. Wow. I think you have to break the ice off the heads.
What does this happen? You can't even hurt this thing. You got to break the ice off.
That's very, yeah. See, I can't get close though. That's like death. If I get close.
I don't know why I'm even trying it. Stop using guns. When I get close, I get scared.
The guns suck. Stop using them. My theory. Correct, bro.
Hey, is my theory correct? I need to know his moveset is.
Devil may cry free in stores at Walmart. Now pre-order for the devil may cry collectors
edition with a life size Dante poster. Devil may cry free available at Target today.
Do you guys hear that? That was word. I'm probably going to add. Sit down. Sit down.
Come on. Come on. Look at this combo. Holy shit. It's like a 600 combo.
Oh, fuck I got cocky tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap
Wait, wait, whoa
Come on get it. Holy shit. I'm getting what am I doing? What's happening here? I'm getting I'm getting so sucked up
Okay, we're good. We're good. I was just through so bad
I love this voice
What's that thing? Nunchucks. Well, that's my new weapon for sure
Three-sided nunchuck. I'm never using the sword ever again
Orbs yep, that's me. I collect orbs. Where are they? I lost orbs. What? Would they despawn?
I was testing my new weapon. They got a figure that you're gonna do that when you get it. Just testing my new moves though
Are you going to the park? What's the hurt you get an invitation?
This was the part where I walked out of the theater
No, I would stay
Hey
Look at that
See for orbs. How that's not even how did I lose out on?
Did I actually lose out on a lot? It was a lot hum. It was like 2k. Are you kidding me? Bye
I'm supposed to be the orb guy and I couldn't even do my couldn't even do my job that I'm supposed to be doing
Oh, that's bad. Oh
Well, it's okay, how come all my titles have that three face like we mod keeps doing that so I want to know who
For a second, I thought this guy's clothes were on backwards
I thought he was wearing a jacket like the other way. No, that's not how I don't know
Why my brain just thought that for a second. I was like, wait, does he have his shirt? Oh, no, it's like a suit
Like a all the way up suit. All right. Do I want to change anything?
How am I still level one trickster? You're like that's I'm gonna be in a mobile game. I don't want to be a level one trickster
I'm curious
revolver level two
Windmill I can do a windmill
Spin the nunchucks around in a propeller like motion to rapidly slice into the enemy. I like that
Not enough orbs. Yeah
Yeah, don't remind me
I'm alright for now. I'll try this new stance though. This is the PC version. This is the part of the HD collection
This level is going to take you two hours
Is he saying that because they just introduced the map system map goes off your surrounding area from an overhead perspective
Interesting. Okay. It shows a graphical image from the room you currently occupy. Yeah
Press the d-pad to view the various floors you have visited
So I get it this is where I am and this is where I'm going I get it I'm Tays inferno
Redditor wrong game
Wrong entire series. I don't know why I keep saying that there a double jump. No
You got to be really just strict with you have to go like, okay
Okay, this is a lot harder than it looks
There we go. That's actually a lot harder than it looks. I'm actually kind of surprised. I just did that this door
Dope Oh
Red door means enemies Dante press B
I like the nunchuck during a certain circumstance you can repeatedly press a button to execute a special high-speed combo attack. Yeah
Okay, so that has to be with the sword. Oh, dude. Yeah, I'll do it. You know, you know, it's not a weapon switch now
You gotta come back to the stream. He knows what he's doing now
Bro, I told you I was going to eat dinner like fucking 40 minutes ago. Stop messaging me
Did you see my last message stop? You just messed up my combo. Where is this person? All right, that's not fair
They're in a weird spot and I can't change the camera. Everybody else hit hit wall. Hit hit. All right
That's too advanced for me. Do more static X's. Hey, it was my birthday yesterday. Can you Elmo for me?
I'm sorry. I have a strict policy where I can only do an Elmo if it's somebody's birthday today
Right now being with the will of the thunderstorm. I bestow the soul of steel
I'd do like a magic spell on this one
So I gotta go up that way
Not over here. Does the map tell me where I'm currently standing or is that just the room I'm standing in?
Okay, so that little indicator does not tell me where I'm standing. That's just I thought the little yellow diamond was where I was standing
So what do I get for doing this?
Just money and then have to come back and do an electrical spell to that thing
Okay, this way's too much how can I break these
Of course I can you think the Lakers are gonna win tonight. I will give you a prediction. I think the
Lakers are gonna take it
95 to
You're gonna lose money if you bet that number. I don't even know what the context but yeah
Hey, buddy, I don't know if I would do that. I wouldn't take that bet
We understand this the streamer
Who hasn't watched a basketball game since he was 14?
So I told me that's very sad. Oh
You just ruined everything that was that was really sloppy. I
Cleaned it up at the end
That like a parry or something. Let's go. It's a combo extender the orbs
Who was it Lakers even playing right now?
I don't even know the answer that question playing Denver. Look at mod for a score update right now. Oh
It's a hundred and eighteen to 104 Lakers are down right now
Don't yeah, do not bet that they can't take points away in basketball. Yeah, I'm coming in
I'm just uh, I want to put a bet down on the game that's going on right now. Sure
What what can I do for you? Yeah, I get that lake is gonna take it I think 95
9586 um
You want you want to take that you bet that's what you're betting right now
Yeah, it's that Lakers gonna take it sir. I
I'll take the money
Um, I can make that jump. What are the odds on that again? It's like guys. I got 15 to 1 20 21
Well, sir, the odds are that right our zero. That's all right stuff. That's our how fucking still do it. You sell cigarettes here
I'm gonna fall off this look at my health. What?
That was annoying. All right, we got a
Okay, how am I supposed to deal with that?
Damn, this is horrible. It's horrible
No, I want to target. I want to customize the controls
I don't like the pressing in left stick to change kind of annoying to do having to push left stick in to change target
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, I don't like it. You kill me. I'll be very upset. Okay, we're good
Off-screen enemies won't initiate attacks. It's a balance
That's actually really good
Where am I going I can go up through this door or right back I'm gonna go up right? Oh, man
We had a boss again. I like that though. I
Really like that
Although I really don't like having no help
How far back is the checkpoint if I lose here? I'm kind of concerned. Is it just that door?
All right, so don't waste the help
All right, you got to do it in sections
We'll go sword for this too. Hey, where's the guy that goes?
Okay, what do you can I fall down? Oh, I can I thought it was death I want to turn him red
He's kind of looks like ribs. Yeah. All right, you turn him red
Then he hides away
Then go back out
Okay, so unironically I have to jump on top
That was good
unironically
Shit I missed come on. Sorry. I'll get it. Try the V attacks. Oh shit. I'm Tazin Burnham
Somebody complained about the refs of the Lakers game in here. All right, this isn't that bad. I think I get it
Can we do a poll?
Who do you guys want to win Lakers or Denver? It's definitely gonna be the Lakers, right?
What's going on right now?
Things were going really well until
Five seconds ago. All right. Somebody said they hate this boss now. I understand why
Where where are you? Yeah, what does this jumper remind me of? It's like it's super sticky
It's like a straight up straight down. I feel like I weigh seven million pounds. That wasn't bad over here
I'm gonna heal
Like most of chat voted for the nuggets because they're hungry do not let these despawn. Oh
Good a good helping a chicken nuggets. That sounds pretty good
That was cool. So there's one direction. I didn't go which is this way
Is it not going the right way? I wish I could tell if I was facing north or south. Try B button on nunchucks
Seems kind of good
astronomical board powered by time
Normally 15 minutes left in the game, right? No, I don't kidding
Somebody said he wants to stop playing so bad. No, I'm I'm fucking around. I'm having fun
Your tricks
Here's that big nose
Just hear me out you got nothing to lose, right?
My name is Jester and I know a thing or two about this place
That thing there
Is a power generator for this entire sector in order to open
The door you need to apply a little something. Looks like you and my teeth aren't that nice
Is what the something is remember that kid write it down on your hand if you don't trust your head
You
Guys understand what I have to go through just to brush my teeth in the morning you still piss me off
That's just how it is
BBC DS brushes his teeth in the shower. Sometimes you can save a lot of time
CBD gamer
Alright, okay. I need to see them all so I'm gonna pick royal guard you save two minutes by brushing your teeth in the shower
and help
Don't be humble just take it
Whatever you've done
You could see the conclusion of this battle if you pre-ordered devil may try three
Collectible art booklet included. How do you deal with birds like that? It's like that
The hell I do it. Oh, I have a different move right?
My brain has so much trouble with multiple button context menus
Like holding right bumper and pressing X and then hitting like left trigger and then pressing Y
And then pressing in left stick and then switching. It's a lot of combinations
It's a lot of combinations that are just across the whole map. I dodged it the wrong the exact wrong time get over here
crazy good
Get that up to a where's that thing old why with the sword launch?
Came out in 2005 I forget just how old this game really is kind of forget. Wait, I have to fight him
I thought it was my friend
God, all right. Watch out for the work shit. I
Just got that was good. I can't even move
Watch out shit my name
Why is it
Oh
All right, how do I hear what's he'll what's he'll what's he'll what's he'll what's he'll all right, it's up on the d-pad
That was a tick-tock. Oh
So now I'm starting to understand why people like this game so much
Let me give you my first impression after an hour or two. This game is its bosses
You just fight a shitload of bosses. Is that correct?
It's just run down a hallway and fight a few things, but then fight the boss. I like games like that
I enjoy them. I like fighting against bosses. I can't go this way. Can't jump down you fight a few things and make it look cool
Where am I going?
Straight and then straight does that make sense? Is your taunt and your pause the same for some reason?
Uh, I can answer that so I'm pressing select because in my mind
See in my brain in my brain. So my brain does this thing in my mind
They forget about like the sentence that I say for every other sentence
This is the map
Like this is come on. I'm trying to press I'm trying to open the map
Or like a sub menu and then I realize it's start and then in the start menu. He does this thing with his mind
Get it again. How do I get across this? I can't get across that the orbs here. I didn't get
Just go it's fine. Oh, we bring it back the just go meme. That's an old one. I remember just go
That's an old one. Okay
Is it fall damage?
All right. I think I want the windmill hold down right bumper plus back and press apply. I
Don't want to waste too much money
How many of these do I have? How come I only have two blue orbs didn't I have three?
I thought I had three fragments. Oh
I bought a I bought a blue orb. What can I even do with it? Damn it. It's expensive. It's just more health bar. Oh
Very cool. I'm saving my money. I am gonna buy
one more of these I
Know this is so look at how stupid this is now. It's just gonna keep going up
I know you just spit out your food and you were eating a taco and you just made a mess everywhere. I'm sorry
You just could not believe what I just did and it fell down and went into the couch. You're sitting on
Down into like the crevice next to you, which always sucks. It's like, okay, that's food
I have to go fucking find that and it's gonna take me probably
20 minutes to get it all cleaned up because it went down into the fucking couch
Especially with something like lettuce. Oh
Man, it's gonna stick to something at the bottom of the you're gonna it's gonna be awful. It's like you like an hour
Okay, I wanted these something else open too. Where was it? I saw it. It was an item right there
Has this happened to you an ornament, okay
Has this happened to you? Yes, this happens very frequently and it's always I I
Eat a lot of meals on the couch. I actually prefer sitting on the couch and eating things like dinner
I just feel like it's better that way. It's like just I love it. Just like alright, I'm sitting on I got I have a table
But something about eating just sitting on couch
Is so good
I'm missing something here
What's up that on TV? You give you got a TV there?
What's the what am I doing now?
Let me pay attention for a sec. Can I go up there?
All right, I gotta go up there. Yeah sitting down putting on
That's what I I will tell you when I talk about
Oh, yeah, when I watch this other person's stream or I watch the streamer or I watch a YouTube video or a TV show. I
Wish I was making this up
I've been eating food
Every single time I mentioned this I opened up a wall down here. I wasn't it was I picked it up right here
It was right there
What does it go though?
down here
Like what is this? Wait, I don't know
blue door
Didn't I go in the blue door though? Yeah. Hold on
That's a very weird jump this way. Oh
I mean, it's alright. It's alright. I don't love it
Can't say I like it. Are we useful in some places? Yeah, but I'm what I'm saying is every piece of media
I've ever watched or ever consumed I had food in front of me. What does this do?
It is actually a parry the parry block. Okay. Oh, yeah, where do I put it in here? I
Put that somewhere
This goes up. Oh
Right. Okay, right, right, right
For some reason I did not think this had three prongs. I thought it was one. It's a fork man
Come on, we didn't say Gwen afterwards. So I don't understand what you wrote
Essence of a powerful and fearless soul eating ice cream while moderating, you know what challenge I'd love to see
You know, you see speed running no hit speed run fastest time
I want someone to beat Elden Ring while holding a soft serve ice cream cone
And they have to like lift the sides and by the way you get points off for all the drips on your hands
How fast is the Elden Ring speed run right now like 12 minutes? I think you could pull that off a
new category
cone percent
Wait, please have a hair cam. No, no, not tonight. What about a door cam?
What about one naked cam? No, didn't we talk about one time?
If
What was it? It was like what would it be worth if I would have be like scream naked?
We try to come up with a number. We're not scream, right?
But like let's say I had like a platform where you could see me naked and I remember people like
What was this?
No, I'm not doing this
I'm just we were making a stupid joke about this a year or two ago and it was
What how much money would I make doing that?
Versus anything else and you guys convinced me that it would be insane. I was like, oh
You got to market it. It's literally free money, dude
No
Yeah, I'll do it. It's a free money. Don't how you know, I'll be so funny if you did that. Oh my god
I'll be wicked funny. Yeah, I'll be laughing my ass off if you did that Jerma
Please please please please god, please if there is a god, please if there is a god, he'll do it
Please if there is a god, I know what you're doing
You don't think I fucking see right through you bullshit. All right. Now, where do I go? I got that soul thing
Can I go in this door crimson flames twist and dance around the door keeping all would be trespassers at bay
back to the bridge room
Bridge room is all the way around. Although can I can I go left? I
Guess I get a green door
Do I go I'm this
Can get that I can get up there I can definitely get up there
Shit fucking hard
They wouldn't change the camera angle if you weren't supposed to be over here in a wall jump
It's kind of hard to do though. I'm honest jump up on the other pipe
I'm trying
My whole body wants to just move
Okay, what I need to go into that little door into that little crevice right there
It's just so the those of you that played this game. You know how this jump is
It's like I don't know I can't even describe it. All right, what the hell is that it I got it
There's nothing else for me here to go to how do I get out of this? Let me see. Yeah, there's nowhere to
There's another door
Where's the other door? There's the green one here
Other side of the fence
Go to the yellow door. You mean the one in?
Hold on. I'm getting confused
I'm gonna go up there
Goodness
Thank goodness. Let's go. I
could
How would you have known you could do this without me literally reading it in chat?
How would I ever know you could do that? You have to read it. I am the combat
Adjudicator only a technique. I see cool to the core. Well, look what I got
Come on I have two moves to do
These aren't cool enough for you
There it is. Okay one more of those and I'm good
You're in the soul of steel
Inside of every collectible pre-order box of devil may cry for
Is the soul of steel plastic toy you could claim your own it also comes with a
10 inch tall figure of Dante himself. What did I just do?
Secret mission. Oh
I don't think i'm gonna be able to do that. Oh my god. Let me get the sword out goodness. Okay, fuck off
Oh
My god, I had it. It's just like I fucking was in sludge. Oh, I was in sludge
I was in sludge. I when you locked on and you walk you walk
You don't run and I just was walking in quicksand
I got it orbs speaking of orbs. I just got a new one
Oh
Bottle is now a permitted term
For now until I well, I just said that so now it's gonna be gone
What is this behavior? This is behavior we're seeing over here
You guys supposed to be you guys must behave
All those orbs are missing
Ah, that sucks
Okay
Wait, I want those orbs
Try the parry
I think i'm probably gonna go back to trickster
Having a dodge roll is just so so good
That was not bad
You gotta be shitting me
That's just a lot of meter or whatever you want to call it. They having fun. Yeah. No, this is great
I'm just hanging out and playing i'm having a good time
um
Sorry, i'm paying attention to fighting am I supposed to get off?
I need to kill them faster
They need to get off. Oh shit
I got it. We're good
Let's go for it. They're weighing the elevator down
Oh my god
At the very least I have to change the lock on button
It's making my life a living hell right now
Can I do it through here? Please tell me I can do it through here. Thank goodness. Okay
Change target. What do I want to do item is up
Map is right change target. I don't know. What if I make that?
I I don't think there is a better button maybe one of the triggers
But I definitely don't want change going to be left stick. Oh, that's not bad
Oh, that's actually not horrible. Yeah, actually, but I have to take my finger off
I'm gonna take my hand off them. Actually, he's not great in theory. It seemed like a good idea though. Appreciate the help
Honestly, even right stick would be better. I think i'm happier with right stick because then I can do
I think yeah, that makes more sense to me. That's good. All right, let's go
It's a hard game
Are you speaking in simlish? No
Give me the shotgun for this too
I honestly probably shouldn't even lock on anybody
All right. This is
This is this is very
Like you get knocked off the
God only use neutral inputs. I'm trying to knock them off with the uh that but that's probably a bad idea
I'm just gonna stand in the middle
Don't move
Die already
There we go. Finally took me long enough
Break everything
All right. All of you devil may cry
lore masters
What what should I realistically get next?
air hike it's 20k
I'll save for air hike. I'll hold on. I'll hold on
What if I got windmill part two?
What does holy water do?
End off demons. It severely damages enemies
Very what is it gold or magic golden stone made by a secret process can recall lost souls
Don't buy anything don't buy anything. Okay, it gets you drunk
It's
It's an extra life. That sounds great
Items are for cowards
What is
How long are you two gonna keep carrying on like this
In case you didn't get the hint i'll spell it out your guest
Wants to go through
Got it enough
Give me one
Oh, they are way smaller. I thought they were huge
Let's go. Come on
All right back up back up back up back up
Walking should be illegal for the enemies to do in video games
Oh
Oh, who am I attacking here?
Shit i'm trying to just get rid of one
I'm dead. All right. I gotta I gotta burn one down quick. Does it count that I all right? I gotta burn one down
Very very fast
I'm gonna go with the green guy
Come on
guard break
I thought I said
Um, this is very hard
Okay, I got it. Oh, I could change my style. I'm not even using this thing
All right, got one break guard break guard break
How do I heal? All right, let's go. Uh, so they
All right. This is
Not great. I don't know
Okay. Thanks for the thanks for the heads up
Get up got it. That was hard
Yes
Okay, but on one condition what is it name it no talking
No talking
Whoa, they think all right. I want to use these I don't care what any other weapon is
This looks he's a cool
I don't know. I kind of I think I would want to
I would want to talk don't you think you'd want to ask a few questions just pass the time a little
I would be the annoying one to them fire
And tornado
Okay, you can only have two different weapons at a time
Got to change it up. So what do I have? I I can't change that now, right?
I'll try it instead of the sword. I had that had to been much better
what
Yep
Okay
All right
Hey
I got the orb. That's all the matters, right?
Hey, dude, do you want us to disable the tweet command because you yeah, I mean
I just have to tweet anything else. I I might just write
I don't know. I'm writing like oh, hello. I'm
Oh, hi is my tweet. That's uh, wow
Uh-huh
Tweet about the lakers game
Be like I can't I can't fucking understand what's going on. Just pull out like five random players
And be like, I don't know what fucking happened there
The three pointers tonight from they weren't very good
Is that a cannon that thing looks pretty crazy
There it is. Yeah, that's what I want. I I want a cannon. I hope I can get this item
You're saying this is a ps2 game was three still in the ps2 era. That's kind of remarkable if that's
Is that real?
Wow
I it does look like a pia. I was wondering the cutscenes are a little
a little scratchy around the edges
I was wondering
I did. Yeah, that's ps2
That's kind of unbelievable
All right. Well, i'm definitely going to try
Let's try these
All right, i'm gonna buy these until I have no more money left and then turn my power button on my computer off until
I turn it off
And then just and just leave
All right. I want to test these out
So you put them together
Do they have a backswing move?
I guess I could go look right
Okay, so
Why why why why why why why pause why why why pause why pause?
Why and then just in midair forward on the stick and why I still have this?
So type three combo is what I have to use this with
So I need to I need to do why pause why pause why why why why why why let's try it
That is
When do I start to mash it
After the second pause
My goodness, that's insane
The regular combo is good, too
On second pause why pause why pause
The upgrades make this weapon fun
Okay
Can I move this?
Whoa
Where did those come from?
I don't think I have enough I could try it on jet stream level two
Uh, should I get air hike for this?
Did you tell your mother's happy mother's day? I did passing one trial still shows lacking
Passing two expands horizons passing all three unlocks true potential
Your wisdom we put to the test your technique to the test and then your warrior's heart the test
I'm gonna go here. See how smart I am. That was easy. All right in a game scenario
This is actually hard to do because I think these enemies are just horrible
Yeah
They're all fucking room full of them. I want to start this room over actually. Yeah start over
All right
So these have little lit this this is one four and then three one two three four read the hint
Use your lifetime experience from the crawling infant to the man standing tall and finally the old man leaning on his cane
infant tall man old man infant infant
What is in which one of these is an infant? He's already seen it in chat. It's too late. Yeah, it's too late
Yeah, I'm I was pretending to walk around and not know where I was going. I was like, okay
Infant tall man where and i've read it a minute and a half ago at least hey, look at that. There it is
I won't read chat anymore. So I got an m. What is it a blue gem? What is that thing? So I got it
So can I just just go wherever? All right, i'm not going to reach half of this one
I'm just going to try to do it overcome the onslaught of obstacles to guarantee your future
All right. All right, so that's when you gotta go like right here. Oh my god. Wait, did those hit me?
Those don't hit me
I thought the one's pointing down we're gonna hit I got it
I gotta break it. Can I turn this back on and maybe get them hurt?
I hate these fucking flying motherfuckers without I hate them. I hate these things
This is one once I attack one another one's already attacking me
Oh my
I hate these fucking things. I have one
hp and
I already did it that counts. Okay. Does this have anything that I need to read light all the crests
I think this is just a fight dying is actually a speed run strat. That's funny. Okay, let's go. Whoa, look out. Stop walking
Go all this guy doesn't walk
I think I have to turn these on die
I was at s2 shit. Is it on timer? I need to do that move
Why pause why pause why pause? I can't pull it off
What the fuck? I'm gonna lose
I have to sit here and practice this move until I can do it without thinking about it
Why pause why pause why pause?
Like that, right?
Why pause what?
All right. I have to get this down. Otherwise, i'm just gonna take the weapon off
Why?
It's why why why that's it there, but I I want to do the thing you do you spin him around like crazy
Yeah, why pause why pause why why why why why why what i'm doing won't work. It's longer pauses
Yeah
You're doing why pause why why why pause why pause why why why why why why why
Yeah, but aren't I supposed to mash after the second pause to do the follow-up? I feel like I just did the same thing
All right, so it's okay it's much slower I think I got it let's do it if you're playing at 60 fps
You have to mash really fast. Oh
Is that actually true? Okay
Why pause why pause why why why why why there it is? Oh, that was it
You really don't want to do for that long though. You're just vulnerable
Okay, well, let's go. So I'm I'm I need to light these up, right?
Focusing on trying to learn how to do that move and not play the game
Whoa
All right, let's go
Watch out
Do it. Oh my god. Those guys are fucking horrible. I might die again
Jesus they powered up. I gotta get powered up too then they're invincible unless I spin the wheels
That's what I was thinking too. I was like why are these guys so fucking horrible?
It has to be something to do with this goddamn wheel
Much better. All right, I think I can't hurt them again. Yep. There we go. I feel much better about this now
All right last part hit it. I'm so paranoid. They're gonna hit me
Okay, be careful here. Oh my god. You are the worst enemy in the fucking game
You're worse than the bat whatever they are the bat thing. Shit didn't do it fast enough
Am I hurting them?
Whoa
Don't get out of the way. I want to hit this thing
Holy shit. That was really really wacky. Somebody said finally ban that person or let's go all in a month
And now what passing one trial still shows lacking. Okay, so I did three right? What do I put them? They go in like a
All right, do I want this on the regular sword? I don't know. These are fun. It's for any weapon
Oh wait, it's for every weapon. Does it carry over? I'll get used to these
I feel like these are gonna be better. I'm sticking with these. I gotta get used to it and maybe it'll be better
All right double jump. Wow, that makes this so much better
That's amazing. So I did that put them all in okay a gun of the demon world that discharges arrows
It's a gun. Ooh, i'll try it. Oh, okay
Thank you
The gunslinger gun, otherwise, it's not great
Oh, look at I only have 700 orbs. That's not a lot. I'm playing on trickster
You point a gun at me your own kid
Your dear papa the only family I ever had was my mother
And she's dead
You break my heart
after all
It was I who gave you your name
One day a game or a movie will have that happen but it'll hit him right in the face
Plenty of orbs. I got plenty of orbs
Imagine getting a b
Because you didn't use any items and collected it all the stuff
You got a b for perfect attendance
That's what it feels like
Well, this is my kind of rain
No wonder the sky looks so funny today. Let me go
Let you go, but it would be a waste if you ended up with just a pretty stain
It did happen
Here I am trying to help you and you show your thanks by shooting me
Whatever choose you please
So he's a demon, too
I'm beginning to think i've got rotten luck with women
Okay, uh
I try these
I'll give them a try see if they're any good
All right. Let's take a few break. I'll be right back
I'm back in place some more. Did anybody know how how long is this game? The first one was
Like eight hours or so are they all kind of like
Seven to ten. It's 20 missions 20 chapters
Just was curious
I will be right back
Uh, I can't really alt tab. So you're gonna have to be left with this on the brb screen. Unfortunately
Oh, well, it didn't matter. I will be will this work? Let's see
All right, i'll be right back. What is going on? What's up?
It's back on
Well now you can hear it
There we go. Oh, I forgot I was supposed I gotta clear my throat before I say anything
Hey ordered a dork cube years ago with your promo code or still haven't received it
um
Yeah
I don't think I can't afford anything either. So i'm gonna go
Try the new weapon
Can I charge it?
Find out normal shot. I guess not. Yes. It's just a regular shoot weapon. Whoa need to level gunslinger
That would make sense. It's 20 missions in every devil may cry except for one and five
Okay, is the quesadilla just a really thin taco you're asking the real questions tonight, I think no, I don't think so
Sorry, I was reading chat
Wait, whoa. Whoa, there's a lot of stuff down here. Look at this. Look at all these orbs. I gotta get all these
What else is up here?
Just going all the way up
There were at least five people that said to ban that guy i'm also realizing something very important about myself
I need these to be switched and i've been playing for like three and a half hours already
But I have to change this it makes way more sense
I can't believe that guy got banned for a month for what he said
I know
me either attacks. Damn it. Damn it
I wish that staggered you're bad at chess. Yeah, I am. I know that. Oh nice. Hey, did the lakers lose? Uh,
Baby, did they? Oh, what if what if somebody t voted though? I don't want to spoil it for them, right?
If somebody t voted we don't want to they might want to watch it later out of that. That's a lot of people
Dude, come on. I just got full health
You guys are all standing in a good five foot square around each other. I can't get in there
I just went right into it. Watch out. Do jump x jump x jump x. Okay. Those guys had trillion health
secrets
Ah, you can only do the double jump when it's active. That makes sense. I get it
But this bird I thought this person said do you have a super ball under your chair?
I'm trying to figure out what the hell that was supposed to mean magic essence. Oh, I can't get into this one
Damn it. Nice. This is what the elevator is. That's the elevator control power panel
I gotta go put that thing that other gem in that slot. No, that doesn't go there
Tom's flames. Oh, I know what that is. Can I go back to there? There's a door with the fire on it
I think that's where I gotta go. All right, come on
Okay, so
Where is that place? Can I even get back there from here? Okay, I think i'm going the right way now. I hope so
Steam, uh, yeah, this is the pc port part of the hd collection. Honestly, this is my favorite weapon so far
I think it's the best one
Yeah, I like it the most for sure back to the elevator that I was thinking of doing
Will you do anything else besides the third game?
I I probably will just play them all at some point. I have to imagine
They're not particularly long games. Not like it's like oh my god
It's gonna take me like a month to beat it a couple of streams per game probably that makes sense to me
All right. So that's a power source for the elevator
Just skip two. I feel like everyone's telling me how bad two is
Everyone's like oh, no, no, no, no, no, you get away from two. Don't play two
I almost want to play it because keep I keep seeing people say such awful things about it
Can I go into two with the mindset of i'm gonna play it for an hour and just not care?
Would that be okay?
And look if I play it and i'm like, holy goodness. This is really awful and i'll just stop playing it. Not a big deal
All right, let's try to get a perfect here well it was there but I screwed it up stop
Oh my goodness
Does this game have any bathroom humor? Um, I don't think so
Maybe no
Is that your criteria for if you're gonna buy the game or not? Where's the bathroom humor, dude?
You're better than this. It's more dad joke humor. I can say that
devil may cry 2 gets boring very quickly once you realize how effective bullet spam is just overall not fun encounters
piece and take
It's a good take I think what's bathroom humor stuff like this like if I were to make a big
From your understanding, why are these games titled devil may cry?
So because i'm dante from dante's inferno
And there's a demon that i'm going after and I am so good
I am so
I'm so talented and i'm so dangerous that the devils are the the devils are afraid of me
So oh dante's coming. Ah, he's gonna kill us
Everybody like that's what I think like devil may cry
Because whoa dante is very scary
That's how i've always viewed this
Let's get in there
And even you can do combos like that if you put your dante's inferno free, okay, I don't think I can
Come on
How do I get out of here
Okay
Oh is actually that I actually had to do that. I would have stuck here for a while. Come on gwen. Come on gwen
I like that. That was a good chat. That was a good message. Did I do it? I don't think I did it
I don't know what I let's do it again
I think if I break the statues that's what I would be doing
Is it not smash into these statues that do I just would break the ball?
It's glowing in fact, I just heard that
That like child laughing sound effect
Oh, I get it. All right, you guys know that the stock laugh sound they're like
Yeah
I can't do it
I'm fine
No, I like I want to see where i'm fucking swinging this thing
How do I get the camera to go this way?
Popular stock sound effect is it there it is
That was it. You've never heard that before. No, no way. You definitely have you just didn't process it
All right, turn the camera
No, stop. I want to face this direction
Dante
Dante, please
Just hit it. I am
It's a it's not a physics puzzle
I'm not supposed to break the statues or break. I was saying that too. What you guys told me I had to break the door
All right. I'm never looking over here again
Oh my god
I don't want to do this again
How far away am I right now? What is going on?
Where what's happening right now? What's going on? Where am I? Why did they put me all the way back here?
He asked if it was hard and then a laughing face
Oh, it's over here
This is hard
Yeah, it is
Can I just do I have to do any of this? I guess I don't
Okay
I'm good. Can I leave? No, I can't I have to be
And how come they get to queue up a swing during the cutscene and I don't
Unfair my lord
Is there a mod to make the lock on better?
Can I please install one pushing in the stick to change enemies is
Is driving me insane, especially when there's so many enemies in a room to have to switch between
Having to press the stick in makes me want to throw up one and it and it picks a random fucking person
What a drama queen. It makes me want to throw up blood. This lock on is so bad. It makes me want to puke blood
Whoa?
It he's always so dramatic
I'm trying to think of any other
Hold on. This is the only scenario where you can talk like that
Right. This is the only scenario where you could where that people I mean it was a weird thing that I said
But in any other scenario, it's like what the fuck is this person talking about?
Can you imagine going to the doctor and you have like a wart on your finger?
Hey doctor, I got this ward on my finger. Let me take care of that. I I I can get that ward off
They're very hard though
Oh kid
That's this thing. This thing's really giving us some trouble here. Hold on still. Let me just get that word up
This is so hard. Just makes me want to fucking puke blood
It's like, uh, all right
Didn't you have a ward on your finger? No, it was a gamer boil and I want you to get it right
Get out of the way
Oh fuck. Let me out of here. I mean that made me just want to puke blood
What did I get for doing that? What was it? What was the point of this?
I got the thing right. What did I just pick up?
What did I pick up this thing right here? Right now this goes in that other side. It has to back
up this way
Back to where the elevator is
I gotta get these
It's time finally
The people that are writing that I just want to make sure you understand
Um, i'm not going to tolerate it. I mods what I want you to do anybody that says finally
I'm not going to tolerate it. I would like for you to start timing people out
For exactly five seconds every time they say that and if they do it again
Then I want you to time them out again a second time
All right. I have to play the fucking video game
I gotta go all the way up. I just keep seeing things shining on hold on. It's the yellow door, right?
Wait, can I actually
Can I go this way?
No, where's that elevator? I kind of just appeared in this room. How do I get out of here over here, right?
Oh, right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. The camera was weird. I already got that i'm doing that the hell
No, this is wrong
This is wrong. No, it's just right. That's right
Oh, he does a backswing
one two three
Oh shit rematch
How do you pull off a guard break or does it just a certain amount of damage when they're guarding
Oh, that does not work here. Yeah
10 000 why are you attacking him when he did nothing wrong? I had to
Hey, sorry, I had to fuck him up, okay
Oh, this is weird. Oh, it's worth doing anything right now. Probably not
Yeah, it's all right. You probably need to be a gun specialist to care about it
All right. This is the one here. It's definitely a boss. Am I happy with this?
I like the nunchucks
Yeah
Get streamed level two
I'm not doing anything. Not yet kind of scared. What's through this door? Let's find out. This is the fight
You showed up
You sure know how to throw a party. No food
No drinks
And the only babe just left
my sincerest apology
I was so eager to see you
Somebody said well time to puke blood. Am I gonna get mad?
Uh-oh at any rate it's been a whole year since we last met kiss from your little brother kiss from this
This is what they call a heartwarming family reunion
I got this die
Yeah
I'm getting crossed up because I changed the this is what happens when this just this just kill me just kill me
Let me explain
Uh, let me explain
So the leftmost button
Can we all agree?
the leftmost button
Of the face buttons i'm talking ab x y whatever the leftmost button
Should always be attacked right like just like swing weapon always
It wasn't that
I halfway through the stream changed it to that
And now i'm getting crossed up shooting when i'm swinging and I should have just done it
I should have fixed it in the very beginning
X x x it's not y to attack. It's x it hit x
Sometimes i'll be like jump y it's like why did you do that blood?
Imagine you imagine saying that
You you you blood you go blood. Oh blood
That wasn't even a good one. That one sucked. My goodness gracious. Where's it? Where is it?
How do I just do it again? Where's the how do I hold down like r to restart?
All right, I got it
How did you hit me from all the way over here?
Oh shoot him. Yeah
Oh blood
You refused to gain power the power of our father sparta father
I don't have a father
I just don't like you. That's all
Oh, oh we saw this
Foolish fight controls everything and without strength you cannot protect
Back both arms out the spell spartacast will be broken. That's not the end of the game. So what happened?
We should leave for the most we have all that we need
Wait, we're not done yet. We have what we need plus he still hasn't done
Shine the light against the mirror and point that mirror at a different mirror
Shine the light against another mirror
my hardest
Fucking room yet
Lucifer spoilers, I got that so wrong. It's not even funny
All right
Oh
uh
Hey, i'll take a beat
He's boring beef of boring i'm doing style
Is
No, no not these I hate these
Why don't you fight like this too hard, huh, okay
Intrigued i'll keep what I got. I kind of want to upgrade these though. I'm doing it
At least once
I might even do it twice
That probably was
Insane what I just did you probably just are you can't believe what just happened
i'm doing it
How is this still level one?
I'm still level one
I gotta get to level two
Devil trigger unleash dante's true power need three
Gauges to transform into demon form. Okay, so it's left bumper and you press and hold left bumper. All right
That sounds kind of cool. Let's try i'm gonna find these
Dante's inferno
Puzzles like these mind
Ending puzzles await you
Get your pre-order in now
Knock it off. I have not heard knock it off
Knock it off. That's I've not heard that in a very long time
That's like the like the boys are over for a sleepover and we're talking a little too loud
And your mom, you know come it's kind of late you hear it. Hey knock it off boys
Um, okay. Okay, that's the knock it off. It's getting late. Ow, knock it off. I love that
I'm gonna start using that
Where the rest of this is open?
Hey settle down
Settle down eight settle down. Oh, just don't fall off
I can't hurt think I have to knock it off knock it off. Okay, the issue that i'm seeing here is
What was that move that I just did?
Okay, what I just I tried to hold it I can
I got like knocked out of it
I held it down and it didn't do anything
Oh
What?
Is that good?
Uh, this is a secret mission and I don't really want to do it
What? Okay. I'm pressing do I have to have three to turn it on?
How can I do it with one do I have to have all three turned on?
Okay, so all three have to be activated
It's the only way I can hurt anybody
This mission is awful and so you're really powered up
Yeah
How do I just i'm gonna die
Let's wait. Yeah. Yeah, kill me kill me. All right. Well, i'm not doing that one. It seemed pretty painful
I get up here. I think I can get up here
This is where I started or something. All right, there's one more of those things. Where is it?
The second door over here
This is where I came from
I have no idea where this is
I have to break it. Is he trolling?
No
Where do I even go?
Didn't I in the cave? Yeah, it wasn't it wasn't just in here. Yeah, I hit this one
And then I went this way and I couldn't go anywhere else
I can get off here
All right
What the heck? I wish I could move the camera so bad. I feel like uh, look he too is behind me
Anybody knows what I mean by that? What is that? I spent all my money on uh,
on
frivolous things that I didn't need oh dear this does not look good an organ rides ferociously on the other side of the
Membranous wall can't get any closer. Oh, yeah scared the shit out of me
Go why I can't run any faster than this
Come on
What? Hey, he just got whacked
Probably stinks in here
Yeah
Yeah, I would I would I would almost said I would hope so
I just got triple s. I've seen that before
All right. I think this is the big scary boss part. This is a weird zone when they cry
Come on man, let's go
What finally holy shit you love that spin I do I really do so much fun
Are you talking about that one? Yeah, I like it god damn it. I knew it was coming, too
People here now
Oh wait, I forget it's all dark now. It's a hundred. I don't know where I am. I think we're on the right way. Yes
Wait, no, I was told not to buy items. That would make me bad
Oh the combo was going so strong, too
Let's go
Shit, uh, my face is itchy open
Stop. Oh shit. Oh, he's just gone. This one's more about patience than anything else style up
Oh, whoa, what I do. Oh, okay. Cool. I can dash twice
Can I break through this if I hit it enough times or no, I got that I heard it
Can you read germa how am I supposed to read the chat and look over here at the same time?
Chat read what am I supposed to be reading? There's no text on the screen a little crazy
Uh, I need to just kill me
I wonder should I kill both left and right first or no?
No, I gotta clear the enemies out. That's too many
god
No, don't hit me from behind come on i'm fair still alive what oh come on
Oh my god, don't don't don't please don't
Break it break it. Oh, yes. All right, let's go. Nice a foundation that brought out
The right one has less health I think the weapon was a little more tanky
Rage and agonies of the people those who were confined here
With their desires for evil being unfulfilled
It was all because sparta slapped stealing devil trigger the world in their faces
What's wrong?
Yeah, it's still on normal
Late night stream cozy
Playing some game
You know
Really nice
All right
Haven't seen an a stylus yet
So much how am I so bad with damage though?
Damage at a d
Oh, it's how much damage i'm taking
That's like 50 000 damage. That sounds like a lot man. That's how much i've been taking
I would want to be friends with leviathan
How would I do that?
So this is the next stage
wait
If you're asking for a date
Forget it because I make it a point not to go out with women who shoot me in the head
Date a demon
I'm not that desperate
Besides, I really don't care for guys who stink like blood
You're right
Then what should I call you I don't care whatever you want whatever lady
I'll leave this to you
Because I don't want to miss the party
I'm gonna eat
I know i'm gonna call them souls, but that's the way it is
I want it. This is the
I don't care. I want it. This is my favorite weapon. So I have a question if my favorite weapon
Are currently it's the nunchucks
Should I
Do sword master will I get more if I do sword master trickster is good, but
You can jump cancel with level two
High energy stream
This is the lower energy stream
You're gonna have to level it up. Uh
Yeah, that's true. I'll stick with trickster. No
The game is very high energy
Yeah, but as long as I can turn
I don't know if I can turn my brain off
And focus a lot of times I usually can do okay
I mean d is still passing great
The time is there right now 11. Okay, maybe at the end of this section. I'll call over tonight. That'll get us on
Chapter 10, which is essentially perfectly halfway. I think that makes sense
Oh
They're not okay. They're not that bad. They're not as bad as I thought they were gonna be
They're still kind of weird, but whatever
I think it's way better now
Don't okay, it says there's a little wind up there
One more where is it? Is virgil playable? I would imagine
The answer to that question is yes. I don't know though. Wait, is that a mirror shine the light mirror?
Puzzle is that is that actually here? Is this for real? This is really in here
Oh, well, all right cool
Radiate the image sunken in the depths below to open a new path. It is a spin the mirror puzzle
How do I spin it?
How do I turn them oh I get it
He needs to use critical thinking skills. Yeah, but I thought that was I didn't know if there was a tilt button or something
Hit b on stuff. What does it even do for me? I got no money
Oh, I cannot go that way. What's for breakfast two sausage patties. Yep
two sausage patties and
Breakfast sausage patties by the way, one fried egg three four pieces of pineapple
Over medium. I don't like over easy. All right, so a few pieces of pineapple two
Sausage patties one egg could be all right. Well, these things hurt you on the edge
Ooh
You can extend that
Actually, I like hard-boiled eggs, but I don't like them after a day. I used to eat them all the time
I would make a dozen eggs. I'd get a carton of eggs
And hard boil all of them and I would eat two or three of them every single day for breakfast
And then sometimes I'd have another one or two later. This is when I was lifting because then I was going to the gym all the time
Uh, I would eat a lot of eggs and a lot of tuna fish. I used to eat tuna out of the can
as a snack, I would go to the gym and
I would do
You know
Backed and biceps, right?
And then I would eat a can of tuna
When I just got back
Why do you meal prep hard-boiled eggs?
Hard-boiled eggs are awesome for meal prep. They're great. They go with tons of stuff. They're really good
Not cooked and hard-boiled egg is boiled
boiled egg
Stop lying. I'm not I've talked about this like in an old video
From like almost 10 years ago
anchovies, I I
You know what? I talked about this a lot
Anchovies not anchovies sardines sardines are really really good
If you can get over
What what it is you're doing right? You're eating they're just in a can
Did I just walk backwards while talking?
Oh, there it is ambrosia
The most delicious of the gods the most dessert that only the gods eat
Fruits covered in whipped cream and fucking marshmallows
Only the gods will eat this
And make sure make sure it's been sitting out for at least 12 hours
And by the way, even when you put it in the fridge in three or four days go by
Take it out of the container and just it's the same. It doesn't matter. We'll eat it a week later
for the gods though
little candied marshmallows
The mucky bag turn it on quick. You can pick it
Oh no
If you can get to an s rank combo, I will
Well, i'm gonna i'm not gonna read the first part but I want to tell you that i've done that probably 30 times already
So that's gonna happen. Oh, I want to try something. Can we try something weird?
That's gonna take some effort here. I want to try something
So this is a fun experiment that I've wanted to try for a little while. It doesn't work to this music though
It needs to be a little more relaxing
I want the mods to
record
with
You know to log all the responses and i'm curious if there's a
i'm curious if everybody sort of has something that they really care about
Or something that they really want right now
and without thinking
But what the fuck what the fuck? No, no, no, no, stop. Stop. Listen
Like this music is speech jamming me. Hold on. It's like
I hold on. Let me turn this off
So when we think i'm i'm gonna say something and I want after I say this
I want the mods to keep a record of what everybody says
Yeah, just like oh what just what everybody's saying after when I say this I want everybody to right now
think of
So something that you a food item it could be a snack
It could be a dessert something that you want right now so bad that you're craving right now that you
Not your favorite food, but just what do you want right now? What would just do it for you right now?
What would be that thing that would do it for you right now? Cool. Yeah, not your favorite food
Not oh, well my top 10 just you know do this for me right now
In an italian sub just a cold italian sub. I want it so bad
It's interesting the reason the reason why I wanted to do this is because i'm curious as to how many people here
Have the exact same
Omega craving right now. Do you know what i'm saying? Because that that that's cool
How do you want us to log this?
Um, yeah, I just copy and pasted me and and did you have something that's let's say you like man
This is really specific, but I really want it
Uh, I want a piece of baklava right now and it did more than three or four people say baklava
Because holy shit look at that. That's a pretty interesting connection. I thought about it because it's
Food is one of those things where you get these cravings. But what what right now? What do you want?
Somebody's like for instance somebody said everything bagel. That's a perfect example of this experiment
Was there anybody else that said everything bagel put it on a spreadsheet
Yeah
Yeah, let's get on a spreadsheet and then i'm gonna go over it on stream the next time and how many people said certain things?
Does pizza have a hundred?
Does pepperoni pizza have ten and what had the most what had the least don't really need usernames?
But the specific thing that really specific thing that you wanted right now. I'm curious. We'll see how it works
You know what else I want to do I here's another interesting thing going over your steam game library
In alphabetical order now i'm one of those people that has I have a lot of steam games
I've had a ton of steam games pretty much every game you've ever seen me play
On video or on stream whatever right but a lot of them are not a lot of them weren't but go alphabetical on steam
And pick out every single game that you've ever bought that you ever kept
Why like how did you feel when you played that game? Why did you buy it?
What did you think of it?
Because there's a lot of weird just random shit that I think a lot of people have bought and did you beat it?
Why didn't you? I think that's fun. I have like 200 games to laugh my ass off. Yeah, that's kind of cool
Did you start a google survey? Well, I don't want no no
I don't want you guys to all do this
I'm just saying maybe I think it might be fun to do that on stream one day and just go over them
I have 800 games. Well
It'll take you a while
But don't you think it's kind of interesting to go back and kind of look at especially if you have a steam account that's been
More than a few years five plus ten plus years old
You get to sort of look back and be like what the what the fuck was I thinking back then?
What was the reason why I bought this and did I get what I wanted out of it?
I think it's interesting to do that or even like how do you feel even looking at the name of that game?
Nostalgia trip. Yeah, because I could we'll do one right now like devil may cry three
Okay, it's a game that I got because I knew I wanted to play devil may cry
Uh, it was a fun hack and slash game. I never played devil may cry and it was interesting
I started with the third one
And that's where I stopped because I never played any of these other games ever again and I uninstalled this one
Um at the end of this stream, which is really interesting that I did that
Um makes you kind of think about how you approach things in the future
Surprise pop quiz. All right. Well, maybe I need to look
surprise pop quiz
All right. What am I doing here?
No, i'm gonna i'm this game. I'm having a good time. I'm kidding
Seven days to die me and my sister played it and we were like whack but kept playing it because she loved zombie games
There you go. Exactly
Thank you for proving why the experiment is an interesting thing to do
Look at that and didn't you do what? How does that make you feel?
Isn't that like interesting?
I just walked in
I'm walk. All right. I
Am I going the right way or i'm just being an idiot?
Did you just discover introspection?
No, but when was the last time you looked at a steam game that you bought like eight years ago?
I I mean it's been a while
I'll stay on trickster
Oh look at over there
I have a bunch of porn games
Well, we know exactly how you felt when you are, you know, do you need to even tell us that?
How did I feel when I downloaded this one? Hmm. What was I doing? What was I thinking?
Maybe
I guess this one was
Because I really wanted to work it, you know
Have a little bit of me time
Oh, this one is too. This one's also me time
Hmm
He's going off the rails. No, that was funny
I got this one because I wanted to fuck the cheeseburger sub
Yeah
I was laughing so hard at some of those conversations
yesterday
It's this fuck mary kill for sandwiches. That's
That's so stupid it was just it was killing me last night. I was just thinking about how dumb that was
The other people that weren't here
Mary kill, how would you uh, do I don't if I need to tell you that?
I mean, this is a mature audience stream. Are you really asking me how how?
What do you mean? How?
Hold on wait, wait, we got one here
Fuck mary kill cold italian sub turkey bacon club or tuna tuna fish sandwich
This is easy. I think my game crashed millennia
Here we go
What's that from first person gets a prize first person that says it gets a prize
First person has to get a prize
Who got it? Who did it? Who did it? No, i'm serious. Who got it?
Who was the first person to write the s3 or dark souls 3 who got it?
You're getting a prize dragon breath 75. You just got a prize
Dragon breath. Congratulations. You just got a prize
What's the prize?
Um, i'm trying to figure that out
Pick any game on steam that's not train simulator in all the fucking three thousand dollar bundle and it's yours
It can't be like a ten thousand dollar like a bundle of like train train simulator or something
Sims 4 and the thousand dollar dlcs
Yeah, no, no, uh
No pornographic games either
They want pizza tower done
Uh, please allow, uh, please allow two to four months for delivery now. All right. How does this one work?
I don't think I can hurt her
All right. What am I gonna do? I'm gonna break something or do something here
I gotta I gotta break something, right?
All right. Hold on you got these have to like attack these things
Oh, there we go
No
Get out of here gotta throw them all that's fine
I'm gonna die. I'm dead. All right, i'm gonna set up. What's the best way to get the game? Uh, i'll figure it out
Let's do another one. Let's do let's do another one
All right. I'm gonna say a line and you need to get it right and whoever gets it right just gets a game on
Steam, whatever you want. All right, here we go. Ready?
I don't know. Oh, that's so bad. Come on. All right. I get so greedy here. It's it's stupid
Oh, yeah, it is late
I'm so greedy with this fight. I don't even know what it is
I'm probably gonna start over
I've been i've been literally paying attention to like 10% of this whole encounter
Just kill me i'll start over
All right, i'm gonna hum a song
You have to get the exact name of this song. It has to be to it has to be the exact name
No
My computer just turned off. Are we good? Am I still alive?
That was weird
What how did I get more help?
I'm really confused wasn't I trying to die?
I I don't know what just happened
Greedy again, it's so annoying
All right. I got all right actually just start over because I just keep looking over in chat and thinking about a song
I have to hum
Let's do this first and i'm walking in
Hit me
Okay category is old cartoons. What song is this from a show?
Oh
Cat dog, that's it. We said cat dog. I will accept cat space dog or cat dog one word. That was uh,
wolf
wolfie
515 pick a game on steam. We'll get it too
Latency difference. Yeah, that's true. Yeah the advantage of uh, I guess living in
Closer to the united states
paying advantage
All right time to pay attention for real honestly i'm gonna turn the volume up for me that's better
No, stop running away stop running away
Hey
Damn it no
God damn it
Oh my god, I had I forgot I had heels I got another one for you last one of the night here it is
This is a sound effect aka a voice line from a video game. It's an older video game. What game is it from ready?
Ready
I'm gonna type it in the mod chat ready
Ready? No one's gonna get this i'll win this one. No one's gonna get it
Ready? No, not even close. I'll get all right
I'm gonna give you the console because I think a lot of you are not in the wrong track here
N64 is the console ready somebody got it. No way. Holy shit. You actually got it. It's mischief makers
Boss fights and mischief makers every time they're about to hit you at least one of the bosses goes ready
The bird. All right. Well, that was uh, I believe that was
We're gonna see who was first
Do we have to confirm who it was?
You know what did only two people get that was there literally only two people out of 10 000 that got that right?
It was multiple
Okay
How many people?
How many people was it?
Any way to tell
After you said it a lot of people said it. Oh shit. I think it was kill the boss already. Yeah, I know I got you
I got it
I'd be I gotta be more patient with this
God damn it. I forgot about that shit
This is this is a this is a wash
On really go down. Oh, that was annoying. Stop running by the gods. You're annoying
What the fuck
3d but I got it. That's it. All right, so there were five people they got it. Oh my god
You think so
How did five people guess a fake game
What the fuck? Okay, the nevan
Dante can control bats by jamming on this curious guitar. Its sickle attack is deadly
I kind of want to try it. I'm starting to get it. I get it
I know why this is a very celebrated franchise. I get it
You gotta get it first and then gotta get into it anything else I can do here
Oh, but I want to make sure people still here apparently five people got mystic maker all five of you. What do you want?
ceo dot biz sick magics
rimstone
blossom bullets and reldrich
You've whatever you want. Yeah, we're just fucking having fun. We're just having a good time
Why not? I still take way too much damage
Unfortunate. I want you to pay the subs you owe us. Oh, that's right
My credit card kept getting declined from twitch
And I just never did it. I tried it like five times and it never worked
That sounds like such a bullshit
If you think about it, but I assure you it is not
That sounds like total. Oh man. I tried but my credit card just didn't go through
It's something I don't know something with their servers
But I promise you it was real try it now
Um, that's a little late
I
Why does that matter? You know what it's because I don't want to go like get my credit card
We're about to end the stream
It's too late
Now remind me remind me when I turn this room on again. We'll do it
Are you going to give people the games we'll figure it out
As long as it's on steam, oh shit
Sacrificed your loving wife to become this I thought you'd be more useful to me
I was wrong
Now that the final door is open I have no use for you
There we go mission 10
All right, and that's what we'll call it that is where we will call it
Uh, yeah, we'll figure it out. I
We'll have the mods are already reaching out to people just a fun little thing. That doesn't not like a running like a contest or anything
right, it's just
Decided hey, fuck it. Let's do it
You got another 30 minutes in yet? Uh, no, it's midnight
I think I think it's probably time to call it off mischief makers. Did I win?
I'm sorry
But it is when?
It is when we could see it in the chat. It is when we could see it in the chat room over was first
Can you give us a good night?
Uh, yeah, I like these no cam streams
Yeah, I i'm telling you i'm there's a i'm there's a new philosophy here where I just i'm gonna just do whatever I want
Right. Sometimes it's gonna be devil maker eyes might be something else random then
Just hang out and play just chill
I much prefer being able to do stuff like this more often way more often
So more of these you've already seen a bunch from already, but we're going to continue to do these
So let's talk about the next stream. I'm going to finish devil may cry 3
I will be live on friday and we'll probably do friday and
Probably friday saturday or friday sunday. I'll pick out a couple of days this weekend here friday sunday friday saturday
We will finish
devil may cry 3
And then on either saturday or sunday, we will move on to
I don't know. I got a list of a bunch of stuff. This game was on a list
Yeah, it was on my list all the devil may cries were. Oh, yeah the food result thing
I want to go over that on um on friday, too. I think we got we got everybody. All right
I think we got everybody that
um
Said the the name of the thing that I was saying the food thing is going to be a challenge
Maybe we just dump it in like a word file. It doesn't matter. All right, i'll see you guys later
If you stayed up late, have a good night
If you're just waking up have a good morning and if it's in the middle of the afternoon
Then get up and stretch and that's it. See you guys on friday
Great rest of your night. Thanks for watching devil may cry 3
Very hard, but I get it. I get it. So let me ask you this
I know a lot of people here are probably big fans of this game. What's the best devil may cry in your opinion?
What is the is it this one? Is it five the three five?
One there was a lot of debate in the pre-stream of is five the best one we need music
I got you got you. I got you right here. Hold on four is underrated. It's pretty good
Hanging out an offline chat earlier. I put a poll up to see what people were thinking
I think only two people voted for four out of a couple hundred responses
Yeah, four is good, but five is just so much better
So what's the deal with the first one then because everybody said no, no, no, no do not play the first one. It is way different
You're gonna hate it
What's the um, what's the deal? It's just very dated very old. I mean, it's got to be
2003 or something for devil may cry 1
Or was that still in playstation 1 was it ps2?
Wow, it was originally resident evil 4
What hold on?
I mean you've got now i'm intrigued. I need to know what that is. It was gonna be a resident evil game
That's cool. All right, I kind of want to check it out
Same director is resident evil 2
Re4 had a lot of revisions
Have any advice on how to make colonoscopy prep more palatable?
You talk about drinking the the gross drink that makes you like shit for fucking three days
um
Yeah, you know what? I'll tell you that's the worst part
That's actually the worst part and that part sucks. Don't get me wrong
But for a colonoscopy colonoscopy is not
It's that is is simple the procedure is simple
It's just that
Drinking the drink in eating the thing
To clear you out. That's the actual worst part
so
You are doing the worst part right now
So when you're done with that and you get the few days you have to do it
On that last day
Just look in the mirror and go
Now it's time for the easy stuff
Because it actually is
Yeah, it sucks. But you know, you gotta take care of yourself. Do what you gotta do, right? Do what you gotta do
Thanks doc
Yeah, and then go get a large iced coffee
Uh, that's funny
I did say I was gonna puke blood today. Yeah, but that was just
That was just nonsense
All right. I'll see you guys later. See you friday. Thanks for watching. Take care call your mother
I mean especially if you didn't call your mother a few days ago
But now
Have a good one. Good night. Goodbye
See you soon