I am I am not late at all. I am precisely on time precisely with a really fucked up voice as per usual
Hi, how are you? That was the first part of your week then hopefully it's been pretty good. How was your Monday?
How was your Tuesday? How was your weh? Ah?
Wait, it's not Wednesday that whole joke got ruined Wow
um I
Was gonna hold on. Let's try that again. How was your?
I
Already saw you on Wednesday. So let's do this again. How was your Thursday? How was your Friday? How was your Saturday?
How was you set up? We don't know yet. We'll find out soon enough
Hopefully we can have a good Sunday together. I actually thought it was Wednesday. Hello
That's the streamer mindset. I wasn't even a joke. It was me
Just got doing a little thing I did that you should be laughing because I don't know what day it is and
Not only do I not know what day it is. I was way off
Way off like not even remotely close
That's what you should be yellowing in the chat about not you know anything else. It's my voice sucks
I couldn't even do yellow well correctly. Do you hear this? I don't know what's wrong with me. I don't get it
There are any doctors in here
I went to the doctor about like having like junkie voice and like a junkie like painful kind of nose and I was getting
Dizzy and shit. I go to the doctor. They put that camera tube up my nose
They do an MRI of my head in the brain and shit and they go
Oh, no, you just have like cysts all over inside of your mucus cavities. I mean they can cause those problems, but no
That's not what's happening
Take get it. Take them out. Take them out now get rid of them. I don't want them anymore
anyway
We're doing fine. We're doing just fine. Oh, they like it in there
You can't just take them out. No, I mean I can get them I can get surgery. It's so stupid like I
Almost look forward to when we're all just machines
Like I could keep our brains and keep our hearts because that's important, but honestly, ah
Mr. Elbertson, you've got a hernia
we're gonna have to fuck cut into you and cut all the flesh and shit and
Mucus membranes and then like pull it out cuz it's stuck there and then you know, that could be why your whole body hurts
Okay. Mr. Elbertson you have cysts in your nose and they're growing and they're huge and ugly and we need to cut them out with scissors
Whatever the hell they do
We need to be made out of steel and platinum and gold
None of this flesh bullshit. It's stupid and it gets in the way. That was a big true. Somebody said that right now
Are you I'm just kidding my god, I can't I can I not go off on these as comedy rants anymore
But honest to God, yeah, I don't know why that you probably noticed it every so often the last six twelve months
I gotta figure out what I want to do about it
My vocal cords are fine. They've looked at those
It's just something going on up in where those cysts are that I'm just gonna have to get them taken out
but from
Wait, I'm not gonna announce it yet. Hold on. Hold on. We gotta wait for people to trickle in. What did you say?
Would you let raccoons do surgery on you?
Does the raccoon have his degree in surgery?
Because yes, if that's the case
If a raccoon can get through med school and get a degree in surgery, then why wouldn't you I mean they let rocket raccoon build
A bunch of spaceships. You don't think that he could if he wanted to become a doctor or something
What about a frog? Would you let a frog do surgery again?
If the frog went through med school, what what do I care?
Your hands are too slippery, but they somehow got through med school and got through surgery school
They get with gloves. Would you do would you do surgery on yourself?
No, because you're looking down. You can't really see that
Well, I wouldn't would be somebody we need to be doing it like on top of me right like like cut in the middle
You can't look down and like do that. It's not gonna happen
He's a mirror
at cameras exist, but
You're at you're referencing a ludicrous statement. I need another coffee
It's like a two or three coffee day because I'll tell you got a major announcement for you
And I'm gonna pull back the jokiness because I'm actually gonna talk about a lot of serious things here
But should I wait until there's like a ton of people here? Should I do this in the intro?
Maybe I'll wait
Let's wait for a little bit cuz if I feel like it's it's important enough to talk about it not like put on the
Jokey YouTube voice
I'll talk to you as me my real voice
That's how you know that we're getting serious
When I start talking like this, so no more Jokey voice. This is my real voice. That's how I actually talk
You're at 10k now. It's not enough. I'm in a weird mood today
I'm sorry, I just screamed at you. It's not an it's alright. Just hold on. I'm really excited today. Okay, I'm sorry
Compressor just fought with you. Wait, did it like screw that up?
Do AI dungeon what we're gonna do a house builder first cuz it popped up
I had a plan to play AI dungeon and novel AI today and
That's what I told everybody I was gonna do
Everybody was aware of that
Last second I saw a pop-up for house builder
So I changed every single one of my plans. That's what we're doing
It's still available though. We could still play it. It's ready to go
People were saying that I shouldn't play AI dungeon. I should play novel AI
It's AI dungeon got I got like nerfed or something like they they got it out some of the AI or something like that
I don't know but AI dungeon has kind of the quest thing, right? I'll try I'll do them both. Don't matter
Why is your mouse squeaking?
Wait, what do you mean my mouse squeaking? What do you mean?
Who's getting too expensive to run so they have yeah, I mean, I mean look Geo guesser is you have to pay for it now
too
right this
It's not that expensive. It's look if
It's like Geo guesser like a few dollars or something to play it
It's gonna support the people that make the game and support it and keep it running. Whatever that that's that's that's cool. That's fine
As long as it doesn't ever become like actually pay to
like win
Geo guesser is cheaper than subbing here. Yes, it is
Yeah, I got them both a to win Google Maps
All right. All right. It's time to mute the music
Time for the music to stop. I
Need to say something gonna talk about something
I gotta get this like other music out of my ear because I want to talk to you guys very much
to you
This has nothing to do by the way with the discord changes
This is a completely separate thing that I'm announcing
So it's not like I didn't plan on having like a bunch of huge discord
Changes and then like and by the way, here we go. That just kind of happened this way
Tell a fart joke. I'll tell a fart joke in the middle of this announcement to ruin it. How does that sound?
How does that sound I can't win with this record? All right, my go XLR won't record it. So never mind
Alright, here we go. No more stalling. No more delaying. This is what I want to tell you
And then we're gonna talk about it for a little bit
So if you if you thought you were gonna go right into house builder, I got some news for you
You got about five to ten minutes sitting here looking at this starting suing screen. Maybe not maybe a little bit less
We just sit in the menu too. That's fine. Yeah, that's fine. So
What is the in five minutes is okay. So as you know, those of you that have been on this channel for a long time
Some of you for more than a decade, which is crazy
You know that sometimes I do very large streams whether that's the dollhouse whether that's
The Halloween stream Bugleberry shows up sometimes. He's a good friend of mine, by the way, good friend of mine
baseball other stuff that I really want to do it's starting the bills are starting to add up and
Over the next kind of arc of my career here, which I'll be honest
I kind of want to make this like the like the big one what is happening now
As I've decided going back and forth and talking with various people and various things
I am now signed with evolved. I'm now under the evolved umbrella
Evolved is the company that represents XQC in a talent agency way
Also, cutie Cinderella, I think Austin show and a shitload of eSports players, right? So why why why are you doing this?
Whoa, whoa. Whoa. Oh, wait a minute. This dude's now all of a sudden. He's like signed with a talent agency
He blew up his discord and like now what the fuck what corporate Andy is taking over. Is that what's happening?
No, just wait everybody. Hold everybody settle down settle down. I need I want to make this really clear
He's becoming a CS go pro. What if that was the announcement?
What if no, that would be so dumb
That would be so that would be such a bad dumb move for me because I don't play CS go and I'm not very good
It what's below bronze is there a wood like I would be wood rank in League of Legends or whatever it is plastic
so
essentially what this means is that there's now a lot there's gonna be a lot of opportunities now to tap into potential sponsorships and
brands and
money and
Making money from these different avenues and stuff, right?
But I gotta be really clear about this the big shows cost a lot of money and we struggled
I was I was actually thinking about having Jake
Community Jake come on here and talk about this with me because he's a lot more well-spoken than I am and a lot of things
but I
I'll be very transparent with you guys the streams that you see from time to time
They rack up and have racked up hundreds of thousands of dollars in bills over the last few years
dollhouse alone was an
Unbelievable amount of money and I have to start to think about as I go into this kind of this arc of my online
Entertainment life for whatever you want to call it e clown world
I have to start to be able to pay for these things and I could I maybe pay for them
Oh, I probably could it would be pretty bad though
I think over another few years of doing this it might actually not be a good thing
So I'm opening the idea of being able to have a bigger dialogue with sponsors
Be signed with a talent agency so they can handle this shit. They come to me. They say hey, dude
You want to do for instance?
You guys are I've talked about it a thousand times. So I'm just gonna talk about it again
I want to do Jerma rumble live on twitch, right? I want to do Jerma rumble live live and
That show is going to be an absolute metric fucking huge amount of money to be able to do stuff like that
I need to have the capital to be able to do it and I'm going to only take sponsorships and only take money from places
That I know that I'll have control
Streams are not gonna change. It's I'm not gonna do like fucking like
Laundry detergent tweets once a week that's not happening as I tweet like five times a fucking year
Anyways, you think I'm really who wants me to do tweets for their business
But I have to start to think about this stuff and I have to really start to take into consideration
That there are companies that their whole goal is to make you
money for stuff and
Sponsorships and bring brands in we it was a painful experience to get the dollhouse paid for a lot of behind-the-scenes stuff
You guys don't know about that show that was very very very difficult to have happen. I want to try to eliminate that
I want to make it easier on
production on people that are showing up on myself to not have to kind of
Drag their heels into the ground trying to figure out how we're gonna pay for a show and some of you might be saying
right, maybe not maybe not something maybe I'm just making you up, but that's fine. I want to say this anyways is
Well, then what just don't do the shows like don't just don't do the big shows if they're this much of a
Financial kind of burden in a lot of ways don't do them. Just don't do them
We don't need them. I have to be very honest with you
If I wasn't doing the big shows, I would have quit two or three years ago
I would have retired years ago and I made a very very important statement over the last three or four years
The if I'm not interested, I'm not gonna stay and yeah the the the replacement stream joke
That was that was a joke
but you know
I have to really think about how I'm gonna stay interested and that is what interests me doing like German rumble live is
What I am interested in doing doing baseball is what keeps me interested
And if these things weren't here and I wasn't actively on a daily weekly basis trying to you know
Get these shows off the ground. I probably would have stopped. He actually hates streaming
He actually hates no, that's not what I'm saying. No, I love streaming
I what are you talking about?
You would have seen the shows the the projects the events
That's what I'd live for right now, right?
But this stuff has to get paid for and if that especially if I want to do them as more often like you've been seeing
It's been pretty much
Every what like three or four months every like few months
There's like something that's not like just like kind of sitting in a like a desk stream, right?
So what evolved is gonna do is they're gonna come in and they're gonna connect me to brands and to people that hey
You know what? Uh, yeah that stream that you want to do sounds like really fun and really cool
We'll give you money for it. That's the whole purpose of this and I know I said it was gonna be five minutes
And I know it's been like 15. Ah
Also, let me make I'm gonna give you some hard lines here for you to understand if I will not have
complete direct control over
Everything I will not take a sponsor a lot of people wouldn't when they saw the coinbase sponsor
They thought that it was like holy shit. Oh my god. The stream is ruined
He's gonna be shilling coins and NFTs. That's not gonna happen. That is not going to happen
Let me be very clear with everybody that is not ever going to happen
If I do not have exact direct control of everything, it's not happening
I'll say no, thank you
But that's where that stands if you see a sponsor on this channel over the coming months
It's because of a few reasons reason number one
fucking
Reason number two
What was it? Oh, I'm paying for shows. No, I mean, I'm just fucking around but seriously
Reason number one and pretty much the only reason is to make money to pay for the big stuff and the big stuff is
Very expensive. I'm not trying to make a shitload of money from sponsors to take and put in my personal bank account
I want to pay for shows
I want to be able to pay the people on the shows and be able to do them without
stressing myself out financially or sitting there in the middle of like our dollhouse production going
Okay, we fucking need money or this isn't happening. I want that to not happen ever again
So I I think that it's a good fit
Yeah, and we'll see going forward. It's gonna be
It's gonna see how much I like it
I'm very very happy with what they've said so far and I hopefully the relationship like in a business wise can flourish and
Evolved can come in and help out this channel and you guys will see what they do also
I know five minutes. I know another important thing to understand is
I if I'm gonna do a huge show that's gonna cost tens of thousands if not hundreds of thousands of dollars
I don't want that to be a financial burden on the community, right?
Like I don't want to have to be like oh shit
Well, I really should like really need some more subs this month. Otherwise, it's gonna be hard to do
It's gonna be hard to do that the playground stream and we get a bunch of playground equipment and we do like
Olympic level playground equipment
Competitions like right that's not happening that I just made that up
But that's my you know
I mean like I don't want to have to I would rather it be a sponsor comes in
Drops a bunch of money and it's I don't have it's not like the burden is not put on either me or me needing to kind
Of tell everybody
20k
Cuz I don't want to do that
And I've never ever this is five minute Andy
The only time that a stream or a YouTube video really has ever been sponsored
It has been dollhouse that I never really have ever done a sponsorship. Maybe one
Back in like the YouTube days. I don't even like remember it's been so long
but all the major streams that you see all the major videos guys, I
Liquidated my 401k to make the German rumble video
That's a that's a story you've heard many times
So it's not I
Need to start to think about who is gonna pay for these things and if it's gonna be me
You know who knows maybe I'm like maybe I'm not brand friendly
What I will will find the right brands, right?
This plunge of companies that I've talked really highly of we won't know who who is going to
He says fuck all the time
But you know, there's there's a lot of opportunity I just want don't want people to think that this is now
Oh, he's cash it out. He's getting kind of the end of his like career. So he's putting all the chips on the table
Hey, fuck this whole thing. I'm pulling out all this money. No, that's not happening. I
just want to be able to pay for shows and
However, we can do that if I need to do some sponsorships if you see it here in there
That's what's gonna happen. It's gonna be I'm gonna make sure it's stuff that I really want to do though
Which makes hey, excuse me all all advertisers. Excuse me all advertisers, please pay attention
Don't you think that makes this this channel way more fucking valuable? Wait, he's only had wait
He's only had one sponsor ever. Oh
Like we can get on there. Give him 10 million. Give him 20 million. Give him 30 million, right?
Like that's pretty valuable
He expects 20 million dollars. No
He's so fucked up, but I'm only gonna start today
I'm gonna take sponsors from things that I really want to take sponsors from and I'm gonna have control and
Evolved has been very very upfront. They said dude. We get it this music. This has been the music that's been on the whole time
What is this like church music? Oh my god, turn that off. It's I'm in a boy. It's not bad
It's like nights like it's nice music, but I feel like okay. He says he's gonna use it for big shows
He's gonna use it to pay. No, this is
televangelist inspirational bullshit
It
Really does feel like I'm a televangelist
I am asking you I am set talking about money and where money is gonna come from to the to the church to the congregation
You know, I'm sorry everybody what I have to start to think about here is
How we're gonna make the church grow even bigger than it is now and we do that
By talking about this company here as you see I
Can't I don't want to make a joke about a sponsor because like I'm like sponsor Andy now, right?
Oh, that's off-limits. Can't talk about that. I can't bring up this company. Okay, just in case they ever were interested
People like okay, but if all it doesn't know just don't tell them
What they don't know is like they're gonna come to me with sponsor people
Hey, we've got this deal for you. Maybe it'll make you a really good amount of money
You can take this and then like all that show in fucking June is gonna be awesome. Okay, sure
What was the company again? Oh
Let me let me give you a list of all the companies that are interested
Okay. Well, I told that company that they suck. I told that company to fuck off. I said fuck that company
I said this company makes disgusting dogshit products. Um, I can't use any of these
Wait what? Yeah, unless you come in at me with like hamburger helper
Or like McDonald's is the only two companies have ever spoken highly of you said to know other companies have ever talked highly of
If you like jet blue
Well, there you go. This is your criteria
And for your helper he'll and
Chuck E cheese
Please don't do NFT guys. I okay turn the funny music off. Let me just be really clear. Yes
You guys know that I've had I had the coinbase sponsor. Yes. I've been involved in crypto over the years
You understand that right? But I'm not going to do that
I'm not gonna I don't I'm not gonna jump into like the NFT game now that I have a sponsorship
That's not gonna happen. I'm not gonna do that. I have no interest in NFTs. I have I don't care about them
I don't I don't focus on them at all. It's nothing that I care about
I have no interest at all. So I gotta make that because people people are probably gonna think that like if I tell he's gonna start
Taking sponsorships. He's gonna he wants to take big money sponsorships. He took a coinbase sponsorship
No, I am in control of what I want to do and I have no interest in that space at all
I just don't so
I've seen that pop up in chat a little bit and I want to make sure that that's people understand that is it true
What about subway? I mean I have I talked bet. Okay, you guys have to do me a favor here
Well, I mean we need to kind of come up with all the companies that I've spoken highly of right
imagine being like a brand person for one of these companies and you go to this you pay a bunch of money to have this like
streamer do this shit and
Somebody links you a clip of them like taking a bite of your of your most famous sandwich and saying this is dogshit into the camera
All right. All right. I know I know I've been sitting for like 20 minutes
it's important though to write and I want to touch upon the discord stuff as well because I've seen a lot of people kind of
Talk about what the fuck is happening on the discord. I I need to start to get some of these places more manageable for me and
Over the last few months
I've been trying to figure out how to do that how to make the discord the cleaner experience for me better for the mods
Better for me to manage because at the end of the day
It's it's the German 985 official discord
Which the buck stops at my desk and I kind of have to see how things go there. We've seen problems there
We've seen great incredible things come from that space, right?
I have to try to get it to where I can pay attention to it to where I can manage it
Have a group of mods that can think it can manage it with me. You're gonna get TV burning
Look, there's a few important things going on and no, I'm sorry. There's like little sparkles going on over here
So it's gonna be fine
It's not gonna burn into my monitor as this channel kind of changes and as this channel
Evolves you're gonna there'll be some things you'll see that are changing and
Like I said, I'm trying to keep myself interested
I'm trying to keep myself connected to the space as best as I can
You can't minus to the new agency that has signed to me. That's not how it works
But as we go forward here
I need to find ways to make it so I can disconnect because you guys have known this for the last
Most almost 11 plus years of being around I disconnect I don't interact that much and that's very much by design
I need to disconnect. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to do it for this long
The constant kind of stress and the constant awareness of having a community this big is
my way of handling it is
To not to really disconnect from it a lot of times and I mean, like I said, I don't tweet that much
I'm not on social media that much
So in the spaces that I'm you know, officially a part of that I officially own going forward here, too
Not just on discord on twitch on you know, the YouTube space on like the sponsor space
I gotta get it under control because I'm not really that much of a participant. Please play dude. The edibles are kicking in
Oh shit that guy that do art that one guy
Was like ready for house builder and it's pissed because we've been sitting here for 25 plus minutes
Talking about like the state of the channel in the community and shit and this guy is sitting here
sinking into his couch and like starting to the world is zoning out and
He's sitting there going to please pick up the fucking cement truck and just dump the cement dude
This is too much for my fucking brain. What do you got son? What do you mean Italian? He's evolving
No, I don't want an evolved version of this fucking weirdo. No. No, I'm leaving the community
I just that person just left the community that person thinks I'm like turning into like a new Pokemon or something
Like I just fucked it very TLDR
Sponsorships are gonna become a thing now. I want to pay for big streams some of the biggest streams I've ever done
Even more large in scale than the dollhouse are currently underway. I'm gotta I've got I gotta believe
All right, let's go. All the things that I'm doing are trying to make my life a little easier. That's it. Okay, you fucking criticize me
You're gone. I will ban you fucking permanently with the click of one of my fucking fingers. So watch it. Okay
All right house builder, this is not like house flipper. It's different
You build the houses rather than flip them this game
Might be dog. You know what?
We're turning over a new leaf because at some point, you know, you got a can't just say that about anything that I come across
Corporate Andy, let's go. All right, we're gonna start. I think you start small. You can't say anything bad about anyone anymore
Hey evolved. I'll give you a list. Okay, I'll give you a nice list. This is an igloo house. It's easy
This is a mud house and it's easy it's the only two I can do and now let's put on that youtuber voice
Should have a face cam. No, maybe in a minute. Maybe if you're good the igloo
We're gonna learn to play about instead of a house. We build a home. I'm that person up for 30 minutes
Good to see you builder. I hope the weather won't scare you off. Let's be honest
That's a tough job as you probably know we build all around the world
You might expect bigger buildings more mechanics and construction challenges in the future
But for now, let's see how you handle it. Have fun a
Little loud for me, but it's probably not loud for you. Is it? Oh, we have a dog. Can we pet the dog?
I mean kind of start building the igloo. You must first cut out ice blocks
What to do this grab the highlighted bone knife and come near the ice quarry and while holding the left mouse button draw a
Contour along the scratch on the ice
What it just jump scared me?
Okay, snow bricks
What? Okay, so pick up the ice block. Oh
Pick up the knife. Oh, there's a knife. It's like a melee weapon get closer to the source of ice
This is the source of ice. I mean isn't ice just literally surrounding us. It's so bright. It's so bright
I think I'm gonna need to put on some HD glasses some brightness reducing glasses
Thankfully, I'm open to sponsorships now. I wonder what kind I would put on. I wonder what brand I would be using
God really need them now own
Igloo knife before you start you'll have to find an igloo bone knife press e to grab it. Okay
You already have a knife in your hands draw a contour along visible track on the ice
While holding left when you see there's no more ice on the hole. You have to look for another source. What we're here
Whoa. Oh shit. Okay, cool new skill available. Oh my god
It's like the path of exile skill tree
This is bigger than path of exile. Let me see. This isn't accurate at all
You know what else isn't accurate at all not well, I was gonna say not I thought I didn't have I thought I didn't have
The love zone never mind joke ruined
With this skill you will cut two times more snow blocks at the same time. Okay, I got it two times more snow blocks
Cut ice for the new snow blocks. All right, let's go
Doesn't matter how sloppy it is. Oh
Dude, it's I got two. Ooh
The bonfire is dying you have to throw more sticks into the fire or you will freeze
Wait, we can I can die
Get more sticks in there. How much to show to use? Wait, am I using way too much? Oh shit
I'm like, I'm the guy that you don't want to survive with the better. All right more ice
Yo, man, I got if we burn a hundred sticks. We'll get a huge fire. It'll be really warm
Eat that guy first, okay skill tree. Yeah to start building the igloo. You must first cut I already did this
Okay, I'm just gonna cut ice for a little while. All right. Why would I go back and forth? This one's empty
What they're telling you because you're doing an awful job
Well, I'm gonna get awful job this one square meter that I can cut ice out
This game is fucking sick. By the way, I thought I was gonna be building houses in like a
Good neighborhood or something. This is actually cool. You have to like
Make your way build your way up to that. How much can I carry? This is an IRL scream
I hope nobody ever does an IRL scream like this. I feel like I'd be terrified the whole time
Okay, so now
with my blocks
Whoo? I got a new skill
It's kind of a cereal box game, but I actually really like it. I'm gonna be honest
I got new skills with this skill. You will cut six times more blocks
Yeah, this is this is this is definitely like I like a cereal box game
This is like the CD that comes in the cereal box, but you know what some of those games are actually really good
Whoa, I love it. It's so easy. It's a simple
By the way, please make sure you join me for my Elden Ring launch party
Probably like four or five o'clock like maybe 16 hours into the launch
Be one of the last streamers, you know playing it. I would probably assure you of that
All right, what about this? Oh, I can sprint 30% faster. Okay, cool. What's wrong?
What is the dog doing?
It's not trying to add oxygen to the fire. Good boy. I have to hurry up
Oh go go go go. I gotta get this done before nightfall
Shit, how is it at 0%? How is it at 0%?
Wait, wait, wait sprint away igloo. Okay, 15 times more blocks. Nice. How far can I go?
We've got some sections here. Oh
That was so satisfying. It's like a little marshmallows. I
Just gotta collect blocks already 40. How many should I get?
Come on stop this game actually runs really well
Don't you think this is one of those games that should run at like eight frames a second all these games run like shit
So it's actually kind of surprising almost done. I get the roof. It's games from tooth. Yeah
Just give him 2011 no, it's not it came out like it last year or something. I don't build the roof
Not building the igloo. You must first cut ice blocks. I know that's right. How do I jump up here? Can I go in?
Scratch, okay. This is a really really funny igloo. I don't know how to twitch chat integration. That's funny. I'm killing it right now. I
Got it. I got it. I got it
Well, can't you go like get us a rabbit or something like go go get us like some food. What do you come on?
You're wasting wood. It's fine. We're gonna be surviving in there. Anyways, we'll find a rascally rabbit. I
Don't even know if there's another one. Nice. I think the wood respawns. Oh, okay. That's good
Thanks for quelling my fears. I
Think that should be good 50. Yeah, that's good
The new Samsung smart fridge has switch integration and Skyrim integration talk to the fans about that
Yeah, I just said that without you paying me to say that
How dare you?
Please reach out to my evolved representative, please
for a
retroactive payment I
Gotta get inside. I thought it was 365 degrees in here
I was like what how many ice blocks does it take to do this?
Goodness, okay. I need more your characters arm is identical to a character in the Incredibles
I I've never seen the Incredibles. No, I haven't I know I know that's like saying I've never seen Star Wars, right?
The last what was the I think the last Disney Pixar movie that I saw was Meet the Robinsons
The only reason why I watched that movie is because I thought the bowler hat guy was funny and cool and like I wanted
To see his scenes only in fact now that I'm remembering this
I think I just went to like YouTube and typed in all the bowler hat guys scenes
And didn't even watch the movie. Oh, no, I think I saw it. I think I watched it. I got it. Don't worry
All right, we're almost done. No, it was a nice movie. I especially like the trailer when the dinosaur goes
Big hand new arms. I did
We have to driveway press O to open the shop. Whoa
Wooden barricade, where should I put this? Am I supposed to be doing this?
To build an entrance to the igloo you can build one in the same way you built it
I can move it, but where does it want me to put it nice?
more
Where am I supposed to put this? I can't move it anywhere else. Do you mean it's like I can't
Okay, it was stuck on there. That was weird
Can only build one to go. All right. All right. Look arc
You're playing arc survival evolved. I like that name
I'm sorry. It's so bad. It's so bad
It's a jump to how about destiny to that was hard. That was a really hard game
This doesn't have really good feng shui. Sorry, the igloo doesn't have
Like what do you want? How do you want me to feng shui this?
Looks like the igloo got punched in the face and lost a few teeth. That's it. Oh
Cool. I did it. I got five stars. I did in 13 minutes. I ran
986 miles. Oh
Wait, stay here. Nice. This is a pizza oven. Okay, what's next? There are gunshots
All right, so let's go
Report a bug. No, no, no. How do I leave here?
exit save
Go to the main menu. Yeah
Okay, play I did this one. Nice. So what is any other things open up or do I have to go to the other one?
This is a mud house and it's a level medium. Looks like we're gonna start to include some wood
Here comes primitive technology German
Fun fact, you don't give up easily. Do you?
Do you I thought I said it twice like do you good as another challenge awaits you hope you brought an insect spray
You may need it. We heard some stories about a hungry lion around here. Let's get the job done quickly
So we don't have to face him
What?
We still have a dog
Okay, the first step is to lay stone foundations
Look around for stones in appropriate size collect the required amount and put them in the right places. Alright, so here's a stone
Okay, so let's get rocks
using a player sense
Wait, I oh
I have like I
Have like hitman vision
Jim the skill increase your strength by 50%
You can carry more materials with you in the tray without having to throw them away. Oh, that's a big deal. No
Alright, so we're gonna find rocks. Let's go look around collecting rocks
My gamer vision this game's awesome. Is it can I actually get attacked by a lion?
Okay, this is just MMO quest without the quest givers
I just have to go get like a hundred rocks and just go bring a hundred rocks here. I
Actually kind of like it. It's just arc. I mean, it's not really arc
This is probably more like lost arc than it is arc. This is a baby sensory game. It kind of feels like it
Good one. Thanks. I know that game is very relevant right now. It's my relevant game relevant gamer Andy
I'm just gonna do this for a little while. I
Kind of hope you can actually get attacked by a lion that would make the game a full letter grade higher for me
What if I can't do it? I don't have enough
Games really relaxing. Yeah, this game's good
This is it actually
all told our judgments, but I mean this is I like this just
Collect thing and bring thing here. It's so easy for me to understand one more. All right level up
Pick up the axe
What get closer to a palm tree with the axe equipped this melee attacks in this game?
Cut the palm tree down. Wow. Oh it falls into pieces
Pick up the log with E
Okay, cool
Um pick up a log. Wait, did I not?
There's no way to go. There's no way to do. I need to use my gamer sense. Thank you. Let it go
What oh I got to cut it. Are you serious?
Whoa, why am I talking like this is some huge innovation? Okay now
Some of these sticks up. I need more trees. Ah
You sound like you're experiencing life for the first time. It's kind of interesting
As go look at the steam store page for this. It's like cement trucks and shit
We are this is we're just scratching the surface
skill up
Faster tree cutting I'm gonna say oh
60% faster run speed
We're in a 30-second loop
Yeah, but it's a fun 30-second loop gameplay loops are okay if they're fun. They cut the music really didn't it still here
Alright, here we go. One two
There it is
New skill now, what do I do? Wait, there's more
The skill allow you to chop palms faster. Yep, where you do the same thing over and over again. Yeah, that's kind of it's relaxing
I like it
There are more trees
DMCA one turn on the furnace
What is there a free demo version of this game? I I don't know. What is this? I've like logs already here
Living in the 21st century doing something mean to it. What are you saying?
Living in the 21st century doing something mean to it better than anybody you ever seen screams from the haters
those are the lyrics I
Don't listen to any music
Because I think the last piece of music I listened to was like one of the attack on Titan intro songs
That's it that's it and then before that I think it was a radio on the radio I
Have a lot of these Twines
It's actually it's pretty helpful because it's kind of how it works, right? This is how you build a house
There there ain't no more trees I've cut them all down
Music's annoying me
Relax, it's you know, if you want to listen to like another 10 minutes
What's right? I like it. I think it's good
All right. Here we go. I think that should be in a good spot. Now we have to get those
Keep the construction from falling apart
You need to you need to tie logs together using rope made of tropical tree bark as you cut down trees
You may all have also found some tropical rope to collect the required amount and put it in the correct place
All right
Let's go
Build. Oh, there it is. Hey that tied it together. I
Did it?
Support for roof tiles in this stage. You also need palm logs collect them by cutting down trees as before
Do I have any?
Still have a few shit. I need more trees
That voice sounds like Joel
It does hold on. It sounds like Joel. I need to hear it. Let me just cut down a shit load of trees
Somebody just said fuck SNL and the whole cast what what are you talking about? What are you? Why saying that?
This is German. I need five
This is German stream. What what are you? Why are you saying that what happened? What are you doing? What happened?
Why are you saying that about I what does that do that? What does it do with me? I?
Keep thinking you guys are talking. All right. I'm so out of the loop with everything
completely out of the loop
100% I thought there's some guys coming in here going like hey, by the way, dude
Like fuck SNL and like fuck the whole bell cast just like all right, man, like what?
What do you want me to do about it? Why are you saying that to me?
I think there's enough trees rip the SNL sponsorship. I got it. You know what?
What are some sponsorships that I really would actually want? What should I say? What what should I get? What should I try to get?
biggest thing
Something that makes sense to me something that it makes sense to me
Donald's I would do that. Yeah, I would we I literally did that last stream and this is before
Doing anything with like a sponsorship or anything. I literally did a big a full like 10-minute McDonald's ad
I would do it. Yeah, that's a good one
Smarties guys if you think that smarties is going to pay some random dickhead streamer like me to do anything like you're out
Of your out of your mind
Skill increases your strength by a hundred percent
Got a shop now fence of logs
Or decoration. How about a fence of logs?
Should I put this? Okay. I got I got that twine. I can do this. I got a lot of it
Like the sounds all the sounds kind of make you remind you like you're collecting gems or something
I've got to do it like a bunch in a row
So it's like I walk in and I open up the crate and a bunch of gems fall out and I touch them all
In like one second, right?
That's good. That was good
That's good
All right time for some walls mix making mud
What do I have to do put mud in here and then fill it with water?
Pick up a shovel. It's some clay. Okay, put the clay into the basket
Got the wooden bowl scoop some scoop some water into bowl from scream
Or water in the basket. Whoa, I thought that said stuttering help like if the game is having a problem. Whoa, what is that?
fake reactions
Okay, so I can make clay
Mud shaper you have a basket full of clay and there's a block from near the stove
Take the clay out of the basket and put it into the form
What? Okay, cool. Now what? That's it. How much do I have to do? Oh my god. This is just like tasks the game. All right
There's gotta be a skill point I can do for this. Yeah, it's more mud blocks, please. I was really sus, but you just said
This way got it I went to school for bricking
You did
Did I just read another like like song lyric or something, what are you talking about?
I feel like I'm reading stuff that I don't I have no context of what's going on. Oh, hell. Yeah
Yeah
This is gonna take forever, but I'm obsessed. I'm studying right now. Can you please shut up for once? Yeah
I'll be quiet. You gotta here's thing though. If you're gonna you're gonna tell me to be quiet on my stream
You better get at least to see on that whatever it is. Oh, I need mud and now I need water
So you better get at least I didn't say be quiet. I said to get a see
Nice, that's so much better. Yeah mother nature. Yeah
HDTV presents the saw stream
You know what's funny though, I mean don't be surprised
Not necessarily that exact company, but that's kind of funny to me in its own way
How Franksburgers presents the diaper stream?
Like um, you know, you do you know you're signing up for you. That was always the plan cool
That's one wall done. I still have a lot. I gotta do that on all sides. Okay, and I hold the button
No, I mean for a cereal box game. This has great sound effects, which makes me want to continue to place the bricks
But under and by any means necessary
Right
Point you will form unimaginable more mud blocks at the same time and allows you to build brick after brick all the time
There it is
You're gonna play the new Goblin game
I don't know that is probably shouldn't be doing it like that. But that's what the tutorial did
Let's see what ungodly amounts look like
It's not that much. It ain't that much doesn't know you've not played the new goblin game
I can easily imagine that many bricks
I know like the fuck false advertising and shit. Are you gonna have?
Everyone what the fuck is going on? It's a game where you
You build houses. What do you?
What do you want me to tell you all games and all movies and all TV shows?
You could just say like what the fuck is going on
Something otherworldly or something that like well, this is not otherworldly but look you could say that about the Muppets
Okay, do you go do you turn the channel and you get on like Muppets take Manhattan and go what the fuck is going on?
With these like little weirdos. Who's that little green guy?
It's like a piece of media. You just you're gonna you could you'll figure it out. Somebody will help you you can enjoy it
Wait, wait, what the fuck's going on here that bear that bear can talk
Why does he sound like Yoda?
To voice Andy. I have a hundred and seventy four of these. Oh
Oh
Did not think I was gonna like that as much as I do. Holy shit. That was cool
All right, I gotta know was this you can form more mud blocks than you really need. That's fine. Just get it
Remember, what is your IRL house made out of and I think pretty much the same thing that everybody's IRL house is made out of
kitty litter and
That's it kitty litter and water
That's cement. All right. That's what it is. I'm like that
Wow, okay. Now that is actually a lot
That's a pretty decent amount zero. Can I make a ladder? How many clay balls do you think you could fit in a subway sandwich?
One I would assume maybe one
But that would just be the sandwich
It would just be two pieces of bread and a thing of clay, but you don't eat clay
I remember during the Halloween stream when bugleberry was
Eating spiders off of the table, which I'm not sure you could even see on the stream
But there was little spiders that were being pulled with string
Across the table and I was eating them with my hands
I mean I was back I was backstage like mimicking bugleberry like oh, that's what I want you to do like directing
But that's what I was supposed to be and I got a lot of comments
Saying bugleberry bugleberry. Don't put clay like that in your mouth. I
Remember I remember like, you know if if that were to be a mask, right which it's not that's somebody's skin
But if that was a mask that somebody was wearing which absolutely not the case
But if there was a mask
The clay that caked around their mouth like a little kid eating a chocolate bar that stayed there
For the whole BRB
Desperately wipe off
You know, it'd be kind of interesting. Don't eat clay by the way, like honestly
I think it actually people were saying it's like don't put any it's like actually fucking horrible
I don't remember why but I know it's just like don't fucking do that. Don't put it in your mouth
What's the actual like reason why something it's something like that plays just dust
Has a certain disease really? Yeah, I don't fuck around with that shit. Seriously don't
Really? I need one more
There we can pull that back that's minerals
Play from Minecraft. Yeah, that's where my that's where clay is from
Do we have a whole generation of kids that think that clay is from Minecraft? We don't right? What do I need?
Shape the tiles in the same way blocks
Using the mold on the other side of the basket where oh here. Okay, that's it
Wait shape the tiles in the same way to the blocks
But using the mold on the other side of the basket
Light up the furnace by putting some wood into the hole at its base. Finally put raw tiles through the chimney. Oh
That's what this is for
What would be what would be funnier?
What would even be funnier if is if kids hold on that went too fast
If it's the kids thought redstone was from Minecraft
You know, what's funny? I'm one of those kids. I thought I thought that that redstone was like a jokey thing that was made
Just made up for the game
It's not it is wait. It is
So what are you doing to me? Why are you making me look like an idiot?
I put this in put wood, right? How I do this earn on it cries wood to light a fire. So where is it?
Just hit right click. What is happening? Is it working? Oh
Where do they come out turn off the furnace? Where are they? I don't where are they skill points? I don't have any skills
You have to fill the whole thing up. Oh
Shit, okay. I see
Okay, little thing unit lost unit lost
unit lost
Destruction complete. Ooh
Can I reach all the way up there? I'm a girl mustache. I did I looked disgusting and I shaved it and I said never again
I'm just gonna do this for a little while because it's just kind of get that started. Yeah
grow a better mustache I
Can't really grow facial hair. I know that everybody says everybody I know. Yeah. Yeah
Dude, you're not doing it for long enough. You keep getting to like the
You just went through puberty and decided not to shave your face because maybe a you don't know how or
B you think it looks good. I know I'm at that I hit that stage, right and that's all it looks like
That's all it looks like for me. It never goes over that stage. I
Will go a month without shaving and it still looks like that. I need more
I need more this
Anybody else relaxed right now like wicked bad. I want some more coffee. Oh, what how much did you take?
We mean how much of what did I take coffee? I said one cup of coffee one. That's it
I saw all right. I want do we get to like the actual homes like houses like with concrete and
Floorboards and shit. I feel like that's gonna happen soon
All right, I can do this. I got 72. That should be enough. Ooh, look at this
Why are you changing the subject? What subject were we on? Are we on a subject? I don't remember the subject
Read a clock there guys. There are no clocks where I am. It's not it. There's no electricity
So I get up there. I stand on something. I can't stand on this. He's a look up. Oh, I can go inside right right right
Clock debacle. Yeah, I have not really taken any
THC since that I remember okay. I remember very specifically
So when I it's true. Well, actually New Year's Eve last year, right?
So when I did that and I looked back and I watched the clip and I knew how desperate I was to try to just like
Get the right time
So this is what I did. I
watched that footage back in my
I did the thing that you go like this, but you just can't believe it and you're so pissed because you look so stupid
Did one of these I went like this watching it I went
You know, you would wipe your fucking face because you keep like you just can't believe it
Just sitting there going that's what I was doing and I didn't want to have that reaction again
I was just rubbing my mouth going like God
And because I was looking at the chat and here's the thing everybody in the chat saying this has to be bullshit
This has to be made up
Right, like there's no way you are doing this not on purpose, right?
It's like fuck. I just look so stupid
but then I also had this same kind of
Epiphany a little bit here. I thought about this the other day. This is really interesting topic. I
Haven't been now this again. You're gonna say what does this have to do with reading a clock? That's like basic human knowledge
I
haven't been in a classroom
In almost 20 years
And I think about that a lot
I remember being in class and like the memory is so fleeting to me
it's such a distant memory of
doing essays and
problems and tests and
It's I it's a it's a fleeting memory and that's weird to think about
Because I remember like being up all night like fuck. I got a cram for this test
That's so long ago. What am I doing? It's a it's kind of a foreign concept, right?
What the fuck just happened? What are these done?
He's got he's actually finished. Um, I don't I don't think he's done. They are done. What have I been doing?
Muscle man. I mean, let's just get this one. Oh, I can jump but memory is a weird thing because that those memories from like
15 20 plus years ago. They're like they're like stopping existing
They're being
Like my hard drive is writing over that information in a way
Which is really bizarre to think about trust me when I tell you as somebody that's turning 37 this year
Once your hard drive starts to write over information from 20 years ago is when you're gonna start to look around and be like what?
Wow, I do this with this. He's right. Yeah
No, it's a weird feeling because I didn't have this feeling back in my let's say mid 20s, right?
In my mid to late 20s, it was kind of that was still not necessarily fresh in my mind, but it was still close
I'm approaching that period where being in school is a distant memory
Most on there. How many childhood memories do you think your brain deleted to replace with shitty internet memes?
You know, that's like kind of unfortunate if you really think about it, that's really kind of unfortunate
Okay, now I get it now I understand what you're talking about somebody is firing a gun at me I want to get a look at
It. Oh
Trapper house anymore. Ooh a half timbered house. Ooh
Any others that's the trapper house. I'm gonna do the half timber house watch movie
What wait, what do you mean watch movie? What I now watch the movie?
Okay, let's watch the movie
What is this a movie of
Wait, I don't watch somebody else's stream
Hey, by the way, you gotta up your bitrate man
You scream it up like fucking 500k
Trailer it's not out. I think this is early access or something. We just spoiling the whole thing. I don't want to see the whole thing
Showing me the whole house. I want to see the whole house
All you down I got a can all right. I need to know we just saw the whole thing get built
Okay. Well, that's not available
The other one is all right. Let's go to that one. This one's available sell
Wait, I bought it now. I sell it. Oh, I was gonna say what sledgehammer
Okay, unfortunately, you're on your own this time. There are no shops or any civilization here
You managed to bring the tools on a pickup truck
But you have to arrange the rest of the things you need for the construction of this house yourself
Hey Karen watch out for the bears. Good luck. Stop saying that there's no animals in this game
Stopper building a trappers house from the foundations. I thought they weren't gonna help me
Yeah, okay. That's like if dark souls
Would it be like
Here we are fire link shrine you're on your own motherfucker. Good luck. It's dark souls. It's hard as shit
And we don't help you and then I walk up to the first enemy and I take a swing and the game
pauses and this three one two three on the screen images with different paragraphs under each image
Explaining how to swing the weapon. That's what they're doing here. I leave me alone
Which look I gotta be honest. I said this the other day. I said if I'm not playing the VR stuff, too
like the video game tutorial
Just tell me how to just do I do you do I really need to be told how to swing the weapon?
It's left click in every single video game
Like can you just give me like a cheat sheet with all the buttons on it?
I don't know why we still have to go and remember right click is aim
You don't have to tell me that like just show it to me. What is the first game ever? It's not it's
This should be we need to have like a I don't know. Why would that be your first game ever? It's not
Left click is a do thing every game. All right. Let me see what this says. There should be a tutorial game
Yeah, there should be like steam should come up with an app that you can download
That's just like getting started with gaming and you put just have every game follow the same fucking basic rules
And you can open up this like steam
how to
remember most games have left click as their means of
attacking and or shooting and
Then the game can come up. It could be like here we go. Here's the tutorial. Here we go
Instead of spending like six plus hours tutorialing me just please refer to the steam workshop app
tutorial if you don't know how to use a computer and
Then we can shave the first six fucking hours of just stretching to add
Cutscenes to tutorials to make it worth showing so the developers don't feel like
We're gonna have we have to spend two hours telling people how to play the game
We have to make up like a fucking story that they can play through in the tutorial. They don't have to do that anymore
Just get to the good stuff get to the meat. Can we watch the new five nights at Freddy's video?
No, we're not watching five nights at Freddy's you're watching Jerma
This place sucks. So you picked a good one
Alright, we'll start building a Trappers house from the foundations. These are logs that are well embedded in the soil, right?
You can get the logs by cutting these trees. Oh
It's a deer
You move fast. There's pigs. Wait. Why did you develop pigs? Why have pigs and like animals?
Okay, let's go back to what I was saying. Oh shit, it's just like minecraft. I don't know where my house is. There it is
Can I get in the car?
Please tell me I can drive the truck. Can I please it's okay
All right. What the fuck am I doing? I need to read this
Please refer to the steam tutorial app gaming for beginners. I would probably flip out right now
Yeah, imagine if that's what it told me
Suck so much
Okay, you can get the logs by cutting trees nearby. Remember that you have to cut logs by chainsaw
Okay, yes to blueprint size and of course debark each log with draw shave
Good, I'm gonna cut down logs
these down
script scree
Scree, what is that to change just a scroll scroll?
I thought it was spacebar. No, I thought it was spray spray
scrape bar
Am I doing this wrong? Oh
What do I do? He's a one point one five in length
What that's way bigger than that and that's huge. What is going on? Oh
Thank you. Thank you so much. Here it is
This is it right here. I'll need a chainsaw. Here it is. All right, here's my best chainsaw impression
I
Just picked up the whole tree. Oh fuck. Now what do I do? I'm a forester and I'm impressed. Hey, thanks
Oh shit. Okay, this may
Know that's too big. These look like it looks like dog sausages
No, if you guys have ever had combos, okay, it needs to be that tall
How tall is this?
1.5. That's not even right. Why is it doing this? It's like 0.65. Okay right there. All right, got it
That right. What am I supposed to do with this shit? Oh, I have to debark it. How do I do that?
How do I debark it like that? Oh, I actually have to move my hand. I was gonna say what's going on
All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it
He's learning you said everything is left-click. No, okay. There's a difference between adding a game mechanic later
right
But even adding the game mechanics
We spend so much time telling you how to play rather than letting you play Dark Souls greatest game franchise of all time
It's already done. It's too big. No, these are perfect. No tutorial Andy. That one was not even the right size
Guys actually doesn't even matter
No, it doesn't a couple more of these logs
Yeah, that's five says it's a whatever guy. That's not that tall says size doesn't matter
You're wicked funny. You're wicked funny. You're gonna ever do the wink redemption thing again
Let me ask you a question. So back when I had the wink redemption channel points
There were probably three thousand concurrent four thousand concurrent people here like a year or two ago
There are almost 19,000 people watching the stream
Turning winks back on would
That would be the broadcast would be over. It would be only wink redemptions the entire stream. It would never
Be anything else ever because it already was all I was doing back when I had a third of the audience
There would be unbearable. That was a flex. It's not a flex. I'm just whatever just make them really expensive
Do one please fine. Okay. I will do one wink into the I will wink into the camera
If you guys without any like mod help
Right now like oh we can clear the chat. I don't want to see a chat message of
Ten whole seconds. I want the chat to stop and I don't want it to move. I
Want no one to write anything for a full ten seconds and I'll do it
No, not dot dot dots just nothing in the chat it's just frozen and that's not moving
This game has animals that are more detailed than Red Dead Redemption 2
That's actually a really well-made elk. There's a Fox to shut up. Yeah, I see how easy it is to get you to keep talking
Wait, it's doing it for me. I fucked that up. So bad. The game was like, you know what don't worry about it
I'm gonna do it for you
Scared me. All right, use a chainsaw. Uh-huh
All right. We're not playing that game anymore. You also prepare the next logs in the same way
You're cutting another tree you bark them from the bark with a special tool and then you cover the chainsaw
Okay, this is cool. Do I need this?
We have to debark this you bark it
Well, that's way better than what I was doing. I did that in the probably dumbest possible way, but guys size doesn't even matter
What?
Alright now I'm making it bread. I can make wood salami
Make it thinner. Can you make it thinner, please? I love
In slices of deli meat
Let's be honest when the person behind the counter holds it up and goes, is this all right?
You just say yes, you know what I mean? Like what does it really matter that much?
Like honestly if you for a lot of the people that go to the deli and they go
Um, can you make it super super thin for me and they do it and they show it up and they go
Mmm, I think a little bit thinner than that, please and they go. Okay
They could probably just put the same piece of salami up and they would think it was fine
Like oh, yeah. Yeah, I'll do it. How's this? Oh, that's much better. All right. What am I stop doing this?
I need to like actually cut this correctly. How far is this?
two point two point nine meters
Alright, I gotta get this is all trash now. I gotta get rid of this
Like when the person at the deli counter just kind of goes, hey, is that alright? I
Mean if it's way too thick you just be like, oh, can you like a little bit thinner like I or before they even start
Cutting it you go. Can you make it thin?
That's it face came on. We've been good. Mm-hmm. It's my house. Oh, there it is. Okay. Oh
Cute Fox is getting nighttime. Alright, stop. I need to cut trees down
Now I need two point eight meters
Starting here. How many can I get out of this this two point nine right there? I can get probably three
All right, two point nine got it
It's gonna take forever. I'm not giving up
That close enough for this two point nine. I can do it twice two point nine. There it is
So it's three equal pieces, I don't need to measure anymore just do three equal pieces
Hey, pick it up. What? Oh god. Damn it. It's that that didn't okay
Then that's outer edge. Well, that's a whole tree. That's the whole thing. All right, cut another one down. I got it now
Oh
Three equal parts. Wait
Skin this thing. That's way better. Okay, so much faster
one
two three
That's enough. I wasn't even the right piece. It's actually too short
2.9. All right, fine. Let me just do this
Okay, just scaled all this
2.9
Thank God a skill
automatic log measurement
Thank goodness. Oh
Thank God
What a disaster this would have been
Perfect. Okay, two point nine nice log, bro. I you know, I hate that people are called shit a log
That's I hate it. It just seems so
So dumb and gross. It's just so awful
Alright, the rest of these are big for this one. No. Oh, is this too short? It's not this is big
Too short. It's not too short. I got to measure this again because like what the heck
4.7 easy or
There it is. We're seven
Okay, this one should fit too. What's that song from a Red Dead? Oh
We're having a little fun. They will have a little how we're building
Build all things and we have a little happen. Whatever it is. I love that song
Keep picking up the same piece of wood. In fact, just start over. Give me another one
Need
Two that are how long stop stop stop
Or for whatever for or something
That should do it. Oh
you
When are you going to ancient Egypt? I don't know
You also prefer the next logs in the same way. You're cutting another tree you debark them more of this
Automatic laser measurement. Ooh
How long is this? These are all art. Thank you five
All right, four point six four point six four point six four point six
I need for this will fit here one of these will already got all this scrap. I will use it
Thank you. Thanks for the help. Thanks Luigi. Okay. Now this is all right four point six four point six four point six
Is a bear staring at me?
That's a cat or there's just pigs
There's no bear. No, that's a pig guys. This is like a warthog
Can't do it
Shaving them automatically. Oh
You can fuck up by 30% perfect. Yep. We're good. Oh hell. Yeah, he doesn't even matter Luigi's gonna help me
That's so incorrect. You sure? All right, what about over here? If it's too long, they just end up cutting it and helping you
So it's fine. Watch out. There's a hair. There's a herobrine. Oh, no one more
Herobrine
What does herobrine even do he doesn't need to stare at you with red eyes or something and he's like kills you
He's a huge. Okay more of this
I did not put that there. It's weird
There's not a bear
I'm actually glad there's doing this because I can just put these two here. Be sure not this one
All right, one more and I'm gonna have to start making actual planks
There's even more that does sound like you'll like a lot
Okay, I gotta put some more logs down here. I think it's honestly I think it's time to do this
I have to cut down just like ten trees and stack them over here
You can play cruelty squad, I don't know I don't have like a plan to but
I
Appreciate the sport. Thank you. So also keep in mind. We also have AI dungeon
And that I'm gonna be playing probably soon here. I have novel AI and AI dungeon both ready to go
Like I said before I kind of like this
Play something for a few hours move to something else for like an hour or two play something for an hour
I kind of kind of like it now, obviously some games would not you can't do that. I kind of like this. It's fun
It's fun to jump around I'm gonna say two more. I still need another coffee. Well, the squad has stocks
Really?
You mean I could trade I think that's good be three more too short. Oh my goodness
This is next level. All right, still need the big ones. Yep. That's too short. There we go
How many can I carry I can carry this many? I didn't know that
Graphics are all that matter in video games
Um, not really I
Would disagree with you on that and the most fun I've ever had was a game
That looked like it was from like 2004 like 2006
Some games are like 2d pixel graphics and I found them amazing
Companies care way too much about graphics
Way too much if the driving factor for the huge amount of things that you play
About Mario Superstar Baseball
Mario strikers is I'm looking forward to that that game was amazing
Especially that what they had a sequel, right? It was really good. What are some of the things I'm looking forward to?
Elden Ring, obviously
When does Elden Ring come out? When is the actual launch on Steam? Yeah, but what time who knows?
I wonder if it's gonna be like 1 p.m. Or something or it's opening at midnight
The day before
Supposed to be on the 24th. I'll be Thursday at 9. I'm definitely I'm not doing a midnight launch release thingy
You know, I got these really good sections here. It's a fair type of craft beer. I don't really drink craft beer
I don't drink really beer at all
Every time I drink beer. I take two or three sips out of it when it's really cold
And I go. Oh
Mmm. Oh, that's good. Oh man guys. Oh mine's good. What'd you get? Oh, mine's the mine's the
Orange peel the orange peel. What's it? I I don't have any fucking idea. Just picked one. Oh
It's the orange peel IPA from
From Germany. Yeah, and then it gets kind of a little warmer and I I don't like to drink it
But I have to because it's like you don't you can't like order a full beer in like the nice glass
Take two sips of it and just stare at it. Like I don't yeah, you have to get at least halfway done
right, so
Also, well, I don't know why everyone's so weird. Why are we so weird?
Humans are a weird group of animals
I know we like want other people to enjoy the things we enjoy
But but do we really have to say that they that you think the ketchup is house made?
right
Like hmm. Oh, dude. No, this ketchup's house made
It's no stop. It never is
Ever probably maybe in a few places like dude that honey mustard. Oh, man. Oh
Yep, oh man, that's it. That's it. They made they make that here. They make that in house
I wonder how many times like a restaurateur has heard that come from somebody and they just open up the fridge
There's just bottles of like Heinz ketchup in there
Yeah, it sure is. I've never heard that. What are you talking about? Everybody says that like oh this beer. Oh, mm-hmm
I this is so good
Do you see where it's from? It's from this from Italy
Yeah, it is
Italian beer
Ranch restaurant ranch. Oh my god. It's so good. Oh, by the way ranch Andy's in chat
I got a bone to pick with you. I got a bone to pick with you guys
So a few days ago on this stream. We talked about how oh mayonnaise. Eww yuck mayo
all you ranch enjoyers I
think need to take a step back and
Evaluate how you feel about mayonnaise
Because if I if you think that mayonnaise is gross you better think that ranch is gross, too
Because that shit is like kind of disgusting if you think about it. Just like if you think about mayonnaise
unseasoned ranch
Uh-huh
Unseasoned ranch that's so funny. Excuse me, sir. Would you like some unseasoned ranch, please or fucking mayonnaise?
Don't care omega. Well don't care
Ranch actually tastes good. No ranch tastes like ranch
Mayo makes everything else taste better
Mayo brings out flavors ranch is ranch
Not that I'm saying I don't just I dislike ranch, but I mean I can't say I'm like I love it
I'm actually one of those
Giga Chad blue cheese enjoyers instead of ranch. I choose blue cheese every time
If there's a choice between blue cheese or ranch for like a dipping sauce for something I'm gonna choose blue cheese
I don't know that's kind of I can understand why people think blue cheese is gross, but it doesn't matter
To me. I just I know
Don't stop saying giga Chad
You guys say it all the time. You don't think I'm gonna like at least absorb some of that. Of course I am
Aoli, yeah, isn't that taste so good that mayonnaise that has like other shit in it like this like a it's like they
They ground up some garlic and put it in mayonnaise and you love it now. That's garlic mayonnaise
And holy smokes is that good? Oh
Eat I could eat garlic mayo out of the jar. I probably could
Like oh, just put it on bread. I think blue cheese is better than ranch
There's stuff that I would put ranch on instead of blue cheese
Should I like do an eating stream where I like eat stuff and write it for you?
I've seen people do this before you want my real dog shit takes on everything
Oh, what's like a one that you'd want to see your TV dinners?
Hmm you want to do a TV dinner stream get a bunch of them you dog sausages dog treats
That's so stupid dog treat tier list live so many people do like the
taste test stuff imagine if I had like
milk bones and
like dog sausages and like
Canned dog food and shit and I sat there and I did that
With special guess at all. I don't have to give his tier list
And how we do that is I take a few dog treats. I break them up
So they're really small right so he doesn't get like too much so break them up to the little small taste pieces
Put them out in a row far enough away from each other said so he has to decide I
Hold him back as like the other end of the room and go okay
Go watch out and see what he goes for first that is now elevated on the tier list, right?
So then that's like up at like s tier we put that next to another one, right?
That he also likes and we make a dog treat tier list
One thing I'd want to make sure of though is that whatever it was
It was gonna be
Very very small amounts like tiny little little pieces because I don't want to sit there and just like feed him bags of treats
He's saying this, but he's never gonna do it. No. Don't you understand?
Always remember the things I say because two years from now. I'm gonna spend
$40,000 on this as a project
You know what I mean? Like just wait a year or two. There'll be like a
$70,000 stream where this happens
Just wait a few years
That would be actually kind of fun as long as that was done right and it wasn't I wasn't overfeeding him and overdoing it
I think that'd be funny
Make a dog treat tier list. No, but the thing is I wouldn't just do the dogs like food tier list
Like in the middle of that stream
Macho man Randy Savage has to show up and like eat out of the can with his hands
And go like whoo. Yeah, and then leave and like I just have to blow money on that stream, right?
Like I have somebody has to come in and do something weird
Well, like I have to like be like come here I talk and I have to like fall out of my window
Like it can't just be a stream where we just do something like basic like that. I'll think about it. I'll think about it
That's not kind of like a fun idea
Then we'll find out once and for all
No, I know not my I'm not saying macho man
I'm saying like a like celebrity or like a somebody or a thing needs to happen
That's not just Otto eating dog treats this is coming along Otto is a celebrity, you know, that's true
I have to start to get it. I gotta use the ladder
But okay for me, what would you guys want to see me eat? I would do one of these
There's an endless amount of content here. It's a mess in here roots. Okay, I'm not gonna eat dog food. No
Okay, you okay. I see a few decent ones. I see a few good ones
Is this long enough? I need a full tree for that one
There we go. Good dipping sauce tier list
I mean I'll do I'll start with one if you guys like it and I maybe I'll do another one
Canned soups. That's not that's actually a really good one because that's really easy to make
That's legitimately just heating up soup. So I don't have to do a bunch of bullshit where
I'm actually kind of into that one. You're gonna have too much sodium
Well, no, I'm not gonna eat like 40 cans of soup. I'm gonna portion it out
So it's little taste test versions
Cover them up put them in the fridge and then be able to eat them over the course of like a week or like a month
How long I can keep it in the fridge for?
As when they do the coca-cola versus Pepsi taste test you don't drain a 2-liter to make that decision
Contrary to what the commercials of a lot of those products would like you to believe
How many soda commercials do you see where they just tip the thing up and fucking slam it?
Every time I see that happen. I go. Ow
that hurts
Always like in the middle of a jingle, right? It's like cool refreshing taste and they
It's like a guy on a beach
tips it back his head slams back and he is like
an ocean water tier list like the Atlantic versus the Pacific
You're gonna go go to like the Red Sea and be on camera. All right, here we are. Let's find out where this fits it. Oh
This one's kind of this one tastes a little bit different. This one's a little nutty
Let me tell you that's a way for a youtuber to write off a huge vacation. Okay, so just be aware of that
Oh where I got how I'm gonna travel the whole world
To take sips out of different bodies of water, isn't that crazy? I have to go to 30 countries
It's for the video man
Deductions oh, yeah, this house just looks like uncooked hot dogs. Oh breadsticks
This house is making me hungry. It just looks like breadsticks. I want to dump some fucking ranch on these things here. You know, I mean
What about a cereal tier list?
Yeah, but I already know where I stand on that. I know it completely where I stand. I already did that
Yeah, but I mean I didn't eat the cereal on stream
What about like a Yankee candle tier list or like a bed bath and beyond candle tier list?
I just sit there and I'm like, oh
This one's alright
That would suck you would never get the smell out of that room
Okay
Crayon you just made me spit on my monitor
Crayon flavor tier list like I think they're flavors
I don't think that they're just like fun names for colors and actually talk make them out of something that's edible
like have a fake box of like 500 crayons made lay them all out and eat them and
But they're actually made out of like an edible material that I can eat
That would freak out a ton. A lot of people would be fucking freaked out by that big time. I
Actually might get like a message from twitch like hey
What are you doing? Stop doing this?
He's all too short. Hey, it looks good. How often do you get those messages? Um
Okay, but this is a cool idea and I don't want to just ruin it and leak it in case I ever do it
I don't want to like leak it and talk about the whole entire thing because I think it's really funny and
One day I might actually be able to do it right it's possible
So I don't want to like leak it what it is and maybe I've talked about a little bit before but I'm
Just in case that this stream actually happens ever
I'm gonna hold on to it. But yeah, there was there was there was something that I wanted to do
but it was just like
Not a big fan
But I think we could have done it. I think we might have had to tweak it a little bit
It's nothing like nothing bad. It's nothing not bad. Nothing like like
Like violent or off learn. No, nothing like that
Nothing like like sexual or no, no, no, no. No, it was just something that was not didn't sit completely. Well
Which I mean for very obvious reasons, right? But they're not obvious to us
But this is such an I love this idea
I can't I don't it's nothing bad and there's not like oh my god, you can't do this
No, it's just we had to be like kind of careful with it because we didn't want to make it seem like it was really happening
That's what it came down to
No, no leaks. You already know the baseball stream is coming up in like a couple months. So no no leaks
I've already leaked way too much of that stream
Like I was gonna be I'm good. I don't care how what people say about that stream is gonna be one of my favorites ever
I can't wait to do that stream. You have no idea. It's gonna I can't wait
Yes for me that that streams for me. Okay. No, it's for you, too
This is coming along
No for is no leaks. No person someone in chat said it. Yes
Someone in chat has talked about it because I I have talked about it before
Very briefly. I didn't get on going to details of what it meant, but I don't know it was gonna be fine
But I didn't do that stream not because I didn't have like permission to it was just that
Other stuff really became way more important to take care of and do
And it became one of those streams that just fell through the cracks maybe temporarily until some of the other stuff get done
No, it wasn't a car accident thing
fortnight vape stream I
Will do that stream one day before I retire for real
I'm gonna do the vape guy playing fortnight joke. I'm gonna I
Don't know when I don't know how but I'm gonna do that stream
the daycare stream
Okay, I'll talk okay, I'm gonna talk about it because it's stupid
Community Jake told me also that this is probably a bad idea. Let's not do it and I was like, okay fine
there was a stream idea a while back where I
Announced to the stream that I was operating at daycare and that guys, you know
I'm just trying to make some extra money on the side here. I'm operating a daycare and
I'm gonna be operating it in we got some of these children here
I'm gonna be taking care of them and
it was gonna be like
like a half dozen like babies in like baby things back here and I was gonna periodically get them gonna be those babies that like
Made the sounds and stuff and like I had to go feed them and it was gonna be like a look
I'm feeding the babies thing
Where it went off the rails is some crazy stuff was gonna happen
We're like a bear was gonna fucking attack my office and I was gonna have to like defend the babies from a bear and shit
And like crazy stuff was gonna happen. I was gonna have to like fight for them and fight again
There's gonna be they were gonna like be able to vote for what I was gonna play next on stream
I'm not real babies like bait like dolls
What are you talking about?
like small infant baby dolls that just sit back here and I'm like running a daycare and I have to like defend them from like a
Bear is coming in and I fight the bear and like and maybe one of the babies like gets up and like attacks the bear and shit
That sounds awesome though
But it got to a point where I was like, you know what this probably isn't this probably isn't a great idea and
Community Jake is just like yeah
Let's like leave this one on the cutting room floor because like I don't think that this is gonna work and I'm like, yeah
You know what? This probably is gonna be hard to make work
Who would possibly worry about it being real? Well, not that it was real, but I don't know
Especially if like the babies we're gonna be back here like making noises while I was sitting here like talking and like streaming
I mean, look, let me be honest
Is that as bad as me wanting to do another one that got shut down another one that got shut down
Is I wanted to second cat boy stream and I wanted to shit in the litter box that was in the corner of the room
Is that is that the same? Is that just as bad?
That one got shut down too
You guys don't know
There's a lot of ideas that pass through like a small treatment
That me and community Jake will sit to call for like an hour and we'll be like, yeah, I mean, okay
So the for the second cat boy stream
What if there was like just cat toys around the room and I'm like running around chasing them
Maybe like chat can pick on like what toy I play with
Like that will there be a big cat tree that I climb up and like sleep on and just sit there for like 10 straight minutes
Oh, and they'll be like a litter box, too
and like maybe I'll go over to the litter box and maybe I'll shit in the litter box and
It's just like whoa. Well, hold on a minute Jeremy back back up for a second. What do you want to do?
And I'm like, well, no, I'm just saying like I'm just trying to think of like things that like funny shit to do
But I wouldn't actually guys. I wouldn't have actually shit in a litter box on stream
it would be like I would just go be a cat in the litter box and
Like that would be and like that would be like you're like, oh, okay. We're gonna go to BRB
He's like using the litter box. I can't reach this you need to fire community Jake
No, I'm sorry
I'm trying to think of all this stuff that I kind of thought of would be like kind of funny for a second
Then I'm like, no, actually, maybe I don't think I wanted really want to do that one. What else stop cutting logs. Oh
Fuck I am you're right
Hey, what about the AS? Yeah, the ASMR stream too. That's another one. That's gone
That was the one where I wanted to have a marching band come in in the middle of the stream and like while I'm still talking
That was another one where I wanted to I wanted to like shit like shave
Do like a oh, it's you're at the barber getting shaved
Stop giving up on these good ideas
I mean, here's the doll look a lot of stuff hits the cutting room floor for various reasons
I'm gonna have full creative control in quotes lol guys
I think that backtracking on the I'm gonna shit in a litter box on stream joke
It's not what you are describing right there with what you just said. I
Think that is very reasonable that I would maybe be like maybe not maybe not that one
He's not he's brand friendly you came up with the idea I
Have a notebook that I I have a notebook that I just write shit in
It's I fill it with shit. This is way too tall. That's gonna be it, right? There we go
What do you say you say what?
Few years ago you talked on on the on criticals podcast about the courtroom thing. What was that?
All right, I can talk about that
I was gonna go on trial for killing Santa Claus and we were gonna have a courtroom and I was gonna be on trial for it
but it wasn't gonna be like a normal court is gonna be like kind of like a magical court and
Santa's lawyer was gonna be like sing his prosecution at the jury and shit and I was gonna get pissed off and
it's gonna be like a magical Christmas stream where I'm just this evil fucking awful person and
The problem there was a lot of stuff that was gonna happen on that stream
Unfortunately
kind of ran out of time because
That was also right in the period where I was gonna start to move. I was right before moving to Vegas and
the you killed Santa routine
Wasn't really relevant anymore. And like a year goes by two years go by and I think in the chat
I made jokes about oh, you know, the legal system sure does take a long time or something, but it never ended up happening
What's happening? What am I doing?
Did I pick up how many logs do I have? This is what I need, right? Oh shit
What do I have? Oh
Yeah stuff hits the cutting room floor
One of the other things I could probably think of what if it's another one that like I was like, yeah, probably not
There is one that I actually still want to do and it's not it's the one we originally brought up
The one that I that was originally brought up is not the one you haven't I haven't said it yet
Because I think that one actually might still happen it's possible
So I'm not gonna spoil that one. I'll spoil the ones that you are guaranteed to not happen like the German daycare stream
Oh, yeah, there's the chocolate factory stream where I was gonna go and pretend like I had a chocolate factory and do this whole
Willy Wonka routine where we had to eliminate people or something. I don't know what that I don't know what fucks wrong with me sometimes
Hey, looks good
More planks. Give me what about your book? Yeah, I know
I'm aware
Eliminate people like you get eliminated from like the like Willy Wonka need more these planks 30 webcam stream
That was another one. Yeah, who will replace me stuff should have been streamers. Well, the reason why I wanted it to be
actors and not like other streamers
it's because
It I don't know having to be other streamers almost feels
Like it's too
Having actors is almost more real to me because like I wouldn't have another streamer to take like they're they're already a streamer
Like if I go let's get a bunch of like streamers together to do this. It'd be like these are just streamers that you know
You don't know any of those actors. Maybe you did
What do you mean actors? I mean the actors that came in to try to take my role from me. So I mean
Thankfully they were actors. Yeah
What are you talking about I got a bunch of actors together
To see like who could do me the best it came down to if we didn't really need them
because I wasn't ready and
we had a little bullshit happen at the end of that stream and thankfully I was able to you know
Do what I needed to do and prove my case to whoever I needed to prove it to of course like dr
Schmolikson and Ludwig and those guys and they took care of that fucking weird guy
one of those weird actor
Yeah, they're like as I was a good actor
They got rid of the actor and I get to continue to do what I want to do and I'm not gone yet
I don't have to stop like I'm fine. Yeah, somebody was shot. What I mean, we figured it out. We got the right person
It's easy. You are the everybody already knows that you could see through it was clear as day
I'm trying to put forth like the illusion
You know of you know, obviously don't want people to think I'm like retiring
Not I'm just still going stir shot you on purpose
Nobody shot me. Okay, I
Did nobody shot me? I?
watched as somebody was being a little ridiculous and
Game was rigged from the start. You're not the real German then. Who am I then?
Huh?
I'm not the real German of a hot cup of cider hot cup of coffee
What?
hot cup of cider
How much more do I need to prove that I'm real?
This is long, huh?
Aaron
Let me tell you something really important though
If that was to be a show where that would happen, right my favorite part of that show
100% besides obviously like the errand stuff is the fact that some you know
People were given material to potentially look at and see kind of you know
Who that person could be and what's that person like on camera?
They may have had a whole package made for them, right if that were if that were the case and the fact that
Oh
Got cider hot cup of coffee hot cup of cocoa is the thing like the aspect the AI
Was given one thing and then wrote a book about it, right? I that's my favorite part is oh, yeah hot cup of cider
That's what I do. That's me
I
Love it so much. Oh
So welcome. How are you? Oh, yeah hot cup of cocoa. Oh, yeah, that's me. That's what I do. That's my thing
That's all I do. Oh
So I loved it. Oh, can I get a look at me, please?
The best part is how everybody wanted to play Dark Souls and
Here okay, so here's some lore on that stream a lot of those guys didn't know anything about Dark Souls
They didn't even know what it was. So watching them struggle with like the mouse and like trying to
Swing and like take one after one by one by one. They would come in. Oh, I'm gonna play in Dark Souls like oh
Okay, I don't think you want to do that
Getting into like the tutorial room and then Octo pimp comes in and just like beats it first try that was so goddamn funny
No, I loved that. That was so much fun again
If you if you don't know we're talking about or if you do
All those audio problems and all like the stream lagging problems
We have like twitch server issues as well as like kind of issues with our connection like at the venue
so a lot of those random audio issues that would like
Most of those are gone in the VOD that's on the archive channel
So it still pops up a little bit but not even remotely close as much as it did before
Okay, I gotta stop like walking up and down the ladder and actually do this. I need them to be thin like that
Okay, we just need to cut down a bunch of trees got it. They gotta be long. Okay speedrun
Is there any behind-the-scenes stuff from that show? Oh, there might be I think there's a few things
Yeah, I know that um, I know Holly had some behind-the-scenes stuff
I think there's a few videos some pictures and stuff that she had maybe we'll see
You know what? I also have which I just realized the other day I have
You know, I don't want you to do that stuff. I have a bunch of cut
Bugleberry hot tub for hot tub footage of stuff that was not in there. It's not on that stream
Maybe I'll like cut that up and just show it
Here release the bugleberry footage. No, stop doing this. There's so many of these planks now
The Elbertson cut how many do I need? One, two, three, four five like one more
I don't do it and then I think this is pretty close. I just put on the top layer
These are these planks. Okay. I actually have a lot of planks already
Good thing. I had these cut. This is a chill game. Even though it's very very simple. It's I don't know. It's cool. I like it
This is what actually a house looks like. How come it's so engaging. I just is it's just I don't know something about it
Just like it's really nice. I love playing games like these on stream
It'll it allows
It allows for some just we can just talk about whatever
It's fun. We can just it just can just sit in the background while we just talk. It's fun
Over here. Oh, I need one more. There we go
It's time for the roof. These are planks as well. Oh shit. It's a lot of planks. All right
Start the process
Got it. My favorite was the one that did the Yoda impression
Yeah, he's great. They were all great though. They were they were all so cool about everything. They're all so fun
They're incredibly talented, too
It just it's so it's cool to because a lot of those guys were just gonna we just had a casting company help us find all
those actors and
It's crazy to see just how
People have so many interesting things that they can do
Talents things that they think are funny things that they can do. I
Love that shit. I think it's it's really cool. I love doing that
So another reason why like okay like for a lot of these things could I just have like a few streamers do it
I mean, yeah, but I think it's more fun to like see
Like other what other people are doing and have some like kind of actors that you don't really know people that you don't see on
stream be able to show
I'm doing stuff. I that's a huge reason why like I mean obviously dr. Spokes and
dr. Smokin is awesome, and he's
incredibly nice wonderful person and
years ago just kind of like just
Roped him into the channel and he's just been kind of here ever since it was awesome
When I knew that I was gonna do that show it's like, okay any judges
What do I want to judge that and then the very obvious choices are like okay who like streamer friends and
Like obviously like stir right stir obviously has been around for a very long time if somebody knows in quotes, Jerma
It's gonna be stir. It's be people like stir italics and like Ludwig Ludwig is like kind of
Like at the last few years. I kind of really started to talk to him and get to know him a little better
so it's kind of like old
German 985 new German 985 and then like dr. Schmeichsen it was it was just fun. It was really cool
I loved it. I told you that that was gonna be one of my favorite streams
And it was I had so much fun doing that show that I'm like sad
It's gone, and I want to do it like I want to do it again. Who is dr. Schmeichsen? I mean
It's dr. Schmeichsen, you know
Doc the doctor, but that's a whole we talked about evolved earlier in the stream and how I'm signed with evolved
It's to be able to do more stuff like that and have shows paid for have brands be able to come in and help
I
Want to do that stuff that stuff means more to me than anything else. I think you guys are you guys know that?
I don't think I have to explain that I love what I'm doing right now because this is its own different kind of beast
Right sitting here streaming a game chillin talking just made fucking around making jokes, whatever
But like I will always remember all those shows and you're probably noticing behind me on the reddit shelf I put
once the show is done I
Put it up there. I put like a little token on the shelf just enough not enough for any reason just cuz like oh
Yeah, I like it. It's like it's a fun kind of memory of like remembering that. Oh, yeah, I remember doing that
That was cool. What about the dagger? I mean that was not supposed to be on there. It was just there temporarily
So I know people probably like why is there like a fucking dagger?
What is what is the dagger for and I mean maybe it is like a little cheesy is like a little corny whatever
Well, I don't it's not it's nice to walk in the room and be like oh, yeah, that was fun
Let us see it. Sure. I mean there's a there's a new addition
There's a couple of there that I think I would want to put something up there for but I haven't as you see
You notice something up there
Yeah, like you got and it's like but streams that I think really had a great time with if you notice on that
I don't think I've really talked about this. It's kind of interesting because I don't think I've ever said this
Look at the games that are up there too. All right, the thing is on there. The movies is on there. See man is up there
Yeah, the the the Funko pops are kind of being pushed out
Oh, yeah, it's that most of that stuff is like
Oh, this is stuff that I stream that I thought was cool
I thought was fun one of the rocks from archaeology, of course Pac-Man the Wii I think what's down there?
I'm gonna remember where's the fedora up there. I think there's a couple other things I should put up there from the New Year's stream
Oh, yeah, the goats from the carnival. The book in the potion is from the hot tub
Hats from the last one the replacement stream
985 is dollhouse obviously grotto beast is right next to it. See man is right there
The archaeology thing is right there the big geode I'm surprised nobody's noticed this one
You see what's all the way in the left on the one two three on the third shelf
You guys see what that is. It's a rat
It's a rat with a Christmas hat on and the Bluetooth is a Bluetooth brush sitting on them. Yeah, I mean it's a little
Is it a little corny? Maybe it's a little corny. Well, I don't know
You know, it's gonna be sad if like I kind of taking that down, right? Oh
Oh
Time to get existential at times to get time to get real again. Oh, I mean a lot of you guys know
that I mean, I'm not gonna do this forever and how I
Decide on when and how that I'm gonna do something else from here. I don't know what that looks like yet, but
eventually
Eventually, I need to start to figure that out and I'm starting to piece together
What I would want to do after this let's let him on the roof. Okay on the other way
All right, whatever. I just need planks. Yeah, like what what do I want to do?
What do I do? I want what do I want to continue to do?
I have a few ideas things that I'd like to do where I wouldn't just like disappear completely, right?
I don't know. I don't know what that looks like yet, but I've I made the reference and I made the kind of I
Teased this in a way when I talked about like how I've been like my 10-year anniversary, which was last year, you know
It's like I don't know how much longer
I'm going to do this, but I'm just gonna keep doing it until I'm done whenever that is
Should run for president. No, I don't want to do that, but it's it's tricky because
You spend so much time doing something right and it's something that you care about cuz think I there hasn't been
Talk about like channel changes and trying to keep myself interested and keep myself going and I
Want to like want to fucking be here in the chair and not like feel like I have to be here in the chair
right, I think that kind of just goes to the reason why like the whole sponsorship stuff and
trying to make things easier from on myself and
There's been a long time to join the circus. Oh
These are too long. No, they're too short. Come on. Well now I fucked this whole thing up. Come here
You're gonna make me cry. No, that's not the whole that's not the intention. This house looks good. This guy can't stop talking about retiring
It's all he talks about
Well, I know you maybe we talked about the reddit shelf and all like the things that are on it and then
Thinking about like the future and then I put some more shows up there and then but but I I'm going anywhere
Like a door. Oh, but realistically speaking
TM I have to start to think about that stuff. I'm not 25 anymore
All right
I gotta start to think about what it means in the future and if I say the word retirement one more time
I will gift
Community steps. Oh, it's still really fun for me. I'm still having a great time
It's still very much something I enjoy doing all the time
As long as I can continue to keep myself interested and enjoy what I'm doing have a lot of fun and be able to create those
Moments and memories for me and for you too. I want everyone to enjoy this channel in this space, right?
I'm gonna I'm still here. You've said all those things like 50 times by now make it 51. Nice
Signs with evolved and does that immediately now?
I'm just saying this is a chill house stream. We talked about this stuff on the house streams
I think this is done is more how much more is there what? Oh, here we go. We're just talking
We're just talking you can go back to reviewing packages now. Okay. Oh
Right. So what do you guys want to see? So I do soups
auto treats
frozen dinners
I'm gonna do this sooner rather than later, by the way
Like this is gonna be the thing that happens after Elden Ring
Nice. Yeah, Elden Ring is gonna come out. We're gonna do that. I'm gonna try to beat it
I've beaten every new souls games on stream when they've come out
The only exception is some of the older ones before I really got into the Dark Souls games
I did Dark Souls 3 I did Dark Souls 1 I did
Sekiro and now we're doing Elden Ring. So I'm gonna I'm gonna
Grind my teeth. I'm gonna grip my teeth and try to beat it. All right. Did I unlock anything else or is that it?
Japanese house it's been three hours. All right, let's move to the AI stuff
We're gonna do AI dungeon or a novel AI. We're gonna try AI dungeon. I'm gonna take a break
We come back. I'm gonna open up AI dungeon. We're gonna try it if I don't like it. We're gonna do novel AI
I'll see you guys in like few minutes two three minutes. See you guys in a minute. Oh, wait a minute. Ooh
What's this I've got some new that's right fresh new
Lord our music I sure do
You want to let you want to do a little listen party because you're about to hear one of the new songs
Let's see, which one should I put on?
About this one
Let's try this one run off home builders music or house builder. Are you ready? I'll see you in five minutes