Meet me in the park. Hold on. I can't meet you in the park yet. Oh my god. You're about to crash the game, aren't you?
Falling me down
I want to go on the roller coaster mom mommy. I want to ride the roller coaster. I'm old enough now. I'm 14
Thanks, mom
I don't think this is not gonna even fit on the track. You do realize this right? It will
Oh my god, this might barely fit in here
I just want to go on I just want to go on the yes. Yeah
Okay, I guess we're going this way oh we're going up the tractor
I remember back in 1962 the first time I went on the rolly
This thing's been here. It's only one of the first wooden coasters in the world
I can't believe this is actually working seriously ready for the super drop. Oh, here's the big drop
Why is someone screaming I don't know I bet I really don't think you can get me though
I'm pretty sure that you are gonna get blocked off no matter what happens
I think stuck
I'm protected by the shrink shit. That looks so dumb
What?
I don't know what happened, but i'm okay with it
That's a dud that's a dud that's a dud that's a dud. I think this one's a dud. Yeah, that's a dud
That's also a dud. Yeah, that's a dud. That's a dud. Yeah, that's a dud. This is dead too. Yeah, that's a dud
This is also a dud. There's grenades of duds
Why what why is the street what is going on hold on
Is this what is this bullshit
I have no idea what you're saying
All I heard was this is so perfect because you really are t1000 in your robot
I am the t1000
And i'll pay seven and a half
These are just going
These rockets are going through your face
Your face is so dumb
Well, I gotta get like a better view of this
You have this expressionless face
How should I get on your bike? I can't go t1000 get us out of here
Yeah, come with me if you want to live. I have no idea what you're saying come with me if you want to live
Stop moving
Dude, there was like 60 people shooting at us. Stop moving
Stop i'm not moving
What is going on
This is
I can't do it anymore. I don't even know where's my parachute
I
Have no control of my character
I'm not controlling my character. I have no control
I seriously dude. All I can do is move the mouse around. He's walking by himself
What is going on? My health bar is breaking
Come can you come find me, please?
Please come you are still robot
God
Oh my god
I'm it says i'm dead right now
But my character started moving on his own and now i'm lying on this roof like taking a breather and I can't do anything
Listen, can you hear this dog? I'm sorry auto. It was just crazy gta
See if you can like make me move and just come come look at me for a second
Come look at me
What the hell is going on?
Can you
You did it worked
You just killed me
I was already dead and you just like ran over me
I can't be this weird
What is this game? How do we always break this game?
Honestly, I have no idea what you just said, but I agree