Play FNAF. Okay, which one? Which one? Okay, what do I have? I have... I have Five Nights at Freddy's
and Five Nights at Freddy's 2. Five Nights at Freddy's 1? Oh my god, you're trying to get me
fucking... Five Nights at Freddy's 1? Alright, let's make a prediction here. I don't think I'm
gonna get past the first night or the second night. 2? 2 is better. I'll do 1. I'll do 1. Alright,
let's go. I bet you I don't even make it past the first night. You know how I play Five Nights at
Freddy's? I close both doors, have both lights on, and I go like this. Cover my eyes, cover my
ears like this and just wait. Alright, let's play Five Nights at Freddy's 1. Whatever.
This is gonna be loud, isn't it? Does it even have graphic options? No, there's no graphics
options in Five Nights at Freddy's 1. Let's see. Is it too loud? I can't even tell if it's being
captured. There we go. Alright, here we go. Five Nights at Freddy's 1. What the fuck is happening?
Okay, I told you I'm not full of shit. This is a Steam Cloud save file. I didn't get past the
first night. You thought I was full of shit? You thought I was making that up? Here we go.
Hello! Hello! Hello! Oh, look out! It's Chicky and Foxy and Freddy!
No, hold on. I gotta do the right way. It's this. Not like this. My brother taught me this when we
were younger. We went to go see the alien ride at Disney World. It was the thing that used to be
the Lilo and Stitch ride and it was terrifying. And he's like, dude, is that what you do? You go
like this, cover with your pinkies and your eyes and block your ears with your thumbs
and you're gonna be fine. Did I make it? How much battery do I have? I even pressed a single
button. No, I told you. I got it. Look at it. They ain't getting in. Not on night one.
Open the doors. No!
Oh, I don't like having the doors open. I hate this game.
How did I not get past night one? Isn't that impossible?
It's actually impossible. Why did I not do it? You must have been zonked.
Why do you treat all video games like a joke? I just beat Cuphead's DLC in like an hour and
12 minutes. I'm sorry. I'm good. I'm gonna lose because I wasted all the power. They don't even
leave on the first night. They actually don't even leave on the first night. I think Freddy
leaves and goes into one other room. Click Freddy's nose in the poster. It's pretty funny.
Yeah, so then nobody moves until like three or four a.m. I think Freddy disappears.
What's that sound? What is that sound? What's that sound? What's that sound?
Did I spawn like a monster or something? I don't know what that fucking sound is.
What did I do? You made me spawn something. I never pressed Freddy's fucking nose before.
I didn't know. Why would it just quit the game? God damn it. I'm sorry. I fucked up. Can you guys
see it? All right. I'm not going to fuck it up. I promise. All right. All right. All right. I can't
see chat either. Is it reasonably good? Why did it quit? Stop quitting. All right. Can you see?
Hold on a second. Just make a few adjustments to my Herman Miller
MBODY chair. Refund this game. Guys, I bought this game like nine years ago. I don't think
the refund. I think I'm out of the seven day window. Refund the bet. Oh, so what are you
talking about? They would understand. Can you imagine trying to refund a game that you bought
10 years ago? I mean, I technically only have an hour and 20 minutes in it. I mean,
I didn't really like it that much. I didn't really get to it. Other games kind of took over there.
It's actually 14 days. Yeah. Don't play this game. I'm scared. All right. Have they moved yet? No.
Oh, I'm running over a thing. POG 87 power left. Yep. What the fuck is going on there? What was
that? What happened? Excuse me. What are you talking about? Excuse me. Why did that happen?
I've never seen that before. And we're fucking around. Why did I do that? I don't know. I just
spawned something. What does that actually do? What does that actually do? Hello. Wait, hold on. Let
me see if I can get it. That was close. Give me an Oscar. No, no, no, no, no. It's wrong. I had it
wrong. It's like, oh, dude, this is why we're fucked. That fucking Foxy comes out of there.
I heard this. My fucking son played this one. Fucking Foxy comes out of there and
sprints down the fucking hallway. It was fucked up. No, I never played this before. I don't know.
Don't look at Foxy. Oh shit. Somebody fucking moved. They walk down halls and stuff. They
fucking walk down the hall. I played it before. I know it. Wait. Oh shit. There it is. Okay.
I'll fucking drop this guy if he fucking comes in my... If he comes over to the door,
I'm gonna fucking drop him. Ain't nobody getting in here now. That was too soon. I don't think it
was. Oh shit. Get out of here. What happened? What? Close the door. Close the door. Close the
door. Okay. I'm good. Six aim coming. Oh no. What are you gonna do? Bulletproof glass. Bulletproof
glass. You ain't getting in bulletproof glass. Who's over here? Oh no. Bulletproof glass. Oh,
I missed it. Fucking good. I'm fucking good. No, we're good. All right. Night two. This is where
it gets a little crazy. This is where it gets crazy. I'm not touching anything until at least
2 a.m. Just get out of the chair and leave. I have a funny idea. What if I just pretend to fall asleep
on stream? All right. I'm gonna pretend to fall asleep on stream. I'm gonna put a text on the
bottom that says like, dude, wicked fucking tired. I had a long day and then you're woken up by the
jump scare. You guys can be like, wake up, dude. Wake the fuck up. Wait, what do I have to do?
Do I have to do a light? How do I stop that from happening? How do I stop that from happening?
How do I stop that from happening? Where is this motherfucker? Uh oh. Uh oh. Where are you? Oh.
Oh, we'll do it on. Oh, we'll do it on night three. Open the doors up. Lights. Why? That's
extra power. They haven't moved. When's it gonna be 3 a.m.? Dude, it's been 2 a.m. for an hour. Oh,
shit. Oh, where are you going? All right. You went that way. You're here. All right. What happened?
I have to keep looking at Foxy, right? Uh oh. What the fuck? What happened? What happened? Is that bad?
Is that bad? Am I okay? Am I actually, am I okay? Am I, am I okay? Am I all right? Why is it
happening? Am I all right? What does that mean? I fucking quit the goddamn game. I exited the
fucking game. No, I didn't. I'm still in. Close the door. All right. I'm good. Is he still there?
What the fuck are you still doing here, you dick? What the fuck is happening? I don't get it. I
don't get it. I actually don't get it. I, guys, I've played Five Nights at Freddy's for a shitty
YouTube video one time and I wasn't even paying attention to the game. All right. Hold on. We're
doing this though. All right. What should I say? Like really tired today. Not like long day. Just
chilling with stream. Whatever. Right. Let's do, and the cam is going to be huge too. And I got to
look realistic. Why would you fucking play Five Nights at Freddy's? Oh yeah. I'll turn the lights
off. Okay. Hold on. Just like, is that all right? Should it be a little brighter? Hold on. Which,
yeah. Put the death counter on too. So people think it's automatic. Right. People think it's
automatically counting the amount of times I die in Five Nights at Freddy's. I've died 600 fucking
times. Okay. Here we go. Make it 15. That's way too many. Maybe like 30 or like 60 or something.
Right. 600 means I've been here for a long time. 62. Right. All right. That's fine. All right. Can
we get some, can I, how about this? All right. That looks good. Let's go. This is going to be
fucking stupid. Can you guys, can you guys see it? Can you guys, you guys can see it, right?
Okay. Here we go. Why would you do this?
Fuck.
No, I was so close. Reset, reset. We got to reset. We got to reset. We got to reset. Reset,
reset, reset, reset, reset. Fuck. You don't know how hard it is to do that. To sit here and know
that there's like 20,000 people all spamming wake up and shit. And I'm some dumb ass that's
why do I have an auto redoing Five Nights at Freddy's death counter? And why am I sleeping
to this? It's, it's too much. It's too much. My brain can't do. All right. I'm going to go. Here
we go. It's so hard. The bottom text is covered by the game. All right. Go, go, go, go, go, go,
go. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Good. All right.
Let's go. I won't fuck it up this time. I swear to God. It's so stupid.
One more try. I swear to God. I swear. I'll get it. I'm so, it's, I'm so hard. It's so hard.
You have no idea. Again, again, I promise. I'll get it this time. I promise. I promise. I swear
to God. I'll get it right now. All right. Everybody shut up. Go and begin fucking telephone.
It's the stupid telephone that keeps it. It's, it's like the phones ringing in the house
and I'm sleeping. Someone's trying to reach me so bad. It's just like, Holy shit, dude,
you're on stream. Get up, wake up, dude. Turn your stream off. Call his fucking landline.
Dude, I wouldn't call your landline at 10 o'clock, but seriously, man. All right. Here we go. I gotta
get this. I have to. I have to get this. I will do whatever it fucking takes. It's just the fucking
phone ringing. Just sitting there. Okay. Dude, wake up. I'm calling your house. Okay. Come on.
Crazy. God damn it. All right. I got it. Hold on. Oh, fucking hell. I don't know if I can do it.
I really don't think I can do it. It's too dumb. This is stupid, right? This is really dumb.
All right. I think I got it out of my system. I had to at this point. Okay. Here we go. You know
what? It's so loud. I just think of, okay, I gotta get it out. I gotta get it out now.
Because the whole thing is when the jumpscare happens, I'm going to fucking wake up and it's
going to be stupid. All right. This is it. I got it. Fuck the phone. It's going to be funny,
but fucking don't listen to it. Fuck you. I can't mute the phone call. It's so funny.
That's like the funniest part of this whole thing. Okay. All right.
All right. I got to get it together. It's after the phone. I'll be, it'll be, it'll be good.
I just have to get through the phone. Once the phone bit is over, I'll be good. I'll be good.
It's just that phone part for real. It's
Yeah. Yeah.
We got it. Well, let's look, there's a candle in my room. That was so hard to get through that
third ring. What happened? That was a rare death screen. All right. I don't care. I'm done. Streams
over. That's fun. That's fun. Yeah. It looks like there's a candle in here. I think that's,
I think that's the one you go on on. It does look like we could fucking blurry, doesn't it?
Okay. All right, guys, that's it. I'll see you guys on.
There's a lot of shit going on. And I have to tell you really, really. All right. I really don't
want to say this, but it sucks. But I'm just, just in case baseball might need to move again,
not far, not far, but might need to move another few days. Would it would work in our asses off
to make sure that we can get what we need. But it's, it's happening within the next like 30 days.
Okay. I know I keep changing it, but we just keep having things that have to change and keep having
venue things that have to happen. And some venues need to change. And it's been a whole ordeal.
We're working on it. So I might have to change it by the way, green screen stuff you have until
the 18th at 1201 midnight to get your submissions in, go read the rules are in the discord right
now. What's the green, what's the green screen thing, dude, the green screen stream. We did a
bunch of shit in front of the green screen. There's three full streams of it. You can do
whatever you want with some rules and go read those rules. You're going to need them delaying
it to next year. No, no fucking way. That's not happening. All right. I'll, I'll see you guys in
a couple of days. Let's see. Maybe I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Yeah. 24th of July, probably
going to do something. Holly and I might do something. So, so I'll see you guys on the fifth
Tuesday. I have no idea what we're going to do, but I'm sure we'll do something. Thanks a lot,
everybody. See you later. Take care of yourselves. Well, we got a few minutes, so we got some time.
Oh, you can do the mod day. Actually, what a great idea. Maybe I'll do that on Tuesday.
Just get a bunch of mods for a few games. It just apt to have an absolute puke stream. I think that
makes sense, right? Tuesday puke stream. I think it makes sense. Yeah. Oh, what was I going to say?
Elden Ring. Yeah. Okay. I got a question. Does Elden Ring have a bunch of mods? Are there fun
things to do with Elden Ring and modding? Okay. Because I got to have to take, I'm going to take
a look. What happened with the Elden Ring PvP? Honestly. Okay. So here's what happened with the
Elden Ring PvP. So I talked to Ludwig and I'm like, oh, hey, this, maybe we can do it with this mod.
And then didn't Twitch Rivals just kind of started doing it? Not necessarily the community
version, right? Maybe. No, they did sort of. So I was like, oh, I guess the tournament stuff
is already happening with Twitch Rivals. So I guess that's kind of what I was planning on doing
stuff like that anyways. So they're doing like, they did like a PvP thing. You can't really use
mods online. Yeah. I got to be careful too, right? Also Dark Souls 3 has a bunch of crazy shit too,
doesn't it? That I never got to. I did the FPS mod. Did you ever revisit inscription? I did
off stream. I got to the third act off stream. It's pretty crazy. I did not beat it though.
What about the Outer Wilds DLC? I don't know. Maybe. I heard the Outer Wilds DLC was
kind of hard. It was like very specific or something, right? Speaking of Ludwig,
did you guys see the Mogul Money Live? God, that was fucking hilarious.
Uh, let me tell you, Ludwig really is, he's got, he's got some chops on him.
That was so funny. He did such an unbelievable fucking job. It's really awesome to see that
whole crew doing that stuff. So yeah, he's very sociable. He's just so, he's just, he just has it.
He just has it. Does he know what I'm talking about? He's just got it. He just has it. You know
what I mean? Did you get your bidet yet? No. But then again, I never took a picture in a
Mega Milk shirt, so we're even. No, it was awesome. It was fun the whole way through.
But yeah, I'll talk to you guys in a couple days. We'll do some mod stuff and see you later. Thanks
for watching. You bet your ass I'm going to get this to exactly six hours. Exactly. On the dot.
There it is. All right. Good night. Call your mother. See you later. Take care of yourselves,
guys. Have a great night.