Anybody notice the name of the stream and the game of the stream?
Nose pimple? Let me turn this up. Nose pimple? Where? I don't see a nose pimple. What are we talking about?
No, we're good. Turn to the side. I got nothing there. You guys are lying.
All right, let's play Rain World for a little bit. By the way, I'm going into this
upset. Let's see if it makes me happy. I'm going to this upset. Let's see if it like,
if you guys were right. And I am not going to hold back any criticisms of this game.
I'm going to criticize it if I don't like it because it was your choice. Five of you. Is this
a controller game or what? Controller? Yep. Look at him. Fucking hell. All right, here you think?
I'm not lying to you. I'm not lying. It's actually opening. It's opening right now.
I swear to God, people think I'm making it up that, oh, he's just, no, he didn't. Yeah, I did.
Uh, hold on. All right, here it comes. I have an Xbox controller. Don't swim. Actual Rain World.
We played him like a fiddle. I want to know. Rain World. The monk. Weak of body but strong of
spirit, in tune with the mysteries of the world and empathetic to its creatures, your journey will
be a significantly more peaceful one. The survivor. A nimble omnivore, both predator and prey,
lost in a harsh and indifferent land, you must make your way your own way with wit and caution as
your greatest asset. The hunter. Strong and quick with a fierce metabolism requiring a steady diet
of meat. The stomach won't be your only concern as the path of the hunter is one of extreme peril.
Meat and plants. That sounds good. And this is where we fall to F4.
Don't ever tell me to fucking play a game. Don't ever force me to quit a game ever again.
Ah, the clap. Wait, so what happened? Oh no, I'm falling. How does this game play?
Was there an actual wink? There was. Yeah, there was. Move this down. Just keep it on.
All right, we have a map. Eat, throw, and jump. Eat, pick up, and eat. This is the map. Okay.
This is pause. All right. And there's also a throw. Okay. Any climb? Can I climb up on stuff?
You are hungry, find food. What do I eat? Play Elderborn or I am leaving. You bastard.
Can I eat that? What is it doing? It's just following me around. I can't eat it. I can't
eat that. Oh, this is the tutorial. I'm trying to eat the tutorial friend. Catch and eat them.
Oh, eat it. And it's X to eat. Okay. Eat. Four is enough to hibernate. Hibernate. How do you
hibernate? My character's pretty cute. Do you evolve or something? Jump and grab them. They're
delicious. I thought I said I was already full. Additional food above four is kept for later.
Kept for later. Okay. You are full. I can't eat any more food. I can't hear anything.
I'll fix that. Okay. Let's go. Elderborn waiting room. Nope. This is what you're getting.
Leap the gap. That didn't work. This game is terrifying. And then hold A. Okay. Down,
down A. What the fuck are you trying to tell me to do? Okay. Briefly tap down to crouch.
That's what I just did. When crouching, hold the jump button without giving other input.
And then let it go and move in a direction. Okay. That was not very clear. Rain is coming.
Find shelter. Does this count as shelter? Run. What do you mean run? This place is safe. Stay
here to hibernate. Continue? Should I go? I evolve. I think I'm a new creature.
Go explore. There is food and shelter to be found, but beware of predators.
All right. Oh my God. This is a big map. All right. So I'm going to go up, up this way.
Game's kind of rad. We'll see. We'll see. Objects can be picked up, carried, and tossed.
Wow. Why would I want to do this though? What am I throwing it at?
I mean, that's definitely to fight off shit. All right. Let's eat all this food. Eat the food.
I can't eat two at the same time. Why not? Okay. Two more. What happens if I'm out in the rain?
Will I get, you die? Is that like the death scenario? All right. Well, I've eaten.
I can make that. Maybe I can't. I can just climb it. Well, there's nothing even over here.
Oops. What? Oh, I didn't know you could do that. Okay. Okay. Well, now you know.
That really do very much. Uh, I guess I could go that way. I climb up. Let's go over here.
When we sit with any smilers, what is that? What do you mean? Any smilers?
I need a stick to throw over there. Enable smile on BTTV. Should I?
All right. I can't get in here yet. I go from here up. I think I need to throw a stick over there.
What about down here? Oh, I got it. This is a stick right here. All right. Climb this.
What's in my hand? It's a rock. Okay. Can't find this. There we go. All right. And then
can I climb from here? I guess I'm just going to go this way. There was some life support.
I'm trying to like go up there. I mean, I know this exists. I was trying to see if I could do
this first. Can I kill it? Here is a strange energy. All right. Hold on. I'm going way too far.
I'm going way too fast. I eat this thing. Eat the weird flower. All right. Pick up the rock.
In case that lizard comes back and I'll throw it right in his head. Okay. I should leave.
This is probably a bad idea. Whoa. Am I prey? Am I prey to this guy? I might be prey. All right.
I'm going to say, what do the blue circles mean? Does that mean like, hey, go here. You got to go
here. I'm going to go right. You're prey to everything. All right. Where am I now? Maybe
I should go up. Should I go from here? I'm going to go up, I guess. And then I got a stick.
I'm bringing a stick over here. Courage the cowardly dog. OST. Why does it have to be an OST?
All right. So now I have a stick. Now let up. I go up here. Okay. And then again,
this is a shelter. I don't understand what this is doing.
Is it a wink? No, this doesn't. Hold on. My eyes are getting flooded. Okay. I need to eat more
food. I'm going to go down. I'm going to go to the left. Down and left. Still have my stick? I do.
It's crying. What do you want? Oh, it's saying food, food down here. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
There's food over here. I'm going to keep going left. Can I eat those? Can I eat the plants?
Can I eat these? Can I like tear something off and eat it? Who wins? Can I come in there
clean up and eat it? No, they're still alive. I don't think I can. I guess I'm going to go over here.
Food that way. Can I go up? All right. I'm going to sneak around here. Why am I going this way?
This seems like a really bad idea. Food. I don't think it should be doing this.
They're going to come back and kill me or something. Oh, he's dead. All right. Now throw
this spear in the back of his head. All right. I'm going to get scraps. Bring him back to my cave.
This is food for a week. Uh oh, uh oh, uh oh. Do you know I'm here?
Eat this. Why can I eat it? Eat it. Eat it. Eat it. Why won't he eat it? Why won't he eat it?
I was thinking maybe that would work. What is this in here?
Gee. All right. Give me, give me a bat. I need to eat something.
Uh, I don't think it should be able to open like this. Oh my God.
Eat that plant. Eat this plant. Quick. Eat it. All right. Eat. Why can I eat this? Eat.
It's X, right? Eat. How do I eat this plant? It's not food. Everything is food in the goddamn wild.
Come here. Oh, fuck. I think I just. Oh, okay.
Are you stupid? Oh my God. They're finding me. In that hole.
Wait. Oh, the rain's coming. What's a shelter look like? What's a shelter look like? I don't,
I don't know. What do you mean you don't know? I don't know what a shelter looks like on the
minimap. Am I safe in here? Oh my God. Holy shit. Where do I go? But that's it. That's it. No,
it's not. I'm right here. Okay. What is, what is it? What does it actually look like? That sphere.
Hold on. But they have, they, they have that like a circle. It's a square. Okay. This is pretty cool
actually. So let me remember where this is. So right there is, so we're going to go right this time.
We'll go down to the left. That was right again. I don't love it. I think it was all,
I think it's all right. What? I'm going to go right. All right. Any food? Will you leave me
alone, dude? All right. So left and then up. So up here is a shelter. You got to remember that.
Holy shit. Oh, fuck. But I've just, we just went by each other. We just called each other at the
same time. There's still a way to go over this way. Can I get in? Like once we're here? Wait,
bats. Eat. Eat a bat. All right. Good. All right. Better than last time. I'm, I got,
I got a full stomach. I'm going to go underneath. Now I'm going to go Harbinate, but I want,
I want more food. I want even more food than this. I know I got like a bad nerd neck and I don't,
trust me. I'm aware of it. All right. Now we're good. Now we go back to, is that spikes?
All right. Let's go. Let's get out of here. Wait, there's a shelter right here.
It was saying shelter, shelter right here. Shelter. I can't reach that. Come on. I can't.
Am I down? Where am I? We're both in the same tunnel. Get out of my way. All right. I'm fucking
at it. I'm just going. Just go, go, go. Just get out. Get the fuck out of here. Get out.
Just go. Get me out. Give me the fuck out. Give me the fuck out. I'm just going to the other
shelter I was in before. Give me the fuck out. What is that? Why is there so much shit over here?
Okay. Let's go left. Left again. And then there's a shelter right in here. Right. It's right.
Left and then up. Okay. Cool. Oh, right. My stream title is still that. Only streaming
for 20 minutes. Oh man. It really does say that. Whatever. All right. Let's hibernate.
This is my house. Get out of here. You can't come up here Kenny.
All right. So now we level up again. What is this? I thought you were going to play Wayne's World.
I tried to play another game and I got annoyed by it. Everyone was jumping on.
Five people told me to play this and I was like, all right, this game's kind of cool. And then,
uh, and then you can't hear me right. Cause I don't know why this game is so loud.
Why is it so loud and then so quiet? All right. Let's keep going. Where do I go from here?
Anywhere, right? It doesn't matter. Do I keep going right? I feel like there's something over
there, but there's food down here. Get over here. Did I get it? Nice. Eat it. This is a pack of
cigarettes. What the fuck is that? What? Holy shit. There's a lot of food over here. We're going to
get back over here this way. You are also food. Oh, exhibit a cycle three outskirts cycle three.
You are also food. Yes, I am. Let's go eat it. Fill up. You don't want to, you don't want to bat.
Let's fill up. And then we're going right back to fucking bed again. Eat it. Watch out for that
weird lizard snake thing. Don't wake him up. This is like, I feel like I'm playing Oddworld.
All right. Back to bed. All right. Where's the shelter? It's down. I guess I go back up and
I could go all the way down. No, just, you know, down into the left. That's like a far away though.
Let's go right and then up or avoid eating enough food. All right. Let's just, let's just go back.
No, let's go down, down, down, down, down, down. I stayed a little, I've been up here for a long time.
Let's go down again. Yeah, we're going to go down and then when I come out, I'm going to go right
and then down. I'm fully fed. All right. Let's go sleep. Close my door. Close the window. Wait,
what? Evolve? Okay. So I'm going to go all the way right. There's no evolving. Slug cat is a
perfect being. All right. Where do I want to go? I want to go down this way. So we're going to go
up, right, and then down. Why is this bigger? Wait, what are you doing? Why is he showing me
like a movie? He's still going. Yeah. I said today was going to be longer. Can I go down from here?
I guess I can't go down. What does this take me if I go up? Can't go down. Shit. Okay. I'll keep
going right. I got, I got stuffed last time. Right. And then right again. And then Ray,
I was going to go right, right until I can't go right anymore. But don't get killed by. Oh,
fuck. Just run away. Why are there two of them now? The game is really quiet. Yeah. It's unfortunate
because the game is really quiet. And then when I get bit, it goes to 5 million decibels. Okay.
This is where I ended up last time. And I freaked out because there was, there was like a giant
mosquito over here last time. Yeah. We're going to go right. And then up. So here we go.
And I eventually eat the giant mosquito. I got to go where he is. He doesn't know where I am,
right? Like, how do I get in there? Actually anything we'll do in here. Um, I have a stick.
I got to get this stick to stick on there. And I, I'm going to kill him. I'm going to throw this.
Should I throw it at him? Can I get this to stick right here? If I jump? No, I want to try to get it.
I'm not going to happen. Cause I can't like get up here. Wait, how did you do that? Wait, how do you
do that? Hey, thanks for the tip. And let's get in here. Okay. This is new. Now this is how you get
up here. And then I'm going to go up. Can't grab this. No. Wait, can I go in here? Oh, all right.
This goes all the way up. Um, get in there. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to do. Is there even a way to go? No, this is like the top of the world. There's nothing
even over here. Like there's nothing in here, right? No, there's nothing here. No, I can't do
anything about this. I got to go. Like let's go right now. Okay. Go, go with that. Uh, I need to
find the shelter for the rain now. I haven't even eaten. I haven't even fucking eaten anything.
Fucking animals are in here. Wait, wait. I should eat one. Is there any? I gotta, I gotta go. I gotta
go. Nice. Oh, I made it back. I made it back to where I. All right, cool. Let's go. I need to eat
something though. Right now. I mean, you little shit. Get over here. Eat. Oh, okay. Now I actually
have to eat a ton of stuff. So this is what is the final point where before I go in the way,
the survivor, right? I got to go to thought I was in uncharted territory, but apparently not.
Where do I go? All the way left, all the way down. I'm going to say left. I need to eat food
all the way there though. Before it's a disaster. Nothing. No bugs or anything I can eat. All right.
Left. Uh, okay. I haven't been all the way down. All right. We're going to just go left all the
way left, left, left, left, left, left. Bottom left. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away
from me. What? Okay. That just stunned him. All right. Move. Is he going up or down or around?
He's going. What's he doing? Oh fuck. I'm going to do that too. Hello. What? What do I have in my
hand? Give me another kid. Where the fuck am I? Where am I? Oh, can I die? Okay. In the vent.
Can that thing kill me in a vent? I feel like it could have. That's why I was freaking out.
Yes. Yes, it can. Okay. Yeah. Of course it can. All right. Same deal. That's a cool move. Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I went two screens. I eat those weird mushrooms.
All right. Where am I? Something over there on the left. What's, what's this? Is it food over here?
I eat this. Wait, what? What's, what's the food that's right here? Bones or something. I don't
understand. What is here? Uh, what's, what's the, what does the bones mean?
Is food on the floor? I don't see anything. You died here. Oh, okay. Wait, that's in here.
Double bat snack. Nice. Okay. I just need one more. Uh, this, I don't know what this G thing is. Let's go
all the way up and left. What is that indicator for? I can't get in. My hands hurt.
And this doesn't do anything. I can't eat this either. Right. Is that one, there's one spot to go
over here. Can I go anywhere else from here? I think I already did. I'll just eat. I have eaten
completely. Maybe it was just sleep. I missed one to the left, but down. Eat and then sleep.
Eat and then sleep. Uh, is this just a shelter writer? Well, um, God, this Barry's over there,
though. Where the hell am I going? Um, what is, what is that? It's like a, like a villain vine.
Don't touch that. That's like an evil vine. Don't eat it. Can I, can I buy it? It's like,
right or something. Eat, eat. Uh, this is a dead end. What's this one? Also a dead end.
You gotta hurry. Oh fuck. All right. This is, I know there's something down here though. All
right. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Um, but is that thing gonna, is this thing alive?
This thing looks, it's alive, isn't it? Get out of the fucking way, man. Get out of the fucking way.
Go get, fight each other or something. Go down there and start getting attacked and run away.
Run. Out. Out. Out. Get out of the way. Oh, come on. Get out of the way. What? I grabbed it.
I grabbed it before and it didn't do anything. I just lost fucking points for that.
I was, can I get off of that? Yeah, that was horrible. All right. Let's do, let's do it again.
Same place. I want to go to the same place. That fucking stupid lizard didn't go like this way,
that way, this way, that way, this way, that way, this way, that way. I would have been fine.
He was scared of the vine. He eventually did it.
Uh-uh. Auto, just wait that way. That was, that's very cute. What a cute dog.
All right. Again, all the way to the left. And then we go down. Just wait that way. Just wait
that way. Just wait that way. Can't get into G. All right. It's tempting, but don't do it.
Just got to go down. Very. Eat, stand up and eat. What are you doing? Eat. Where's the other one?
Over there. All right. Give me, uh, give me a couple of bats. Hey, but wait, I'm good. I could
explore. I need, want to eat a couple of bats. Come here. Just wait. They'll come back out.
I wouldn't even ready for it. I wouldn't even ready for the bat when it came out. I wouldn't
even ready. Did I let you go? What am I fishing? Oh, fuck. He got it. You. All right. Let's get
back. What is this thing? Is this evil? That looks like an evil plant. It is. It is evil.
I'm going to bed. Get me out. So I got to go. It was down. Where was it? Down to the right.
Watch out. He's all right. Get me in here. Delta. Nice. Delta. Watch out for the vine.
All right. Well, now at least I get to go back up where it was.
Hold on. I have to like crack my chest. What do I think of this game? It's pretty, it's fun. It's
good. It's very, very interesting. It's very fun. All right. Now I want to go. I want to go down.
Wait. Somebody said there was an evil vine down here. Oh my God. It was this one. I want to go
down. Can I go down from here? I don't think I can go down from here. Oh, I hate this thing.
Can I go down here? No, no, no, no. Don't. Don't even. Come on. Really? Really? You're going to
dump through two alligators on me. I got to go through this. Okay. There's berries here.
What is that thing? What the hell is that? Why are they doing this? A snake? I'm going down.
Uh, is we're beetle coming over here. All right. I got full, uh, I got full food.
Where is this? I'm going to go down. It's just water. It's fine.
Sandbox item unlocked. Sandbox item. New arenas unlocked. Hello? What was that? Open the door.
Open. Open the door. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. Rainage system. Wink.
Wink. Why am I going over here to swim with this guy? Hold on. I hear Otto. I think I have to go
talk to Otto. Otto is like, okay, let me go get Otto. Am I dead? Why can I not go in there anymore?
Wait, what? I hold on. I can let me go get Otto. I'll be right back. So you can drown. You can
drown. I guess I am an animal. It makes sense. Show Otto. Hey. Hey, you. You want to be on camera?
Please read important to sewers. Uh, you're going the wrong way. This is not the way you
would have gone wrong way. It's an optional hard area. Otto, you want to go out on camera?
Uh, he doesn't want to be on camera. He wants, he wants to go outside.
He's like, oh, I didn't want to come in here, dude. He's like, I want you to take me out.
He's like, get me out of here. Get me out of here.
He wants to go outside. I'll be right back. He also wanted some food. I gave him some food.
He's just down there having a good time with Otto. I just drowned too, didn't I?
Did I, did I devolve again? I did, didn't I? On a scale of one. Just wait. That way. Just wait.
Oh my fucking God. And that concludes the super stream. I'm done.
Oh, that's evolved again. Fuck. Oh, come on. That was the best 20 minutes ever.
Fuck no. One. All right. One more try. What are you doing here? Get out of here. This is,
Oh, we both did the same thing. Are we both streaming the same time?
What are you afraid of me? He's afraid of me. Wait, he's afraid of me. He's afraid of me. Can I kill
him? He's afraid of me. All right. No, no, no. Wait, no. Eat. Eat him. No, wait. Do you want him?
Wait, eat him. You have him. You can have him here. You can have him. What? Oh shit. Don't move.
Can you see me if I don't move? Get over here. Idiot. I want to touch that thing, right?
Act for safe. Face cam. Okay. Same deal. I want to go back down, but this time don't go into the
sewer. Am I going into the sewer? Is there, there's nowhere else to go from here, right?
I can go up. Can I eat these bugs? The sewer is a big no. Okay.
Fuck. Come on. Do it. All right. Okay. Let's try to, let's try to crack my ribs.
God damn it. Why does my rib cage have to suck? What's wrong with him? I'm trying to,
I'm trying to like push my rib cage. So I go, hold on. Ah, auto step on it. It's not going to work.
Okay. All right. So those of you that don't know what's happening. So I have costochondritis.
And sometimes it's fucking really, really hurts like in here and like back here. So if I.
Okay. We're good. Yeah. It's a pain in the ass. It's a real pain in the ass. You just got
diagnosed with that too. Are you serious? It sucks. It's a real, it's a, I'm not touching the flower.
What do I want to go from here? Can I go up from this way?
Oh, I'm going to call it. I'm going to call it here. Yeah. It's probably a good idea.
So I can stretch it and move around and probably take a bath. Yeah. I don't want to push it. You
know, it's from, if I'm sitting down, you want to do stretch stretching with German. There we go.
Ready? Oh, okay. Okay. That feels good. Sweaty yoga. If I push my chest out like this, it feels
better. I felt pretty good. Did that feel good for you guys chat? You will full screen. No,
I'm so disgusting right now. All right. Ready? You know, what actually feels really great
is if I bear hug myself and like squeeze pimple on nose. Oh, I'm, I'm hugging you guys.
Come over here. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I got as much as I want to stick around for another hour or so.
I'm going to call it here. I'll call it here. I'll call. I got to take care of my body. Drink plenty
of water. Yeah. I think it's, you know what it is. Maybe it's the way I'm like, I don't have my
boomer brace on idiot. I'm not wearing my boomer brace and I'm sitting here for eight and a half
hours. What the fuck am I thinking? Actual idiot rookie mistake. Yeah. We'll, we'll, we'll slow
it down here. We'll call it here. I'll be live tomorrow with, uh, either mega man legends or
Nintendo Wii. Last stream ever. That's not true. Uh, no more heroes is on the table,
but I kind of want to play the bachelor. I could keep playing this too tomorrow.
Maybe we could start with this or start with a Wii or something because this game is actually
pretty fun. Rain world and then the bachelor two quality games. All right. I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Uh, tomorrow we're going to start at the normal time. So we're not starting at
noon tomorrow. We'll be starting around two. Thanks for sticking around. I'm glad at least
I got to sit here for at least eight and a half hours, a little more because we're doing the end
of the stream. So I'll see you guys tomorrow. I'm going to say this would be nine hours,
nine hours. Have a great night guys. See you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves.
I can stretch and wear a boomer brace if you need to. Nine hour streams of fun. Yeah. I just,
I really should have been wearing this. It really crept up on me. The last like 40 minutes
it was okay, but it really just, no, it just fucking crept up on me pretty hard here in the
last like 20 minutes. Don't know why. What's this called? It's called costochondritis inflammation
in my rib cage that connects where my sternum connects in my chest and on my spine. It's a
beauty, but I was, I was getting to the end anyways. That probably wasn't going to stream
for more than another 30, 40 minutes in that game. So it's all good. I'm good to go. All right. What
do you say? Let's do the bits and the subs and all that great stuff. All the support you guys give
the stream. Thank you guys. Uh, do I, where's my stream? Let's go open it up, but we'll see
tomorrow. I'm going to go take a nice hot bath and then an immediate cold bath. That'd be awesome.
Freak.
That sounds like hell. Cold plunge. Dual welding bath. He's tempering himself.
Hey, I'm a pain. Thanks for the 250. Hot wheels. Thanks for the thousand bits. Dermot, I've been
lurking for years, but finally subbed for two months. Two months ago. Thank you for that.
And I wanted to give you some bits and tell you that you've been a significant part of my teenage
years. On Friday, I had an interview at Universal Studios to work with the film studio. It's the job
of my dreams. I find out if I get the job next week and I just wanted you to know that you got
me through some of the hardest moments in my life. Thanks, Dermot. That's pretty awesome. Hot wheels.
That sounds like an awesome job. Hopefully you get it. Good luck to you. We got a movie star coming
up potentially here. Seriously though, I wish you the best of luck. Thanks for the thousand bits.
Autumn Dragons. Thanks for the 250. Hi, Dermot. I'm getting back into the Mega Man series after
nearly a decade and I can't wait to watch you stream Mega Man Legends, be it tomorrow
or today. And now a question for you. Okay. All right. How much of the many Mega Man series are
you into? Mega Man X is the only one I really actually played, if I'm going to be completely
honest. Mega Man X is really... Mega Man X and Mega Man X 2. The ones for Super Nintendo.
The only ones that I really cared about. I played the original one or two or three of them
for the regular Nintendo. But once I got past two or three, I was just done. I was just like,
ah, that was fun. And then Mega Man X came out. I really got into that. I played Mega Man Legends
too as well. Regular Nintendo versus the Super Nintendo. That's right. Yeah. Not aware I left
them. Wembley. Thanks for the 250, Dermot. I've been playing the 500 sub video before working out
to get me pumped up for lifting. It's a good video to do too. Any good tips for working out?
Not anymore. And I feel like people probably have so much better stuff to say about lifting
than I do now because I just haven't done it in so long. I've been out of that for like seven
plus years at this point, truly. So I don't really have any advice for it anymore.
Just eat balanced food. Eat a balanced diet. And don't eat tahini paste every day like I did.
It's not good for you. I mean, it is good for you, but not in a high amount of quantities.
Thank you, though. Good luck on your workout journey. Curr Bumble. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Will you be able to give any kind of heads up for the GameCube stream? I really want to make
sure I don't miss you playing Gotcha Force. And I still can't believe you even know that exists.
Oh, yeah, that's I will make it very clear that what I'm going to be playing
because I want a chibi robo and Gotcha Force are going to be back to back probably.
And then of course, I got Super Mario Sunshine too. That is the case. I can't wait for chibi
robo, man. That's going to be so much fun. I don't even know if I'm going to like that game,
but I'm going to play it. And it was a ton of money. We'll see. But yeah, I'll definitely let
you guys know when I'm going to be doing the GameCube streams. It'll probably be
probably either next weekend or the week after that. But like the week of that, like the 24th,
25th, maybe because it's still I have a couple things planned for the next few days.
We'll see all of one zombie. Thanks to the 250 you ever considered instead of a wink,
you could read popsicle stick caliber jokes that wouldn't require the webcam. I'd buy a joke book
so you don't die of a heart attack after three months. Somebody also suggested you read a line
from a children's book. Just have jokes open. Well, yeah, that's pretty good idea. But then
I'm going to get a shitload of minus two. It's the shit I didn't even say. If I read popsicle
stick jokes, people are going to minus two every time it happens. See, they're already doing it.
I didn't even do anything. Well, that's the joke. Ah, fine. I'll get it. I'll do some research on
that. And be farming minus two is yeah. Apple shift. Thanks for the 250. Hey, what's your
favorite accent to hear and favorite accent to do? Favorite accent to hear is
Irish and favorite accent to do is Irish. Done. Also, happy, happy late Valentine's Day. Thank
you. Apple shift. I appreciate it. Happy Valentine's Day to you too. It's too bad you suck at it.
I really don't. Sometimes I do. But like, for instance, right now, it's, it's not very bad.
It is pretty bad. But it's been eight and a half hours. Almost nine hours. That's not even bad.
That's fine. That's not even bad. That's not bad. That's not very bad. That was good. That sounded
like I came right from Ireland. Hey, nondescript civilian. Thanks for the thousand bits. Bravely
default OST, please. Maybe next time. Ireland, Missouri. What the fuck? Gnarly. Thanks for the
250. I hope one of the 20 games you bought is Bowser's Inside Story. Sorry to tell you it's not.
In all seriousness, though, have you ever, you ever going to stream an RPG in the future?
I have Chrono Trigger installed. You remember for three or four months ago, I talked about how
I wanted to play that. I remember after Mario RPG was like, what would you do next? And I was like,
well, Chrono Trigger is one of my favorite games ever made. And then I saw Vinny was playing it.
And I was like, well, great minds fucking think alike. Great minds have 500 IQ together. Remember
when I was playing Diablo 2 and he came over, he was like, oh, this is like my favorite game ever.
Well, yeah, like brilliant fucking incredible minds think alike. You like Chrono Trigger,
but not Final Fantasy. Great minds also click 13.8 clicks per second. Yeah.
Oh, you motherfuckers. I forgot about that. It's been a long stream. It's been like kind of a long
day. I've like forgot that that happened. That was if I, I was going against somebody streaming
my face and shit and, and I, they were beating me and oh, that was wild.
Hey, whole of one zombie. Thanks for the 250. I tried eating some raw tahini. It tastes like
sand. You think the beach tastes like hummus? How would you eat raw tahini? Unless you were trying
to do the dumb thing I was doing, which is not smart and you shouldn't do it. Derma 13. Thanks
for the 250 bits. Uh, nine eight five. We've got a problem. The old warehouse has been reactivated
presumably by a malicious actor and the defective models have gone missing. Commissioner Derma 3
wants to see you in for some questions by Wednesday. And yes, this likely means that Derma 65
is back online and is already planning his next move. That doesn't sound good. That does not
sound good. It's okay though. I am the 905th, 985th iteration of this thing. I've got fucking all
kinds of like, I've got laser fingers and shit. He doesn't have that. I'll be fine.
He had programmed him with one eye. So I got two of those. I'll be okay. We're going to be fine.
Don't worry. Derma 13 again. Thanks for the 250. Uh, additionally, we have reason to believe that
model 65 has been retrofitted with the experimental Jax module that was designed for you. Well, now
you've got me a little bit concerned and is now posing an even more serious threat. We need to
act fast. Hope we can rely on your help. 13 out. Well, why did, why did you guys let this happen?
What the fuck are you guys doing over there? Good luck. Hey Reaper, thanks for the 250. Hey
Derma, this paperclip game is too boring that I actually fell asleep for an hour. I just woke
up and I can see that I missed nothing. You missed me. Come on. Thank you. Hey Peaceful
Haley, thanks for the 250. Derma got some good news. I got affiliate. Sick. It only took me a
month or so. And yesterday when you didn't stream, I did. And I got nine fucking subs
first day on affiliate. Fuck yeah. I want to say thanks to the chat members who supported me. You
guys are awesome. And thank you. Derma as well for inspiring me. Who knows? I may rival you someday.
Well, let's fucking go. Bring it on. Okay. I can't yell anymore. That like hurt the O and on just
like hurt my back. I'm all right. I just want, you know, sometimes, you know, sometimes I just
want to just go into the dryer and turn it on. You know what I mean? Like maybe I'll feel better
when I get out. Like just like, I feel good. That was a good dryer therapy. But good luck Haley.
That's, that's pretty sick. Nice work. RNG physical therapy. Yeah. I got another appointment to go to.
I have another appointment to go to. I'm doing PT twice a week now. So yeah, let's hope it works.
Thank you Haley for the 250. Thank you Wembley TTV. Thanks for the 250. If you always wanted,
you can go into a money exchange and ask for the Iranian rile, the Venezuelan sovereign boulevard
and remember to get a few wheelbarrows to take the money home. I don't like they have those just
in your local bank. Do they? Cause I'm not even sure they carry Canadian. If some of them do maybe.
Hey, Peter, thanks for the, oh, the inflation thing. Right. Yeah, that's right. That's right.
Hey, Peter, thanks for the 300 bits. They say cool guy. Back at it again. Cool guy. Thank you,
Peter. Uh, itachi. Thanks for the 300 bits. No message, just 300 bits. Five community subs from
Peter. Thanks for the subs, Peter. 20 community subs. We caught it earlier from Morkus Borkus.
Thank you, Morkus. Thousand bits from Mr. Him. Thanks for the 10 bucks, Mr. Him. Money from my
favorite e-clan. Love you, Jerma. Thank you. Thanks for the thousand bits. Jujojrotter.
Thanks for the 500 bits. They say hi. Thanks for the five dollars. Hi, back to you.
Jujrotter. Jujrotter. All right. Mr. Him gave five dollars on top of the 10 dollars. Thank you,
Mr. Him. Appreciate that. Hey, many rabbits. Thanks for the 300 bits. Appreciate it, many rabbits.
My best friend from college was sent back to Brazil after I graduated. We got into contact
again three years later. In our first conversation after three years, we found out we both were on
your stream together for months without knowing it. One of the most surreal and happy coincidences
I've experienced in my life. Thank you for so many hours of pure joy. Holy shit, that's awesome.
It's given me the capability of changing my life for the better since then. You're a great
entertainer and a wonderful person. That's really, really, that's really awesome. That's so weird. I
can't imagine how fucking weird that would be. Imagine just like, that's pretty cool. Thanks,
many rabbits, and go where your friend is. Thanks to them too. Appreciate it. Gooberry Juice. Thanks
for the 250. Jeremy, here the score is currently of people racing you. Oh, I've, I already won.
Well, did I win? How many of you guys were playing this when I was playing it? Poseidon Shadow has
about 50 million beat that person. If he's best, he wasn't racing you. He was figuring out Windows
2000. Okay. Fluffy Dragon would have beaten you, but his computer froze. He still might beat you.
Hexerman, about 20 million and going. You got this. Roju, 150 quadrillion. Pog,
Redski, 300,000. Don't give up. Hey, Tangy, thanks for the 250. Last month, Cheez-It was finally
brought to Canada. What, you just didn't have Cheez-Its? So I bought a box to try them and they
were better than I expected. I always thought that you were over-exaggerating, but they really
are better than any cheese flavored cracker. Yeah. Welcome to the dark side. They never were in
Canada. That's weird. That is really weird. Why? I feel like they should be. I feel like they would
be. Hey, Jules, thanks for the 250, Jules. And they say, Hey, Germa, my brother said that while
he was watching one of your streams a long time ago, you said your name originated from you not
washing your hands after using the toilet. The toilet handle and your privates are full of germs.
Hence the name Germa. Please tell me this isn't true. Typical tip was older brother. Is it an
older brother? Typical older brother. Don't listen to a goddamn word that he has to say.
Older brother. Real wink. Hold on. Oh my God. Teyon, thanks for the 250 bits. I was racing you
I beat you by the way, but to be honest, I had no idea what I was doing 90% of the time.
That was, it was a fun game. I had a lot of fun. We could just sit there and talk and just hang
out. Stretch. I might need to like, I might actually, I might take a little walk. I'm going
to take like a lubricated walk. I don't know what that means, but I feel like I do. Hey, Bitslave,
thanks for the 300 bits. Appreciate it Bitslave. Germa, it's me Bitslave again. And it would mean
the world to me. You didn't say that. It would mean a lot to me if you checked out my video on
the gamer drink of the day. Thanks for buying with wonderful and gaming drink of the day.
This is like, this is like, this is alcohol. So how is this? Why is this a gamer drink?
Maker's Mark, Kentucky. Why is this? Why is this a gamer drink? Maker's Mark,
Kentucky bourbon whiskey. It's handmade. It's distilled, aged and bottled by the Maker's
Mark distillery incorporated in Star Hill Farm, Loretto, Kentucky, USA. All right.
Let's get this started. What are you doing? Are you going to drink it? You didn't like it.
You didn't like it. You clicked on an ad. You clicked on an ad. Shit. Let's get this started.
Well, I'm a Johnny Walker guy myself, but you know, ads are getting out of control.
Thank you Bitslave for the review. But it wasn't even a review. You just drank it and went,
ow. Will you marry me? Don't get me wrong. It'll be in name only. After we're married,
you'd still be free. You can date anyone you want. I mean, you can sleep with anyone you like. I don't
mean to be rude, but I'm not physically attracted to you. I'm sorry. What it means is I'm not
attracted to any streamer. All my relationships are with real men. I won't touch you. We'll go
to a hospital, have artifice. Okay. Goodbye. Thanks for the grant. Thanks for the five dollars.
Chris Bach. Thanks for the five dollars and 10 cents. Thanks for letting me shut off my brain
for 20 minutes watching your stream. You're welcome. It's news and comfort. Thanks for the
400 bits. I don't know if it's funny or sad, but all the recent times you've played a game,
I recommended. Chat hated it. Anyway, next time you play music on stream, can you finally play
the Yonoid 2 into the Void OST? Write it down somewhere. I've been wanting you to play that
for ages. All right. I'm going to keep it in a tab right now. We'll play it tomorrow. Also,
you can play the game too, to be honest. Yonoid 2. Wasn't there like a coffee
pasta about that like seven hours ago? I got it open. We're going to play it tomorrow.
Spliceable Spleen. Thanks for the five community subs. Appreciate it.
For real though, thanks for the 300 bits. Since you recently said your favorite 40k
faction was the communist space anime fish. I mean the Tao. What? I was thinking you should
play 40k game like Fire Warrior. Baby. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey, let's get the credits
rolling. All right, it's rolling. I lean side to side. Let's build a gamer birdhouse. I already
did that and everybody hated it. And like a thousand people, it's a favorite stream and
like people like, I get gas lit saying that it was everyone loved it. Thanks for stopping guys.
I loved it. I loved it. I loved it. See? I unironically loved that birdhouse. All right.
See? Wasn't it nine hours long? No, it was not. How long was that stream? That was a nine hour
long stream. 12 hours? No, it wasn't. Why would it be that long? But here's all the subs from
tonight. Thank you guys. We'll see you tomorrow. Still about four or five bits to do. We'll take
off. It was 14 hours combined. No, no, it was not. The longest stream I've ever done was like 13 and
a half. Hey, Black Bear CJ. Thanks for the 300 bits. Have you tried putting your hands in the
prayer position behind your back or doing the over the shoulder behind your back,
grabbing your hand, stretch to crack or unsolicited advice. I just have fibromyalgia
and those two things. And those are two things that are always good for me.
Good to go for me to crack everything in my torso. You know, I have this foam roller
that if I lean back on and kind of roll back and stretch my arch, my back a little bit,
it just relieves so much pressure. And like, I feel like I have to go do that for like five
minutes or so. I don't really want to crack it. So, you know, I mean, that was just me
venting frustration, but it's more so just stretching it and opening up the rib cage a
little bit. The worst part about something like costochondritis or what I've been told
is sometimes it just fucking disappears if it's just gone. You can have it for two months. You
can have it for 10 years and it might just disappear forever one day gone and you'll never
have it ever again. What the fuck? Foam rollers are Gucci. They're great. You just got to be
careful with the foam roller. You don't want to do it too low. If you do a foam roller low,
it's really not that great for you when, you know, there's nothing to support it.
Costochondritis. Yeah, that is the term of what I have been diagnosed with. It's a pain in the
ass. Costochondritis. Hey, it's Boo. Thanks for the 250. Hey, my birthday's next week and I'm
heading to Hash House. Not. What? Why would you say not? What are you trying to do here?
How many are there? At the link since I live in Summerlin. Going to the one on Sahara again,
but it was still awesome. What are your favorite meals? How many links are there in Vegas?
Not links. How many? No. At the link? What? At the link. If you're not going to... I thought
there were two? Three? I know there's two. There are three. Where's the third one? Where the fuck is
the third Hash House? Wait, hold on. I need to see this. I know the one that I go to all the fucking
time, but hold on. Hash House Go Go. Where is it? There are three? What's this fucking secret location
that I don't know about? There's like six. One, two, three, four, five. There are five Hash House
Go Go's in Vegas. Holy fuck. I go to this one. One of the links is the best one. I refuse to
think any of the other ones are any good. Go to the one at the link. You know, the thing that I sent
you. Business is booming since you mentioned it. Business is going to be booming all the time. It's
a 24-hour diner on the Las Vegas Strip. I think it's going to be just fine without me. What time
is the spring tomorrow? 2 p.m. Pacific. Hey, Shadow is one disciple. Thanks for the 250.
Oh, what am I? What are my favorite meals? The blue cheeseburger is the best thing on the menu.
And then they have an awesome fried chicken. Blue cheese. All their burgers are the best.
Blue cheeseburger is the fucking most incredible thing there. They have like a meatloaf sandwich
is thousand out of 10. Shadow is one disciple though. Thanks for the 250. Hello, Jeremy.
When you're in the process of reading this bit message, I will redeem the German wink.
All right. Whether you eliminate the German wink TM or raise it to an exorbitant amount of channel
points, it is likely that you will never German wink at my behest ever again. Thus, my request is,
even though I know you hate performing the German wink TM, that you may enjoy this particular wink
and cherish it. Wow, you really did do it. Cherished it. Thank you, Shadow is one disciple.
And that's the end of the stream. I will see you guys. Have a great rest of your night. Take care,
guys. I'm going to go walk in a circle, stretch my legs, stretch my back. Let me take a bath.
I'm going to be wearing my boomer brace tomorrow. That's for sure. Thanks for watching. See you
tomorrow. And we have a couple more. Reaper just came in 250. Okay, Jeremy, just admit the real
reason you stopped YouTube is because you forgot your password. That's the reason why you never
did an I'm streaming now or a goodbye vid. I should let you know that YouTube can get your
password back so you can start uploading again. I did the I'm streaming now video.
But one of my my last video is talking about how I'm going to be streaming like three or
four times a week with a schedule. I made that video. I didn't make a goodbye forever. I'm never
going to make a video again video I did. I'm streaming video. I talk about like Tuesday,
Thursday and Friday. We're going to be streaming on twitch.tv. I made that video.
I remember saying those words. I didn't need my mic down here. Nile Orion. Thanks for 300 bits.
I had a dream that I started a Pro League of Legends team and you are our top laner.
But we would have lost every game. Hopefully we won games in your dream,
because that would not happen in reality. Hey, I'm geese. Thanks for the 250. Hi,
Jerma. Every time my friend comes into chat, she says I'm Jeremy Wormy and you never say hi back.
Hi, Jeremy Wormy. Hi, Jeremy Wormy. You never say hi back. There's like 7000 people here today.
I'm sorry. What is making that sound? Do you guys hear this? I'm sorry. I'll try to catch it next
time. I'm sorry. Hey, future gamer. Thanks for the 250. PSA to cure hiccups. Take a big breath in
and swallow twice. I've gone many days suffering hiccups without this knowledge. All right,
I'll remember that the next time. That face when Jeremy Wormy doesn't reply to all your messages.
Don't do that. You'll shit your pants. I'm not a doctor. This person's not a doctor and you're
not a doctor. That was three doctors that just said things that doctors don't say.
So take all this advice of the grain of salt. All right, see you tomorrow, guys. Goodbye.
Just crossed nine hours. I'm glad I could do a longer one. Sorry, I had to stop, but it was
probably going to stop around this time anyway. So I'm going to go foam roll for a little bit and
I'll see you guys tomorrow at two o'clock Pacific. I've got a lot of things to play
and there's a wink right there. Don't worry. I'm not going to miss it. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye.
I'll see you tomorrow. Where's the Vinny raid? Vinny raid, Vinny raid, Vinny raid, raid, raid,
raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid. Who's streaming
right now? Let's see. What's Vinny doing? Chrono Trigger. He's playing Chrono Trigger of this game
and this is the finale. The finale of Chrono Trigger. Here comes spoilers for Chrono Trigger.
Chrono Trigger, end of the game spoilers, but this is like my favorite game. I have to.
In the middle of my playthrough. He's played it so many times.
Let's say hi to Taleks. Let's say hi to him. What, he's playing Rimworld? All right, let's say hi to
Taleks. Yeah, that's too much spoilers. No spoilers. Let's say hello.
Oh, I'm German high five. Yeah, if he's at the very, very, very end of the game. Yeah.
All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves.