Hello, how you doing? Welcome to another edition of streaming with Jeremy.
Right, people don't know the real spelling of my name. Jeremy. A-E-R-I-M.
Hello, yeah, I'm on the toilet. Uh, sorry, I feel like every time I stream now,
I have like an opening with an apology video. Hey, sorry buddy, sorry that like the stream's
like three hours late. Uh, sorry that the stream's like two days late. Hey, sorry, guys, sorry about
this. But that, I'm gonna, let's go over this, because people, I don't want anyone to be
concerned. I don't want anyone to be annoyed. Uh, although I can't really control that 100%,
but I'm gonna, let's just let, here we go. Uh, I kind of fucked myself up the last few days.
I'm doing some new stretches and some new yoga moves to help with the chest and spine pain.
And, um, I kind of got locked up in the middle of one, and I kind of fucked myself up.
So, that was fun. Can you fart? I mean, my body is physically capable of doing it,
but I'm not gonna do it for you. All the exercise is killing you. No, there's so many theories as to
why or what I did, I don't know. But, I, my like back and like shoulder area, kind of in the middle
of my back, straight through where like the rib cage is, on the right side, I think I like pulled
something or pinched something trying to do some of these yoga moves. It's like, that's just funny
on its own. Like, I'm the old fat guy that does the yoga shit and like goes to the hospital,
like hurts himself, of course. I didn't, I didn't go to the hospital, let's be never really clear.
Um, but yeah, I'm trying to do it. I'm trying to move some of the muscle and the tissue around
this area. Again, if you don't know, if I, I'll say it again, I have a three year going on
a chronic pain problem that I'm still trying to figure out exactly why it's happening.
And, yada, yada, yada, x, y, z. Okay, let's go, let's stream. Here we are.
You're practicing the sit and reach. I still don't, I get it, but I still don't get it,
if that makes any sense. Anyways, today we're gonna play a game that I've wanted to play for
a very long time. And weirdly enough, the guy that made this game remade it this year and it
came out like seven days ago. Uh, those who know the M. Dickie games, I've always heard about them,
but I never played them. There's been a lot of requests to play Wrestling Revolution 3D
and I took a look at the trailer. I've looked at a little bit of shit about it. Don't want to
get too into it. Um, it looked insane, but he remade it. This is Wrestling Empire. I guess he,
remastered it. So I was like, oh fuck, well, I'll just wait for that one. And here it is. So
there's, I don't know about character customization. I don't know if we can make a character, but
in the last day or two, just kind of poking around, I've edited a few people. So I think
we're going to pick a character that we want to be and edit that character and play as that
character in career mode. This game is fucking rad. I've, I've heard about it, but I have never
experienced it. So we're going to experience it together. And it's weird because I looked at
the control scheme of this game. I opened the tutorial and just looked at it and kind of walked
around a little bit and I'm just like, holy shit. This is, this is, it's like no mercy. This reminds
me of the old N64 games with the grapple. And then you're in a grapple and you hit up, uh, attack,
down attack, left attack. This feels very no mercy to me. And if this is the closest thing that I can
get to no mercy, then this is going to be one of my favorite games. Important is your surgery
before the big stream. Well, I don't, sorry. That's why I was like quiet. I was like silent,
just reading. Oh, I fucking back. Anyways, um, no, I don't have a surgery on schedule yet.
That's something that I haven't, I have another doctor's appointment in a week and we're going
to go over the timeframe of when that will happen because there is a lot of major projects going on
that I don't like that. I'm not going to just cancel scream it. No, but anyways, let's go. I'm
ready. I hope this is not DMCA. Tell me immediately if it is, we're going to find out right now. Is
this DMCA claimable? Yes, it is. So I'm going to try to find a way to, uh, I'm pretty sure this is
like a song. All right. We're going to make a character. We need a career mode. I'm not going
to tell you guys very much about this because I don't know much about it either. Let's go over
here. So this is M Dickie's wrestling revolution. And I know there's a lot of unlockable characters.
Is it not? Is this okay? I'll go. I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll be fine. All right. So where am I? Who
should I pick? All right. I made this guy. I made craft Ben. Uh, I made smoke. Uh, what else did I
make? I made like one or two people just messing around in the creator. Who do I, what, what does
the, okay. So there's green, this pink, and then there's purple pink. What are the different colors
mean? It looks like pink is women. What is the purple? Oh, it's, it's heel and face. Oh, shit.
Okay. Well, what, what, what do we want to play as? Should we play? I don't, I, I don't want to play
as smoke. I just made this guy in like 10 minutes for fun. I play as smoke, but I, I don't, I don't,
I wanted to make a character on stream. I don't want to just play as this guy for my career.
All right. Well, we have to make him less popular because that's too popular. He has to have a
fucking C-minus in every ability. EMCA, whatever. Look, what about attitude? Should I put that
somewhere? No, we're making our own character. No, no, no. We'll have plenty of interactions with
smoke over the next two days. Okay. Who should I, okay. I want to be a, I want to be a heel.
How about heckle horn? I'm just going to recreate them anyways. Heel or face? Which one? I think I
want to be a heel. All right. I'm going to be heel. Let's, let's, let's edit heckle horn. Okay.
I'm going to change that name. Let's all right with the theme music. What do we got?
There'd be wicked fast cartoon clown sounds. I kind of like that. Enos music. You could slow
it down too though. Hold on. That's pretty, I like that too. Yeah. This like kind of, this like sucks
at like 80%. You actually doesn't, what do you mean suck? This sounds awesome. It's not like
I'm underwater. Yeah. I'm keeping that one. The name's got to change, but all right. Pyro,
fireworks, fountains, smoke or full works? All right. We're doing full fireworks.
Do I come in with a prop? Microphone, camera, bell, explosive, explosive,
baseball bat, chair. Why would I come in with a grenade? What the fuck? All right. How about
baseball bat? All right. Let me ask you guys. How popular do you think I am?
No, no, not just talking about twitch.tv. I'm talking about all everywhere. 60% popular,
70% popular, 40% popular. How popular do you think I am? No, no, no. Household name is like,
is at least 95%. No way. And if you really think about it outside of like the twitch sphere of
content creators and community members, it's probably like this in like the grand scheme of
things. Uh, but you're the sus guy. All right. You know what? That bumps you up at least a few
points. We'll just, let's do 65%. How does that sound? Strength? It's pretty bad, but no,
I don't want to be like a piece of shit. I wouldn't really actually play the game.
My mom knows you exist, but that's because it's your mother and you probably talk about me at
dinner. You probably like do the sus face at dinner with, with like fucking green beans in
your mouth and your mother's probably sick of it. I, uh, 67% strength, 68% strength, 70% skill.
Uh, I think I'm, I think I am kind of skilled in a way. Now we'll do 70. Uh, it's going to,
oh no, hold on. I don't want to be, it's going to be, it's going to be hard if I don't do it.
My dad watched your spore stream and thought you were stupid.
Whatever. That your dad had one small example of my stream. I'm going to put skill up to like
78 and agility down and the stamina is going way down, but no, I, it's going to stay at 65.
That looks good. My attitude is very good. I'd say it's 80%. My added, I have a very good attitude.
I do 82%, 80%. Okay. Now we can, can we get, I got to get off this like song. All right. Build.
Yeah. Okay. 26. That's Oh, old. Can you go and go to a hundred? Who'd be wrestling at a hundred?
All right. We're going to just do me. Okay. Whatever. Four, six, two, seven, 10, four, six.
No, we're going to be, I'm doing me. That's so skinny. That's how much I actually weigh though.
All right. Can I like beef it up just for the fiction? Why is there a five, eight emote?
Whose emote is that? Why do they have that muscle mass? It used to be all right. I even, okay. Even
though over the years I've dropped a lot of the muscle from when I was working out, like
medical bullshit, I still got pretty big ass arms. And I'm not just saying that I got, my arms are
pretty fucking large and you've seen them and you know, that's never, that's never going away.
I think that's fair. I got big ass arms and big ass shoulders. All right. I'm okay with that.
I have like a tiny little waist, a huge ass, huge shoulders and big biceps and tiny forearms.
I look like an ant. I fucking, like a weird endomorphic ant body. Okay. That looks good.
Uh, hair. I'll change this. Um, hairstyle one, hairstyle. Oh, there's different variations too.
Hold on. Let's, let's go to a variation. All right. That's kind of accurate. If I got a haircut,
this is what it would look like. That's why I'm afraid to get a haircut. Why am I turning this
way? Oh, there we go. Honeytail middle. No, I don't want a low ponytail.
All right. That's, that's not bad. It's not EMCA. I don't know what to do. Look, uh,
well, look, well, and you know what? At this point, I've played this song like
eight times already. It's been played like 10 times. What? Oh, I make sure you mute it after
the 11th, 12th time it plays on stream. I'm already fucked if it's here. I think you swag
land gaming for the five community subs. Appreciate it. Yeah. At this point, like if
you robbed the bank, like you go and it's like, oh, I'm going to rob the bank. I was like,
there are the registers open. You don't go, you know, I'll take a $5 bill. Oh, I've just robbed
the bank. I'm already robbing the bank. So I'm already here. He admits he's a criminal.
So you're going to rob the bank. You might as well go rob the bank in a Cadillac. No,
that's what I'm saying. I'm saying like, if the bank is already being robbed, you're not going to
ask for like $1.50 in quarters, which I have to shave like the top of my head. What is this
shaving? All right. My hair is kind of like, all right, that's kind of like Lego hair, right?
Everybody says I have. It's your bulge. I thought you were serious. I was like, oh shit. It's like
that. Okay. That looks fine. All right. Let's go back. Face. Let's talk. I got to get these
glasses off. How do I get this thing off? My, how do I get the glasses off? Okay. Yeah. We're
taking this off. Oh God. All right. We're going to the Lord of the Rings war. We're going to get
the right face. Let's go. Here it is again. This is the song. Oh my God. That one's not bad.
Neither is that one. These are not, that one's not bad either. Oh fuck. That's I think that's
the one. Oh yeah. That's the one for sure. I don't need to even see any other option.
No, no mustaches or beards or anything. That kind of looked like that. Mask. Do I wear a mask?
Why do you have a huge bulge? I didn't make that. The game made that for me.
This is me in a shitty gambit costume. No, no masks. It's going to be me. Eyewear. Glasses.
People are going to want me to wear the hat, but I don't want to wear the hat.
No, I'm going to go none. All right. No, we don't need any of that. Head shape. Normal. Slim. Chubby.
That actually is pretty good. That's kind of accurate looking. Does, don't he think?
Squashed head. No, not that one. Not even close. Not that one either. Is it big nose? It might be.
What the hell? It's this one. I, I don't think I can hear very many arguments against it.
Okay. I like it. I just realized I had all this chest hair. Hold on. Let me move my microphone
a little bit. What's wrong with my, oh. Material. Over pattern? Under pattern? Oh, okay. Hold on.
There is something like an open vest. Yeah. Oh yeah. No, no, no way. Uh, how come, how come
I'm not seeing any of this? Under pattern. Over pattern material. Oh, that's why. Okay.
Do I even have anything under? This is how Ken Shamrock used to come to the ring. I remember
he used to have like this tiny denim vest that probably like was uncomfortable to be in.
He was awesome by the way. The tuxedo vest? All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. I kind of like the, Hey, what time is it everybody? Uh, yes. Email from, uh,
D Entertainment. I don't know. I don't know who made this song. Uh, you are being sued for playing
my time 65 times in a row on stream. Each offense is worth $15,000. Therefore bringing your total,
uh, lawyer fees up to, I don't know whose song this is. Who sings this song? Whose song is this?
This is Kanye? No, it's not. Is this Kanye? Kanye East? All right. I'm going with this because I
don't know. I don't even care. Wait, this is fireworks? Does that say I am verified with
like a blue check mark or something? I feel like that's the kind of shirt people would wear around.
You'd wear that to Starbucks and just hope somebody looked at it and was like, Oh,
you are? This is fine. I don't care. The costume doesn't match. I have like a bow tie.
No, no collar shape, tight or baggy. We'll do tight. Keep the choker on. I'm not keeping the
choker on every cover. Should I have tattoos? Elbow pads. All right. Yeah. Elbow pads, wristbands.
I want to keep the gloves on. Nope. Those are smoke. So I can't take those. Skeleton hands. No. Yes.
Why did they turn me into a Roblox character? I have to mute this. Otherwise, like, what the
fuck am I doing? All right. Whatever. I'm going. Legs. It's just dick dastardly Richard's pants.
I'm German rumble. All right. Is it paint splatters? It's paint splatters. All right.
We're going to do paint splatters. Just be in a diaper. I'm going to wear just swishy pants.
That's what I wear every day. It's like loafers. Oh God. Wait, why do I have? Hold on.
Skirt with a swishy pants stripe on it and swishy pants. All right. I kind of want the shorts and
the pants. Length. Bike shorts. All right. We're going to keep it like this. I just wear bike shorts.
No, I like that. It's stupid. All right. This is my wrestling attire. This is my casual attire.
I'm going to do this really quickly. What if my casual attire was a different person's face?
Oh shit. No, you can't. I forgot what face I had. There it is.
Yeah. You can't change that. That's too bad. All right. Casual would just be like a t-shirt.
Worst game ever. I don't agree with that yet. I would just say big green shirt. That was just
a German 95 colors, right? It's just like that kind of greenish blue and like pink. Yeah. Let's
do that. Oh, material. What is this second pattern here? What's this shit on my arms? Oh,
that's arms. Okay. Okay. How do you make pink? This is just the Riddler. Well, you only think
it's the Riddler because they have those goggles on. Just wait till I take the goggles off. How do
you make pink? There we go. All right. There we go. But I don't want them to look like that.
Yeah. A little lighter than that, isn't it?
It looks fine. No gloves. I'm not going to wear gloves just hanging out like at a coffee shop.
Legs, we're going to do green and we'll do pink. Whatever. Yeah. Imagine how much of a fucking
weirdo you'd have to be to dress in your channel branding colors every day when you went out to
like the grocery store. Like, why would you do that? What would the point of that be? Why would
you be doing that? Why? It's a flex, but it wouldn't even be a flex though because nobody would know
that that's you. They would just see the colors and like this green and like pink and blue.
It's a, it's very popular color scheme. It looks like an 80s workout video. Do I have 80s workout
video color scheme? I do. Don't I? Yeah, I do. Oh, that's fine. This is not matching the top.
Whatever. Do I really care that much? Maybe a little bit. Less blue. I think it's less blue.
Yeah. No, less blue, less green, less red, less blue. 150, 3100. 150, 30, 100. Different material.
Oh shit. Okay. All right. Perfect. It's perfect. So that's casual. This is what I come to the ring
in. Oh, and I want to change the, I want, yeah, I want tucked in. Yeah, that's better. And then
referee. I don't think I need to change referee. This is, what do you mean referee? I can be a
referee. Can I be, can I do a career as a referee? Holy shit. This would be the best game ever.
Can I just be the referee? All right. I'm ready. What just happened? Oh my God. I just freaked out.
All right. We're fine. Moves. All right. This is, I'm not going to take that much time doing this,
but like I kind of want to. So like, whatever, we're going to be here for a while. All right.
These are taunts. Oh, this is entrance. I like that. Haunt. Go away. Go to sleep. That's good.
I like that. Let's see if there's a German walk. I will put, that's footwork. Not that one. Not
that one. Not that one. That one's not bad. Here or there. Hold camera. I mean, I can come up with
a camera. Invite applause. Make decision. Make a point. Middle finger. Microphone speech. Oh,
that's good too. That's good too. I like that would be the combo. This is, I love this already. All
right. Hold on. We're going to do the footwork one. Not go to sleep. Yes. The Hulk Hogan. Classic
move. Special. Oh, this is what happens when you have a special. Do the rumble in this game. I'm,
look, I blocked out two days for this game. So it's today and tomorrow because I really
feel like I'm going to be obsessed with this game for the next at least two days. Present.
Punch the air. Raise the roof. I like raised finger. Roar. Rub fingers. Oh, I don't like that.
All right. That one's fine. I'm assuming this is when you win. That's a static backflip. It's like,
holy shit. That's perfect. This would be wave. I like that. Yes. Movement. Unbelievable.
Oh, I think I want power. Point at face. Point at chest. Pat stomach. That one's good. Stance.
Fists high. Fists low. Martial arts. Grappler. Low grappler. Powerful. Eminent. Default. I think
I'd be a guy, I'd be like this. Let's see. Hands up. No, it'd be hands down. It might even be hands
lower. Do you know what this reminds me of? Those of you guys that played like FIFA or MLB the show
or Madden, they had a playlist feature where you could go in and, oh, I don't want to hear this
song that often. Maybe I want to hear this one a little less often. You could, you could remove
songs completely from the playlist. And I remember going in there when I was younger and just having
the same two or three songs that I really liked on loop. That's what this is. Like I just, I only
have one song in the playlist that I like. The only one. Even in like the WWE games, I remember
playing, what's Tess's song? Honest day, I see clearly, everything is clear. But that song,
I used to play that on repeat when I was editing people. That's Edge. Well, whatever. Sorry.
I used to put that song on repeat while I was making Earthworm Jim back in like 2014. That's
a real story. We're good. What a fake fan. Whatever. All right. That's gestures. I have to play
something else because I'm, I can't, I cannot listen to that for like another 30 minutes while
I make moves. And that's nothing to the song, right? That's nothing about what I feel about
the actual song. It's just hearing it that many times in a row. I need to have something else,
right? So I'm going to put on like a little OST or something. I'm sorry. I have to. How about,
what's something that I can just chill and make this character? Undertale OST. Oh, but that's so
good and so easy. Uphead music. Holy shit. What a brilliant idea. That's actually kind of a
brilliant idea. Oh, it's good to turn it down. Okay. I can't hear this. Why?
Okay. I don't know. Penis music. Why can I, why can I not hear this? But you can. That's kind of
strange. Why can I hear this? Now I can't. Oh, because I'm stupid. I turned it down with my
mixer. All right. Let's go. I, I can handle this. This is like character creator music.
So we need, what have we got? Attacks. This is just like no mercy, man. I can already tell you. I
already know. Can I beat puncher? I don't even, I don't want to look at any of the moves.
Slap. Is there one that goes across the face? Not down. Is this DMCA? What? Is it DMCA?
Fuck. Why? No. You know, it's crazy. Like a lot of video game musical artists that like just
kind of don't care. Isn't it weird that like a lot of their music is like just better
than the shit that gets DMCA'd? Am I like, is that, is that a shit take? Tell me. But uh,
I'm not putting that back on. Skullgirls OST. Terraria is good. That's an easy one to go back
to. Yeah. Terraria OST. Great one. There we go. Okay. I think it's going to be the slap.
This one, it's way bigger. All right. That's slap. Lower attack. Left extension kick. I like left
hook. That was not bad. I think it should just be punches. I would never kick. No, I, I physically
cannot lift my leg higher than probably the middle of my waist. I tell you, you and I ever
get in a fight, just go for the legs. Cause I, I will, I'm, I'm a puncher. You know what I mean?
Like if I would, if I'm in a situation where I was going to have to fight somebody,
it would be a flurry of right and left hands. So fast that you wouldn't even just see them.
It would be like, and you were on the ground at like three of those ago, by the way. My legs are
useless. We'll do right hook. Big attack. Bicycle kick? No. This is me falling on my back.
For a second, I thought that was part of the move. I was like, Holy shit. Diving clothesline.
Yeah. It would probably just be a huge punch. Holy shit. Although seriously don't underestimate
just running and jumping with all of your body weight at somebody. Right? How does that not hurt
you more than it hurts the person you're doing that to? Headbutts pretty nuts. Wait, it is a move.
Running attack. It would be that one. A huge running, diving punch in the face.
Well, I think this is off the top rope. I would, I would do a flip of some kind, right?
But I definitely would be holding my neck because I would be kind of scared that I was going to like
break my neck and hurt myself. Okay. That one. Flying kick. Flying clothesline. What is it?
What's this one? Middle rope. Springboard attack. Moonsault. Oh, I think this is top rope. Super
punch. Suicide dive. Wait, you just, I kind of want that one. Thrushes. Oh, so when they're on
the ground. Punches. The rest of these can probably be pretty quick until we get to the grapples.
What's this one? Big leg drop. Moonsault. Senton bomb. That one. Running move when they're on the
ground. How about, uh, how am I doing? I'm doing all right. I'm doing all right. I kind of hurt
myself a few days ago or a day or two ago, but you know, I'll be all right. I don't want to be
too ridiculous. Like this is way too ridiculous. I'm going to get so annoyed at doing these moves.
Yeah. Just like a splash is fine. That's fine too. Springboard. That one. There is one thing
I have to make sure and I hope they have it. And I think they do is my finishing move has to be
the stone cold starter. That's incredibly important. This is top rope. Elbow drop. Yep.
All right. We're almost done. Front moves. Oh God. Wait, who am I doing? I'm doing this myself?
Suplex. Monkey flip. Monkey flip. Clothesline. Chokeslam. There's no way I would be able to do
that to somebody. This does feel like a workout video of some kind, right? I'm surprised this
hasn't happened yet. Oh, like UFC workout. You need two people. Get one of your buddies over.
You're both going to be able to burn 500 calories an hour working your core, your abs, your obliques,
and your calves at the same time. You just kick the shit out of each other. Like you have to
scoop slam your friend and then he scoops slams you. Only 500 an hour. Hmm. Oh, I like that.
Into the submission. Air crash. That would have hurt so bad. I like clothesline drop. Yep.
We've got monkey flip. I'm not going to have monkey flip be every move. So we're going to do
this one over the shoulder. Well, there's no. OK, that was crazy. Piledriver. This move is banned,
but we're going to use it. I like that. All monkey flip. All right. We'll make a character
eventually that has only monkey flip for a move and it's going to be infuriating. There it is.
All right. Well, that's my special move, though, not a regular move.
I love this stunner. It's like the best move ever. Test of strength. Need that one. Actually,
if it's just a regular move, though, that kind of sucks. Work and run is pretty sick. Cross
body is pretty sick. I like that one. Running. Spear. Run and slide is headlock take down.
Just make it a headbutt. Running and down is DDT. That's cooler. Pick up move. Oop,
insecure. Sunset flip. What if every move was the stunner, though? Would that be better?
Play the right version. What are you talking about? This is the way you want to play the old
version of the game. This is the one that just came out like six days ago. Why are you beating
up Hank Hill? Front power slam. I like it. Small package. Oh, I don't know, but they don't really
know. They don't really know me very well. Shoulder drop. Shoulder boulder screwdriver.
Holy shit, that would kill somebody. OK, momentum. Monkey flip. All right, fine.
Running. I like that. High cross body. Diamond cutter. That was awesome. Hey,
speaking of diamond cutter, didn't Diamond Dallas Page make a Pilates or a yoga program?
And it's actually like one of the best yoga platforms you can possibly do. Isn't DDP yoga
considered to be like one of the top tier, like A or S tier yoga programs? Maybe I should get it.
Half crusher. Whoa. All right. That one's weird. I like it. All right, here we go. Stunner. This
is my special. This is my finishing move. But the tombstone is awesome, too. But there's no way I
would be able to do the tombstone. Stunner. Yep. Nice. OK, rear moves. These are less important
after me, I think. These can be fine. These are all fine. Just like a face plant DDT. Yeah,
that one's cool. How about rear special? Here we go. Dragon suplex. The electric chair. Oh,
burning hammer. Holy shit. Abdominal stretch. Yeah, I did one of these like three days ago and
like tore a muscle in my shoulder. It sucked. I'm going to use it in the corner. Head smashes. Oh,
yeah, I like those. Yeah, I'm doing mounted punches. All right. So this is these are fine,
although I do want to do the the sharpshooter legs and attack. Do they have a sharpshooter?
There it is. If you were in this, you would get right. The hitman heart put you in one of these.
You weren't getting up. You were done right in the middle of the ring. You got nowhere to go.
It's over. Legs and run. Half crab. I want a Boston crab. All right, that's good.
And I think that's it. I just don't want to be heckle horn. Relationships promotion. I'm in
wrestling school. Roll wrestler. Oh, I could be a referee, but should I just be a referee?
No, I can't. We'll do that another day with another character. I want to be like a wrestler.
I want to be a heel loaning manager. I don't have any friends or anything. I'm just going to be like
a lone guy. OK. All right. All right. All right. This is fine. We'll make our own friends and
enemies as we play. I do need to change this name from heckle horn. I think I have to type it.
I can end up press A. OK. All right. There we go. I can turn the terraria soundtrack off.
It was good. You can now go back to the actual game sounds. You might get to hear my time one
more time. All right. I'm ready. I'm excited. Yeah. I spent like an hour fucking around,
but whatever. I'm in for the long haul right now. At least today into tomorrow.
I thought this was terraria still. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good.
This is done. There's Jerma. Jerma985. I think I picked career. Are you ready? Are you ready to
play? I think I know how to play. Let's go. Play career with Jerma. That's me. I'm ready to start.
OK. Wrestling school. July 2021. Singles versus tall order. Zero dollars. X zero weeks. Creative
control. I have five thousand dollars. What about gimmick? Oh, OK. I think I just go. All right.
We got all order. How come there's nobody here? Wait, why is there a chair already?
Wait, why is there a chair? Why is there a table? This is me. Oh, I got to wait.
No, get in the ring. Fucking ring. Why is there a chair? This is where your story starts, Jerma.
What? You'll have to learn the ropes here each week. For some people, it never happens while
others wish it because they've up back here broken. Why is he holding a chair? Be careful
what you sign up for because there'll be a lot of promoters trying to take advantage of you. OK.
But if you look after yourself and make smart choices, it's perfectly possible to have a
fulfilling career. OK. Anyway, let's see what you got before we see how far you'll go.
Why does he put the chair down? Get off the top floor. Is he here? Wait, don't fight the coach.
All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Yeah, motherfucker. Pretty good. Can I use this?
I'm going to use a weapon. I'm kicking the shit out of this guy. All right. Give me the. Here we go.
Drop it. Drop it. Take it. Take it. Take it. Whatever. Get out of the way.
Ha ha ha. Pick him up. Pick him up. Give him the Boston Crab. Come on. Break his neck. Who's
Blonde Blunder? Who the fuck is this? Get out of here. What do you do? What do I get from the
audience? It's two on one right now. This is not fair. How come the referee is not kicking this
guy out of the ring? Yeah. Get him out. Get this guy out of here. Get this guy out of here. What the
fuck? Oh, this is awesome. I got to pick him up. Here we go. What is it? What's coming out of his
head? Pick him up. All right. We're going to do it. We're going to do Spine Buster. No, we're not.
I'm going to throw him. How do you throw him off the ropes? Ow. Hey, wait. He just kicked me in
the balls. That's illegal. I'm not going to tap out. I'm fine. Get up. Here we go. Off the ropes.
Why did he not? What the fuck? Hey, what's that? Wait, he's mad at the ref. I'm not fucking around
anymore. How do you block? This guy's like two weight classes ahead of me. This is not even fair.
This guy's like 400 pounds. I'm 150. Am I bleeding? There's not even an audience to do that for.
Get on the top rope. I'm still winning. Oh, that was pretty sick. Pick him up. All right. I got
him right. I must have a special, right? Get off. Why is he on the top rope? All right. Should I try
to pin him? He just literally just kicked me in the balls. Get up. That's so stupid. Yeah. Thanks
a lot, referee. It took you like a full three minutes to kick the guy out that was in the ring
that shouldn't have been in the ring and he's still here. He just tripped and his face exploded in
blood. How about the spin punch? Oh my God. It worked. Five minutes remaining. We're taking too
much time. Why can he just do that to me? Reverse it. God, I just want to throw in a weapon so bad.
Um, hold on a second. No, not on the first match. I saw something down there. It's because you
dumped all your stats into attitude. Well, I'm, I better get some points for this. Oh, it's over.
Pin him. How do you pin? Oh, fuck you. Stay down. Pin him. I need a special. What the fuck just
happened? Oh my God. I think I killed him. Get over here. What the fuck was that? Ow. Ow, my chest.
I know this game is going to be bad for me. I already know it. I didn't even need to start. I
just started too. Oh, is he going to get up? Go on the top turn buckle.
Just taunting the ring. What happened to this guy? Oh shit. He grabbed me at nine. Are you
fucking kidding me? No way. Get off me. There's only five minutes remaining. He's getting sick
of this. Wait, you're going to get disqualified. Isn't he going to get disqualified? We're both so
fucked up right now. Why can't either of us win? We're both so fucked up. Just pin him.
I can't win. Look at how screwed up we are. At what point does the ref stop the match? Because
this is just embarrassing and horrible for both of us. What? This is the practice match? All right.
I got to go for a big move here. Right here. Right in the head. Good night. I was at a one count.
Stay down. Stay down. This one minute. We're about to hit the enrage timer. Does the referee start
fucking punching us? Get over here. All right. That's it. There it is. Wait, I've just received
word back from backstage that this match must be restarted immediately. What? What are you talking
about? He just gave me the finger. That guy just flipped me off. That's not fair. What are you
talking about? What? He's just like killing me. I'm like puking. What the fuck? That's not fair,
dude. No. Give me that bat. Give me that bat. I'm here to challenge you to a match on the fourth
week of July. Oh, you really? All right. If this is the only way to get your attention,
you'll agree to face me in front of the whole... All right. It's a date? All right. Fuck this guy.
All right. It's a date. Get off of me. I guess you're not the coward I thought you were. At least
you'll put up a fight before you lose. Wait, I'm fighting this guy right now? What are you talking
about? Isn't this the fourth of July? What day is it? What fucking day is it right now? I think
that's blonde blunder. That's the guy. It says I'm fighting him. That's illegal. That's illegal.
Throw him out of here. That was illegal. He just threw a bat in my head. That's illegal. That's
illegal. He just threw a bat at me. Okay. You know when you play Bloodborne and you go and you
kill like fucking 30 people, your clothes are just covered in blood. This is so unfair.
Just pin me already. Am I even supposed to win this? Stop. He's dead already. I know.
How do I get out of... I have no control of the character. Okay. I have to pin this guy.
Is there anything I can do to kill the... Okay. You know what? Fuck it. That guy didn't get
disqualified. So neither am I. Yeah. Drop it. Okay. Are you... This is so stupid. I love it.
This game is amazing. This is like the first match. Fuck you. Yeah. Disqualified, apparently.
It's me who decides who wins and loses, Jerma, and I've decided that you're a loser.
Why can I still fight? I need a second. I need to take a... Hold on. I need like a five second break.
Okay. So the wrestling review. In all the latest action from Wrestling School's training session,
Jerma was disqualified at 12 minutes and 17 seconds. Jerma's strength has risen to 70%
after participating in that match. In all the latest action, Tall Order's profile has risen
after taking part in such a compelling match. Blonde Blunder has generated a buzz by interfering
in that one and I made... I lost $200 because I used an explosive or something. Is that what it
was? Expenses? What is this? I see you had fun out there, Jerma, but you made quite a mess of
the arena. Okay. If we ever want to book this venue again, you better pay $100 towards the damages.
How about you referee? That's absolute bullshit. Why are there sticks of dynamite in your arena
lit that have like a hairpin trigger if they're touched? What are you talking about? That's not
my problem. It really isn't. I suppose you're right. What did they expect when they let a
wrestling show into the venue? All right. I got it. Third week of July. Your bat prop costs money.
I hope it doesn't. New middleweight champion. Booker Hudson has defeated Greg McMahon to become
the new middleweight champion of Weekend Warriors. Crucial Kennedy feels great today and is in perfect
health. Blonde Blunder has developed a heated rivalry with Jigsaw Jeremy of all American
wrestling. Yeah, that guy sucked. Jerma's proposed match against Blonde Blunder on the fourth week
of July has been canceled. Oh, so what was that all about? That guy just fucked up the whole match,
came down, challenged me to a duel, and then canceled on me. I've had, and somehow I lost
popularity. A lot of it. Okay. Well, proceed. All right. I got to win this one. Singles. Let's go.
Who is it? Oh, wait, I thought he canceled on me. Wait, he canceled and moved it up to the third
week of July instead of the fourth week of July. What are the rules of this match? Can he just hold
that? Put it down. I'm not putting mine down until he puts his down. I'm not getting in there until
he puts it down. The referee got a camera. Why does he have a camera? Wait, are we allowed to have
these? Anybody who couldn't beat tall order doesn't belong in the ring with me. Tall order is nothing
compared to me, and that makes you less than nothing. Holy shit. My mouth. That's so unfair.
That's unfair. That's unfair. I ran at him and he, I was like a bull. Get away from me. Why is my
health so low already? He's just doing my moves. All right. I got to play this smart. God damn it.
Get that shit out of the ring, please. Here we go. All right. Slow and steady. I don't know what
just happened, but I got hurt. I let go of him. Why did I let go of him? That was good. Pick him up.
All right. Good. Momentum. Keep going. Good. Come on. I grappled him. Why did he reverse it?
Let go of me. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go. Why can't I reverse moves?
That's my, that's my move of choice and the spin one. Oh my God. Why? What the fuck?
I need somebody to come interfere for me on my behalf, right? Is he biting me? I hear bites.
I get off of me. Let go of my neck. All right. I'm going to win. I'm going to,
I'm going to do a coward's play here. Is it 10 count? That was pretty good. Double disqualification.
It's the only way I can win. Don't let him get out. Don't let him leave. I win. Oh, oh my God.
Okay. I feel like I don't tap. Don't tap. Don't tap. Don't tap. Don't tap. All right.
I'm not doing that bad considering I started with less health. I got to do some reversals.
I think it's just random though. All right. Come here. How did I hurt? How did I hurt my balls?
Jumping. Bat? If I use the bat, I'm going to get disqualified.
God. How does he keep hitting me in the balls? Get up. What the fuck? It's not fair. I started
with half health. Dermot's profile has suffered considerably, considerably after being defeated
so easily. Juan Blunder's progress is being hindered by the limitations of wrestling school.
I'm taking the bat away. I'm literally losing money. Mary Class has defeated Ivy Windsor to
become the new women's champion of Maple Leaf Grappling. Gimmick. Whoa. Why is that? Why am
I losing strength? What was that? That was weird. What was that? Get this prop out of here. Yeah.
No, none. I'm just wasting money. Does this mean training strength? You were losing health to gain
strength. All right. I'm going to go for one more attempt. Proceed. I took the bat off.
Whack Axe will visit school on the third week of August to inspire the students.
What the fuck? Danny Might could not be woken from his sleep this morning. The 51-year-old
veteran is thought to have died of natural causes. What? What the fuck? The industry will come
together this week to stage a special tribute memory of Danny Might. Nice to meet you,
Jerma. We invited you here to discuss working for Rising Sun Fururesu. Is this a new promotion?
You're not exactly a priority for us right now, but we'd consider bringing you in with this deal.
Advance. $200 per week for 32 weeks. No creative control. May not make or refuse any changes. Um,
that seems like that doesn't- that sucks. Wait. I want a- I want $500 a week. I want creative
control. And I want- and I want $2,000 upfront. And I want $800 a week. And I want it for 30- 28
weeks. Who do you think you are to make those demands? You're obviously not taking this very
seriously. I just put it back. Nothing has changed since the last time you proposed that.
You're obviously not willing to compromise. I didn't mean to do that. All right. Well,
obviously not getting anywhere. Let's just forget about it for the time being.
Smoke! Hey, Jerma. I understand you've got a match against Slasher Sweetie tonight.
Shmo- Shmoke Mentor arc? How would you like me to take him out for you? If you give me $130,
I'll make sure he hobbles to the ring. That's- what? No problem. Consider the match won already.
Once I'm finished with him, there won't be much left. What is this music? Why is this slow?
This is- wait, guys. This is my time, but it's slowed down. Why is this happening?
Okay, here we go. Proceed. Singles match. Oh, we got a crowd this time.
Jerma! And with Coach Emerson. Why is he coming out here? Why does the referee have a mask on
and a bat? Waving to the fans. Slasher Sweetie with Lance Monaco. He's all fucked up, but he
has a microphone too. I just tried to throw the microphone at him. I just threw the microphone
at him. Fuck, I fell. Who's giving- did he give him the finger to who? This show is dedicated
to the memory of Danny Might, who recently passed away. What the fuck? Get away from me.
Danny Might's work in this ring meant a lot to fans, but the person he was backstage meant
even more to us. Who am I talking to? He lived for his family, and through them he lives on.
We hope the donations from this show bring them comfort. Oh wait, this is- oh, that's enough
talking. Danny Might is sitting up there waiting for his show, so let's give him one. Did I like
sabotage this guy on a charity event? Are you fucking kidding me? This guy's not
getting up. Get the fuck out of here. Oh yeah, eat this! Wait, what? What the fuck? I can hurt
the people and I can hurt these people? Wait, why? What? Where is he? Oh shit, he got up.
Actually, I don't know if you could like attack the commentators. He's gaining health. All right,
no no, no more fucking around. I'm gonna beat this. I'm gonna beat it. I'm gonna- here we go.
I can't. I can't play this. This is so stupid. I can't. Ow. Why do that? Okay, I gotta settle down.
Okay, I just- oh, come here. Just get out. Sit down already. This weird shit just keeps happening. I
can't fucking focus. Why would the referee do that? All right, get up. All right, here we go.
This is it. Tap out. That was a wheeze. All the air just left my body when the referee
used his clothesline. It doesn't make any sense. Why would a referee do that? That's it. What the
fuck? This guy's pissed. That's a pin. Referee, get the fuck over here. Oh my god. Pin! Oh my god.
This is it. Oh, he's not gonna get up from that one. It's over. I literally just broke his head.
I smashed his skull. It's over. Got it. He's biting the ref. He's so mad. Slasher Sweeney
has damaged the reputation of all American wrestling by failing to win that inter-promotional
contest. Irma's profile has improved considerably by winning at a major event. Lance Monaco is
disappointed that his client lost that match. All right. Holy shit, do I get some of that?
$450,000. I only get a hundred bucks. I don't get any money. I didn't get anything. Oh, that was
right. Right. Never mind. All right. I'm sorry. I forgot that was a charity event. I'm sorry.
I forgot. Look, I'm sorry. I didn't mean that. Midwinter and Monica Marquez have defeated Major
Merc and Sergeant Acer to become the new Tag Team Champions of Wrestling Revolution.
Lestat McCabray has defeated Helix to become the new Intercontinental Champion of the Federation.
Obby Ball has been appointed as the new Booker of Weekend Warriors. Game of Thrones. Federation
Online have overtaken All American Wrestling to become the most popular brand of wrestling with
a ratings of 89%. All right. 4200 bucks. Why am I bringing pops to the ring? Gimmick. All right,
let's go. Proceed. Singles match. Outback. I need to actually win. Let me actually wrestle and win
a match. I don't have to have it just be total insanity. That guy already has a grenade in his
hand. So I don't know what's going to happen with that. I don't know why he's holding it currently,
but he's looking at the referee. The referee's leaving the ring.
Do you still have it? I ain't going in there. He's holding two. He's going to videotape himself.
What? What is going on? What's wrong with this guy? Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to this singles
match. Weighing in at 170 pounds and standing at five foot eight, first welcome Jerma. Weighing 254,
511 is Outback. Holding a cartoon stick of dynamite and a camera. Let's ring the bell and find
ourselves a winner. Uh-huh. Can I get that out of the ring? I'm trying to get it. I don't want
to have it be in the ring. All right, here we go. Evenly matched, except he's got 60 pounds on me.
Oh, Jesus. Fuck. Is it a dud? I don't think it is. All right, I gotta fucking wrestle and do this the
way that I do. There we are. That was a big move. Nice. Why is he? He just baited me. That was
fucking ridiculous. He just caught my arm. All right, step on his head. Wrench it. This is doing
damage. Oh my God. That was a bad place to be. All right, more. I'm going to throw him against
ropes, but that was nice. Good job. Monkey flip. Perfect. Good execution. Oh, he blocked it. Shit.
Sorry. Rope break. Oh, fuck you. Still evenly matched. It's fine. Test of strength. I don't
know. I don't have no idea how to win. He just raffled. He did a goofy scream.
Holy shit. What did I just do to him? How do I do that again? Get out of here. Get that shit out of
here. Oops. Sorry, he didn't see it. Move out of the way, ref. I'm trying to fucking work here.
Goodbye. All right, I got the hang of this now. Oops. I almost have my finisher. I gotta build up
my finisher and actually do it. That hurts. Watch out. Run away. Just get away. Get away. Get away.
Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Watch it. Where are
you going? Are you fucking kidding me? That was a good move. I grabbed his ass and I spun him
around. How is this guy doing this? It doesn't make any sense. Get in here. All right. I just
grabbed him. Why is he instantly reversed this shit? There it is. Nice. All right. Good. Good.
Keep it going. It's because he's stronger than you. Get out of the way, ref. Why would you stand in
the way? Good. All right. I still have the upper hand. I'm fine. Good. Grab him by the head. I gotta
grab him. I gotta get him in the middle of the ring. Where's he going? Come here. Where'd he go?
What the fuck are you doing? I have no idea what just happened, but I just fucked him up bad.
Watch out for the bomb. I'm not touching that. Damn it. Oh, that was worth a lot of points.
Let me try that again. Oh, here we go. There's no rope here. I might get him to tap. There's no
rope in sight. He's got low health. This is over. That's my special. It's almost there. Oh, we're
gonna get to see the stunner. Come on. Tap out. Am I even putting pressure on him? What's going on?
I feel like this guy's just letting me do this and just taking a breather for a few minutes.
This does not hurt him at all. And he's just like, thank God this guy, this this wuss thinks he's
hurting me. I can breathe for like five minutes. Rip his arm out of his socket. Oh my God.
Why did I lose special for that? Yes. Here we go. It's over. It's time for the stunner.
Good night. Game over. That's a popularity boost right there.
Is this illegal? Why did I lose skill? Nerma's profile has improved considerably by winning
so convincingly. Outback's profile has suffered considerably after being defeated so easily.
All right. There was a lot of people in the attendance. Oh, what? I'm just bleeding money.
Where's this hundred dollars of expenses coming from? Anybody know?
It's the training. All American Wrestling product has come under criticism in recent weeks with
ratings down to 85 percent. A new women's champion, Nervana's defeated comic Connie.
Oh, Nerma, aren't you tired of pouring your energy into working out for such small gains?
For just a hundred and twenty dollars, I could hook you up with some steroids.
It will give you big results. Fast. Um, do I get, do I get caught? You'll feel the results in no time.
Holy shit, it worked. Four man elimination versus multiple opponents in this one.
Needles. I love how they just put tables out there even when it's not a hardcore match.
Driver 88. You did steroids and you're versus needles. Yeah. So are we all in the ring at the
same time? How long can my entrance be? This is so stupid. Can I go into the audience?
I'm like signing autographs. All right, I'm in. Oh, you want to give me the finger?
And the final contestant is Black Axe with Matt Dickey. Wait, the dev is here?
This guy must be a big deal. The dev is, is literally this guy's manager.
Who should I focus on? Black Axe, you only remain the world champion this long by ducking me.
Everybody knows that I'm the biggest threat to that little title. My mouth. Ow, my face.
Please. Now I'll show you why you were right to fear me. Okay. My manager is always just in here.
All right. So this is the, why do I? All right. Here's the play. The play is to get out of the,
just run away and have these guys fight each other and kill each other. And I come in.
It's like the scavenger as the vulture. Just pin the last suspecting person.
Oops. Watch that. Watch that. Watch that. All right. I'm going to focus on,
why don't we all just gang up on Whack Axe? He's the champion. It's just carnage over there.
What if I take the belt? I'm going to grab the belt and just like leave. I got it.
All right. Fine. I'll put it down. I got to focus on this guy. Oh my God. How is anybody supposed
to get pinned in this? Right in the face. I have to wait till they get to my level. But I, I'm
going to do what I used to do in no mercy. Just stand in the corner and taunt until I have a
special and use my special on like the lowest guy. This taunt builds your special. If it works
like no mercy, it does very briefly. And they're getting pissed that I'm doing that. All right.
This guy right here. Get out of here M. Dickie. I have such a low health. It's not even funny.
Distracted by the chair. Idiot. You know what? Get. All right. Come on in. Get in. Get in. Get
in. He's not paying attention. All right. Do something stupid. Hurt him. How did I let him
do that? I tried to grab him and he grabbed me by the head. It's cause I'm so weak. I even did
steroids before this match. It didn't even matter. I did steroids an hour ago. Here we go. Nice.
Black Axe. Austin crab this motherfucker right now. You two fight each other.
I, I pinned him. No, I eliminated him. What? What's happening right now? Why is he not like.
Like he's out. He's eliminated. Get him out of here.
I just know I eliminated his ass. Get him out. Come on. All right. Don't get eliminated. Run
away. Run away. Let them fight. Grab him from behind. There we go. Nice. All right. Don't pay
attention to me. You focus on each other. Good. Just I'm just a person in the audience. Don't
mind me. I'm going to get a special. I'm going to use it. Oh, does this make me more popular
if I play to the crowd? Holy shit. Sneak, sneak, sneak, sneak out, sneak out, sneak out, sneak out.
Oh shit. I'm trying to run away. Come on. Get away. Oh my head. Now I'm getting just double
teamed. This is bad. He was holding my arms back. Why is he taking his chair? He just. Why? My
coach just literally took the chair that the commentator was sitting on. Why? What's wrong
with you? The commentator is now coming into the ring. Like what are you doing out here?
This is who is this? Tony Land. All right. I'm going to stop this guy. No. Reverse it, please.
That's fine. Pin him. I could care less. That took me so long to get up. That's fine. Kick his ass.
What is he doing? Okay. That guy just got fired and he just doesn't care. Check this out. Stunner.
Come here. Come here. Stunner. Pin him. No longer the champion. He's gone. Oh, there's no ref. I'm
fine. I hope he fights the commentator. I don't know what the ref is doing. I have no idea. Thank
God. Coach. What's his name? Coach Emerson. I think this is going to be a win. Am I going to be the
champion after this? Referee is not looking. Referee is not paying attention. Oh shit. Test
of strength. Let's go. Oh, he's so much stronger than me. No. I'm so much weaker than him. What the
fuck? Get up. Get up. Let go of me. Fuck. Nope. Not going to happen. Wait till he gets up. Oh my God.
There it is. Going top rope. Oh my God. Oh no. Oh, that sucked. Don't let him knock you down. Good.
All right. We got it. I'm going for a submission again. He's done. Don't coach. Don't screw this
up for me. This is really close. I don't know what just happened there, but apparently not
something good. Get up. I'm so dazed right now. I'm just going to hang out out here until I get
my breath. Am I all right? I think I'm okay. I'm going back in. Whatever. I don't care if I
hurt the ref. Did I just hurt my own shoulder? Oh fuck you. No way. Get off me. Reverse it. Reverse
it. Reverse it. Reverse it. Reverse it. Rope break. I'm so slow to get up. I'm so weak. Oh no.
Good. Breather. Take a breather. Take a breather. Take a breather. All right. I'm fine. That was
huge. I just got to get up. Take a breather still. I grabbed him and he did a move to me. Oh, that's
bad. Just stay in the ropes and I'll be fine. Did he help me? Is he helping me or hurting me?
Was that a hindrance? I'm so weak. I can barely stand up. I'm just gonna have to use body weight.
Hit him. Oh, come on, dude. Again. What? I was gonna say no way. Reverse it. Reverse it, please.
Reverse it. He's holding me for way too long. Oh, come on. What's that guy's name? Schmo? Oh,
you're fucked now. What the hell did I let go for? Come on. Get in here. Get in here. Oh god,
he elbowed me and I fell down. I don't think I'm gonna win this match. I think it's over. No,
he's down too. I gotta run. I gotta escape. It's so close. I know. I gotta run away for a minute.
Take a breather. Good. The bait worked. Holy shit. I actually just fooled him.
Damn it. I missed. Oh, come on. Hurt him. That's it. No, it's not. Look at how much
slow I am to get up. I'm trying to get up so fast. Come here, you piece of shit. No. No. Fight it.
Don't let him beat you. No, he's got me even worse. Oh no, this is horrible. This is
horrible. I'm passed out right now. I'm dead. I'm not responsive. Good.
I can't do this. Boom. Shit. Come on. Get up. Get up, please. You're doing such a good job
distracting for me. I'm not getting up. It's over. I'm at zero. I'm actually at zero health.
I have to slide out of the ring if I have any chance. Get up. Come on. Coward move. Out. Roll
out. Oh my fucking God. Why did I do that? Come on, coach. Coach, you're really getting in the way,
man. That's it. That's it. One, two. Yes. Get out of here. Oh, that was insane. I can't believe it.
Wackax appears to have been sustained by adrenaline in that match and is suffering from exhaustion
now that it's over. Okay. Dermis profile has improved considerably by winning at a major event.
Driver 88's strength has risen to 76% after participating in that match.
Needles has damaged the reputation of Wrestling Revolution by failing to win that inter-promotional
contest. Why not get any money? I have to get signed. All right. Come on. Sign me. I got a match
coming up that I'm not sure I can win on my own. Okay. Would you consider assisting me at the ring
side? There's $60 in it for you if you do. 60 bucks, man. Let's go. Sure. I was going to come out
and protect him. I paid $130 for mine. I'll just make sure that he doesn't lose. I got Matt Black
with Jerma. I can't get in the ring, right? Can I get in the ring? Yeah. And then Burlain with
Matt Dickey. Oh, it's manager versus manager time. Can I get in? I think I just punched him. Do I have
to get out? So it's okay. The guy with the bald head. Wait, there's two guys with bald head. Where
am I? Wait, what's wrong with my character? Matt Dickey, I think. I didn't press any buttons. I'm
pretty sure Matt Dickey just fell off the ring. I did not press any buttons. I don't even know where
I am. Where the fuck am I? Where am I? I can't see myself. This is their match. Yeah. I got to make
sure he wins. Are we under the ring? Where are we fighting? Okay. Holy shit. This is awesome.
Where are we? Where the fuck did we go? Oh my god. That was cool from here. All right. Where are we?
Oh shit. There I am. My stomach. I'm here. I made it. Okay. Let's change the camera back to normal.
What was it called? Hard camera? What was it? Like 70, 80 percent? 60? How much percent zoom was it?
I don't even know what I have no idea what the actual camera was. All right. I'm coming in.
How do I go in? I think I fell down again. Where's Matt Dickey? How come I can't go in
the ring? Oh shit. Look at he's almost dead. Okay. Can I throw a weapon in the ring and hit him?
Well, what do I care if I get disqualified? That doesn't matter, right? Does that matter
if I get disqualified? Did I hit the ref? Come on. I got you. Oops. I'm picking up the stairs.
Here. I'll pass it to you. Right on the chair. And that was legal because he didn't do anything.
Hit him. Let's go. Hit him. Hey, get down. Get down. Get him down. Get him down. Yeah. I'm not in.
I'm not in there. This is not illegal for me. All right. Fuck it. I'm going in. Get this motherfucker.
Get him. Shit. Get in. Fuck. Oh my god. He landed on top of me. Put that down. Put that down. Put.
Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. Let's kick his ass. Ow. Sorry. All right. This guy's really
injured. All right. I got him. Get in the ring. Get in the ring. Get in the ring. You're fine.
Put the bat down and get in the ring. I got it. I got this.
Why is this guy on permanent two count? Change it to scope? Oh, scope. Player only? Relevant to
player? Is this relevant to player or contain all? Which one should I do? Player only, right?
I don't think that matters. Why am I tired? Count him out. I have no idea where M. Dickie is,
but he's like, I think he's on the ground somewhere. Don't get yourself counted out. Let
him get counted out. You idiot. Come here. I gotta go find M. Dickie. All right. Camera.
Bird's eye third person. The third person contain all? No, that's only covering these guys.
He's on the rope. I'm trying to grab the ref. It's like a superhero jump. All right. Pin him.
Oh, there's M. Dickie. What are you doing? Why would you just do that? That's a rope break.
All right. Get him down here. This camera. Fuck. Contain all. There we go.
Hey, what are you guys thinking about the match so far? Who's getting counted out?
I don't know who's getting counted out. I think it's this guy. Are we about to win? What's
happening? Count him out. Yeah. I don't know why you were refereeing this match outlaw eaten
because you're obviously not qualified. I can't play this game. I'm going to do that every 10
seconds. It's the biggest mistake of your life. I have to relax. Every time I see something stupid,
I just like all the air leaves my body. Oh, this is not the game to play. I have to pull
with a muscle in my neck. God damn it, man. All right. I got to settle down. Relay his damage,
the reputation of wrestling revolution by failing to win. Matt Black's profile has improved. Okay.
Matt Dickie is disappointed that his client lost that match. Oh my goodness. People paid
money to watch that match. Yeah. I think that's worth like five times what the WWE pay reviews
are. That was insane. Dangal has developed a friendship with Buddy Brew. Oh wait, this is
Matt Black. Bully Demise walks around like he owns this place and has been making our lives miserable.
Do you think you could teach him a lesson? There's $80 in it for you if you do. Teach him a lesson.
Um, why am I this guy's lackey? I don't think I can do... All right. I'll deal with Bully Demise.
Do I... Can I bring a weapon? I don't have any... I can't. I don't have any health. I need a week of
rest. You're not part of the solution. You're part of the problem, Jerma. No. What the fuck?
All right. This is I think big match coming up here. What am I doing? 75, 76, 72, 60. All right.
Sumo contest. What does that mean? Call me Hawk. Oh, by the way, for those of you that are curious,
I recognize this name because I think I went into the editor just to check and see what it was like
and I think I changed his hair. I don't think he looks like this. Like the default character.
What does sumo match? All right. For a second, I thought that was Tony Batagor.
I don't understand what a sumo match means. Just throw him over the ropes? What are you doing,
ref? What's wrong with you? Don't leave the ring. Okay. Five minutes? This guy is like seven or
eight. That guy's like two feet taller than me. Lance Monaco is coming in. For who? Me? No,
this guy's a dick. This guy, I don't... Get him out of here. Did I just lose? Come on. What? What
the fuck? Why did that guy interfere? That's not fair. Tommy Hawk's profile has improved considerably
by having a guy interfere, walk in the ring, and then I bounce off of his body and fly over the
ropes. Oh, he generated buzz. Lance Monaco is so popular. What the hell? The doper is complaining
about cheating. Running short of staff tonight, Jerma. Could you sit in on commentary for the
next match? Oh, hell yeah. Yes. Oh, absolutely. I will work as a commentator. This is awesome.
Thanks, Jerma. You just saved the broadcast. Please accept $60 for your time. What do I do?
It's another sumo contest. John Crockett. That's John Crockett versus in a sumo. I thought he
just eliminated himself. Versus Wurikusan with Coach Emerson. Okay, same rules. If you go over
the top rope, you're out. Very cool. So, I am sitting over there. Do I have to... What do I
have to do? I'm just the commentator? Jerma will be joining us on commentary to share his insights
in this match. This is awesome. You know what it takes to win. So, how long do you see this match
going? It will go longer than five minutes. It will take less than five minutes. If it's a sumo
competition, someone's going over very quickly. It'll take less than five minutes. You heard it
here first. Jerma thinks this match will be over soon. So, let's find out. Okay. What's this camera?
Wait, what am I... What the fuck? What's happening? What is happening? Why did I... I didn't mean to
climb. What? Do I still have to do commentary? No. Get off. Get off. Get off. Get off. Sit back in
the chair. I got it right. It's over. I got it right. See? The real winner tonight is you, Jerma.
You predicted this match would be quick. That's right. This... Okay. I'm telling you right now.
I'm going to make this very clear. This is some of the... This is some of the most fun
I've had. Just chilling out, playing a video game. I have to be honest with you. It's been a very...
It's been a while. A very long time. This is fucking fantastic. All right. Yeah, that match was 35
seconds long. All right. Their profile suffered considerably after incurring a loss at a major
event. John Crockett's profile has improved. That was so fast. Coach Emerson is disappointed
that his client lost that match. Shmoke's status is being compromised by the limitations of
wrestling school. Kylee Barrier's profile has dropped considerably after being criticized by
the press. What's coming up next? Something on TV? I have actually full health this time, thankfully.
Okay. What do we got next? Last Man Standing versus David Highbrow. All right. Let's make this one
quick. You're going to get signed soon? I hope so. Versus Jerma. What are the rules? Last Man
Standing. Jerma, I'm sure you think winning a fight involves being on top for three precious
seconds. Well, when you win a real fight, the loser doesn't get up ever again. They kill each
other? You're about to find that out when only one of us walks out of here in one piece. Share
him in the face, please. Actually, the three counters there protect my victims. There'll be
no mercy for you now. Oh, there are no rules? How does she have the chair? Is there no rules?
All right. There are obviously no rules. Obviously no rules. Going to get weapons. Oh my god.
Holy shit. That was brutal. Oh, I got to get the table in here. This guy had a lot, talked a lot
of talk. Holy shit. Okay. I got to get him through the table. Get the table in here. I'm going to
pile drive him through the table. Come over here. Are you man enough to come over here and get on
the table? What do you think? Come on over here. Why don't you come face me on the table? Face me
on the table. Face me on the table, coward. Fine. I'll just put you on the table. Get down here.
I just punched the thing. All right. Get over here. Give me the shit. Ow. Bring the table into
the ring. Who does a submission move in like a weapons match? Quest it. I think the ref just
bit her lip. Oh my god. He caught me. Why does she care? Excuse me. Fight it. There we go. All right.
Break his neck. The goal is to get the table in the ring, get him on the table and to do a back
flip on him through the table. I think it has really hurt him. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Shit. No. Come on. That was stupid.
Can I sit him in the chair? What's the count for? Wait, what's going on? All right. Can I put him
in the chair? All right. I'm going to put him through the chair. He has to stay on the ground
for 10 seconds. Oh, okay. I get it. Fight it. He just punched me in the balls. All right. Yeah.
Whatever. Last man standing. Fine. And you're going to go there? Oh, there's an announcer's table
over there. Oh, you're down. See you later. I'm not going to let him get up. Stop the match. Hey,
down. This guy's, this is horrible. Out. No. He was baiting me. Did you see that? That was a,
that was a fake. I'm going to get the other, I'm getting the announcer's table and put it in here.
Give me, is he down? Did I win? I won. I killed him. I win. His profile has improved considerably.
Nice. All right. 78 attitude. David Highbrows is way down. I need to get signed by an actual company
so I can start bleeding money. While Eaton and and all Cobain have defeated Midwinter and Monica
Marquez to become the new tag team champions. The ball has defeated Lestat Macabre. I want to
be a champion. All right. This is it. I've been keeping an eye on your progress and think some
changes need to be made. I need an agency, right? You're not talented enough to give fans the
technical wrestling that they pay to see. What? Get your scale up to 79% by the second week of
October or you'll have to find a different line of work. What? Oh God, what's going on?
Jeremiah, aren't you tired of pouring your energy into working out for such small gains?
For just $120, I could hook you up with some steroids so that I give you big results. I
immediately, immediately after hearing that went to the drug dealer. Okay. What are my stats? 79%
right? My scale is 80. I'm good. We're good. All right. This is a regular match. I think I have a
club. Oh no. Tommy Hawk. I got a rivalry with this guy. This is just a singles match. All right. I
have to beat this guy. I got to just do technical wrestling, beat him, actually play by the rules
and just win. Lock the medicine cabinet. Jerma is on the prowl looking for his next fix. That's
unconfirmed. Cat's out of the bag and now everybody knows you're a filthy drug addict. That hasn't
been confirmed. You brought shame on this sport and everybody who has tried to keep it clean.
I'm just so sure about that. Why don't you give us a urine sample, Tommy Hawk?
After I beat the piss out of you, the whole world would get to see who you really are.
I have to win this. Otherwise I have to do a drug test. I think that's what,
I think that's what this is implying. Start. Good start. All right. I got to focus here.
Focus, focus. I don't, I don't know what just happened. Thank you. Ref just helped me
accidentally. I have to do really light moves on this guy because I can't lift him. I really
don't think I can lift him up. Nice. Holy shit. What a perfect event. That was unbelievable.
I almost have my special. A couple more of those and I'm going to put them up.
Good. Good. Do it. Use it. Idiot. Oh, the fucking reversal. The double reversal. Shit.
Test of strength. I really am on steroids. Come on. This is it. This is where I can end it. I can
end it right here if I get an adrenaline rush here. I got it. It's over. Stunner. Good night.
Pick him up and do it again. Quick. Good night. That's it. Oh, nice try. Don't get too cocky.
If he wants to leave, let him leave. How did I miss that? How did I miss that? How the fuck
did I miss that? I went right through him. What the fuck? He's hurt. He's actually hurt.
I was holding his side pretty hard. If I didn't start with 50% health. God damn it. All right.
I'm fine. I'm fine. Just relax. Actually exactly where I want to be. Go up. Take the time to gain
some strength here. Relax. All right. Bring it back. Step on his head. Don't let him grab me.
That's all I need to know. Watch out. Do some dodging. That was an eye rake if I've ever seen
one. Oh, get out of here. Here we go. And shit. Move. Consume his fist to gain power. No. Just run
away. Run away. I'm slowly whittling him down to my level. That was a really good move. Oh,
come on. Break that rope, please. Again, rope break. Oops. Well, it worked out in my favor.
It's okay. Watch that return. I don't want him to kick me. All right. Come on. He's getting low.
Fuck. What? Oh, that cheap little bullshit. Oh, oh, I'm so good. Use it. Use it. Use it on me.
Use it on me. Use it on me. Use it on me. Oh, god damn it. Get him with a submission. I gotta
get him on the ground. Got it. Got it. Oh, fuck. Again, on his head. Break the arm. Break the arm.
Twist it. Come on. Hurt him. I don't want to get a drug test. Do it. Do it. I don't want to take a
drug test. Twist it. Come on. No. Oh, he's so close. This referee's crotch. Tap out. That's it.
Yeah. Tommy Hawk's skill has risen to 66%. The ref was just listening to that.
All right. More stamina. Imagine being the ref and hearing that. What the fuck am I listening to?
I don't want to take a drug test. No. I have to win. Tap out. I don't want to take a drug test.
Birdboy has left All-American Wrestling to pursue a career at Super Lucha Libre.
Jerma appears to have gained weight. The 35-year-old now weighs 247 pounds.
My skill went down. Jerma has been challenged to increase his skill to 79%
by the second week of October. Oh my God. How do I lose weight? I can go train. Oh,
my health is so low. All right. How do I like throw a match? Tables and chairs match versus
Tommy Hawk. I just beat this guy's ass. Oh God. You gained 80 pounds. Tables and ladders and chairs
match versus this guy. I'm actually really happy about that because that means I have no health,
but neither should he. He just tapped out at zero health. Going right for the table already.
Okay. All right. I can't believe I gained almost 100 pounds. Taking the announcements table.
We're all holding chairs. Wrestling is a business more than anything else, so it doesn't really
matter who wins or loses. For instance, if you were to pay me $160, I could make sure this match
goes your way. Sure, I'll pay you $160. It's a pleasure doing business with you. I'll do everything
in my power to make sure you win. Okay. Do you think we probably should have did that backstage
before we got on the ring? Wait, what? Oh my God. Make sure I win. I got to put him through
that huge thing over there, right? All right. Get over here. Shit. No, I wanted to put him through
it. Give me that. Give me that. I don't know. I don't care what it is. Oh my God. These eyes
made him fucking weird. I just fucked him up. Get on that table. Did I? Oh, wait. He broke it.
He's blocked it. Are you kidding me? I want to get up on there. I need to get him up on here and
we got to make this. I got to do this. How do I get him up there? Will he come up here?
Holy shit. I'm so high. Oh my God. Dude, I paid you. I paid you almost $200, man. That's no way
you're going to do that. Oh, the eye. Oh, fuck. I need to get you up here. Oh, shit. Give me,
give me, give me, give me. I wonder how you place him on the table. Just give me the chair and I'll
be fine. All right. Whatever. Whatever. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. Just run. Don't let him.
We're good. Thank you, ref. I need to do more tables and shit. God damn it. I love how the
referee is just doing this. Do safe play. Just kill him. Nice catch, dude. In the head. Way more
damage if it's in the head. Okay. Give me that table. Watch out. Give it to me. Give it to me.
Give me that table. Let it go. Let that shit go. Eat shit. Let's go. Oh my God. I just, he's done.
Goodbye. He's dead. It was never any chance of you giving me a fair chance in this match. Outback.
Are you up already? Next time you want to mess with me, you better be wearing your ring gear.
That was sick. My profile improved considerably. Uh, Tommy Hawk's profile suffered. I, I, I got
offered to wrestle for that organization and they never called me back. I've won like seven of my
last eight matches in a row. I got it. Congratulations, Jerma. You followed my advice and made your
prospects better than ever. I wish I could offer you a reward, but at this level experience is the
only reward there is. Okay. Single. Why? I don't want to fight this guy again. Hardcore singles
match? Why do I have to do this again with Tommy Hawk? He just got paid in exposure. Yeah. Um,
at what point does this guy leave me alone? Hardcore singles. All right. I'm just going to
get the chair and he's going to mic this time. There's dynamite over there. I'm just going to
throw it at him. This guy's my nemesis. Yeah, but just because somebody's your nemesis doesn't mean
you face them in a match every day. No, actually wait. God damn it. Give me the fucking mic.
Let's go. All right. What do you have to say? All week we've been polling fans on which match
they would like to see and they voted for Jerma versus Tommy Hawk in a hardcore match and an
arcade match. Who can get to a thousand points in Gallagher first? I think I just got hit by the
bell. He hit me in the face. I'm 90% positive. I'm on the ground right now. Oh, those rules suit
me perfectly. So it seems these fans want to see you suffer. No, they just felt they had to do
something this drastic to make one of your matches entertaining. All right. I'm getting the ladder.
Fuck it. I'm going right for the ladder. What's wrong with this ladder? Holy shit. You suck. Oh
my God. Get out of the way, ref, please. Oh, I didn't hit me in the face. It bounced back and
springboarded into my mouth. Great. Excellent. And now I'm like tired. You don't block a chair
shot like that. You really don't. I got him. Why would I do this? Don't worry. This isn't an
invasion so much as an Exodus because I'm leaving Maple Leaf Grappling Federation. Oh, are you?
Cool. I'm seeing stars. I'm not kidding. I have to slow down. This game is going to hurt me.
I'm actually seeing like stars right now. That all the air just came out of my body again.
I, I need to pause it. I promised I was going to settle down too. And it just doesn't matter.
That is just so stupid. Why? Why? This whole scenario is so dumb.
The guy interrupts the match to tell us that he's changing his, he's leaving this league to go to a
different league. Get the fuck out of here. Like, what do you do? Why are you here? There's no reason
for you to do that here. And this guy was so mad about it. I tried to jump. I was on top of the
ladder and I believe, I believe he pushed me off the ladder, climbed on top of the ladder and was
so annoyed with what this guy was saying. It jumps off the ladder into him. You know what I mean?
That whole scenario just makes all the gas leave the body. You know what I mean? Like, what the
fuck? I'm on the ground. Okay. So, but who is this, who's this, what, I don't know. What's this guy's
problem? Is he just, he just, I don't, I've no, I can't even describe what's happening. This is
ridiculous. Oh shit. He's going to pin me. I keep going over that in my head over and over again.
Um, please, can I have that back? Oh, this is just a fight to who gets to play with the camera.
Off the ladder. We're going to get some ladder action here. You want to come face me on the
ladder? Can I hit him? Oh shit. All right. Give it, I gotta get a chair or something. I'm gonna,
no, I gotta whip him into the, what are you doing? Get the fuck out of here. Why does this guy come
in the ring? I'm hugging this guy. Whose belt is this? Whose belt is that? A championship belt?
The camera. Shit. He's videotaping. This is how I felt when I was filming weddings. I used to film
weddings guys and sometimes you just didn't know what the hell to film, especially during the dance
stuff. Somebody was always doing something weird and it was like, oh fuck, but do I record like the
drunk uncle guy, like doing a break dance or should I go like film the bride and groom kissing?
It was incredibly difficult. I don't even know who I hit. I don't care. This is a, this is a weight.
Oh God. All right. Here we go. Who is this mustard guy? Why is he in the ring?
Is this guy in here? Why are you in here? Get out of here. Get the fuck out of the ring. I don't
even know. Is this guy an audience member? I have to. Five minutes remaining. All right. Here's the
plan. I'm going to knock him in the head with this and I'm going to go off the top turn buckle and
spin him. Okay. Let's go. Big splash to end it. Come on. Why is Jordan of his teeth? What are you
doing? No, this guy is dual welding. Don't let him pin you right now. Don't let him pin you. Come
on. Get the mounting in here. What's he doing? Fuck. I missed him. Oh my God. I was trying to
like Sonic roll on him. I'm not going to get up. Balls count anywhere and I'm still on the ground.
Come on. Don't let him do it. What just happened? I don't know. All right. Get some breath here.
You're not going to. Oh my God. He did it. I didn't think he was going to do it. I didn't think he was
going to do it. I didn't think the AI was going to do it. I didn't think the AI was going to do it.
Nowhere in my brain was the AI actually going to jump off the top rope and do that. I love this
game. What a fucking mess. I just have to pin him. I hit the mic. Finally. Just pin him. Go. Ref.
Fuck. Do you see that guy over there? Just looking, just watching this guy was asleep.
I'm going to get pinned and lose now. This is fantastic. All right. Get up. How has this guy
gained? I beat this guy's head in with a bench weight. You know what I mean? It's not even
possible to get up from that. I had it long ways going into his mouth. Like that guy is dead
in one of those, not five or 10. All right. This is the, this is it right here. You are seriously
going to fuck this up, aren't you? One minute remaining. Ref. That's it. Oh my God. That's it.
Pin him. You piece of shit. You got to be fucking kidding me. Don't even. There's only 19 seconds
left. Ah, what the fuck? Oh my God. No status effects. Tommy Hawk's profile has risen after
that. Okay. Yeah. He got his ass kicked for 15 straight minutes. Duke Miniman has generated a
buzz. That was so funny. Oh, that was so stupid. I couldn't have gone any better. I feel like I've
just been like wheeze laughing this whole time. Like you've all you've gotten is like loud laugh
sounds. Sharon has received her, renewed her contract. Lola has left Strong Style Wrestling.
Psycho Kid has left Super Lucha Libre. Okay. Okay. Cameron Cool has been released. He's free agent.
Cameron Cool has come down with an illness in his poor health this week. What? All right, here we go.
Remember, don't you ever wish that there was someone in your corner to guide you to victory.
This is the guy that's been supplying me steroids. So long as you give me my cut,
I'll make sure you never lose another match. What do you mean my cut? I let the steroid guy
be my manager, but we need to get signed first. I feel like I need somebody because it's a pretty
much a coin flip. If somebody's going to interfere with the match, I just grab a microphone, start
talking, and then attack me. It's 50%. No, it's not. No, fuck off. Yeah, whatever. I can be solo.
Didn't I take those goggles off? Why are they still on? I can be your best friend or your worst
enemy. Instead of helping you, now I'm going to make sure you lose every match. Great. That was
a great idea. Tag team versus Tommy Hawk's team. Training session versus somebody. Nothing scheduled
here. And then a public show. All right. Well, here comes a tag team. Who's my partner? Lucy Lakes
and Tommy Hawk. What's wrong with Lucy? Uh, it doesn't look very well. I don't know what to say.
Cracked out? No, I think she's really tired. I think she has zero health. This should be easy.
You can't come into the ring with zero health. And Schmoke. Are you kidding me? What?
When did this alliance happen? He's fucking tired too. Hey, evil corns. Thanks for the 25 community
subs. He's so tired. You all right? He's sleepy. He said I'm sleepy. What? You all right? I'm sleepy.
All right. Come on, Schmoke. I'll order. I know you're watching backstage, which is the safest
place for you to be, but I'll get my hands on you one day. And this is just a preview. What will
happen? That I just won. Why would you have Lucy Lakes be in first? Ow. What does it mean? What
does it legal? What do you mean legal? That's a rope break. Uh, dude, that's a rope break.
What the fuck's going on here? Why is he doing that? Can I tag him in? No. Why would I ever
tag him in? I can make sure he can't tag anybody. Fuck. Ah, fuck. I'm so tired. Here we go. All
right. I'm going to do some more moves. I have like an up B. I have a down B. What's he doing?
Why is there always a table too? We go. Nice move. Come up. Bring it together. I need more.
I need chain wrestling. Holy shit. Oh my God. Lucy Lakes. What the fuck was that?
Oh, where are you going? All right. Pick them up. Chain wrestling. Let's go. I'm going to do up.
I'm going to do left B and I'm going to go down B. Oh, it's the kick move. Okay. I hurt my back
doing that. Nice. All right. I'm going to have my special. This should be pretty easy. Submission.
Yeah. Let's do a submission. Smoke. Smoke. Grab him. Smoke. Smoke. Do something. Smoke.
What's going on? All right. I'm tagging in smoke. How do I tag him in? Where is he? All right. Smoke.
Let's go. How do I tag in smoke? Come on in smoke. Do your thing. Box him. Holy shit. He's like a
champion boxer. Get off the top turn buckle. Can I just go over there? I'm just going to go over
there and just pull her down. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. All right. I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm trying to leave. I'm literally trying to get out of the ring right
now. Get him. You idiot. Tag me in. Tag me in. Come here. Tag me in. Tag me in. Tag me in.
Old man. You're all washed up now. Come on. Tag me in. Good job. This is it. Wait. It's okay.
Here we go. Game over. Count it. Count it. What's with the slow ass counts? Count it. What the
This ref is paid off guaranteed by them. Like I did. Remember that time I did that?
Boop slam. I'm going to have my special in a second. I don't know what I'm doing here with
this guy, but I'm... Holy shit. I got my special in a second. Oh, it's over. It's over. Stunner.
That's it. That was a one count. I don't know how. What happened? That was a one count.
Come on. Shmo. You got to do something. Whatever his name is. Shmork? What's this guy's name?
What? So that was a total screw job is what happened. Um, well, maybe I guess I deserve that.
Omnihoc Stamin has risen to 80% of participating. Yeah. Great. Lucy Lake with zero HP. One, two,
three. Now what? We're running short of staff tonight. Could you sit in on commentary? Oh,
I love this. Yes. Absolutely. Let's go. I need a contract. I've been in wrestling school for three
hours. What the hell? Winston Barker and John Crockett. I turned the contract down. I didn't
think that was going to be the only one ever. I taunt. No, I'm not going to do anything stupid
this time. I'm just going to actually commentate. I'm not going to get up and like punch the guy
next to me. I didn't even know it was possible. So what, what was this match type? Is this just
a singles match or what? It's a sumo match. Okay. I'm going to say this is going to be really,
really, really early. If that's the thing that he's going to ask. Okay. You know what it takes
to win. How long do you see this match going? It's the same thing. The AI is just so dumb.
They're going to get too close to the ropes and bump into each other. Less than five minutes.
Commentating to no one. Well, there's a broadcast at home. Holy shit. The announcer.
That was the guy announcing the game. I think, was that the guy that was like doing,
ladies and gentlemen. Okay. Five minutes. It's going to have, it's going to be over right now.
What's the guy looking at? Why are you looking at me? Quit looking at me. I got,
I got my money on, uh, why is the guy staring at me? Gotta go over the top ropes. He's going
over right now. It's over. Oh shit. He went the wrong way. I was just staring at John Crockett.
I, I, can I, can I do like commentary? No, we just sit here and watch. Unless I want to go
interfere and be an asshole. Get in there. No, not yet. Unless I have to. I need to get popularity.
People hate me. I keep losing respect. Ref versus the ring announcer. It's okay to be hated. Who
are the contestants? Russell Haystacks and who's the other one? Roland Wiener. Off the ropes we
have, uh, Haystacks going into the corner here. No, going outside. Referee now and Coach Emerson
decides and the ring announcer at the same time coming in the ring. Doug Turner now has got
Haystacks by the waist as we have a little bit of an altercation outside as Haystacks misses the
grapple going into the referee. But no, it seems like Coach Emerson has some type of barbell in
his hand and the ring announcer seem to be climbing the ropes and going down at the same
time. Maybe practice seems exercising. Good workout for you calves and your hamstrings.
Into the ring goes the barbell as Haystacks now big right slap into the face of Haystacks.
And that's it, ladies and gentlemen. That's going to be, no, it's not.
He almost eliminated himself, it seems. As we have these two guys are just freaking me out.
They just keep doing this. That would have been so funny. Rope break there as the ring announcer is
still very angry with the referee. Watch out for that bell there as Haystacks comes into
Roland Wiener and he gets caught with an arm bar. Referee is going to probably try to break this
one up. No, there he is again. You know what? Hold on a minute. It seems like German 985 has
decided he's going to get up from his chair and he is walking over towards Roland Wiener right now.
Or John Crockett. I believe it's John Crockett who German 985 is going to be walking over towards.
As he gets close enough, German 985 I believe is going to, looks like he's getting a,
he's going to do a spinning punch right into John Crockett. There goes John Crockett now.
On the ground, German 985 has decided that that is going to be the place he's going to go. Another
right hand onto John Crockett. Roland gets grabbed by the arm and is getting his arm bent backwards
out while he's, while Roland has just grabbed him and tossed him over the side arm bar.
Oh, I don't even know what just happened. I thought it was a sumo match. He's still
holding on to me. I'm losing health for this, aren't I? This is supposed to be a like relaxing
day. Doug Turner's status has not been affected. Winston Barker, it's improved.
Emerton's disappointed. Okay. The Women's Champion. Alright, now what? I've been keeping
an eye on your progress and I think some changes need to be made. Well, give me a contract so I can
work for something. You need better attitude to help with what we're trying to build here.
Improve your attitude to 78% by the second week in November or give your spot to someone who
appreciates it. All right. Confrontation versus Schmoke. Well, this does make sense because he
just screwed me in the last match, which is completely unfortunate. What's going on here?
Ugging Lucy Lake pretending to be my tag team partner, paying the ref? That was a 3v1. That
wasn't fair. What does he have to say? Wasn't I friends with this guy in the beginning of the
game? Why did that change? I'm not going anywhere without a weapon. That guy's a ladder. I'm not
making that mistake. All right. What do you have to say? You made me look bad for the last time,
German. Why should I tolerate failure? When you cost me a win, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you were doing it on purpose. Betrayal is the only way you could have hurt anybody.
You betrayed me. We all make mistakes, Schmoke, and agreeing to work with you was my biggest.
What defines us is what happens next. And you'll need another excuse after I cost you this win.
And why is that legal again? Why is that legal again? And why is it legal for him to have like
a stepladder? Get away from me. Get away from me. We were friends, Schmoke. We could have been good
friends. But instead, you had to be the traitor. And then you paint me as the traitor. That's
bullshit. I'm sorry, but I have to do this. American Psycho? It's hip to be square.
It's hip to be square. Hey, Paul! I'll fight my friends a minute soon. I'll watch them on TV.
What just happened? I knocked out Schmoke in one minute. Schmoke's profile suffered. I don't have
any friends. I need to make my attitude better though. Okay. More happenings in the league.
German has been challenged to increase his attitude. What am I with it right now? 75?
This is my only friend. Why are you hanging out with people like Outback? I thought I was the only
friend you needed, Germo. Why are you gatekeeping me from having friends? I need to see other people.
I'm not even friends with Outback. You got weird information. I don't even know who that is.
I don't even know what he's talking about. I'm glad to hear it, Germo. We can't allow anybody
else to come between us. Okay. This guy's... I don't like this guy. My attitude. Can I make...
I can't make my attitude better. How do I increase my attitude? What do I do? I have this match
coming up next. Go to relationships. Story enemy is now Outback. Real enemy is Outback. Why do you
think I was my friend? This guy hates me. It's RNG based. You basically lost. Oh, did I? I'm
sorry. I'm proceeding. Did I do any... Wait. I at least should level up like strength or something,
right? How do I get a better attitude? 75%. I did it. No, I didn't. Did I? What did I need? 78.
Shit. Okay. Oh, I'm in trouble. Germo's been challenged. 78. All right. I think I have...
I mean, even if I lose this match, I need to get that attitude up. Come on. Fuck. Shoot,
fight versus... Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What's going on? Shoot, fight. Okay. I'm so tired now.
Oh my God. This is in an octagon. I can't even climb the ring. Wait, is the... Do I just have to
leave the ring? You won't have to worry about attitude when you're dead. I still think I can
beat this guy. Taking the chair from... Okay. I thought he was... I thought the guy was still
sitting in it and he was going to bring him in with a guy sitting in the chair. Fall down, please.
I just took the mic from his hand. There's nowhere to run now that I got you locked in.
Only one of us is getting out of here in one piece and it's not going to be you.
I'm not locked in here with you. You're locked in here with me. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out of the ring. Get me out. Get me out.
Is he going to climb in here? This guy sucks. Actually, this guy might actually be the thing
that helps me. I think... God, here he comes. No. My attitude is down. I'm dead. It's over.
I need to... We're running short on staff, Terma. Can I count on you to referee one of the matches?
Yes, this is my last chance. Can I get my attitude up? It's a singles match. I'm the referee. What
if I do a really good job? I still have two weeks? I'm so tired. Master Chrome. He's going... He's
going for another hug. Oh, this is the organization that I could have worked for. Look at how well they
treat each other. God damn it. Get out. You have to get out of here. Stay out of the ring. I want
a clean fight. Easy. All right. Oh, right. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Get this illegal item out of the ring, please. All right. Go on. Are you okay? You okay? You
okay? Are you okay? How you doing? Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you all right? You okay? Sorry.
That looked fun. Put that down. I got to make this interesting. How you doing? Why does this guy
have so much more health than the other guy? What happens if he doesn't get up? All right. Get out.
Excuse me. You're not supposed to be in here. I said get out. Coach Emerson, you're... You're
out of here. I kind of want the guy with less health to win because I don't know,
it's more interesting to me. Let's see if I can like bait them into doing stupid things.
What if I put a table in here? Where's the table? Where's the table? I need to find the table.
Trash can lid. Get off the... All right. Now you're just being goofy. Hey, what are you doing in here?
Get out. Leave. Leave. This guy is just acting like a toddler. I think this guy tapped out already
like three times. Okay, so I can disqualify people but will I be disqualified from refereeing if I
do this? No. It's an illegal item. Excuse me. What the fuck? How do you do that? Holy shit,
he got me a seat. This is awesome. Oh wait, hold on. I got a better idea. It's time to be the world
shittiest rep. Excuse me. Well, you knocked me down. I can't even count. How am I supposed to
count when you knock me down and I'm not even ready? I really hope that nobody does anything
illegal behind me. It would be such a shame if somebody were to do something illegal. Work. I
feel like I'm watching my son at the playground. Hey, hey, get out of here. You're not supposed to
be in here, man. Oh, whatever. I don't fucking care. Just don't do anything dumb. World's worst
lifeguard. What am I doing? Shit, I'm trying to jump over the ropes. Count. Oh, right. One, two,
three, four. I forgot I was supposed to count. Oh, right. Whoops. Come on, give me some reputation.
Give me some attitude. Seventy-nine attitude. Seventy-eight. Come on. Shit. Yeah. Oh,
there has been challenged and I don't think I got it. Oh, I'm in trouble now. I don't know what to
do to make my attitude better. I can cheat? What do you mean cheat? I can't cheat. What, a database?
Just take drugs. I can't take any more drugs. I took drugs a bunch. You don't have to make every
goal. Oh, okay. I'm going to just rest up. Go back to the main menu and edit the universe.
I guess I could do that. Oh, I failed. I'm afraid this is the end of the road for you. Maybe you'll
put more effort into your next big idea. After 17 weeks, Jerma has retired from wrestling at the age
of 35 with meager savings of $2,900. He only ever worked for wrestling school where he won 50% of
his 12 matches. Shit. I'm gone from the roster. I actually don't exist anymore. I gotta try. Now
that I know how this game works, I'm going to make a new character. All right. Wrestling school.
We're going to do C Breeze. We'll be a good guy this time. I gotta go pee. I'll be right back.
We're going to do another career. I'll be right back. I'm back. Oh, man. This is definitely not
the game to play after I like pulling muscles and I like right middle shoulder into my lower rib
is on fire right now, but it's worth it. This is so fucking funny.
Yeah, this is, this is an absolute 100% buy. Like this is a run to buy this
in my opinion so far. It's just fun. It's funny. Oh, all right. So let's cut back over here.
So who I don't want to be me this time. I want to be a huge person.
Let's do that first. I want to be like seven feet tall. Should I be 710 and 500 pounds?
Okay. I'm going to be 525 pounds. I'm going to be absolutely massive. I'm going to be like 20.
You know what I mean? Like 24, 25. Not even on the screen. All right. Let me, I gotta slow down a
little. Let me see my character. Okay. Hair. Oh shit. Okay. I gotta mute this. Should I put
the Terraria soundtrack back on? Let me put the Terraria soundtrack on. I think it's still open.
It is. Make him tiny. I think he's got to be huge. About like a huge Elvis. Make him really skinny.
I kind of like that face. Do you have like the weird like melted chin? I kind of like that.
This is scuffed Johnny Cage. Mr. Satan. Holy shit. What a great idea. What does Mr. Satan look like?
Is this a Batman game? What is Mr. Satan? I gotta get a picture of Mr. Satan. He's an online reference.
Mr. Satan is a big mustache. It's kind of like got a bald, but it's like an Afro.
Okay. Let me see. I do a big mustache. There it is. That's actually not bad already.
I think that's it here. Holy shit. It's Mr. Satan.
I'm the strongest man in the world. I tell you that much.
Okay. Beard. He needs... Okay. Glasses off. It's not really Mr. Satan. Hold on. That's kind of...
Okay. Male 4. Male 4. Male 6. That's pretty good too. That's really good. Yeah. That's that one.
All right. Let's go. He's got black hair. Oops. Whoa. What the hell? A little lighter than that.
And he has... He's got like the cape, right? Can you do a cape? Oh, wait a minute. He's got...
Wait. Doesn't he have that? No. He has sideburns. Okay. He's got like a ripped chest.
Yeah. It's ripped. Okay. Over pattern. Zero. A cape. Oh, that's... Is that as close as we're
going to get? It's 23. All right. Remember 23. 23. Yeah. It's 23. Okay. And what color is the cape?
It's almost like a pale purple. I think it's purple. Wait. What? Oh, there we go. Red and blue.
Not even changing color. Oh, okay. There we go. All right. It's like a pale purple. It's like this.
Right? Like that. Okay. What does he have? I need like a full picture of him. He also kind of has
white. It looks purple here. It is white. Why is it purple in this one? Okay. Um, and I'm going to
try really hard. I'm going to actually try to win every game because super sucks. What does he have
for pants? He's got these like kind of fuchsia boots with white. Is that Otto? Hold on. Let me
get Otto. Okay. There he is. He wanted to come in and hang out. All right. So now we need
a, uh, that looks fine. Now we need pants are everything goes arm. It kind of like baggy pants
and they're white. That baggy. Oh, those are too baggy. That's fine. All right. These are white.
Tell Otto chat says hi. Hey, Otto at says hi. Doesn't he doesn't speak any. He doesn't speak
English. Okay. All the boots, the boots are tucked in actually. Yeah, they're tucked.
Those look good, but I need them to be purple, at least a little bit. He's got like fuchsia lines
and the materials got to change. Is there a split one? There we go. All right.
How do I change this color? Here it is. All right. I was going to flip it.
Damn it. This is probably as close as I'm going to be able to get this. It's just reversed. Look on
the shape option in shirts to change the Cape. Okay. All right. There we go. A little more purple.
All right. That's good. They're not that purple though. They're like a like almost like a maroon.
I can't really, there it is. Okay. That's better like that. Now let's do the person that goes
shirts and then shape. Oh, I see what you mean. Okay. Baggy baggy baggy baggy. That's fatter.
His body is baggy. Yeah. What?
Okay. Like I kind of like that. Cool. All right. That's fine. His skin is going over his pants and
tucking into his pants. All right. Cool. The hair needs to be a little lighter. Maybe a little bit
of variation. No, I can't do any big extensions on this. No, I can't. All right. Texture. What
about the texture? Is that fine? Oh, it's good. It is a curly texture. It doesn't look like there
is. It's just good. I mean, that's he's kind of balding in this one. Is that actually the one
we're going to use? I kind of it's the only one. There we go. That's like darker. He needs chest
hair. Why are there crumbs in his chest? Well, that's the only one I can do. Wait, I don't want
tattoos. Why are there tattoos all over him now? Is it the arms? Why does he have tattoos all over
his arm? Oh, there we go. Okay. Oh, wait. I could like add this and make this part of the Cape,
couldn't I? That's just the Cape, right? Oh, yeah. Look at that. This is just part of the Cape.
There we go. This would be the same material, though. At least close enough.
Material two? Material two. It doesn't have wristbands. Does he have gloves? That's not bad.
That looks more like a Cape. And I got to make the material the same thing. I'm going to sneeze.
Collar. Yep. That's fine. That's good. All right. Mr. Satan. I'm going to sneeze again, I think.
I'm trying not to. I'm going to mute. That's the perfect time. I just, I think I fixed it.
Okay. Legs. That's fine. That hair is awful. I know it is. What about this one? No. I don't
know which the closest one. No bald spot. No bald spot. All right. All right. This one,
that one looks fine, right? Ah, that's it. That's fine. That's good. Okay. Now I got to make him
bigger. Yeah. How big is Mr. Satan? He's at least like seven feet tall, right? Look it up. All
right. How tall is Mr. Satan? Mr. Satan is 6'2". What? How old is he? I thought this was like a
typo. He's 736 years old. What the fuck are they talking about? I'm not going to make him that.
How about 7'2"? He needs to be big and imposing. All right. I'm happy with it. All right. Casual.
I don't, whatever. It doesn't matter. I don't, it doesn't matter. No, I just changed his body.
There we go. Okay. Oh, he shaves. All right. Whatever. Whatever. I don't care. Wait. Isn't
Mr. Satan like the strongest man in America? He's the strongest man in the entire United States.
I'm thinking this is a different person. Who's that? It's the world. Oh, okay. It's the world.
Nevermind. Is that this song? Oh, it's Terraria, right? I thought it was Mario Galaxy.
I don't even care. Let's go. Referee. What are his moves? Gestures. I don't even know what he does.
Would it be martial arts? Powerful. Oh yeah. He would be standing very tall. Right, right, right.
Okay. Yeah. Hold the camera. Make a point. Double peace signs. Hands on hips. Grind hips. Go to
sleep. Go away. Get out of my face. Footwork. Folded arms. Fist pump. Is there a peace sign?
Diamond sign. All right. Look at the P. Peace sign. There's no peace sign.
Would it just be prayer? He's raised arms. Sure. Yeah, they're good. They're good. Good. Good.
And middle finger. Middle fingers. All right. Attacks. What does he do? What does he even do?
Big uppercut. He actually did do the middle finger in the Japanese version. He did. Drop kick is good.
Forearm. Flying knee. Flying kick. Flying drop kick. That sounds awesome. What is his move? His
ultimate move. Because that's what we're going to give him for his special. He had very flashy
big moves. Okay. It was the death punch. Dynamite kick. Spinning heel kick. That's pretty sick.
That one's sick too. Top rope attack. Look at that one. That's huge. I like, um, super punch. Yep.
All right. Crushes. These can be pretty normal. Stomp is fine. Leg drop is fine. Running when
they're on the ground. Double stomp. That sounds good. Flying in the air when they're on the ground.
How about just like a big splash? We'll go give him a senton bomb. Five star splash. All right.
So top rope when they're on the ground. Give him dynamite as the prop. I'm hurting the training
dummy here. You see that? Okay. Here we go. Now these are important. I want to look at the specials.
So he said dynamite kick was his special move. Let's start at the top. We got to get this right.
Bear hug. Brain buster. Bulldog calf crusher. Canadian destroyer. Cartwheel takedown. Chokeslam.
Flows line. Collarbone slam. Crucifix power bomb. Death valley driver. Diamond cutter. Dragon screw.
Emerald flojian. Falcon arrow. Nice. Front power slam. Flying head scissors. Oh no. I thought it was
going to be a big kick. This definitely a super kick. I would be shocked if it wasn't. Oh that's
brutal. Headbutt. Headlock. Toss hurricanrana. Inverted atomic drop. Jumping DDT. The jackhammer.
Jumping face buster. Kimiro lock. Kiss of death. Low blow is your finisher. MDKO. Monkey flip.
Northern lights. Lancia? Jesus. Damn. Pop up stunner. Oh my god. That's not even a move.
You go halfway and then give up. Power stunner. Power bomb. Reverse shoulder. Samoa drop.
Crew driver. This has got to be a super kick. Come on. Shoulder breaker. Shoulder drop.
Shoulder knee strike. Shoulder slam. Body slam. Sitting power bomb. Sling blade. Super kick. Where
is it? Stunner. Spine buster drop. Standing clothes line. Damn it. Where is it? Built a world.
Head scissors. Tombstone. Tornado drop. There's no super kick. You guys know what I'm talking about?
Shawn Michaels. He would stand in the corner and he would do like a little crow hop and his foot
would come up and boom. Sweet chain music. Oh that's unfortunate. Low blow fits. Alright the
rest of these we'll do inverted pile driver. Hell. Okay monkey flip. Let's do pop up drop. Pop up
power bomb. Turning spine buster. Drop him on his stomach. Super kick is in the game. It's just a
strike. Okay. Running. Let's do a head stomp. Run inside is going to be a hammer lock. The
enziguri for the special they're claiming it's a kick. I had the enziguri for the other guy.
So they catch your leg and then you jump and kick with the other one. I'm talking about you just go
wham. You do two crow hops and you kick him in the mouth. Air crash. That's good. Oh shit. Standing
clothesline is awful. Yeah. Back hammer. Absolutely. It doesn't read any real messages.
The stream is pre-recorded. I just read like three. What are you talking about?
Head lock drop. You're a bully and a coward. First you steal my channel points.
Can't send you germa terraria meme links. Alright we're gonna have him have no no you can't just
have him be a stunner for every move. I want to do that though. I want to give somebody the stunner
for every move. That's fine. I like that. Special's low blow. Alright so what about attack? Somebody
said big attack. Oh shit there it is. Super kick and okay yeah super kick. You just go
whack. Nice. Alright. Rear moves. Rear special is going to be
bull nelson. Pretty cool. Corner is going to be a uh mounted no super flex. Make it another look.
Make it what if every move is a low blow. Ground moves. Alright what should we do for these ones?
Recliner. Sleeper. Yep. Bow and arrow. It's like I'm cracking his back.
Groin kick. Just make every single one of these groin kick just to make sure I get it.
That's it. Relationships. We're gonna keep. Wrestling school is fine. He's a face. Manager
don't really need one. Now I need a name. Mr. Satan. We need a theme music for Mr. Satan so we
can turn this off now. Thank you terraria. That was really cool. Alright we need Mr. Satan music.
Not this one. Uh should we do reds greens blues yellows pinks blackout dark twilight
dusk smooth disco how about fast disco you thanked terraria like they were a person in the chat
yeah I'm just saying I'm just saying thanks for the music whoever it was
somebody had to request that alright now I'm not gonna fuck this up because
honestly attitude who cares let's make sure it's like high enough where it's not gonna be a problem
we're gonna make everything like decent enough so I don't just get fired in the first like hour
is he popular he is popular isn't he max his popularity sounds pretty dragon ball z to me
yep okay prop microphone camera bell explosive bar would bat cardboard ladder piece plank pipe
nightstick cane dumbbell weight trash can explosives or do you just but I'm gonna get it should be mic
oh none I know it's a way it's gonna cost me like $300 a match no
all right we're gonna do what's what should you do smoke mountains fireworks
full thing full works all right mr satan is done this does not look like mr satan at all
okay let's start a career mr satan I'm ready wait somebody please tell him
let him know that he needs to take any contract that comes his way since wrestling school can
always ask him to raise stats oh shit okay good to know all right let's kick some ass mr satan
single versus duke miniman I'm ready what's my popularity what the fuck oh it probably just
resets it no drugs this time yeah mr satan wouldn't take a drug why is he talking where the
fuck did I go do the voice all right I'm gonna kick the shit out of this guy oh it's it's wait
this guy age this is the mountie isn't it why did this guy age like 30 years hey do I have to
babysit the new kid he doesn't belong in the ring with me don't you remember your first time duke
miniman the canvas still has a stain where you pissed your pants we were all here at some point
in our lives and now this is mr satan's chance that's right it's my chain yeah well your first
chance is your last chance you never should have signed up for this kid is he the strongest man
in the world is somebody talking to him on a radio come on catch him in the face with that
oh see ya he's weak yeah but he's the strongest person on earth that move is not good I don't
like that at all test of strength versus mr satan what are you out of your goddamn mind
now that's how you really get a battle going I don't think I ever trained with no truth did you
all right so what happened last time remember last time when I played it went the full duration
neither one of us could hurt each other I want to kick him right in the fucking face
like that oh it's time it's time what's the special move oh he's punching with the balls
that move sucks what a terrible finisher that's not gonna win me any matches that's awful all
right this is he's done oh my god this sucks that would be so painful he's not tapping out though so
I mean I'm gonna keep doing it I'm pulling him so far back I have the ref too oh my god dude
I don't think he can tap out I don't think he's physically able to I don't think he's conscious
what happened this guy I'm gonna injure this guy all right can I pin him I just pin him
I gotta end this all right I'm gonna end up with a super kick ruining him yeah good night
two three that's so rude all right so I just like ended that guy's career Mr. Satan's profile has
improved considerably by winning convincingly in that that man Buddy Lee has renewed his contract
all right are I thought this had a hard gamer okay nothing is scheduled so let's just you know
what if nothing's scheduled I'm gonna go ahead and just do some let's do some strength training
82 that's good you believe grappling's ratings have risen okay here we go Mr. Satan you ever
considered changing the strikes in your arsenal oh I like the way that I fight all right I can't
tell you how to fight I just thought you might want to mix things up a little singles versus
Tate Madison let's go another person just to absolutely decimate this guy doesn't look
finished um all right score Ben I know you're cowering backstage clinging that undergraduate
title of yours that may be the safest place for you right now but that treasure can't stay there
I want you to pay attention to what happens in this match because you're next
oh I thought he's beat me oh my god I got him from behind again why is it ref holding the
microphone like put it down bro perfect suplex what oh wait that's illegal what did I just do
all right don't fuck this up he's done what are you thinking dude are you serious I'll get you
every time why is it what's referee what are you doing that Mr. Satan is way better than
German 985 was this German at five was awful in comparison look how much cleaner these matches
are and it's not even a stats thing I think the stats got reset didn't they again one two three
just like a DBZ fight oh my god oh my god that was horrible that was fucking horrible
that's making me that's making me cringe backwards this guy's actually a formidable
foe get up all right let's do this one again I don't know what just happened but I think I won
I think I did a good job there bring the frame rate down on the screen to make it look like a
DBZ fight what's he doing wait do I have him or does he have me I can't tell I think I had him
oh that felt good I wanted to go off the ropes all right this match is over holy shit all right
pin him again again can I catch him with that you get you get to get one move on me that's fine
now you don't even get one move pin him hate Madison please get up that's not gonna happen
all right let's break his neck I want to hear those crunches that's it yeah it's it's over
there's literally nowhere for him to go besides to tap up I'm pulling so hard in his head he's got
resilience you know what I like about this game I like that you okay so see how if I hold down
the strike button you do like oh or you can just do it lightly there's a range of holding it
this is honestly the best like actually wrestling video game that I've played since like no mercy
I really think that this is actually a good wrestling game does this one make sense the
new wrestling I've tried to play the new WWE games it's kind of confusing and weirdly controlling
it's like hard to control it's strange hey Mr. Satan everybody knows that decision was bogus
are you gonna fall down if you had any decency you would agree to restart this match and prove
that you can beat me properly um sure fine restart the match let's do it again I'll take
the shit out of you a second time you know the coward I thought you were but we both know the
result will be different this time are you leaving don't leave this time I'm gonna kill him okay
let's see how you feel after this one all right it really yeah it's double or nothing this really
is just me you know what don't let him get away get into the corner never mind he's this is just
sad count him fucking count him what are you doing are you kidding me oh my god he's broken
a damn I really want to like break his neck I know that's like fucked up but I mean this guy you
can't come in twice what is he inspecting oh my god really I just ended he's dead no you're not
gonna pin me you know what this is so good to be huge because I will rope break 30 to 40 percent
of every single pin just because I'm big I am all right what's the UFC thing gonna happen where
the guy just steps in and starts pulls me off him and they have to call this oh let's lose the test
of strength the guy that's barely standing there's no way this guy is gonna get up after this shit
I'm sorry why is he still going get the fuck out of here this is supposed to I've fought him
let's roll my arm I broke his back that's enough stay down what does it take to keep this guy down
seriously what does it take to keep this idiot down like just stay down that's it
finally that is counter established mr satan as a heel what why would that make me a heel the guy
challenged me to a second fight and I kicked his ass again why does that make me a heel doesn't
that make him just stupid why do I have to be a bad guy because the other guy is dumb because
he broke his neck four times whatever that did you're gonna challenge me to a double and nothing
match in the same day it's because you kept hitting him in the balls oh here's this guy again
hey mr satan don't you ever wish that there was someone in your corner to guide you to victory
yeah I mean sometimes I do but I heard that you're a real weirdo I want nothing to do with you
perhaps we can work together some other time I've always got your back if you need it mr satan
now this is the creepy guy that only wants to have you be his only friend all right four man
elimination going for it this is four man just quicken to the point you know samson is that
this is a john cena thing samson and score bends I like the red duke mini man back at it again
why do they always do that the ai just goes you know what I'm gonna grab the table for a second
being forced to defend my title against three of their opponents and that's just not fair
wait this is for the championship I'm not even out of school there's some sort of conspiracy to
get the title off of me but I didn't become champion in the first place by backing down
from a challenge this will be just my biggest win yet we're all stopping this guy hey what are you
doing duke mini man get the fuck out of here beat the absolute shit out of your face how my biggest
win yet wait aren't we all against him so wait why wait should I not have been punching him in
the face I'm confused I'm so confused I thought we were on the same team what the oh my god let
go my leg let go how do I get off wait who's leg am I the one with the red pants no all right
I was like weird I didn't know which character I was all right spring snap his arm off do something
I can't believe look at my health that's so dumb
wait no ref can't see this is illegal if I do
I broke his finger I hit him right in the index finger and I smashed it into like a little
car curled up thing oh my god that was horrible looking what the fuck was that
put him down oh that was ridiculous his poor finger like he was showing his boo-boo to the
school nurse wait is something pinned all right I'm that was a double right there you you know
what I'm coming for you fuck you I'm sick of this guy it's just first to get a pen
oh my goodness that almost happened holy fuck that was insanity if you're a big fat guy just
roll over get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get
him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get
him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him off me get him
off me get him off me get him off me get him off me really he's gonna take turns this guy
has almost full health this samson guy oh fuck he caught the leg he's biting me fuck I missed
nope oh I missed saw that he springboarded off of my belly what was that cartoon tom and jerry
bullshit what was that do I get credit for that if he gets eliminated you know I'm going up that
would have snapped his neck in half I must have a special too no somebody help me oh my god that's
that's it I'm the champion I'm the champion oh no never mind that was insane I like bellied
it back suplexed him into the guy's head and he did a hurricane run on the guy I'll take this one
too get out of the way I want to hit him right in his forehead there it is no if I don't want
to step on the ref on his head on his head on his head this is a big opportunity for me to get
will I be the champion will I actually just be the champion opportunity knocking right air come on
he hit his head on something that was that was a very loud noise what's happening right now
cartoon boink sound oh that was deadly all right this is the game winner right here did you
actually reverse that how this by the way guys this is drug-free so don't even tell me that I'm
on drugs um um no get up that's fine that's eliminated that's eliminated oh boy that's big
that's huge right there that's huge you want to eliminate yourself that's fine I'll just taunt
till I have a low blow and then I'll hit you in the nuts and pin you is it some kind of
taunt like you're gonna be the champion you're the next champion is that what this is okay sure
you know you have to win to be the champion you know that right you have to actually win dude
like you understand and you're never gonna wake up after that one ever again
fuck that's my belt actually see you later I'm now that I'm now the champion
undergraduate champion all right now I'm gonna get a lot of offers right I'm gonna get called
by all kinds of agencies I need to get I better get a lot of points for this okay that makes sense
Mr. Satan the new champion look at that how do I lose points I got the victory Royale still not
signed a lot of changes this week all right now what we've taken each other to hell and back Mr.
Satan and I've had enough of it I don't even know who this guy is why don't we bury the hatchet so
that we can both get back to concentrating on our careers let's make peace oh this is Samson oh no
it's the previous champion um oh you go fuck yourself I just remembered why I hate you so
much I should have known you couldn't be reasoned with oh yeah I'm supposed to be a good guy
whatever after three for the undergraduate championship versus hard gainer to win with
with three matches in row yeah wear that shit get a good shot of this ref hard gainer oh it's
the skeleton guy okay letting you do your own intro is really cool it is for anyone who wasn't
paying attention I am the new undergraduate champion of wrestling school a lot of people
thought it would never happen and you ignorant moron should admit that you're wrong I've achieved
all this without anybody's support so the only person I think is myself doing a 40 to 50 percent
Mr. Satan so I can do it for a long period of time here if Mr. Satan will change wrestling school
forever oh that was not fair all right hard gainer let's see what you made of can you handle a
fucking flurry of punches like this goodbye get a shot of that one oh it seems that Goku
seems to have fallen down out of the arena join us next time on Dragon Ball Z see what happens Goku
oh I hate this voice sorry I gotta do another move besides that nobody's a match for me
I'm just so strong I'm not even that much different than the Jerma character was though
that's the thing that's more annoying damn that was cool let's do some more stuff off the ropes
get in that corner all right this guy's fucked now that I got him on the ground let's go oh
shit nice there's three weight classes above these guys oh yeah aren't I like 500 pounds
you know what time it is it's time for the balls punch I have to do this three times
pick him up let's do um like that that's what makes you a heel just do it's a jumping double
stomp that's kind of a cool move I like that waiting for him this is what Shawn Michaels used
to do well not in not in that order but you know what point is that like not allowed he's
counting with the chair the falls again one fall just spin it again stop I didn't I wasn't trying
to do that on that one yeah I'm sorry it's time for the dive what am I doing I'm trying to grab
him for the ropes am I stuck oh come on I didn't even want to do that three two that's it match is
over it doesn't matter anymore Mr. Satan has cemented his reign by defending the undergraduate
championship this is going way better than the last one all right give me a contract an online
poll is identified Lance Monaco as the highest paid wrestler in the world Mr. Satan have you
ever considered changing the way you conduct yourself in the ring what do you mean the way
you do something can be more important than what you do a few gestures could help you express
yourself oh he wants me to be nicer sure I can change that's very open-minded of you I look
forward to seeing the new you um how do I do that all right let's take away the low blow I don't
want it I want something cool something powerful what the power factor how about just a straight up
just power bomb yeah the power bomb or that's horrible pop-up stunner no no no more ball
crushing no I want no more this one do jumping face buster how did your special move is just
throwing a guy into the ropes horrible got wrench suplex i mean I've been doing a lot of
submissions he's been working pretty well maybe I should really just do just a special move that
just rips their head off yeah all right he wants me to have like a I can't even change the gestures
oh that's all right that's fine this is the last man standing versus score bends
oh it changes the gestures for you automatically oh this is stupid it's just me waving to the crowd
I have to be Mr. Nice Guy now wave to the kids all right score bends last man standing make sure
you pick up a weapon bring it into the ring really really slowly and then drop it because it's
illegal I've been where you are now Mr. Satan I remember what it's like to be under the
undergraduate champion but I've also felt something you can't yet imagine and that's the burning
desire to claim it back if I have to climb over you to get back to the top of the mountain then
that's what I'm prepared to do anybody worth of this title would have let it go you were losing
and score bends and you're losing out it's two o'clock in the morning and I don't want to wake
up my mother in the other room by doing the mr satan voice so I'm doing a really shitty
awful version of it put that down wait can we even can we use that is that illegal doesn't say it is
why do I keep hitting myself in the head why do I keep hitting myself why is this what you want is
that what you're looking for he throat punched me oh my god what happened that hurt me more than it
hurt him holy shit oh I'm sorry how do I let you go how do I let you go keep counting keep counting
this is fucking awful stop it mr satan stop
I have to stop I can't I'm gonna get hurt why does he keep doing that I don't understand why
he does that I don't get it why does he hit himself in the face as hard as he can why
oh no give me that back oh my god he's wearing the belt
I win oh he suffered considerably considerably mr satan has cemented his reign by defending
uh the championship again there has to be some reason why maybe if you do it too many times in
a row you'll just mess up and hit yourself in the face but that it seems to happen all the time
mr satan's association with matt black has a negative effect on his attitude no it doesn't
I don't care about that guy why would I care about that guy mr satan why don't you give me
a shot at your undergraduate on the first week of september okay you know yeah sure sure that's a
date you know why I'll see you on the first of september make sure you're ready because I know
I will be that's a respectable thing to do he didn't interfere with the match he didn't like
come up with a mic and talk a bunch of shit about me he didn't like be somebody's manager and hit
me from behind and stuff he literally just said hey like I'm I want a shot at the title do you
think I deserve a shot it's like yeah all right let's see what you got this is a tables match
versus crucial kennedy nope I don't want to throw that in I want the table there all right what's
power bomb crucial kennedy who's this guy by the way why is that guy out here oh my god
that was been so funny if you stayed out there whatever I don't care what you just said nobody
cares yeah you wish you could have that don't you through the table oops no reversal get over here
do I have any what do I have a suplex or something I want to put him through the table
that's no god damn it I want that back all right the guy's coming in here to fight me I think
oh he just was crossing the ring oh I made this guy by the way I made craft men yeah I he was
supposed to be a craft beer guy and I thought it was like funny I'm just loading the ring with
fucking tables okay he's still in here this is a tables match and we're gonna I'm gonna use them
all right let's do it oh you want to stack this shit are you out of your mind can we do three
look we're both working together we're like building a house together holy shit are you
kidding me um oh god damn it what what what what are you kidding me I've waited too much
did I weigh too much that was stupid that was actually stupid that was for the championship
it was a trap okay whatever I lost status yeah that's unbelievable all right I had the belt for
five matches I'll get it back there goes the contract no I'm gonna get off at a contract
right now if you were watching you would know that that was a fluke that was bullshit everybody
knows it there's a total fluke that guy didn't beat me I'm still as skilled as I was before
I'm just too heavy to stand on three tables I got too cocky I've weighed 600 pounds guys
that's not being a bad wrestler that's just being too big oh this guy's probably really pissed
this is the guy that wanted to do the title match but I just lost the title
so now he's just oh well great we're just gonna have a regular match now he's probably pissed
I heard of his back is hurt already I asked her a sunflower pick last stream oh well I'll I'll
show you pick when I want to show you a pick we don't demand we don't demand things when I have
photos of the sunflowers and they're nice and full bloom I'm going to show them to you we don't demand
things here excuse me that would have been awesome if it hit him oh shit I'm fine all right he's
gonna mess this up oh that's a broken leg oh shit hey that's bad news get out I just rolled into
that I feel like that happens to me in Dark Souls all the time pick them up big DDT shit this game
is Dark Souls PvP all right I'm gonna try another move here let's go like this let's do the arm
spread let's do the like pregnancy class thing okay I just spit all over myself because of how
close the referee he was getting uh what happened oh my god is he okay I hit him I think I think he
got hurt he's what's what happened to him I think he with his broken arm don't even tell me this
guy's gonna beat me with like a broken shoulder oh well I know what to do now okay yep come here
I want to pin him oh he's not moving um oh he tapped instantly Roland Wiener injured his
shoulder in that match and will be out of action for the next two weeks oh you can actually get
injured Mr Satan's profile has improved all right get me back in like a big title match
I'm running short of staff tonight can you do commentary yep I'd love this
I think one of my favorite things is sitting at the desk and then deciding when I'm going to
laugh out loud get up and attack somebody my favorite thing to do Valhalla am I drinking
just water nobody sabotaged this guy it was a landmine somebody just what hey we're using that
desk okay um Rupert Royal what are you doing all right I'm fucking using that
fuck you buddy all right I'm sick of this bullshit give me that fucking thing
cut the shit ridiculous Mike Bale with shank was a tag is it a tag team
I am I you know what it's like to be in there how do you see this match ending
uh the best part about this is it's bent which means I've already hit somebody in the head with
this it'll be by pinfall of course let's see how if it ends by pinfall where am I all right I'm
supposed to be doing oh I'm a commentator right just give them stuff to like disqualify each other
with somebody will make a mistake you know what I mean somebody will make a mistake and wait can
who am I even doing this to like I should have just downed a beer before I do that and like do
a backdrop into a pool right on my back it's like everyone at the party's like holy shit dude that
probably hurt a lot fuck everybody here crack on his back and it's like oh fuck he's got his back
as he gets out his back is bright red okay I'm gonna sit down oh this is stupid I don't even
know what's happening it's a pin I got it right that's right I did oh that was unbelievable
this game is insane oh what a ridiculous game did I get any points Hank is disappointed that
his client lost okay second week of September do I get another title match oh
tough love the industry will come together to stage a special charity event on the third
week of September Mr. Satan has been branded negligent for injuring Roland Wiener in their
recent match what is coming up next is this is a submission match versus you smoke
my special move is a submission all right after play god damn I can count on fingers and toes
the amount of times that I've laughed really hard at this game this is what a what a treat
this has been I'm serious this has been unbelievable do I get to put this in game of the year even
though it's a remake I can right like this is up there it has to be it's like top three games of
the year it's so fun it's so stupid it's so funny it's fantastic what are you doing um oh
what I can't even think oh you've gotten lots of I can't I can't submission right submission
make the old man tap right now it's over he's gonna tap right here no it's all right I'll get
him with uh I'll get him with the submission that hurts if I get my special uh it's the crazy choke
ref get out of the way I can't smoke everyone um because he's not good again that's good this
this is game of smoke I'm sorry this might be actually end his career this is it everybody
say goodbye finishing move good night oh that's it that hurts that's incredibly painful that
hurts even to look at folks profiles suffered considerably mr satan improved a little okay
looking good I still haven't been signed somebody sign me sign me let's go just sign me
add new moves to your repertoire no sign me do I have to go to an agency I think they approach
you we got approached last time oh here's the okay steps what is steps versus manny quinn
um what does steps mean the steps match go to database I don't think I can select any of these
you just wait to be recruited these people are lying okay what does the steps match mean this
one actually is in front of people I could make a brittle uh I can make a real splash here we have
to build a staircase together coach emerson it's very important do you like cantaloupe um not
really I don't usually I kind of avoid the cantaloupe in a fruit cup and if I still really
want to eat it I'll eat the candle up at the end the melon I usually leave that for last
who am I fighting manny quinn and I are out here for just more than another wrestling match
this is a special charity event that will raise money for good causes all over the world
so let's hit each other in the head with stairs those in attendance have already donated
I've already done their bit by showing up so give yourselves a big round of applause
we hope you'll be joined by many more watching at home who can also pledge their donation online
enough talking manny quinn let's give the world a match that's worthy of a big donation
what's that um uh are we supposed to be fighting manny um this is no this is like bad I don't like
this manny let's put on a big show hold on here keep him out there oh stay out there all right
I'm trying to hit him in the face what no I want to throw it at him my goodness what are you doing
what's wrong with you what are you doing why are you like this you do this every single time I'm
in a match you're actually like the best person to have in the corner let go of me what give me
give me that can I have that thank you what constitutes a win if he's dead they're booing
me I want him to come up here I want to give him a power bomb through this I need to do something
through the table let's give him a show that's what they want come up here that you've come up
here let's give him a show come up here let's give him a goddamn show idiot idiot you idiot
oh my god this is I this is no I this is like a charity event I'd be like all right can they
stop doing this this I don't this I don't like this where did he go he just gets like sucked
into the crowd is he in here he's got me in a boston crab okay hey it's for charity
you're hitting people in the crowd I am not hitting anybody in the crowd this thing closed
I think this is this is closed I am barely balancing on top of this this is a closed
ladder oh no it's not it's open okay I think I have to pin him but I don't know why but for
a second I thought that said take a five minute break like all right there's time for us to take
a break get the fuck out of here oh shit put him on here I want to like get him on the table
there we are oh fuck all right that guy's not gonna get up for a long time I don't think
there's no way I tap out here he's still here okay all right all right I'm pinning him I'm
pinning him all right I'm doing a move and I'm gonna pin him pin this asshole once and for all
it's over thank you how much did we raise for charity don't even tell me you're gonna get up
you piece of shit 100 bucks we raised a hundred dollars for charity we know we raised like five
dollars this guy's covered in I can't even say it this guy's covered in blood covered in blood
I don't even care who I'm hitting anymore holy shit he dodged it that's the bloodiest guy we've
seen all night that's enough that's it with the mic oh my god I just can't stop laughing it's so
stupid oh John Crockett is currently on the ground oh okay that was all right we've raised
almost half a million goddamn dollars for charity oh wait Mr. Satan has been booked to face Mike
Bale in a handicap hardcore match on the fourth week of October you kidding me steel cage escape
to victory oh hell yeah cage match time is this for the championship or is this just for an
exhibition match can I get two of the championships sorry half of somebody that half a million dollars
donated and how much is that is to go to that old man's surgery to reconstruct his entire body
god damn it god oh dude you know what I'm gonna do it's just so easy it's so easy to just
dive into the announcer's table not right now give me my mic we're gonna talk you know where
to run now that I've got you locked inside this cage crucial Kennedy one of us only one of us
is getting out of here in one piece and it's not going to be you you're not locked in here with me
ever locked it in with your whatever he says wait can this legal I think the mics are legal
locking it with your mic this would be hell to listen to in the audience imagine being the guy
that has to wear the headset and listen to this yeah yeah right don't think so sorry buddy that
ain't happening like oh me that was cool I get him I'm going for it get out let's go come on oh
what who did did he do that what shook the ring all right that that's a lot of damage that was
a lot of damage oh you all right you know stay down for a second this is it I'm gonna get it
what the fuck is happening am I too heavy to climb out of the cage what um excuse me what was that
bullshit what the fuck are you talking about climb the cage got it no don't let him get it
I gotta grab him I'm getting out holy shit I'm there
champion oh
it's right here with like like the sims 4 with all the mods on it and it was just it was just
total nonsense for like five straight hours I feel the same way this is this is insanity
it's so funny I still haven't been paid yet yeah I have not been paid once
oh okay I have nothing scheduled so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna train I'm gonna train
what should I do strength or stamina I'll be standing up ready to get this 81 all right I'm
good with that rest it's nearly 1 a.m. I know I'm having fun though I'm having a blast go all in on
stamina okay hardcore versus crucial Kennedy again all right well I just won the belt from this guy
all right I'm gonna just beat him with the bat until I hit him that's the plan go all in on
strength yeah I'm gonna try to get to like 90 strength I was trying to kill him I was just
trying to kill him missed ladies and gentlemen welcome to this hardcore match first allow me
to introduce wrestling school's undergraduate champion Mr. Satan weighing in at 211 pounds
at six feet we have crucial Kennedy I'm your referee coach Emerson so let's ring the bell
and find ourselves a winner big fucking mistake this is just like when you're like a level three
in Warcraft and you just waltz into like the level 60 zone what the fuck were you thinking dude
oh my god I'm gonna I'm getting through this table too let's go weekly wild reference yeah
whatever don't put me through that thank you I was gonna say that was a really risky move
all right come here I'm putting you through this get this in a good spot because I want to do it
off the top turnbuckle I want to put him through the table off the turnbuckle you know what I'm
saying I gotta get him in the corner get over here coward coward hey don't touch that I moved
it over there for a reason stop it get on there say good night I'm gonna hang you here till the
blood drops and then I'm gonna have to drop you on your head I didn't even break the table how
the fuck did that happen that hurt me more than him great come here I want you in the corner
no in the corner come here too far away I did it that's exactly what I wanted to do
that was pretty sick actually I too bad we didn't get to see it I did not know you could just fix
the table that's pretty interesting move what are you doing why are you doing that what the
fuck is this guy doing group project Mike Bale why is he in a referee outfit uh what are you
doing don't even know why this guy's here what are you doing here why are you here what are you
that guy just waltzed in here and was videotaping like he was on vacation this guy's role playing
as a referee why you're not the referee in the throat you're not the referee get out of here
yeah take your belt take your belt shove it up your ass I think this guy's lost I don't what is
he doing with the table I'm very confused as to why he's doing this he picked the excuse me
excuse me I've ran too fast all right I gotta end this oh shit sorry coach it's a pin
pin him wait he is the referee what is wait what's happening is anybody as confused as I am why can
that guy count he's not the referee the coach is the referee you can't just interfere and be
the referee that's not how this works what the fuck is going on because I thought the coach was
a referee hey I'm so confused but whatever I'm it's over three two okay I won thank you
Mr. Satan's progress is being hindered by the limitations of wrestling school I need to be
called up this should have pinned the ref the entire sport of wrestling has increased the
population for 2021 whatever that's so wrong here we go nice to meet you Mr. Satan we invited you
here to discuss working for Rising Sun Pururisu we feel you'd be a valuable addition to the
roster and we're prepared to make it happen with this deal holy shit what fourteen thousand dollars
three hundred dollars per week to lose every match all right hold on cannot be terminated
prematurely wins pay what health insurance existing relationships assigned the same deal
promised to be booked as or against a champion part-time scheduled to work fewer dates
what the fuck how about this no I won't sign with a rival promotion all right how about
you can I don't care you can tell me what to do how's that yes all right I think we can make that
work I don't have to lose every match thanks for showing up at same but I'm afraid we couldn't
find a spot for you on the card does it get fired nothing scheduled oh shit well then let's level
up strength oh almost 84 all right give me my money there we go you scammed your someone what
even worse deal what they said that I have to lose every single match and I said I don't care about
I let me wait no creative control means I they'll they'll make me lose that's worse
oh not only did I sign I signed a contract where they control literally everything about me
and my concern was I didn't want them to control me losing matches but I just signed a document
saying that they can control everything including everything which is matches where's my lawyer
why was my lawyer in the room why would I ever sign that with a lawyer okay whatever new contract
I think I have like another two weeks smoke could not be woken from his sleep this morning
oh that's not good the 60 year old veteran is thought to have died of natural causes
oh my god the industry I didn't kill him you stage a special
in the memory of smoke mm-hmm okay just saying I'm keeping an eye on your progress think some
changes need to be made you're not talented enough to give fans the technical wrestling that they see
get you skilled at 82 by november you're gonna have to find a different line of work
singles versus shane asterisk my skill at now I can do that later um was I the last person he
fought isn't this guy that like has been under a bad contract I want to sit in the chair and
not stand on it shane asterisk with fanny monaco fight that killed smoke how could you
joe's dedicated to the memory of smoke who recently passed away what I'm doing this
smoke's work in this ring meant a lot of fans with the person he was backstage
meant even more to us fucking god get out of the chair get out of the chair oh my god
that's not no I couldn't stand up I didn't I thought that was next week I thought that
was next week guys you have any idea I thought that was next week I didn't know this was the
charity event oh my god I can't I have to fucking all right whatever I'm gonna fight him
I what are all these people doing in here sitting I didn't mean to sit down I swear to god
I was hitting every button spamming to get up oh that's so bad it's all right all right let me
doesn't have any fucking idea what's going on out there what's happening why is why is this
happening oh drop it shit that's illegal why is all this stuff in the ring these guys all right
let's play stop playing rancho relax oh ng I'm sorry get out of here fighting the fucking ref
what do you can't lift me too big I always have my special somehow I don't know how
I don't know why but I thought like I had a mattress in his hands and I thought he was
trying to make it safer for us I hit my head on that all right whatever all right string stuff
together let's go good he's probably gonna go out the ring remind let me go up I who did the move
to who I love doing that to people is it and huge wow that was into the special this is um that's
one of the announcers by the way this lady did not come with anybody like I don't know what the
fuck you're doing why would one of the announcers come in what's the point of the announcer you know
I'm just gonna throw a barbell into the crowd and see what happens I dropped it I'm fine what
let's go uh from the front let's do this that was pretty sick and that's probably it
one three the winner I get the championship wait what about my client what about my owner or my
the owner of the company that I work for yes there we go seven hundred thousand dollars
where are my wages don't I get three hundred dollars a week oh your owner I'm talking about
the owner of the company like that's the owner of the company Mr. Satan has been challenged to
increase his skill to 82% I'll get it right here Mr. Satan has been booked to face Snake
Suzuki in a red light match on the third week of November what does that mean a red light match
the skill has to be uh 82 right it was skill right make sure you get this right I'm gonna be
really weak for this fight but I don't even care I have to do this because I have a day off tomorrow
which I can get it to 82 all right let's go is this a singles match oh it's just a red light match
I know it's not let's go as I'm sure you're all aware I'm the reigning super junior champion here
at rising sun poor that was disrespectful throwing my belt unfortunately the competition in this
division is so pathetic that I've resorted to finding my own that's why I'm pleased to
announce that I'll be granting a title shot to whoever wins this match yes of course this is the
day that I train did you just grab me why did you just grab me that was not fair I think I can still
do it I really do I was gonna play smart all right let's play smart nice he missed
don't don't don't don't don't don't don't do it again get out of the way man what did I do
all right I didn't I don't know what just happened who ow I gotta equalize this down here
even though it's four seconds I gotta hit him the fucking head with the chair
all right give me that give me that get the fuck away from me I'm gonna get counted out
or is he who's six am I six who's seven is it me he's filming this he's stuck count him out please
oh god damn it I have to get him out here he has to come out here and have to kill I have to beat
the fuck out of him with the chair where's the chair it's out here somewhere where is it
blocked that guy he blocked two hits with the chair I think I lose yeah I'm camping look at
my health I started this with no health put him down I gotta reset this no put him I'm dead he's
over he punched me in the balls and he's gonna run away you dick it's over it's over it's it
get me in the ring give me the ring holy shit I did it okay here we go what's wrong with me
okay what's wrong with me I couldn't move he was staring at the stick and he hit himself
in the head I didn't do anything so fucking tired get up oh it's over I think I don't think I'm
getting up oh that's sad that's it it's over it literally jammed that stupid stick into my head
where am I am I still on the ground I'm still on the ground oh shit come on why
what's wrong with my controller I can't press any buttons
I think the game broke Mr. Satan has been booked to face Tower of Misawa in a no
ring tag team match okay okay when I hit myself on the head with the stick
it broke the controller doesn't work anymore let me try replugging it back in
I don't know what just happened what just happened what just happened what the fuck just happened
what what did that happen I don't even know what happened I skipped a day but how okay I've got
full health I got one more day to get to 82 this is the red light match versus snake Suzuki
today is the day isn't it week three is it week one isn't it wasn't what day wait what day were we
on wait wait wait wait hold on a second what are you talking about it's the fun way I thought I
didn't didn't I have a day of rest tomorrow and then the exclamation point isn't that what I need
to look for what if I quit I always skipped it wait can I quit oh thank god okay we're probably
gonna stop fairly soon anyways but we're gonna have to find a stopping point because my neck
right now is way worse than it was four or five hours ago that's a guarantee my leg is shoulder
and chest red light matches means it's red I want to end this as fast as I can because this looks
I don't like how this looks is everything is anything legal travel all right against ropes
let's do a grab I just okay well whatever I fucked up this is the virtual boy match yeah it is
don't you mean the face all right I didn't mean to do that but it's all right it's effective
just a slight little hip toss keep the chain wrestling going oh just flip three times I'm
doing the running punch moves the crowd is silent okay same guy that made hard time you know I
heard of that too I was gonna play these games a while ago and then I finally comes like you
know what maybe I'll try it now well when I say now I mean like maybe two or three months ago
and I just saw that he was making this remake so I'm like shit do I want to play the
old one or just wait for him to do the remake and instead was coming out in only a couple months
I was like well screw it we'll just wait and here we are and this is a special move let's see if we
can break his neck our time is literally 10 out of 10 you should play it that it happening yeah
he's oh no our time is like this but it's prison oh I can't even imagine how insane that probably is
that was a beautiful move and that's a pin for sure no it's not
so much blood this guy's trying to get away from me that enough you make an earthquake every time
you walk cover him ref there it is people if I killed smoke I made that guy he's deleted from
the game he's not he's gone it's not like oh yeah but he's still in the roster no he's gone
he was deleted yeah I got my skill points good can I buy stuff I have $17,000 there
congratulations mr satan you followed my advice and made your prospects better than ever please
accept a $1,000 bonus as a reward just make sure you keep up the good work there's more to this
business than what takes place in the ring mr satan why don't you join us for a drink to unwind
it probably wouldn't cost more than 100 bucks well that's 10 drinks um but okay sure that's like
oh sometimes 20 drinks cool I hope you can handle your beer it'll be good
this is not good no ring tag team utter monk and tower misawa I got him I actually hit him
I hit him in the back what are they doing you picked a child out of the crowd for all the
good it's going to do you the weapons are allowed oh it doesn't matter if I'm hung over
weapons are allowed fuck don't let him are you serious who's on my team I don't know who's on
my team again it happened again I don't know who's on my team who's on my team it's this guy's a bad
guy right where are you going I have to stop that that's my boss that's so stupid I love it
I'm so tired oh fuck you caught it all right let's let's let's let's work together work together
here we go work together who's pinning who do we win we're getting it's smoking
are you smoking a cigarette why can you you're smoking
oh that's my guy so close to these people
like wouldn't you move don't you think you would don't you think wait what we get disqualified
what happened you off kick the judge they're not a judge that's a commentator that's not
the judge this isn't the Olympics they don't hold up signs with a score on it
the judge and I count on you to referee one of the matches all right this is the last match and
then I'm gonna I'm gonna call it it's getting really late this is final match of the night
720 bucks I'm referee tonight it's a submission match oh oh that's so funny like we they were
so close why wouldn't they move even after I punched that person in the face that guy just
still sat there oh I'm gonna have to take a bath tonight I'm seriously gonna be in it
I'm so tired too look at my guy this is definitely a bath night without a doubt
oh my god my chest and back how am I coming in with them oh no never mind all right who do I
want to win what I'm on the uh what whose team am I on okay I think I'm on their team right
just to make it look like I didn't like me I just look like I'm like fair I can't get up
into the referee it's just on his like sleeping oh all right I'm up I'm up I'm up I'm up I'm up
I'm out again I keep being unplugged when they plug me back in I'm just still in crazed mode
I didn't change out of that oh and over his head that would have been so funny imagine if I hit
him right in the mouth and he went backwards oh my god I would have to end stream right there
that would have been the end of the stream I'd have to quit you want the guy with the black
shorts to win yeah I think we're in the same organization right I'm not doing that much
influence I'm just every time it looks like he's got the upper hand I'm gonna hit him we have the
same boss yeah and when it looks like he's he's gonna win I come in yeah I'm the ref should I pin
him what if I pin my own organization guy uh no you got a little too far I have to make it fair
right hey we're the same team I'm so tired all right easy now you want to go for a pin
if you pin him right now I'll count really quickly what the fuck bring your son to work day
just I just landed on my neck I'm trying to pin him get out of here all right pin him pin him pin
him pin him I gotta get up here so I can get a better view I'm like a baby what am I doing
I'm sitting like biting my nails just sitting here perched what's that guy doing back there
standing excuse me out out out out out out of the ring out of the ring out of the ring
and your punishment get the shit beat out of you with a chair for five minutes how am I missing
all right can somebody pin someone no one's even attempted to do anything like I've been bored
somebody do something somebody do something
get out get down get out the boss is on him all right I gotta all right who's fighting who
wait I've just received word from Motorola Chan that this match must be restarted immediately
really just count them out again where's the all right get back in the ring get in the ring
nice job everybody wait that's my boss okay I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm done
oh my god I can't laugh anymore I can't laugh like that anymore I can't I can't laugh like that
okay I'll see you guys later I'm supposed to stream tomorrow I okay here's the thing
we're streaming tomorrow I'm just gonna I'm gonna play this again tomorrow I kind of want to keep
going and just play at least for a little while tomorrow um if for some reason I wake up tomorrow
and I am like a brick person it's very possible that I may have done some damage um and we'll
just do Monday but tomorrow if you don't if you'll hear from me a couple hours before the stream at
least see how I get up tomorrow if not that was do Monday oh listen to my voice is gone like my
everything is done that was watching the funniest movie I've ever seen and it was
like two Lord of the Rings movies back-to-back of the funniest movie I've ever watched
please don't kill smoke he's already dead I can't bring him back oh my goodness is this a save
automatically I think so it's bashing it's facing with a chair and I didn't even whatever oh my
goodness gracious all right I'll talk to you guys tomorrow if not tomorrow then Monday
we'll play this again I think I feel like I'm having enough fun with this that I want to do
this again at least try to get to like a higher championship and just see what happens in like
maybe another few hours we'll see I'll see you guys later have a great rest of your night we're
gonna just throw this over here I believe it is it should be saved and I'll see you guys soon
let's talk I don't want this because that's um I'm a DMCA Monday stream incoming I don't know
probably I'll let you know tomorrow before I start like maybe two or three hours before the sus which
will be probably around two three plan for Monday but I might just get up and be fine and we can
just go at like 2 p.m. uh but I would yeah I would plan for Monday literally every time I've ever
said it's gonna happen on the earlier day it's never happened one time in 10 years so I'm pretty
predictable at this point that was awesome I loved every second of that um thanks again for the subs
there were a lot of subs I missed a lot of them too because I was just sort of completely engrossed
and everything going on don't push yourself no I'll be okay I I don't worry I take plenty of time
off if I feel like I can't then I just won't is this the game of the decade um it's definitely one
of the funnest most I would let let's put it this way it's definitely one of the most entertaining
games I've played in the last couple of years that's 100% for sure Otto hello this is going
to be a really long second germa video it's going to be one of those second germa videos it's going
to be one of those germa 985 videos uh where it's just the wheeze laughter cut between wheeze laughter
and me progressively getting like a more blown out voice
by hard time once I get my fill of this we'll see there's a couple there's well actually I
could tell you this uh remember how I broke my uh vive controller it actually broke and I couldn't
use it anymore like I it's actually broken um well I got an index so we can do that with the
knuckle controllers so at some point probably next week I would say we're probably gonna get
back into VR and do another VR smorgasbord for a night or two at least we'll probably we'll
probably do another two day next weekend because if I'm gonna do VR I'm gonna want to do like
at least four you want to go out I know I'll let you out all right let's go you must go outside
uh thanks everybody for watching as always sorry that I started like two days late and that I
started like three hours late and apart for the course on this channel at this point as you all
know but yeah I'll probably either see you guys tomorrow or see you on Monday plan for Monday
have a fantastic rest of your night I'll see you very soon within the next couple
days we're gonna keep playing wrestling empire night guys see you soon