Hey, sorry I didn't start. Sorry, I got lost in the mail, you know. I thought I could get
myself shipped here in a timely manner, but I got lost in the fucking mail. Look at this.
But I bid you hello. Hope you had a good couple of days, three days here.
Speaking of three days, we are going to do three days. That's one, two, three, in a row
of virtual reality. We're going to start today with Mind Show. If you don't know what Mind Show is,
well, I'll tell you. You get in that headset and you act out scenes from movies that you
make in your mind. I'm going to show you guys some of my acting chops. What's wrong with my
desk? No, no, no, no, no. What is this? Why is there like goo on this desk? I use coasters
every time. I need to get like a desk cleaner. Oh, that sucks. What is this? I'm not happy about
that. Someone's in fucking deep shit. I don't know who did that. They're in deep fucking shit,
though. Let's see who comes in this room. Me. Anybody else come in this room? No, just me.
You're in big trouble. I'm sorry, I didn't need to not use a coaster. Use a coaster
next time, every time. Not next time, every time. No, not the top row. Anyways, let's turn
the camera on. You want to? No, not yet. I don't like that. I don't want to be on camera yet.
Not until I've had my coffee because I have to finish it. You know what? Fine, fuck it. Let's
just get on camera. That like, that like ultra gamer hunch. Did you see that? That was
almost like I was, somebody was holding me up by my neck like this, like pinching, like
that. Twitch TV. I got Twitch shirt on today. Just in case you didn't know where you were.
That's all right. I got, I got the influencer shirt on. The thing is though, it's incredibly
light. So it allows me to go like this. I had to prepare for this stream. Guys,
I've been walking. I've been taking walks to prepare for this day. Remember last time I
streamed VR? I was, I kept going like this, like, no, I, I've been like moving.
It's been great. I've been taking like a 40 minute walk every day. I'm dead serious. That's
not a joke. This is not one of those scenarios where like Jeremy says something completely
fucking untrue. And then we laugh about it in 40 minutes. No, I'm staying active. Get active.
Facial hair? Yeah. I mean, I just, I just didn't care. I was thinking, here's the thing.
I don't, help me out here. How many of you guys hate the way that you look with a freshly
shaved face? I hate it. I need like two days after shaving before I'm happy with what's
going on up here. I don't like it. So what happens is I, I know that I have to shave,
but I know that if I shave, I'm going to get that weird like crystal face. I don't like it.
So I usually try to wait like a day or two and then it's been like four days and then
four days turns into five and then it gets hard to do. Just trim it. No, I have an ugly
fucking beard. Look at this. Like this is, I grow facial hair here and like here and then
here. I don't grow facial hair here. It just looks like coal. Shaggy. Yeah, it doesn't look
good. I know people that can grow big thick beards up here. No, not me. I'm lucky if I
get, and if you look up close, I'm not going to do it because some people might be eating.
So I'm not going to do that. But up close, see from here, this is, oh, he's just got like a
little beard today. If I go up close, you can see every individual disgusting hair and I know
some of you, I probably snack it. So I don't want to make you throw up. Anyways, why don't
we go ahead and get this started? I've been here long enough. Let me just, hold on. I got
to finish my coffee. Let me get this dog mug. You want to see it? You really want to see
this? All right, fine. Let me, I'm going to be fair warning. If you've got like a ballamaze in
front of you, put the fork down, get the bib off and just go like this. You don't want to see
this. You see? This looks like I glued on hair on my face. See what I'm talking about?
It looks like I went to the barber, right? I went to like the hair salon and like I'm
just like crawling on the ground. They're like cutting people's hair and I'm just like
picking up pieces and going like, oh, that's a good one. I like put that in my pocket
and then I get home and I like glue them on. It doesn't, it doesn't, it's all right.
He's covering the zit. No, I was stretching my, look, there's two there. I'm a human,
okay? Some people want to pretend that they don't look like shit sometimes. I'm a human.
Humans look like shit. That's just the way it is, all right? So for those of you that
have trouble seeing a guy with like a pimple right here, humans are gross. That's all you
need to know. Do you have any gross things your body does on a daily basis? All right,
no, no, no, let's go. Let's go. I'm done with this shit. I'm picking up my VR headset. I
don't want to be like, I gotta like get started. I don't want to talk about every
gross thing that we do. Saliva, think about it. Inside of your mouth right now
is a viscous liquid that is never ending and always is produced. That's disgusting.
It's gross. When are we going to get the ability to like sap the DNA from trees?
And I just want to become a tree person. I actually was talking to Kim about this two
days ago so she can bounce for it. I probably swear to God. I was talking about trees and
how like I want to be like a tree. You had to be there, all right? You had to be there
because trees don't have like, oh fucking nerd neck. Anyways, here we go. Let's get in
here. I gotta get, hold on, let me get these on first. Is this the right, is this the right
hand? I don't know. No, okay, this is right because you guys are on the left. We were
talking about, I can't even explain it. That's a very, that's for like a Monster
Rancher type stream, all right? Let's talk for 40 minutes on how I wish I could be a tree.
That's the title of a book. Are we sure that like Shel Silverstein didn't write this
poem? I think he may have. I really think that exists. All right, is this going to work?
What's going on here? All right, I'm going in. This is Mind Show. Can you guys hear this?
I hope so. You can still let me know. It's been a while. So give me a break. I don't know.
Never mind. I was going to say never mind. I'm all over the place today but that's probably
a good thing. I'm happy. It's a happy day. Oh, and before we get started, I want to show
you this. This came out of my faucet. Is this okay to drink? This came out of my,
out of the tap. Is that okay? It's a fucking lemonade relax. Here we go. Yes, I know I'm
stalling and I'm going to continue to stall because you know how fucking bad I get in here.
My like life flashes before my eyes after two hours in VR. Oh, I just three stoogesed myself.
God damn it. Hey Larry, come here you chump. Give me a break. Oh, there you guys are.
No sound. I don't think there is sound right now. All right, so I'm in the right spot, right?
Can you hear that? Now let's do a vocal warm up. Read this card at a normal volume.
Do robots have butts? Uh oh. Great. Now you're ready to play. All right, it worked.
Point and pull the trigger to start. So my show is what you'll see.
Hey there. Welcome to my show where you can remix and share crazy animated shows.
Let's watch a show and learn how to remix and share. Okay.
Easy. Great. Now your turn. Hit remix to start remixing. Is that the remix button?
Remix. Point at the alien and pull the trigger to hop in.
That's you now. You're an alien. Get comfortable. So I'm the alien now. How do I record?
Now you're ready to record. Try talking to yourself in the mirror. Make something up.
When you're ready, click record. How do I click record? Oh, right. You can do this today.
You're going to go out there and you're going to show everybody what you're made of.
You're going to show everybody what you're capable of. Not what anybody else is,
what you are. You have what it takes. You're in that. Now click play to watch what you did.
Now you're ready for something a little more intense.
That's too quiet. I'll turn it up. I'll turn it up.
Looks like this show could use a remix. Click remix to start remixing. I'm the alien.
Now point at the alien and pull the trigger to hop in. All you got to do is react to the
other character. Don't forget to use your body and your voice. When you're ready, click record.
All right. So I got to get a good scene here. All right. I think I'm ready.
Hey, hey, hey. You buying my girl a drink at the bar?
Don't you ever look at my girl again. That was quite a performance.
Let's watch back your remix. Where is the bar? There is no bar here.
Great. You just did your first remix. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. I want to
let's talk about this. Not sure about sharing. You can always hop back in and redo your
record. I want to play it again. Let's talk about this.
It's terrible. Why didn't it pick up the thing I said? Share to stream?
Click here to share. I don't want to share that. Who's that on the screen? What does that mean?
Congratulations. You just shared your first remix. Now let's check out what some other folks did
with the same show. What's with my voice?
This hot new religion. Come on. Come on. Why is my voice so fucked up?
It doesn't even understand why am I.
How do I do that?
Oh, there is a giant. If you like a show, hit the heart button on your hand.
That'll send some love to the person that created it.
Daniel's remix called to follow. Well, I don't want to follow anybody.
Oh, that was wild. Personally, I liked yours the best. When this show ends, you're taking
to the home space. Try following a few folks by pointing at their picture and holding down
the trigger. After that, click on the games tab and play a game. All right. I'm ready to
make a show. Star Wars episode seven. I mean, nine. Why am I screaming? I feel like,
okay, this is weird. I feel like when I'm inside the helmet, I have to be louder.
I don't understand why that is. All right. What am I doing? Games, play stream, stream
games, holiday party, part one. You can't like you contribute to these holiday party.
Which one do you want to contribute to? Get in part three. All right. Let's contribute
to this one. This is a holiday party. Just play along with the scene. Don't
forget to use your voice. Here we go. What? Hey, what's happening? What? The party's
canceled? Unbelievable. That's stupid. We pay $40 to cover. I don't know how to get back.
Then we have to go through the portal. You want me to hit him? I'll hit him. I'll punch
him in the face as hard as I can. Let's go. Ready? Share your show. I don't want
to share that. That sucked. That's my voice. It's canceled. That's stupid. Yeah. Sorry
about that. I don't know. You know how to get back? Yeah. Problem. That portal's
only a one way portal. You're kidding. These blocks can help you. You want to
try that? You want me to hit him? I'll hit him. I'll punch him in the face as
hard as I can. Let's go. Okay. I didn't think my voice. How do I make my voice
different? I'm not sharing that one. Fine. I will. That was just me talking as
me. All right. Get me back here. All right. What about Hungry for Veggies?
I'm just like, I'm ruined. Okay. I'm just ruining other people's shows. Is
that what this is? Hungry for Veggies. Do I have to pretend to be like
Hungry for Veggies. Part one? Why are these clocks on? Oh, okay. I see. It's
downloading. We'll do part one. I need to change my voice too. Otherwise, it's
just like Jerma985, the fucking loser. It's my voice. It's just me. No,
I'm going to be like monsters and shit. All right. Here we go.
Just play along with the scene. Don't forget to use your voice. Here we
go. Grandpa. What are you going to do during the holidays? I'm going to
visit you and hug you. That's what we do here today. You and me. That's
interesting. I'm just going to chill out here in the fridge. Do you have any
cookies? You guys, they're planning on eating us. What? Oh no, what am I
going to do? Now share your show. I'm sorry. I was so...
I was so...
Italics! Italics, don't worry. Don't call the police. I'm fine.
I'm going to visit you and hug you. That's what we do here today.
You and me. That's so awkward. That's interesting. I'm just going to
chill out here in the fridge. Do you have any cookies? You guys, they're
planning on eating us. What? Oh no, what am I going to do? Why would
you stop screaming there? You know what I mean? Can we show that
again? How do I move the camera? What are you going to do during the
holidays? I'm going to visit you and hug you. That's what we do here
today. You and me. Is this a ninja turtle? I'm just going to chill
out here in the fridge. Do you have any cookies? You guys, they're
planning on eating us. What? Oh no, what am I going to do? Hey,
welcome to the scream stream. How do I do that? I don't know,
I'll go back. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Export video. 360. No, share.
Yeah, there we go. I don't know how. Love it. That was great.
Unless I can press a button, maybe? All right, we'll get in a
couple more. Let me go fuck up somebody else's mind show. I
had to do it, right? I had to do it. You can import source
filmmaker characters in this game? How loud was that? Did I
really peak the mic that much? How bad was that peak? There we
go. Well, there's the new phone. How do we get in to get
it? How do you think Santa's going to feel about that?
Sounds good to me. Let's go get that phone. How do I do
this? I want to remix this. Remix.
Need to get phone in case. Not big surprise. I can do it.
Let's go. Wait. Well, there's the new phone. How do we get
in to get it? No, I just put a bit. How do I be the heavy?
No, no, no. Record tools. Here. No, no, no, no. Go back.
Reset, reset. What's going on here? Google Play? I just
implanted him into the scene. How do I play? Did I do something
wrong here? Right hand. Okay, that's move. Is there like a...
Okay, there we go. Hop in, right? Hop in. Is this like
protected? Hop in. Delete. Okay. Hop in. Trigger. Yeah,
I'm pressing the trigger. Maybe this, maybe I can't like
fuck with this one. Let's go back. No, no, don't you?
Okay, there we go. Remix. So hop in. That was weird. Okay.
No, no, no, no. All right. Well, shit. Okay, I want to be
the heavy. I'll just do them both. I'm just going to do
them both. I'll show you my acting skills. Ready? That
looks good. You can do like sad. There we go. Hey, hey,
hey. Do re mi, do re mi, do re mi, do re mi, do re mi. Okay,
I'm ready. There's the cell phone that you were looking
for.
You fucking break in, you fucking idiot. How else do we
fucking get in there, huh? Actually, if you have a brick
or something, we could throw the brick through the window
and steal the phone. That's my hand. You're swearing way
too much. I did not raise you like this. I did not raise
you like this. You swear too much. Your mother says the
same thing. You're going to go to jail one day.
There's the cell phone that you were looking for.
You fucking break in, you fucking idiot. How else do we
fucking get in there, huh? Actually, if you have a brick
or something, we could throw the brick through the window
and steal the phone. That's my hand. I think I fucking
kissed the new fucking phone. You see that shit over there,
man? That's my fucking new iPhone 25. I did not raise
you like this. I did not raise you like this. You
swear too much. Your mother says the same thing.
Fuck yeah, do as fucking do it. You're going to go to jail
one day. Let's just remix this fucking one, too.
We got that one.
There's the cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy wants cell phone
to use. Yeah, actually, if you have a brick or something, we could throw the
brick through the window. That's good idea. Let me try. I will break
door down. You're swearing way too much. I did not raise you like this.
Swear. I did not raise you like this. You swear too much. When did I swear?
I will crush puny man with fingers and squeeze. I'm kind of doing
Reinhardt right now at the beginning. All right, whatever.
There's the cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy wants cell phone to use.
Actually, if you have a brick or something, we could throw the brick through the window.
That's good idea. Let me try. I will break door down. You're swearing way
too much. I did not raise you like this.
Swear. I did not raise you like this. You swear too much. When did I swear?
I will crush puny man with fingers and squeeze. You're going to go to jail one day.
What the fuck was that?
No, no, no, I don't want to be a scream stream.
God damn it. I'm sorry for everybody. Just lower the volume a little.
There's the cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy wants cell phone to use.
Actually, if you have a brick or something, we could throw the brick through the window.
Squeeze. That's good idea. Let me try. I will break door down.
You're swearing way too much. I did not raise you like this.
Swear. I did not raise you like this.
You swear too much. When did I swear?
I will crush puny man with fingers and squeeze.
I told you to be ready for it. I'm sorry.
There's the cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy wants cell phone to use.
Actually, if you have a brick or something, we could throw the brick through the window.
That's good idea. Let me try. I will break door down.
You're swearing way too much. I did not raise you like this.
Swear. I did not raise you like this.
You swear too much. When did I swear?
I will crush puny man with fingers and squeeze.
This is fucking terrible. Can I delete this character forever?
I'm not going to do that. You're going to blow my vocal cords out
if I have to put him in every single scene.
He just has my voice. He doesn't even have a cool voice.
By the way, I'm just coming to a realization here.
This is part two of somebody's story that they made.
I just came in the middle. This person is making a cake.
The cake has got eggs, it's got baking soda, it's got vanilla extract.
I just walked in. They went to the bathroom.
And I came in here and I just dumped in a bunch of gravy
and just fucking shook it up and left the house.
That's seriously what I did. Okay.
I don't think I can add any more people.
Let's watch it one more time and then we'll move on.
There's a cell phone that you were looking for.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Remix. Remix. Get me in here.
Get me in here. We're redoing this one.
There's a cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy, what cell phone?
I didn't break it.
That's a good idea. Let me try. I will break the door down.
You're saying too much right now. I didn't raise you like this.
I did not raise you like this. Your mother says this too.
I will crush puny man with fingers.
I'm kind of...
There is a cell phone that you were looking for.
Yes, cell phone in there. Heavy, what cell phone?
I didn't break it.
I didn't raise you like this.
Your mother says this too.
I will crush puny man with fingers.
I'm fucking out of here. I'm out of here. I'm out of this. I'm done. That was bad.
What happened to mine? Oh, I went back.
Why is it always a little kid? It's always a kid. Why is the biggest guy always the little kid?
You break the window.
Alright, I'm getting the fuck out of here.
What else is there? I love this. Let's do, uh, Big Barb's Bee Farm.
Hamsgiving. Space Trek. Space Trek. Part 3. Let's get in this one. Watch this.
Make them all screaming lettuce. Guys, you want this stream to be like 45 minutes long?
Is that what you want? Because the more that I scream as loud as I can, the more it's going to be over in like less than two hours.
Alright, here we go. I gotta go in for this one. Who should I be? Let's find out.
I could have gone a little bit better. The alien was pretty hostile, I gotta admit. But, you know, at least we're here in this great desert.
There are literally no life signs on the entire planet in case you were wondering.
Oh, that's good.
Well, I wasn't wondering, but thanks for letting me know. Good to know.
Well, at least there's no one left to write us a bad report, right?
Well, I hope we can find our way back to the ship.
Watch this one.
Come on. I can't be like the tourist. I can't move you? Oh, it's protected. Come on.
How is this like protected? I was gonna put them all the way back there and be sprinting down screaming about how there's no oxygen on the planet.
Oh, come on. Yeah, I'm hoping it. Can I? How do I teleport? Can I teleport?
Here we go. Teleport. No, no, no, no. That looks good.
Am I gonna bump into anything? Where am I? I don't know. I'm gonna smash into something. I'm not careful.
Thank God. This light. Hey, it's quicksand. Shit. Hey, why do you not have astronaut helmets on?
There's no oxygen on the planet. No. No. No, I told you.
Okay, I'm back. Quicksand.
There's no one left to write us a bad report, right?
Try it. I'll come over there and I'll give you the oxygen pills.
Why is this one different? Where's the camera? Wait, what? No, give me over here.
So, how did it go?
It's quicksand. Shit.
It didn't go very good.
It didn't like me.
Why do you not have astronaut helmets on? There's no oxygen on the planet. No, I told you.
Well, at least there's no one left to write us a bad report, right?
Try it. I'll come over there and I'll give you the oxygen pills.
What a fucking mess. How do I move the character? Put to boomer in.
Hold on. I'm going to delete this character. Hold on.
All right, now we got our own scene.
Go right here. What are we going to do about that? Characters.
What about voices and shit?
Is there a way we can change that?
Let's hold on. Looks good. No, no, no. This is like more... There we go.
That's better. Okay.
Three o'clock.
Do you know this guy?
You all right?
Why do you not have astronaut helmets on?
Because we can breathe.
There's no oxygen on the planet.
You're stupid.
No, I told you.
Do you know this guy?
Quicksand.
We can move around fine, man.
I'll come over there and I'll give you the oxygen pills.
You're stupid.
How do I change the voice?
Jesus.
Is there a way to change the voice?
Auto changes. Okay.
Oh, hey, Keywell.
Here we go. Ready?
I got to get this right because we have to both like suck in the air at the same time.
What do you got for a time?
Three o'clock.
Thank God it's light.
Hey, it's Quicksand.
Do you know this guy?
Shit.
I don't know who that is.
Hey, you all right?
Why do you not have astronaut helmets on?
Because we can breathe.
There's no oxygen on the planet.
You're stupid.
No, I told you.
You are an idiot.
Do you know this guy?
I don't know that.
Why do you keep asking me that?
I got a rope.
Hold on.
Little finger.
That's a rope.
Oh, shit.
I got too into it.
I got too into the fucking scene.
Hold on.
Go back.
I wanted to see it so bad from this angle.
I got to learn how to do like cameras.
Like I think it's like this, right?
So we can start here.
Thank God it's light.
Hey, it's Quicksand.
Do you know this guy?
Shit.
I don't know who that is.
I can move in like here.
Hey, you all right?
Why do you not have astronaut helmets on?
Because we can breathe.
There's no oxygen on the planet.
I hate that.
I hate it so much.
You're stupid.
No, I told you.
You are an idiot.
Do you know this guy?
Quicksand.
I don't know that.
Why do you keep asking me that?
I got a rope.
I'll give you the oxygen by the finger.
Hold on.
Okay.
My hands are like too shaky to do this.
God damn it.
Hold on.
My hands are like fucking shaky as hell.
Thank God it's light.
All right.
Hold on a second.
Let me put this down.
Where is it?
I'm down on the ground.
All right.
Let's sit here and watch it while I have like shaky sniper hands.
Thank God it's light.
It's Quicksand.
Do you know this guy?
I don't ever get it.
Why do you not have astralisks on?
Because we can breathe.
There's no oxygen on the planet.
No.
I told you.
You are an idiot.
Do you know this guy?
Quicksand.
I don't know that.
Why do you keep asking me that?
I got a rope.
We can move out of the highland.
I'll get over there and I'll give you the oxygen by the finger.
What do I have?
Save performance.
Okay.
How do I do that?
Now get this off.
Quick share.
Share.
There we go.
There you go.
There it is.
Somebody filmed a wedding?
What the fuck?
So this is...
Wait.
Wow.
So how did it go?
This is...
No, it is another one.
Where's mine?
I want to see mine pop up in here.
Wow.
So how did it go?
I didn't even use the right characters.
Yeah.
There are literal life signs on the entire planet in case you were wondering.
What's wrong...
At least there's no one left to write us a bad report, right?
Sorry.
What the fuck?
Recreate the clip frame, we've got plenty of things to do here.
I'm going to do a full scene in the gym.
scene. And then I'm gonna do the Clippet scene. We've got a long way to go. I might even go get
fucking wine. This is amazing. What a fun game. I can't wait. All right. One more of these. What
about games? What did I do? Oh, okay. I was on games. All right. Hold on. One more. Let me
just go and see one more. Secret agent. That's so cool. Let's do secret agent. So you want to
be a secret agent. Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done. So you want to be a
secret agent. Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done. I've shit in my hand and I
ate it only one time though, but that was weird. It was, I was hungry and there was no more pizzas
in the fridge in the freezer. Is that enough? I don't have any combat training at all. Zero.
And I'm very afraid of knives and it's pointy shark things. So it is indeed terrible. So
you want to be a secret agent. Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done. I've shit
in my hand and I ate it only one time though, but that was weird. It was, I was hungry.
There was no more pizzas in the fridge in the freezer. Is that enough? I don't have any
combat training at all. Zero. And I'm very afraid of knives and it's pointy shark things.
It is indeed terrible. So you want to be a secret agent. Start by telling me the worst thing
you have ever done. Let me think about this. Five seconds from now, snap your neck,
throw you over the table, bend your legs backwards over your head, crack all the
bones in your body and snap them in every direction. Is that enough for you? Oh yeah,
by the way, look at me. What? No. So you want to be a secret agent. Start by telling me the worst
thing you have ever done. Let me think about this. Five seconds from now, snap your neck,
throw you over the table, bend your legs backwards over your head, crack all the bones in your body
and snap them in every direction. Is that enough for you? Oh yeah, by the way, look at me.
What the fuck? Why did I say that at the end? It is indeed terrible. Why? I like fruits. By the way,
look at me. Oh, by the way, look at me. No, get back in there. Get back in there. I'm going to
do a different version of that one. So you want to be a secret agent. Start by telling me
the worst thing you have ever done. Worst thing I've ever done? First of all, that laptop right
there, smash it down onto your fingers just like the old pie cartoon thing where the person puts
their hands on it and the grandma comes over and slams the pie down on their hands and then
break your face in half, take both your eyeballs out, eat them both at the same time and then
you, I would make you watch and then boot you in the face as hard as I could. So you want to
be a secret agent? Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done. Worst thing I've ever done?
Worst thing I've ever done? First of all, that laptop right there, smash it down onto your fingers just like the old pie
cartoon thing where the person puts their hands on it and the grandma comes over and slams the pie down on their
hands and then break your face in half, take both your eyeballs out, eat them both at the same time and then you, I would make you
watch and then boot you in the face as hard as I could. So you want to be a secret agent? Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done.
So you want to be a secret agent? Start by telling me the worst thing you have ever done. Worst thing I've ever done?
First of all, that laptop right there, smash it down onto your fingers just like the old pie cartoon thing where the person puts their
hands on it and the grandma comes over and slams the pie down on their hands and then break your face in half, take both your eyeballs out, eat them both at the same time
and then you, I would make you watch and then boot you in the face as hard as I could.
You already know what's coming.
This is a Food Network Star Season 41 audition. What makes you a Food Network Star?
I don't know.
Let me get the camera.
I need to move.
This is a Food Network Star Season 41 audition.
That's what I'm doing here.
What makes you a Food Network Star?
Worst thing I've ever done.
First of all, that laptop right there.
Smash it down on your fingers.
Just like the old pie cartoon thing.
First they put their hands on it, then the grandma comes over and slams it.
The pie down on their hands.
And then break your face in half.
Take both your eyeballs out.
Eat them both at the same time.
And then you...
What does that have to do with pasta?
Let's watch it.
This is a Food Network Star Season 41 audition.
No, goddamn it, stop.
That's what I'm doing here.
What makes you a Food Network Star?
Worst thing I've ever done.
First of all, that laptop right there.
Smash it down on your fingers.
Just like the old pie cartoon thing.
First they put their hands on it, then the grandma comes over and slams the pie down on their hands.
And then break your face in half.
Take both your eyeballs out.
Eat them both at the same time.
And then you...
What does that have to do with pasta?
Let's watch it.
The camera man.
Yeah, I'm just realizing that.
Why is the camera man in focus?
It should be from that perspective.
It's time to make our room, okay?
Let's share this one.
Sure, why not?
What's...
Oh, there we go, okay.
Is there another one?
So you want to be a secret agent?
Stop.
Alright.
So, my create a show.
Let's see how this works.
Okay, untitled by Tommy Pickles.
We got hip.
Space, a diner?
Okay.
Is there a gym?
Here we go.
Alright, opening scene.
Environment.
Characters.
Okay, let's go with...
Let's start with you.
Where's my other options?
Why are they locked?
I can't move them?
Do I not have access to this?
For some reason?
Why is it locked?
It's DLC!
It might be in record mode.
How do I get that off?
No, it's not DLC.
Weirdly enough, it thinks I'm still trying to videotape.
I wonder if I can just put somebody else in here.
I'm still doing the same thing.
Nothing like over here.
It's just glitched out in record...
Alright, let me go back to the main menu.
Let's try it again.
Create show.
Pretty good.
Huh.
Maybe I should need to restart the game?
Green screen?
Hold on, hold on.
Behind me.
Click one of these sides?
Oh, hold on.
Props.
Environment.
So you want to be a secret agent?
Just record it and then edit it.
I guess I'm just recording.
Okay.
No, it's not recording anything.
I think I might have to restart the game.
I can't even press this.
Yellow dots?
Clear?
Nah, something's not right here.
Something's not right.
I'm stuck in the void.
I'm just going to restart the game.
Yeah, let's just restart it.
Give me a second.
I'm also, you know what?
Let's get some wine up here too.
I'm going to make a whole goddamn movie.
Let's get some wine up here.
Let me get out for a second.
I'm going to restart the game.
This is a ton of fun.
I will be right back.
I'm going to get this restarted and grab a glass of wine.
It is like 4,000 degrees in this room already.
All right, let me get back in here.
Let's hope that fixes it because this is...
I'm not going to say it yet.
I'm not sure.
But this could be...
This could be like one of the coolest VR games.
Very possible.
Reopen it up.
Mind show.
Okay, let's try it again.
Hey, everybody!
Hey, did you see?
Okay.
Welcome to mind show.
I'm drunk.
This is not...
This is like...
That's a heavy pour, all right?
It is.
But I said I'm going to be drinking it for like four hours.
All right, let's go.
Get me back in.
Show it again.
This also might be skunked.
Because this is the...
Hey, hold on.
For all of you like scientists, if this...
If you leave a bottle of wine out for like six hours after opening it and you put it back in the fridge, are you going to die?
Does that kill you?
Am I going to get tapeworm?
I don't want to get tapeworm.
Am I going to get like...
Am I going to get worms?
All right.
Yuck.
Ew.
All right.
I'm ready to do my comedy routine.
There we go.
It's already dirty in here.
Sweat check.
We're good.
I know you're not supposed to do this, but fuck it.
I have to.
It's too greasy in here.
All right.
Wait.
One more sip of wine.
I thought it taste right.
Tastes like batteries.
That tastes like batteries smell.
Wrong hand.
Okay.
Where's like...
Assistant!
To help me get in here, you need a personal assistant to get in and out of VR.
That's why when they do the demos, it's like three people there holding stuff for you.
All right.
I'm ready.
Fuck.
Wrong hand.
How did I do this?
What?
I just checked it.
Assistant!
That's flat.
I'm better than that.
Email notifications.
Get notified.
Don't email me.
Followers?
Who am I?
I'm already following people.
Here we go.
Can we...
Why is this different?
Hey!
Look at that.
Why?
Why did this switch?
Whatever.
Comedy club.
Can you guys hear?
Is it muted?
Shouldn't be muted, right?
Okay.
All right.
Let's do it.
So, this scene is going to be...
Let's block it out here, everybody.
Acting 101.
103, actually.
The first thing you need to do is...
I don't like it here.
That's better.
First thing you need to do in acting is get into a character, right?
So, we're going to pick a character and we're going to...
I'm going to give you the whole backstory.
New.
Okay, move a little closer.
Wait.
We're going to have a few people in the scene here to laugh at the jokes.
Snow person?
I can only have three people.
Shit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Shit.
Okay, well that's fine.
How do I drop the mic stand?
The mic is too high.
All right, let's get this blocked out.
Ready?
So, I'm going to get in here and we'll go with happy.
Dude, are my hands actually this shaky?
What happened?
What?
Didn't I switch this?
I'm confused.
Okay.
I don't know.
I switched it like three times.
Okay, I just poisoned somebody's drink.
Sitting across from them and we switched the poisons back and forth enough times where
I poisoned myself.
Whatever.
We just did the princess bride.
All right.
Here we go.
Can I grab the mic?
We're going to get some jokes here.
Okay.
How's everybody doing?
How's everybody?
All right.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's get him.
He's got something down here.
Okay.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing tonight?
How's everybody doing?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So, I just...
All right.
They didn't have...
I need to be...
First of all, have you been to the airport?
Wait.
That's all the time I get.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Look at that acting.
All right.
They didn't have...
I need to be...
First of all, have you been to the airport?
Okay.
Here we go.
Thank you.
He can't reach it.
Everybody in Twitch chat.
Right.
Hey.
Everybody in Twitch chat.
First of all, have you been to the airport?
Wait.
That's all the time I get.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So, I just...
Look at that acting.
All right.
right he can't he can't reach it sure sure you're tiny he's tiny you're off
the stage
why am I so shaky I don't understand
you can't you can't reach it you can't reach it
you can't you can't reach it
sure you're tiny he's tiny
alright alright alright
now they got it
alright let's get the camera up here let's be a goddamn director
you can't reach it
everybody in twitch chat write it
he can't reach it
sure you're tiny
alright alright alright
alright let's watch it let's watch it let's get let's watch it
I'm gonna watch it
you can't reach it
everybody in twitch chat write it
he can't he can't reach it
sure you're tiny
alright alright alright
right here
first of all
there you go
get it out of your system now because that's the only one you're getting
alright so can I
can I add another scene right
can I add another one on top of this
I'm not shaking around that much
can you enable labs mode labs mode what is that
where do I find labs mode
from the main menu okay well I'm gonna save this one
is it saved
every stream every day there you go
alright so what happened
what's going on here
did I just fuck it up
what the hell happened
alright let's go do labs mode you got that one
alright back to the main menu
because that means I can do more characters labs mode warning click to enable labs
we're in labs mode
welcome to labs alright
we're gonna break the game
alright great show
we're in labs mode now alright let's do
the gym is this gym I can't tell I can't tell
what this is no this is not a gym alright it could be
we're gonna block out over here shit it's doing that thing again
no
it's doing that thing again is it something I can do to fix this
or do I have to reload the game again I don't have a character
so I don't have the options okay well let's get a character in here
we need a gym guy
yeah see what the hell come on
no try creating a spectator camera
empty wacky weather report he can't reach it
google it yeah let me google that
try let's check the options
for more characters in time
experimental tools I guess I'm gonna put it on
clear give me something here
alright there we go no no no ragdoll
what oh that's experimental tools
now I can't do anything on the controller
no damn it
well turn the controllers on and off
do I turn the controllers off
let me switch settings
controller camera customize
controller binding steam
VR no that's not it
hold the button down yeah that's what I just did
this is off I mean I'm just holding it
okay that one's off let's try this again
come on my energy my energies are here
alright they're both off I could have just pressed that couldn't I
okay now let's go back to here
now god damn it if you're playing with a
starter certain parts of the land menu will have locks over them
for each part of the starter in a specific order
so I have to do the starter stuff but I mean I just
reloaded and came back and I could do the comedy club scene
hold on let me see play stream
I have to beat the tutorial but I mean what is
the tutorial I mean we kind of already did it
didn't we just restart the game
well let's just restart it that worked last time
alright let me just turn let me just hold on
I can do this shit this is restarted
I really hope I don't have to do this every time
be kind of irritating oh well let's just open it again
it's when I bring up the camera the actual
recording camera is when it screws up unfortunately
get rid of the camera in my hand yeah but you only do that by
navigating out I can't navigate out I can only go to teleport
the audio is ahead of the face cam that
doesn't make any sense shouldn't be like that
everything's on zero alright let's try this again
why can't I open steam what the hell's going on
why is my whole computer fucked up oh dear god
give me a break it's the future VR
you just need like four assistants to get it to work
it'll get there one day alright let's open it back up
let's try it again frustration levels
are rising welcome to mind show
what I already did this quickly
quickly quickly quickly before I cause a problem
I don't know man that smells like acid tastes
I'm ready let me play my
video game alright I'm going in what did I just do
5.58 p.m. 6 o'clock ah thanks
for watching man it's like kind of getting late a little bit here
I'm doing like a Bobcat Goldthwaite alright here we go
give me a show create show
do I slabs mode activated does that stay on
no it's not
fuck okay
I'm ready it's a gym we got our
stuff back hop in alright so let's delete
let's delete you let's scale delete
delete delete delete
delete delete this is a
gym there's a wait what if we go for props
props maybe like a workbench okay
no no no camera
come on it's gonna be like dumbbells you're gonna have to use
the hammer okay can I I can wait can I
glue shit together because I could get okay hold on
let me get an item and then you get that again and then I'm gonna glue it
together no that's not the right thing actually
these are probably what is the how what's that prop
I want that prop did I go buy it
I don't see it in here am I stupid
am I dumb am I stupid
where is it it it's not in here
whatever that's fine we'll just keep that as it is alright
so this kid we're gonna move this out of the way this is just like
another barbell that's fine it's like a heart rate thing they have in the
gym sometimes alright let's get let's get this
going so that's the bench press
so then I need characters
gym guy it's heavy
who should be this is pretty good
let's get yeah that's perfect like skeleton
so now how do I get you to lie down
can I get you to lie down on here do I have
I think I have to physically lie down I have to lie down
I have to lie down on this alright
so we'll start with you actually yeah
we'll start with you we'll do somebody over here like doing push-ups
and shit look at another character where the hell did he go
okay this is like the push-up bench let's get
let's get like the actors blocked out and do their thing right
okay that's good
ah ah
ah I can't I can't do I don't
okay that's easier
that's much easier alright that's good
three
four
seven
you can do it you can do it
ah here
here take it here just take it it's easy to pick up
I see
okay they're done they're just back that's just background actors
now I'm going to get you
but my legs my
no this is not going to work I can't
lie down I don't even know what this looks like
I have to go like this I
huh three yeah yeah I can use a spotter
thank you oh you're a really smart person
okay yeah oh yeah sure
together I don't know if I've come
let's do it or anyone
you can do it
no no no
what are you listening to
can I get that playlist
you're on Spotify
oh
together
fuck come on it's going to be over here
oh hey man hey bro what's going on man
I see you're having some trouble with the weight there
if you need a spotter let me help you out here man
alright now it's going
okay
I see you're having some trouble with the weight there
if you need a spotter let me help you out here man
okay now stop stop stop wait wait
hey bro what's going on here
I see you're having some trouble with the weight there
if you need a spotter let me help you out here man
alright stop stop stop
stop stop stop
I can't stop it now he's got to be
closer oh dear I don't think I can
move him anymore okay so let's hop in again
is this the beginning
oh god damn it's the beginning alright
hey uh bro bro you just
dropped the weight man you need some help with that weight
let me spot you here you're looking at a little bit of trouble
let me help you yeah I'm not
pretty intelligent okay you ready let me give you a spot
you got to do the work man you got to do the work it's all in you
now everything's comfortable everything's fine
you can do it I believe in you bro come on
okay come on yeah this way again
you can do it man you can do it bro come on bro
yes you can you can do it
it's a playlist man
yeah it's a custom playlist
gets me pumped up and in the zone alright
okay now let's try it with an actual weight this time because we haven't done anything
hey uh bro bro you just dropped the weight man
you need some help with that weight these people need to shut the fuck up
these people just suck
sir you can do it
alright I'm deleting these two
I'm deleting them
alright I fucking hate this
these people don't even need to be here
they're just annoying and loud how do I turn them down
I get to do the sounds with my voice
this is not going to happen alright let me get the camera out here
hold on wait wait wait
do you see what's going on in here
we're locked out of the room we can't get in there
there's a surgery scheduled in 20 minutes
what are we supposed to do
just call the cops
this is unbelievable
hey you're dirtying up our stuff
dirtying I know I know how to say it thanks for the correction asshole
you can do it
have you used your key card yet
unbelievable
at least get your cell phone out and film this this would be a viral video
some of these people aren't even alive that's a skeleton in there
whatever
I get a salary nonetheless so it doesn't matter
okay let's try it with the actual weight
yeah I just
we're locked out of the room we can't get in there
there's a surgery scheduled in 20 minutes
I know there's a surgery scheduled
I scheduled it
I already did
I know
hey you're dirtying up our stuff
I know I know how to say it
you can do it
shut it you got
you got like 3.6 on Yelp as a surgeon you suck
my key card I know what I'm doing
at least get your cell phone out and film this
some of these people aren't even alive that's a skeleton in there
that is kind of weird you're right
it's a plastic playlist
should I put weight on it
yeah me too we both get paid so who cares
this is going to be chaos
we're locked out of the room
we can't get in there
there's a surgery scheduled in 20 minutes
I know there's a surgery scheduled
I scheduled it
we're locked out of the room
I know
hey you're dirtying up our stuff
I know I know how to say it
you can do it
shut it you got
you got like 3.6 on Yelp as a surgeon you suck
you can do it man
shut it
you can do it
I got to put a cell phone in there
it's a plastic playlist
gets me pumped up in the zoo
I got a salary in that one
I'm going to go
I got to think about how I wanted this to be shot
because it's going to be fucking mayhem
so we start in here
let's just go as we go
teleport
I think start over here
camera
let's start here
back it up
we're locked out of the room
we can't get in
it's a surgery scheduled
I know there's a surgery scheduled
there's like 3 different scenes
going on
back it up
there's so many things going on here
we're locked out of the room
we can't get in
it's a surgery scheduled
back it up
we're locked out of the room
we can't get in
get me outside here
it's a surgery scheduled
let's go with this
let's look at the scene
I scheduled it
this is unbelievable
hey
you're dirtying
you can do it
you got like 3.6 on yellow
I don't even know where to put the camera
you can do it man
at least get your cell phone out and film this
you can do it
this is fucked
I can't even handle how fucking dumb this one is
are you guys ready to watch this shit
I need to save this one
how do I do that
did I do it
yellow dots is saved
it said save performance
let me see if this works
where's the camera
did I just lose everything
why would it do that
did that actually work
I did all that work and then I said save performance
and it just exited the screen
is this going to save the camera shit
I hope so
it will not
hold on let me see
I'm so confused at how that works
I did everything and on the top left it said save performance
can I watch that now
because I can't
where's my
hold trigger to record that's like what I did
that's kind of an odd menu system
because now
I've misclicked when trying to save
the recording thing is still red
how do I watch it from here
there's no real clear indication of
when I record like this
where does it go
I'm just going to go to the menu to see what happens
I'm just going to go back
sharing to stream
saving the performance overwrites the camera data
why the hell would that happen
it's working right
oh
ok
I scheduled
I don't know what you are telling me
did that work
I'm so confused
hey you dirty
dirty
you can do it
You can do it!
I mean, I can't believe you can do it.
You got like, 3.6 on you.
I think it's just doin' it.
Come on, suffer.
What the fuck is happening?
You can at least get your cell phone out and film this.
This is getting a lot of video.
No, it's working.
Some of these people aren't even alive.
That's a skeleton.
Hey, I just proved I'm a playlist, man.
Am I gonna make you in the scene?
Yeah, it's a custom playlist.
It gets people hooked up in the Zoom.
I gotta stab her in the head so that I don't hurt her.
Yeah, okay.
Well, let's try it a little bit.
I'm just gonna wait.
Did I do it?
What the hell is going on here?
What the fuck?
Does anybody have any idea what the fuck is happening?
It just went, it's going crazy and now it's like doing the thing.
It was rendering, was it though?
I feel like that's the beginning.
Did I have too conflicting takes?
Nah, I don't think so.
I mean, it's exporting, but it's exporting like, incorrectly.
So if I like even, if I even touch right trigger at all,
it deletes the whole thing.
You'd think there'd be like a confirmation there or something.
Like, oh, you sure you want to like delete all the camera shit you just did?
I don't, I don't think I did that though.
That's the multiple takes at the beginning.
Oh, okay.
How do I get out of here?
What?
Did I beat the game?
This is all fucked up.
Okay, come back.
View, viewer position.
What the fuck is happening?
So I have to do that again.
So this is the very beginning.
God damn it.
All right.
Fuck.
That was done.
All right.
So let's do it again.
What a pain in the ass.
I'll make it quick.
No, back up here, back up here.
All right, slowly but surely.
Some of these people aren't even alive.
All right.
Okay.
Nobody move.
I got it.
So now it's ready.
I didn't need to do this.
It's already saved.
Well, but what about the camera?
Like freaking out all over the place?
Because I did like the multiple tapes, right?
I didn't need to redo it.
Oh, it already did it.
Oh, what the fuck?
All right.
Let's watch the damn thing.
You ready?
No.
No, play it.
I just practiced it needs to render.
All right, but like
so what not save performance from here.
Look at my computer.
What about it?
What are you talking about?
Labs is the culprit.
So you tell me if I click on save performance
or if I click on more and I do save.
Yeah, I okay.
I know it saves it in documents folder, but
so if I go to export right now the files are on yeah,
but like how do I know it's even saving what I just did?
All right.
Hold on.
Documents mind show videos.
Okay.
What the fuck?
I see it, but it's all fucked up.
All right.
So it's the cameras all fucked up.
It's all shaking around like crazy.
I don't know why it's doing this.
Holy shit.
It's so fucked up.
What the fuck?
All right.
I'm going to export this one and see what happens.
Yeah, this video is all fucked up.
It's the same.
I'll show you the curse after.
I'm going to try to save this one.
So all right.
Let me get this straight.
Save performance export video, right?
My god, this shouldn't be this complicated.
Save performance.
What?
All right.
The export.
Where is it?
What you see what I'm talking about?
What happened to it?
Share 60 FPS.
It's gonna work.
I can't hear this anymore.
You just dropped away.
There's a surgery scheduled in 20 minutes.
I know there's a surgery scheduled.
I scheduled it.
I think this is working.
All right.
If you've got a save performance button in the top left.
You got to go right to another menu after that.
You can just fuck it all up.
I thought like save performance, save it and save it.
But it's not like the video.
They're two separate entities.
Okay.
All right.
It's time to watch that video.
Oh, thank God.
It's finally done.
Time for the next scene.
Well, there wasn't no tutorial on that one.
I had to just guess.
We're not going to watch this one.
We've seen this one so many times.
Like this one.
I don't want to hear the wait thing.
We'll watch them all at the end.
They see the skeleton in there.
You see the skeleton?
I don't want to hear that fucking line anymore.
All right.
I know now I know how to save and export performances.
I figured it out.
Some of these people aren't even alive.
That's a skeleton in there.
Yeah, I'm going to put all these awkward.
I'll do a compilation at the end of the stream.
It's a 3.4 on Yelp.
All right.
Next scene.
Give me an object.
Give me a place.
Oh, no, no.
I'm going to do the clip thing.
Right.
See if I can recreate the clip.
I do have to do a fight scene too.
Acknowledge the please for rat movie.
I can't do all.
I can't do the whole rat movie guys.
That's like fucking seven minutes.
I'm lucky to get one scene done with 30 seconds minute long.
That was like a painful procedure.
All right.
Give me a scene.
Give me an object.
Give me a thing.
Give me a person.
Give me a place.
Give me a thing.
Give me a noun.
Give me a verb.
Give me an adjective.
Give me an adverb.
Give me a conjunctivitis.
Force.
Okay.
I can't do that.
Sorry.
Believe me.
I'm going to wait for this to be done.
Go.
Hey, we're back.
We don't want to see this.
Get me out of here quick.
New scene.
Clear it.
Oh shit.
Oh, God damn it.
No, that's fine.
Just in case something goes wrong.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay.
All right.
Clear it.
New place.
We need a...
Hello.
Hello and welcome to another episode.
Hello and welcome.
Hello.
See you.
Deaf.
This one's going to be experimental.
We're going with an experimental poetry.
I'm not even doing that.
Do you see what happened here?
I'm not doing that.
Stop it.
My father was fairly wealthy.
He would sometimes come home and shower us with gifts.
Various toys, trinkets, and the like.
But my father also brought something else into the house.
Animals.
Lots of animals.
See, he was a zoologist by trade.
And besides the money, which was great, we had an entire zoo in our backyard.
Although through the years, one would say that sharing a bed
with a giraffe is not so great.
After a while.
We grow distant, him and I.
The last time I spoke with him was July of 2006.
And here's why.
He killed my mother!
I don't know.
That was not enough time.
What?
Various toys, trinkets, animals.
This sucks.
He was a zoologist by trade.
And besides the money, which was great, we had an entire zoo in our backyard.
Although through the years, one would say that sharing a bed
was not so great.
I'm not going to do tons of like, cuts and shit.
We grow distant.
The last time I spoke with him was July of 2006.
And here's why.
He killed my mother!
I don't know why.
Are you ready?
My father was fairly wealthy.
He would sometimes come home and shower us with gifts.
Various toys, trinkets, and the like.
But my father also brought something else into the house.
Animals.
Lots of animals.
He was a zoologist by trade.
And besides the money, which was great, we had an entire zoo in our backyard.
Although through the years, one would say that sharing a bed
Ow!
was not so great.
We grow distant.
The last time I spoke with him was July of 2006.
And here's why.
He killed my mother!
This one sucks.
My father was fairly wealthy.
He would sometimes come home and shower us with gifts.
Various toys, trinkets, and the like.
But my father also brought something else into the house.
Animals.
He was a zoologist by trade.
And besides the money, which was great, we had an entire zoo in our backyard.
Although through the years, one would say that sharing a bed
I'm trying to think of an animal.
I was so desperately thinking of an animal.
You can feel the cogs turning there.
We grow distant.
The last time I spoke with him was July of 2006.
And here's why.
He killed my mother!
Hey, I make sure to scream at the end.
Look at this camera work.
You don't think I know what I'm doing?
You don't think I didn't go to school for this shit?
Mods, please.
What's going on?
Don't turn that into a coffee pasta.
Jesus Christ.
God.
July of what?
Various toys, trinkets.
That was just...
Alright, so, you know...
When words just come out, but they mean absolutely nothing.
Words were just coming out of my mouth.
And they meant nothing.
It was just word soup.
It didn't mean anything.
It wasn't going anywhere.
It was just a...
It was a run-on sentence.
Fix the audio, DC.
I don't know what...
Hold on.
What are you talking about?
What are you...
Hold on.
Ready? Like...
It should be...
There's no sync.
Game audio.
That shouldn't be a thing.
Video has desync.
Alright.
But how much?
Already?
Let's do a test.
I wanna see.
It's three seconds.
What the fuck are you talking about?
What?
It's three seconds of desync?
No way.
You gotta be kidding me.
What the fuck are you...
What?
Are you serious?
Why?
That doesn't make any sense.
How does that make any sense?
Alright.
Hold on a minute.
I gotta do some testing here.
That makes no sense.
Save it.
Save this.
Alright.
You ready?
Click.
Are you hearing that when I click it?
It's delayed.
Alright.
But by how much?
So are you hearing the...
It's actually bad.
I'm surprised.
No.
It is not five seconds.
Click comes way later in the video.
That's fucking strange.
That's strange.
Alright.
Hold on a second here.
So it comes way later.
It's like two seconds?
It's actually a couple...
That makes no sense.
Because of my...
It's to do with the game.
No.
That's weird.
Because on my screen it looks fine.
Let me see if I can delay this.
So...
Tell me if this changes anything.
I'm sorry guys.
That's really weird.
Tell me if this changes anything.
Ready?
Click.
Now it's worse.
Hold on a sec.
Let me try this.
I'm gonna try something here.
Tell me if this changes anything.
I gotta add a...
I'm gonna add a filter on it.
And see if I can just make it...
That's annoying.
Damn.
Wait, wait, wait.
Restart the game and it'll be fixed.
It's a known issue.
Oh, are you kidding me?
Okay.
Alright.
I'm gonna restart.
We'll try it again.
I saved that one.
So that one's ready to watch later.
Let me make sure these are actually coming out okay.
Because this would be a disaster if later on I put a giant like 8-minute compilation and they all suck.
They all don't do anything.
No, that's good.
Well, they work.
I'll just put it that way.
Alright, we're good.
I'm gonna restart the game apparently.
Jerma is upset.
No, I just wanna make sure it's not...
It's not like a huge delay.
You know?
That'd be like kind of hard to watch.
Great Canadian Fuck Club 5 community subs.
Thanks a lot, Great Canadian.
Thank you for the five.
I've not been paying much attention to bit...
I really can't.
Streamlabs has turned off for VR.
As you're aware.
Let's reopen it and see if it fixes it.
Get in there.
Get in there!
Okay.
You tell me.
Hey, thanks.
Welcome to Mind Show.
Okay, you ready?
You tell me.
You should be hearing like...
My chat.
It's...
I have no idea why the fuck that's happening.
It's the game audio that's delayed.
I wonder if I should just...
Delay all the audio then.
Let me see what it sounds like.
That's really odd.
Ready?
I'm ready.
I have no words for why that's happening.
Hold on.
Let me try something.
That's like a six second fucking delay.
Alright, hold on.
Ready?
Can I delay this?
Yeah, I'm gonna delay the video and mix the audio.
Jesus.
Why can I...
I can't add a filter on here.
I need to delay.
So if you're hearing it like...
Let me see if this works.
Tell me how this works.
Ready?
I'm sorry.
I...
This is an issue I've never run into before.
Alright, ready?
So it's like...
Let's just say it's like this.
And put the mic delayed too.
So now...
You tell me if this change...
That it's gonna be delayed even worse.
Because now my motions will be delayed but the audio won't.
Ready?
One, two, three.
One.
Nah, it's even worse now.
Why would...
Why would that be happening?
Restarting SteamVR?
Yeah, maybe I'll try that.
This just started happening after you recorded the ghost character.
Okay.
So...
Let me...
Let me try a couple things.
I apologize everybody.
Give me like a couple minutes.
I'm gonna be right back.
Let me like try to get this fixed.
I'm gonna restart SteamVR.
And I mean, of course.
Get another one of these.
Fuck.
Well, this is gonna be a technical troubleshooting stream.
God damn it.
Alright, I'll be right back.
See if I can get this fixed.
Alright, come on.
Don't do it to me.
Don't do this to me.
I've got so much going on right now in the VR.
Fuck.
I'm trying.
The effort is here.
Come on, work.
Get back on camera so we can test it again.
Yeah, um...
I really don't know what to do with my hair.
I was thinking maybe let it grow out a little.
And then maybe you can trim it and change it a little.
Uh, sir.
Sir, this isn't human hair.
Oh, I know.
But I took a little bit of uncooked spaghetti.
And then put it on here.
Can you still do something with it?
Can you still work with it?
That's an old joke.
He said that before.
Welcome to Mind Show.
Shaved your beard?
No.
I'm gonna grow it until it's on the fucking floor.
That was an old joke.
It was.
I know.
Who cares?
This is just what happens.
My appearance is at the bottom of the ladder right now.
Stream functioning is up here.
Appearance?
Who cares?
I don't want this delay to be a fucking thing.
Pubic hair.
Nah, I was gonna give you the finger.
I was thinking about it.
Oh, I was thinking it was supposed to come up.
See?
Oh, I'm trying to keep it.
Just don't do that.
Okay, we're fine.
Uh, you guys are gonna have to help me.
Let's see if I can test it.
All right.
You tell me.
Are we fixed?
Ready?
Click, click, click, click, click, click.
No, it happened.
What the fuck happened?
I don't understand what happened.
You tell me this started after I went into the ghost thing?
I restarted SteamVR.
It's even lighter now.
Shit.
I'm gonna try one more thing and we're just gonna move on.
We're gonna go.
I got to.
I can't just fucking do this all day, you know, guys.
Sorry.
I can't just like do this all fucking day.
God damn it.
Let me try one more thing.
Hold on.
Shit.
Delay all the other audio and yeah, but I tried that before and
you can't queue it up.
Validate the game files for Mind Show.
I was having a lot of fun too.
God damn it.
I don't know what's going on.
Let me reboot again.
That was going somewhere too.
It really was.
Let's reboot VR again.
There it goes.
Let's see what happens.
I have to kill the chat too.
So sorry guys.
I won't be able to see what you're saying for testing purposes.
Welcome to Mind Show.
Last attempt.
Before I have to kind of, I guess just have to deal with it.
Maybe.
Ready?
Is this fixed?
We good?
Yeah, it's fixed.
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Hey, piece of pie.
Good?
I don't fuck.
What the hell was that?
I've been doing this for almost 10 years, right?
And sometimes like shit just don't make no sense.
It doesn't matter how much you try to get ready for something
to prepare and that shit makes no sense.
What happened?
I don't understand.
Fucking computers.
Don't ever buy one.
Just read a newspaper.
Do the crosswords.
Don't buy it.
Oh, I'm shredding off.
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's going on?
I didn't do anything.
I was playing the game and my computer.
Just only do crosswords.
Don't ever fucking buy a computer.
German, do you have any like specs I should buy?
Yeah, it's called fucking a book.
Go read Lord of the Rings.
Don't buy a computer.
All right.
I'm ready.
I can't do OVR drop right now.
I can't do the chat here yet.
We got to move on.
I got to make something and we'll go back to it.
I'm sorry guys.
I can't see the chat anymore.
Maybe that was the problem.
That might have been fucked up.
I don't know because I didn't have it on here.
Fuck.
What a disaster.
It's been like fucking 30 minutes.
Thank you for sticking around.
There was like 4,400, 4,300.
There's still like 4,000 people here almost.
Thanks.
Glad you could sit through this fucking nonsense.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
That wine is so gross.
I mean it just smells the way that tastes.
You know what I mean?
Like what the?
I'm ready.
I can't see you guys reactions.
I don't like this.
I need like reactions, man.
I'm a reaction streamer.
Dude, can you fucking believe what that thing is?
What the fuck?
I got shit in my eye.
God, no, I don't care.
Deal with the pain.
I got stuff in my eye.
I have charcoal in my eye.
I'm ready.
Create show.
Where are you?
I can't see anybody ready for this one.
I got it.
Oh, what?
Oh, I got it.
Check this shit up.
Lab mode is not on.
Don't worry.
Okay.
So who has the mythic key to do this?
We're a mythic plus eight.
So I mean you got to be ready to go.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You see that I'm the guild leader.
So I determine when we open the door.
You're the key holder.
That's what it says on your resume.
On my resume, it's guild leader.
This can be tough.
Shut up.
You don't matter.
Okay.
I love World of Warcraft.
I can't wait to go over there.
So who has the mythic key to do this?
Oh, I do.
I do.
I got the key.
Plus eight.
Yeah, there's a mythic plus eight.
So you got to be ready to go.
I'm ready.
I've been ready since there was extra run trying to me into the guild.
No, no, no, no, no.
You see that I'm the guild leader.
Yeah, I know.
So I determine when we open the door.
But can I open the door?
You're the key holder.
I am the key holder.
That's what it says on your resume.
On my resume, it's guild leader.
But we're called guild leaders.
You don't matter.
Yes, he does.
World of Warcraft.
Okay.
I can't wait to go over there.
So who has the mythic key to do this?
Guys, I got to go.
Plus eight.
My baby's going to be born in 45 minutes.
I've got to get out of here.
I've been ready since there was extra run trying to me into the guild.
No, no, no, no, no.
You see that I'm the guild leader.
Yeah, I know.
So I determine when we open the door.
But can I open the door after that?
You're the key holder.
Just open the fucking door.
I've got...
My baby's going to be born in 45 minutes.
Are you listening to me?
It's fucking raw.
Do you understand?
You don't matter.
Yes, I do.
Yes, he does.
Oh shit, I'm stepping.
I'm falling down.
World of Warcraft.
Okay.
I can't wait to go over there.
So who has the mythic key to do this?
Guys, I got to go.
Plus eight.
Yeah, it's the mythic part.
My baby's going to be born in 45 minutes.
I've been ready since there was extra run trying to me into the guild.
No, no, no, no, no.
You see that I'm the guild leader.
Yeah, I know.
So I determine when we open the door.
But can I open the door after that?
You're the key holder.
Just open the door.
My baby says I'm your resident.
My baby's going to be born in 45 minutes.
Are you listening to me?
Well, where Kogu is fucking raw.
Do you understand?
You don't matter.
Yes, he does.
We're going to start over.
That was...
That was not even worth saving.
Okay.
Okay, Mind Show news.
Crisis zone.
Is it weather?
Weather report.
Okay.
Let's get a crisis report.
Let's go over here.
All right.
Okay.
Get you closer.
Right here.
No, back here.
Get...
Will you get back here?
Jesus.
What are you doing?
Okay.
Hello and welcome everybody to VR news.
I'm LD and welcome to the show.
First up on the news.
The se...
Hello!
Good again.
Welcome everybody.
Now that was bad.
That was too good.
Hello and welcome to VR news.
I'm LD and here is the top stories today.
Today, two more tech demos came out for VR and nobody fucking uses it.
Not one AAA developer has made anything for this platform.
So we're left to make our own fucking movies in this kind of little fun little show game.
That's bad too.
Welcome to VR news.
I'm LD.
I don't want to hear that one again.
Hey everybody.
Welcome to the show here.
As you can tell, we're on IGN.com.
No, don't do that.
That's bad too.
Don't fucking say that.
Don't do that one.
I mean, I was going to do a thing where it's like playing on the GameStop TVs.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not doing that.
Terrible winds have hit the coast of Las Vegas as we will hear from our weather report here from Dave the Dragon.
Dave the Dragon, how's the weather looking over there?
Well, you see, if you can take a look over here, this is the moon.
This is not even Las Vegas, but the sun is going to come crashing down.
I mean, you're mentioning winds, but you're not mentioning the fact that Las Vegas is going to be wiped out by the meteor.
I bumped my hand on the table.
No, table, but that's the thing about the interdimensional fucking shit.
Oh my God.
This is bad.
I like, okay, let me tell you something.
I like lost my mojo spending 40 minutes troubleshooting the stream.
We were on fire too.
I can't even, whatever.
Here we go.
Ready for this one?
Fucking VR trouble.
I'll give you VR troubleshooting.
You want to hear this shit?
Hit the coast of Las Vegas.
No, no, no, no.
Delete the whole thing.
I got a better fucking idea for you.
All right, we're good.
Ready?
Here we go.
Hi, welcome to the news, the dragon news.
I'm Dragon Team Buford and today our top story is one that you're going to want to listen to.
First of all, World of Warcraft has been cancelled.
That's right.
Their subscriber numbers have dropped so much that they can't even keep anybody around.
They got WoW Classic coming up, but nobody's going to play that because WoW Classic wasn't even very fun.
Everybody thinks that it was fun, but we're going to...
No, you know what it is?
It's the fucking time limit.
Go back and...
I got to do the lab shit.
Get me out of here.
I'm like up against like a 20 second clock.
Get the...
There.
Now I don't have to worry about like a 10 second time limit.
This one will be good.
I've like lost it.
Oh my comedy is gone.
I got nothing funny left in my body.
Check this, it's even worse.
Dragon over here.
It's 45 minutes.
What happened?
Zoom in on that with my brain.
Sorry, it's sinking.
Let me...
Move that over here.
Oh, what's your problem?
Let me...
Google.com
www.google.
What is it?
Oh, I'm having a problem with my sinking issue if I straight...
I like it.
Alright, alright, alright.
I want a good clean five from you two.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
But don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm just the judge.
I'm the judge.
Oh, that looked like it hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
Okay, you know, he's fine.
He's fine.
Are you ready?
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Nice.
Get it on, gentlemen.
Alright, that's it.
He's dead.
Yeah, I want a good clean five from you two.
Yeah, you will.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Fuck you, man.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Come on, let's go.
Don't hurt me.
I'm the judge.
Look, that looked like it hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
Okay, you know, he's fine.
He's fine.
Are you ready?
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Let's go.
Come on, man.
Fuck, man.
Nice.
You bet.
Stop doing that.
Get it on, gentlemen.
You did it once already.
Alright, that's it.
No, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm not ready.
Alright, alright, alright.
I want a good clean five from you two.
I'm not ready for this at all.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
I'm not ready.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm the judge.
No, no, no, no.
Let's go back.
I gotta be closer.
Hello?
Okay.
Let's get in.
Alright, that's close enough.
Right, I think.
Alright, right, right.
I want a good clean five from you two.
Yeah, you will.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Get me.
Don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm the judge.
Look, I can hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Give me that.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Let's go.
Come on, man.
Stop doing that.
Get off me.
I'm the best fruit in business.
Ow, dad.
This is awful.
Alright, right, right.
I want a good clean five from you two.
Yeah, you will.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Get me.
Don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm just the judge.
I'm the judge.
Look, I can hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Dad, you know, he's fine.
He's fine.
Give me that.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Get off me.
Stop doing that.
I'm the best fruit in business.
Alright, let's get it on.
That was dog shit.
That was so bad.
That was worse than anything.
I've never made a piece of media that was that bad.
I don't think ever.
I'm going to puke.
Oh, I just like hurt my back.
Oh, that hurt me so bad.
That's 4,000 fucking people just watched like the worst thing
I've ever fucking made.
I almost threw up on straight.
That would have been banned.
I would have seen you guys in like fucking four days.
You really want me to film this one?
Why are we in the?
Where are we?
Why are we out in the open?
There's no reason for this.
It's not even a ring.
It's just like a pasture.
That really did hurt so bad.
I like rib cage.
I like pulled my ribs.
Can you do that?
I didn't think it was even possible to pull your ribs, but I did.
Jesus fucking Christ.
This hurts.
God damn it.
Alright, alright, alright.
I want a good clean five from you too.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Ready.
I'm ready.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Oh fuck.
Don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm just gonna jump.
I'm the judge.
We're gonna get some fucking crazy angles here.
Ready for this shit?
They're even like taking five.
Watch this.
Like it hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
I'll fuck you.
No, he's fine.
He's fine.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Stop doing that.
Alright, alright, alright.
I want a good clean five from you too.
Yeah, you will.
Thousands watching at home.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Yes.
Don't touch me.
Don't hurt me.
I'm just gonna jump.
I'm the judge.
Looks like it hurt.
Are you okay?
Can you still go on?
Are you sure?
I'll fuck you.
You know, he's fine.
He's fine.
Give me that.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's get it on, gentlemen.
Stop.
Fell asleep.
Stop doing that.
Are you ready?
Alright.
I don't even want to fucking see it.
Oh my fucking God.
I don't even want to look at it.
I thought I'd let it render.
What's going on here?
I'm embarrassed for you.
You should be.
I'm embarrassed for me and it's me.
Tweet this?
No.
No way.
Not in a fucking million years.
Do it or no balls.
You want me to tweet this video?
Okay, fine.
Fuck it.
I can't.
I've got to like connect my Twitter to this app.
I don't.
I got to like link.
I don't even have my Twitter password.
I don't even know my password.
What if I videotape it and film it?
No, it's not going to work.
I have no idea.
I'll do it later.
I will upload this video with no context, no message, nothing.
Guys, okay.
Let me tell you something.
I haven't tweeted since February.
Okay?
Do you really think I give a shit about my Twitter account?
I haven't done a real tweet since like February 13th.
This is fine to me.
I'll do it.
I will.
I promise.
I did a tweet three hours ago.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a difference between tweeting out your stream and
making like an actual tweet.
All right.
Let's get a good one here.
I want something elaborate.
Let's do like a dinner.
Are we still good?
Let me give you guys some of these.
Let me give you guys something to work with here.
Ready?
Oh, it's me, Jerma, by the way.
That's an alien.
Isn't that funny?
No, please.
Please don't do it.
Don't hurt me.
I'll do anything.
Please don't do it.
Don't please don't hurt me.
I'm real.
Okay, I'm real.
That's all you get.
That's it.
What is back there?
What the fuck is that?
Iwhat is back there?
I don'tget that out.
I'm gonna get that out of here.
It's me, Jerma, by the way.
That's an alien.
Isn't that funny?
No, please.
Please don't do it.
Don't hurt me.
I'll do anything.
Please don't do it.
Don't please don't hurt me.
I'm real.
Okay?
good luck ever using that for fucking any reason I don't think there's any reason to use any of
this never mind what is that okay give me a table with some chairs stools isn't really all they
got I think it's got a decent scene going here okay kind of scary but that's fine all right
get some actors here and one two three there's dad one two three four that's fine please oh my
god what's the point of even having these they get they're not gonna sit on them blessed our
Lord for these thy gifts that we are about to receive from thy bounty to Christ our Lord
give us this day our daily bread as we forgive those that trespass us and we forgive those
that trespass against us lead us not into temptation but deliver us from evil amen
yeah well I got an A- in my math class and the teacher told me to come after school to run
the the the national play so I've been doing very well a plus exactly blessed our Lord for
these side gifts from thy bounty from our Lord a man give us this day our daily bread as we
forget those who trespass against us and we forget those who trespass against us lead
us not into temptation but deliver us from evil amen amen oh me oh me I have some news I have
news well I went to a field trip today and the teacher called on me and said
I had the best answer out of all of them I talked about how the cows get milked three
times a day and Johnny said to bless it blessed our Lord amen
and the teacher told me to come after school
I went to a field trip today and the teacher called on me and said I had the best answer
say your goddamn prayer
oh my god nice job kids so what's telling about their day who wants to tell me what they
did today you you you get to speak
good good you go I went to a field trip today and the teacher called on me that's my boy
what did you do
I went to a field trip today and the teacher called on me and said I had the best answer
out of all of them I talked about how the cows get milked three times a day and the
teacher called on me and said I had the best answer out of all of them I talked about
how the cows get milked three times a day and the teacher called on me that's my
boy
can I have somebody play the piano never mind it's a huge desync again I'm gonna
render this and we'll try it again I restarted steam VR before let me render this let
me get the right camera angles that I want it's hard to really make like a full thing
in a minute you know I mean like you got I get there's a lot I want to condense what
I'm gonna have to do so the next thing I'm gonna do is one minute per scene and we're
gonna have to watch them all back-to-back I wish I could extend that timer I feel
like I could do way more all right so let's get the camera here okay let's
open this up here right here
I got it nice job kids so who wants to tell me about their day who wants to tell me what
they did today
I went to a field trip today and the teacher called on me and said that I had the best
time fuck I need a part two
I don't know what to do I don't know what to do I don't know what to do I don't know
what to do I don't know what to do I don't know what to do I don't know what to do
all right what did you do is the last thing we're gonna wait for that to render
what did you do now it's time for time for to speak desync whatever yeah
export a video well let me get this done that's so sad so every single time
I export a video the desync gets exponentially worse just stop exporting
videos apparently oh well still fun can I export all of them at the end I don't
think so this is called mind show untitled 3 so look I gotta get one more
one minute we're gonna get the broccoli's answer and we'll go on I'm
not sure if saving them is it and then doing it off stream is a good
idea because it seems like it seems like you only get this one instance
of the scene am I correct on that just watch yeah that's true I could just watch
it but that we had a problem with that before too
remember I tried to play the last one you just wouldn't play it was skipping
all over the place all right I'm gonna fit it we're gonna do part two I'm
gonna finish this up dad's gonna see how fast they can eat and that
determines where the favorite child is is it's storming that's in the game
that's not outside here no it's not storming yeah where's the jazz this
feels really out of place all right the next thing I'm gonna do is singing I'm
gonna try to sing like six or seven people any particular songs if you'd
like to hear we're gonna do harmony acapella September you know let's
I got idea let's have them sing okay so he comes over here so that's saved so
now he's over here so he goes you so that's her turn I wish I could just
pick off right where I left off I can't go away the end here there's some
things I would change in this app all right I think I have to make a whole new
scene because this is just let me get to the end see if I can add really
no that can't be fucking for real I can't just like keep this scene but
add I'm just gonna do a new scene and just put everybody back in here don't
like or delete the other characters that's true let's delete them
okay dear god he was over here right okay all right here we go
I G A B C A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R M T U V W A Y and Z
now I know my bcs next time won't you sing with me
next time won't you sing with me right these props are fucking stupid just get rid of them
don't add anything they just gave the fucking way
what did you do let's hear it come on F G H I come on all of you now T U V W A Y
and Z now I know good ABC's next time won't you sing with me yes do that at
church tomorrow I'm serious
I don't know this app sometimes makes no sense why is it spinning my hands in a circle why like
what let's get some more characters in here you have to this character right what are you
doing ah let's do it yeah I wish I had any idea what the fuck was going on okay what did you
come on Q R T U V Y and Z now I have to go to the bathroom I'll be back I have to go to the
next time you're food I don't know what happened to you food seriously me yeah I'll come to
church to the church tomorrow a dad your spaghetti was it actually spaghetti who was
it glass because my stomach's fucking tearing apart I'm sorry for swearing
Q R T U V Y now I know my next time
come on F G H I come on Q R T U V Y and Z now I know my next time won't you sing with me
I have dreams about that kind of shit just wait till it's put together with editing I gotta go
back I gotta get in there and edit hold on my entire legacy is I got that I laughed I
gotta fucking fix this shit what did you do
yes we're all gonna go to church I don't know I feel that too I'm sorry for you
this is all fucking why is it like this
yeah of the 1400 people that unfollowed tonight I hope to see you soon hope to see
you back when we do something else tomorrow Jesus Christ I'm living in a goddamn dream
right now you understand here we go I'm who cares let's get it done for fuck's sake
what the fuck is this family I'm serious
all right that's it I'm done that's enough what are you doing what are you doing what are
you doing what nothing works I can't press anybody no no why fuck nothing does anything
can I not even save all the dumb dog shit that I just did for 30 40 straight minutes give me
a break dad is mad I want to love this game I really do I really do I want to love this
game but there's been like a dickload of technical fucking problems that just kind of
what the fuck this game is so good what the fuck try teleporting off the table I can't go
anywhere nowhere is safe damn it really I don't want to delete anything I want to save it hello
what the fuck just happened what next game damn it really ah the game is so good that's such
a fun game I don't know what the fuck happened there we're gonna play we're gonna move on fuck
come on we got videos to watch it's half of them I don't know if they saved or not but
damn it that's so that that was so stupid that took so long that was such a terrible joke I
needed to see it play out it's probably the labs mode yeah it's probably a shit oh well well
what's there is really really really fucking fun I think we're just using the experimental
mode too much but unfortunately we're gonna have to move on let's watch the videos we made
listen to VR Josh what did we are just saying look into the beta build called mind show unleashed
it might be more stable oh you know I'll give it a mind show unleashed is the beta more stable
that does not sound more stable the beta had a fix for that we'll come back to it how does
that sound who knows okay well what is there is a fantastic fun little movie maker just some
unfortunate technical issues can plague ABC you know it's probably a good thing let's be real
that's probably a good thing that that happened because I was all over the place we lost like
450 viewers so we're gonna move on I'd like I wanted to see that come to fruition though
we're gonna move on to what do I got disassembly VR elvin assassin jet island those are the three
choices right now I'll give you a vote why not right but that was mind show for what you know
that was a lot of fun I'll be fair for the weird technical issues and we'll watch them when
I come back I'm gonna grab one more drink and we'll move on from here when I get back we'll
watch them there's like three things to watch I think and I will give you a vote for the next
string or I mean next thing we're gonna do tonight so we got elvin assassin disassembly
disassembly the fuck do you spell that jet island so then we need to finish eventually
right and gorn hey go vote there you go see you guys in a few minutes now that it was
wouldn't even fucking link I'll be right back see you in a second oh my god we have to do
what the fuck is that guide get that out of here elvin assassin is the name of the
title of the poll okay I fucked it up wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on how
did I make because I fucking know stupid elvin assassin jet island damn it Jeremy
disassembly and corn okay sorry about that go for it again I'll give you 30 seconds all right
what we got elvin assassin disassembly it looks like this simply ten more seconds that's it it's
close close mmm two votes separated damn come on that's it oh elvin assassin 200 votes close
oh we woke up the lurkers woke up the lurkers elvin assassin three two one that's it elvin
assassin that's it thank you for voting that's the end of the poll sorry that we had to get
rid of mine show had some issues with it sorry it was a lot of fun it really was I actually
had a blast with that game what was available was really really cool so let's do elvin
assassin hey look there I am oh the videos right okay let's watch them might as well
see the fruits of our labor right let's go movie night to tweet the fight I promise
I will tweet the fight later all right we got mine show all right this is what is this one I
don't know okay well that one sure did work didn't it hold on what here it is you ready I
hold on here we go wait wait start over three two one
you you got 3.6 on
all right there's that one great what's this one three two one action
besides the money which is great we had an entire zoo in our bathroom well over the years
one would say that sharing a bed with a giraffe not so great after a while we grow
distant him and I the last time I sculpted him July of 2006 and here's what he killed
what is I don't know what this one is is another one three two one action wait wait wait play it
again all right I want a good clean fight from you too yeah you will thousands watching at home
are you ready yeah you ready I'm ready let's get it on Joe yeah don't touch me don't hurt me
I'm just a judge I'm the judge oh that would make it hurt yeah look like it hurt are you
okay can you still go on are you sure I'm fine yeah are you ready yeah you ready let's
I don't have any words for that one three two one what okay never mind three two one
action what okay that didn't capture didn't capture okay here's the last one
nice job kids so what's telling about their day who wants to tell me what they did today
and the teacher told me to come after school to run the the the national play
I I I went to a field trip today teacher called on me and said that I had the best
answer of all that's how the cows get milked I wish you got part two was so much better
hey be see the Resident Evil 7 the Resident Evil 7 why couldn't we have got the second
part unfortunately it's still saved hold on if I could I mean that thing was absolutely
terrible can I export that out can I welcome to the family son yes I can I can welcome
are you sure because that what that took a lot of stupid shit work okay my shows replay
how do I like load one test veggie party people game screen I don't think it's
available mm-hmm take a look ready like where is it my shows is just this right there's
nothing here there's no there's nothing there we've got games my shows there's
nothing here unfortunately stream abducted doctors dear wait hold on Sam wait a minute
hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait untitled untitled listen this
is my stream hold on no it's not here where would it be people my shares no it's not
here turn the labs on my shows remix no spring no sort by new no nah this is it it's gone
forever let's open up Elvin assassin that's shits gone probably for the best