Hey, I've never seen anything like this before. Are you kidding me? That's how far that goes.
I'm fairly certain. Okay, throw throw a shuriken as far as you possibly can in the air. I'm pretty sure I can throw a rock father than that.
Yeah, it drops off. That's real quick. Oh, I threw it like 10 yards. Oh my god. That's the whole team. Oh my god.
Oh my god, the same time too. Your arms are just really sore. It's okay. Yeah, I haven't paid attention. Is there only one banner that anybody can grab? Is it like in the middle and then we have to take it to our own? Yeah, it's like a giant. That's more fun than capture the flag to me.
It's a giant like World of Warcraft staff. Yeah. Hey, don't don't mock my faction. Good. I can't describe fucking wrong owner again. German. Stop it. German. I'm a knight. Give me that staff. Give me that epic staff.
Plus five to dying because it makes you a giant target. I don't know really. Stupid knight. I just stabbed him in the eye with a shuriken because he sat there and did his battle cry. That guy just dropped a bomb down here. He's doing it again.
That is just like watched it happen. Your teammate just killed you. I was sitting there watching it. I wanted it looked like a firework. I'm just pulling this thing. But how far do you have to pull it back? You just hold as far as you need to. Actually, I think the boulder appears once you've reached the threshold.
Okay. Sorry about that. I thought that was in the game. They're coming to play the game. It's a fucking emergency. I seriously thought that was an ambulance in this game. I was like, why is this in the game? I can respect their culture and also tell you to get the fuck away from if you try to kill me.
This guy's AFK. What did you think was going to happen? You're sitting there AFK, dude. Did you see what I did to him? You chopped his leg off or something. Is this you with the fist right now? Yes, I'm punching you with fist of fury, ninja buddy.
Come on, fight me with your fist. Come on, be a man. How do I do it? How do I throw my thing down? Fist me. I don't think I can do that. Fight me. You guys are hitting each other. Come on. I'm going to make you guys kill each other. So what do we do with the banner? Oh shit. How am I still alive?
There we go. That took forever. I can't even make this on a gamepad. You're telling me I can't make this on a gamepad and I can't change any settings? What is this song? I've heard this song before.
That's supposed to be an old man. Who squeezed this guy's nuts? That guy seriously just sounded like somebody was pinching his testicles between two pieces of bread. I don't even think I'm going to make a video on this. This is just not even fun. It's not even funny. It just sucks.
Oh, I magically have a weapon all of a sudden. Just poke them. Poke them to death with your tiny little swords. I told this guy's girlfriend she was fat or something and he's freaking out of the bar punching me. You had far too many Guinnesses, bro. You're not going to hit me for shit.
Everything is going to shit. No, we don't. Maybe you need some better teammates. Of course I do. That's what I've been fucking complaining about this entire time. You're going to have to trade your friends for better teammates.
I can't. This guy's is taken. Here we go. I am leaving. You go to our spawn with it. Holy shit. I thought there was auto balance. This game is broken. Mr. Garrison got the first blood too. Mr. Garrison. I just got switched too. This is great. I think it's like I think it's auto balancing people.
Mr. Garrison's the giant. See the red team. All one of them. All three, four. There Mr. Garrison lies. Oh, man. He's actually killing people. What's this guy doing? What the hell is this guy doing? Get out of here, man. What are you, friendly fire killing people?
Mr. Garrison's living. That guy was just attacking me. He was swinging at me like I was an enemy and I shot him in the throat. All sham no wow was my nemesis and my easy target. How does that make any sense? Oh, this guy was destroying you the entire time, but he's working easy to kill. No, no, you get 10.
Ah, okay. Ah, where'd that come from? It's really not a lot of arrows, right? Oh, hey. No, not really. Goop. Goop. Stop it. Hey, hey, dude. Hey, look, you're down there. This arrow is just in his ear. Pretty sure that would probably kill someone. How many times do you have to shoot somebody in the fucking face before they die? This guy's got two arrows in his face.