The story you'll hear is heartwarming and charming, although some of you may find it alarming.
On a napkin I write some ink and a nail. I'm writing, of course, from the old county jail.
Those fuckers got me, as you can plainly see. What do I do now, besides take a pee?
Arrested for much I'm about to explain. Sit back and relax while my words entertain.
Our story unfolds on a cold Christmas Eve, a two pairs of socks night, if you could believe.
The TV was loud and just how I like it. Fodded 30 times, trust me, I counted.
What a glorious night, not a care in the world. Nothing could ruin this holiday, this great...
I'm having a really good time. Really, I can't think of what rhymes with world for this current situation.
So it was just fun. Sipping my tea and eating my crackers, an annoying voice came up through the rafters.
It's Christmas Eve, Grandpa. This is not good. There are no gifts from you underneath that hood.
Of that beautiful tree that we spent so much time making. I'm not messing around and I am not faking.
Get your ass out of that chair and into the snow or Christmas is ruined. Hurry up and go.
Jerma sucks. That's all that needs to be said. I really wish he would permanently go to bed.
Standing up from my wonderful man station. God damn it, my procrastination. Stores were all closed.
Nothing was open. This new found bad news, I was having trouble coping. I had to think fast.
There was just no more time. I was all out of options. So it came to a crime.
The night came quick and I acted with swiftness. For there's only so much you can steal on Christmas.
Out through the door there was no looking back. It was time to rip off a neighborhood ass crack.
Down the street I trotted on my imaginary horse. The hallucinatic drugs I took were running their course.
Through my body and blood it made things all hazy. This house looks good. But was I going crazy?
There was nobody home, not a light in the house. I got off my steed and creeped close like a mouse.
Dressed all in black from my head to my toe, I smashed through the front window with a perfect
brick throw. Climbing through the clearing I slithered like a snake. No one's home though.
I could have been a fucking earthquake. Once inside I went right for the jewelry.
Because that's the most expensive. There is no tomfoolery. On my way out I left an IOU.
If I ever would pay it. Not sure if that would be true. Into the brisk wind from which I first came,
a cruiser was waiting. They were ready to tame. This old man can still run, I shouted and screamed.
A sharp pain I felt shooting into my spleen. I was feeling the wrath of over 5,000 volts.
My body struck down like a lightning bolt. A taser, really? I'm an old man for Christ's sake.
Every single inch of my body did ache. Into the back of the cruiser we rolled through the night.
I heard them joke and giggle about my pathetic attempts to fight. I don't blame them though.
It was really dumb. Would I take it all back? Was I feeling numb? Do I plead insanity?
Shit myself in the backseat? Punch myself in the face and blame it on Wall Street?
No. I think not. I'll do my time. I've made the mistakes put forth in this rhyme.
Sitting in this cell with much time to think. Not being with the people I love really does stink.
So remember this tale this holiday season. Don't do dumb shit. For absolutely no reason.
Happy holidays everyone.