Mummy vs Kruger. Are you ready to get thrown into the flames of Kruger?
Do you even know a single button to this game? I don't want to do strategy games because people will expect some level of skill.
Just hold on a second. We need to make sure we...hold on. I gotta get my buttons in check.
So before we get started, we need to do a button check. So okay, button check. That's that. That's that. Okay. Button check. I'm just button checking.
I'm okay with this.
Alright, button check is still going on. Alright, my button check's good. Good, play.
You wanna mess with the Kruger?
You wanna mess with Freddy Kruger? You wanna mess with me? You ready to go?
I wasn't expecting this, to be honest with you.
It's cause Freddy Kruger is like broken. What the hell are you doing? You're like sucking out my soul.
You wanna play this game?
Oh, how do you do like the X-Factor? How do I like sing on UK television? The X-Factor.
I don't care.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck. Get crushed.
This game is brutal. Are you not gonna do anything?
I did it wrong. I did it wrong.
Dude, that was horrible. You just jumped up and like you broke my neck and then you shattered my spine.
You know who I honestly thought would have, Jerma would have picked immediately?
Who?
Look at his face.
But that's Baraka though. Baraka is like Baraka.
Barack Obama is like, we talk about him all the time.
I don't wanna play as Barack Obama. I wanna play as the God of War Kratos.
Okay.
Either God of War Kratos or like this beady-eyed motherfucker.
Because this is Mortal Kombat. This is the storyline.
Oh, actually no, I have seen this. This is where Stryker is, right?
Uh, Kill Cool, we were playing. We were like actually playing and not like looking at something.
Oh my fucking God.
Are you gonna seriously just combo the shit out of me while we're like looking at like stuff in the background?
Yeah. Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
Alright, if that's how it's gonna be.
Can you get it by the car?
There's stage specific fatalities.
Oh, cool.
If you flawless me right now, this control is going through the fucking wall.
Well, that's some motivation.
You seriously cannot flawless me right now. Do anything, desperation.
No.
Yes.
Oh, with this. With this. I spam it in my own face.
It would just break your neck. Oh, yeah, sure. Okay.
Cyrax.
Oh, teleportation.
I'm a robot.
Where is Star? Star is going to be exterminated.
I am the robot character. Star will be exterminated.
Are you a Dalek?
Star will be exterminated.
Oh, it's water. It's water.
Get her off me.
It's water. Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
That went on for way too long.
Alright, what's the funny thing you wanted to show me?
The water is what I wanted to show you.
Oh, that was the funny thing? Oh, okay.
That's pretty funny.
If you kill me with the water, I...
Here comes the water.
Alright, here we go. John Cena versus the mummy again.
Here it comes. Here comes the paint.
You know, this is like a title of a pretty good movie.
John Cena versus the mummy.
Coming soon to Disney DVD.
Yeah, coming soon.
Wait, let me guess what Jerm is going to do. Is he going to jump and press buttons?
Coming soon to Disney DVD.
John Cena versus the mummy.
Okay, now you're playing the character you know how to play.
That's cheating.
Oh, he has a gun?
Oh, it's okay. I'll just shoot you.
I'll give you a chance to kind of do it again.
Oh, yeah? Oh, the flashlight!
You just shined a flashlight on me!
Again?
Oh, man!
Haven't I had enough?
And now I shoot you.
That flashlight was sick.
I'm going to defeat the mortal human being.
Ooh!
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's going to combo the absolute hell out of me.
Ooh, surprise!
Yes! Yes!
I was blocking the bullets.
That doesn't make any sense.
Hey, did you know
that noob cyborgs
backwards is Boon Tobias,
the guy that made the game?
Isn't that good?
That's a good technological
information. Yeah.
Ow. What?
You noobed me.
Yeah. Right hook, left hook, left hook.
Yeah. Turn it for the box and turn it.
This is the turn that I'm going to be practicing for.
Yeah. Get the fuck out of it.
Fuck you, motherfucker. Get the fuck. Fuck you, motherfucker.
Yes! No!
God damn it! That was the whole plan the whole time
and it didn't even fucking work.
Yeah, yeah.
Go ahead and get fucking X-Facted.
What? I was hitting you. You have hit
damn. Ow.
Dude, some of these are so... This is a
1v1 game.
Oh, he's puking. He's puking.
Noob Subbot's my favorite character because he makes people puke.
Confirmed favorite character
in the game. Because people throw up
when they get kicked in the balls.
No, okay. This is tied up.
I'm going to stop messing around here and do some
moves. Whoa!
What? What's going on?
Okay, well the game decided you don't want to have a video.
What? No videos.
The game desynchronized?