Is this game out yet? Is the game released yet? 430? No? Shit.
Where the fuck did this game come out? Real voice? What? What's wrong?
Maybe in 30 minutes? Alright, well what? Okay, so fuck.
Hey, first of all, hello. Hi everybody. How you doing? Good to see you again.
Today, plan is we're going to play Monster Rancher 2.
Trying to hold my excitement. This is one of my favorite games ever.
Fart on the mic. You got it. Why do so many people want streamers to fart in mics?
Is it funny? Oh, I saw a clip. I've completely forgot it. But let's talk about this real quick.
I completely forgot that. So during the dollhouse stream, there was a lot going on.
There was a lot of stuff that we recorded, right? Like the costume selection stuff, right? That was
all pre-recorded. And then there was stuff going on on the set. And my mind was not like watching
the stream and I completely forgot. And it took until I like, I like reminded of this like weird
thing where I spun around in the middle of the costume change scene and like do this like fake
spin fart loud into the microphone thing with my mouth. And I had a reaction to that like a few
months ago. Then I forgot about it. And I saw it like a few days ago. And I was like, I why is that
in the why is it here? I like didn't want that in the video. What is just there? I didn't want
that in the stream. But anyways, who cares? Let us see your face. I know I told you I'm sitting here
waiting for the release of Monster Rancher. And I'm gonna play Monster Rancher 2. And by the way,
who cares? I do. It was my fart for all the new germamites that are in attendance right now.
I played this game before. This is a re-release of the old PlayStation 1 games.
I can't I'm so excited. I can't wait to play. We be prepared to be more emotionally invested
in this than anything else you've ever done in your life with the microphone. No emotion for an
hour. I feel like I'm sitting in the line at Best Buy waiting for the new iPhone. I just want to
play. All right, hold on. Do I just do no emotion until the game comes out? Why did this turn into
like a weird like protest stream? I'm not I'm not like protesting the game. I know I'm I'm just
waiting for the game to come out. Turn on the cam and smoke cigarettes. I don't want to talk about
too much about the game because I want you to be surprised by how fun it is. Apparently the port's
pretty good too from what I've heard. It's almost 3am. Yeah, what time is it? When is it? Okay,
when is the next region midnight? Does anybody know? Like where is it 11.35 right now?
If you look at your clock and if it's 11.35 p.m. tell me where you are. What region? Ireland,
it's 12.35. Okay, so what is this? What is this release? It's 1am. 11.35 where? Oh, it's 11.35am.
That's not right. No, I'm talking general region. Region. It's 11.35am in Australia. I'm looking for
regions. It's not even out yet. I know. So look just fucking okay whatever. Ask ask me ask me
whatever you want. Okay, I'm fine. I'm sitting here till it comes out. Whole Europe is after zero zero.
You look unhealthy. Somebody said that. I did. I can I can I can stall as long as I want. Don't
you believe in time zones? I do believe in time. You know okay you're asking the guy if he believes
in time zones. The guy that has to respond to the EU viewers that yell at him because I stream too
late. You're talking to that guy. You don't think I know time zones? Seriously, what is this time?
I don't know. I'm waiting for Monster Rancher to come out. It probably doesn't even come out.
It's probably like an error on Steam that the game comes out like today. It says on Steam that the
game releases in less than an hour and that was an hour ago. That was at like that was at four o'clock.
What's your skincare routine? My eyes! You look you look greasy. Thanks. Oh you guys. Hey I'll
show you something interesting. I'll show you something interesting. Okay so this is my I had
to do this today. I had to put on a t-shirt. I had to put a shirt on today. Your tags are inaccurate.
What do you mean? No pants. Well no I do have pants on but this this is like the I'm in a zoom
call professional Andy. Just make sure uh just make sure you don't stand up so they see your
Darth Vader pajama pants. Look at this. Oh look. What's up guys? Yeah v-neck. I got a I got a cool
v-neck on. Don't stand up otherwise they'll know. You have one of the three shirts you own. I need
to go close. I look can I can let I have to talk about this. Listen to me. I need to know if anybody
else relates to this. So I have I have I don't like okay I own a shit load of really nice clothes
that I've purchased. I bought a bunch of clothing. I went to a bunch of nice places. Bought a bunch of
nice like tees. Really nice like button-up shirts and shit right. They are all wrinkled to fucking
hell in the closet. I have not worn them once because I don't want to mess them up. I don't
want to ruin them. I always feel like if I put my nice clothes on I have a bunch of it that I I will
somehow like sweat through it or drop mustard on it or something. I never want to wear those clothes.
I don't know why and they they seriously look like they look like they're in a vacuum sealed
bag because of how fucked up and scrunched and wrinkled they are. I don't think any dry
cleaning would work. I think I literally have to get new clothes because they're so wrinkled up.
This is not going to happen. I tried to iron one of them once and all it did was make make like
a bunch of lines and it was bad. In the pre-stream you promised Mario Golf. I was shit faced when I
promised Mario Golf like six months ago. So sorry. What'd you say? Don't eat mustard then. How often
are you eating mustard? Are you wearing really nice clothes to a ball game? No I don't know. I
always just feel like okay I feel like I sweat a lot and like I'm gonna get those like orange stains
under the nice clothes. What causes those orange stains by the way? It doesn't happen to me but if
it did what is why does that happen? Game out yet? I'm in the wrong category too. Yeah I gotta move
to like just chatting for like 20 minutes or wait is it is it technically a Monster Rancher 2 stream
if I'm talking about how pumped and hyped I am for Monster Rancher 2? You look red. I know
I'm very flustered. Why is you sweat orange? No it's after when it dries. It's aluminum.
It's an allergic reaction huh. Derma you still owe me four million dollars for stealing and
crashing my jetpack. Jetpacks aren't real. Why do you look so nice today? Who did you kill for the
youth today? I shaved. So I killed the millions of tiny little hairs that were on my face I'd say.
You look 15 years young. Guess I shaved my face. This is a fresh shave. How come you're de-aging?
I'm not de-aging. I'm this is just what my face looks like after I shave. I could use a haircut
too. Your face looks red. I know because my white balance is wrong and it's like I'm a little warm.
My white balance is screwed up. This wall this wall is not like green okay. It's it's like white.
It's kind of like a off-white. This chat's going too fast. What's on the reddit shelf?
Uh on the reddit shelf we have I've kind of been doing a little collection here so I'll move this
way. Uh every major stream people have maybe been paying attention to this but every major stream a
prop like a little piece of it goes up there and eventually I wanted to get to the point where
all those Funko pops get removed. I'm gonna start replacing the Funko pops with like one little prop
from a major stream. So hopefully over the next year or two that shelf is fucking overflowing.
It's like it's a nice I don't know it's a nice little reminder like walk in and be like oh yeah
that one that one that was fun that was fun that was fun that was fun.
The geodes there yeah most of them all the major streams the big event streams are up there with
the exception of maybe maybe I don't know maybe one. He's holding on to the past. No I would be
holding on to the past if this was like 30 years from now and I come in and I pick up the 985 plaque
and I'm like oh I remember when I did that oh it's it happened like six months ago. Remember when
what was your favorite stream? I don't have a favorite. Game out yet? No. You need to get the
Deathwing Funko pop. Why would I do that? I don't give a shit about that game. I don't care at all
about Deathwing. Why would I ever get the Deathwing Funko pop? I haven't played World of Warcraft
since I swore off of it like six years ago when you watched the Meltdown stream. What did you say?
Do a cool camera effect. No I we have 15 minutes before I can I hope it unlocks. Okay this is like
me waiting for the iPhone at Best Buy except Best Buy didn't tell me didn't say anything about
what time the iPhone was coming out. I'm just here. Excuse me sir we never we didn't like tell
you that like the game was the the iPhone was going to be out today. Yeah I'm just here I'm
gonna wait for it. What if it's like three weeks from now? Yeah that's that's fine I'll just like
I'll just hang out. Well how do you like McDonald's? I love McDonald's. Remember how's TikTok treating
you? You tell me. What's my favorite bug? Praying mantis probably. Yeah we're doing the game awards
tomorrow. Absolutely. That's also at 4 30. Hopefully that actually starts at 4 30. Do I have any
vinyls? No I don't have any vinyls. And what hold on what's what's going on here? I need to make
sure something here. Should I just switch to just chatting like I'm just sitting here? I'm not going
to sit in the wrong category for like fucking an hour. Don't no more swearing either. Just chatting
return to the farm. Whatever that means. I swear to god if I change category and it comes out in
two minutes I'm gonna be mad. Now all right if it doesn't come out at five then I will just leave
this category. If it isn't ready can you play the Manos hands of fate game? No no thank you. Do
something wacky? Um I don't think these pants will allow me to do that. I could give you a TikTok
though. You want to talk about world's greatest TikToker? Yeah I could prove it to you. Can I
stand up? This is not inappropriate right? There's a pair of pants with I have underwear on. Why do
you have to ask that? Why do I have to even say that? I sometimes forget how many people I'm
talking to. My mother's pissed probably. She's probably like Jeremy. I just heard my mother's
voice go Jeremy. TikTok fine. You want to see the next fucking big TikTok dance? I'll give it to you
right now. All right fine. Okay I've trended on TikTok three different times in the last fucking
three years. Bring this one to the fucking front page. Oh this one the goddamn orangutan. See on
the front page. Holy shit it's already gone viral. It's already viral. I didn't even do it. I just
did that for five seconds. You think I could be on TikTok.com? What the fuck did that guy do?
That's the latest TikTok craze. It's called the orangutan. You keep talking just make it already.
I'm not gonna make a TikTok. Jerma I would, Jerma I would rather see you in the hospital
than on TikTok. Holy shit dude. What the fuck? Can you be toxic? Sure fine. No I don't do that.
I'm too excited. By the way, important, the New Year's Eve nominations are still open.
Still open. If you have something this year that you thought was really awful or really cool,
go to the Discord. I'm winded from doing the, it's a tough dance. We've got 10 minutes until I have
to panic and figure out what the hell I'm gonna do for the next few hours. Be funny. I just did
the orangutan and that was fucking hilarious. Don't you remember? This is why I shouldn't
ever fucking go live unless I exactly am ready to stream the game. You guys that's why I don't
do like IRL is because I can't be trusted with anything. That was trendy but it wasn't funny.
That was trendy. Why am I so red? Why? Dude I don't understand. Why do I have so much blood in my skin?
Why am I like this? I don't think I really am though. Does that mean I have too much blood
all over my whole face and shit? What does that mean? You're regressing to 2011 Jerma. Yeah the
Jerma that was red in every video. But I was burnt. That was burnt. I don't know why I decided
to turn the face cam on and do videos when I was just burnt every time. Was it? We've seen the
orangutan but can we see the... I don't know what that is. You're very sweaty. I'm not, I'm real,
I'm not though. I'm just red. Nine minutes. Nine minutes. Remain. Why is your bed on the floor
behind you? That's a dog bed. Or that could be very far away, right? What if I just freaked everybody
out right now and I got up and I started running and walking towards that and I started getting
smaller and like five minutes later I get in that bed and lie in it like I'm this big. That would
have been hilarious. Jerma it comes out tomorrow but look at Steam. I'm telling you look at Steam
says the game releases in less than an hour. It said 23 hours an hour ago. This is not copium.
This is factual information on the Steam website. It's gonna be five. I think so. You're already
fitting that perfectly. I, I gotta fix this. I don't know why I'm so red. I'm like, I'm like
turning purple. Am I or is that just my shitty monitor? I can't, I have no idea. You're bruising
because your lights are too blue. Let me, let me see what I can do. Hold on. Bear with me here.
Okay. White balance. Let's change it. Oh there we go. I'm actually like blue now. I don't, why am I,
I don't, do I even have human skin? Why is it like so hard for me to white balance my face?
I don't get it. I promise I'm not like this like red and purple. I've made like videos on
TikTok before. I'm not this red and purple. Why do I have so much blood? I don't know.
I don't know. Six minutes until we don't get to play the game. He's so scary. I'm,
all right, give me some questions. This is supposed to be an ask me anything before Monster,
ask me anything about Monster Rancher. How does that sound? Because this is a Monster Rancher 2
stream. What does your mouth look like an optical illusion image? Like the ones with Obama where
one version's facial features are upside down. I don't know. My cells split like differently in
the womb. I don't know. I have no idea what you mean. That was actually kind of funny.
All right, what'd you say? You're still going to play the Monster Breeder? Yes.
You like Ranch? Not really. It's okay. How old were you when you first played Monster Rancher?
Now that is a good question. I believe I was 13, 14, PlayStation 1. I loved it. They replaced
the CD system. I am not going to give a judgment on it until I play it in approximately five minutes.
What are your thoughts on Honey Mustard? I love it. Why do you look like that? Why do you, why do
you look like that? Is this 2D or 3D? It's 3D. Why is your face red in Monster Rancher? When was the
last time that you touched grass with your fingertips? Does soil count? Like does dirt count?
Because I've done a bunch of stuff with plants over the last like few months. That should count.
Four minutes. When I drink that's a nice coffee. What'd you say? Why did I see you blink like a
reptile two minutes ago? I don't know. I'm really blinky. I'm really blinky and I lick my lips all
the time. So maybe I am a lizard. I don't know. Your straw is longer than your forearm. Holy shit.
This is huge. This is, this is huge. Why is this so huge? Oh my god. How are you, why are you so
perceptive? What? It's, it is fucking gigantic. What? This is probably for like a 40 ounce drink.
I actually, I'm really happy about it though because I don't have to like move. I can just
go like this. Takes too long to get to your mouth. No it doesn't. Perpetual
kinetic energy gets it there faster. Am I, I'm not even that red. It's just a shitty monitor.
How many people are in here? There's like almost 12,000 people here. Is it out? Your straw is as
long as an oil pipeline. Play a game already. I'm so, I hope this releases in three minutes.
Please release in three minutes. What'd you say? Are you hip with the kids? Talk to me in an hour
when the orangutan is trending on the front page of the app where you cannot be over the age of 35
to use it. That's an ego, egotistical. What the? This monitor is, you know what? It is this monitor.
Remember when I thought that like a green like vegetable was gray or something? Because this
monitor's colors are all screwed up. Two minutes! Yo dude, where's my door dash order? I don't know.
Why would I know that? There's a bug on my face. Good. Okay. 60 seconds, come on! Come on, come on,
Monster Rancher. Monster Rancher 2. If we all say it collectively at the same time,
it's going to happen. Ready? Monster Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2. Monster
Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2. Come on! Monster Rancher 2. Louder! Monster Rancher 2. In the back!
Monster Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2. I feel like I'm at a camp. I feel as enthusiastic. Monster
Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2. Monster, come on! This game will, it just says coming soon now.
That's, wait, that's normal? It's normal? Somebody said that's normal. Does that mean it's like about
to come out? Like right now? Restart Steam. Is it out? It's out? Restart Steam. All right,
I'm gonna restart Steam. Oh shit, it's out. This deserves an orang attack! It's not even out! Where
is it? I just, are you lying to me? Come on, it's out! Install it already. Somebody says yikes.
No, it's out. It's out. It's out. Come on. Holy shit, I can't wait. Fucking install it!
Hurry up and install it! Come on! Dude, you need to chill. Yeah, I know. Dude, the iPhone just came
out. The iPhone just came out and I'm in line to get the iPhone. Are you on meth? That's fucking
funny. We did a drug test like a year or two ago and the only thing that came up was cocaine. So
like, I mean, that person's fucking wrong. Why can't, come on, download. Wait a minute, hold on a
second. Why is this fucked up? Shit. All right, hold on. I'm restarting it again. I don't do
fucking drugs, guys. Marijuana is the only thing I've ever done. I drink alcohol like six times a
year. Come on. Is it installing? Oh dude, here it goes. All right, my stream might crash because I
can't like do two things at once. I might be downloading too fast. Let's see, tell me if the
stream crashes. I can't wait. I'm so happy. I get to play Monster Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 2.
Monster Rancher 2. How do my headphones in? All right, open it. Turn the volume down in case it's
too loud. I'm opening it for the first time. It actually is out. It was really loud. Can you hear
this? That's so loud. I got scared. Turn this, turn it down. There's no audio for you. Okay, well,
there is now. I'm sorry. I just made it loud for you. That was my fault. All right, Monster Rancher
2. Monster. This is, I got to go to the options here. Sound on. What is it? FF. FF? Resolution
settings. Here we go. I want a full screen. Full screen. Oh shit, I didn't have a controller. Okay,
I got a controller. Stop. Let's chill. Gonna fucking hang out. Play Monster Rancher 2. It's a
fucking pretty fun game, dude. Minimize the face cam. I have to make sure the game works first.
Why can't this? Full screen. I want it full screen. I don't know what FF is, but I'm just gonna say
okay. Confirm. I don't think that did anything. Oh Jesus, I don't know what's going on. Okay,
hold on. Let me capture it. Oh shit, this is, I can't wait. This is fucking unbelievable.
All right, so listen to me. I can't fucking wait, dude. There it is. I just looked so pretend
interesting. I'll do face cam for 10 minutes and it's never going on ever again. What happened
to my hair? Why does my hair look so like fluffy and weird? Okay, here we go. So if you guys don't
know anything about Monster Rancher, let's talk about it very, very quickly, very briefly.
Monster Rancher, where'd it go? Where'd it go? Why isn't it being captured? What just happened?
What the fuck is going on? What happened? Why is it doing this? All right, I want to do new game.
Why is this not showing up? It was just, you guys just saw it, right? There it is. You ready?
Monster Rancher is a monster training and battle simulation game. This game takes place over the
course of a few years, I think five to 10 years on your ranch. And what happens is you get these
monsters, you can breed them and you fight in battles. And it's way better than Pokemon. Okay,
Pokemon is not even close. Neither is digital monsters either. So what's going to happen here
is I'm going to get into the game. I'm so fucking excited. Let's go. Please sign your name here.
No, matches are open to public view. Do not include any personal info or offensive
wording. Some words made up. Wait, there's online in this? Holy shit, really? All right, what's my
name? What should it be? I don't have to hurry up. Dean Baxon. This is not the name of my monster.
This is the trainer. I feel like there's a significant amount of lag. Okay, this is important.
How about Jaxxus Cole? Sus guy is not going up there. The orangutan. No, there are orangutans in
the game though. A lot of you new viewers, I have no idea just how fucking cool this game is. I'm
able to change your whole life. We've played this before a few years ago. It's one of my favorite
games. You're about to experience one of the coolest fucking games ever made. And I'm dead
serious about that. Pay attention. All right, it's just Jeremy. Jeremy. No, Jaxx is fine.
Why is it X? What's with the X? How do I? That's interesting. Should I use the keyboard and mouse?
That's the wrong X. How is it wrong? Jaxx, you will be a new trainer, right? We're going to have to
take, you're gonna have to learn and type the test. Please answer these questions. I have never lied
in my entire life. Uh, I have, I lie all the time. The effort I put forth in reaching my goal is more
important than the outcome. That depends. That depends. I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say, can I just,
can I click the thing in the middle? I'm gonna say yes. My dream can be realized as long as I do my
best to achieve it, but also luck at like right place, right time. And yeah, I don't know. I gotta,
I gotta click the one in the middle. It's 90% luck. You're a millionaire. Just say yes. If I have to
choose, I like spring better than winter. No way, dude. Before I start proceeding with something,
I should make sure it's safe. But it's safe how? Like safe physical danger or safe like out of my
comfort zone. I'm gonna say no. In a battle, what counts in the end is mental power. Um, unless the
person has a gun. When I'm ordered to do something I like, I'm confused. What does that mean? When
I'm ordered to do something I like, I'm confused. I don't think, I don't think so. I, I think it's
like that. I'm like surprised. Like, oh, this is cool. If someone does something displeasing,
I should not behave the same way. Yeah, I'm not, if somebody's doing something doesn't mean you do
it. When I am absorbed in something, I don't notice what's going on around me. Yes. In order
to truly succeed, sometimes I need to make a risky choice. Yes, absolutely. But have backup
plans. That's all, thank you very much. Please wait here for a while. I'm, I can't fucking wait,
dude. You guys have no idea how fun this game is. Hello Jax, thank you for waiting. I was explaining
the type of trainer you are to the trainer assistant. Uh, I am a trainer assistant. Oh yeah,
okay. I remember the exam pass date, the exam score a little bit hasty. Okay. This is the trainer.
This is the trainer that I have for help. She is the trainer assistant who is going to your place.
She is still a bit childish, but she sure is a good girl. Here she is. Coltia. How do you do Jax?
I'm Coltia. Please call me Colt. You're going to work with her for quite some time.
So please try to get along with each other. Do your best to raise a monster well so that it can
win the major four. Way better than Pokemon. I'm looking forward to your performance. That's my
opinion, right? My opinion is that I think this is better than Poke, Pokemon. That's my opinion.
You might have a different opinion. Your opinion could be different than mine and that's okay.
Yes, sir. Well, Jax, let's do our best. First, you should obtain a monster at the market in the
town or at the shrine by generating it from a disk stone or a slate and then take it with you
to the ranch. How this game worked back in the day is there was a certain code that was embedded
onto every CD and DVD that you owned and it would pull a random piece of data from that. For instance,
I put Adam Sandler's Click in when we played this a few years ago and you get a specific monster to
that disk. Obviously now CDs don't exist anymore, so I don't know what the hell they're going to do.
I guess now there's like a gigantic database where you can look up your favorite songs and
movies or something. I don't know. I wonder how it works. We'll find out. But it was really fun
because I got like 40 just random CDs and DVDs and we just generated monsters and the monster
will always be the same for that disk. It can be a million different combinations, although it's
probably like way less than that, but it's a lot. Thank you. Did you see that information there?
I'm still a rookie here and Jax, you too have just become a trainer, right? Is there anything
you would like to ask about? I know everything there is to know. I've already played this game.
Are you done? Yes. And let's go find our monster. We're going to get a default monster. We're going
to get our Squirtle. We're going to get our Charizard or one of the plant stones back.
So wait, should we go to the shrine? Excuse me. Is this your first time visiting the shrine?
What's your name? My name is Colt. This is Jax, a trainer. I am Chally, a priestess of the shrine.
We generate monsters using disk stones and slates, backup data of Monster Rancher. So this is like
save game and stuff, right? What do you want to generate? A disk? How does this work? Disk stone?
Uh, I wonder how this works. The music is... I'm so excited. I am too. Here comes DMC. I don't...
No, hold on. Where is it? I don't think it actually plays the music. It definitely doesn't play the
music. Oh shit. What am I doing? How can we get... Wait, what did I do? Oh, okay. So what should I look
up? Oops. The title of the song or an artist? Cautions? All right, how about just something
simple? Okay. How about Crazy Frog? Does that exist? There's no search result. Please change
the conditions. There is no crazy frog. Toxic. Uh, toxic by 30 forever... There are toxic by
Britney Spears. Okay. Are we ready? What do we get from toxic by Britney Spears? I regret to tell you
that this rare monster can be generated only by an authorized trainer. Please come again. Remember
that for later. This is a rare monster. Okay. Well, let's try again. Thumbnails. Elvis? What
do they have for Elvis? Elvis Costa? No, no. Where's Elvis Elvis? Where's Elvis Elvis? Elvis...
Okay. There's Elvis Elvis. How about a little less conversation, a little more action? I think that
one. A little less conversation. Elvis versus J-X-L. Okay. Let's see what we get. Here is the big
moment. Are you ready? It's a brown dinosaur. What is it? Strong looking monster. Why is it so tired?
Looks dependable. Okay. Do you want to take this monster to your ranch? All right. This shit's
really important. That's not bad. High skill. Intelligence is awful. Power is not that great,
but life and skill are really high. I think we can have a bunch. I'm going to take it. Can I take it?
There's a hundred gifted subs. Who gave a hundred gifted subs? What? I just, how did I miss that?
Soveen 4500 fucking community subs. What are you doing? Thank you, Soveen. The a hundred community
subs. Finally noticed. Speed is horrible. From what I remember, intelligence and power are the
important ones. Intelligence, power, and life. Which is the one that replenishes guts? Guts is
like mana, but thanks. That's an insane amount of money. That's never, never necessary. Never
expected. It's crazy. Thanks for the insane amount of subs. Name this Alvin. We'll remember
because they don't change. We'll remember. So I'm not going to take this one. Elvis, a little less
conversation, a little more. All right. Let's try it again. How about Kevin McCloud? Definitely not
here. Is it, how is it? Is it Mac? Like that? Damn it. Oh, Freddie Dredd. Let's see it.
It'd be Freddie Dredd. Spelt it wrong. If there's a Freddie Dredd on here, I'm going to have to do
it. Is it two D's? What is it? I'm spelling wrong. Is it two D's or is it A? No, it's two D's,
right? That's not, it's not like that. Or what if I do that? About a hundred gecks. Not here. I think
it's based on, from like 1999 or something. This is not like, I think this is actually pulled from
like the CDs that were available. Weezer? Okay. Weezer. Which Weezer album? I've done, I don't
know what any of these albums are. How about Christmas with Weezer? Sounds good to me. I regret
to tell you it's too rare. All right, whatever. What's on the market? Radiohead? Yeah, you can
buy Monsters 2. So Monsters have two different types. There's the main type and the subtype.
And pretty much all Monsters can be combined. So if you have like a Dino type and a Bug type,
they can be combined. Sometimes it can just be Dino, Dino, right? Which is just, just Dino.
Or you can combine Monsters 2. So I think everything in the market is just a straight,
just straight up like Dino or like Ivysaur. Whatever, right? Okay. Let me see. They, oh,
they buy Monsters from you too. I forgot about that. Let me see what's in the, in the market.
So we know what we're looking for. Let's see. What do you got? Please choose. So that we had,
this is a regular just Dino. Choose a Monster you like. Okay. Zoom? Suezo? Or a Mochi? What's the
Dino's, the Zoom? All right. That's actually kind of, is that better than the one that we found?
This one's actually a little better. It's way better. Typing the talking heads. All right.
Let's go over these so people know what's going on. Life is just your health. Power is physical
damage. Intelligence is magic. Like tech damage. It's green. Skill, I don't remember. Speed,
I don't remember. And defense is how, you know, damage reduction. I forget what skill and speed
actually do. Speed I think actually is your, that's regeneration? Skill is accuracy. Speed is turn
order. There you go. Skill is hit chance. Speed is evade chance. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
I don't want this one. Let's go back. I know the music is like a cartoon clown one. I know.
The actual game of Monster Rancher. Just wait till we get to it. Holy shit. It's one of the best
games ever made. I, you know, I'm just, I'm going to, I'm going to drag this out for like the next
two weeks. Hope you guys are ready. All right. What'd you, who, who should I do? Frank Sinatra?
What? Frank Sinatra? Talking heads. Okay. That's not here either. In sync. What? Nirvana. Okay.
Nirvana. Which one? MTV Unplugged in New York. Which one should I do? MTV Unplugged in New York.
I guess we're just going to do this one. Here we go. The unplugged album is actually good as hell.
All right. All right. So this is a, like a Triceratops thing. It's very small. Holy shit.
That skill though. Life is bad, but that skill, that base skill is huge. The life is bad. I'm
taking it. You have to give it a name. What will the name be? All fours Barney. Barney all fours.
Gumbo? It's Barney. What a, I'm crawling. Barney Sanders? I like Barney. All right. Hold on.
Barney. How about just Barney? I like Barney. How about Barney fours? I like Barney fours.
What about Kurt? It could be Kurt. I like Barney though. This is just the first one. I like Barney
fours. It sounds like kind of like Barney rubble, but not at all. I like Barney fours. All right.
Here we go. All right. This is an auto save feature. That's amazing. So let's go back to the ranch
and let, I'm at, the controller's not really, this is where the game begins. You can get a ton more.
Yeah, absolutely. The whole point of Monster Rancher is you train them and get their stats up
and they, before they die, you freeze them and then you get another monster up, a shitload,
and then you freeze that one and then you combine them and you get something else.
They can die. Yep. Which food do you want to give it this month? Okay. How much? I have 5,000 gold.
Uh, though most monsters don't like such animal foods, a few do. Nutritious Milk? I don't know
what, what he, what he likes. I remember the strat was like tablets are insane, right? I don't
know what he likes. Do milk. He's a baby. Yeah. So the, the way this game works is there's a hidden
stress and a hidden fatigue meter. The higher your stress and fatigue are, the more life is taken
off of you at the end of your life. So if this monster base monster value lives for two years,
if you keep your stress and fatigue high, it's just like chain smoking cigarettes. You just all,
you're just losing life at the end of your life. So you have to try to manage their kind of hidden
stress meter. Cup of jelly reduces stress from what I remember. Tablets just are, they're expensive,
but they just taste gross. They don't, they don't like it, but it makes them train better.
I don't know if I go right into, um, tablets and they, they like certain foods too. We'll do jelly.
Jelly is usually pretty good pick. Or milk. I'll do milk. Do you want to give milk? Yes.
Here, eat. You like it? Yes. Who is it? Oh, quote, long time no see. Master Pabs. Nice to see you.
Jax, this is master Pabs. Jax, I am Pabs. Nice to see you. He was the greatest trainer ever.
Stop it, Colt. Oh, they can run away too. So we have to be careful. Jax, keep up with the good work,
Colt. I have to go now. I have an appointment. Master Pabs used to be the number one trainer
among IMA. He's not running. He's fine. I know he doesn't look like that. Bonnie. I hate this.
Bonnie four is very well. All right. I'm curious. File. Where is it? Monster data. Okay. Here we go.
All right. So Ari. Why are you giving me so much money? 75 more subs from Ari. Why are you giving
me so much money? This is insane. Thank you. That's a lot of money. All right. I need to see more.
This is the win loss record style even. Okay. Likes meat does not like cup jelly. So if we
feed this character cup jelly, it's going to be pissed and it's going to increase their stress
and reduce their life. Not their HP, their actual how long they get to live. So we got to be careful.
It's a lot of money. All right. Uh, bad natured likes meat as these two moves scratch and bite.
Pretty good hit chance on, uh, yeah, this is, this is like a power based, uh, tax. Okay. So we need
to do power. So let's take a look at battle because if you see here, the game is based on weeks. So
one loading screen is a week. So this week there's nothing going on next week. Nothing going on. So
essentially we have all of April and into may and in may there's going to be a tournament with a
thousand gold prize tutorial. Andy, I have to be tutorial. Andy, a lot of people have never seen
this before. Why would you compare this to Pokemon? You'll see, you'll see. All right. So we got some
time. Let's do some training training. So we want power. Okay. Dominant power is up. Fatigue up
study is intelligence run is life. So this one is power and life, but you lose speed. It's a bunch
of fatigue. I think that's not about his life is terrible. Probably life. These do a ton of stress
on the monster as well. I think we're just going to go with, and also when they're, when a monster
is a baby, like this monster is, they get a lot less stat gains until they get to like the prime
of their life. Let's just do, let's do health. I feel like health is important. Here we go again.
Come on. How'd you do? Yes. Plus two health. Still a baby. This will eventually, this will end up
being like plus 10 health plus 20 health. Uh, Bonnie four as well. Okay. Should we rest or should
we do it again? I need to buy like mint leaves and, um, and, uh, nut seeds, whatever it is again.
All right. Let's go again. Let's do it again. Although should I really work that hard as a
baby? Let's see. All right. We got one that I don't have to do any skill. Okay. Looks all right.
Work him. I don't want to, he's a baby. This is a baby. Errantry is you send them on a mission
and they can learn new skills, but we're not doing that right now. Let's just, let's do it. Let's
Okay. We're going to train again and then we're going to rest. They can fail these too.
Sometimes they, it's like, Oh no. Like I just said, Bonnie did not finish its drill,
scolded. No, the baby. It seems to be delighted. All right. I need to go. Uh, seems well. Let's
rest. I don't want to overdo it. Based stats are crazy on this guy. Okay. Yeah. Let's just relax.
Don't have to do anything. So rest, rest for the week. You want to let Bonnie rest? Yes. Perfect.
Don't be such a softy. I'm not. I, it's a, it's a baby. Loyalty 11 style soft. Let's do some drills.
You can do it. Oh, come on. Shit. Why Bonnie's did not finish their drill. Skulled them. It
seems disappointed. I, I can't be too, which food do you want to give it this month? All right.
I think I'm going to go with the, he hates cup jelly. All right. For those monster rancher,
enthusiast here, even if he hates cup jelly, does the stress reduction on cup jelly negate the fact
that he hates it? Cause I know that cup jelly reduces stress. He wants meat 300. Don't overeat
this though. Not worth it. All right. Well, he wants me 300 bucks. We're really going to gauge
if this is going to be long-term and not based on the amount of, uh, how good they are in tournaments.
And they're very well as well. Let's take a look at the battle calendar. All right. We have it.
There's a tournament coming up here. So that means if I want to train, it's either train once
or skip the tournament. Cause he doesn't even have a hundred health. What do you think?
We'll just go for it and see how we can do in a tournament train rest battle. Let's go for it
this time. Come on, actually complete it this time. I, I fucking love this game. This is the
only thing I'm going to stream for the next 10 years. And I mean that in gerbil years. So like
a week, there we go. Nice. Good job. Seems well. Okay. 15 soft. Should we rest? All right. We're
going to rest and there's time for the first tournament for Bonnie. I'm so excited. Just wait
till you see the battle. It's, it's awesome. All right. Are we ready? First fight. Grade E round
Robin four entrance. Bonnie has little loyalty now and may act confused. Do you still want to
participate? Yes, I do. Pay attention to your monster's guts level during the battle. If the
guts level is low, it can't use an attack. Guts essentially is mana. It regens. Don't get KO'd
or your monster may get injured. So just give up when it's in trouble. Four foot button to give up.
The blue sky cup. It's snowing. It's hard to believe it's spring here in the Papa's arena.
Under this condition, blue sky cup is about to start. Jax, let's go for it. What's the
competition look like? All right. We got Bonnie four. Harry kicks Oakley man and Leon. All right.
This is kind of a mirror. I just dropped out information. What do you got? Our opponent,
Leon has high skill or to KO before it gets our monster. Can I see the data?
Do I get to see the data? Do you want to give Bonnie advice during the battle? Yes.
Because the CPU is an idiot. I wonder how you, oh, I'm going to kick the shit out of you.
All right. So there's like things on the sidebar, but I have a controller. I wonder how this works.
Can I just move with the controller? How do I move? I don't know how to move. He's confused
because it's based on where you are. What is going on? All right. These controls,
I got to figure this out. That was a big hit though. So I can't, how do I move left and right?
I want to like, is it L and R? Okay. All right. All right. It's L and R. I'm going to lose maybe
again, quick. All right. So it's L. So the, all the moves are based on just position. I can't do
scratch if I'm back in the second position, like darkest dungeon, except with one person,
I have to be in that exact slot to do that move. Just so you know, prediction result was yes.
Kicked his ass. All right. Bonnie one. All right. Versus Oakley man. That's a beanbag Sonic.
We can't get too excited. You're going to get wrecked by Oakley man. Okay.
Eric kicks one. All right. Bonnie versus Oakley man. Let's go. All right. You got a lot of health
and you have a lot of power. So it's L and R to move back and forth. And then it's just A to do
technique. So I just get in the right spot and do it. Okay. I'm going to back up, build it up.
All right. Go for it. Nope. Scratch again. 20 damage. Back up, back up, back up, back up,
back up. That's a lot. Holy shit. That hurt. Good dodge. Dodge again. Bring it together.
I got a lot of guts. I got to get in close. Get in close. Come on. I have so much guts.
Just keep using it. Dodge. I have so much guts. Just keep using it. Come on, dude. Get it. Oh,
again, again, again, again, again. Guts. So every move requires a certain amount of guts.
You regenerate guts over time. Every move has a percentage to hit, which is increased, of course,
by skill. I think we're still okay. Oakley man needs to lose. I don't think it's going to happen.
Okay. Leon won. Everybody has won one game. We're going to have to do it again. All right. Let's go.
A bit 30K. I should win this. My skill is way hard. Got to get in close and we're doing bite.
What are you going to do? You haven't moved this far away. Shit. All right. Stay in close.
Don't let him get away. He does the most damage. Back it up and do scratch. Damn, that hurt.
Come on, dude. Really? Get over there. What are you fucking dodge at? Scratch again. Fuck,
I'm going to lose. That 95 health sucks. Absolute asshole. Give me a crit. Come on,
again, again, again, again. What's the percentage? Did I lose my percentage? Oh, yeah.
I got two wins. We're good. I got to try to remember. Okay. So I have to select the move
and then be in the range or do I just have to be in the range? I forget. All right. Oakley man
lose and I win. Come on, Leon. Kick his ass because I can beat Leon. It's over. We have
monsters whose scores are tied. So we will now hold a tie breaking match to determine which I'm
going to lose. Do I forfeit before I get him hurt? I don't know. I don't think I'm going to beat
Oakley man. Do it. Fight. I can't. I'm going to lose. He might die. They can die. If he gets knocked
out, you can actually get the, you can actually kill him. It's not worth it. All right. I'm going
to say, so what's withdraw or drop out. Isn't it the same thing? I'm with them. Yeah, I'm
withdrawing. Withdraw. I don't want him to get hurt. Oakley man is the winner. I did put it for
the first time ever. He's a baby. This is the result of the tournament. I got, I got in second
place. I get 500 bucks. I get 600 bucks. Okay. It was a thousand dollars to win and get fame
and potentially die or $600 to come in second place and be alive. I gained one fame. Oh no,
nevermind. Nobody cares. Jax, I think Bonnie Fours has learned a lesson in this tournament.
See, look, always learning. Always learning. See, if I didn't withdraw, that doesn't happen. Good.
Nice work. Bonnie Fours could not be a champion, but I think it did a good job. Praise it. Yes,
absolutely. It was the first, first competition. Keep it up. I'm going to Oakley man's stream.
All right. It's time to rest. Well, guess what? Oakley man stays in E rank their entire broadcast.
So just be aware of that. All right. Food. I'm thinking we go all out here and we do tablets.
Tablets reduce stress, stress, whatever. And they make it so they're in a good position to train.
What do you guys think? I think tablets. I'm going for it. I also need to go to the market and buy
some mint leaves because that reduces stress too. Because otherwise your monster dies in like a year.
The first official tournament is scheduled at the end of the month. You have to prepare
Barney right now. Who is it? Oh, you have mail. Thank you. Who's it from? Look at this.
Errantry is usually expensive. Shall we send Barney four? Notice this month the
Errantry Management Office is promoting a price reduction for your monster's errantry.
We cordially encourage each friend to participate during this period. An errant, errantry. Okay.
How much cheaper is it? We want to send our monster to an errantry. Oh, you have to fill in
the paper there for errantry. I'm not doing it. Write down the monster name and the trainer's name.
Yes. Yeah, you send them on a mission and they get stats and they find items and shit,
but it's really taxing on them. It takes a ton of fatigue.
Maybe I shouldn't do errantry when the monster is this young. I don't think it's a good idea.
Errantry term is a month. During that period you're not allowed to contact with a monster.
You choose a location from five different sites. It'll cost two thousand dollars.
Some locations are not for the low ranked monsters. Also, a wild monster appears around
here occasionally. Yeah, and they kick the shit out of you. I remember this. Yeah, it's the monster
who attacks monsters during the errantry. If your monster wins, you'll get the prize money.
Of course, there is a chance that your monster will get killed. Is that good? You could do it.
And then I'd fucking die. Discount. It's a huge discount this month. I think I'm just gonna do it.
All right, what do you think? This is a huge, huge skill in life. I think we need to do life,
though. Hour in life? I need to hit way harder. The stats suck. Don't do it yet. Is he too young?
It's probably bad, but it's a thousand dollars off. I'm just like opening the door to like the
back slider of the house to like a fucking puppy and going, yeah, go, go for it. Find some items.
That's probably a really bad idea. I don't want to do that. I'm not doing that. No,
like that's too dangerous. Too dangerous. We'll have him. I need to go to the store.
I want to buy some stuff. Uh, welcome to the market. I want to get.
You already have a monster. What if I get items? Lab? This must be your first visit.
My name is Dadge. I'm in charge here. You want to combine or freeze this place to do it? Okay.
What do you like to do? Uh, so what happens is you can freeze a monster. It stays at the exact age,
the exact stats and everything before they die. And you put them into cryogenic freezing chambers
and then you combine their DNA. Okay. So it's not there. Where is it? Lab? Job? Job? You can come
here whenever you need a job. Do the job. Where do I buy items? Is it not unlocked yet? The item
store? Yeah. The market doesn't let me do it. Or is it on the farm? He's so tiny. Item. Oh, shop.
Here we go. So we need to get nuts and mints. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Let me buy. Buy. Please get out
of my way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. You can
fit more texts than this, by the way. Like what are you going to do? Second line, third line,
there's four lines of text available. All right. Monsters love to snack on this tasty fruit.
Candy. Uh, most of these reduce or add stress and fatigue. Mint leaf. How much are they? It relaxes
your monster and relieves its stress. I need to buy a bunch of these. I'm going to buy five mint
leaves. Sweet jelly, sour jelly, nuts oil. Okay. This helps with fatigue. I'm going to buy five of
these. All right. Now I need to save some money. It's rumored that a monster will become popular
if it eats this, like a fame fruit. I'll get a few mangoes too. It's like a little treat.
So I'm going to use mint leaf, right? I should probably use both of these because it just helps.
Did you get high to do this? No. We'll do the mint. I'm going to do both. I think, I think I have
this correct. Take it. This reduces your overall stress by a certain percentage so you live longer.
You're supposed to use one of these each month. That makes sense. Only one at a time. Okay. All
right. So we've given that. How are you doing right now? All right. Get in there. Elf,
throw us a run. What's this like ice cube thing? Cheated. Cheated? Barney cheated on its drill.
Sometimes you got to know what it takes. That's, that's my boy. That's my smart boy.
He's very fond of me. Let's do it again. What's the next? I want to, I want to stuff
fucking fist into that motherfucker's face. Whatever his name is. That guy, the guy looked
like a rock. What was his name? Oakley man. I'm not doing the tournament. Not yet. I need
at least a hundred health. No, it's not worth it. Too much. Do it again. Help me. I'm trapped.
Cheating again. Yeah, that's my boy. Maybe I shouldn't praise the cheating because
it's going to do it more. That's probably not a good idea. Hey, did you, hey son, did you win?
All right. Don't do that anymore. Seems sorry. All right. Barney as well. If you're well, then
why not just do it again? When's the next major tournament? It's the official cup. I don't know
if they're ready for this. I don't think they're ready for this. I could try. Rest up for the week.
We'll enter the official cup tomorrow. It's only cheating if you get caught. Yes. Let's enter the
tournament. Barney's in good shape. I'll bet you, I bet you'll rake the points. Very well. Good.
Let's do it. Official cup. This gets us out of E rank. If we can even do it, which I don't,
who knows if we can even do it. All right. Let's fucking go. Just give up if you need to. Yeah. I
don't want to get any, I don't want to get anybody killed here. Grade E. Young monsters
gathering the place with ambitions to be a tomorrow's star. It's the time to start the
official tournament. It is the time. All right. Official tournament. Let's go. This game looks
great by the way. Can I just say? Oakley man's in this fucking competition. What if I just withdraw?
All right. Let's go. Let's go. All right. Let's hopefully I don't get killed. His health is so
bad. I need crits. A lot of them. All right. Let's go for it. Back it up again. Damn it.
What is his speed at? 55% chance to hit. Oh my God. What is your speed at? I just have to win
with, uh, I don't have to, I don't have to KO him. Nice. Good job. Oh my God. Do it again.
Again, again, again, again, again. Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up. Get out of his range
all the way back, all the way back. Just run it out. Run the clock out. Oh, Oakley man. You
just got fucking destroyed. I just beat him out of range. Get out. See you later. I win. Although I
got to beat everybody else. Nice. All right. Oakley man. Now you're on the ropes. Good luck.
Although I have not seen these other people though. I want that thing, whatever it is,
it's like a weird dolphin. A one and one here. We've seen these two. All right. That was close.
Bunny versus gnats. Is it a bunny? I think the bunny's fast. Oh, you're dead in two hits. Goodbye.
Why did you even enter in the competition? What's the, what's the, what's the point?
Why would you enter a monster with 57 health? I'm going to kill you in two hits and I'm going to,
I'm going to, I'm going to try to kill you. That was kind of fucked up. Yeah. All right.
Oh, all right. So you want to fight. All right. That's how it is. You want to fight.
Now I am going to go flood. Stay close. Stay in close. He has one fucking move and it's in the
third slot. Just stay in close. Oh my God. He's going to beat me. Anger. He's pissed.
Grit. What is that? He gets an extra health. Oh boy. This is bad. Get in close. He has one move.
It was like fart and punch in the third slot. I wonder what does anger do? I forget. Okay.
It's really important that Juno mule loses this fight. All right. That's the one to beat.
Oakley man's going to beat Leon. Beat him last time. Holy shit. What happened? Leon got stronger.
Leon is not. Oakley man sucks ass. All right. Interesting. I got to go three and oh,
I might actually lose this one. I don't know. I'm concerned. Stay in close. Scratch. Get in
close again. Bite. Bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite, bite,
bite, bite. Dodge. Let me do my bite. Come on. He keeps pushing me. He keeps getting me back.
Bite. Don't get confused by bite. You just bite him with your mouth. He doesn't want me to do
anything. This closed. There you go. Again. Do it again. Do it again. I have plenty of guts.
More. Again. Don't get confused. Come on. 57% chance. Give me a fucking break.
Let's get a win by percentages here. Oh my God. I think I just lost. Did I lose? Oh, nice. That was
close. Bonnie's pretty good. This is the only second tournament ever for Reno. Imagine the
doubters. Yeah. What the fuck is going on here? We got, we got way too many doubters in the chat
right now. Too many of you. All right. This is important. I'm very shocked by this in one month.
Leon is now unbeatable. All right. This fight doesn't matter. I'm not going to see either one
of these again. Anyways, this is like championship fight coming up here. What? How did you get so much?
How did you get so good method? Oh, it's power. Let's do it. Let's go. I'm curious what the stat
change was. It seems like it's kind of a huge change. No, it's not. Oh, did he beat everybody?
I have better stats than him. And I had more trouble than he did. It's okay. What this fight
has to be is just getting close and spam bite it in close or go, go, go, go, go. He's so much
bigger than me. Look at how much bigger he is than me or don't let him fight. Get out of here.
Tournament over. I won E rank. Let's go. Oh, I love this game. It's so fun. It is now impossible
for me to lose the tournament. I think I just get a buy, right? Who have I not fought? There's one
person I haven't fought. Who is it? Oh, it's you. I could lose this. I just forfeit. Who cares? I just
win. I'm 4-0. Would that be shitty if I was just like looked over there and I was like, no, I'm good.
I just win for the money. All right. I don't know the strategy. The strategy here might be to run
away. Those stats are insane. The fuck? How do I do dispel on a controller? I wonder. Dispel is when
you're close. You can press a certain button combination and it goes boom. And it knocks you
guys back all the way. Eleanor at the same time. No help. I mean, don't tell him I'm trying to win a
tournament. All right, let's go. He has nothing long range. I could just, I got a strategy here.
See if it works. Oh, he's getting confused. Get in close. Dodge it. What the fuck? Do a move. Do
a move already. Do your bite. He's literally right in front of you. Get angry. Get angry. Bite him.
Bite his throat. I was spamming. I still win the tournament. Yeah, I'm four and one. He's three. I
won the tournament. I win. It doesn't matter. Oh, wait. Okay. If Leon wins this. Oh, you've
got, you lost to the fucking 50 health rabbit. Oh, you deserve to not be in the top two.
You lost to the rabbit. The rabbit sucks. Must've been tired. Yeah, now I actually win. Oh,
they'll wait. Oakley. No, Oakley, man. No, I'm good. Tournament's over. I won. Bonnie Fours is the
winner. Nice job. Do a dance. That screenshot. This is the result of this tournament. Prize 500.
700 bucks. Some more fans. Eight people thought that was cool. I got eight new fans. Hey, Jax.
I think Bonnie's has learned a lesson in the tournament. So smart. See, look. Health just
leveled up. Very good. Excellent job. Praise. Very delighted. Nice work. All right. What food for
this month? This is important. Should we give him meat because he loves it? Or should we just keep
going with the tablets? I think the play here is probably tablets, but they love meat. So they just
did a good tournament. They just won. Let's reward with the thing that he likes the most. Have some
meat. Yes. Who is it? Is this Jax's residence? Please sign here. Okay. Thank you. Good. Have
a nice day. That's kind of like passive aggressive. It's from the IMA. International Monsters
Association card. Based on your performance, we will grant you the rank mentioned. First rank.
Oh, maybe I can now go open up the new capsule. You know what I'm talking about? I think so.
I'm pretty sure I know what you're talking about, but just go ahead and explain it again.
Trainer ranking is the official document of all trainers by rank from beginner to master.
It's every trainer's dream to reach master ranking. We're at the first level, so we have nine ranks to
pass. Let's make it. I'm excited. You hear about the meat? Master Pabs, why are you excited?
Not good for your health. Don't be silly. A battle between IMA and FIMBA is finally about
to begin. How can I not be excited about this? Really? FIMBA is the neighboring Continents
Monster Association, isn't it? Yes, it's finally confirmed. Every four years, we will select
representatives from five different grades. It's five on five battles. Representative, representative.
I guess we cannot be the one. No, if you win at an elimination tournament held at the end
of this month, you'll be the one. Why don't you enter the tournament? Okay, let's do it.
Let's represent this association. It's great to be a representative. We got to be one. Bonnie depends
on us too much. I guess we spoiled it. Seems well. Oh, but they've been doing so good, though.
No, all right. Let's do some training. When's the next thing? All right, so we unlocked C rank
battles. No way am I going to be able to do one. Elimination grade D. What's the one that they're
talking about? This is the official D cup. Okay, I'm not doing C. I'll get my ass kicked.
I think I don't think I can do. I got to train him a little more. All right, let's do how about one
of the old diseases is he right now? How old are you? Three months. What's the age that they
kind of get older? Six months because eventually they get to a point where the training is way
more efficient. One year. Okay, so we got a little bit more time. We'll do some drills. Let's do
power. Let's do power. I'm going to feed him some mint. Good job. That was a huge success
wasn't it? Oh, because huge success I think is a way more increase. Bonnie's tired. Let's do
let's give you some mint leaves, some nut oil. Someone was going to do mild voodoo on you. Would
you want to know or would you rather continue to be oblivious to it? Can you like leave me alone?
Would you just like leave me alone? Like you know what I mean? Like why can't you just leave me alone?
All right, mint leaf. Let's go. That's not an option. All right, well can you do the kind
of voodoo that makes me get like a 10 million dollar lottery ticket? Are you going to do bad?
Are you going to like curse me and shit? Do you feel an itch on your forearm right here?
That was weird. All right, let's go. Training. Are you still tired? Let's rest. What if we do
healing spells? Yeah, do healing shit. I want you to heal and give me good luck and good tidings
and shit. Don't like make me itchy. That sucks. Don't do that. Why would you do that? What did I
ever do to you? I'm gonna start wearing like garlic on my neck. Uh, power again. Let's get a
huge success here. All right, Bonnie says, I want to play with you next week. Do you grant its request?
Do you play with them? Yes, but we're spoiling. We're spoiling the shit out of them. Yes, of course.
Anything for my little baby. Yes, we can play next week. Ooh, nice job. 150 power. I'll be happy with
one like 70. Jax, didn't you make a promise that you'd play with Bonnie? Are you going to play?
Yes. Good. Bonnie's going to be happy. Aren't you happy with the nice weather, Bonnie? Today,
Jax will play with you as promised. Okay, let's play. I need some lip balm. There it is.
The mud ball fight. Tap the screen to find the monster on the field. Mobile port. Mobile port.
Sorry. Tap the screen. The arrow on the lower left of the screen will show you which direction
your monster is. You can move sideways while still facing forward by using the moving buttons. Okay.
When you see your monster, press the okay button to change to the aiming mode. Now touch to set
your sights on the monster. This is a pretty good mobile port. Okay. In fact, hold on a second.
Is this going on iPad? Does that mean that this is going to go on iPad? Is it on iPad? That does
not upset me. It's on the Switch. That's not iPad though. iPad's very different. I don't mind if I
drop like the iPad in the toilet or in the bathtub. It's on iPad right now. No it's not. Who uses an
iPad? Me. All right. So we got to aim and fire, throw a ball. Be careful because you cannot move
in the aiming mode. I'm going to lose this so we'll just figure out how it works. The number that
appears in the upper left is Jax's points. Do your best to try and beat Bonnie. Let's go. Ready?
What the fuck was that? How am I supposed to do this? What happened to him? Why did he just fall?
What's wrong with him? Oh it's tied. Stop. Why do you have so many more balls than I do? This is
unfair. Oh I beat him. Hey good game Barney. I didn't lose to a baby. I won. Did I just like
Billy Madison play dodgeball with a three-year-old? A four-year-old? What? I shouldn't be happy about
that. I should be annoyed. All right food. Let's go with tablets. I want you to get big and strong
and I want you to have lots of power. Be careful you don't run out of money. I'm not even. I just
spoiled. All right. When's the next battle? There's no way I'm gonna do this. Not a chance. I don't
think I'm gonna do this one either. I'll do. We'll go. We'll do the official D. I want more training.
I'm gonna go for it. Huge success. I'm over. Okay. Leveled up my power. Over 150. Do some defense.
I could go see if I can unlock the other monsters. We need to freeze. Freeze this guy. I don't think
freezing hurts him or does anything bad. Yeah freezing I think just locks him. I don't think
this hurts the middle. Somebody tell me if this adds to stress or something. I don't think it
does. I think you just kind of freeze for a second because you can just unfreeze. Yeah just freezes
them at their current exact moment. Okay. See you later. That was kind of sad but it's okay.
Let's see if I can get toxic. Okay here we go. Toxic by Britney Spears. Do I have enough ranking?
I don't. I am an authorized trainer. Don't you see my license? What are you talking about?
Give me something else. Hatsune Miku? Okay Miku. There is no Miku. I guess I'm gonna go with Bird
by Mikuni Shimokawa. What? It's rare. Remember that. Write that down. Uh Dino Crisis. Dino Crisis
What about Dino? Dino Dinoasorius. Dinoasorius. Viva La Vida? Dino Crisis by Capcom. It's a bunny.
Cute. Yes it's a very cute monster. Do you take? I'm not taking this. No the monster sucks ass.
Look at this. No. No. How about Dino Crisis 2? Dino Crisis 2. What's with all this rare shit? Come
on. I have to win another couple tournaments. Weird Al? Time for Weird Al? Kanye? No. Gorillas?
Aw Demon Days let's go. What we get from Demon Days? All right. What is that? Cute. Yes it's
a very cute monster. Holy smokes that's 200 intelligence. That's almost 200 base intelligence.
Those are gonna hit so fucking hard. That's that is the keeper. All right name. Noodle? Noodle.
Who's L? No that's Nudie. L is right here. Nudie. I don't want it to be Nudie. Noodle.
Not Nudie. All right let's do it. What do you get for moves? Dude we could combine Noodle and Bonnie.
You know what I'm saying? I wonder what we'd get. Barney Noodle. All right what do you got? So you have
monster data. Let's see. All right E. Noodle. Level 4 intelligence already. What do you get for moves?
Nature. Best nature. Likes nuts oil and doesn't like tablets. Okay you got a few moves here.
This is bolt. Holy shit this could be insane. This thing is guaranteed to hit but it kind of sucks
damage wise. All these are such high hit percentage but not very powerful. I wonder how powerful it is.
Why would you use kick instead of pat? The only difference is I mean I guess it's a little bit
less guts cost but who cares. All right well we're gonna give her a item. We're gonna give nuts oil.
That should help. Now let's do some training. Just intelligence. Let's get it over 200. Study.
Are you learning? I don't. Okay I guess they learned. That's a level up. Level 5 and level 6
intelligence. Do it again. But this time I want health. Her health is really low. No cheating.
Good work. Why are you black and white? Wait I am? Does the webcam look like washed out?
Is it? Oh my god it kind of is. It does feel like an old movie. Oh shit hold on let me fix this.
It is really washed out. Is that better? Can you see me? Good his red face is back. Need more
red face. All right the life is bad. We gotta keep doing life. Still doing all right. Do it again.
Is there a light? You don't want to do because this is considered to be heavy work and when
they're a baby heavy work you don't really get that big of an increase. So it's kind of stupid
to do heavy training because you're just really taking time off of their life for no reason because
they don't get that high of a gain when they're a baby. Uh we'll do life again. I I think that
I think she's gonna wipe the floor with the first train with the first tournament.
For me you need a haircut? Yeah I know. All right what did you like? You don't like tablets.
I think cup jelly is this the yeah let's get cup jelly. She doesn't like tablets. Cup jelly
is the best thing to do because it's the only thing that just reduces stress right off the
bat no matter what. Look at this a diamond mark? If we collect five of these we'll get a fun can.
Really? I always wanted this as a kid. It's like pepsi points. All right official tournament end
of the month. When is the official tournament E rank? She's gonna destroy everybody. Not concerned
at all. I need life. So what um it's all right don't worry about it. This huge success right
is that just a flat percentage? No it's fine. We'll say great. Okay rest. This is just like
nintendogs. All right we got I don't think I'm even gonna I think I'm just gonna rest.
Yeah double rest. Tournament let's go. Official tournaments happening this week seems to be good
shape. All right let's go for it. Yeah it doesn't matter she's 200 intelligence. All right it's the
same group of clowns that we've have absolutely destroyed before so I'm not scared at all. This
is like a person running into a Pokemon field and kicking the shit out of Pikachu. I don't think a
person would really do that. I think Pikachu would kill you as a person. Oh wait we got a new uh a
new person here. All right so the goal here is we're trying to we're gonna stay back in the third
slot and we're just gonna zap zap zap zap over and over again. Here we go see how it works.
Confused. That's not good. Back it up. That's a cool move but I wish it would work. Oh my god
she's confused. Bolt! Move forward. Oh my god really? That sucks actually. Oh shit she's gonna
lose. That should be doing way more. I have no guts. Stay back. Oh my god please don't die.
She was not ready. Glass cannon. Glass cup. Didn't do anything. Her move was doing 10 damage.
I think with proper training it should be okay. That's a lot of it. There's definitely a move you
can learn that's a higher damage intelligence move. This game is rad. Yeah it is and we haven't
even scratched the surface. There's so many different monster combinations. It's just a fun
game too. I think I believe in okay we should destroy Oakley man because one reason defense is
for power attacks only. Intelligence is also defense against intelligence attacks. If I don't
beat Oakley man here this is a big problem. Let's go. Don't be... What's confusing? Shoot him.
All right. All right. That looks good to me. Back it up. Ease? I don't know what that is. Ease.
Stay back. Get some guts. Don't ever do that move again. Don't ever do that again.
Holy shit. You're gonna kill me in two hits. Back it up. Back up. Back up. Oh my god. Back the fuck
up. Back. Get over there and fucking do it. I need the combo to push people because I don't know what
the gamepad combination is to like do the push. I need to learn that it's like one of the most
important things in the whole game. He lost to a puddle of oatmeal. He has like 150 damage.
I gotta get in the menu and I gotta look at the controls. What is this? Battle keys? Oh here we go.
Dispel. I don't know what I'm even looking at here. All right. Dispel is... Wait. This is original
song. Original? It's X or A depending. It's probably X. I'll try that. Well I don't think
she's... I can't win now. I'll try X. Oh right. It's gonna be the clown music. Maybe I should
put it on read master. It sounds gonna be worse. Okay. This shouldn't be too bad. It's gonna be
horrible. I'm gonna lose. Guaranteed. Left and right. This is like putting your hands on an iPad.
So I... I'll try X. I'm gonna lose. There's no way I win this. Let's try the move though.
Try X. Is it X? It's not X. Is it B? Oh it's B. It's B. It's B. All right. No it's A. Okay good.
I got it now. Stay back. Pull back. It's like catching a fish. Again. Again again again again.
Again. How much gust does it take? I actually might win this. Push push push push push push push
push push push. Don't hurt me. I think we put this lady in the freezer. I gotta withdraw.
I gotta pull out. I gotta. I have to withdraw. I haven't won. No. Get out. Drop out. Drop out.
Drop out. There's no reason to do this. I'm gonna die. Drop out. Do an errand tree. I think it's
time to do an errand tree with her. I'm not giving up yet. No fans. That's fine. Don't spend your
money here. That's true because of like no encouragement. We're too soft. We keep making...
We spoil everybody. Sorry. Hold on. I don't need to read this. Sorry. I didn't mean to scare or
upset you with the voodoo comment. I won't keep you updated on it anymore. I want some... I want
some fucking warlocks in the chat right now. Whoever you are. You need to counter that person.
Don't update me. Don't tell me about it. But just make sure that you're like countering that person's
spells. Right? I want some like wizards. Like witches and warlocks. Just counter that person's
spell. Right? I will. Thank you. That person's casting spells on me. I don't... It's like a weird...
It's such a weird feeling. I don't want somebody to cast spells on me. And that like wouldn't it
make you feel like odd every day? I'll protect you. Okay. I just need some protect anti-magic
spells on me. All right. What do we do here? I'll tell you what we do. We're gonna go pee.
I will be right back. And we will continue. We're back. It is... It's like 85 degrees in this room.
You've washed your hands? Always. Always. Oh hey. Big pro tip. I'm eating something here.
I'll tell you right now. I used to not like cliff bars at all. But holy shit. The blueberry crisp
cliff bar. It cannot be compared to anything. It is so good. It's so good. Don't get the peanut
butter and chocolate meme bullshit. Blueberry crisp. Try it. I'm telling you. Chocolate mint.
No thank you. No thank you. I'll take blueberry crisp please. Want to see what it looks like? I
don't even know why it's called blueberry crisp. It's just good. This just tastes good.
I respect you a little bit less because of that statement. Nothing matters to me right now. I'm
eating a blueberry crisp cliff bar. All right. What are we doing? I kind of want to just freeze
her. I'll be honest. Cliff bar has gluten. What? What? What'd you say? Are you kidding me?
I'm gonna freeze her. I don't want it. Might be... Maybe later. Game's too loud. I gotta...
You're still eating it? They're good. Which one? The remastered one's a little more pleasant. This
one's a little harsher. Heard it off too. All right. Freeze. I don't want to... Somebody said
don't spend money. If I don't think I'm actually going to use this creature, I'm not going to spend
money on it. Maybe later. I need some more songs please. Rush? What's the song? The trouble with
the maples and they're quite convinced they're right. What's that song called? Trees. Yeah,
that's what I want. The trees, the sea, and the sun by Guy J. Sure. This is a big moment.
Something cool. It's kind of a weirdo. It's a thing inside of the people's heads in Men in Black.
Sorry if I spoiled a 30-year-old movie. Very energetic. All right. Eastie boys. How about,
how about Shake Your Rump? Shake Your Rump Remixed. Whoa. All right. What do we got here?
A bit scary looking, isn't it? All right. I think I can work. That's actually not bad. Space.
Love Batman. Let's go. It's a snake? All right. Sorry. I didn't know you were such an expert.
In Monster Ranger 2, monster types. What do you like? Oh, you like Cup Jelly. You don't like
potatoes. It's perfect. This hit percentage is awful. The whack and belly punch. D. Shit,
you kind of suck. I'm going to send this guy on an errand tree. What should we do? Just straight
up power? Yeah. No. Come on. Get back in there. Come on, dude. You can do it. Freeze. No. That
was pretty good for a baby. That was actually really good for a baby. He looks like you put
your action figure in the microwave. Maybe a little. What's going on here, by the way? I don't
like this part. You know what I'm saying? I don't like this part. See what I mean? Take a rest.
Shave it. F. Please do it. See if we can just kick people's asses. What's the next one? All right.
This one will be easy. We'll do this one for weeks. Get in there. You're freaking me out here.
Do it again. You like Cup Jelly, which is perfect. I have to make some money. I'm kind of just burning
through my five grand. What is it? We get some mail? I'm sending him. I'm sending him on an
errand tree. It's half off. Speed, life? What do they got? Speed, life, intelligence, life,
skill, life, power, life. This is the one. He's not going to gain anything, but he might learn a move.
He is too low, intelligence. Won't he potentially learn a move? He needs more hit chance. He needs
intelligence. I don't know. Just send him. Let him die. Who cares? How long you've been eating
at that single Cliff Bar? You don't know much about Cliff Bars. Cliff Bars can take sometimes
four hours to eat completely. They take 40 minutes to eat. They last an hour. It's so much nutrients
and protein packed in one cube. It takes a little while. You're trying to make me choke?
Maybe this is a stupid idea, but yeah, I don't have enough money. I really just don't.
Let's do a hit chance, which is skill, right? Let me see your data. Your skill is absolute dog
shit. All right, we'll do skill. Come on. You're cheating. Did you at least get points? You got
one point. Don't do that. Do it legitimately, please. Get in there. Don't cheat. Oh, come on.
You failed it? This guy's really just real dumb. I won't scold you this time. Back into the
microwave. Microwaved action figure. When's this fight? No, he's not ready. I might be ready for
the official cup if I can actually get you to do what you're supposed to do and stop screwing
around. Hit it. His skill is so bad. It's going to take so long to get him. Do it again. Get in
there and actually do it this time. You're wasting so many weeks. Stop it. Get in there and do it
the right way. Go get Bonnie back. I think we go get Bonnie. Bonnie's loyal, fast, strong,
intelligent, quick. I'm going to give this guy one more month if he's still annoying and we're
putting him into the ice. Got to give him at least one tournament. I know it's there. He's dressed
out. Oh shit. What the fuck was that? He got a weird scream. I like it. Eat a mint leaf. I could
sell it too. I could sell him in town. Fuse with noodle. I don't know if I want to fuse this guy
with the noodle. I'm going to do the battle this month. This one here. No, the E one. It's the
official one. I like that. I do like that sound effect though. I do like it. I'm buying two shit
monsters. It costs money. I think it's like 500 gold or something. I don't have enough money to
do that. I have to win a tournament. Please don't cheat and actually do it this time. This little
shit. I swear to God. Look at this terrible increase. It wins the battle. All right. We're
going to rest and then train and then rest. Do it for real this time. Please. Oh my fucking God.
Why can you not do any? Why? Well, let's see how good you are in a tournament. You need to ice
this dude. Not yet. He might, he might be really good in the tournament. He's unruly. He doesn't
listen, but what if he just KOs people in three hits? I'll try it. Let's go. We need money.
Like really badly actually. I'm going to start to burn too much money. If I go below a thousand
gold, then we have to just go get Bonnie and just try to just win tournaments. All right. What we
got? Same shitties that we saw last time. All right. Let's see what you got. Both these moves
are pretty bad. They're like probably 30% chance to hit. Uh, I don't, this doesn't look good.
42% chance to hit. This one does more damage though, doesn't it? Belly punch. Come on, do it.
Do it. That was, that was pretty good. That was actually really good. Belly punch is great. Stop.
Just close the gap here, please. Finally. Jesus. Just when who cares? You don't have to K or
everybody. Okay. Oh, I'm getting a headache. Trying to drink water. I'm going to literally
know like this game. End of the stream. No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm very invested in this.
It's voodoo bullshit. Stop voodooing me. Uh, this I'm going to probably lose because this is power
versus power. Hmm. Hit chance is way more important sometimes than just power because I'm going to
miss half the things I swing at them. That's a cool profile picture though. I like the profile
picture for bug Batman. All right. We're going to get, come on. The, the, the whack has such a
terrible hit percentage. 51%. That's so bad. Why? No, don't do it. Holy shit. That was a lot. Don't
do anything but belly punches. No reason not to. She's just getting confused. All right.
I don't hate this guy. I do see a little bit of potential with a bug Batman. Probably going to
lose the one versus Oakley man though. Oakley man has lost once. Hopefully they lose twice.
Then we're good. I played this game my entire teens growing up. It's my favorite game of all time. So
happy you're playing it. This is probably one of the most fun games ever. I would put Monster
Rancher 2 somewhere in like the top 10. I'm really glad that they're supporting it still. Uh, I would
love for them to do another one. And by the way, steal this from me. If you want to do a Monster
Rancher 5 or like even if you did a Monster Rancher, just get rid of the numbers and just
make Monster Rancher. Right? Like everybody does now is you get too many high numbers,
you remake the whole thing, whatever. Make it URLs. URLs. Simple. I think that's a no brainer.
QR codes. I think that they have this system here that is song data. But you could just like
kind of just grab a shitload of website stuff and just have it be URL based. Either that or Steam
games or QR codes. Yeah, there's at least two or three ways to do it. Pornhub. I'm just saying
URLs would work. Do it from a photo on mobile. Yeah, there's so many cool things you could do.
I'm available. I'm available. All I ask for very, very basically, simply, is 60 to 70% of all the
gross sales. That's it. And that's like not even a big deal. That's not even like a high price to pay.
Like a fucking idea like that. It's not even like really that much. Good dodge. So if you're
wondering why the question marks keep popping up is the monster has low loyalty and is really young.
So when I tell it to do that move, as you see the little blue bar when it crosses over and I hit
the button, he's a little stupid. He's too young. He doesn't really know what I want him to do.
And he messes up, but holy shit does he hit hard. It's really hard. It's another win.
Hang on, I'm right here. One more. 47 damage. What a dumb fuck. It's like three months old.
He's two months old. Imagine like you have like a baby in your life, like an infant. I don't know
whether it's like a friend's or a family member's baby and you go over to the baby and the baby's
like kind of in the crib just like kind of giggling and laughing and shit and like people are like
shaking keys and you just lean in and say what a dumb fuck. You're not going to get invited to
Christmas again. I don't understand where you think you're coming from here. You're not going
to get invited to Thanksgiving. That's objectively true because your babies are stupid. That brain
hasn't even developed yet in the ring. So why are you playing a baby cage fighting game?
They're babies. They grow up. They're not babies forever. They're not just babies. They're little.
They grow up. They get big and strong. Why are you making babies fight each other? Oh yeah? Your
favorite game. Pocket Monsters. Pokemon. You throw this little fucking circle at these guys
and you trap them into this like 12 by like four by four inch cube. Do you see how these guys are?
They have like a big house. They're like out out in the grass and shit. The Pokeball that you're
trapping these Pokeballs. These Poke Monsters in there. It's a cube. It's a circle. Free-range
Pokemon. They like it in there. Okay. You're literally freezing a monster on a whim in this
game. Hold on. I got something important to do. Not bad. I think I might just run away now.
You get one more hit and run away and just let that time go up. That's bad. Give me an opportunity
to move. For god sakes. Come on. 66%. Oh my goodness gracious. I'm about to put this guy
in the fucking cooler where they'll get like the Pepsi's and the bottles of water. Hit punch.
Don't let them just zone you like that. Get in there. It's not good. Too much help. Whatever.
Would you eat a Pikachu egg? No. But I also I wouldn't eat anything besides a chicken egg.
Do Pikachu's have live birth? How does it work? The eggs? What do they come? What is it?
All Pokemons lay eggs. They do? Eggs? Even Wailord? Wailord is something like a gigantic egg?
It's because of the house? I don't. No. Wailord has live birth guys. I'm sorry. Wailord comes from
an egg. Ban this conversation. Like we can't talk about like the chicken and eggs and stuff.
Okay. Let me I want to make sure this is very clear to everybody. Me talking about Wailord's
eggs or birth whatever is not okay. But zooming in on my ass when I get up from the chair and like
look at his huge ass. That's okay. That's fine. I just want to be clear about what you got. What's
appropriate to you in the chat room. Don't talk about eggs. Don't talk about eggs. Zoom in on his
ass. Zoom in on his ass. Zoom in on his ass. That's which one's fine again. I'm just trying
to understand. All right let's beat this guy's ass. Do it again. Spring it together. Don't even
let him do anything. Be the first one to do the input. I don't have back it up. I don't have enough
guts. Spit. Back it up. Pull back. Run the clock out a little bit here. I don't want to lose. Punch.
That lick is a ton of damage too. I'm glad I didn't get hit by it. You just let these guys
spit in your face over and over again. You're really going to let them just do this again again
again again again. There it is. That actually might have been really bad. I love Swayzone.
I kind of want one of those guys. Oakley man. This is uh I think I'm going to lose the tournament.
All right come on Leon. Beat him. Come on. That's a victory right there. Tournament over. I won.
Nice. Nobody has four wins right? Nope. That's it. Hog Batman is the winner. Okay now I can't
freeze him because he just did an official cup right. Remember the Monster Rancher anime? I never
saw it. I never watched it. How do you get less fame than Arnie? Learn something from that. That's
pretty good. Those are good increases. Now just listen to me and just do what you're supposed to
do and you'll grow up really big and strong. Listen. Go. Don't cheat and just try to do a
little bit of work. Cup of jelly. Why are you playing two and not one? Um in my opinion two is
just the same game as one but more stuff to do. One's a little more direct I think. I think two
is a better game. As much as I love all of them. Besides the fourth one. The fourth one was awful.
Monster Rancher 4 was truly an unbearable game. It was awful. Oh is that wait is that Evo?
Evo. Which one? What's the bad? What's the really awful one? It's three four or Evo. I don't
remember which one it is. Well one of them is terrible. Evo is the bad one. I think whatever
the last one was made because that probably just I guess Capcom is probably just like
this is not even Capcom. I'm just saying of wrong company name. Whoops. Wait it wasn't a Capcom?
Who made this? Didn't Ko- Didn't Koei Tecmo make this? Wait didn't Capcom make the first one? I'm
so confused. Why do I think Capcom made the first one? I don't know. All right do it. Please don't
cheat. There it is. Oh my god you can't do this. You just can't do it. I don't think he's capable
of doing the skill based training without cheating. I don't I really don't think so. We've tried it
like seven times. I'm gonna try this one more time. Finally you actually did it. Good you got more
than one point. Shoot again. Uh I don't want to do this tournament. Bonus disc chips. Oh I think
those are actually worth having. I might try that. No maybe the next one. This one here.
Bonus magic banana. Two thousand gold. All right we're doing this one. Uh I want you to get more
power. Four thousand gold. Dude you're getting tablets next month. Tablets. Take the tablets.
Why is this thing such an asshole? Because it's got like bad nature and it's scary or whatever
right? So like it wants to cheat and evil or whatever. To do D rank we definitely we need
at least 180. You're just wasting all of my time and money. Oh you're tired. Are you tired? Come
here. Take a mint leaf and take a nut oil. You are killing him. I am not I'm not killing him. He's
failing at his task. This is a child. I'm trying to be. I'm trying. You can rest. He's a failure.
Not really because he just won a tournament. All right you're doing very well. You had some mint.
You had some tea. You had some delicious like sunflower oil. Now get in there and crush it.
Do it. I know you can. Now we praise. That's a big increase too. I think I get this 200 to 200.
Where's the one that's above four thousand gold? All right it's this one coming up.
Round robin. Four entries. I don't know if it's if he's strong enough.
Two thousand gold though. Should I try? I'll try it. Or do another E. I think I'm gonna go for it.
Rest up. Let's go. See if we can get you in the D rank. The f1 is 4k for jelly.
Let me go look at that again. It was 4,000. Everybody here? Our entry is cheaper. This one's
what are you seeing 4,000 gold from? No the only one that's here that's more than a thousand gold
is this one. I'm sending him on the trip. It was the f1s. I got uh I only have 1800 gold.
I don't know is it worth it? It's a thousand bucks. I'll have 800 dollars left. I'm gonna
soft block. I'm gonna soft block myself. Get in there. Come on. I know you got what it takes.
Let's go. I know you got what it takes. Get in there. If you don't you're getting you're getting
frozen. Spring rain. Under this condition para para's cup is about to start. Let's win. This is
gonna be a short tournament. There's only four entrants. Winston, Pella, and sleet bomb. Sleet
bomb. I think this guy has a lot. Oh okay. This is this is uh a war of I gotta hit him once and
then run away. Come in slow. Yeah. You idiot. Dodge. Good. No you're not an idiot. I was
kidding. I made it up. Get one hit and just good. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back
it up. Back it up. Nice job dude. Excellent work. Back. Back. Back. Dodge. Dodge. Oh he's good.
Dodge. Holy shit. This is so much RNG that's going in our favor here. Dodge. Dodge. No.
Just keep hitting him. Take win by percentages. He's so slow.
Oh shit. It's all right. All right. I gotta win this one. I'll get prize money if I come in
at least second or third place. This defense is so high. Isn't this an intelligence monster?
Well let's see. No it's not I guess. It's weird. Good start. Again. He just pissed him off. Great.
Do it again. Just unlock. Lock him up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up.
Good. Again. Oh what the fuck was that move? Oh my god. He cubed me. Yes. Can you please win? I
just did. Okay now I at least get some prize money. I need Winston to lose. I mean sleep bomb is the
favorite. What? You're not the favorite. What's so special about Winston? Oh. Dude this 86 health
100 power. This character sucks. Oh it's because it's intelligence moves. It's not a power. Okay
I have to. Here's the strategy. Get in close and just spam. I just gotta hit him a few times.
He doesn't even have intelligence moves. Look at his moves. He has all power moves.
Bro how you win. Bro. Bro how are you winning so many moves?
How did you win against the huge guy? Hey bro. Again. I win this. This is huge.
Stop getting confused. This is a big deal if I win.
Oh my god dude. Fucking hit him. Oh my god. Fucking hit him with one goddamn move you shitty guy.
You shitty guy. No. I still win. It doesn't kind of hurt to do that. I don't like this part.
Oh no. I have to fight him again. Wait a minute. This is three-way tie. All right.
Winston versus sleep bomb and sleep bomb wins. Sleep bomb. Okay tie breaker. Shit. I have whoever
wins this has to fight sleep bomb. Wait. Right? Nice v-neck. I beat him once I could beat him again.
I got really unlucky at the end there. My percentages just died for some reason.
Okay. Same strategy. Just gotta hit him a few times. Don't miss it. 36 percent. His speed is
so high. Here we go. Again. Just two more of those. Back up. Thank god you missed that because that
was an intelligence move that would have killed me by even one hit. Do not back up. Don't get in
range of that shit. Yes. Got him. Are we farming today? Farming what? What emote am I farming?
All right. Wow. How did I win? Dude that's 2,000 fucking gold. How did I just win that? Wasn't it
two and one? There were three people that were two and one. Did I win by more or something?
Higher seeds. Oh okay. 21. I was about to be bankrupt. Thank god. I got a magic banana. Okay.
What's a magic banana do? Oh we learned something. That's not bad. I would have liked to see health
in there but oh well. Good job. You're really powerful. You're just untrainable. Okay. What
have we got? Power. What's a banana do? I told you to leave it alone bug man. Do errantry. It's
gonna be two grand. Oh it's still the same month. All right. Power life. Is there skill? All right.
Do we go for the skill in life or do we go for power in life? Hit harder or be able to hit more
often? Skill. Errantry will take. Yeah this is somebody has an absolutely good advice here.
Errantry takes away from the monster's life. He doesn't have high enough stats yet to succeed
at the trials in it. Really? Send him anyway. Do you want to send your monster to this errantry
location? Wanted. Oh there's a wanted posters? Whoa. We probably should do the one with the E
right? Okay. We'll do the bunny. Okay. Let's go. This is important. All right. That was a nice spin.
He split it. He got it. That's a that's a success. He got it. Oh yeah. That's a lot.
Another one. Go for it. There's dog hair in my mouth. Land it. Oh that's gonna be a great
success. All right. He's a little sloppy but he made it. Hungry sharks. Nice. Watch out. He's good.
This is gonna be like a plus 20 skill. Come on make it. That's all right. That was a big one.
It's all right. That was a big one. Hungry sharks again. You can do it. One. Left side.
Even side. Handle it. Get him. No. Okay. What'd he gain like 12? 13 stats? You're too hard on it.
He's gonna pass out. What? Have some nut oil. Mint leaf is stress reduction. Nut oil is fatigue
reduction by the way. Rest. You tried. It was it says I'm soft. What do you mean too hard?
Let him rest. Oh my god. What happened? Not strong enough. We'll go for this one. That's too grand
in a gemini's pot. All right. I gotta get him get him trained up. All right. Is it time to begin
the hard training? Use that magic banana. These are big increases. Use magic. Its effect differs
each time you feed it to your monster. So what does it do? Remember this is not related to any
buddhist stuff. I was just curious about how your left ear is. Um that's actually kind of funny
that you say that because my left ear has been ringing for the last like six months. Thanks a
lot. Thanks a lot. Appreciate it. Thank you. Thanks a lot. I'm gonna hold it for now. All right. Those
of you uh lore masters. Is me doing these hard ones now worth doing even though they they're
very damaging? Is he old enough? How old are you? Six months old. He's still too still too young.
I don't know if he's matured yet. Do them but use a mint leaf. All right. I'm gonna see how I'm gonna
let's see how old if he's old enough. We're gonna do pole and then I'm gonna use a mint leaf. I'm
seeing. I'm curious. These add way more stats but they're really really taxing. You got it.
I'd say that's pretty damn good. You need skill. We'll do that after this. I know. I'm okay okay
okay. I need speed too. Rest up. How can you tell when he's going to pass away? Um depending on what
type of monster it is different monsters live longer. Because like I said there's base types
and then there's subtypes right? So this is a base type of whatever the snake monster is
and a subtype of something else. And they both have like the snake monster as all snake monsters
live for a base time of four years. Uh the uh like Swayzo lives for an average usually of three years
and it kind of just combines the two types. So some monsters live longer than others and then
stress and fatigue obviously weighs on it heavily too. This game might seem pretty simple but there's
a lot of in the background stuff that you need to be aware of. When's this battle? All right we're
gonna train and then we're gonna do power or skill. Skill. Go for it. Don't cheat. Good job. Plus five
at least. And you still use CDs you cannot. How the game handles it in this port is there's just
a gigantic database of hundreds of thousands of songs and CD data and you just pick it and
one comes out. And you see these nuts and then you laughed with all capitals. That's pretty good.
All right we need that we need that two grand. Oh what a fucking classic. All right here we go.
Two thousand gold in a gemini's pot. Let's see if I can win this one.
Why are you doing the black tourmaline copypasta? All right let's go for it.
Quick tournament. Only four. Paramar. Capella. All right we've seen Capella.
Millium. Good luck bug Batman. I just gotta hit you like once. Twice. It shouldn't be too bad.
Stay close. This is an intelligence monster. Again stun lock. Oh it's 33. It's a one in three chance
to hit right now. Stay close. Literally four damage. Who cares. Easy. Stay close. Come on.
28% chance to hit. I just dropped my guts. 50% chance to hit. Oh I'll just fine. I'll just win
by. It doesn't matter. You can't even hurt me. Okay that's fine. Just keep doing no damage.
Whatever. I'm still lost. I just got angry. All right that's good. That at least potentially
guarantees us some prize money. Why is German a bad mood? What? I'm not a bad mood. What are
you talking about? I'm having fun just hanging out playing the game. I'm not a bad mood. What
are you talking about? Bad mood. What? How come you're not doing anything funny? Why do I have to
do something funny? I'm enjoying my favorite game of all time when I was 16. It's because he's so
red. What did I do about Smug? What did I do? He hates streaming. What did I do? I didn't do
anything. I didn't do anything. Good. Stay back. Watch out for that thing. He does that dice thing
and it does like 50 damage. Don't let him dice you. This motherfucker needs a new move so bad.
What the fuck was that? Dude will you attack him? That's not enough right?
He's redder than Boston baked beans? Baked beans are like what are you talking about? They're not
red. Those are like regular baked beans. Regular beans. Are beans? Yeah they are red. Boston baked
beans. This little guy. I just made 100k. Well you're going to lose this next one because I'm
going to... His defense is so bad. As long as I can hit him. A little like owl. I just have to land
it. We gotta just focus only on skill. Here we go. Good. Stay back. Again. Back it up. Push him back.
All right. He doesn't hurt at all. That's fine. Guard. Good job. Why are they booing that?
That was a cool move. I need two wins. Really? I mean a three. Don't even...
Okay we're good. Go for the kill shot here. Kill. Get more points. Everyone's fucking booing me.
Why do you look like Woody Harrelson? I'll tell you. He's going to be carnage. I remember when I saw
that. I was thinking that was awful. Well let me just tell you something. He's going to be carnage.
All right. Rematch. This is for two grand. All right. I can do this as long as I can get the hits.
I can't believe this. Yeah. I can't believe Capella lost that. I just have to get lucky here.
Capella's stats are so much better than mine in every conceivable way. I have to get lucky.
All right. Exactly what I wanted to have happen. Again. Do it again. Again. Again. Again. Again.
60% chance. Getting close. 41. Don't do the cube. I'll just stay back. Whatever. I'm just going to
play like a coward. This is for the championship. Well the money. Oh my god. That hurt so much.
That was so stupid. He couldn't even move. God damn it. At least I get to make the
errantry money back. Okay. All right. Not terrible. I got to get that over 200 power
and then I'm setting an errantry again. You did a good job. You're okay. Is it half off errantry?
Tablets. Can you do Tommy Lee Jones? Yeah. That's right.
How much is errantry? Stop drugging. I'm not. It's nutrient pills. What the fuck?
Why are you calling me a druggy? What? Dude, you're a druggy. What do you mean a druggy?
No. The joke there was why do you want me to do a Tommy Lee Jones impression?
I can't tell you the last Tommy Lee Jones movie that I watched. Take your vitamins.
All right. We're doing. What's next? A thousand bucks. Two thousand bucks. This is the one we're
going to win and then we're going to move up to C rank. Okay. So how are you doing right now?
Should we do errantry? Come on. You can do it. Two thousand dollars, dude. Is this stupid? Go for it.
Go. Do it. Do it. Let's see it. Is he going to die to the sharks again? He's better than he was
before. Clean landing. Clean landing. I want to play this game so bad now. It's really good.
You get both of them. You get one and two. This is the big kicker right here. Let's get ourselves
a new technique. Turn around. Turn around. Whack him. Fucking idiot. Here's another chance.
This side. Come on. Do it. Turn around. Get him. Oh my God. Why? Come on. You were so close.
He's too grand. He's too young. Now I only have a thousand dollars left. He's got 44 loyalty. All
right. Rest. Take some stress reduction. You've spoiled him and you're too hard on him. Yeah.
How does that make any sense? How much for you to stream the thing again? I stream the whole thing.
Go for it again. I need to. I have to make at least a little bit of money. This is two thousand
dollars, which means if I come in second place, I get a thousand bucks. You're going to stop
providing your kids with alternative medicine. All right. This is not bad because the big
weird dog muppet thing is not here. Come on. It's all right. Bounce. Bounce it.
Get angry. That's good. Get angry. Use it. Will you use your anger? Use that anger. Dodge it.
Holy shit. That's so clutch. That would have been awful if I got hit by that.
Dodge it. Why are you voting? Why are you rooting against me? We can beat this,
this little owl thing. I beat it last time. Staying close. Bingo. All right. Again. 68%
chance. Come on. That hurts a lot, but it's not that big of a deal. As long as I can spring
with you together. Your skill is so bad. Put them on ice. I'm done. I'm done with this guy. He's
getting frozen. He heard me say that. Now he's going to be hit way more. Go back. 62% chance.
You still can't hit him. What are you swinging at? What are you swinging at? Thank you. Thank you.
Knock him out. That's back to back 60%. 60 is really not that high. If you want to hit more
often, save up your guts. The more guts you have in the bank, the more accurate and powerful the
move is. Yeah, I heard that too, but this early though, I feel like you have to get hits in.
That might be the complete wrong strategy. He moved it. Moved it. All right. Capella wins, but
I can still come in second place if I beat Winston, who has lost twice.
I'll get a thousand bucks out of this. Stay away from that ice breath move and I will be fine.
Stay in close. That's all right. That's fine. I mean, if you weren't just such a dumb ass and
just every single move, you just don't know where you are. Again, can we start eating
Wheaties for breakfast? Why are you second place? Get it. Hit him. Fucking swing at him. What
happened? Oh, my controller unplugged. That's why I couldn't swing at him. That's very interesting.
I have it plugged into because this cord is small, so it's plugged into an extender that
goes to the computer under there. Oops. Do I get any money at all? Who even won? Did I get money
for that? $50. That's not even going to cover the expenses. That's not even going to cover
like the medicine. I gained one fan. Oh, that sucks. Keep going like this. Like,
my head's not itchy. It's just like a nervous habit. I don't know why I'm doing that.
Did you not learn anything? The monkey seems pretty tired. Go ahead and rest. It's time to go take a
look for another monster. If you consider dandruff shampoo, my head's fine. It's not itchy. I'm just
like my fingers need somewhere to go. Whenever I'm sitting around, if I'm doing something that I'm
really interested in and really like intensely focused on, like my hand will just like have a
mind of its own and just like go and move to different places and like move around.
Like I'm not in control of his hand. It's just like, just like up here. ADHD. Yeah. I mean,
that's probably what it is. You're a fidgeter. I am a big fidgeter. You're right. Told you.
All right. He's almost a year old. It's time to, let's get some training here, please.
Vigorous training. I'm doing the powerful drill. We're doing skill. There's nothing that's
powerful skill is there. Speed, power, intelligence and defense. There's this one,
but I don't want intelligence. Power. Power. Go. I need money. Bad. Can you please? Who is it?
It's going to be Erentree, isn't it? I wasted the last month. I did this and wasted money.
It's Erentree. God damn it. Crap. This is a thousand bucks. I'm just going to go here and just
win. Rest. I need that thousand dollars. We're going to go, we're going to drop down a rank
and just kill people. Smurf. This monster is miserable. He's not even miserable. Combine
this guy with Barney. I'm scared to do that because what if we get a shitty combination?
How much can you say? Yeah. You know what? Let's find out how much I can sell. Welcome.
Okay. What would you like to do? Sell. You pay a hundred gold for your monster. What a
low ball offer that is. A hundred gold. That's, that's nothing. Give me a break.
Back to the ranch. I'm giving this guy one more opportunity. We're going to take him.
We're going to do Erentree. First, we're going to drill. I'm going to do the easy
tournament. Just try to get some money. Be glad she's paying anything for something so worthless.
Skill is actually increasing. When is that one? All right, let's go. Let's just go wipe the floor
with a bunch of low level Smurfs. Wait, what did that say? Do I care? I don't know if I care.
I'm going to lose subs for this. Monster pups cup. I'm fighting actually literally children.
That had like a little cartoon children's intro. Okay. How much fame do I lose? They have better
stats than I do. How am I going to lose fame? Why are you still doing an E rank? Dude, this
character is E rank. I can't hit anybody. I've been hammering skill for the last like three
months and I can't even hit anybody. I'm not losing to children yet. Okay. I'm losing slightly
to children. Oh my fucking God. I'm going to lose. Dodge something. Dodge it. There it is.
Percentage as I win. Thank you. You guys are betting on every single match. I wonder how many
guys are just losing over and over again. This one should be easy. I got this. Let's build some
guts up. Let's try that strategy because right now it's like a 40% chance to hit. But I don't
just want to farm guts while he beats the shit out of me. Still at, okay, we're at 80 guts.
We're at a four. That's something like that. We're at almost a hundred guts.
I'm not sure it's worth doing that. I gotta hit him. That was big. If you bet against this,
I don't know what the hell you were doing. It's all right. Is the equivalent of sending an 11
year old to a kindergarten karate tournament and not being sure about the win? Well, I'm pretty
sure of it now unless the bunny, if the bunny loses here, it's over. That's it. I'll take the
victory. Wait. No, this is the victory. I have to win this. This bunny had 50 health. It's going to
be so simple. Don't worry. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to keep. Okay. Ready? If you bet against this,
I want to bet for me right now. Staying close. The rabbit has no moves up close. I can just try to
keep the zone here and let's go for it again. Stay in there. Stay in there. Don't let him close
the gap. What would you, what are you thinking? Wrapped and clapped and try to kill him.
All right. That's a thousand bucks and an item too. I think the little disc chips you,
when you combine monsters, you use a disc chip and it adds stats. I think pretty sure. What do
you think? We have to wait till I can at least get this guy another skill. He's winning tournaments.
Disc chips and learn something too. All right. I need to get 200 power. Oh, let's praise him. Sure.
My eye. Okay. Make sure to blink. All right. We're getting there. It's almost time. Give the
banana. All right. It's banana time. I don't even know what this does. Eat the banana. What did that
do? What did that do? It didn't do anything. Loyalty went down, but banana trades fatigue for
lifespan. Did I just make him die faster? That's not good. Crap. Go learn another move. Power to
200. I got, he's got to learn another move. Get rid of him. This is a, he's a loss.
I don't think so yet. We got two of these now. Okay. Aaron tree. How much does it cost? It's
2000. It's wait. No, it's not. It's a thousand. Come on, dude. What? It went back. I thought it
was still, oh, it's a different month. One monster Andy. I need to get somebody up to at least a year
level up power. Thank you. When is this battle? Should I go for C? No, not yet. I want to
participate in attorney and fight next week. This is what I mean next week. There's no fight next
week. Is there? Yes. I don't remember the being one. No, there's none. Sorry. You can't. 57. I
think it's time that I go power and I'm not doing enough damage to people. Our again does over 50
a hit and complains about damage. Oh, he's probably, he's kind of hired and he's not.
All right, let's do it. Rank D. I should, yeah. Rank D. I should just wait and take him to F.
What do you guys think? I will get crushed in C. He needs to get older. He needs to actually go
into the like adolescent stage, which is between what? One and two years. All right. We have not
seen one of these people yet. Just stay in close. Don't get hit by the ice ball and kill. That was
very, very good. I'll just hold it together. Don't be too crazy. Let the guts build up. Good. Go for
it. Clean. Very clean. Be an idiot. Do not choke on Capella. I, I'm going to try to play it safe.
I'll lose. Nice. Hail fall. Okay. I, Millium has 40 health. Let's do it. When are you going to peep
the horror? When is the game, when is he going to pee? I don't know what that means. All right. Stay
in close. Build up the guts. Come on. Really? Combo again. Shit. Good. All right. Now don't
be moron. Don't be moron. Go back. All right. Can I swing once? Get in there. All right. I win.
Hopefully I gave him the fame back if I win. Joe Biden called me cringe in his latest appearance.
That guy is just so cringe. By executive order, I'm going to make it so it's illegal for him to
stream. He's the cringiest damn guy I've ever seen. Imagine if I had something like a president
like executive order for me to not scream. What would I even do? It's a cringe tax. I have to pay
a cringe tax. I have to pay an extra 10% of my income to the cringe tax. That's so stupid.
All right. This guy lost twice. I can handle it. Get in close. I think it's cool looking though.
Don't get stabbed. I feel like that thing hurts. I'm getting really greedy here.
Hit him. Hit him. Hit him. Okay. Time's up. That was close. Is this for GameCube? This is for Steam
and Switch right now. You can get it right now. It's a double bundled Monster Rancher one and two.
It's a doozy. Explain how Millium is winning any matches. All right. Let's take it home.
Bad intelligence is so high. Get in close. Holy shit. You actually got it off. It's okay.
It doesn't matter. Your moves are so bad. Just don't let her get any range. I can take six
damage a thousand times. It doesn't matter. Build the guts up. I just have to punch her once in the
face. Oh, you motherfucker, please. Oh, I got her. So that's definitely how she's winning matches.
She's ranging. I'm just trying to stay back. I'm just winning by countdown. All right. It's
now impossible for me to lose. Actually not possible to lose now. Tournament one. Oh,
make sure you tune in tomorrow for the game awards. I'll be live during the game awards.
And then after the game awards, I'm probably going to play this again because I want to play
it again. This one's just for fun. What time is the game awards? 430 Pacific? Oh, three o'clock
Pacific. Maybe four o'clock Pacific. Maybe five. I can lose this fight. It's okay. Combo. Combo.
Again. Combo. Again. Knockout. All right. This is a win. Stay back. Watch that stupid thing.
I could really get carried away here and die. Yes. Perfect score. I'll take it. That should get a
lot of fame for this then. At least five to 10 fame. I hope these mobile controls look like ass.
I would imagine this actually would be terrible with a mouse. I mean, maybe you do left and right
on the arrow keys or W-A-A. It feels a little weird. With a controller, this is fine. It plays
just like it did 20 years ago. Prop the source. Yeah, there's to be black bars, right? Wow. That's
pretty huge. Wow. That's actually a big deal. Nice. I know I can't freeze them because now
his stats are going to be really good soon. Where's Beanbag Sonic? We'll probably see Beanbag
Sonic soon. Maybe not. It's all that kind of random. Is this emulated? No, this is on Steam
right now. Came out four and a half hours ago. Express mail from IMA. Next, this is it. What?
What is it? Here we go. This is my official license. Got rank two. All right. Does that
mean I can actually get toxic from Britney Spears? Second rank. Today is Bug Batman's birthday.
Should we sing happy birthday? Me, me, me, me. Oh, that was not what that was. Happy birthday
to, happy to you. Happy birthday Bug Batman. Why? You can't even get a fucking license?
Grow and be a strong monster. Hope that didn't cost money. How is my song? Not bad, huh? You
didn't even sing happy birthday. Are you from a different planet? Imagine trying to search in
your head for a song to sing someone on a happy birthday. On somebody's birthday. I would love to
sing you something, but I'll make something up on the spot. It's a happy birthday. Warner Music
invoices the copyright on a happy birthday since 1949. But they know they don't. Oh, there's a big
cake. Take this to our monster. Here, take this to our monster, Joy. Big birthday cake. It's DMCA.
Rest up. And then we're sending you on an errand trip. Is it worth doing this now?
Or should I do some heavy training? I'm doing heavy training with power. I'm curious. I think
it's going to be all right. Go for it. Make it happen. Get up there. Come on. Really?
You just had a big birthday cake and pills and everything and you can't go up the hill.
Try it again. I want to get you into the next C tournament. I want to participate in an attorney
and fight next week. I don't even know if there's a tournament next week. Can I see? What? Um,
you made it. All right. Good. All right. Big increases now. Huge increases. That's like,
that's a lot. I'm going to keep doing it. What does this peak the horror thing? I don't even
know what that is. Oh, again, another 20 stats. Well, technically did it. That was cheeky. Food.
We're going to do a cup of jelly. Stress reducer. It's a reference to a dream someone had about you
had blew up on Tumblr. What? It's a dream someone had about you. There's a comic book about it.
What? I need to buy some more mint leaves. Read the comic. Okay. Um, I just read this?
Okay. I'm just going to read this. I had a dream last night.
Derma became like a mainstream celebrity by pioneering a new type of stream where he would
play a game like normal. But every once in a while he'd let chat peep the horror and put this like
red and black pulsating mass on screen. Kind of look like an AI generated image. And the whole
deal was that everyone who saw it thought it was the funniest thing they'd ever seen. But every time
he'd show it, one viewer who saw it would die. It ended when he showed it on stream and dropped dead.
The stream was left on for 72 hours to honor his memory. It was dead quiet with just his body and
a slowly pulsating red mass on screen beside him. What? That's a fucked up. Whoa. That's
what it looks like? Hold on. That's so scary. But I'm the one that died? Not lucky, man.
What's with that RNG? Oh, Popeye's Prize! No, don't show that! That's it. That's it right there.
All right. Nobody can believe you. What? I need to read this one more time. One more time.
Why does his face look like this? Hello? Is he all right? All right. I'm like freaking me out. I don't
show this anymore. So somebody would just die. There's more. So it was this weird sort of
strange god scary kind of other sort of old one power where we all it like hit us and like
fucked up our brains and we thought it was really funny. Keep the horror. That's actually really
crazy. Okay. Hello. Welcome. I hear that Jax achieved the second rank. Keep on going. You work
hard. I would like to buy. They hate the smoke snake. Supposed to make it so they're not spoiled
anymore. So much money. I'll buy two. Feed the snake a snake. No. Go for it again. Pull. Get up
there. Get up there. Beat the horror please. I know you can do it. I want to participate in
a tourney and fight next week. Sure. You can fight next week. But if there's no tournament you're
gonna have to fight me. Dude. I even. Wasting time. Jax didn't you make a promise that Bog Batman will
enter a tournament? Oh he's really tired. He's too tired to do this. What should I do? Just let him
rest. He's gonna be pissed that I didn't let him do the thing. Loyalty went down. Well maybe if you
did one of these correctly we wouldn't have to waste all this time. I want to do a tournament
and fight next week. No. You're not ready to do any tournaments. Actually not ready. Thank you. All
right. Now I will listen to your requests. 17. Nice. Very nice. Very nice. This month I think we're
gonna go with a tablet. Just watch the video. Do a tablet every first week. Nut oil every second
week. From now on Bog Batman's strength will be affected depending upon how we raise it.
We must use more training skills. All right this is it. This is where we get him to like three or
four hundred power. Go for it. Go for it. You can't. No. I'm sorry I just punched everybody.
I gotta move the mic. I'm an idiot. I'm so sorry. All right let's see a huge increase here please.
I want him at 300 attack. Do it again. One more. One more of these and then that's it.
No. And then I'll do speed to get it back up. All right. Rest rest rest rest. I'm doing too much
work. What's the next battle? Should I? I should try C. I'm going for it. He's got a lot of power.
You need another move besides like punch and scratch. I need you to have something else to do.
I can go up to B rank. No thanks. C. Let's go. Why are you so serious? Be funny. Not serious.
Man that person for 700 years. All right let's go. Oh by the way. Human years. That's a move that is.
Oh as opposed to gerbil years. Oh this is big. There's a lot of people in this one.
Oh shush. Shush. Shush. I can't wait to kill this guy in two hits. All right this is uh
uh 366 kill. Get the fuck out of here. Are you serious? Power punch in the stomach.
Come on. Good. Again. What? Holy shit. He killed me in one hit. That's not cool.
I want one of those like handsome rock people. All right. Who am I going against?
I might have to pull out. Oh yeah. No way. C is not going to. This is not going to happen.
This was a stupid idea. This is a stupid idea. I could get lucky though. No way. I'm out. I'll
get. He'll die. He'll actually die from this. Holy shit. Okay just kill me so I can leave.
He's gonna die. He's gonna fucking die. He's gonna die. I gotta leave. Susvane's gonna win
the whole thing. Close. Get out. It's not worth it. Waranmo is the one to beat. Do I get a fame?
I don't get a dollar for showing up. Do I get any fame for showing up?
Oh no. Freeze him. He's ready to train. I can't. Not yet. He's in the prime right now for me to get
like a shitload of stats on him. Just splice him. Just hold on. Just a regular skill. Stop cheating.
You're just messing this whole thing up. All right if he does it again he's getting frozen.
You're the lower attorneys? Yeah. Get in there. Good job. Maybe if you raised your kids right.
All right. F. Oh what do we have here? A new year cup? Is it worth doing? It's a lot of money.
What rank is this? Just F rank? But who can participate? Anybody? A new year cup.
Game just crashed. When was the last time it saved? Right. That was weird. Okay continue. Use the data
to load. Monster bug. Yeah this is literally like right here. There it is. All right so let's try
that again. I love this game. Okay don't crash. Oh it's a tournament. Like actual tournament.
How how how are these guys strong? Oh my goodness. They're like look at how they look. I don't think
I can do this. I shouldn't be here. Gordorf had a splendid victory. Boatwreck and Epsilon. These are
rare scary monsters. I'm gonna die. Bug Batman versus kitty. Can I just leave? Can I just walk out?
That's not good. Maybe we should watch from the stands the rest of this.
Do I get money if he's showing up? What the fuck was that thing?
Um I want one of these. Where am I gonna get one of these? I've got this like stupid like
dementor that I I want one of these things. We will now hold the consolation match to take
the third place. What do I care? The final Boatwreck versus kitty. I mean kitty did 300 damage to me.
I don't I'm glad I didn't fight that guy. All right did I get any money?
I mean I was like an extra. Record loser? Oh I thought it meant I lost the fastest ever.
I need to make money. I'm gonna freeze him and I'm gonna go see if I can get toxic.
I don't think you can. I think I have to be like rank A to do it. All right let's try it. I'm gonna
try it. Put him on ice. The rare monsters I think you have to be A rank. I'll get Christmas Weezer.
Hold on a second. What does it take to combine? Combine 500 gold to combine. I'm gonna cheat here.
How do I save the game manually? I'm just cheating. I want to see what we get. I'm curious. 500 gold
and we're doing Bonnie and Bug Batman? Okay combine with you. What do I get?
Let's use an item as seasoning. Yes. Fisk chips. Seasoning. This can be used as a secret seasoning.
All right should we proceed? So there's a 31% chance we get a Kabalos. What's Terror Dog?
Blue. That's only five percent chance. Crimson-eyed blue sponge. Let's try noodle.
Yeah let's try a noodle. Bonnie and noodle? I'm curious. Or Bug Batman and noodle. We need the
blue sponge. PB and noodle. All right let's try that. Add some seasoning. Okay what do we get? 20%
chance for a Ripper. Allure. Basula. Ivory Wall. Ripper. Let's see these two. Gatton or Mint.
A Dayton? Mint? Dayton? Let's try it. Go for it. What do we get? Allure. Allure. Into the trash.
I don't want this. It's like it never happened. Um let's just see if we can get something else
interesting. I don't think I can get uh toxic. I think you have to be rank A. Yeah rare monsters
can only be- I gotta be rank B or A. Any other songs that you want me to try before I pull out?
Who should I play with? I think I'm gonna keep going with the um Spongebob? Spongebob Squarepants?
Super Spongebob Squarepants Battle for Bikini Bottom. Oh it's the actual game disc. Rehydrated?
Let's go. Come on. It's rare. Remember that. Spongebob Squarepants. Spongebob theme song
metal version. Stop being rare. That's annoying. What about Undertale? Undertale. Undertale soundtrack.
I gotta win a rank B match. That's the only way I can do it. There's nothing for the Simpsons
really? Limp Bizkit. Uh okay how about yeah chocolate starfish in the hot dog flavored water.
Give us something. Not this bullshit would have to be rank A. It's a piece of granite. Funny looking
monster. This thing is stupid. I mean I'll phrase it. What did I- I got one of these before. What
did I call it? It's just a wall again. Yeah. Oh Roblox. Well Sweetrind was not- Sweetrind was
like a watermelon wasn't it? Oh the Xbox Series X. Where's space? No no. Wait I can't do a space?
Freeze this motherfucker immediately. Train him. No he was sucked. I want to get one more. Team
Fortress. Sonic. Sonic Attack. Sonic Booms 1. Sonic by Soldier Boy. Alright. Rare. I hate when they're
rare. We're not good enough to open these. Crazy Frog. We already looked for Crazy Frog. Oasis.
Wonderwall. Everything is rare. Dragon Ball. I've seen too many names. Celine Dion? Really?
How is Celine Dion not here? Aerosmith. Aerosmith's greatest hits. Alright I'm just
gonna go win tournaments because like this is stupid. I want one more. Halo. Halo 4. Halo. Halo
4 original soundtrack. Finally we get to see a goddamn monster. Alright I'm interested. I'm
very interested. Dependable. That's a high defense. Those are good. It's kind of like crab. Crab
scorpion. Crab scorpion. Crab scorpion. Crab scorpion. Crab scorpion. Crab scorpion. Crab scorpion.
Master Chef. What are you doing? What are you doing? No stop it. Would you say what? Stop it.
Wellington. Actually I kind of like that. I like it. What is this? Is it a combination? Or is this
just a straight up crab thing? Let's take it. Why does he pick the worst one? Well how is it the
worst one? That's Wellington. I like it. Alright I need to know a lot about you. Who are you?
Alright you got pretty good skill already. Power is really good already.
You don't like cup jelly. You like battling. That's kind of unfortunate. Punch. Claw. Assault.
This is really good. Hit percentage. The force is bad on both these though. Bad scaling. But
at least you'll hit. Wellington is not a crab. And now you want me to freeze him after that?
After that shit? Are you serious? Alright what do we need? Power. I'm gonna say power. Intelligence
is real. It's definitely not intelligence. It's power and maybe speed. Power and defense. Alright
go for it. Let's see what you got. Right off the bat. That's alright. You're a baby. You just
figured it out. It's okay. It's okay. Don't worry. No you're fine. It's alright. Everything's fine.
I do want to buy more of those stress things. I need mint leaves. Somebody has to win a fight.
I'm gonna lose all my money. I need to take him through a tournament and just win. This is gonna
be bad. Okay no more. Stop spending. That was so cute. I love him. What'd you do to Weezer? I don't
know. Alright get some more power. Just enough to win a tournament. You got it right? Nice. Good job.
Level up. Perfect. Uh oh Jax you're running out of money. You better enter Wellington into a
tournament to make some bucks. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Right now. He's gonna do the voice
every time he says it isn't he? Whatcha doing? No stop. I just have to say a few things. Stop.
I love that. It's like my favorite thing about him. He's standing there like this. He goes like
this. He goes. Looks like it's raw. Not good in the middle. That's why. Absolutely. That's whatever.
I feel like I have pants on. I have pants on. Top half of your head was gone. Whatever. Who cares?
You're gaslighting us. Watch anything that Gordon Ramsay's ever done. He goes like up on his
on his heels. Like he goes on his toes. He puts his hands up like this. And he goes like up down
up up down. I'm serious. I love it. I think he has some amazing mannerisms. Alright let's kick some
He does the orangutan. Oh delicious. Absolutely delicious. Now in the pan. Did you put it in the
pan? I'm so sorry. Fucking idiot. Oh no. Oakley man is back. This is not good. New animated emote.
Actually might be okay. Damn that's good. We're about close. Not bad. That hits for a pretty
good amount. Job. Get back. I watch out the guts here. I can hit like two or three times and it's
over. Holy fucking shit dude. Give me a break. Wow. That was that was unbelievable. That just did so
much fucking damage. What a joke. What a joke. 80. He did almost 80 damage to me in one hit.
Wellington picked up the victory by default. Why? This is still winnable. I just have to beat Leon.
It should be a win. Back to back. Good. Back it up. No come on. I couldn't hit it. Alright go on.
How many coin flips am I gonna lose in a row? Kill this motherfucker. I'll just play it safe.
I don't want to get hit. Alright let's end it. Damn it. I don't think I can't beat Oakley man.
Okay. What keeps happening to Oakley man? He's always. I can do this. Started early. Alright
stop going for the big hit and just land the ones that have higher percentage. I'm not taking my own
advice. I don't know what I'm doing. 78 percent and he just gets confused. Thank you. He's got 99
guts. Why won't you swing? You make me look bad. I gotta do something. This is literally 10 seconds.
I fucking hit him. Swing at him. I'm just trapped in this stupid. He's zoning the fuck out of me
dude. Come on. That was stupid. I couldn't go left and I couldn't go right. Yeah yeah cool.
Excellent. At least I have enough to not go bankrupt again. Congrats to the guy that just
won 800,000 points. Are you serious? Jeez. Did you actually learn something? Alright that's good.
This is your first tournament. You almost won too. It's just like just to flip a goddamn coin if
you'll hit somebody or not. Isn't this guy's skill high? What's the problem here? You got 150 skill
at rank E. What's the problem? What's your problem? What's your problem? I don't understand. What's
your problem? You can rest. He doesn't like cup jelly right? It's not good because that's
something that lowers stress. I don't want any tablets. It's way too expensive. What did he like?
Milk? Fish? Maybe milk? Nutritious milk? Oh he likes battling. He doesn't have a preference.
Alright if you don't have a preference then I'm just gonna give you fish. Alright it's that time
of the day. It doesn't matter what it is. Whatever I see first in the chat is gonna be what I order
for food. We got new mail. It's gonna be Erentree isn't it? Alright if it's Erentree then I'm gonna
go freeze him and go use the other guy. It is. Alright. Alright. Fuck this. How much money do I
have? Alright there's a D rank battle right now. I'm gonna go freeze him. I'm gonna bring out.
I don't even remember their name. It was the snake. I'm gonna win this tournament and then I'm gonna
he has to learn. I gotta go freeze Wellington. Frozen Wellington. Disgusting. Really?
Frozen Wellington. You know I have to get rid of him because I'm not gonna stop doing that so
I would I probably should just freeze him. Frozen Wellington. No more fucking around. I gotta go
win the tournament and then do Erentree with that snake guy. Wake up bug Batman. Get out here.
What you doing? No stop. What you doing? Leave me alone. You're gonna fuck me up. I'm gonna have to
say it a hundred times. Shit he's so tired. It wins the next battle? Alright I have an idea.
Take this and then fight. You're definitely strong enough to do a D cup. Please win me this money.
Two thousand bucks and then we're gonna let you you can rest a few days then we're gonna send you
on a trip. Go for it. Only four contestants. It's not a big deal. Rank D. It's not gonna be hard.
Oh it's this motherfucker. This guy's gonna ruin everything.
Not sleep bomb. I have to come in second place. This is bad. I just did I was just a burn fight.
He's got so much more health but his skill and speed are awful. I just have to hope he
misses over and over again and just try to burn him down. Get up close. Miss. 70 fucking three
percent. Get out of town. Move. Bash his fucking skull and hurry up. Don't do another move. Dodge
it. Dodge it. Dodge it. Dodge it. Oh my god I killed him. I win. Okay that was very very stressful.
Don't lose my points. I want one of these. This thing is so cool. I actually want one of these
things. My webcam needs to be moved. It's too big. That's better. Alright two grand. That was
the hardest fight of the whole entire time. Come on now. Hella lost. Alright I'm fired. The thing
that's gonna kill me here is the high defense. Pretty evenly matched though. I got more health.
Give me a crit. Oh dodge is nice. Dodge again. I got him in guts. I got him I've beaten him in guts.
70 percent. Hit it. Combo. Fuck you. Yes. Oh that was so close. That would have been really bad if
I didn't win this. This is gonna save the whole run. I just need Winston to lose. Come on sleep bomb.
Get it. This guy every time. Is it just because he's faster? Alright well this is it. Stay in close.
Same thing. Don't be an idiot. I can take the hits. It's fine. I can hit him harder.
70 percent. Doesn't hurt. Two grand. Now I can definitely beat C. Get a new move. I'll get a
bonus. I'll get some of the fame back too which I lost it all. This game sucks and it's even worse
if you aren't good at it. How do you know this game sucks? You play it yet? He did the thing. He
did the thing. What? That's good. Uh praise. You don't like the game. You don't like the game.
You want to participate in a tournament and fight and you just did. That's gonna be really. I can't
do that. You just did one. Alright now we need some real rest. This game is one of the best games
ever to watch. Um it's whatever man. Like I knew when this was coming out I was gonna play it a lot.
So this is what we're doing and if people think it's fun that's awesome because I think it's fun.
I love this game and we're going to beat this game. Not like last time. Last time I did B rank
and I stopped playing it. We're going to beat. We're going to get to at least A to S rank. We're
going to. But no I mean I was fucking around earlier right? Like if you don't like the game
and you think this sucks then it's alright. I'm still good. See you next time. Alright so we should
go to uh alright our entry time. Please. Skill and life. This is gonna be it. We're gonna learn new
move. Finally. You know what? Go kill one of these guys too. Like Norty. Go fucking strangle Morty.
We can handle Morty. Come on. Good. Good start. Really good start. Plus like 15 or something.
Plus 20. That's alright. The shark part I just have to. I got a skill? What? I didn't even see
it. I didn't even see it. I got a skill. Did I? Oh damn this is awesome. Alright come on. Give me
over 200 skill. I want to fuse this guy with somebody. Take out the sharks. Yes! Come on.
Keep going. This is huge. This is the last one. Gigantic crab. Oh he got knocked down. Is that bad?
Oh that's it? Did I get it? I don't know what counts as a success here. What's going on?
What's happening? Did I lose? What are you doing? What the fuck is wrong with you?
I wonder how many failure points are here and I think I just did it.
Fall down. One last punch. Dude get him. Oh fuck. I don't this. That's alright.
There was probably 10 different failure points there. It seems pretty strong. Praise. Praise.
Let's go take a look. I'm really curious. Did you just become top tier? Alright come on. What do you
got? Whack and stab. Oh thank god. Finally. It took long enough. Now I can actually hit people
without a problem. Hit percent A. It does withering and sharpness. Yeah we'll keep these two on.
Thank goodness. Excellent. Excellent. Excellent. Excellent. Let's go. Okay there's a C today but
I can't do it. We'll try the C one next week. So let's take. Let's go rest. Take some nut oil.
Maybe some stress reduction. Keep the horror. Sure. I'm not doing that ever again. I want to get to
200. Is it next week? It's not. Wait is it next week? That's not. Good work. 200 finally. I think
I'm good for skill for now. And we're gonna do tablets and see if I can get a little bit more
power. Yeah I'm gonna do the heavy training I think because I need to hit harder. Alright so
it's rest. Is he ready for C? I don't know. I need more speed. What kind of monster feeds his pet
gummy vitamins for an entire month? I just pulled my first monster and all the stats were under 10.
That sounds awful. Let me take a look again. I don't think it's enough. I think we have to skip
this tournament. 300 power. Get back to over 100 speed. I need health too. Yeah I'm gonna skip the
tournament. When's the next one after that? Alright we're gonna be ready for the official one. So
we're gonna do some training. I want to get. Let's go for the heavy one. Come on don't fail it. You
can't fight every single week man. You can't fight. I keep losing loyalty because he wants to fight
every week. It's like you have to rest man. Get up there. 300. Close. Close. Errantry again. Look at
this. It's from Auntie Verde. She's having a sale at her shop. Oh that's. Yeah I need that. I use
these items all the time. How much is it per percentage? Great discount. Not that much. Like
10% off. 20% off. Whatever. I mean I need them. Alright don't run out of money.
20%. What's up with that? How much can I get for.
I don't want the chips. Okay so we're going to train speed. I want to get this back over 100.
Does that count? Truancy? It's what he took off? Rest. Your boy is soft. Try it again.
Don't run away this time. Nice job. Alright back up to over 100. That's good. Very important.
I'm running out of money. So we're going to do fish. Why are you playing with this dingleberry?
Jelly. He doesn't like jelly. But no wait no he does. He's the other one that didn't like it.
It's going to be a 24 hour stream. I don't think that would work considering I'm
streaming the game awards tomorrow. Only two more of those tops.
Official tournament. Let's see if we can get it. How much time do I have?
Alright so it's train train rest C. What are we doing here? Should I go for some omega speed?
Dump it into power. Health probably. I'll do health. Nah I'll do health. It's a good idea.
Don't cheat. You're cheating. But I'm not going to scold you. Dude I want to participate in a
tournament. Yes you can. No it's not even next week. It's the week after. Get it up over there.
I'm going to feed him a mango. But will that make him happy? Yeah have a mango. Maybe that'll make
him more loyal. Not really. Okay rest up. I don't think I'm going to be able to beat this. Maybe
I'll try one of the lower ones then. C rank or should I try for C rank? I need money. Ungrateful
prick. I'm going to get my ass kicked. I'm going to get my ass kicked. Come on. I got over 300
power. 200 skill. Sussvane had. Wasn't that bad. Okay Huey. I got that new move too. Jesus.
What do you have for intelligence moves? Do not go anywhere near. Holy shit I can't believe
anything hit by Garfield's fucking laser hands. Stab him. Stab. Oh god damn it. Holy shit do it
again. Stay in. Don't let him push you. That move is sick. Fuck. Don't let him hit you. Don't let
him push you. No don't get hit by his laser cannons. It's alright. I can still come in second
or third place. Sussvane didn't even hurt this guy. I want. I want one of those. I want one of
those monkeys. Alright. Recknen. What do you have for stats? I'm just barely not good enough for
this. Defense is terrible though. Just got to stay in. It's going to just come down to who hits who
because we both have the same amount of skill he has. We both have power. He's got more health.
Just stay in there and stab him. Good dodge. Fuck off. Fuck you. Tails. Tails. Tails. Tails. Tails.
77. You won't swing the bat. Swing. I'm feeling like a fucking grandpa is yelling at a baseball
game. Swing. Hit him. Good. Get in there. Again. Stab. Fuck you. Hit him. Oh my fucking god.
Every time. It's just. Every time. Can I ever get this guy to have more than 47 percent? 50 percent?
I've been dumping and dumping and dumping and dumping and dumping stats into skill.
I got over 100 fucking extra points. I got to start winning games. Actually mad. Yeah I guess
I want to win. This is the guy that's beating everybody in with flawless victories. I'm not
even going to be able to get one. Well actually hold on. His defense is crazy. He's going to have
like a 30 percent chance to hit and he's just going to have to hit me one time and I'm dead.
Good luck. Can I dodge? My speed's awful. What is so confusing? No. Don't let him swing once. Back up.
Back up. Back up. All right go forward. Hit him. Back him up. Okay. I think I'm all right. Run in
and stab him. Oh my god. How do you miss this? It's impossible. I'm just holding left. Let's go.
We're good. I just can't lose. You literally fought a rock. Yeah and he was huge.
Sussvane is losing a lot. Yeah this Huey is going to win. He has like eight moves. He had this like
fire breath. He had a laser cannon. He had a dashing claws. I don't know. He was all over the place.
All right this is the monkey. I am very scared as I should be. I don't see how I win here.
But get lucky. Nice. All right. All right. All right. Hold off on the guts. All right. 60%. Keep
it going. Don't let him get near you. He is out of guts though. Four guts. Are you shitting me?
Just string it together. He can't do anything. Again. Again. Again. Again. Again. He can't do
anything. He has no. He has no mana. Dodge. What is so confusing? Oh what's he doing to my Wellington?
Come on. Got him. Why are you guys saying Trump? Did I sound like Trump?
I am actually still in this if I don't lose another one. Oh shit. He lost. Good. Okay. This
should be a pretty decent victory. This should be easy. He's the lost three times. Trump voice. I
need to hear this. I want to know what he's talking about. Why did I say that? What was that for?
Okay. Let's go. I think this guy's intelligence. I don't know how this person has lost three times.
Bad defense but everything else is really good. Even the power. All right. Well do not stay in
range of any green attacks so get the fuck in close now. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Just hit him one more time. Watch the guts.
Oh my god. What the fuck did he just do? You stupid game. This game's fucking rigged.
I can't believe it just died. Yeah. I literally just pressed one button and I died instantly.
How am I supposed to get away from that? I'm not an intelligence character so I just die?
I'm trying to stay in but he can like push it. Batman sucks. Yeah this is bullshit. I'm Batman
and go up against a bunch of fucking superheroes. Oh I got money and can aim good. Cool. These guys
have laser eyes. Your defense is too low? Yeah but it but okay. All right. Hear me out. Intelligence
moves. Defense means nothing. You only you take less damage from intelligence moves based on your
intelligence skill yourself. So if I'm not building an intelligence character then I'm gonna get
killed by the intelligence moves. You have no money and can't aim. So what are you? Um I don't know.
What? All right. This guy sucks except for his skill. He's just this is just a mirror match
except he's kind of better than I am. I would love to do a move. My guy doesn't know what what
fucking state he's in. I'm gonna get flawless now aren't I? My loyalty is not high enough so if I
try to tell him to do a move he blacks out. This guy's blacking out like 10 times a match because
we don't have a great relationship together or something. Why is he blacking out? Why is he so
confused? Into the freezer. No he's the best thing we got right now. I can't. I gotta at least beat
Zambor. Come on. It's time for some. All right how do I build loyalty? What's like the what what can
I buy him? What item can I give him to make him more loyal? Best you actually have is probably
Wellington. Probably actually. Don't come in last place I'll be happy. One more. Good. Oh shit.
Oh thank god. Uh I mean I I'm not gonna get any money but maybe I'll get fame.
Possible that I'll get fame? Hard to tell. How can you beat him without the last two?
Threw coins in the air and whatever one landed on heads three times that's the one I wouldn't.
He needs more loyalty that's why. The more loyalty he has the more. All right loyalty is like the
most important stat in my opinion at this point. Because if you tell him to do moves
and a third of the moves you tell him to do he doesn't do. I mean that's I'm just gonna that's
less damage. I'm not gonna get any money but will I at least get fame or something? I got 300 bucks
that's not okay I'm happy with that. Fame? What about auto fight? The problem with auto fight is
from what I've heard the CPU is notoriously notoriously unbelievably stupid apparently.
Like sometimes it just won't just will walk around it won't do anything. Very nice.
You tried. You tried your best. I need to win a tournament. Maybe this one or I gotta win money.
Well get him ready for this one. Should I just rest him up and just kind of fight the D?
I can't do crap. I'm not good enough for C. Maybe I should uh I need the I need $2,000.
It's so important. Rest him up. Get into that tournament and win. I actually will lose. I will
soft lock myself. All right let's go win this. You can't go lower than zero so don't worry.
I love this game. It's so much fun. I love just like needing to do better and try harder and train
better. You gotta make a golem or a jelly they're both pretty pog in my opinion. The naga is good
only once it's been trained to shitload. What don't okay so different types peak at different
places right? So from my understanding is some some of the base monsters like year one is where
you peak and you get the most amount of stat increases. Some of them are like year three near
old age you get the most amount of stat increases. Where what is this type? Is this later on in life
or third monsters have different growth spritz? Yeah so the base that I have here is peaking now
okay. Why are you doing the German explain thing? Dude you peaked in high school. I actually didn't
though. I peaked it I don't know like 10 to 5 years ago. I didn't peak in high school. I definitely
have passed my peak of I don't know I think maybe I'm coming down. I think I still got it though.
Did you see that tiktok orangutan dance? All right let's let's win. I need money. All right
bounce it back. Bounce it back. 40. I'm good. The thing is I'm not even ranking down to do this.
I haven't won a sea cup elimination tournament. So I mean like I got held back like six times in
the eighth grade. I'm still in the eighth grade right? Yeah I'm like 19 in the eighth grade.
Is that even possible? I don't think so. What happens? I don't think that happens. What happens
if you get held back like four times? Once you hit the soft cap for the first year you have to go
to the shrine and ask to reset there. I thought you're talking about what happens if you stay
back four times. You have to go to a shrine? I was trying to figure out what the fuck you're talking
about. Okay stay away from the intelligence moves I think. This stab is really good just to farm
these lower ranks though. These characters don't die. How long do the um what are the types that
I have? I think I have a wall right? The obsidian wall and it's a wall. It's a bug in Batman.
You have Wellington. I know but I have to make money. I have to make money and I have to get to
at least C or B rank so I can at least. This monster is peaking right now so I have to train
this monster. Try to win at least to like B or A rank so then I can actually get some cool monsters
and rare ones. I will let Wellington shine I promise. Maybe I'll combine them. Should I combine
Wellington and Bug Batman? Maybe I'll get maybe that'd be better. All right that's cute. Bye bye.
Uh Winston's passed away. You actually they actually can die. All right two thousand dollars
twenty two hundred maybe you'll get a little bit of fame. You have to get to at least C with this
monster. This game's like Dark Souls. You're supposed to just lose a bunch of times until
you get like the right combo. 2150. Go to Nagile whatever that is. Learned more? Yes.
You can't do a tournament back to back. No that. What's wrong with this guy? Why don't you ask me
that? Is it a re- what? Retire? You're not even two years old. What do you mean retired?
You're getting old? How long did they live? Are you shitting me? They die one year and eight months.
He's 68. You need to start training Bug Robin. Okay battle. When's the next- okay here it is.
He's gonna win this. He's gonna get to B rank. We're gonna freeze his ass and then we're gonna
combine him with Wellington and then we're gonna have a good base stats there. We'll take Wellington
all the way up to B rank. I gotta- I'm not gonna stop screaming am I? I'm like having two of a
time right now. I love this game. Uh I'll be all right. All right so this he's getting to the end
here. Well let's rest him up. See if we can take him to at least up to B rank which then combine
him with Wellington and see what we get. Go for it. All the way. Nice. Yeah we're really starting
to lose the uh prime there. It was like 18, 19, 18, 17, 18, 18. Now it's 9. All right but I don't
think I want to give anything too expensive. What's for dinner? I don't know. Train. Let's do- what
if I- I really need life maybe? At this point maybe I should just go all in on power. Just hope for
the best. What do you think? I gave him a cup of jelly for his last meal. He gets to eat- he'll eat
one more time. 300. Um I don't think I'll even be able to beat rank C. I think we freeze him now.
Past the prime here. 314. Seems well- not even tired. Get him- we'll get him in one more tournament.
What happens when they die? Um they die. Oh unless I freeze him. I can freeze him and combine him
which is what I'm gonna do that. That's kind of the point. I'm not gonna use any more stress
reducers on him either. Yeah there's a little funeral. There's a little like goodbye. All right.
Can we do it? Train twice. Rest. I'm just going straight power. Just power. There is no tournament
next week. Hope somebody freezes me when I get old and pass my prime. That was good. Seems well.
One more training session. This is the last time we will ever train this piece of absolute dog
shit. All right rest up. It's time to battle. I'm just kidding. I'm very fond of this uh this
little guy. Okay very well. Loyalty is pretty good. I don't- I think we're gonna get our ass kicked
but I'll try it. It's three moves and then into the freezer. Have increased my power by like 20
plus percent though. Some new faces here. All right. Xamber. Let's go. 330. High defense but
I do- I have a lot of power. Let's go for it. Let's see if I can just get in there and smash.
Don't want to get hit by that. Good start. Keep it up. Don't do anything yet. Go for it. Very good.
All right. Just hang back a little bit. Don't get killed. I need 14 guts to do this move.
Don't even you dare. Okay thank god. Win us a championship before retirement. Come on man.
You're gonna stream till like 12 a.m. Uh well we started really late because the game didn't come
out till 5 pacific. We will absolutely be playing this tomorrow. I have to beat the game. Tomorrow
is the game awards at 4 or 5 p.m pacific. I'll figure whatever it is. And then after the game
awards game awards are gonna be what like two three hours. We're gonna go right from the game awards
to this for like another three or four hours. We're 30? Yeah. Well we'll start around the same
time we did today. But I'm not done tonight. I still- I have- at least I want to get through.
I want to combine somebody and get a good round floor for the next monster. Yeah what is that
little thing? Offry? All right we got our ass kicked by Reckton last time. But it's a new day.
Just shred through that defense. It's a DPS race. I hope I can actually do moves. Dodge again.
Nice. All right. Okay okay okay okay. All right get in there. He's using all his guts.
Beautiful. All right this is good. One more. All right back it up. I- we're in pretty good shape.
We'll be at B rank. That little weirdo. Hey who said he was past his prime? Not yet. Another weak.
Maybe. All right this is the 2-0. Offry. I'm very curious of how strong you are. Okay you're very
very weak but you're impossible to hit. Stay in close. The intelligence moves are gonna kill me
in one hit. Get in close close close close close. Fuck! Stay in close. He can't even hurt you. Just
stay in close. Let the guts build up. He's gonna waste all of his toy hammer bullshit. Just don't
let him do an intelligence move. Okay get him. Yes! Take that motherfucker outside. Yes. Okay is
anybody else undefeated? Pivorous is currently undefeated. Pivorous. Not anymore. I'm gonna lose
to Sussmane. He's a mirror. Let's get in there. That's why you're so dangerous. You have a lot
of health. Not a lot of defense though. You're just a gigantic damage sponge. All right get in there.
Jesus Christ. Please. Watch that. I'm gonna build up guts. Don't just spam. This is how he wins fights.
He's just a like watermelon chewing gum. That's fine. Use it all. Go. I have to hit him like three times
and go. Oh get that. Get out of here. Now just don't die from. Now just let it just wait it out.
Stay in close and wait it out. Got it. Yeah you build up a bunch of speed. You build up a bunch of
health and then you become. You get hit two or three times. Doesn't matter. You can dodge the rest.
Is. Have I secured it? I think I have to win one more match and it's secured.
I know. Because if I have five wins it's impossible for anybody else to get to five wins right?
As long as he doesn't die on the floor then we should be fine.
If he dies in the arena then that's bad. I think can happen. All right here comes a real test. This
guy beat me bad last time. This is the monkey. It's gonna take a Christmas miracle to not lose
to this guy. I want to get hit by the intelligence moves so I have to stay back and then run forward
when I want to do something. All right back it up. I want to get hit by his INT move. What does
that do? They're booing him from eating a banana. Okay stay back. In. Back it up. That's fine. That's
fine. That's not a problem. Don't. There's so much. There's so much like tug of war going on here.
Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh. Uh oh. Holy shit. Thank god. That would have probably done 100 damage.
That was really really lucky. I win. Do I win? Okay. Reckonin? No. Pivorous needs to win the
rest of his games and Offry needs to win the rest of his games and it's a tie. Who's next?
Okay Reckonin needs to beat Pivorous right? Oh it's over. No. Okay. Reckonin needs to win right now.
There it is. Okay now Offry has to lose their next match. Zambor is lost every single time but
let's see. Well it's gonna be me versus Offry in the championship. Unless I win right now.
This is what it comes down to. This is to secure uh the C rank championship. I'm looking to try
to get hit by the INT moves if he has any on his bar which he doesn't so this is gonna be
just a fight. It's a mirror match. Good luck. Yes! That's it. C rank. C rank championship baby.
Hell yeah. It's the last thing this guy's ever gonna see unfortunately. Well no he's gonna
be combined. His DNA is gonna get combined with somebody else. I did not have any faith at all.
That was that was my mistake. I should have given him some um encouragement. Now we'll have access
to B rank which is great. If I go seven and oh though I'll get a ton of fame I think. All right
what is what monster is this? Nicole? It's like a cat. You're just hard to hit. That's all. Nothing
is too scary. Just have to hit you a few times. There's one. That's all I need. That secures it
I think. As long as I don't get hit by something horrible here. This just drains my mana. Still
win by percentage here. God you're a pain in the ass. Still win by percentage. Oh my god what I
don't I what's what's the percentage? Wow that was annoying. That was annoying. That's all right.
Sometimes a champion can't go undefeated. Let them play out the rest of the tournament. Whatever.
Why is the cat winning? Uh high speed and annoying moves that drain guts.
Nice work. Did he lose every single match? Zambor lost every match. I know what that's like. I can't
talk shit. Only 16 fame. I was almost undefeated in the tournament. Perfect. Perfect combination
here. Good job. You got us a B rank. You don't want to fight. You want to rest. It's time to rest.
What food are you gonna get? Uh I got five grand. Holy shit. I'm making money now.
Have a cup of jelly. You did good. Who is it? Oh I think this is it. Do I actually get to
become like an actual trainer? Rank three right? Oh yeah. Professional. I am now I can now open up
those other boxes. It's time for toxic. Very good job. Good work. So before we do anything let's
freeze you. I'll be using you later. Don't forget about spot. Yeah I gotta remember the exact ones.
All right the first one was spongebob square pants and it was the which one was it battle
rehydrated. All right this is this one. Generate. I'm not an authorized trainer. Very high level.
I need to have I need special rank. All right how about uh Christmas by Christmas by Paul Cardale.
What you got Paul? Cosmic stone. That's pretty good. 168 intelligence. Hold on to it for now.
Cosmic order. That's cosmic order. Cosmic calamity. Close enough. Cosmic calamity. All right freeze
this motherfucker. Wait hold on. Save the game. I'm gonna combine this and the and the other one.
These are really good base stats. If I combine this with the dragon this could be pretty big.
Save again. Okay let's do it. Yeah freeze. Cosmic Andy. Oh yeah Cosmic Andy. That's my favorite
character. I need something good. Bug Batman. Cosmic calamity. Doesn't know what the sub is.
What is that? That's a secret sub. See I saved it. That's a rare subtype. That's why it looks
cosmic. Crimson eyed. Oh that's already what Bug Batman already is a crimson eyed. No. All right
what about Wellington and cosmic calamity. Noodle and cosmic calamity. This can be used as secret
seasoning. Prospect here is unsure. Silhouette. I think I'm just gonna get cosmic calamity.
That's like a rare subtype. Why don't you just level that one up. I'm just gonna use the wall.
Why not? I might as well use it. Let's get really awesome base stats too. Yeah let's bring out
calamity. Let's go. 168 base intelligence. That's awesome. I'm sorry about the music. I can't help
it. All right let's go. What do you like? Likes meat and doesn't like tablets. Are you off putting?
Flattening and charge. No intelligence move. I need to we gotta get him out there. It's just way
too high. Study of the little bird. Scary. I almost fell out of the chair. I slipped. Try to
get him to 200 before we take him to a tournament. He's supposed to be smart. Let's do a little bit
of the mint leaf. Base sucks. Yeah it's scary. Definitely can't do F rank. Let's go. We'll do
this one. Should be all right. How do you cheat? Don't cheat. I mean don't cheat. Use that oil.
Academic dishonesty. Anyone know how long the walls live in general? You like meat. All right
we'll give you meat. Two weeks. 100 years. We'll do this one. Maybe we'll just wait till. I think I
could bring him now. He needs an intelligence move. I gotta look at his stats again. Once he gets to
200 intelligence I'm doing something else. Although honestly I really probably shouldn't even be doing
this because he doesn't even have an intelligence move. I should be doing something else. Health
probably. Health and skills. Whoa that speed though. Holy. Whoa that's bad. Seems well. When's that
battle? Nope. Yeah we'll just do the official one. I'm gonna keep doing this till he gets to 100.
He'll get hit by everything. I hate this wall. Take a hammer to it already. Health maybe? Yeah.
How does a wall run? He's cheating. Why are they? I have so many bad natured people. It's gold.
This looks like a PS2 loading screen. I know you don't want tablets but I'm gonna give them to you.
Tablets are always a good decision. The benefits well outweigh the fact that he doesn't like it.
Air entry? Yeah okay. I wonder. Should we just do it? I've got money. Should I just try? I know when
they're like a baby baby under under three or four months it's usually not worth it. I need an
intelligence move. Really bad. I have to get him an intelligence move. It's on sale right now.
It's just way too young. I'm gonna try to get the move. Will it not? It won't work.
Save and do it. All right so now it doesn't matter. I'll rest up though because I want him to be very
well rested. If I actually get an intelligence move this is gonna be huge. Sorry I swallowed the
back of my tongue. If I get an intelligence move it's gonna be huge. Okay. Int. There it is.
Go for it. There's a chance to acquire a new technique. You can fight that guy who cares. Go
for it. Monkey race. Beat him. Oh the block. Is that technically cheating? He's gonna be a big
deal now. I really hope that's an intelligence move because if it is then he's this is the new
this guy will bring us to be at least. We'll get B rank with this guy. Heard? Good job. Very good.
Very good. This is huge. Go all the way. Get another skill. It's all right. It's okay. It's
all right. You got to move. That's all that mattered. It's okay. Try again. Try it again.
There's another chance. Boom. Break out. Get out of the way. Dodge it. That's okay. All that matters
is the move. Good job. Nice work. Seems pretty tired. Give it some rest. What is the move?
Scratch. Why did you learn scratch? And it sucks. Okay. I can't do that. We're gonna have to do this
one. Round robin. Four entries. Thousand gold. Go for it. Speed again. Load the save. No I mean
he's got a new move. He gained a lot of stats too. Uh three weeks. Do some oil. What song was this
from? I think this is from Christmas by Paul. Something like that. Christmas by Paul. Did I
just rest? He's tired. Tired is he? Did I just rest? Or should I rest? I forgot. Build the loyalty up.
Yeah. Yeah I'm not gonna be left. I'm gonna stop the stream soon. We'll come back at it tomorrow.
Eleven thirty. Eleven. Okay. All right. Yeah we'll end. We'll end soon. Oh give him a cup of jelly.
Stress. I want to fight at least one time and then we'll end.
I lifted up. Your model is a rare class that's the highest ranked model type.
But your naga is a d-class and basically garbage breed. Really? Okay let's uh let's eat that
stress reducer. Train a little bit and maybe some intelligence. Thinking about maybe a little bit
of intelligence. Batman got farther than the dumb slab ever will. I don't I think he's gonna be
all right. All right battle is I don't know I don't have I gotta just do E.
I definitely do not have what it takes. Rest. Gonna go to bed? I will soon. Very soon. We'll
see it. We'll I'll be around tomorrow. Game words. It's bottom it's like bottom five monsters in the
game. Are you serious? That sucks. All right after this we'll I'll be done. This train a little bit
more and then we'll go from here. Maybe one more tournament. Maybe. I got a defense. I got high
defense. Let's try that new move. Scratch. I mean it's kind of funny looking. 85% you won't even
do anything. Come on man. Oh that hurts guts too. That move is fucking stupid. Good. Good. Be close.
Dodge it. I think that's a win. No more bets. Yeah no more betting. I want to get to a point
where I have 800 power and shit. You know what I mean? I've only peed once today. Or she drinks
some water. I drank water right here. Uh just go for the one that hits. Which is flattening.
Unless this little shit beat me please. Oh my god am I gonna lose for the first time ever?
The rabbit. It can't happen. He's gonna KO me. Do something. What the fuck? The rabbit is the
shittiest enemy in the whole game and I actually lost. All right I have to beat you. How did you
not get an intelligence move? I don't understand. Get it get it get it get it get it get it get it
combo combo combo combo. Back this shit up. No. 62% swing at him. 85. He just his loyalty is too
low. Tried to bring him in too early. Damn it. I thought I had that too. At least I get the money
back. It's fine. That's okay. Uh I'm not praising you at all. I'm sorry but you don't get praised.
Style even. I don't want to. The last character was so spoiled he wouldn't listen to half the
things I said. Send his ass on an errand tree. It's too expensive right now but I want to.
Official tournament. He's not ready. Actually just not ready. I need at least 30 to 40 loyalty. Not
worth it. I want to send him on an errand tree so bad. Not going to though. Don't do it. Just train
normally. I'll eventually get an intelligence move. I will. That was pretty good. How much garlic do
you have to eat to become handsome? A couple cloves a month. Eat the banana. I think the banana is
killing me. That's another good one. Probably seven or eight. Damn. Why buff intelligence with
no moves? Well because there's a certain finite amount of time in a monster's life that they will
gain stats. They'll gain way more stats than they would when they were a baby or when they're older.
So I'm just trying to dump intelligence into this motherfucker. So eventually when I get if I just
hammer intelligence I'll be able to get him an intelligence move and he'll have like 400 intelligence
and I'll laser beam people in one second and he'll be gone. Gone. Disintegrated. Intelligence again.
After this one I will. I'm gonna do one more tournament. No I'm not. Errand tree. He is.
Fuck the errand tree. Forget the errand tree. He's got so much health. So much. Not health.
Whatever. He's getting a lot of intelligence from this. Do it again. Just do it again. He's
killing it. Little ding. There it is. All right. I need an intelligence move. Okay. Probably.
Should I send him on an errand tree and just say screw it? And well I really want to unfreeze
Batman and do a tournament. Rest up. You're going on an errand tree tomorrow. If I lose all my money
whatever I'll just bring Batman out of retirement and just have him win a C rank or something or a
B rank or a D rank. Why are you even increasing intelligence? How smart do you have to be to just
crush someone? But look at him. He's made out of galaxies and planets and stars and stuff.
He's eventually gonna be able to learn a move that is gonna be like a galaxy bomb or something.
I don't know. He's like he's intelligence based right? All right let's save it.
Errand tree intelligence. Let's go. 2,000 bucks. Don't care. Intelligence. There is some chance to
acquire a new technique. Go after this guy. Come on. I'm looking for 10 intelligence each time.
Beautiful. Bruising past 200 plus intelligence at this young of an age. He's a little genius.
We got a raid? Oh shit there's a raid. Who raided? Oh shit. Atriarch. What's going on? Thanks for the
raid. We did it. That's a big raid. That's a lot of people. What's going on? Thanks for the raid man.
Playing Monster Rancher 2. The new meta of Twitch. Guaranteed. Don't let me be the one to tell you.
All right we didn't do this one last time. Stop doing that. I'm not doing a tuber voice. I'm just
being in person. He couldn't make it last time. He's gonna get up there this time. I guarantee it.
Do it. He's got it. He's got it. He's got it. He's got it. Oh that's slick. Any new technique?
No new technique. Got one more chance. Big gorilla. He's gonna knock it out of the park
and he's gonna get an intelligence technique and everyone, all the haters, all the doubters,
are gonna be shut up right now. Welcome everybody. Did I hit him in the bum? I'm hot. This is to prove
how intelligent I am by fucking with a wild gorilla. Is this intelligent or is this really stupid?
Stop pretending to be normal. I'm fine. I'm not normal. He got it. I think he actually did it.
New technique. Oh shit. I have to fight this. Low defense. High health. I was gonna crush this guy.
Just scratch him and crush him. I don't even play. It's the computer. Fight him. Come on. Get in there
and smash. Smoosh him. The computer is so stupid. Stop just touching. Stop walking into him and crush
him flat like this. Like a pancake. There's no timer either. It's just something you have to die.
Do some other move please. He just has to hit it. Good. Not good. One damage. Attack him.
He probably has 80 plus guts right now. There it is. That's what we wanted to see. Do it again.
I don't think it's gonna happen. Come on. The scratch is the best move I have right now and
he needs to start using it or just bow. What was the bow for? Do something. Oh you did a move
finally. Great. Very good. It's close. Do it. Get him. Get him. Good. I have to hit him three
more times. Again. Do it again. This idiot has two other moves. He's not doing any of them.
He might actually win by doing this over and over again. He's clutching it out right now.
This could be huge. Alright. Yeah. Shoulder tackle. Shoulder tackle again. You got it in you?
He just fucking won. You just beat him. You actually just beat him. Actually just won.
Give me a new technique. I did the whole thing. Great Cosmic Calamity. It's an easy battle to win
against those guys. Let's go back. I didn't get prize money. Oh it was 50% off because we won.
Beated a wild monster. It's wonderful. It could not acquire any techniques but its
parent tree was very successful. It was. I think you can catch them. Pretty tired. Alright.
Look at this data here. This guy is going to be at 300 intelligence before the first
goddamn tournament. Go to YouTube and type worst monster rancher 2 monster. It's literally this
one. What? Is it actually the worst one? Do I just have this so wrong? But he looks cool.
Let me turn this down. I can't hear this. Raising the worst monster in the game. Are you fucking
kidding me? I know if it's too loud, too quiet, anything like that. It looks very well. What?
It's a good one. I must have done it. It's not what it can't be. What? It wasn't paying
attention at all. What does it say at the end? Plus three again. Plus three again. 500? That's
500. Plus three again. I want to hear him say. Plus one. What's wrong? We died. He's dead? What
do you mean he's dead? Cole, I'm sorry about Proxima. Is it actually the worst monster in
the whole game? This is the worst combination in the game. I'm way too invested. Read the
description of that video. Bugs and bad stat growth make Monal just terrible to try and raise.
Worse than Metalners since at least Metalner live a hundred weeks longer. We try to raise
Proxima the best we can and beat the major four. But what if they fix the bugs maybe in this release?
His first intelligence learned move he gets when intelligence and speed are over 400. Are you telling
me I gotta ice this guy because I can't even do this? Are you kidding me? Over 400 intelligence?
What if I get to 400? I'm gonna get him to 400. All right, so I get him to 400, which we're not
even that far away. He needs 400 speed. Oh, that is not gonna happen. Wait, it's 400 combined
intelligence and speed. So not 400 each. People are saying something about the Papa's Errantry?
You need to do the Papa's Errantry to unlock strange light, which is an int move in the slot
before scratch. Okay, so I think I'm there. All right, so I gotta get to 330 intelligence.
Easiest thing I've ever done in my life. Let's go. I gotta leave. I'm so sorry I just like screamed
in your ear. I did not think it was gonna be that loud. Yeah, it's time to go. It's time to go.
I'll be live tomorrow. We'll pick right up tomorrow. Don't worry. Read the comments on that video.
If you see this, it'd be so great to see playthroughs with all the unique monsters.
This is nostalgic. Oh, you guys. Well, you know what? I'll tell you. This guy, Jack of Hearts,
got Monster Rancher 2 channel pretty much like doing Monster Rancher 2 shit. It should fucking
stop for this person. Give us a delayed raid song. I'm gonna just put the camera off. Thank you
for the rain. I see Monster Rancher 2 tomorrow as well as the game awards. I don't know what
I'll do first. Probably game awards first. So I can just go right from that directly into this.
Game awards. Let me actually look that up and get a correct time for you here. Thanks for sticking
around this long. I'm surprised that this many people still here. It's very, very late, but I'm
gonna play this game a lot. At least get to the end. I can't promise there'll be a face cam on
every time, but you know, whatever. This game's incredible. It's a lot of fun. It's just a good
time, so we're going to keep having it. Yeah, that's it. We'll end it there. Game awards are
what time? They are 4.30? Yeah, 4.30. I'll be live at like 4.15 just to kind of chill and wait for
the broadcast to go live. So I'll be live at 4.15 Pacific time in the afternoon tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves. Thanks for watching, everybody. I'm gonna make sure I save the game.
That's so unfortunate. This is the worst thing in the whole game. I gotta get to S rank at least,
right? It's about the personality of the monster, not the stats. You make the story.
That's true. That is true. You do have a point. There was a lot of community subs today, too.
I'm gonna give a hundred, which is insane. It was a 75 community sub as well. That was Sovine and
then Arawani. Thanks, both of you. The monsters. Very, very cool. Atrioc, thanks for the raid,
too. You guys are still here from Atrioc. Thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking around. Maybe
we'll see you again, and we will see you tomorrow. He's spinning around in a circle.
It's very late. Nobody's really live right now, but I will send you guys... I'm gonna send you
guys to Miskiv. What are you doing, Miskiv? Art contest? I'm following... Yeah, Miskiv is live
right now. Go say hello. No, you can say that I missed him in Smite because I play that game
all the time and he didn't even ask to play with me, by the way. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Take
care. Have a great night. Drama. Peep the horror. No more horror peeping. I'll see you guys later.
Have a great night. Why is this... Five seconds. What do you mean five seconds? What are you talking
about? I just said raid. What? Okay. For a second, I thought it was raiding in five seconds. I didn't
have time. Everyone relax. We're fine. See you tomorrow for the game awards. Good night. Goodbye.
Take care of yourselves. Go say hello to Miskiv. You better get me at least 7,000 viewers. Otherwise,
come on. There's gotta be 7,000 people going over there. I'm not... You have to. I just told you.
Come on. Do a reverse raid song. Okay.
Did you tell what I said? I am excited for the game awards tomorrow even though I played literally
probably one game that came out in 2021. I'm gonna have no idea what to even say.
All right. Goodbye. Good night.