Hey, what is going on everybody? Jirba here with chapter 2 of
Nightmare House 2. And I'm just gonna go where we left off. I know a lot of you
guys wanted me to do the prologue and I absolutely will do that. I apologize.
I thought the prologue was just some kind of cutscene or something like that,
but that actually is Nightmare House 1, I think. So I will do that at the end of
this playthrough. I'll make sure to get that done. But in the meantime, let's go.
God, will you... What the hell? Enough with the jump scares in the first 11 seconds.
Anything over here? Get out of the way, you stupid thing. I have a gun at least
and I have bullets. I have... Turn up the flashlight. Radiology department. Never
lose hope hospital. Oh yeah, never lose hope except for the guy that like got
locked in there with a monster. God! How many shots does it take to kill a zombie?
Can I get in there? No. I only have 10 bullets. Are you absolutely kidding me?
X-ray, CT scan, MRI.
Okay.
Good to know. That's locked. This is locked. And come on, lucky number three.
They're all locked. Can I like break through or something? Oh, of course I can.
This guy's going to come alive, guaranteed. And like, he's going to start
attacking me and I'm going to scream. Three, two, one. Nope. I could do without
the flashbang in my face. All right, this is gruesome. Oh my God. Get this guy on
the wheelchair. Something horrible is going to happen right now. I'll take an
ice cold. I'll take an ice cold Dr. Pepper. I didn't even read the tagline. So
cold, it'll make you S bricks. I knew it was going to happen. What am I? Can I
like just hit him? I'm just like playing patty cake with this guy like, die, die,
die. Danger. Admitance to authorize personnel only. Which means me get some
recharge my light. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Health kit. Probably shouldn't have
done that. Anything here? No. Where am I even supposed to be going? I don't like
that TV. Okay. Well, can I like make a collect call to my mother? Hi, Ma. It's
me. I just wanted to let you know that I'm in the middle of like a zombie like
apocalypse. And all the doors open. Okay, let's go into the radiology department.
All cell phones and electronic devices must turn this on. Oh,
yeah, I'm breaking the vital medical. I'm like smashing the medical equipment
right now. Anything even in here that I need to know about? A box of tissues can
blow my nose. Just keep going. Recharge the light. I can take this away.
To get in that door. Get out of here. Anything in here? Ooh. Bullets. Thank you
very much. I will take those. What? What? What? What? What? What? What? But what the
hell is going on? Come on here. I can't get out. I have no flashlight either. No.
God, why does she have to do that to me? What did I ever do to her? Okay. Oh, all
right. What do I do with this thing? I just drop it. All right, let's bring this
over here. Can I put this in here? Can I just fit in there? Just go in here. Go in
like that hole right there. Damn it. There's got to be a box right here
somewhere then, huh? I have no idea where to bring this damn thing. I'm just
carrying around this power supply. No, I have a feeling. What about in here?
There's another one. What's with these power supplies? Like, what am I supposed
to do with these things? What? What? What? What? God. Ow, my brain. Where did he go?
I didn't just do that, did I? Can I get in here? I can. No. No, stop. It's totally
black. No bullets. And all these things. I just don't know what to do with these
things. I keep pulling out the power supplies, but I don't know what to do
with them. Maybe I bring the... I think I know what to do. This one's glowing. Where
is he? Where is he? Son of a... God, there's a couple of them. Go for headshots.
There's three of them!
Get away from me! Get away from me! Okay. Definitely have to bring this back and
put that in the other one. For sure. In here, right? Get in there. All right, what
does that do? Is this operational now? It is. Okay. I have no idea what I just did,
but I did... Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. It's like everything's exploding. I can't... How am
I gonna get out of this room? Was that... What the hell? Was I supposed to do that?
What did I... Jeez. Now what? Oh, damn. It blew a hole in the wall. Okay. Get up
there, you bastard. Get up there. All right, we found a new little area here.
No. Where are you? I don't know where you are. Locked. Oh, I thought I just saw
something. My whole body just tingled right... What's going on? What's going on?
Why can't I... Why can't I do anything? Was that guy in, like, a gym suit? What the
hell was that? I do not like that. That guy... Oh, it's another vent. Oh, great.
Another vent. Okay. How do I get up there? Can I, like, jump on something? Um, the
wheelchair? Sorry, whoever that was. I needed to use it. First of all, I am going
to recharge this light.
Oh, that was ridiculous. Please don't just jump at me. What? How is that even
possible? That's impossible. Get out of my way. So glad I have a gun. Without this
gun. Hey. You can't even... Okay. They can't get in. That's okay. Yeah, no, no crap.
Oh, why isn't this guy here helping me with a gun or something? Go arm yourself
with a machine gun and get out here. Go get an assault rifle. Oh, I'm going to
throw up. Come on now, really? Get down. Storage. No, that's the... So what did I
just do? I came from here. This is the MRI machine. So I went down this way. Let
me try going over here now. No, I already went over here. Where is this girl? That
always means the girl's around. What the... Whoa. Hey. Well, that's not terrifying.
Get me out of here. Whoa. What? Oh, man. That's going to do it again, isn't it?
What the hell is that? Where's my flashlight? Where's my flashlight? There's
nowhere else to go. What is that? Is that a chair? It's a chair. Where am I? Where
am I? What's going on? Okay. Where am I? Where's my light? I think I'm alive. I'm
alive. That's good to know. Well, now what? Chapter three. All right, guys. Well,
that's going to be it for Scare Saturdays. Hope you enjoyed... That thing wasn't
human. That thing wasn't human. I will see you guys all next time, of course. And
take care, everybody.