So, Jackbox. If you've taken off, I'll see you this weekend. Thanks for participating.
Let me open up Jackbox. This is gonna be loud as shit, isn't it? Let me turn it off. Party Pack 3,
by the way. Hey, there it is. Jackbox 3. Is it gonna capture it? Come on, man. Oh, that doesn't look
right. Why is it so small? Hold on. Why is this so small? Full screen mode. There it is. There we go.
All right. Volume control. That's fine. Full screen is on. All right. So, what are we gonna do?
Faking it? Quick Blast 2? TKO? I am. Remember to join the room first. I will. But first, I need to,
I need to put a title here. Jackbox wind down. Get off of just chatting. We'll do, yeah, we'll
do TKO. Turn it up. T-K-O. Anybody can play. We're gonna do turn off full screens. I need an, I need
another window open. Uh, we already know this. Please draw three times instead of four. And
writing time is shorter. Yeah, we want that. Audience on. Audience suggestions. While players
draw and write, audience can enter suggestions which appear on the screen. Meh. No extended timers.
Require Twitch. Yes. Manual censoring. On. Allow room code hiding. On. Okay. Here we go. I'm not
gonna do anything. I mean, there's no rhyme or reason to this one. There's gonna be, I'm gonna dump
it into the chat. Because we're only gonna be able to play one or two of these anyways. Change game?
I did. Refresh. Refresh. Refresh. This is taking a while. Please check your internet connection.
What's going on? Is Jackbox down too? How, how could Jackbox be down? I'm still live, right?
We're sorry. We can't seem to connect to the Jackbox games server. What? I'm still, I haven't
dropped any frames or anything. Okay. That's something fucking real weird is going on here.
All right. So I'm going to turn this off and then I'm going to put it in the chat. I'm going to join
it first. Or code. I think I'm just going to say it. I'm just going to say it because then
there's no advantage. Something with me connecting to like websites is fucked. What the hell is going
on here? This is really fucking strange. Okay. Try it again. All right. Well, that was weird.
Okay. Are you ready? The letters are, I'm going to, I'm just going to say it out loud. Here we go.
W E Y U. Hello. What do I want to be? The fire. Of course. All right. You can also join if you're
in the audience, extra players can join the audience. You're both who influenced the game.
You play on your device at jackbox.tv. You punch in this code and then you play. Here we go. You're
ready. One, two, three, fight. That was a nerve wracking. I'm just happy to get out of this house.
Welcome to TKO. I am the tournament master. I'm over 5,000 years old and I'm on my 200th
rewatch of the wire. Feast your eyes on beautiful t-shirt island. I call it that because it's kind
of shaped like a t-shirt and because of the t-shirt theme blouter that we hold here. So it works two
ways. Chapter one training grounds. Round one. After victory starts here at the training grounds.
You will use your device to draw two drawings. Okay. Feel free to draw anything that strikes
your fancy. And if your fancy isn't feeling so fancy, hit the suggestion button. It's time
for your first drawing. I'm ready. Right now. Okay. First drawing. Here we go. All right. How
much time do we have? No, not a whole lot of time. I got to just go. All right. Here we go. What do
I want to do? This sucks. Okay. How much time? Only seconds remain.
Fuck. Did I wait? Do I have to click the button? Oh, stoop. You have to click the button.
I thought it like, no matter what, it just takes what you did. Well, I...
You have to submit or else nothing submits. It should just take what you did.
This is just practice? I don't think it is. This is the second time I've done this. This is probably
like the 12th time I've done this. It's all right. I got my second drawing in. Did you just take
what you did? I have to put this in a different window. I'm putting it over here. Minimize this
window. All right. That's not the game's fault, no matter how bad you want it to be, but it still
should just do that. What about like the grandmothers that play this and they don't finish? Wait,
where's my drawing? Last exercise, you will write as many slogans or phrases as you can.
These have nothing to do with your drawings, so just put those out of your mind.
And there's no shame in hitting the suggestion button if you need it.
You didn't give up after one, did you? Keep writing. There you go. I got it. ASMR typing.
I wrote like five. Enough training. Direct your attention to your device.
You have a series of drawings and slogans at your disposal.
Choose one of each to make the best t-shirt champion that you can. Okay. Don't phone it in.
Uh, why? All right, I'm gonna pick this one. Yeah, this is where fireman actually came from.
This is it. Why are we here just to suffer? Versus... Look what you've done. I...
Using your devices to vote. I don't know. That's tough. Is that supposed to be Sam and Max over
there? That's... that's like scarecrow and Max. This one is taken on. Germacraft remastered.
I mean, it's... where's the Minecraft in there? There's no Minecraft in that t-shirt. It's just
sun and clouds in the sky and grass. What? All right, Germacraft versus... I can't believe
you've done this. Uh, that's just... I've seen that video before. All right, Germacraft cannot
win because it has the word germa in it. I did vote for it. What? What is... what is going on here?
Uh, half the t-shirt? Germacraft related? Which do I pick?
He thinks he's gonna escape Germacraft.
What? All right, okay. That's... I... that's just like a run-on sentence.
I... I didn't know... I didn't know what to do. Run over bitch with 2006 Toyota Highlander. I... what?
Versus? It's just a shame. Just a damn shame. Read it in the yoda voice. Run over with 2006 Toyota Highlander.
All right, whatever. Oh no, it's sizzled over here. That means this one wins. I win. Versus?
Hey, does anyone know where the bathroom is? I'm lactose intolerant and...
and the world's on fire. He's just looking around. I don't know where the bathroom is.
The world's on fire. These are the winners? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. All right,
this time I'm not gonna fuck around. I'm not gonna fuck it up this time. Don't worry. Uh, I get...
Got it. Got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Don't worry. How about um... Wow! Oh, I got a two!
This sucks. I'm bad at drawing. So am I. I can't do it for shit.
So I take so long because I just second-guess everything I do.
Worma. Can I get that in blue? Yeah. No. Can I? Worma. Can I get that in blue? Versus? Yeah.
This is one of the emoji faces. Versus? Versus? I don't like either one of these. What is this?
Does the audience decide? I think they influence if there's a tie. I don't even know what this is!
Homina homina homina. Versus reality could be whatever I want. Oh yeah! Yeah, I know what you did.
No, you don't. You don't know shit. What? No, you guys found out that was the one that I made,
so then all of a sudden you want to get rid of it. Oh, that's a big, big F coming through. Yeah,
I know what you did. I know what you did is gonna win versus... I drew that! He's lag switching.
I drew that one. A long tie and I drew that one. Yeah, it always starts at like four o'clock.
God hates compact streamers. What the fuck are you talking about? If you press pause and unpause,
it should catch up. Yeah, I actually did. I sent a message to Cox today saying,
God damn it. It's happening again. Fix the fucking internet and see if they get back to me today.
Which is here. Chapter five. From the previous rounds were made, the tournament ends here.
Why would that be the... Better not. I mean, this... I don't know if I would wear this shirt.
I don't think I would put this on. Yeah, I know. Versus... This is like the
kitty. Funny like cat face. Oh, this is tough. I had to... Does anyone know where the bathroom is?
What's the next one? I don't... I don't even want that one available for a shirt. I don't want
anyone to be able to buy that and wear it. Because they'll like... They'll wear it to like a convention
and point at it and be like, hey! Hey dickhead! Yeah! Yeah, I know what you did. The cat won.
Oh man, we really might like... We might truly go down down. Thankfully, this is kind of just
the end of the stream. Like last hour of the stream anyways. This is bad.
All right, let's uh... Should we do another one of these? Or should we do one of the other games?
Another. Another. Yeah, we'll do another one. The other ones go faster anyways.
So we'll go do a new game. Exit. Thank you for playing. This one. Do we do a quick flash? Quick
flash is good to kind of just... We wanted another TKO. Yeah, but take... It takes... I'd rather try to
get some... We can do it again. I'd rather do one of these that can take less than get more people
to play. And then we can do another TKO. Let's change it up. Because if I... The stream might
actually just turn off. So I want to at least get this one too. Because this has been very very bad
the last couple of minutes. We'll find out. All right, so make sure the settings are correct.
That's fine. Extended time's off. Require twitch. Manual censoring. Yep, yep, yep. Room code.
So I'm just going to type it. And it's going to be in the screen on your twitch chat very shortly.
Say it. Well, when I say it, I have to type it. Because everybody will see it at the same time.
Because if I say it, people that are on like source will hear it first. So usually I would
do this in like a discord or something. But we're only going to do this for like another
20-30 minutes or so. What do you mean the same thing? All right, if somebody opens the stream
and they're not on source versus people that are here, you know, if it... No one's seeing this at
the same exact time. It's like three or four seconds between people. If I put it in chat,
you might be like watching this stream like a second or two behind. All right, here we go.
I'm just going to put it in. Do the first three letters? All right, all right, fine. No, just...
There it is. I also typed in G.
Oh, here's the code for reporting. That one.
Unfair to me because I don't know how to read. Fuck!
God damn it. I was so busy. Like, I'm just going to put the code in the chat.
And like we dropped to zero and the stream just like turned off.
I hate this internet so much. It's so distracting. It just... I literally just saw it. It's going to
zero again. Like right now. Fuckers. Cocks motherfuckers. I'm sorry. I got distracted.
I thought he quit because he took the I can't read comment. No, I just... I didn't go into the
room because I went to zero and I just ran out of... I was an idiot. This is so frustrating.
Seriously is. Four hundred dollars a month for this internet. You fucking believe that shit?
Four hundred fucking dollars a month. Four hundred dollars a month. Oh, it's unfucking
believable. I wish I could like sue these motherfuckers, but you just can't.
It's a scam. Yeah, it's called pay for extraordinarily overpriced business internet
for them to give you dogshit service like two weeks out of the month. It's like that everywhere.
Fucking everywhere. You can move to like three cities in the United States to get like fiber
reliably. A bunch of dogshit. That's so fucking annoying. I'm... Oh, he's actually... Oh, I'm
actually mad. Actually mad. You're hearing like real actual mad. Can we do this shit all the
fucking time? It doesn't matter what city you go to. It's everywhere. I was talking to people
before. I was talking to a couple of streamers that are like, hey, my internet's so bad. Should
I like... Where should I move? It's like... It doesn't matter. You could go anywhere. It's like
this in California. It's like this in fucking Nevada. It's like this in Boston. It doesn't
matter where you go. You can go to like Austin and get Google fiber. All right. Well, everyone's
gonna move to Austin. I'm not gonna move to EU. Pain in the dick. All right. Here we go. I'm gonna
punch it in. We'll do the first three letters this time. I'm sorry, guys. I'm just distracted
by this bullshit. Here we go. Here comes the first three letters. There's another letter.
Internet. I think everybody's in. Here is now the code for you to see. It's just,
it's so normal to have shitty internet in North America. And it's incredibly expensive.
Fuck me. Pain in the ass. How did they guess? It's only one in a 26 chance.
So those are the names you're going with, huh? Okay, if you're sure. This is round one. You'll
score points based on the percentage of over 30. I'm so upset I got him the first time. I'm really
sorry. It's my fault. I'm sorry about that. I really am. All right. Here we go. Attention,
audience. While you wait for these annoyingly slow players, why not try the audience play along?
Okay. That's it. Oh, shit. I forgot about the audience. I forgot. You can write anything.
It's just chat. Wait, I thought that people could just write anything they wanted and they could do
like the most. I think, yeah, I think you can. Yeah, you can. Almost out of time. Use the safety
clip button if you have to. Fucking internet. Internet. Internet. Internet. I'm gonna make my
own damn internet. Let's start this show. Number one on the list. A bad name for a proctologist.
Bad name for a proctologist. Dr. Dr. Yucky Gross. Dr. Yucky. Oh, Dr. Ass. Dr. Yucky Gross.
Wait, not like Dr. Dr. Schweikson. Why is Dr. Schweikson? Should be there. Next,
nursery rhyme that's guaranteed to give your kid nightmares.
I don't know. I mean, that one's pretty horrifying.
I don't know why you give a child that. They would probably be very, very upset.
The name of a bra for dogs. Bra or D-pup.
That was when I was mid-meltdown. All right. Give me some credit here. I was very upset
about the internet. I just had to write something like a bra. A dog bra. I don't know.
Tiny high bee in living. Honey, I shrunk the furniture.
Right. Pretty clever. Pretty clever. Get the laugh track.
Dude, I was in the middle of being angry. These two weren't. This is not my prime here.
Better internet. Canada doesn't even have better internet.
Canada has, I think, worse internet than the United States.
Says he was caught. I know, right? A good restaurant to give a restaurant a zero star review.
They served auto or no garlic bread. You mean like they served auto food. They served dogs in
the restaurant and somebody saw that and thought it was disgusting. They're like, why would they
be dogs at the table? I would give a place zero stars if they didn't have garlic bread. That's
fucked up. Next is who buys a jet ski? It's a personal card that says this.
Anybody that buys a jet ski has a personal card that says this. Wave high or certified
gamer license. What would you have a gamer license for? I mean, you don't need a gamer
license to ride a jet ski. It's not a game. Round one is in the books. Let's see this.
Everything can be a game. That's true. There's a chat meme. I know. I'm ready for this one.
Here we go. Audience members instead of just waiting around while the players
type try the audience play along. Okay. Fuck. I'm here. I'm here. I put the funny epic edgy joke.
No fun allowed. Yeah, this is not an open world stream. This is a closed world stream.
Choices don't matter. No choices. Yeah. Your choices. All right. Here we go. I'm going to get
monumental points here. Yeah. Force stealth would be me putting on slow mode.
Sub only mode. Why is old saying your grandma taught you look before you leap? Look before
you buy lottery tickets in Nevada. This is that's the just what this that's just a saying.
That's a call back to me not understanding that I couldn't purchase lottery tickets
in Nevada because there's no state lottery. So like actually physically look and physically find out
if I can actually do that before doing it. So that's pretty good. That's pretty good one.
I think that wins the game. Next one. Buying a new home. Always make sure the previous owner
didn't blank. Thank you for explaining the jokes. Well, there may not have been people here
on that stream. So, you know, you have to tell something. Make sure the previous owner didn't
move away to Las Vegas. Leave wasps in here. I don't understand this. Well, let me tell you.
So I moved. The sequel to Shakespeare in love would be called Shakespeare in blank.
Which one is it? Which one is it going to be? I got the audience. I got the audience on that.
Next up. The dark secret of Frosty the snowman is that he blanks. What is the dark secret of
Frosty? He has bones on the inside. Isn't made of snow. What is that supposed to mean?
What do you mean not made of snow? What else would you be made out of?
Cocaine. You wouldn't you wouldn't be able to clump them together. It would be awesome if you
could grow blank in a garden. Get to voting. It would be awesome if you could grow cool person
in a garden or garlic bread in a garden. I mean, either one of those would be pretty
would be pretty pretty awesome, I guess. Cool person. Next in the hopper. A job that doesn't
exist but surely would have the highest death rate if it did. Oh, this could be a lot of
Ready, set, vote. This already this is a thing. What are you talking a tuber
would have the highest death rate. I could I could take care of myself just fine.
Okay, next one. Thank you very much. Something to stuff a bra with if you're in a hurry.
Put in your votes. If you're in a hurry. More bras. Watermelons.
Yeah. Come on. You're better than that. No, I'm not. It's voting time. What a turtle looks
for in a mate. Oh, we're getting political. It just got political. It just got political.
How quickly could you stuff a watermelon in a bra? I don't know. Depends on how big it was.
Who is no more? Let's see the damage.
Aren't you supposed to be the funny guy? I use my funny powers when I deem it necessary.
Welcome to the last lash. The final round. There's just one prompt and you're all getting it.
Make up the full name for this acronym. Full name for this acronym.
I don't know. I don't know. Oh, that doesn't make any sense. That doesn't make any sense.
Mine makes no sense. I don't even know. It might win.
You got that one. There's an O in this season. There's an O in that one.
Great. Let's see where those medals ended up. First, the bronze, silver, and now the gold.
Now we transform those medals into points.
Jerma, what the fuck? I was trying to go for the click. I was trying to go for the clicks.
It's over. Let's see the final scores.
All right, fourth place. I still get to go on to the next Mario Kart track.
I'm going to keep being Koopa Troopa. Still lost? Well, I mean, but what if I'm in first
place next time and I get more points than Mario does and I end up getting the trophy
after three or four more. All right, let's do you lost to three people who are good at guessing
letters. That means that they're like they have swiftness. All right, so we're going to do the
t-shirt one again and then I got to get out of here because I have to get ready and I have to
go pick up somebody at the airport. So I got to get out of here. Let's do the t-shirt one again.
Thank you for playing, guys. Wait, what are you doing? I want to exit. All right, I'm going to
do a good one this time. Just you wait. So this one, we will exclusitize this one. I'm going to
put this, I'll give you some time. Don't worry. I'm going to put this in the sub discord channel.
Okay, I'm going to do three letters again in the sub discord channel. I'll give you time to pay to
win. Well, it was one out of three pay to win. Two out of three for free. All right, let me just get
it started. Let's get this off the screen and I'm going to put it in that discord. I'm going to have
the first letter missing. Okay, the first letter is going to be missing in the discord. I'll give
you an opportunity to get in there if you want to, if you're available. I am now in. Okay, ready?
First letter is going to be missing. Or, no, yeah, the first, that's actually kind of, yeah,
that's better. First letter will be missing. Okay, here we go. This is the last three letters.
Remember, last three letters. I will give you a dash just so you remember. Somebody got it.
Somebody else got it. There's still plenty of room here. One more slot. Oh, somebody got it.
There it is. It was O-P-K-H. All right, I'm going to draw something very good this time.
We ready? Three, two, one, let's start. Oh, well, there's your countdown. How about you give us the
code and you have to guess the first letter. I'm not sure that would be a thing that would work.
Can we skip this? All right, I know exactly what I'm doing.
I don't think we can skip the intro.
How do I undo? 40 seconds. I'm done.
This game is so cute, it is very cute. It's a very nice little game.
Remember to hit submit. That's true. Second drawing. All right, that's done. Done. I don't
need to do it anymore. Let's go. Oh, JervaCraft. What if we all just did JervaCraft? Every single
one. I'm glad I said that after this was done so then people wouldn't have the opportunity to do
it. Mine is so bad. So is mine. Don't worry, they're all going to be bad.
Here we go.
You didn't give up after one, did you? Keep writing. You may want to finish up.
Fuck, I almost said four. Nice hustle. Zero. One.
Training is over. Look at your device. Select one drawing and slow it to create the perfect
t-shirt combination. And I do mean perfect. Oh my god. I'm so disappointed. I'm disappointed.
Sorry, dad. It's okay. You can turn off training in the settings. Oh shit, okay.
Well, I'm sorry about that. Thanks for the tip. I'm disappointed in you too.
It's okay. Let's go. Rat Movie 3 will never be released as an angry rainbow versus
Yeet Me Into the Grave. I don't know what this is. Oh boy, that one was burnt up. All right,
Rat Movie Rainbow versus Scoff at Him. Mom, can you pick me up? I'm scared.
Scoff at Him. That's just Lightning Man. Oh man, Lightning Man coming in, I guess.
Fireman 2. That's just Fireman shaved and started going to the gym.
Zapman or Riot. Doesn't look like it. Sorry, guys. I do like the little zap guy though.
A new challenger appears. Six Flags. Six Flags. Who is that? Oh, that's you.
That's you at Six Flags. Yes. All right, I get it. Oh, what? What? This is mine. I didn't even
want it to win. Telling the truth. Mom, can you pick me up? This is... I'm conflicted here
because these are both mine. I drew the one on the right. I picked the text for this one
and then I drew the one on the right. I believe in auto. What the fuck is that? What is that?
I believe in auto. All right, I believe in auto versus... No, I'm not giving you guys an opportunity
for everyone to click sans. I'm sorry.
I wanted sans. No. No, we're not gonna have a sans...
I want the funny skeleton character. Fuck, I almost got it.
Make a shirt. What has he made? I love how you save one game and then you get sucked in.
Well, it's fun. It's fun just to play these weird little things.
You're... What does this say? You're grounded. What is it? Apple? The great pet...
That's a sans though. That's a sans. What is it? The great pet... I don't know what this is.
You're grounded. What does this say? Okay. That's a sans. I'm just kidding.
You cracked me up, little buddy. What does that say? Can we zoom in on that?
Well, this is you guys. Does it say sans? I don't know what that says. Six flags. Why would you be
unhappy at six flags? He's calling me at the worst time. That's sans. That's a sans eye. Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm not good enough. Oh, the airport! Oh, my friend! No, don't worry. Late to the
imagine? That'd be so awful. Hey dude, where the fuck are you? I've been waiting in the terminal
for like two hours. Oof. Looks like the circus is in time versus I'm sorry. I'm not good enough.
There goes the cat. Oh well. Burger versus channel meme. Which one?
I'm not sure. This is actually going to be 50-50, I think. Burger it is. What? How? How's it
possible? Oh, great. And it even has this on the bottom too. All right, I got a confession to make.
I drew the sans and I did the A A A A A A A. I was hoping somebody was going to get it and put them
together. Center. I was trying to debate the win. Uh oh, this is tough. Oh, come on. Versus like
the flexing guy at the gym. Sensors others then makes his own. Like sensors then steals and says
it's his original content. Come on. Well, 128 of you are smart. You know, you're smart. Oh,
and what's that? That's mine. I win. Burger versus Zapman. Sorry, I'm not good enough.
Uh oh, what's the auto? Oh no, this is the new little guy. That's a very good burger though.
That's a very steady hand. What's the last one? Oh, I forgot about I believe in auto.
He clashed the titans. Yeah. Uh oh, that's it. I believe in auto. That shirt sucks. Choose
Zapman. I believe in auto. I could see you all compete in this tournament before I died.
Show auto. He doesn't want to look up. I have to like point this down. What's that auto? What's
this? Hello auto. What's going on over here? He's like, what are you doing? Look over there.
Look at him. He's like, I don't want to look over there. I don't want to look over there.
He's too sleepy. He really is just like, no. He's so cute. Okay. Sleepy dog. Come here.
Over here dog. Shaggy and Scooby. Now show Cheeto. Oh right. Come here Cheeto. Look at
how long my nails are. Holy shit. What a psycho. I could like go do Wolverine trials with these
things. I'm gonna take care of that after the stream. All right. That is gonna be it. Click
here to share or buy these shirts if you really, really feel like doing that. I'm gonna post the
link here. This is a link to all the shirts if anyone is going to purchase any of these.
Here they are. They're pretty much all here from this past round. Yoda was a not, I didn't draw
that. That was a fake drawing because I didn't, I ran out of time. Did anyone have a link from
the last round in TKO? Because that one had Yoda on it. Thanks for playing guys. There's the,
okay there it is from the last one. Cool. All right everybody. I will see you guys on Saturday.
I'm gonna call it here. I have to get ready and then get to the airport. Do Jackbox some other
time. Yeah it pops up from time to time. This stream was fucking, my like throat hurts from
laughing at that robot in the beginning, the first like few hours. And it's always fun to play Jackbox
and chill and hang out and have a good time. So I will see you guys on Saturday. That's the next
time you will see this stream activated. Appreciate everybody for hanging out. And we only had like
one real like streamer meltdown about the internet. That's, that's the first. It's been well done. No.
No I'm not gonna let that ruin my good time. It was fucking a ton of fun. But yeah I'll see
you guys soon. We'll do the bits and the subs. Let's get them on the screen. Why not? I need,
there it is. This chat too. Thank you everybody. Thank you to, especially to these people.
Go back a few hours ago here. We had a bunch of community subs too. Thank you to another maple.
Happy birthday another maple. Happy 19th birthday to another maple. Some guy, thanks for the five
dollars. Hey so how about that children's book deal? Don't worry I haven't forgotten about it.
Children's book deal? Daylight? What day? What day is today? Today? It is Wednesday my dudes.
I don't even know what that is. It's like everybody's a Scrooge yelling at Tiny Tim out
the window. Uh thank, thank you some guy for the five dollars. Uh thank you R Ken for the three
bucks. Just wanted to let you know that I love you man. It's been tough to catch your streams
as I'm currently on an exchange from Australia to Finland. Probably be asleep by the time you
read this so mind wave me some good dreams. Will do. Uh thank you so much for the three bucks and
Australia to Finland. That's pretty long ways away. Thank you so much for the three bucks
and you're on exchange from Australia to Finland. I wonder what, if you get this maybe give us an
update. What for? What are you doing? That sounds interesting. But thank you. Thank you the Jack for
the 280. The AI recognizes people as well so if you type in Todd Howard it will talk about Skyrim.
You can write in screen writing style so do your silly little voices. I might have to play with
that again. Should have typed Jerma. I typed Jerma a few times. It just gave us like weird responses.
It gave us like weird chat logs every time I would put my name in. Uh thank you Growlithe for the
five bucks. Been having a rough week and this stream is exactly what I needed. Been watching
you for years. Love everything you do. Keep being you. Thank you for the five bucks and for the
really really nice fucking thing to say. Thank you. Hope you have a better week. Happy to be
able to hang out and you know at least have fun right? Tingy thanks for the 250 Tingy. Is this
where BF Bugleberry got his Halloween stories? No I wrote the entire Halloween story. The last
one I wrote the whole thing. Bugleberry's like four page Halloween story about like
the loud man. I just I wrote the whole thing. It was dog shit but I still did it. Thank you though.
Amferik thanks for the 10 community subs. That was earlier a couple hours ago. We also had two
$100 bit drops from Smotherum and Lexi. Thank you both of you for your huge amounts of money.
Uh I think I missed Reim. ReimTV gave five community subs an hour and a half ago or so.
Thank you Reim for your sub drop here. Kalula Sniper thanks for the 250. Holy shit Jerma this
stream was one of the funniest things I've ever seen. That E3 bit absolutely slayed me. BRB you
need to wipe the tears from my eyes. Dude some of those six flags that the Six Flags one with
the Great Wall of China was seriously like I I wish like I said I wish I could like eat that image.
What like a fun thing. What a fun thing. Yeah there were some really fun ones.
Tales from the Tomb Raider. Thank you KRYSKris for the five dollars. Time to play GeoGuessr.
No we're taking a GeoGuessr break but thank you with the five dollars. Thank you Jess you got it
for the 250. Here's my contribution to the lawyer fund so you can sue Cox. Oh yeah didn't I want I
did I say I was gonna sue Cox. I turned into like a fireball for like 45 seconds. I don't remember
what did I say. The volcano erupted inside of my body and I said that like I what did I say fuck
Cox I want to sue him. Jesus Christ. He said you wish you could sue them. Oh well those motherfuckers
I'm about to sue them. Oh I can't contain my rage. This is impossible. You kept repeating
400 400 400 400 400. Oh god. You used motherfucker twice in a sentence. It was the most genuinely
angry I've ever heard you. That's so fucking ridiculous. Get a business line with him. I have
that's what I have. I have a business line from Cox that is the business package. I already have
it and it don't matter. Why business? Because if you have residential internet and you have a problem
they send the residential technicians and they don't really care. They tell you to turn your
modem off and on again when they have packet loss and noise ingress in their line going to the plant.
So if you do if you do not have a business line from one of these internet companies
they do not fix your problem. And the thing about uptime guarantees is they for when I'm
streaming right so let's say I drop like 20 000 frames on a stream and like it fucks up every
10 minutes or so. That's still technically they can still spin it whereas well yeah but I mean
it's still 99% up. What about the times when you're not streaming and you're using the internet on the
line? So technically in a 24 hour day these like 30 to 40 000 frames a drop it doesn't matter like
that's still part of their like uptime. No they don't give a shit. They never will. The people
that are on like the ground level do care. It's it's kind of funny because you'll talk to some
of these technicians that are like you know they come out and they try to service and they try to
figure out what's wrong. And there are people above those people who are above those people who are
above those people. So it doesn't matter. Somebody has to figure out what they want to do about it
and it's not the person that comes to your house. That person cannot fix your problem.
They can tell someone else that it exists and then that person has to deem if it's necessary for them
to fix it and tell the next person to do so. So getting upset or angry at the technician that
comes out is is just wasted breath because that person cannot even fix your problem.
All they can do is start the chain. It ends up being a game of telephone which is why
fortunately for for this particular location every time there's been a problem the thank you
every time there's been a problem like a real addressable problem where you know
20 30 40 000 drop frames per stream for a week this guy that I have contact with does fix it
like he does do what he can and he does get them to do it but that process to get there took like
six months of getting that guy that you can talk to so you can get a business contact with cox it's
like having a representative of the company that knows you we used to offer those to our property
managers yeah it's it's just hard it's hard because there's so many employees there's so
many customers that it just it's impossible to stay on top of it no matter where you are
but it's all good like obviously i'm gonna fly off the handle sometimes when it
ruins a stream right because when your stream goes to zero and you get a buffer and you have
to refresh the page that fucks up the stream that takes my mind and all of our collective
good time we're having into oh well hold on a minute hold on hold on give me give me like
two three minutes okay is it are we are we through it oh okay can you hear me you can hear me okay
good it's just an inconsistent fucking mess they know it breaks the immersion well just it just
it's just not fun when you're interrupted every two or three minutes you can't let when you get
in a groove and then you look over and you see the red zero it's like well oh better quiet better
stop talking for 30 seconds and see what happens and it's almost like yeah you it's almost like
i'm sure you guys have noticed when there's internet problems start happening let's say
they happen for like an hour or so right that hour is me trying to dance around frame drops
and it impedes on the stream it fucks with the stream because then whatever i was doing
previously now i have to think in the back of my mind and glance over to the right here to my
obesity when i drop down when can i stop talking should i just i'm dead here refresh you know it's
it's a pain in the ass rather than just focusing on what we're doing it just really it really
really really just is annoying but like i said i'm not gonna let that ruin my good times i
said my piece maybe i said it for about a minute or two we moved on and it's been up i'm not gonna
let it ruin the good time today was a ton of fucking fun i'm not gonna let that sour a really
really fun day so hope it didn't for you either let's keep going we were at where is it here
we were it was just you got it for the 250 here's my contribution to the lawyer fund that's what
started that creation come undone thanks for the 10 bucks hi german i'm the guy who originally
suggested talk to transformer during the day's gone stream hope you had fun sometimes all it
takes is one guy that's true all it takes is one guy it was a great suggestion i had never even
heard of it thank you for the 10 bucks tingy thanks for the 250 i'll have you know west coast
canada has very good internet we have two isps who are in direct competition with each other
with both working on expanding their fiber infrastructure one of them now offering up to
a thousand down a thousand up for half the cost of your business internet yeah yeah but here's
like the the worst part about this is if there's let's just let's say that there are like i said
like a handful of american cities that have reliable fiber or you know best internet in the
country reliable everywhere it really doesn't matter because you could have like massachusetts
like boston has the best internet apparently like it's in the top 10 or something for internet in
the country but i had problems all the fucking time it really doesn't matter how like fast or
how good on paper internet is supposed to be it there's always pockets that are just terrible
and it's impossible to know where those pockets are you can't know that unless you go in and you
use it for like a month or two straight it's about stability yeah it's not about how fast or good
the internet is supposed to be it's how stable it is while it's running and it's you'll you'll
it's just so hard to you know i've said it before and i've heard other people say it like well why
didn't you just figure out what the internet was and how good it was before you went there
actually asked people actually asked realtors and shit like hey does the do you know how how's the
internet and over every single question is exactly answer the same way i just high speed you call up
these companies and you say hey what do you have available here uh yeah we have high speed we have
this package for high speed do you have fiber yeah oh okay do you though no no we have this
this thing it's a thousand down but it's 30 up but it's not fiber no it's not but it is the fuck are
you talking about you know what i mean it's like impossible to like get straight answers for
anything and here's the most the worst part about this is if we if i was to walk down the street
and plug in my computer and stream there might be zero dropped frames just because of where it's
located on the node on the street you know what i'm saying it's impossible to find that exact
location that has zero problems okay can i can i come in and feed off your internet please
just be a bum streamer no i i i just got really unlucky that i had kind of sloppy internet
in one place and then it's the same kind of sloppy internet in the next one i tried i tried to figure
out what the best place the best like internet i could get it's just unfortunate and it's funny
because i talk like this and i look at like my twitter feed and i see a ton of people writing
sorry guys i had to stop the stream because i can't even stream for more than an hour
my internet turned off again you know it's like it's this is not uh it's not abnormal what i'm
saying which is kind of annoying it's pretty much every day i'll scroll down my twitter feed and
other streamers that i follow at least one of them will say something like that nova is having the
same problem yep it just sometimes it just happens sometimes you just get fucked and that's it but i
could go i could talk about this for ages we'll uh we'll move on i gotta get out here anyways
because i have to go obviously to the airport pick somebody up following streamers laugh out loud
uh so let's get the credits on the stream and we'll do the final handful of bits here there's
like three four or five more here are all the subs from today thank you everybody hope you had a good
time i did i'm gonna have to like to go gargle salt water my throat is fucking killing me but
thank you to tingy for that about west coast canada i'm glad you have good internet i'm glad
you have reliable internet you are the envy of a lot of people so happy to hear that uh zake
thanks for the 250 hey man it was pretty cool to meet you yesterday it was nice chatting with you
it got kind of weird though when you stole that kid's ice cream and started screaming obscenities
at people still love your streams though it's all right i don't i'm not a thief i don't steal
smelly boy thanks for the 250 smelly boy uh keck or cringe what what is something about jackbox
i don't know fat boy sent thanks for the 15 dollars fat bossy and 15 bucks if it's here if
secure gets dlc will you play it yes i will do securo dlc on stream if it is a thing definitely
thank you so much for the 15 dollars yes i will dark soul 9669 thanks for the five dollars i just
want you to know that i'm watching the vod and i got details from the tomb raider and i mean the
same condition you were during fart and scream compilation thank you for the streams take this
small sum you got you got a long way to go that is the tip of the iceberg there thank you for the
five dollars i'm happy that you had a fun time listening to it in the vod also thank you to i
corka for the 10 bucks they say auto i showed auto thank you for 10 dollars thank you thank you
thank you uh devakitty thanks for the 250 germa you should absolutely play with the transformer
thing again i was having difficult deconcentrating because how good it was it was a fucking bunch of
i thought tale of the tomb raider was a real game that's why i was i thought it was an e3 presentation
for tail of the tomb raider i was gonna go get the e3 presentation and play it out
tail of the tomb raider but thank you devakitty glad you had fun freudian weapon thanks for the
250 all the giant bats you say all of them take of the tombs raider right the jack 473 thanks for
the five dollars the jack they say oh zapman emote when zapman i think zapman shouldn't be an emote
because zapman's pissed because he's not an emote you know what i mean but thank you i appreciate it
awsm stevie awesome stevie thank you for the 50 dollars of 10 minutes ago or so i didn't i just
barely was missing it while we talking about internet bullshit but thank you awesome stevie
for the 50 dollars they say someone hacked my twitch and paypal accounts and bought 140 dollars
worth of bits out of my money for some fucking reason i got the money refunded but i still have
the bits and i've been giving them out but you get the biggest donation because you're my favorite
streamer uh they might you might get that pulled back too you know then when when they they might
might be processing still but uh i thank you i'm honored to be your favorite streamer thank you so
much uh but i would probably i would check you i would make sure that you got you know make sure
it's processed correctly you might not have you might actually have just spent money those sirens
coming out of germa's mic but nonetheless thank you i appreciate it and i appreciate all the subs
that just went through thank you everybody i'm gonna take off you'll see me again on saturday
thank you again for watching see you saturday ms dos night a lot of shit show streams this last
week huh it's fun though i'll take it take care everybody see you very soon much love to you good