Um, people are just spawning in here like crazy.
Oh my gosh, there's so many people in here.
Let me see if I can find you guys.
Oh my.
I feel like somebody just opened up a server for the first time and just told the White House to shout it out.
There's thousands of people on these servers.
I feel like I'm at a costume party.
Like, oh hey look it's Batman, or it's like a sexy nurse.
Is this Halloween server? This is what I feel like we're playing right now.
I see Link, I see Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle, I see Spider-Man. I'm Deadpool right now.
Yeah, this is like the biggest costume party we've ever been to.
Jerma, where are you?
I see you. You, like, bearded king thing.
Oh, there he is, he's Jimbo.
I remember when we made that for you.
It's so dumb.
There's a lot of people here, man.
This is gonna be complete chaos.
There's like gonna be 24 people doing this.
This is gonna be awesome.
We're gonna insta-die.
I don't think this is gonna happen.
I might as well just shoot my feet right when the game starts.
Oh, here it goes!
What? What?
Now we got 15 seconds to spread out.
They're still spreading out!
You do not get a bow.
You don't get a bow?
I don't know. It looks like you're supposed to get hit.
Alright, it's starting in one second.
Oh, you do get a bow!
I just shot that guy in the face.
This guy, get away from me, dude.
Oh, get dropped.
Get elevated.
Hello?
Is my name still a different color?
No, it's not.
I'm doing what it's Alex is doing.
I'm looking at the ground.
I almost just killed myself.
You almost just killed yourself.
No, please!
Come here!
Oh, no!
Tino, leave me alone!
Tino, get away from me!
No!
Come on!
This guy's standing still! Get the guy that's standing still!
What?
We're the last three and then we make our own rules to finish the minigame.
Oh, no, no, no, no. Don't you try.
I'm not going to attack any of you guys until we're the only ones left.
It's going to be hard either way.
Tio, stop attacking Jerma.
I want to kill Jerma!
You can. Trust me.
I can't make them fall.
All of us go for those two in the car.
No!
I know!
I know.
Alright, I got my money.
But I'm going to...
I got my money on Tio.
Tio's still in this, huh?
Tio's riding the circumference.
He's going around the circle. That's a good idea.
Are you dead as well?
Oh, he's right there. Look.
It's just you three and then this other guy with the...
Real's nagging for me. Real's frozen.
Oh, he's gone.
Oh, no!
That's awesome!
It was lagging!
You just teleported around in a circle and then just dropped through the center.
God damn it.
Oh!
Oh, it's Alex is alive. I thought he died.
Oh, I got one!
Oh, my game froze.
You're still there.
It's my time. I'm going to die.
No, that guy hasn't...
Oh, no! Please!
No! No!
He just walked off again.
Oh. Oh.
All right, it's Alex. You've got to prove your worth here.
Oh, we can still watch from up here?
Yeah. Oh, that was a pretty sick shot.
Oh!
You've got to lead him. Lead the target.
Oh, it just fell down!
Look, this guy didn't even need to do anything. He's just walking around in a circle.
There we go. It's on.
Who's going to get smoked?
Oh, Tio goes in with the first blood.
Peanut-pone.
Oh, Alex!
Where were you?
I was on the rafters.
Oh, this guy spawned camp in the stairs.
Oh, my God.
Where the hell were you?
Right behind you.
Ah, there's explosives all around me.
Little snake.
Oh, baby.
No, don't kill me, please.
I don't think so, stealth. It's nice to meet you across the map.
God, I feel like I'm playing like direct hit soldier right now.
Oh, Tio, if I had killed you from that shot, oh, my goodness.
The 360!
Get me out of there.
Oh, hi, Tio!
I did get him.
No, I spawned kill you from my spawn.
The reverse spawn kill.
I always feel like somebody's behind me.
Check my back.
God damn it!
This music doesn't fit at all, by the way.
I always have music turned off.
It's like...
It's like the most peaceful music.
Hold on a second. I gotta turn this up.
Turn it up.
It doesn't fit at all.
This is pretty good, like, let's kill each other music.
Didn't feel like chasing you around the map.
I didn't feel like chasing you.
I got you, friend.
I didn't kill you with that?
God damn it!
Oh, yeah.
God.
Oh, come on now.
God, stealth.
I don't know why, but anytime I can, I jump.
Stealth, I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, I got revenge for you.
I just heard you, like, upset.
Like, in complaint.
I right-clicked, I was like, I probably shouldn't.
And I did.
I don't know why, but I always jump off something.
Very tip-top for fun.
I'd be a horrible tactician.
This is what I do.
And we jump off.
I run to the top as fast as I can.
And just make a leap off the top.
I honestly just can't believe it.
You can do this without installing any mods.
Yeah, it's completely mod-free on the user end.
Where is everybody?
What's going on here?
I got teleported to a different part of the map where
no enemies were.
Except for me.
Oh, okay, here we go.
Alright, alright, fine.
You stood still, I thought I got you.
No, you...
God!
I saw you pick your little cactus head up over the blocks.
I got you.
I gotta stop looking over that edge.
It's like the death of me.
Oh my god, I am gonna freak out.
Oh, hey!
Jerma and Tio, the last two people I killed,
returned to their crime scenes.
No, no!
Alright, I'm not dying again.
I'm not dying like five times in a row.
I'm gonna go on a spree.
Yeah, that's what's going on for me as well.
That's my plan also.
We're making like a little choo-choo train here.
Ask Tio, who I was stalking,
and it shoots me instead.
I'm going down in like the spider kingdom.
If you wanna meet me down in the spider kingdom,
you're welcome to come try.
Where is the spider kingdom?
You don't know where the spider kingdom is?
Oh!
I knew it!
Oh, hello!
Tio, why are you there?
I run the spider kingdom.
Whoa.
Take that, Tio!
Career.
Are you trying to tell me that that didn't...
Okay, I was gonna say.
Jumped up 360!
Oh! You got me!
And Tio gets...
That was a long shot.
Jerma!
I was about to kill that guy.
I know, it's Alex!
Oh! I missed twice and you still got me!
Who killed me from behind?
Oh, it was...
I don't even know who the hell hit me from behind.
Stealthy's one more point.
And he wins the golden cup!
Oh, wow.
It's Alex. Get down from there, you kid.
Oh, baby.
Come back, come back!
Somebody show me your body!
It's Alex, can't win.
Ah!
Is he one more?
No!
From the top turnbuckle.
Hi, it's Alex!
Hey!
Yay!
I'm so mad!