What's happening guys? Jerma here for the 2,000 subscriber extraordinaire. Thank
you all so, so much for subscribing to the channel. I can't even... it's been two
months. It's been two months and already there's 2,000 people. That's a thousand
people a month. That's insane. You understand how insane that is? Look at
this cake. 2,000 subscriber cake. Thank you all so much everybody. You are all
awesome. I love every single one of you for real. I dressed up as the Scout just
for you guys because I know you guys like that shit so. Got a couple of cakes
here. Got one cake here, one cake... You want to cut that out? We're trying to film a segment over here.
Hey, Dorian. What's your name? What do you say we take care of that engineer right now? Boy! You thought
that was it? You thought we were done with this fool? He's still... I got him
from a long range. He's still dazed. He's lagging out right now guys. He's lagging
out. I only got like another 30 seconds until his connection comes back.
Get out of there! Oh my god, this is like sludge.
Alright, this is barbecue sauce. Get me a barbecue. I have sweet and sour in the McDonald's bag.
I can't do it. Somebody else has to do it. Alright, never mind. That's good enough.
Thank you all so much again. I really appreciate it. And as this channel grows, I hope to see more of you people.
Hope to see more people come in. It's gonna be a lot of fun. So, thank you all again.
Take care. I'll see you all next time.