On a fucking iPhone. Am I even live right now? I might be on my shitty iPhone. I can see the chat too, that's good.
I'm like right up in your face tonight. Where's the camera? Right here? Right there, okay.
Well, you're... Well, no, no, I can't, I can't talk yet. I need to wait till everybody's here.
This is gonna be like a 15 minute stream because data! Ooh, I'm gonna be spending money on data!
This is where, I don't like this. I don't like this setup. I can like see myself
and I get the chat. I'm like, I'm... Can you hear me? Can you guys even hear what I'm saying?
How shitty is this quality? Is this, is this like 2G? You can hear me? Okay, good.
Finally, I'm at least able to stream on my dog shit device. Is it like 240p? It's probably
worse than that. It's probably like 60p. Makes me look really old. Whatever. But I can't...
Where are my stats? Oh, there we go. I can see my stats. I can see you guys now. So we
still don't have internet. Our house is currently in a total... We got nothing.
We've got another line that's come on in and still doesn't work.
So now, there's a whole other scenario here where they have to do a lot of work.
This is why I'm coming to you from the phone. And that kind of segues into the next topic
here, which is because I don't know when I'm going to be able to stream from this office.
From... Let me get you guys on where you're used to, right? Hold on, here we go.
See? It's like nothing ever... It's like there's no difference. See? You can see my office in the
door like last time. But yes, it's an office. It's a goddamn office. Because it's not my
bedroom. It's another room that's used for the purposes of streaming. But... No, this is
going to hurt my arm. We're going to do this. That hurts my hand. That hurts my fingers.
There we go. So I don't know. I have no idea when we're actually going to be able to
reliably stream from this place. So what that means is that means I've decided to do something
that we've been talking about for a long time. And that is the green screen stream. Remember that?
Remember I was going to get in front of a green screen? I was going to go to a green
screen studio and do all that shit? Well, that's now happening much sooner than you think.
So let me break down how this is going to play out as you count the fucking neck rolls.
How many neck rolls do I have now? When did that happen? What the fuck? When did I get
like a turkey neck? Like a turtle? Whatever. You know, nobody even cares. You're not even
going to look at it. Well, now you are because I just said it. Anyways, so the purpose of this
stream is to kind of pad the time still to be able to actually live stream. So what's going
to happen is I'm going to say it and it's good. I gave the mod some warning here,
but the Discord is going to open up here with a new channel. And on that new channel
is going to be stalling. Well, I can't stall. I'm on like G right now. I'm going
to get a call from my provider and they're going to be like, oh yes, you use like 16
minutes of 240p data. That'll be $400. I'm going to be like.
So in the Discord, there's going to be a new channel. It's going to be action recommendations
because what we talked about before, a long time ago, months ago, when I first wanted to
do this idea, I'm going to get in front of a green screen in a professional studio,
not just like, oh, I'm going to put a green screen behind me. No, I'm going to, it's going
to be like a 50 foot space and I'm going to be able to do anything. We're talking,
I'm not going to give you any ideas. What you guys are going to have to do is come
up with about 30 of them, 30 actions that you want me to do. It's going to be a
nomination process. The mods are already aware and I'm not going to see what they are.
So you have, depending on how long it takes for us to get the internet fixed,
I'm going to try to do this within the next three or four days. So that gives you at least
a couple of days to nominate some actions, which by the way, I get three vetoes. So
just remember that I get to veto at least three of these things that you want me to do
out of like 30. So you better get good ones because I'm going to have a big rubber stamp
that's going to be like, bang, I ain't doing that. But that's going to happen
starting tonight and into tomorrow and the next day. And then I'm going to that studio
and I'm going to broadcast from the studio. So that's the plan. Now, before we continue,
why are we at 280p? Because I'm on an iPhone on like shit internet. I'm on an iPhone right
now. There's no internet in this. I don't have any internet. It just doesn't work.
I'm turning red. You said the word internet. No, I did. I said the word internet and I
just got red. Anyways, so I'm going to get to veto three of them, but let's go over rules.
Let's go over a couple of important things because I know how deeply this could go
totally south. What do I mean by that? All the mods have, they're going to delete
submissions that are sexual. No sexual bullshit. I'm not going to do anything in front of a
green screen. What you can do is, you know, I'm not going to happen. So use common sense
with what you'd like me to do in front of a green screen because they're going to get
picked out. Oh, am I dropping? Am I dropping frames on my iPhone screen? I just was for a
second. But yeah, so just use common sense. Like I ain't going to do anything like
fucked up in front of that green screen for you to then like, oh, let me like, dude,
let me put him here. Look what he just did. I mean, that's, that's the purpose of the whole
thing. I mean, but I'm talking like in, in like a bad sense, right? Cause what's going to happen
after that is after three or four days, I'm going to do the stream. We're going to do all
the actions and then I'm going to put on a host site or I might not even have to,
we'll see how the quality is. The footage, right? If you guys don't want to pull it from
the stream itself, then I'm going to put up probably raw footage somewhere. And then
it's you guys get to make whatever you want as long as it is okay. You know what I'm saying?
And we're going to have a community event a couple of weeks later where we watch them all
on stream. All of them are going to get processed. Mods are going to watch them to
make sure. Like I said, no, nothing's going to slip through the cracks here. So we're going
to watch it. No, it doesn't, it doesn't need to be like PG 13. You can do some R rated
material like, you know, but nothing no like bullshit. Do you know what I mean? And you know
exactly what I'm talking about. When I say that I don't even do it. I don't need to explain
what that means. No bullshit. Okay. Use your goddamn common sense. Yes. People, you guys
get it. You guys get it. But anyways, we're going to do a big community event where we watch
them and we watch what you guys have decided to do with the green screen footage. There's
going to be like probably like an hour of green screen material. I look forward to what
you guys do. Eye contact stream. Well, it's cause like it's right here. Would you rather
me look over at the chat? Cause that's what I could do too. Free material. No, I mean,
well, look, look, look when the reason why this is an interesting idea is because
all the shit that you guys were doing with the bee stuff, like the wasp snapping and
everything. There's some creative fucking people in this community. And I'd like to
see it actually flourish, you know, not just like, Oh, there's me and I'll put a bee here.
I think that's really interesting to see what people will come up with.
And we're going to do a whole event. We're going to watch them all. So again, the discord is
going to open up with the new channel. All the suggestions go there. I'm not going to read them.
I'm not going to see them. I will not know what they are until I get the piece of paper
at the studio that I go to. And again, I get my big stamp that I'm going to stamp
out ones that I don't want to do three of them. So I wish I could give you an example
here. But if there is a certain, by the way, let's make this rule very, very clear as
well. If the, if there are no doubles, there are no doubles are going to be allowed here.
So if you put down, let's say, I don't know, like six or seven different dances,
I don't know. And they're all the same, like, no, no, no, no, no, no. You know doubles,
they got to be all unique or I'll fucking veto them. I'm just going to veto them all.
You want to see, you want to see this motherfucker do a dance, you bet your ass,
you better come to a consensus on it. Because I'll veto that shit. I'm already not looking
forward to it. And I already know what and I already just gave you the idea. I ain't doing
it. Just already know that that's that's good. That's that's going to get vetoed.
That's like an automatic veto. But I have some you buddy, you better have some better shit
on there because I get three vetoes. Do a default dance, default. Well, what is it? What
even is a default dance? So no stream tonight? Well, no, unless you count this,
which I wouldn't because it's just a quick little thing. I just wanted to make sure that
I got people aware of what's happening and told people the, you know, what's going on
because you guys have waited at least three weeks, two or three weeks or so for
me to come back and it's like, hey, I'm back. No, I'm not just just just kidding.
So I want to do something fun while the internet's up because I don't have to use
I'm not going to be using my internet. I'll be in the studio. We streaming from there.
So in the next two days or so, try to come to a consensus over the next 48 hours of what
you'd want me to do for actions somewhere around with them. I've already talked to the
mods about it. So somewhere around like 25 to 30 ish dances. I mean, not dances. No,
I mean, 25 to 30 actions, 25 to 30 actions is going to put every single fortnight dance,
but that's not going to happen because that's two step. That would be counting as a double.
If there's a fortnight dance on there, it's getting vetoed. I'm just, fuck it. Let's
just say it. And if you put it, if you put like 20 fortnight dances on it, it doesn't
double. So that doesn't count. You're not going to be able to do that. So it's just
getting fucking vetoed. You know what? Let's just go with this. Don't even put fortnight
on the list because I'm not doing it. Don't even do it. Pick something else. Do something
better. It is double. It's the same area. It's the same spot. It's the same company
that made the game and the same animating studio created it. I didn't want to say
it, but I had to. Now this is not epic, but yeah. So that'll be in the next few days.
Come to a consensus on what you want me to do. And by the way, if you do mention props,
right? I'll give you an example of one that I would definitely wouldn't veto at all.
Absolutely not. That German getting lost kayaking, right? Like, I mean, that's,
that's a fairly non vetoable fun thing that I could do in front of a green
screen with the whole kayak there and be like, oh, rapids, right? I mean,
that's a pretty good idea. If there are props involved, I'm going to need to know,
right? Like I'm going to need to know what props. So if you do want to include
props, it's got to be something that I can obtain. That's not going to cost a
shitload of money because it is that I'm going to have to improvise. Are they
going to what? This chat is too small. I don't like being that close. Do a
little action clown. I that would be tough. You'll see what you come up with
for the most part, though, try to keep it something I can do on my own.
And if there's going to be a shitload of props, maybe the mods can get
involved there and make it so I don't have to buy like a bunch of fucking
weird shit on like Amazon, you know, I still, and that's like,
even if I get two days shipping, it's going to take me a couple of days to get
some of those props, but you'll see. We'll get it going. Any questions?
People are subscribing and giving money and shit and I can't even keep up with
it. I'm so sorry. Thank you, everybody that came in here. You got questions.
Okay. How you doing? I'm doing pretty good. That's pretty good question.
No questions. What's your favorite Fortnite dance? What's probably this
one? I think it's definitely this one, but the kid goes like, right,
but like the backpack kid, something like that. Should I just did a, I
just did a Fortnite dance. I like, you like my ladder? That's because I can
reach up there. You know what I'm saying? It's hard to put those up there.
Well, you're not that, uh, I mean look at how strong I am though.
Come on. Give me a break. Give me a break. These ceilings are like 15
fucking feet tall. Even if you were 6'2", you wouldn't be able to get up
there. It's like, this ceiling's a fucking
30 feet tall. Ah, all right. Any, any real questions?
I'm trying to think about if I didn't, if I missed anything. All right,
let's go, let's break it down one more time real quickly.
No internet still. It's getting resolved. It will be resolved
soon. Hopefully. I have no ETA. Because of that,
iPhone stream. Internet phone stream. iPhone stream. That's why I'm here
doing this. iPhone stream. Uh, uh, because of
that, streaming from a studio in probably three or four days.
Studio stream. Green screen stream. Go to the discord. Get your
nominations in. Find out what you want me to do. 30 actions.
No bullshit. No dumb shit. I mean, well, no bullshit.
You, you. That guy right there that said that exactly what you want me to do
right there. I'm not going to do it. Make sure you get that figured out.
No bullshit. Come to a consensus. No doubles.
And that's it. Are you actually, am I a house tour?
No, I don't want you to know what's in my house.
Here, I'll give you a tour. Let's just show you this, by the way.
You see how, do you see this? Do you think you can reach up there?
This is, this is a five-foot ladder. So right now,
right now, I am like 15 feet tall. You see? Like, I'm, I'm, the ceiling is
still here. And look at this. My arm is like a good two feet.
I'm 5'8". This is five feet. This is like a 12-foot ceiling. You think you,
you think you're so funny? Oh fuck! He's gonna fall!
Oh! That wasn't, look, there's not much I can do with a
phone in my hand. I, like, I, I, I'm, I'm, I'm...
All right. I'm glad we had this conversation. I'm not touring the house.
There could be like shit over there that I don't want you to see. Like,
I don't know. I don't like house tours. I don't, like, I don't know why people
do that. Okay, let's go ahead. Over here.
Hey, that's where I sleep every night. That's right in that bed.
Oh, there's like underwear on the ground. Let me just move that out of the way.
What's this? I just like, this is like my dirty underwear.
Whoops, sorry. Oh, there's, by the way, there's my, oh,
let's go to the garage. There's my car. Oh, cool!
Hey, that's my fucking plates. No, no, you don't,
I don't want anyone to know where I sleep. Because then you'll know, like,
where the bed is. You know, you'll know what, like,
the window is. You'll know where the bed is.
Oh, it takes us some guy, like, oh, I'm gonna case that house. Where,
where, where's all the valuable shit? Oh, this is where I keep my safe of
money. You know, it's just right there. By the way, there's the window, or if
you're curious. I gotta get out there and fix that.
He's gonna fall. I'm not gonna fall. If I fell,
it's not like, what, I'm gonna fall like fucking five
feet. What happened to the other one? It's because I was screaming. That's
good. Good? I don't think that's good.
This is just barely hanging on now. What, what, what did you do?
What did you do? This took so long to do.
This took so fucking long to do. I gotta fix it later.
The whole thing is, the fucking whole thing.
Whatever. What the fuck. Oh, now I know how loud I can get in this. What
happened? Oh, that one fell too. Well, now I
know how loud I can get in this room before
stuff starts to fall off the fucking ceiling. Bad acoustics?
No, they are, they are fucked up. You're right.
You're actually right. Where's Otto? He's, he's
hanging out with Kim right now. He's like sleeping and I'm not going to wake
him up. There's bugs on the wall. Those are not,
all right, fine, fine. Those are fucking caterpillars.
Bugs on the wall. There's just like black slugs coming in. Oh yeah, those
are, those are slugs. They're everywhere in this place.
You want me to eat one? Want me to eat one of those caterpillars on stream?
All right, I'm gonna run out of data. I gotta get out of here. I'm
gonna get a fucking call from Verizon. They're gonna be like, oh, excuse me.
Do you wish that you could have our service?
Verizon Fios, the best fucking service ever, like
absolute number one internet ever. Don't you wish you could get that?
You guys know, I'll shill it every day. I swear to God.
You know that's $39 a month for a 100-100 Verizon Fios connection?
Why won't you just expand? We, please, I want that internet.
Give it to me. I'll pay quadruple. I'll pay septuple for that internet.
Most reliable network in the fucking world. That's time, it's time to move
again. All right, time to move back to Boston.
They got Fios there. Desperate streamer sells out for
internet. No, it's gonna be fine. From the
understanding that we've had, it's not like, oh, the internet just
sucks here. No, it is just a, there's just a problem that needs to be solved
and then we're gonna have lightning-fast speeds from, I'm not gonna even say
their name, because I wanted to work first, you know
what I'm saying? I already did. I already did, you're right.
Never mind. Lightning-fast. Show the ladder before I leave.
Why? I don't get it. Why do you want to see the ladder? I don't get it.
But what? Prove the height of the ladder. Oh, it's staring fucking down.