Hello everybody, welcome to the stream. I'm sorry, I was in chat talking about taxes.
We were discussing taxes, paying taxes and all that stuff. What are taxes? You know, we had to
go through an entire... this is for the vlog viewers, by the way. We had to go through an entire thing
of what taxes are dating back to the British, right? That's where it started and that's, you know,
that's how... that's where it began. And now the British now run the IRS, so we still have to pay
England. It's weird, but you know, no. Yeah, the one thing about taxes I will tell you is if you
are 1099, right? Because I used to be... you get a W-2 and somebody pays your taxes. And so I took
up money for health insurance and retirement and, okay, I don't have to do anything. When you become
full 1099, it's all you, man. You're gonna do it all. And it's just like, wait, hold on, what do I
have to do? But back in 2011, I got a CPA and I made sure... I was like, please, like, make sure
this is all correct. Thank you. And I've been using them for like seven years. Keep those receipts. Oh
yeah. And they have to like... that's like the next part is understanding what is like an expense,
what isn't an expense. It's difficult stuff. QuickBooks self-employed is pretty helpful.
Yeah, I just... I'm an idiot and I'll fuck something up. I'd rather just have somebody that
knows what they're doing that specializes in it, be able to do it, because I can't. I'll open up
QuickBooks and I'll be like, oh yeah, this, this, this, this, send it in. I'll get it wrong.
No, no, no, no. A good accountant is like a good mechanic. If you find one, do everything you can
to keep them. That's, that's the best statement I've read in the last 10 seconds. Even everything
laid out. And never do it for free. The next statement is the best. What about a barber?
That's yeah, there are a couple of things that you really need to hold on to in life. A good
CPA, like a good accountant, right? A good, a good doctor, right? Everybody wants a good doctor,
good accountant, good doctor, good car mechanic, a good lawyer, a good chef. Make sure you always
have a good chef around in your house. A good maid to make sure like you're very clean.
All these people have to come with you, by the way, wherever you go. And they all need a room
in your house. A good mailman. That's right. Yep. Imagine you had a doctor like live in your house.
Oh, that'd be fucking amazing. That'd be the best thing ever. I wish that were the case.
Imagine waking up with like you, you, you brushing your teeth and you're like, wait,
hold on. You're like, you stick your tongue out. There's like a little spot on your tongue and
like your tongue hurts. That's happened to me. And what am I going to make a doctor's appointment
for that? No, no, you just go bang, bang, just like, Hey doc. And it's like, it's like six
o'clock in the morning. He's like, fuck, what is, what is it? Hey, look at my tongue for a second.
He's like, hold on to me. And he like pulls the tongue and let me see that. Nah, that's just an
inflamed taste bud. You're going to be fine. It's like, Oh God. And he goes back to bed.
And then like you go to the next, you know, while that happens, I drop a plate and it smashes on the
ground and the doctor goes back to bed and I'm like, yeah, don't worry about it. I go to the next door.
Uh, maid? Open the door. Yeah. I just dropped a plate on the ground. Can you like help? Can
take care of that? Yeah. Yeah. Sure. Sure. Like they take care of that and you're good.
Oh God. That's got $50. I'm just going to have like a hotel of employees,
not even employees though. It's just all people that do jobs that are, that are very like skilled
jobs, things that, that are difficult to do a service jobs. Have like a police officer too,
just to have in here, just in case like the doctor fights the mechanic over breakfast or something,
like somebody who picks up a fork and he starts to lunge and all that. Oh, the cop is going to
take care of that. Just explaining this is the white house. This is just being the president.
This is the, this is being the president. Uh, anyways, thank you too. But to, all right,
to back us up here. Yes. Uh, having a good accountant is a good thing to have, especially
because you got to make sure you buy the book. Otherwise, uh, I'm going to have to answer that
door and it's my turn to open the door and it's a laundry list of, excuse me, you're coming to
court now. And I'm like, hold on, wait a minute, get the chef. And the chef comes down and he's
like, what's happening? And he's like, oh, you get, you're getting arrested. All right, whatever. I
can't do anything about that. Or it was the chef and I like to take the chef and I like push him
in front of it. It was the chef that did it. What are you talking about? I just cook and they're
like, they like cuff him up. He, oh yeah, he was cooking the books. I understand. And then I like
wink at the, I wink at the fucking guy at the, at the, the officer at the door. I'm like,
fuck that whole segment. What do you mean that joke was awful? Somebody, one of you guys said
that I was responding to it. It was a great joke actually. Mod that guy that made it.
No one said that. Yes, they did. Scroll up. They're now modded. Okay. Anyway, what are we doing?
Where am I? I'm in front of, I'm in front of a stream. Oh, shift the blame. Yeah, it was this guy.
It was this guy, Jacob. It was me. All right, we're going to play, uh, jack pox, jack pox party pox.
That's what we call it here. We're going to play jack box tonight.
Then we might as well just switch over to it right now because, uh, why not? It's right here.
Jack pox party pack, jack pox party pack five. It is going to be fun. Did I say it was going to
be fun? Why am I speaking in the past tense here? That doesn't make very much sense. But,
but more importantly, $50 came in from cookie CRM. 50, $50. Thank you cookie for the 50 bucks.
Hey, German, just a heads up. Uh, patently stupid is not a good game for stream. It's not very funny
or fun to play. Split the room in mad verse city are fantastic. All right, well we'll see.
I mean, we're going to try them all even if we do it once, but I heard, I have heard that a few of
these, at least two or three of them are very fun and very funny, but whatever this is, this is,
this is community night. You know, we do, we do sometimes we do, we do community night here.
You know what I mean? Uh, by the way, speaking of that, how this is going to work tonight
is just kind of scared me. So, uh, in the sub room of the discord is going to get the code.
There are a lot of you now, so good luck getting into the room. If you get into the room,
we kindly ask that you do not come back for another game. Uh, you can only play once. If
there's a way that I can remove somebody or I have to restart or something, that's what we're going
to do, or we might have to make a separate room, I will figure it out, right? But only one time,
only one time. So, I hope you're ready to begin, because I'm ready to begin. Which one are we
going to start with? How about we just go from top to bottom? Does that make sense? Why is this one
not family friendly? This is the only one that's not family friendly. What does that mean? We mean
it. Well, what do you, what does that mean though? All right, well, the parent, okay, this is the not
safe for work trivia game. All right. Oh, let's do it. You don't know Jack. You don't know Jack.
Shit. So how's the audio? Should I turn myself down? What are you trying to say? What are you
trying to say? What are you trying to say? Oh, I didn't tell Twitter. Ah, you're right. I didn't
tell Twitter. What do you say? This is the stream. There's people looking up at my bald fucking head.
I'm not even bald. Why do we do this thing on this channel where things are just absolutely
100% not true and we treat them like they are? You died to pinwheel. No, I didn't. You're bald.
I have fucking more hair than probably half the people on this website. I got a full head of hair.
What, what's the bald thing? You're stupid. Oh, really? I can't. All right. Well, that one might.
I can't fight that one. You're short. Not that short. All right. Let me tweet this up. Oh,
Chunky baloney. Chunky baloney giving out five community subs. Thank you, Chunky.
That is five. That is a five spot from Chunky baloney. I got one. I got one.
Thanks a lot, man. Your hair smells. My whole body smells. What are you talking about?
No, no. I mean, not right now. Hold on a second. I'm supposed to be tweeting out the stream.
Yeah. Jack box five. And then after the stream, hold on. Jack box five. See, now I tweeted it out.
Now everyone can relax. You know what I'm saying? Um, describe, describe the smell. Um,
cinnamon, uh, uh, jade, cinnamon and jade, clean cinnamon jade laundry. There you go.
All right. Uh, this needs to be, uh, right. Audiences on require Twitch, right? That's
important. Post game sharing. Um, I don't think I want to do that. Hi, gibberish. I would have to
delete my Twitch channel if that were the case. Uh, allow room hiding. Yep. Allow room code to be
hidden to prevent players from joining early. Recommended if you're streaming the game. Yes.
Max players eight. Sounds about right. Sounds about right. Let's scroll up a little bit here.
Okay. All right. I think that's good. Make the game loud. Oh no, that was them. Just all right.
Here we go. So, uh, for pro grammatically generated content, I think I'm going to,
I think I'm ready. So how Jack box works, you know, played it streaming services,
they'll tell you pipe is more than just the trivia hit. You don't know. Jack.
It's also a deep well of content that we cannot legally guarantee. You'll ever be able to access
or interact with. But, uh, so you go to jackbox.tv and once you're in jackbox.tv,
you're going to get a room code. If you're in the sub discord, it's going to show up
there in just a moment. What's the matter, Mark? I'm trying to find my blood type,
but these medical forms are just so complicated. Nevermind. Not for this first game by the way.
No, just send all your information to binge pipe and they'll find the
not for the first one. Hey, come on in everybody. Welcome to the first day. Yeah.
History credit card details, voting record, deepest fears, food allergies,
romantic preferences, and lucky numbers. And they'll sort through it to find the data I need
and leftover details for themselves. That sounds great. Looks like I won't need this paperwork.
And with the extra time we can get whatever. Do you like burritos?
I don't know. I'll have to ask binge pipe. Sorry. Sorry. I'll do it again.
The number one over medication that prevents nosebleeds caused by whatever it's we're going
to be here for like four or five hours. It's okay with your mind. Then my taxes is right.
Go to jackbox.tv. Put an HZ NE punch. I am the lion punch. You'll be able to participate as the
audience of the demon ways. Protector of the five shards of the crow core. HZ NE
avenge my father. And that's what I'm going to do.
Yeah. I wanted to, I wanted a mod or two to play the first game and then I was going to
put it in the sub discord and then I accidentally pressed that button.
I have to, my father just saw what happened. I have to do it and I will do it with or without
felt that was going to happen. I'm in the room. What are you talking about?
I'm in the sub discord right now. All right. So everybody's in. No way. Press everybody's
in the start. That's a lion punch on binge pipe. Please just press everybody's in.
Do I, do I have to join? No. Wait, what? Do I have to do that?
To be the new home of you don't know Jack. $50. No, $50 is not a stock photo.
All right. I'm cookie Masterson and I have no idea why they call it a cookie.
Cookie CRM just gave $50. What do you mean I'm not in the game? That reminds me of my childhood dog
because he also ate people specifically mine. I don't, it doesn't automatically put me in
because I'm the host. I have to go on my phone. What? I was the host of the game. I have to,
oh fuck me. I have to be in the browser. I thought I hadn't played in like two years,
whatever. I'm not even in the audience. I got to join the audience.
No, no, I'm turning this off. I can't fucking believe I'm about to do this.
Enter the, what was the room code? HZHN. What's the room code?
HZNE. Enter your name. Bill. Okay, I'm ready. I'm in the audience.
All right. So it's a septillion. Yeah. I hate to lead you on. None of you got it.
A quintillion has 18 zeros and consequently six commas to go along with it.
I need to like, no, this is funny. This is cool. I want to participate. I mean, I would keep all
my money, of course, but the poor can have half the punctuation. Can I participate? I can't. All
right. I'm like, I run the server here. After this question, I'm going to start over.
Everyone's going to be mad. I'm going to disconnect everybody. I'm the server.
I'm just hosting this for people.
Fucking damn it, man. Right at the very beginning too. How could I possibly screw it up?
But, um, cookie. Okay. What'd you pick? You did a bad job.
Well, now we can, we can correct our mistake from beginning.
I just spit all of my fucking screen. God fucking damn it. I'm so upset right now. You have no idea
how mad I am. Not at the, I mean, whatever. I screwed up. I spit all, this is a new monitor.
New monitors in front of me. All right. So this time, first of all, cookie has given a hundred
dollars. Uh, cookie says, German, we know you screwed up. It's okay. We love you. Anyways,
big hearts all around. Have some more money. Cutie. Thank you. Thank you. Hey, thank you.
Thanks a lot, cookie. Well, let's go back in. I, I'm not going to fuck this up again.
So you can wait here. We're going to the chance of, I'm going to, I do want to mod in because it's
fun to get one for the first game. We're going to have mods, right? Like I'm going to put like
a weird body slider in and like pull his eyebrows off. Okay. Don't show the fucking room code.
Some critics say isn't a real service. It's just a framing device for a video. Okay. These are
entitled to their opinions and their privacy. So don't go looking for them. They're fine.
Okay. That's that. Let's make sure we get, I gotta, I have to go into. That's very important.
I almost did it again. With my old streaming service, I can never get a hold of a customer
service representative. Now that I'm a binge pipe customer, they never leave me alone.
I gotta make sure I get it right. I almost just said the name of the room I love.
We're grateful for their ever seeing eye. The second my binge pipe router went out requires
Twitch to log in. I have Twitch. Hold on. I gotta like open up another fucking browser.
What's the fucking code? Thank you, binge pipe.
I am logged in.
Twitch. Am I in? I'm in. I'm in. I'm in as Twitch. All right. I'm in as Twitch.
All right. Here we go. I'm in Twitch. I'm in. All right.
Good luck everybody. And we are full. Welcome everybody. Thanks for playing. Here we are.
All right. Everybody's in. Sit back and relax. I'm in. Everybody's in, right?
That's me, right? That's not like another person. How do I get this back over here?
Snack on this content. All right. We can play now. Finally. I'm Cookie Masterson. And if my mom
could see me now, I'd say, what are you doing, mom? I need a note jacked. While I hosted this game.
Everyone in? I didn't think you knew this many people. And I see we've got some gawkers.
All right. So we've got two mods, grump and no super you. And then we've got a bunch of other
random people. All right. Now we start for real. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for being so
patient. Thanks for being so patient, guys. All right. I do.
I don't want to. So hold on a second. If after taking a sociology class,
that's not even a, this is even a question. It's not even a real question.
I mean, I know the answer, but that what kind of question is that? Can't do anything right. Can you
more ease folkways and laws are for cultural norms. Ethics can only help shape norms.
Okay. Although drinking 12 beers a night also has an effect on the shape of norms.
And how would our lovely audience do? Oh, just what I look for in an audience. 25% correct.
That means that right answer is worth even more. 700 of you. You can thank me later.
All right. Here we go. No, I don't want another question. I want one of these weird things.
Take a good look. How is this not safe for work? You know, the weird thing about the novel,
the three musketeers is there's a fourth musketeer wandering around that wasn't this one,
the not safe for work one started talking about it. If the musketeer left out of the umbrella term,
three musketeers angrily trademarked their own candy bar, what could they call it?
What could they call it? The port, those peanut chew Maurice's Milky way or d'Artagnan's date bar.
What? I don't, I don't, these are like computer generated
Google questions that an AI decided. It will never go near something called Lumiere's nut log.
Oh, what not safe for work. The three musketeers, but he spends the whole book as musketeer number
four. It's all right. I got $744. All right. Super hot aliens for those Huey and Martin short.
I got it right. 35%. Wow. How do we get to do these cool ones down here?
Mixed tapes and marmalade. And what goes with that better than a dis or dat.
Dis or dat. I'm going to list seven things. And for each one, you tell me if it's something that
happened to Paddington bear in the delightful family film, Paddington two, something that
happened to rapper Lil Wayne in real life. Okay. Don't think too hard. But I mean both.
Give you a few seconds to decide between Paddington. Spoilers for Paddington bear.
And you're all doing this together. So let's do it. No, I don't want to see that born in New
Orleans. Um, I don't know. I raised by his aunt Lucy. Uh, no, I don't know. It could be both
worked. It was Paddington bear, a window cleaner. It was, uh, this, this has got to be some story
where Paddington bear. Oh shit. I didn't answer. I don't, why would Paddington bear is not a human
being. So no, that's Paddington bear. That's Paddington bear. That's not Lil Wayne.
Was in a coma. Uh, I don't think Lil Wayne was ever in a coma. What? When was Lil Wayne in a coma?
You can't spell disastrous without us, but you, why he was, you just plain sucked at that desert.
Holy shit. Binge pipe customer retention protocol has been activated.
Sounds like it's screw time. That is the truth cookie. Use the screw to make answering a question
harder for all the other players. The results may surprise you and you'll receive a bonus for
anyone who answers incorrectly. This is like an ADHD computer. Use them wisely or don't you do you.
The question that doesn't care. Are you kidding me? See that, what, but that sentence
is hurting me. Stig Larsen. The answer of course is Stefan Edberg. It did in 20th century
Dov Lundgren is the guy from Rocky. No, that's not him. Uh, I don't know.
Oh, I just gave everybody an answer. Dov Lundgren did not found Ikea. No wait, Dov Lundgren is the
WWE guy. Oh no, that's another Dov.
Uh, what is sex? Oh, that's why you can't join it.
What? Oh, he made it harder. I don't understand. They just made it hard to read?
No, I just picked the wrong one because I got screwed. I just picked the wrong one.
It's incorrect on this side.
That's the whole point. Yeah, well why are we giving people in Jack Puck's party pack?
The blue turtle shell from Mario Kart is trivia questions, man.
Currently player four is in the lead. All right, Drosophilia doing all right.
These players are making everyone feel bad. So here comes the screws. And don't forget. Oh,
more screws. And they'll net you more cash for each player that gets the question wrong. So
don't be afraid to use them. The rest of you better answer quick. Screw this entire game.
Remember questions are worth twice as much. Oh, plus two. What are you trying to say?
Just wonderful cookie.
Try this on for size. Turtles all the way down.
Going by the divine comedy. Are there more levels of hell or seasons of entourage?
More levels of hell or seasons of entourage? There is more entourage.
So watch out. What the fuck?
I'm just trying to answer the question. Don't forget your password.
What is the password? We have to put a password in. What? Did I get it? Wrong password.
I can't even type the password in right. According to Dante, there are nine levels of hell,
but there are only eight seasons of entourage. I did type the phrase and I couldn't get it.
What is entourage? It's when Mark Wahlberg showed on camera
how cool his life is. That's the whole show. That's actually the entire show.
There's nothing else to that show besides Mark Wahlberg has a really cool life.
While solving a mystery all the game spoilers the tag of his collar floating in a pool of blood.
How do they know it's his? It's shaped like a paw print. It's shaped like a scooby snack.
It's shaped like his head or it has his initials on it. What is on scooby-doo's collar? I think
it's it has his initials on it. Stop giving people answers.
I forgot you could hear me.
Congratulations everybody.
Player's choice now offers content surveys. What does that mean? Would you like an attractive
question or a question with a great sense of humor? Use your device to select your preference.
Uh I'm gonna say well I'm not gonna tell you who I vote for because that would be that would be
against you know I'm going in there and I don't want you to know what was I doing oh yeah I didn't
turn my lights on it's like dark in here it's dark in this room there we go the votes are in
wait why didn't that not work you have chosen what a great sense of humor up next a question
with a great sense of humor which of these is not one of the four humors ancient greeks believed
made up human biology i know this i know this black bile or white pus
i know this i would say it right now but you guys would all hear me i love this part
is it phlegm is one of them blood is one of them the humors were believed to be blood
phlegm black bile and the fourth was yellow bile got some smart people here yes there were
two bios just like modern humor the greeks thought geno genos confirmed for smash brothers
behold a community first a business second who wrote that track
what is it i could do without these splash screens in polaris and vega we thought you'd like
dancing with the stars rupal's drag race shark tank or duck dynasty i'm polaris and vega i don't
know what it's even asking this um let me pick this one i'm gonna go with that one okay that would
make the most sense to me oh i'm gonna enjoy this minus two thousand names of stars in our galaxy
those are stars would be what you want dancing with polaris dancing with vega
you know what i'm saying stars named polaris and vega then what are we all doing
the youtube joke uh but i hate to tell you jack uh there's an entire group wasn't there an entire
youtube group that was called polaris it was like 5 000 youtubers if you decided to start you were
right shapes which would offer the most stable relationship who offers the most stable relationship
the charming rhombus the passionate circle or the hunky triangle no no no i know this one
oh in emote only mode because of uh answers
is it what it's not the rhombus the rhombus has like the legs in that
triangles are the strongest and most stable of the shapes no it's not that's bullshit and the
rhombus has the why they cut pizza right out bottom because it will never ever let you down
that's a big they did it because they want to make a pizza reference
pizza should be cut into rhombus shapes you made it to the attack
when you see an answer jack attack the category tap it on your device the faster you pick up an
answer the more cash you make oh elmo the last the latest avenger each time you're wrong i'm taking
some cash away and be careful oh my you should have gone for the head
that stand for something pick the words that the acronyms stand for good luck all right what are
we doing hey uh what is what's screaming at me why are you screaming at me huh what i have to
scroll down here um i think i did it oh i was still going well i'm like being quiet i don't know i
don't understand that's not it i thought that was it and we're still going uh no no no this is very
very odd what how is that how was a laser not energy the laser is an energy guys uh what they
come in it's sacred no no they don't no they don't they uh i got it wrong
no they don't like sneak in i have to it has to be to match up with
how did i not get them all right no i don't mash that was a mash was a show about medicine
what what it's a show about a certain medical people and what it wasn't a show about a
met and wasn't medical at all apparently mash was not a medical show nice work player four try to
enjoy this fleeting moment of glory before you remember you don't know jack at least i have
587 dollars all right thanks for playing guys all right so one two three four
remember these names because we want new players
new players i don't want to play this one though all right now we're gonna go to uh we're just
gonna go down in order i'm gonna go split the room the what-if game where anything is possible
create strange and divisive hypothetical situations cool looking forward to this one
let's get the settings right here audience is enabled uh make sure the other stuff is as well
require twitch yes please allows the first player into sensor players answers uh-huh
yep uh post game sharing uh allow room code hiding and eight players extended timers
oh that it says recommended for streamed games okay no i'm not i don't i want to be able to
censor answers because what if they're bad turn down the host if you want to be confused and lonely
so looks good i got room hiding on right yes okay time to play same deal as last time uh here
this time uh no mods on this one i'm gonna do sub game let me just make sure i don't show this on
stream yet join us all right good luck if you already played then we're gonna have well we will
have to get rid of you if you come to this one so good luck okay looks pretty good looks like uh we
got some new people right i don't see any uh familiar names here come on in they can change
their names well they have to be linked to twitch meow you have to have your twitch linked as we
explore the deepest recesses of your mind you will build strange and complex worlds god damn it
i'm just like putting the code over here and oh fuck me honest to god there's room for more
jesus join the party sorry i'm sorry everybody like i just my brain is like in three different
places okay i'm in i'm in this one mother fucking god come on in i'm sorry to the people that got
in before that's my fault i'm sorry takes me three tries to learn i have to fall down on the bike
three fucking times before i realize i have to pedal the bike you know what i mean like give me a
break mom i understand i can't i fell down on the bike twice you have to pedal jeremy oh oh all right
okay i'm sorry guys seriously but i think everyone's in let's go not if you start on a hill
damn it do not be startled explore the deepest recesses of your mind you will build so embarrassed
i really am i'm embarrassed right now and your thumbs
pathetical situation missing one key part will be transmitted to your device
like this one okay ads before online videos have been banished in their place are 15 second videos
of this they are not skippable is life better there are infinite possibilities you could write
into completely that's kind of funny choose wisely though because everybody else will then answer yes
or no and you will earn i see if you split the room fitting name huh for those of you in the
audience you'll be competing as one player your answers will be determined by a majority vote
yes even in a nebulous void democracy is important at the end of the yes you do not need the game to
play the most divisive you just need to go to the browser got it good now let's begin you don't have
to have the game you just have to have a browser on a tablet phone browser Abraham Lincoln never
existed in another he existed but he wore a fedora it's time to split the room what
okay it's time to build some strange worlds complete the scenario do i try to read this
i don't think i should read this okay i'm not gonna read this
okay i have to read it out loud though i won't understand okay i got it i got it that was just
from that's from undertale that's from undertale that's the flower from undertale okay now we're
just waiting for the vote when we're gonna see why it was a good idea to add the extended timers
there it is 30 seconds and now split the room banned but not forgotten chapter one of nine has
just outlawed this a friend introduces you to the black market do you risk significant jail time
in order to get one uh the government has just outlawed me a friend introduces you to the black
market do you risk significant jail time in order to get to be able to watch the stream
i mean i can't i don't want to influence this vote or anything but i mean unless i'm i know i'm
not going to influence the vote i'll take one germa please on one hand though i mean
maybe if i was made out of gold right i'm not currently but maybe you'd really enjoy the stream
but i'm not made out of gold so the longer it takes the room to answer the more bonus points
you get i'm the only one who said no what about you guys did we split the room purchaser beware
what you just found your dream house and it's super affordable however you discover it's so
cheap because there's this in the basement do you buy the house
you buy the house you just found a dream house super affordable help you discover it's cheap
because the flower from undertale is in the basement are you still gonna buy it
then on one hand you're gonna have a really cool adventure probably
you're gonna meet some characters be have fun with your friend new friend sans on uh from
undertale on the other hand though you just want to live in a house and it's not worth it even if
the sheep go just go next door you don't have to worry about it there we go and he split the room
i split the room brace yourself for the compliment bible i said that loud and i
typed nice thing anyone has ever said about you and who said it for every nice book looking at
the book you have to spend a minute looking at looking at do you spend 10 minutes reading it
is a well is a book full of every nice thing anyone's ever said about you i don't want to
know that for every minute you spend look at what i mean that's not i mean i don't want to
why would you want a book that has everything that someone said about you nice you know what
i mean like if you open it up you're gonna then you're gonna start to pretty much think
about what they're saying oh wow i really think jeremy's hair is so nice i really hope he doesn't
cut his hair ever it's the nicest hair oh jeremy's hair is so nice it's like i can't cut my hair ever
again what if i get a haircut i got short haircut and then that person is not in the book anymore
i'm flipping through freaking out like wait wait no one's talking about the hair anymore
they hate it you wouldn't see the yo because it would disappear because it would be gone
because that person wouldn't write it presents yes go i'm trying to work the room don't you
understand hire an impersonator to do your job for you your co-workers five bucks an hour they
think it's you their work is good but they have one strange tick they do this do you
so for five dollars an hour you can hire i could hire an impersonator to stream for me
everyone will just think it's me their work is very good but they have one they dab all spontaneously
here's one i like to call shelf help you're somebody who feels lost in life one day you
stumble upon a self-help book at a store you open it and immediately find answers to your life
when you flip to the cover you notice it was written by this person do you buy it
you're somebody who feels lost in life one day you stumble upon a self-help book at a store you
open it and immediately find answers to your life you flip over the cover you notice it was written
by you do you buy it i mean it's it's that is a that is a cursed object yeah but why is it cursed
you're gonna put it back don't you want to know on the other end opening that book could spot
could change the course of your entire life right and maybe just picking it up and putting it back
is enough for you to understand that holy shit there's some things that i'm gonna have to do
some stuff you know what i mean i would buy it i was i would fucking buy it are you kidding me
chunky bologna would not buy it well i'd want to i wouldn't want to read that in a dark room
or bust where nobody could see me your home nobody knows what i'm doing the statue of you
in your honor but it has a unique donor group if the statue goes up a plaque will read the
monument was paid for by this do you let them build it your hometown wants to build a statue
of you in your honor which has a unique donor group the plaque or read that the moment was paid
by tax dodgers do you let them build it well okay so you got you get one hand i don't want
to be associated with like tax dodgers right that's not a good thing but does the monument
go up if you know is that i don't see every whoa hold on a minute here it's kind of split
i got a perfect split for justice can see you've been accused of a crime you didn't commit a pro
bono lawyer reaches out to represent you this individual is intelligent and has a lot of
experience however they just so happen to be this do you let this person represent you
what
are they are they a lawyer am i going to get there's no part two to this you know what i'm saying
for free intelligent has a lot of experience they're just sans that's the second undertale
reference and like i don't even i don't even fucking play that game i played undertale three
years ago and then i played delta rune it's not something we talk about all the time why are we
getting all these undertale references literally just played delta rune yeah but like hey he was
in the rumble that yeah he was feast your eyes on you must be this tall to vote oh i wonder how
funny this one's gonna be enacted before you are considered eligible to vote you must do
this there's an actual dog on this year's ballot that is close to being elected do you step up
and vote uh before you're considered eligible you get a free ipod that that's it um who doesn't
want a free ipod with no strings attached oh hey welcome to come welcome to the polls yeah
here's a free ipod for for showing up actually that would be i would actually wouldn't no can i
can i change my answer i wouldn't want to go that would be that would be insane that would cause a
fucking riot free ipods to everybody it'd be like black friday why did i say yes this one is called
for a good clause here's the last one a charity raising money for straight pets asks you to
participate in a fundraiser how do they okay help generate money well by doing this do you
having a mystery oh man but but what is that what is uh but what is it was mystery but what if
mysteries it could yeah but like no i don't know what it is if mystery meat could be like vegan
hot dogs right technically here's where everybody stacks up at the moment how are we doing how are
we doing how are we doing first place there will be two options to choose from door number one is
already provided you will decide what's behind door number two remember you want to chat second
place oh and if you correctly predict a certain player's decision you'll learn some bonus points
oh shit okay i'm ready write an option that you think only some people would choose
okay okay i got it oh okay oh i gotta think something good for this one
oh oh oh oh this is so fucking hard okay i'm ready it's almost starting almost got almost
got the fire almost got the fire time's running out it's starting oh fuck what i start a fire in
why i'm so excited right now i don't know why pick your forever home you're down to two options
right down to two options that are only five feet tall and the other has this which apartment
flaw do you settle for huh so they both cost 1.8 million dollars
imagine fucking building a carpeted kitchen what your apartment do you settle for
god no my lord if you didn't have any sinks what the hell would you do
how you gonna wash your hands you gonna wash your hands in the bathtub you're gonna do
dishes in the bathtub prediction you just earned some bonus points oh well never mind
oh what do you settle for doorways only five feet tall or a dad on the walls
five foot tall doorways really are fucking that sucks that really sucks got the correct prediction
too let's switch things up you and four other patrons at a buffet restaurant are being at a
buffet if you eat everything that's left in an hour you'll be let go you either drink a gallon
of gravy or this food which food for your life nobody can drink a gallon of gravy
a gallon gravy with 10 pounds of mashed potatoes no you can't physically eat 10
pounds of mashed potatoes you'll die you're all gross you'll die if you eat this no dice
you don't know me you'd die i i picked that in a second it took me one second to pick that
the second that door opened i it took me a second to click on the answer
gallon gravy or a can of worms i would eat the can of worms in a fucking second
are you kidding me a gallon of gravy versus just deal with just eating a can of worms and get to
whose ass i don't understand does it matter i mean kind of moving on you need to rent a car
and the only rental vehicles plastered with advertisements you can rent a car advertising
a gentleman's club or this which car ad do you drive around with which car nobody even knows
what that fucking means you know what i mean nobody knows what this is so who cares yeah the
the 4 000 people here know what that is but if you're driving around at a rental car
you make some random lady on a bus is going to look over and be like oh my god he died to
pinwheel from dark souls that's fine it's an easy pick the clown convention everybody i mean why
who cares about the clown convention gentleman's club or a police car with siren blazing which
what are you driving around in it's an ad that's not how it works
ah my stomach i was like i'm instead of a rental car you do whatever
to this come on i won i won the game i won the game don't stop get out of here
the audience get the most likes would you look at that most dislikes oh my god that one was
kind of fun all right but we can we can play through other ones but that one was fun let's
go back to uh we got mad versus city there's the one coming up next but before we do that
i've been drinking soda and coffee and i have to pee really bad so this is gonna be like a two
second break i'll be right back this is just this is a quick just piss really quick all right let's
do this so just uh quickly we can go for about just over an hour i want to make sure what is
aware of the schedule remaining schedule for this week so obviously we're gonna do this tonight i
don't really have like a time limit for this or how long this is gonna be maybe like another
couple hours few hours of this tomorrow tomorrow uh around the same time maybe i'm actually not
sure i'm gonna play red dead redemption 2 online with a friend or two uh you'll see who you'll see
spoiler alert it's vinnie whoops so i'm not sure when that's gonna be starting
and maybe another one or two people too if we can maybe find somebody that would like to play but
that's kind of what we're gonna do tomorrow i don't have a start time but that's what's
gonna happen tomorrow and less i mean there could be a reason why it doesn't happen but
because you saw the internet how it was kind of the rock star internet servers the rock star
servers will fall fucked up so we'll see if we can even play it and then sunday is the movie night
the sunday's movie night submissions are closed by the way just in case you were curious
we're gonna watch a bunch of random shit so we've got three streams in a row here coming up
including this one so there's that's the plan that's the tentative plan i'm gonna try red dead
tomorrow let's keep building mad oh yeah i can do the settings in here all right same deal
audience is on extended timers is on require twitch is on the manual censoring is on hide
allow room code hiding yes eight players sounds good so i don't know how this one works just mad
versus city don't forget to join oh i will not forget i'm not going to forget this time all right
again if you've already played we will remove you if you play again just be aware come on i think
that looks good i think it looks okay don't see any of the names from previously so sweet come on
in guys what's the discord uh discord this will be a link somebody can link it just wait for
a couple more seconds or so so close here we go i have no idea how this works but this is a
apparently you make lyrics or something like that we'll find the fuck up yo you know it's your boy
shadow master mc cookie and tonight we got a lot of interesting mcs in here dj rage tell them how
the game plan is about to go down how's it work hey hey yo don't step on that uh where are you
never mind here's how you do it we'll ask you for a word or what's up with your
you then write a line that rhymes with it we do that about two times and you have your four line
verse what okay so we have to rhyme and we vote on that winner which honestly you all are all
right so this is so we have to put a word robots destroy the city do you get your words together
time to get it started all right i'm ready all right all my hip-hop heads we need you to
write a word or phrase then an entire line that rhymes with the one that we give back to you
you gotta do that twice god you need help just use that suggestion button all right
all right here we go and you you go you're going up against somebody all right i'm gonna fill this
out okay i'm gonna write a we've got a red line here bang got it oh this one is gonna light them
up okay here we go another one uh oh fuck i don't can i go back oh fuck hold on i got i got i got
a minute i'm fine okay what is what's this what's this what's this what i don't understand i guess
i'm ready yeah i'm ready okay we're almost almost done i screw i kind of screwed up but it's all
right you know you click faster well i only got 20 more seconds i'm clicking as hard as i can
i don't understand what do you mean click faster here's the matchups for round one
yo we got rounds two robot battle rappers ready to go so let's go on and get it in
yo hit those voting buttons during the rhyme all right mr sam man versus krosky
my talent's so big we're running out of gold and no shot streamer running in my way and sold
i ain't about in it's the fact that i chat in posting memes and notes and procrastinating
i got big plans i'm a brain yak roses are red violets are blue that's it melt on the tongue
like cheeseburger one thing's for sure i wrote this line oh fuck and i'm out of the state
i'm gonna give you a pass on that because this is your first time doing this but
don't ever come back with that wacky round two time to vote well i mean
i voted i'm not gonna tell you who i voted for but democracy fails i don't think democracy will
work out here let's see total votes 797 71 percent cash and cheer bonus congratulations
krosky where my mc is that i wrote this line let's get it started all right we got kenny
versus box guy box guys going first work i'm a master stream i came here to win but i will lose
i'm no gangsta i'm the original right wire in bed
people are angry we need some heat i'm too hot my body's made of red hot chili peppers
i see your thoughts and she has to help us my mouth's like a trumpet my brain's like a piano
my rhymes real good don't you know no you guys are gonna cheer that one
uh it actually kind of rhymed hit the voting button pick somebody in bed
total vote 783 less people voted than last time what happened victory to kenny and my next two mcs
all right let's go ready to go i'm ready bring it on bring it on scrooge some kind of a bird
i'm sorry you can't be heard i'm so hot i got sponsored by cox
yeah you're back down cause i'll eat your socks oh how am i gonna answer that one
i'm gonna beat this one it's a showdown and my words are my laser electricity is a game
hope you brought a teaser don't look now i stole your the deli what did you say hold the jelly
i fucked it up but the first line was fire okay ding ding the bell has rang vote to see who was
the dopest mc it told me to name a place so i said the deli instead of deli so i added an
extra word that doesn't mean that it wasn't fucking on like burning let's see 859 oh what
what now it's time for the next matchup where my two battle is that this one's fun i like this one
all right kaiju versus start of my victory trip you'll be doing sick kickflips my rhymes fly like
rockets explode like gamers those rockets right onto my haters
you know it's your turn right oh my words are so fresh they smell like a croissant
the important thing is we're all having fun my favorite team is brush floss and eat
oh
they were both good they were both good
oh this one's great i wonder i'm curious who's gonna win this one
834 i'm surprised by that wow i thought it was gonna be close that's how you say oh i know
but it's funny that the game decided to do that let's check the scores
yeah well it's all right just wait till i get my hands on it next time tell us why you think
you are all that follow those instructions on your device okay i'm gonna destroy this one
uh how do i i don't know how to fucking i don't know how to spell that i gotta figure out how to
spell that word right is that correct is that how you spell it yeah okay oh bingo oh man
good luck good luck to whoever comes up against me that's all i gotta say
okay and now i need this okay this is why i gotta bring it home right here
yeah there didn't used to be robots around and that was about a pizza
okay here we go and got it why can i not pick one of these
i'm i'm not my mouth why can i not pick one of these
destroy click it why can i i did i already get one yeah good luck to anybody that's going up
against me you like god i got good luck i'm gonna get signed after this one here's the
undercard and main event for round two somebody made a bet get this money battle of number one
battle of number two let's go bring it on you're gonna feel me right in the medulla oblongata
you look in all angry while i sip this room chata your acts of above you sound just like the beetles
you're in god's house now welcome to this deeper give me a break thank y'all yo where the next body
get your gears in gear maybe you'll understand when you're shorter you're the size of a quarter
yeah anyone home in there hey oh i almost stepped on your mouth oh what a great wrap
god what a great one you're a nice robot all is over you gotta use your devices
come on but my i that was so crafted
time to vote yeah i might be shorter but come on toe had more heart on his
i was that was that's 60 40 holy shit that was closer than it should have been
next battle so we need the next two cats to step up and get down
all right box guy versus mister wait on this reason that you're full of potato
and your face is red as a tomato have you ever considered a career in buying at convention
my doctor says i'm rime intolerant let's keep it moving it's time for you to come back
hold on now you're about to get maimed while these enemy gamers get destroyed
freight trains coming right at your toe real unlucky that you're my foe
was all right that you thought you was about that last one was okay find another hobby check
tell me who was the whack cat and then tell me who was the hotline oh that's tough find another
hobby voting time right now well we're all we're all not professionals here guys okay
i'm rime intolerant let's see wow that's actually pretty surprising
that was that was under the assumption that would be pretty close
okay the next one all right we got kenny versus uh krosky again i'm a hurricane you're a ring
i'm not one bling but you're insane your flow is a disaster like a category five birth
let me see in the chat some germy earth category five birth what the fuck does that mean
ready kid here comes another oath don't pop a lid here's a loaf flip to the end and see that i dab
witness the sick memes that i can grab oh man uh you yeah krosky played to the audience though
he's talking about dabbing and i don't know that's tough you gotta get them votes in
the votes in they both win category five birth first he takes it twenty five thousand dollars
i need my next two couple of mcs to step up all right so this is this is the last one right
all right let's see around town is that you got real lazy this stream's got me feeling hazy
okay you had it you had it you had it was right there it was a meatball down the middle of the
plate oh that's your music i thought it was a yarmulke spouting gibberish like a shitty streamer
let's go get him up you can't beat me my rhymes just bop
the last line okay that's cool the battle is over it's time for you to pick up your devices
and vote yerma it's always yerma right now you're just a shitty streamer let's settle this for the
race around the world i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to do it i'm not sure if i'm going to be
able to do it i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to do it i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to
let's settle this for the race around the block i don't want to rap at it anymore
let's see who can run faster 25 000
we got another round one more let's check out the numbers let's see who winning this right now
all right i got i got a little bit of room here all right now it's time to get them lyrics flowing
you got to get in them so let them have it okay here we go
uh let's see let's see how to get this going make sure you spell it right i could spell it wrong
i could spell it wrong god damn it now i'm gonna lose uh okay okay uh something good uh
ah i gotta get this um um um um i don't know i don't know quick take the headphones up
now if you can't think of anything at all you can use that right for me but
okay got it that was at the buzzer i got it just barely okay we got the card for the final round
you ready let me see you let me see it now let me hear you spit it no i'm ready this game ain't
over until i see you die let's go home and have a little fun you try to match wits but can only
match hats hiding at home i'm out catching rats all right hot fire last round come on let's see it
you done over there or are you gonna keep beating this game is hard i feel like cheating
it's hard not to choke when your lines are trashed this game sucks got to go clear my cash
oh man okay now it's over who's the dopest rapper who's the wackest cat
that was that was good he got it that was i mean box guy that was a good attempt it was
that's a good one what the fuck is champ doing
now it's time for the next couple what the hell is going on over here all right kenny let's see
i'm sweet as honey you're sour as grapes good start work out you're in bad shape
whatever you do i don't give a freak my rhymes are just sick that was that had that had some
structure to it did you hear what they just said that's structured to it what's wrong with you
were you raised by don gorms i see you around park sniffing ass though listen to you i'd rather
listen to kane and i would even pay last time to use your devices to vote on who brought it strong
kane 18 seconds to decide who is the rap rap god this round let's see who won what the
fuck is happening all right put it in sub only you know what it is that has to happen unfortunately
unfortunately that has to happen listen that'll make you imbecile like decker keen i'll make you
stay a while it fucked it up you i got a whiff of rotten cheese keen is in the building you beat
her been the knees whatever it it didn't say it right it didn't say it right your mom is so dumb
she says rap rhymes with taco no wonder you're such a wacko trying to keep up let me get you
in front watch out for that don oh i almost just skipped it all right thank god i didn't
time to pick somebody to vote for let's get those votes in i had some misspellings in the
they didn't phonetically pronounce the correct way to vote come on i think i did a decent job
oh well oh well i tried good job i did try hey man please don't step on me
all right here's the last one listen now and shut your ass i'm gonna copy our son be the copy
your game is ancient like mario
is this how you play acting like a bum i've got more talent just in my thumb
my verse is legend yours is shit in mccain who might add well split that's that was a
both pretty good does it both really good both good officially over use your devices
and swear penalty that was the dopest mc that's hard but i think i made the right choice here
let's get those votes in this is the final vote right wrap with a swear you get a penalty yeah
end quote i knew it was gonna be close give it up to the mcs now we got who won who is it who's
the winner who's the victor scooch almost a million dollars congratulations congrats to you
clap clap clap clap clap well that was really fun that's the best one so far all right what
else we got we got two more patently stupid and then zepal dome this one doesn't have an audience
i heard this one sucks this this is just like a party game you play with five six people right
they don't work okay play it anyway i mean okay we can't i kind of want to just see what it is
i mean i can just kill the server in a second no no it sucks that bad one guy said that
at least fling yourself and win you fling yourself around yeah this isn't like questions or it's you
just kind of jump around a screen this does sound like splatoon and well well i think the game
crashed how does jack box crash that seems like something that's impossible to crash
all right well what about the other one patently stupid do you need people to be talking maybe i'll
save that one so that's that's when you play with like a like a room full of people okay well it's
kind of a without people who talking all right well um i want to do this one again this one was
fun we'll do these two again this one was kind of a split the room was fun this one was really fun
this one is just a party game and then this one you need people to be able to talk all right let's
do split the room go to the other jack box i could open i could play the fourth one too
i just wanted to see you check this one out first you know okay required twitch room
censoring that's right instead of timers and wrong okay and yeah well monster seeking monster is
really fun we'll play that one all right let me uh make sure i don't show this and make sure i get in
i'm in okay guys remember if you've already played leave room for those that have not
i think we've got all new people join us i'm in i misspelled it everybody's in let's go
split the room this one was fun meow do not be startled i am here to go as we explore the
deepest recesses of your mind you will build strange and complex worlds using only your
we already know how to do this and we already know how to do this we this is our second time
but one where the possibilities are determined by your friends scared you should be it's time to
split the room trying to come 99 seconds all right i got a scenario here time to complete it
okay what all right that's pretty good i like this one we already know what
what chat is gonna choose what do you have what do you guys have for chat
oh wait actually i don't want to know that it's supposed to be a secret i'm not supposed to know
oh yes we know it's a secret don't tell him all right well we'll find out we'll see what you
pranksters are doing what's going on he just got really angry what was that hurry up time's running
out three two wow right the buzzer somebody somebody did it binge pie presents be careful
what they wish for why sub only because the people just like spamming here we go i don't know what
the hell is going on but get one wish as a prank your pal wishes your right foot was replaced with
this do you use your one wish to change it back oh my god you awaken a genie you and your best
friend each get one wish as a prank your pal wishes your right foot was replaced with a webcam facing
do you use your one wish to change it back i mean uh is the webcam connected to anything
where is it is it broadcasting is it recording is it even plugged in this is a very very important
question uh can i like cover it can i put like a sock over it can i put tape on it what a shitty
friend yeah i know really i'm over complicating it well he did a good job he split the room
the longer it takes the room to answer the more bonus points you get oh damn up next is
why would you put wouldn't vote no regret well because i don't know you can find a way to figure
it out this person baby on the way free child care for the first seven years of your kid's life
but free child care baby and they're gonna name it this do you agree to the terms absolutely
fucking 100 no who cares free child care for seven years and i have to buy i have to make
boneless pizza free child care the kid would be a legend i know you can just rename him after that
i'll say 450 000 dollars seven years the name the name is a lifetime that name see yes really
room code is right here oh is it you went and now know your angles know your angles
you have figured out the key to a perfect photogenic smile but it means that instead
of saying cheese you have to say this you are taking a photo with nobel peace prize winner
malala you soft side do you use your trick i was i was literally about to hit sensor as fast as i
could i had no idea what that could have been um i instead of cheating this the whole thing is
to split the room though so i mean what stinky cheese cheese it's cute i don't think any you
would not say stinky cheese seven to one split and a time bonus brace yourself for real friends
real friends your imaginary friend since childhood suddenly materializes as this thing
it follows you everywhere the only way to get rid of it is to kill it you're on your way to work
do you get rid of it huh what do you do your magic friends since childhood suddenly materializes as
an 18 wheeler follows you everywhere you have to kill it to get rid of it your own way to work
you're gonna you're gonna kill it you're gonna get rid of it use him to get to work
absolutely sell it zero here we go split it split the rope come on just sits behind you
drives around next to you this scenario is called the saint versus the scoundrel
you run a charity that feeds and clothes the poor but an evil billionaire decides that
every time you raise ten dollars to help the unfortunate he will do this do you still help
the poor oh my god but that it's like you're gonna die you're gonna die your testicles are
gonna explode what are you supposed to do do you get to wear a cup can i wear like four pairs of
jeans do i does it have to be do i have to have it just been kind of hanging out it's naked
that's causing that's causing damage that's real damage
yes feast your eyes on sauce that is awesome sauce that is awesome you have the power to
remove the word awesome sauce from the english lexicon it will never be voted again however
it will be replaced with this new popular expression is it worth it
dude who cares awesome sauce come on just so somebody says awesome sauce what's wrong with
that like if you were if you were at uh for instance like you're just at the casino maybe
like two weeks ago and you pulled a lever and you won 40 bucks on like a one dollar spin and you say
awesome sauce and you high five your friend what's that something wrong with doing that
something wrong with doing that apparently why is that such a bad thing
i mean it's one of my favorite words i hope it doesn't get replaced i say it like every five
minutes and i just like stupidly split the room i don't say awesome sauce don't worry it's time for
i love hate new york okay you have been banned from new york city you know and from new york
set foot in there again that you must do this do you do it yeah you've been banned from new york
in order to set foot that you must and i live in bro all right what do i have to do do i just have
to go stand in front of it you're banned from new york city and for some reason you have to do you
have to just go stand there what's the catch is there a catch how do you get there visit go in
well just like you can just walk in and like turn around let's have to like walk in visiting
doesn't mean anything here's one cheers to the confused couple if you're banned from new york
city you're giving a toast like you you are banned from ever going to new york you just have to go
to you just walk in and then walk out you can remember is this do you blurt it out uh
what you get you say 100 wonderful things if it comes to her new husband totally blank
is that you can remember
uh censor it quick
what do we got yeah whatever that don't matter so what if he dabbed on stream i'm sure he's a
wonderful wonderful person caring fun to be around get ready for very intelligent very handsome
like it's okay one of your good childhood friends recently moved to the city you reside in
he means well but when he's in big groups he starts over explaining this subject even when
no one asks do you invite him to your birthday party uh well here's the problem i've i do this
like oh you know i got colitis and i like my my colon's all fucked up
diarrhea i am this friend you didn't even have to make the joke so i mean yes why not invite him to
the birthday party of course because i've been invited to birthday parties and others before
i've been at parties and get-togethers where i i'm avoiding the the cheese dip oh you gotta try the
cheese dip no i see i can't my i you know i'm like that blood and the colitis that i had diarrhea
and it's a thing but back in like 2009 i was diagnosed with it and yeah i've done that before
and let me invite me to your fucking party what what why would you it's the you're actually
writing colons here's where everybody stacks up at the moment what the fuck is that what is that
there will be two options to choose from door number one is already provided you will decide
i can't i'm sorry i looked over at the discord what the fuck is that what is that decision
you'll earn some bonus points let's begin all right what okay if this is pick the door
write an option that you think only some people would choose okay let me think about this for a
second okay this one's like i don't know that's tough that's kind of tough that's a tough one
oh i guess it's time for it to lose the image rights in the sub discord again
silence silence at the discord shut up dad all right we're almost done here
are we ready there these are these are cat memes you're right it's running out this is a real cat
meme you got it here it is the week on a specialized party cruise but you screwed up the dates as you
walk the dock the only two gangways available are for senior singles or this which seems to be your
singles um that sounds kind of interesting uh i don't understand i mean it this is just like
seniors you could probably get some interesting stories here i'm gonna take this every time
this is this is not bad this is interesting you know how many stories you're gonna hear here okay
yeah oh that's tough though that makes it even harder these are both very interesting
seniors or amateur jugglers yeah you might get hurt there though
uh which themed um well like like like like macaulay kulkin kind of like child star
i don't get it moving on you accept a highly lucrative job as a stripper her company rules
your emergency contact must either be your grandma or this person who do or grandma or who
your grandma or the kitchen chef i mean one of those is embarrassing and the other one like well
let me in defense is your grandma cool with this might be one of those grandmas are just like
whatever do it makes you happy okay i don't know no bonus points for you who do you pick as your
emergency contact rent your grandmother or your ex hmm i wonder oh i thought that was gonna be
much harder wow i'm surprised i really thought that you guys would rather call gra get grandma
called your grandma or your priest i'll just never go to church again
hey call the priest that's all right i'll just like i'll just change churches
okay now for something different you've died and become a ghost you can either
haunt the new work airport or this spot which location do you haunt you need to haunt the
airport or boring
there's so much more to like see and listen to people like traveling and seeing going places
apple pieces just people eating fucking riblets they're like shitty sandwiches like turkey blt you
know what i mean like that's not interesting the oh i don't know like that no nothing interesting
happens at the elbertson house don't worry oh that was a pretty good meme answer though good meme
answer why would you do that to me why would you do that to me why would you go the airport is so
much more interesting day jokes on you my router already is haunted you're gonna have to fight
another fucking ghost to get in there and it's a strong spirit too good luck comes down to this
no it's okay the winner mostly lost congratulations thank you mostly lost playing congrats
nice work congratulations uh well that's where he was cool very cool all right uh here's what
we're gonna do so i'm gonna go back we're going to do we're gonna do the wrap one again and then
we're going to do a couple from jack box four because uh some of those were really fun from
the last one so let me just go grab another drink i'll be right back and we'll continue
i also have to like download the fourth one because i don't have it installed but it won't
take very long be right back okay let's go back so for this one um adversity uh again i think i'm
going to bring some mods in here if they'd like to play see any mods want to play i will put it in
there open it let me get it in there looks like loop wants to play the precious this is all ready
to go it is the big old robot all right okay let me get in first i am in i mean the mods
that would like to play it's in there and we're gonna get it into the sub discord here in just a
second can't see well you're not supposed to see not yet at least not until the people have joined
oh this is gonna be loud i'm sorry all right we got we got holy mack and lucretius very good
now in sub discord who would like to join and point there it is whoa all right welcome your
new contestants and welcome to the game fully back i'm gonna suck so bad no you're not it's i
mean it's it's tough it is hard but it's fun good luck everybody let's go typing that code
on jackbox.tv and you can participate in the audience check it out mcs but y'all gotta back
up i'm not about to be a statistic down here okay it's your turn rach i gotta figure out what's
going on with all these okay is that the guy that makes germa videos that is holy mack second germa
will ask you for a word or we'll use it to complete line one of your rap you then write a line that
wrong we do that about ends and you have we hear him back and we vote on that vote for mack
hey shadows back sure sure let them stay i was kind of hoping to be stepped on today
saw that in my future well we're gonna get we're gonna we're gonna get a holy mack versus germa
scenario it's possible i'm gonna get them lyrics down i need you to write a word or a phrase then
an entire line that rhymes with the one that we give back to you you need help just use the
suggestion button on your device all right you get three minutes let's see what we can get
oh my opponent is holy mack it's here it comes all right it's gonna be good it happened it's
happening it's happening okay oh okay damn it i might get locked up here i think i might get
locked up on this one shit shit no i got it just give me just give me time give me some time here
okay oh this does not work with what i just wrote oh it's just too it's it's so it's so
nerve-racking oh hold on oh i might be i've got it i think oh here we go
who's facing off against who yo we got never versus mack battle rappers ready to go so let's
go on and get it in remember hit those voting buttons during the rhyme we gotta know if it's
dope or dog food let's see it my words are magical call me gandalf the gray one ring to rule the
speed why you running away i won a nobel prize for washing mount doom calling you it's your
final resting washing it spreads good i deliver it hot as spaghetti you won't fight me you're
gonna regret it my words are presence i deliver like harry potter you can't step to the max you're
a fish out of water well we don't have references we've all been pretty good references let's keep
it moving now it's time to use your devices to vote on who brought it strong
they were both fucking unbelievable time to vote harry potter or lord of the rings it's pretty
much what what your favorite series is what we're gonna find out right now is harry potter or lord
of the rings more popular that's it what where my two mcs at let's go what that dad i got my raps
are so furious they caused the rain i'm sorry i didn't mean to join again i'm a new voice like
a modern neighbor hand lincoln hold on wait wait i deserve an ass kicking hold on were you here
before hold on you were here before you were here oh shit he was in the first game
my games turned out charged faster than a motorcycle going faster than the balloon
with odd michael i destroy city blocks like a gigantic rat then i smack your seagulls with
a baseball bat that was just a full full of references okay y'all each line one by one
each one of those lines you gotta get them votes in vote for honesty bambi oh i can't
wear the middle of the game well he was honest the next two battlers are up and they ready to roll
all right mint ramney versus mr dunwich kenya and drank they call me for raid so i dress up as a
maid i can do it all like germa vote for me to win a free ipad go pass on that because this is your
first time doing this but don't ever come back with that wackiness yo where the next body get
your gears in gear i don't even know my futures as bright as a burning medium thin crust with my
opponent's face telling me they're food my lines are so sweet they're covered in galaxies
milky way bitch your verses are all fallacies
you put too many syllables too many words in the first line
oh that was pretty good that was pretty good poetic structure
he just said if i win i'm gonna feel bad why ipad contains of viruses
all right where my next two mcs at here we go we got lucratius versus uh fang kora
they call me steven hawking touch me and you will be the one not walking oh boy
my arms are fresh like right near the deal oh boy that's uh
the game crashed the game crashed get disconnected i didn't do it oh the game
it's fucking crashed oh dear what was your line what was your rap luke
why is jack box crashing what is here to crash well um luke is the new green screen
too many graphics well i think we're gonna do i think that that was any time as any
to open up uh party pack four do i have party pack four it crashed for me as well that's annoying
do i not have this how did i play this before no i i i already own this was it on ps4 i might
have i might have owned it on ps4 yeah i think it's on ps4 oh maybe not hold on maybe i might
be on the wrong thing here no yeah you your account already owns this game so how why can
i not install it it's weird no it was telling me oh you can purchase it but it's weird all right
let's just get party pack four go on here that's so annoying that one's definitely the best one i
think maybe we need some other people in like a voice to do the other games so i'm just gonna
put this up temporarily while i get this going give me one second here's jack box i yeah i have
all of them the only i don't have is two i don't have two so for some reason i have every single
one but two the other one is you give presentations so it's way better when people are talking yeah
that's that's true is it the same site jack box four it is the same site for all of them so you
are good to go i'm opening it i'm going to mute the audio here because it's probably gonna be
very loud so opening party pack four probably should change the title to party pack four
it is very loud so all right oh yeah we got fibbage three save the internet full screen mode
is on i need to just change this to make sure it's getting the right screen of course and here we
go party pack four we're sorry we can't seem to go there we go it was weird so we can survive
the internet monster seeking monster survive the internet fibbage three well let's do monster
monster seeking monster is uh i remember this being a lot of fun this one was a ton of fun
let's turn the audio back on okay audience extended timers yes require twitch room code hiding
uh all right here we go please make sure it's hidden all right uh same deal i'm gonna put it
i'm gonna i'm gonna put it into the uh let's try to get the the if luke if uh you and mac want to
play again because you did get kind of cut off there you did get cut off if any of the mods would
like to play this one i'm gonna put it into the sub discord all right luke is in and if mac wants
to play as well if you don't anybody anybody anybody anybody anybody just luke i think it's
just luke all right it looks like it's just luke for this one so here we go sub discord please only
join if you have not played before oh i have to join too that's very important come on in uh
hey hold on a second here we've got somebody here that's not supposed to be in here uh scooch
is it scooch sorry scooch we need to help open up that spot you gotta open up that spot
uh how do i i can i like just luke is oh luke's vip is there a way luke that you can uh open up
that spot i'm not sure we can even do it you should be able to can you you can't
oh you know he says he left uh uh we'll try we'll all right hold on we'll try it again
that was so loud for some reason all right we're going for it again here you go luke i think it
messed up when he uh left the game all right here we go no i know you can't see you're not supposed
to see all right i'm joining myself all right we got moo this time moo means moo and lucretius
and now let's try it again hey there we go look at that bingo
come on in luke and moo sorry everybody that uh joined it's tough it's tough to to moderate it
and v9 the rim codes are too complicated y c w q all right everybody in so this is when we
have to date each other yep you gotta you text to each other you try to go on a date
you can add more player slots i thought it was eight is that isn't eight the max on every one
of these games oh uh right luke has to press it oh because i forgot i'm not vip all right luke
flash everybody's in audiences player eight oh yeah more slots would be
that'd be impossible to do i think so long i'll be hosting six nights of ghoulish get-togethers
six nights convince other players to go out with you by sending them secret messages each night
you'll chat with other players before locking in the one person you want to date that night if that
person takes you back you go on a date and both earn a heart at the end of the game the monster
with the most hearts wins more or less did i mention you're all secrets check your devices
now to see your secret powers and how you can earn bonus hearts if you put them to good use
oh and you can dig the audience which is collectively controlling this player by voting
on everything they do oh i wish i could play join the audience if you want to play contestants in
the past date me all right night number one let's start by chatting with other players and trying
to set up dates you can only send four messages each night so use them you're only allowed to do
four texts all right so who do i want to chat with audiences first message is automatically sent to
everyone each night and it shows up here on the screen too isn't that fun this is where you
secretly have to type we should have mentioned that some of your conversations will appear on
screen during the date oh well i'm sure it won't be incriminating 20 seconds left to send your
messages don't dilly-dally now on your device pick the one person you hope you're going on
a date with tonight keeping my mandibles crossed for everyone to do well all right let's see it
okay here we go and if you don't get a date don't worry this is just the first night
night queen asked out the audience hey chat how's it going i'm not sure if i like moo means moo
german venus if you see this don't trust moo means moo have fun you lovelies have for a fun
night all you need is murder rejected don't go yet there's more oh luke asked out chat i know
we've had our ups and downs but i you know i love you even if i took away your images
don't trust boobies boo agreed it really smells like swamps around here you've rejected him
boomy's boom wants to date oh anything nah well why did you say yes why did you say yes
someone else wanted in on that action and failed oh no the spiff asked out card hey babes you
you you oh oh give me a break looks like someone was hoping this date wouldn't work out
wow what an exciting first night let's do that awkward thing where we all take a hard look at
just delete the game so you are doing the best and you're doing less so a quick word of warning
whoever is in the top spot at the end of the second night of dates will have their monster
they will have their monster powers shown to everybody same for the highest ranking unrevealed
monster all right night number two the secret word is movie in case that affects your monster power
what does that mean secret word all right i'm gonna let's make it happen let's just
jump into sending out those messages all right all right all right all right here we go
hey if you need to block another player when you hit the info button on their chat screen
there's a block button in there and then you won't see their messages come on
oh chatting in secret is so much fun blocked nothing relaxes me like taxes how is that
something you could even pick how is that even possible okay time's up all right it's time to
pick dates again so did we learn any useful life lessons the first night we'll find out
all right let's see it's date time it's time for dates spartan cat is interested in spiff
the face again the face again no it didn't work this time with more than just one message
even she said it it might help to use oh i asked me out you know i'm the best mod so i'm the best
date hmm i accept this proposal i also want to raise that's where you get rejected you add me into
come on there's more only if you ban the dab emo get out of here take a shower thinking about
dressing as trash oh what oh i hate this moot asked out lucretius uh-oh brahr nuzzles how are you
oh hides under the eight and by anything lately oh my fucking god i can't believe i was rejected
let's see what's what now i was gonna give you a chance oh fun things are happening don't forget
at the end of each night from now on the highest ranking secret monster will have their identity
revealed you're currently at the top let's see you may not trust you you lost your chance
serial killer the serial killer steals two hearts from a player the second time they date each
other okay so you don't want to date the serial killer twice you want on your device by hitting
the info button on their chat screen the same goes for any monster after they're revealed
hmm night number three almost at the halfway point full moon tonight okay message time message
time if you want to get some hands on some fingers they send their messages to me and i show them to
you hey what are you about me 20 seconds and counting
oh sorry time's up i don't have any messages it's times like these i love being a matchmaking
monster hey i know it's hard to choose but if okay let's see i'm just like laughing over here
i'm not even saying anything but grace he wants to date card that's crazy what do you do though
you know banning people that's crazy by the way what's your discord i thought he said
bang and if you stack two lasagnas on top how many lasagnas is it i don't what stick around
there's another one for you another one it's chat i need to get my hands on some fingers i got two
hands full of those i think you can use more germa that's me so i mean maybe what are your
thoughts on uh you're my favorite one kisses blush uh oh and this means rejection for our
extra lonely heart over there we know how this is gonna end oh rejection spiff wants to date
moo we already know how this will already dating we chose wrong let's see come on you guys
standings i picked you guys the first night and then you rejected me so i'm getting my rejection
revenge on a full moon werewolves get a bonus heart for dating and then turn their dates into
a werewolf but if a were you rejected us first you rejected me and then i rejected you i rejected
you first and then you rejected me and then i rejected you back get to messaging
hmm 20 second warning
i got confused about what i just said i just got really confused by my own words okay
time's up all right it's time to pick dates again this part always makes me giggle don't even
fucking know what i'm saying hey i know it's hard to choose but if you don't pick anyone you'll
time to see the date here we go spiff wants to date spartan cat who rejected who there i don't
understand no moo means moo wants to date the audience you had me at apathy i don't care if
bad jokes is wrong i don't want to be right then germa is the wrongest man i know rejected stay
right there there's more hey guys i know i've been cruel but this time i think it's for real
you had me at apathy see looks like someone was hoping this date wouldn't work out
it worked out must date me we know this ends already dating sorry sorry card i'd love to get
banned for my second favorite mod thanks we'll visit you later wait why can't i type in chat
anymore
what is chat chat is uh the ghost the vengeful ghost starts the game with a bonus heart
when the vengeful ghost asks someone on a date and gets rejected that person loses a heart be
careful well that's not good ghost what what the fuck so that's what's been happening this whole
time fever that's why i'm in last place message time you kidding me we're down to 20 seconds
oh sorry time's up fuck i read it at time time to pick your date the suspense is killing me
not literally i'm immortal jokes on you they never answer you don't pick anyone you'll be
severely penalized let's see those dates i'm asking out the audience wait looks like someone
had the same idea let's see same idea fucking assholes why why are you doing that well who do
who the fuck is it then you asked out mu okay yeah you guys got rejected get rejected losing
a heart oh but mu means mu asked out lucretius oh okay this is gonna end that's not good oh are
they gonna do like the fucking face again do you hate sand it's very rough it does get everywhere
it gets everywhere yeah the werewolf dated on a full moon the werewolf turned you into a werewolf
oh i got two werewolves now let's see what's what now well well well stuff definitely happened
there hey not in the last place time for another reveal you are a leprechaun everyone who dates an
unrevealed leprechaun gets two it's two fake hearts leprechaun is revealed that's not good
all fake hearts disappear at this moment leprechauns get one bonus heart for every
player that drops in the rankings so sorry guys one player dropped you kind of just got screwed
i'm looking out it's our last night the blood harvest festival you get two hearts for dating
now because it's such a special night get to messaging okay here we go just 20 more seconds
okay time's up all right it's time to pick dates again oh love so much potential for disaster and
a heartbreak here we go final night he lost a heart no it's hard to choose but if you don't
let's see the dates audience asked out mu means mu oh silence when i close my eyes i see youth
culture rejecting rejected every time losing a heart you guys get rejected every time
who asked out lecraeus you know what fuck chat i just remember to wear protection
hey she is who wants to date spartan cat i know it's a full moon tonight but you're the only moon
i would like to howl at chat is better by not having what someone's lining up hoping to be next
let's see what happens no i'm a godot i'm able willing to forgive let's put us at our past what
did you say really one last owo for the road oh no that's not good
looks like someone else wanted in on that action and failed scammer
one last thing it's time for the after party time to reveal any remaining hidden monster powers
okay let's see your secrets monster hunter i'm a monster hunter at the end of the game the
monster hunter gets a bonus heart for every time they date the monster type they've secretly been
told to hunt and i'm a card everyone the vampire dates becomes a vampire and then so do the people
they date at the end this vampire receives half a bonus heart for every vampire in the game
every time the globe successfully dates three new players its heart tally doubles
it's a lot to a lot to remember invisible person the invisible person started the game with two
bonus hearts the invisible person's score is invisible so they appear to be in last place
until the end of the game not fair time to tally up any after party bonus hearts let's see not
fair became a werewolf two werewolves were created the score i just keep my eye on werewolves
who was the monster hunter hunting this whole time the vampire who they never did successfully
let's see how many of you were turned into vampires
four vampires
dated that guy spartan cat congratulations you won five and a half hearts created two werewolves
and you dated dated couldn't get anyone to date a second time unfortunately or uh trick two
players with a total of four fake hearts spiff let's work nice work uh directly made one vampire
and they made three more vampires uh real rank each night second second second second third fifth
my god tracked vampire all game never did manage to date them couldn't do it inflicted five lost
hearts of damage on players who scorned them yes you did minus 1.5 dated two players never quite
doubled all right cool uh let's go back to the other one so we got uh we got civic doodle
racketeering survive the internet it is very low civic doodle you've been hired to create murals
all over doodle valley compete to see if you can make the best additions in your attempt to beautify
the city let's do this i don't think we even did this one last time i'm not sure we even
did this one last time we played it uh we're gonna i don't think the extended timer should be on for
this one because it'll it's already a long time to draw we did do a bunch of time yeah fireman
was the shirt game yeah fireman was tko that is true all right let's try this one once and then
we'll do fibbage and then we'll see where we're at okay play game so uh let's get let's do mods
again i feel like the mods have been adding some fun to this if anybody wants to do it
let me go like this anybody else that hasn't played on the mod team that would like to play
if not then i'm pretty sure yeah i think all the mods have played yeah let's just go like this
let me get in myself before i put that in the chat that would be a plus for sure uh why is
that not working come on now come on now come on now there we go all right civic doodle
i am in uh grump do you want to play oh why not why not if you want to play it's there
and in 10 seconds i'm gonna put it into the sub discord here it comes in three
two one go okay i think we've got i think we've got i think that no one's been here before
okay there you go i don't think anyone was here before that i can remember all right i gotta draw
myself um okay let's get some hair hey look it's me i'm the audience you guys don't get to draw
all right let's go one civic doodle hey guys hey guys valley i'm authorized to give you one
hug each any takers no all right thank you all for volunteering or being court ordered to
participate in our town beautification initiative remember there's still time to join the audience
and help so you have to add to this you have to keep attitude right wants to turn all the drab
white walls in the town into colorful community art projects isn't that right mr mayor that's
right that's not my name oh it's this guy i remember oh it's a guy that is german during the
void man i remember is doing he's doing the voice as you can see this masterpiece is already started
we invited that famous painting monkey to draw something here but just between you and me i
think you really phoned it in didn't finish the drug where's your follow-through pal we believe in
a little thing called democracy around here so i'll let two of you make additions to the drawing
and your fellow volunteers will vote on who which one's better right oh and i'm keeping you on a
short timer to make sure you don't overthink short timer
all right good luck while these two are drawing the rest of you can express your feelings about
their work with the buttons on your device this is very short what what is going on
so
you took up the whole space
this balloon head this person's a balloon i don't know it's tough oh shit somebody's
getting 50 bucks carlos the clam thanks for the 50 dollars and of course the
50 bucks from carlos the clamp turn the volume down that's right i forgot it was loud right
not so fast this is the loud one uh here's fifty dollar bribe to let me in the next game
no bribes don't no bribes work but thank you so much for fifty dollars dude that that sounds like
that sounds like somebody's desperately trying to do meatwad and donald duck at the same time all
right so let's see what are you gonna add to it what's going on what are you adding what can you
even add to this horns and hair just i don't know horns and crying or bart simpson
where'd you go wow that was ah that's gonna keep happening the most confusing drawing oh wow
all right what are you gonna add you got horns and crying
why is this an eggplant holy shit but they want the mouth papyrus are satan let's count those votes
and the audience ah why do you have to do that to us every time that's why i have to turn it down
next on deck okay next up he's catching a snowflake on his tongue he's crying into his own mouth
never mind i got it wrong
the y makes perfect sense there too
hey disney live back so germa why as far as i'm sure the sour blueberry by the germa stream
experience i i
well this is the germa stream experience you cry into your own mouth
well there we go nice job cookie
let's go i think we're really gonna change some lives with this one
that's the cow he can't hear anything all right it looks like you can you there's a couple ways you
can take this making a second ear on the left playing hangman on the right so we've got bunny
and hangman what's the hangman game though i mean they're both pretty that could be let's see one
two three four five stream let me take care of this all right i got it it looks like we could
play hangman drink next up uh let's see uh let's okay okay i'll get up get some get rid of some
letters here no no you i'm gonna get this right see there we go so cool yeah i'm playing i'm
i'm doing the actual thing you just how are you gonna change this yeah what are you gonna do with
this your sans undertale with the eye okay great i'm this is we're playing hangman over here
don't even tell me sans undertale yeah let's play hangman not like
all right good luck so there's no a's good luck sans and not sans undertale again no what the
fuck no no why no
they're both ruined completely they're both completely fucking ruined i don't know which
one is worse i don't i can't tell you which one is a worse option suzy the left just always seems
to have undertale we can still play hangman look somebody got there's no s there's no s see they
just wrote it twice there's no a and there's no s and that's just what he drew this that's what he
drew the first part no a and no s go for it oh my god ass why eat ass yeah and then like a sand
yeah you could almost okay looks like we got it hangman bingo this one's already completed but
this one's no i i mean that's a pretty good quick drawing but this one's still possible but s and a
are both already gone the up top mean it's supposed to be a and s have already been that they caused
the hangman to go down now they're up there the only two letters that were supposed to be
disqualified are on here what have you done what have you done oh that's it all right i'm going
to solve it i'm going to try to solve it uh that's too many letters is that too bad oh
fucking whatever okay vote for your favorite what was that laugh
that's the audience why am i so invested in the hangman thing because that was interesting that
was an interesting thing okay time to take it sans ass 18 plus somebody's vandalized a church
we just have to know it okay that was oh i got a special treat for our buddy artist
what is it you're all so church of sands you to do a portrait to hang right in town hall
somebody was trying to play hangman and then someone ruined it i was drawing at the same time
of our fine citizens if somebody okay don't even don't do it no everyone's gonna do it
don't do it i know you're going to we need to know i know everyone's going to and now
now we have to all do it
oh my god totally sure what he's getting at but let's just start by drawing some eyes any eyes
you want options here nobody did it i'm the only one only two of us did it i was trying to stop it
i thought everybody was going to do it so i was just i was like if you can't beat him join
him and it ended up being two people did it and now and now good thank god fuck i'm done whatever
fuck it fuck this what the hell are these audience the way what
how are we supposed to add to this i'm gonna start off
you don't think that's funny
i got one i got an idea how about this idea
uh these are all so bad what do the audience think what is this why does it get 60 70 oh it's
the green screen oh i get it i get it i get it makes sense you all did our town proud but let's
see who did it the proudest saved nice job nice job soup
wait do you get to draw what do you what do you get to draw at the end
who's drawing who's drawing right now free ipad i can't why can i not draw i can't draw oh my god
this really is perfect music for the end here unplug it come on what can you get we get three
seconds one two three one two three one two three actually pretty quick all right let's get new
players youtube annotation spam yeah that's really you're right uh that one was fun i want to do it
again uh any of the mods want to join in civic doodle let's do this one one more time and then
we'll go play uh probably i don't know one or two more let's play this one's fun don't unhide that
all right i'm gonna put it into the i'm gonna see if any of the mods want to play this time
let's see if they'd like to join you got about five to ten seconds before that goes into subs
and hold on almost i am in all right here we go three two one go for it all right let's see
uh i see uh i'm sorry everybody i see people that were here before let's do it again i think
there were at least one or two people there there before here we go let's do it again let's do it
again quickly now with the swiftness let's go let's try it again and i'm not going to give you any
time not going to give you any time go i think i think we're good i think we have nobody here
before uh i actually didn't get the i didn't get a chance to see because everyone started drawing
so now i don't know who's in here but okay i think we're good so i i saw like these two i
was like oh no but and everyone started drawing yeah i'm putting it in the discord
in the sub discord all right now let me put uh let's see let's see let's see
oh the audience is in again there that's just my name all right let's go
voting times are too short oh we'll get him all right the traps have been sent where should we
spread artistic joy today mr mayor how do we say i can't skip skip is there a no skip i don't think
there is all right here we go keep in mind i'm putting you on a short timer so you don't
get lost in artistic thought okay everybody ready set good luck to you oh go two very strong
candidates it's up to the voters to pick a winner come on vote why don't you
i want to play oh that's tetris that's that's pretty good that's pretty that's pretty good
moment of truth and we've got some mail in ballots from the audience whatever i want to play hangman
and nobody must play hangman with me nobody wants to play they want to play tetris instead of hangman
the people have spoken okay let's see what you two can do go oh what are you gonna do with tetris
i'm curious to see how this is somebody's just gonna do tetris just continuously do it no
apparently not that was under the assumption we were gonna get an actual game of tetris
is this what is going on is that supposed to be legs well it's either legs or i don't know
what this is and then is that supposed to be like rick that's rick from rick and morty he was gonna
write this is rick all right so we got a guy with this guy with legs congratulations good luck now
let's see what you two can add how is that rick i don't know it just is all right good luck
what are you gonna do with the adding hair
or an antenna i think it is an antenna turning this into a television maybe tv um i don't know
okay the arms sans eye i mean i can't what are those arms those are the biggest most buff fluffy
arms what started this tetris turned into this up next all right go good luck really focusing on
the face on this one i'm not necessarily the rest of the body uh i don't what's what's this
is somebody is it a person person is climbing on top tv sans it's voting time i know i i didn't i
cut i was too i was too much in shock what was what were you even drawing here that's supposed to be
an arm i think our painting is complete but it's still where's it going use your device to suggest
one all right um there you go i guess now vote for your favorite i don't know i don't know i
can't even man focus framework crushed by 300 pound tv time for the big reveal and the paint's
that's on an ice cream shop
just love a god all right moving on
round two and it was 400 pounds that's right there's a 450 pound television the start of some kind
of circle or maybe a um an ear that was quick uh see see see you or a face that was really quick
and it's it's the baseline here where you going with it get jexed so i need to add to this
good luck to you too make it happen uh chat chat rules and then a sans eye sans eye on the right
and then chat rules on the left and a tooth i think i think a sans eye at this point is
an automatic disqualification does that make any sense i think that breaks the rules at this point
all right so chat rules which appears chat rules all right how can i add to this let me think
it's a puppet it's a puppet or a screaming powerful spell moment of truth plus the audience
let's see pretty even actually pretty even but and then 10 shits it looks like we're going
with a puppet up next chat rules now is that supposed to be somebody that's okay so here
this is what i'm assuming here chat drools well see that the you the chat you are the the person
there right and the puppet is your avatar on the internet and you're essentially talking through
that so this this is this could be made into a very very good piece actually uh chat drools with
not no memes no like random was that
ow i know that's just a thing that that's like asking come on got it take your favorite and vote
uh
and the audience oh yeah sure sure we made this a volunteer project instead of you know paying
anyone 23 is to do what now mr mayor i think it's time for final jeopardy final jeopardy
now i'm gonna try really really hard at this thing let's pick out another
i'm gonna give it my best and just flip through the old dual valley phone book
here we go that's who you're gonna draw again no clue who that is sir oh you remember they live
down by the gravy factory you know the river no sands or censored that's right if you put
down sands you're getting censored just to draw some eyes let's do that now
smoother gravy and then that would go on the tracks down to the the plant where they boxed
the gravy up so it's can i be honest i love them okay no sands good anyway sounds like upside down
that one's is that an upside down image audience all right looks like we're going
nobody wanted mine looks like we're going with this one next let's all do the nose
okay wait why is mine not colored in i colored it in there we go everyone adds boogers everybody
everyone adds boogers it's the easiest thing to do it really is out of mouth no
sticking his finger in the nose nobody fucking voted for me mine was so bad finally this
actually is looking pretty good i tried i'm trying to get like a whatever i was trying to
add legs it is too fast don't fuck with that one jesus no uh let's take a look brush your teeth
if you don't want to go to fucking jail beautiful artistic experience like that doesn't even really
the winner was that actually looks pretty good oh it does okay then good job jex you did it
hey look we can draw whatever we want draw sands and you get perma band all right let me uh let's
do one more thing that was drawing like a penis right i'm getting out of here congratulations
thanks for playing that one's fun so let's do can we do fibbage fibbage is fun how about this we'll
do fibbage and then we'll do monster seeking monster one more time let me make sure these
settings are correct full screen mode is on family friendly put the timers on for this one why not
i can censor bad things if they show up that's good uh okay play fit play fibbage enough about
you no let's just do the regular one okay so let me uh see if anyone wants to play let me get this
in there dude i've just seriously been just slamming cokes this whole time this is like i'm
gonna have to go on my set i'm going to my third coke uh why can i i'd like to unhide this please
there you go uh i'll put it in the mod chat just in case somebody in the mod team would like to
play okay but i've said i've had to piss every hour on the hour this will be piss number three
coming up how does the audience join uh you're gonna just go to jackbox.tv and type this code
that you see on the screen into the room code and you can participate if you want all right
it's going to the sub chat good luck all right we've got pretty much all new people i think
we do so now i'm going to go like this and piss and i will be right back just be
all right fibbage everybody's here except i'm falling off of my chair oh my lord what's wrong
with my chair what the fuck is going on here man i am the cookie and i only need to host
three thousand more games to break that which is curse attention oh no here's the code if you
want to join in oh and if anybody else wants to join they can get in the audience at any time
audience members get to guess the truth and pick decoy lies to fool the players okay here we go
that's what you get to do all right round one it's about lying 500 points for everyone you fool
i do this 85 percent of the time i ever talk truth i think i'm gonna be pretty good at this
choose a category this isn't the friends version first up i don't think so i think this is the
regular one weird injury boston red sox boston red sox player clarence levin cut his butt cheek
when he slid into second with blank in his pocket now use your device to enter a lie that might
interesting players into picking it if you're stumped you can hit the lie for me button but
he sliced open his butt cheek when he slid into second with this in his pocket oh enter your lies
lie for me googling i google i just typed him what are you talking about for the truth and tap it on
your device fake teeth in 1923 boston red sox player clarence levin cut his butt cheek open
when he slid into second base with fake teeth in his pocket pencil his locker key a quarter a knife
an action figure of himself tuna can lid i mean his false teeth fake teeth uh
his magnum dong well uh that's definitely not the answer considering he's not frank reynolds
okay what did everyone pick that was mine yeah come on that's you know sometimes you get the
the hunger bites here you know what i mean tuna can lid is sharp as fuck by the way be careful
with those if that was true i would say there's no way in hell that's it right that would make
some sense so what was it fake teeth what is two people google it is that what happened
that's the audience's lie okay so fine so we got a couple of googlers
say it really bit him in the ass but well too late fake teeth false teeth and he slid into second
base with and fake teeth time to look at this japanese figurine depicts two monkeys as they
as they uh i don't know yeah you guys get to pick one in the audience you get to put your own
lie up as long as you all can come to a consensus that is hurry use the lie for me button if you're
stuck all right depicting okay take a look and find the truth are you talking to me
if i um i don't know expand their brains meditate let me ride a frog expand all right
who picked what the odds the audience is that's what you guys picked what the fuck
what
wow meditate so what is it then riding a frog eating a frog it's not expanding their brains
it's it's probably ride a catfish or does it ride a frog or ride a catfish no it's an eating a frog
i mean okay well that's it isn't riding on a catfish it has whiskers oh we got we got a
googler in here among us choose a category uh new category motley crew okay here's your question
in 2016 motley crew gave their friends what they've always wanted and released their own line of
blank he's their own line motley crew gave the fans what they wanted they released their own line
of
mine's the worst i hope nobody votes for mine because it really is the worst one here
all right where's the truth it's probably it's probably honest to god i mean like
it's has to be one of these fucked up answers hold on is it it might be motley crew is a rock
band from the 80s yeah motley brand applesauce let's see what everybody selected wait nobody
know how is it applesauce nobody could type that in nobody has a keyboard that's capable nobody
knows what it's like alt one four two or something right one four one to do that nobody knows that
jinx i told you mine was the worst one i fucking panicked you motherfuckers that
truck nuts i figured maybe it's definitely gonna be
vibrators no way are you serious oh it's the truth please consult doctor feel good
time to buy one get ready round two where all the points are doubled choose a category
karate what do you got the means there is an algebraic theorem that when applied to
meteorology suggests that there must be a spot on earth with no wind no name of this idea
is the blank theorem right your lives now there's a spot on earth that has absolutely no wind
the odd name of the idea that there's no wind here is this kind of is this theorem there is
no it's not
it's not quick we got half the people here have no idea what to write okay find the truth all right
i got the name of this the odd name of this is the area above germa because he's so short
absolutely that's what it is that's definitely what this one is that's pretty good one no
windiness effect thingy oh nino panel no windier gustless cure hairy ball
um did i just actually no it can't be right it's okay to be no windier oh that's too bad
what is that the blank theorem
uh the censored theorem hmm no windiness effect thingy the gustless theorem 16 percent of you guys
the hairy ball theorem got a bunch of googlers in here it comes from the hairy ball the hair on a
ball flat without a cowlick leave me i've tried googling well the whole point is you're supposed
to make it up select a category you're supposed to lie you're not supposed to put the truth up
there no please allow me scented bottoms all right here it is missouri candle maker five
bean company sells a scented soy candle with the name the bottom of blank
sells a scented scented soy candle with the name the bottom of okay i just got here and i thought
i was watching an ad hurry up use a suggestion if you can't think of anything
hold on is does somebody hear afk did somebody leave okay look for the truth and pick it
oh the scented candle that came out with the bottom of west virginia satan shoe the soy
for satan shoe oh i wonder which one of these a bag of chips the barrel mom's purse the week old
hmm now somebody's somebody's on their blue switch keyboard going let's see what you guys
picked bottom of the barrel bottom of the week old trash that was mine thank you for the points
the bottom of saint louis the bottom of satan's shoe what i don't get it that had happened
hold on you both why did you how did you both do that how did you both do that you can't be in
the bottom of mom's purse i take it shavings hey what's the question oh what is that it's candle
give me a category it's a cockroach in here try this one while renovating his home in 1963
a turkish man in the capodosia region was surprised to find a surprise find okay enter your
life renovating his home this man was surprised to find i i wonder i yeah i already know i already
know i already know what's gonna happen and i'm gonna censor all of them they're all getting
censored all right find the truth well renovating his home the turkish man found he was very
surprised to find a tunnel a stash of rare comic books a skeleton that his home had already been
renovated corpse of a dwarf of rat cave a wall dad a lost city or a grenade
censor it all and what did people pick a skeleton if this was the audience i'm gonna be mad thank
god a wall dad no no wall dad in there a tunnel that's it that was a good one nobody nobody voted
for it that his home had already been renovated what do you knock down the wall and there's like
a pristine wall behind it and you all just got fucking destroyed i mean we're talking like
absolutely destroyed oh and you guys got destroyed by uh graveyard a lost city i don't understand
you found a city in your house is this fraggled rock how big is the city this is the final
final finish coming up triple the points good luck in a post-game interview ghanian football star
mohammed anas turned some heads by thanking both blank and blank all right by thanking both
uh let's see uh it's probably it's probably that's not a lie though you know it could be
i don't know i think this is the first vivid question that i actually don't
turn some heads by thanking these two things okay seek the truth okay uh his wife and his
girlfriend his trainer and his wife's killer what the fuck satan and god himself and himself
spiderman venom priest and rabbi of foot and ball what the fuck are these
it might be this it actually might be this they're like it really could be that
all right let's see it i think i got it right i love this part
foot and ball his mercy incorrect uh a priest and a rabbi no uh i it's definitely not this one
spider man and venom whatever his trainer and his wife's killer where did you guys come up with
that himself and himself right oh come on satan and god this could be the other one no no so wait
hold on it's his wife and his girlfriend hope you remember to thank his divorce lawyer oh right
hey thank you for playing congratulations i like how the leaves we actually write them no i know
you know i know you don't write them how would you be able to do it thanks playing guys all right
let's close this out here by doing one more of the uh monster seeking monster monster seeking
monster and then we are going to close it for the night and you'll see me tomorrow tomorrow
is red dead redemption 2 online and i think uh i'm gonna try to get a couple people involved
uh i know i've already i've already spoken to vinnie and i try me and vinnie at least
i'm gonna try to get in and play and then sunday the day after that is uh movie night green screen
movie night so we go we got a one two three friday saturday sunday here when am i gonna start
streaming i for tomorrow i really don't know because i kind of have to see what vinnie's
schedule is what his plan is and if he's gonna be around so we will i he usually starts a little
later so i might not start till a little bit later tomorrow night but then sunday sunday will be
starting at around 4 p.m pacific it's probably the best time to start that around seven eastern
so uh we'll see let's play monster seeking monster oh there any let's see let's see let's
see let's see let's see monster seeking monster i need to i almost did it okay anybody in the
mod chat want to play monster seeking monster there is the code come on in this is the last
one of the night see you tomorrow if you're taking off red dead redemption 2 multiplayer
make sure i get into this as well all right move is going to join us
and good luck to you guys uh do we have anybody that's already been in we do we do unfortunately
we have to do it again we do there are at least one or two i'm gonna go for it again uh move
i'll give you to it again here we go moo and here you go subs yeah give it a go one two three
i think i think we got oh let's see pretty sure nobody has played yet from here i don't think so
not that i can remember you can kick them uh you cannot kick unfortunately there there is no kicking
at least from what i can see all right so here we go monster seeking monster that's the room
code everybody's in everybody's ready i think you have to press start because uh you came in
first and i didn't i came in after jerva is it should be out of here he's been in every game
yeah i know it's that guy's problem anyways and by the way the audience gets to very much
participate in this game so this is probably the most audience uh engagement out of probably all
the games so far so if you'd like to play join it let's do it hello there and welcome to monster
seeking monster i'm your host felicia the teeth nasher which is why i have this he's a game hog
i'll be hosting six nights of putrid pairings well that is true i didn't uh i skip it by sending
them secret messages each night you'll chat with i actually didn't play in the first game you're
you want to date that night if that person picks you back you go on a date and both earn a heart
at the end of the game we have some eager little monsters okay then oh there you go moo there you
go all right this time i plan on dating so many people you don't have any idea let's start by
chatting with other players and trying to set up dates let's start the chat you can only send
four messages each night so use them wisely stream delay is real all right oh the audience's first
message is automatically sent to everyone each night and it shows up here on the screen too
isn't that fun okay did i mention that your secret conversations might be seen by everyone
during the dates my bad that's oh and i why am i so dumb i'm so stupid i actually you only get
four messages and i did three and i'm trying to respond to one other person but i fucked up the
spelling and i i corrected it just out of that's just what my brain does oh no sorry like with a
the asterisk for me change i fucked it up there goes all four the message sending timer is down
to 20 seconds 20 seconds shit on your device pick the one person you hope you're going on a
date with tonight oh this is so romantic sorry i'm a bit of a gooey goo choose who you're going to
date let's go see who picked who and who you know didn't and if you don't get a date don't worry
this is just the first night audience wants to date jerma i want to get back together when i
think of you i think about money i don't want you talking what's your first memory of germa 985
that's right you guys better think about my memory someone else wanted in on that action and failed
you guys you guys maybe bring up the first time i ever streamed oh wow what the fuck that's too
many some of you have to go actually everybody wanted to date chat oh my god i did not see that
wow wow what an exciting whoa let's maybe salt those wounds i feel very special
everyone just got destroyed it looks like you are currently doing the best
and you're not a quick word of warning whoever is in the top spot at the end of the chat will
have their monster power revealed i've never seen that before every night after that we'll do the
same for the highest ranking unrevealed monster you guys are in high demand i'm winning we all
know how this works by now message away okay hey if you need to block another player from
messaging you when you hit the info button on their chat screen you can also find the block
button so you won't see their messages just funny oh just having lots of love over here
time's up what's up with what so did we learn any useful life lessons i didn't even i'm not even
gonna give that a response zombie and i want to get back a chat with me i'm on the reef uh yeah
let's do this chat sucks it's on that was harsh that was cruel stick around there's another one
for you okay so embarrassed about getting rejected by chat yeah chat sucks want a date
let's do it forget about chat all they do is count there you go no one's gonna date you guys
anymore audience is interested in movies what's up with poo not much you for fun i know you need
a shame then i'm always having fun yeah rejected what's up with poo there's more catch any epic
victory royals no i'm on a default skin i got you bro let's squad catch it where we dropping
oh fucking god
asked out hey hey um what's up baby i was trying to think of someone to send my amazon wishlist to
i have no money oh wow really thanks yeah let's see if that changed any of the standings
well well well stuff definitely happened there don't forget at the end of each night from now
first place highest ranking the secret monster will have their identity revealed
you're in the top spot let's see what kind of monster you are oh guys
it's a bonus heart every time they date someone that was rejected
yeah everyone's gonna laugh on your device by hitting i can't wait for everybody to
laugh the same goes for any monster because she's red oh look at oh look at he's so little
he's so little there's a full moon out tonight in case that affects your monster power get to
messaging
what did i just do
like shit face a lot of messages from other players we're down to 20 seconds
okay time's up all right it's time to pick dates again i love just the silence rushing through my
vein who wants to date the number one spot that's the question let's see the dates
uh spaghetti wants to date zombie what's your favorite teletubby tinky-winky resonates with me
if you only get one message from someone they're probably not that into it
movies boom wants to date the audience i can't get butts out of my mind me either
don't talk to me before i've had my evil so you're looking for a bad boy i'm thinking
about dressing as a locust for halloween can't believe you just rejected them stay right there
there's more zombie i can't get butts out of my mind sorry i only do ear gold child in what
audience asked out you did i can't get butts out of my mind you know this is this isn't gonna work
no it's not gonna work guys stick around you knew i was gonna for you yeah i think we both agree
chat sucks want to date i didn't even respond to your text why would you date me i didn't i'm
the move out of one spot i was rejected last night you into that yeah but you don't let me
down okay let's go prime shirt subs merch giveaway money i don't think i'll ever be that popular my
entire life we already know how this will go rejected ban chat they let's see if any of that
changed the social pecking order oh fun things are happening all right everybody knows my
superpower those player so let's see let's see who are you oh i definitely don't want to be
dating you go starts the game with a bonus heart when the vengeful ghost asks someone on a date
and gets rejected that person loses a heart be careful around the vengeful ghost
oh can we stop thinking about germa for a second message time what's happening
what is going on can't meet me at the gorge what is that supposed to mean
oh bottom text time to pick your date i can't watch let's do it closing my 29 eyes the audience
is freaking out right now uh what what have you guys done date time was the zombie hey sorry
portraying you make update rejected yet there's more spuda please date me nobody loves me i'm
committed let me prove it x x x heart heart heart you guys playing connect four
well apparently there's no better show of faith than using all your messages
we know this ends bad oh that doesn't end well rejected automatically
who means mu asked out the audience can't stop thinking about germa i hear they make
pills for that i think you could use more cargo shorts now you're talking what are your thoughts
on betrayal god i'll tell you my social security number if you hit the date button hello please
pam me i put a gorilla in a fake real hey sorry p.m. and fake looking gorilla costume profit real
gorilla i can't fucking believe it worked do really hit it off your rejection i can't believe that
worked the puppets gained tonight that accident i think he accidentally clicked the date button
see what's what now oh things are moving okay let's see your secrets all right audience what
do you got your cookie mom the mother receives a bonus heart every night their child their child
does not get a date i still love you mom so who's the who's your child only two more i'm excited
about that full moon get to message all right only 20 seconds left i'm really into this whole
uh time's up all right it's time to pick dates again if i had real human emotions all right let's
see what happens right now hey i know it's hard to choose but if you don't pick anyone you'll be
time to see the dates audience is looking for spaghetti don't worry i've had plenty of butts
i too actually want to do it if dung is wrong i don't want to if dung is wrong okay here we go
what do you mean wait approaches let's see what happens yeah that's not good news for you sorry
your rejection last night is the puppets gained tonight thank you rejecting the vengeful ghost
means losing a heart oh that's not good we know how this is gonna end sorry boo i can't i'm already
taken giving me free points it's all free points if you earn them with your exceptional dating
skills there's another one for you let's see if we got here i think i could be the child please
let me out of here you don't want a mother she's mothering me rescue oh my god
what just happened there let's see if any of that changed last night pecking order
wow somebody cheated this cheating going on here time for another reveal what are you able
to face the creep the creep earns a bonus heart for every player they reject
but only on nights they successfully get a date it can be hard to trust a creep really is too bad
that you guys in chat weren't the creep because you would have had what five six extra hearts in
the first round together make it count you get two hearts for dating now because it's such a special
night and there's a full moon so fun here we go final night message time
okay
oh sorry time's up once again it's time to pick your date
i've got butterflies in my stomach literally i ate a lot of butterflies give me the victory
okay oh i accidentally voted for the chad boobies boo wants to date spoo top look up
hot singles in your local area click here fff singles.com oh it's just a spam you just
you just junk mail spoodle wants to date the audience what about whispers
chad walks over to you i'll whisper everything what do you not like about politics let's forget
about these politics what do you say looks like someone had the same idea let's see how this works
out oh man uh oh last chance chat i need a redemption arc what do you not like about politics
how political this streamer is knock knock who's there in the past oh you get double hearts too
isn't that cute you're mine mine you don't even know i always was what's that person's name in chat
i want them permanently banned from the channel give me your ghost power i'll pick you no matter
what i got you want some ectoplasm yeah slam through the wall someone's lining up hoping to
be next let's see what about me yeah yeah that's what you deserve that's what you deserve
you deserve that hey chad want to do it you bet i won't do what it wasn't even chad though it was
this weird guy let's see the almost final standings one last thing it's time for the after party time
to reveal did i get enough hearts i wonder time to see your mom's not gonna win right
what do you the body swapper swaps hearts with the person they successfully date oh shit i think
i dated them like twice everyone the zombie dates turns into a turns into a zombie and every new
zombies date also turn into a zombie at the end of the next night everyone has been infected it's
the end of the world the end of the world god here's the monster hunter at the end of the game the
monster hunter gets a bonus heart for every time they date the monster how could you betray me
oh every time the glob successfully dates three new players its heart tally doubles
did you get it any after party bonus hearts who is the monster hunter hunting this whole time
the body swapper who they dated the body swapper but that's not a monster is it no
oh it is that affect the final standing but wait no we still need to find out who got infected by
the zombie virus oh god could be an everybody loses situation i hope not those were some slow
oh shit that's okay thank god we only have two hearts fuck swooped in and dated a player that
had just been rejected three times that's what i did we both won swapped all hearts at once
it was a tie nice work inflicted three lost hearts of damage on players who scorned them
we would have been up there rejected other players two times and earned two hearts
i fucking hate this game is what somebody just wrote track the body swapper all game
day of the month all right directly infected three players of the zombie virus
i'm glad that didn't happen never quite doubled sorry moo earned three hearts for each neither
child i still went dateless and then i won all right that brings us to the five hour mark
and the end of tonight's stream that was bullshit i gotta go on a victory here right come on so you
will see jackbox again because there are a couple that i'd like to do with at least a couple of
people that are in the call so you'll see it again probably at some point like the next week or two
i'm heartbroken yeah we'll do the bits and everything just be aware that tomorrow there's
a stream tomorrow and there's a stream on sunday we're gonna go three days in a row
tomorrow's red dead redemption 2 online with a friendo and then the movie night is sunday
at 4 p.m pacific and with that thank you for joining me i hope you had fun thank you for playing
everyone that got a chance to play we will be doing it again soon so let's get out a lot of here
put on the outro get rid of that hey look at that there it is let's go back into the bits
oh the a comes the end of the stream voice uh we had some big donations tonight so thank you
you guys rock maybe take it off see you tomorrow or the next day whenever you end up coming back
we'd love to have you hey honey chain thank you honey chain for the ten dollars here
is this an expense uh no it is not i'm well it is an expense it's you it's an expense for you
that was it was an expense but it i am not expanding i'm receiving
so thank you so much honey chain for the ten dollars thank you soup or seal for the one dollar
and it's a picture of it's a picture of hulk hogan with my face in the stomach
i don't i've what the fuck is this thank you but i don't even i'm not even gonna link this
this is just like this is like it's almost barely i don't want to what is this why did you show me
this i don't i don't get it what is that it's just my sad face and hulk hogan's stomach uh thank you
super seal to that image cookie cookie crm give a hundred dollars over the course of the night
100 bucks thank you so much cookie and i think you actually got uh i think you played you played
once too right didn't you thank you thank you for the hundred fucking bucks also thank you to uh the
long or the long gg thanks for the two dollars seems good i made the cooking the books joke
and described your hotel as the white house where is my mod dad don't you love your kids
can't give mod to all the children understand hulk hogan looks like a balleris but thank you
the long the long egg why the long gg the long egg thank you you guys are a ton of you guys are
hilarious so it doesn't surprise me that you come up with funny things uh divas p three dollars
thank you divas thank you so much thank you also to uh sushi or sushi p thank you sushi p for the
ten dollars hey germ a big fan of your work you are brilliant and i love your sense of humor
very very kind to say that thank you so much you got it yeah i've been saying it correctly
the last few streams but that means a lot thank you so much hope you stick around there's gonna
be more to see thank you for the ten dollars ten bucks also thank you to uh the david cage for the
one dollar love you dad hey thanks a lot thank you timmy tim tan thanks for the ten dollars old man
is confused by technology timmy tim tam ten dollars i you know technology does confuse me
sometimes but i'm gonna i adapt and i try and i put my 100 of my brain goes into trying to figure
stuff out on stream sometimes that's i forgot to punch in the game code i'm getting older that
happens thank you so much timmy appreciate the ten dollars uh we also have uh maxi thank you maxi for
the two bucks baby thanos distract streamer from winning baby thanos earl of illusion thanks to the
one dollar local streamer doesn't know ass from elbow forgets to join his own game i'll take that
yeah you that's right that's true the long egg also says i forgot to start today's stream by
juggling like you promised i i don't have anything we actually we're going to like the grocery store
tonight and i'm gonna get like oranges i was gonna get oranges to do this so i'm done don't worry
you'll see it i just got nothing to juggle i'm not juggling coke cans because if i drop one of those
and it explodes it's gonna ruin my room so i'm sorry all i have is all i have is coca cola cans
in the whole house you'll see it don't worry kill code thanks for the one dollar kill code hey it's
my birthday today germa i just want to say thanks for being a funny guy and i hope you like my video
on sunday there are a lot of submissions and i do need to say this there were hundreds of submissions
hundreds of them and each one was screened and talked about and i just want to make sure everyone's
aware that just because if you're if it does not get shown on sunday does not mean oh it sucked oh
i didn't like it no no no just there are some specific guidelines specific rules and there were
a lot of submissions so we're not showing every single submission on sunday just to make sure
everyone's aware of that none of this was a contest it's just which ones fit certain criteria
it's not like this person wins just want to make that very clear
that would be really hard it it is i don't want to disappoint anybody by saying oh sorry i'm not
showing yours but but this is this just for the purposes of sunday uh we have to try to keep it
as cleaned up as we can kind of because this is like the movie night that doesn't mean we're
not going to do something like this again so but it uh the mods have done an absolutely fantastic
job double double claps here for the mods because they've been a huge part of this process the whole
time so thank you and moving on from that we also got five dollars from lazy luke no message thank
you lazy luke and about happy birthday by the way to kill code happy birthday dude hope you had a
good one and hopefully it's still your birthday that was a few hours ago but happy birthday man
but thank you lazy luke for the five dollars thank you kill code for the one dollar
thank you also to marvash magali for the one dollar why is jack box crashing you ask maybe
this is a sign that the green screen isn't dead the green screen will the green screen lives
forever because it can be anything anything thank you thank you uh dirty thank you dirty margaret
for the one dollar to the guy who made the murder house alignment chart if you watch the opening
seconds of the murder house ladder match frou frou intimidates chuck snog well with soldier
stretches and then hunts him down please change accordingly
please change it thank you dirty margaret appreciate it uh carlos the clam gave 50
dollars earlier big money carlos thank you trying to bribe into a game but that's not how it works
that's not how it works i do appreciate the absolutely enormous amount of money though
thank you uh honey chain again thanks for one dollar honey chain germa i'm drinking boxed rose
wine it's the worst thing i've ever had i should have gotten the red blend and spent seven hours
building a labo i could have told you that rose wine over a red blend come on i mean that was a
big mistake well at least you'll know for next time you'll you'll know for next time but thank
you honey chain hopefully you at least got some uh some use out of it some use out of the wine
it was on sale okay well that's whatever if you're gonna look if you're gonna buy wine on sale
then you gotta be prepared for the potentially sub par taste flavor profile it's gonna have
right it's just there's a very real possibility but thank you uh thank you were wood for the
one dollar just dropping a dollar do you remember that ps2 game with geo uh any chance you'll
continue to play it one day the mascot with the g oh yeah with the big the big mole creature thing
yeah that was like the the disaster game where there's like an earthquake and you try to escape
there actually is still about seven or eight playstation 2 games that we didn't play
and it's just all boxed up and in the closet back here so there'll be a time probably
sooner rather than later where there's not a whole lot of releases for games or if uh if i'm not
working on a particular project or something like that it'll be available so there's a lot of dream
cast a lot of playstation 2 could always go back to uh monster ranch or two because that game was
a lot of fun it's very possible it's very possible so uh also two what else we got
timmy tim tim again thanks for the one dollar do i have anything to declare
oh i never have anything to declare i have anything to declare no hold on a second what is this
at the customs good morning can i see your passport certainly here it is yes that's all right
have you got anything to declare yes i have i've got some whiskey and cigarettes how much whiskey
have you got a liter that's all right and how many cigarettes have you got 200 200 no i haven't 200
open your case please pardon open your case please open it now oh dear look at this you've
got three bottles of whiskey 400 cigarettes and a lot of perfume does that mean i can't go
at the customs good morning can i see your passport oh look at this yeah you've got three bottles of
whiskey declare yes i have i've got some whiskey and some cigarettes how much whiskey have you got
a liter that's all right so okay how many cigarettes have you got 200 fine what about
perfume uh no i haven't good no open your case open your case please open your case open your
case please open it now dear look at this oh dear bottles of whiskey 400 cigarettes and a lot of
perfume does that mean i can't go i love that does that mean i can't go yes that's what it means you
can't you're not you cannot go sorry oh dear oh yeah that's right hold on that way it's 2.5 speed
so that's all right have you got anything to declare yes i have i've got and how open it now
oh dear look at this you've got three bottles of whiskey 400 cigarettes and a lot of perfume
does that mean i can't go
what a treasure trove of just comedy there's so much there anything to declare thank you to me
tim tim uh kite so thank you kite so for the one dollar germa your imitation of a keyboard sent
my dog into a frenzy my computer monitor is shattered and on the floor my wife is filing
for divorce it was it was quiet it was i'm not going to do it again i don't want to break your
dog or your i don't want to send your computer into a frenzy so i'm not going to do it again
but thank you uh thank you smelly boy for the one dollar do you have a goblin body or a football
jock body there is no in between what extra cheesy thanks for the two bucks look germa i found your
uh just she's a funny streamer who says stuff and loves to comb her hair oh my fucking lord
what the hell is it is that me that's me what did you do what is this what is this from
it's the face app thing oh she's oh my god okay well thank you show i just you guys just saw it
i just linked it did i not link it yeah i did i i linked it yeah it's been linked oh the the
the music sorry about that thank you extra cheesy for that thank you garfield a monday killer for
the one dollar watch this germa goffy is going to make this garf buck disappear right before your
eyes just going to do the magic words i'm not saying these magic words absolutely not germa
check your wallet you just got an extra garf buck through the magic of paws incorporated thank you
you've been a great audience hey germ welcome for the backstage pass to garf's magic show
i thought we could get more cats watching any cartoon cats none of them no all right cat dog
i want cat dog there that's it say it i'm not gonna say it i'm gonna link it that's i'm not saying it
it's like snappity snoopity snee send you know i'm not doing it thank you for the dollar garfield
thank you i want cat dog there thank you uh pockets for the two bucks pockets a bunch of
my friends and i religiously watch you for the past six years it's a large part of our friendship
has been based around the shit that you've said my one friend showed up at a party with an actual
dork cube it was a mess oh god anyways thanks for having such a positive impact we all really
appreciate you so much i can't count how many shitty days you've improved really means a lot
ps not buying a gloom ensure it was the biggest regret to buy life what's the plan for those
they're coming back there there is a plan over the next probably couple months where there's
probably there might be three shirts to buy just available for a month or so like last time just
three of them just not gonna have them come out oh this one and then this one and this just have
them all at the same time and if you want them you want them if not then you don't right it's
gonna happen but thank you so much pockets six years is a long damn time i am absolutely honored
that you and your friends uh can have fun based around some of the things you've seen here
so i'm honored thank you thank you e dragon for the five dollars thanks for the fun stream time
to start my 14 page paper do monday good luck that's a lot that's a lot of words you're gonna
be fine though you'll get it done you'll get it done over the next couple days and you'll breeze
through it you'll just be on a you're going to spree trust me you'll be good thank you e dragon
for the five bucks thanks for sticking around uh spaghetti tony thanks for the five dollars had a
wonderful time playing with you tonight stay amazing you too thanks for playing it's always
fun to play games like this and try to get people involved right i don't do it that often but when
it's available it's especially when it's easy to do something like jackbox you can just kind of
throw it on for a few hours and just play it's not lobbies and oh hold on i gotta like who do
who can i add just makes it easy it's fun uh thank you though thank you fourth consecutive line for
the 20 bucks 20 dollars from fourth consecutive line uh love you germa keep being an amazing
entertainer thanks for everything you have no idea how much you've helped me over the years
my pleasure thanks for being here for the years and thanks for your contributions
thank you so much i hope you still enjoy it clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar
no message clueless thanks a lot man super spy burger flipper thanks for the one dollar it was
an honor to play with you and chat love your stuff i was the jex guy in the drawing game can't wait
for movie night i am so excited i am so excited for movie night that's just gonna be like a chill
fun stream just to relax and just watch stuff sunday evening uh blast toys thanks for the one
dollar hey germa here played spyro the remastered trilogy came out on ps4 highly recommended fans
of the original and new players alike i played the original spyro for not very long and i
didn't experience it at all i think i i don't know how i got my hands on it i may have like
rented it or something maybe i had i played it like a couple hours and i didn't do anything
so i mean definitely would play it i'm not sure if i would stream it but i don't know it depends
thank you for the one dollar and the recommendation hey gondor lane thanks for
the one dollar i got really close to getting you to play bookworm adventures the other day
i'll never stop trying you to get it to play it i fight an eternal crusade i add it to okay when
i play lego island i'm gonna play bookworm adventures right after it a most wanted stream
thank you gondor lane thank you lazy luke again for five dollars no message thanks for five bucks
lazy luke double d11 thanks for the one dollar make a full jupiter and chat right now i bet you
won't be able to i did it take me and traumas me and traumas did it oh no i got scared it up
don't matter well you win thank you lazy luke again for five dollars five dollars again no
message thank you again lazy luke five dollars five ten fifteen twenty lazy luke coming in with five
bucks over and over again thank you no messages here means a lot thank you so much man sputa
thanks for the one dollar had fun on jackbox today laughed so hard my stomach hurts by the way will
you ever beat midir on stream no well those of you that have played dark souls games you know
that you have to be you have to be currently playing a dark souls game to be able to play a
dark souls game you can't play a shitload of dark souls like four or five days straight and then
two months go by and you come back and just go where you left off oh no way you got to be
currently playing a dark souls game to be able to even consider playing a dark souls game it's just
truth but thank you thank you sputa did i ever beat him i didn't i didn't well i mean we we mario
party beat him didn't we maybe challenge run i would get too upset i wouldn't be able to do it
thank you shoes room for the one dollar green screen man broke into my school and stole my
lunch money you need to fix him i can't he could be anywhere thank you shoes room for the one dollar
dark star 700 000 games thanks for the two bucks i've tried not to spoil myself but the new but the
few movie night videos i have seen are absolutely excellent unfortunately due to the many approaching
deadlines at the end of the semester i was unable to make a video but i promise you when i do have
the time to make something it'll be the best shit post possible peace and love thank you dark star
and i again i'm gonna punch home on this again it's not a contest it's just a chill night where
we just play videos that were submitted that met criteria that we thought were interesting or fun
or funny or cool you know it or cool or epic you know what i mean so don't worry it's not there was
no contest or anything but what i have seen yes some of them are very very well made epic fail
i hate that fucking word i hate the word epic i really do but thanks a lot dark star box guy
thank you box guy for the one dollar hey germa i joined in during that robot rapping game and
sucked real bad germa pluto but i'm just glad i finally managed to get into a jack box game
with my favorite streamer it was all in good fun box guy it was very enjoyable so thank you
hey what's cracking thanks for the five dollars thanks for the fun germa and don't worry we still
love you even though you never beat pinwheel thanks appreciate that you know maybe one day i
will thank you what's cracking for the five dollars and lastly double d11 thanks for the one dollar
get uh get italics in here i heard him outside your room he's he's not there he's in his office
somewhere in this fucking house i have no idea if i go through like six different doors
let's roll the credits thanks everybody for sticking around i hope you had fun
looks like there were a shitload of subs tonight too an uncountable amount of people
continue to subscribe to this channel every time i stream returning or new chat wanted to know
how your hair was doing it's doing okay did somebody gifted a sub to fortnight did that happen
why does fortnight have a sub fortnight do you think that that anybody at the fortnight marketing
team whatever or the twitch channel just opens up who they're subscribed to and there's just
hundreds of people they're subscribed to but thank you all of you i wouldn't be surprised
timmy tim tim does it bother you when people like me make a bunch of donations in one night
using a hundred bits at a time no no absolutely not the only time i mean the the only time where
it would ever become an issue is if it starts to become too much you know what i mean so
let's say that as we continue to go here there's hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of messages at
the end of the night you know i mean it would at that point it is physically not possible for me
to read them all it would take six seven eight hours to do that you know what i mean so as if
if we have to figure out what to do then we have to figure out what to do if the minimum has to
increase if that has to happen i try to wait as long as possible before we need to do something
like that i will never turn on uh text to speech ever it'll literally never happen so that's not
an option literally literally look at all these fucking subs my god you see how many people are
here do you see this are you seeing this right you guys can see that on the screen literally
almost every chat member is subbed that that is remarkable hundreds of people subscribed today
thank you guys sub only mode a sub only mode ain't gonna do very much i mean think about that hey
turn on sub only mode oh everybody in chat is subbed oh all right thank you guys thank you for
subscribing thank you for watching i can only say thanks so many times you know and i i broken
record myself a lot i just do but just know that it's appreciated thinking of subs double d
double d just gave up five community subs thank you double d five community subs from double d
right at the end and just like that right that's five more oh and speaking of five thinking of ten
ten coming in from kairatobi ten community subs from kairatobi oh my god kairatobi you have given
a lot of these five from double d and then ten ten people just got subscribed from kairatobi
thank you kairatobi new emotes when i actually think i may have another i think i have slots
now i'm gonna have to look and see what i would want to do kairatobi thank you then thanks all of
you for being here that's the end that's the time i'll see you tomorrow for maybe red dead two online
um i have to talk to a couple people that were involved in maybe setting it up if that does not
happen which it may not happen i'm gonna figure out if it's gonna happen or not for a few different
reasons if it doesn't then i'll figure something out we'll figure something out for tomorrow
so don't worry there'll be a stream tomorrow as the remaining subs come through we also had right
at the end moo means moo gave a dollar glad i was able to be part of this epic stream
delete that it was quite a win anyway gotta go back to looking at those
lol cat memes they're hilarious i sure hope he gets his cheeseburger someday check out his hilarious
site called shoes if you get a chance much love buddy have a good night uh plat to platydunius
thanks for the five dollars 25 cents of the very end got kicked from the last game of msm when someone
else joined but it was worth it knowing that we got to see zombie betray the chat sorry
that i had to kind of detonate the room a couple of times but thank you so much
and right at the very end movies real talk watching your channel grow has been truly
awesome few other people on the site deserve it more than you you work crazy hard in the stream
shows on the stream of yours and i've been able to watch through the years it's been amazing so
many of your streams feel like an event to look forward to so on behalf of the community thank
you for all you do thank you it's my intention is to try to make each stream as fun and interesting
as i can and if it's not if i feel like it's not then i feel i feel bad so just know that that's
the goal every time and thank you extra cheesy for the two bucks germa you're an epic sauce streamer
thank you very much see you guys tomorrow have a great rest of your night and goodbye and thank
you timmy tim tim for the one dollar stalling you leaving like you stole the next mission in
la no more there it is okay good night have a good one i'll see you tomorrow get some sleep