Okay, I'm back. Back. I have clothes on, kind of. Don't worry, I have enough clothing on where I'm
good. All right, let me come back here. Make sure I think I'm not naked. No, I'm not. I'm going E3
mode right now. I'm going E3 outfit. All right, let me do this. Uh, can you see me? Just better
not have a fucking frame of me naked or something. Let me just make sure it doesn't. Uh, that was
Watchdog Legions. Uh, stand up. No. No, I won't. Evil Agent Jerma? Uh, that was worse than FTK. Come on.
Oof. Everybody stand up. Stand, coward. Look, what do you want? What do you mean stand up? Look,
I'm wearing a robe. I'm wearing my gown that I wear every night and I relax at home.
Stand up. I'm standing as, I'm standing up. Open it. This is staying as tight to the chest as I
can get it. Arms to the sky. All right. I look like a fucking dinner table. What's today? Ooh,
mashed potatoes. Chicken, fried chicken. I love that. All right, let's go. Put a shirt on. I don't
care. I'm going. I have a shirt. This is a big one. Let me just capture my fucking window.
Oh, this is not a shirt. It's a huge, it's a huge shirt. Okay. Window capture. What even is being
captured right now? I have no fucking idea. Okay. All right. Here we go. This is Jerma Meltdown
tier list. I don't know what you can see. Where am I? Uh, some of these aren't fair. All right.
This, the way this camera is set up, someone's coming out of there in five minutes and strangling
me from behind. You know, like, oh yeah, I just, hey guys, perfect fucking view of that closet.
No one's coming out of there with like a knife. I don't, it's Halloween, man. Freaking me out.
You're in the wrong category. I'll change it. I'll get it. Category we in? Legion of grandmas.
How about, should I just write watchdogs sucks. Pivoting to tier lists. It really doesn't suck
though. My computer sucks. My computer sucks. Tier lists for 10 minutes. No, how about just my,
my computer sucks. There you go. Okay. Here we go. Uh, I'm actually going to zoom this in because,
all right, so this is, these are the, these are the worst meltdowns I've had on stream.
Start with Katamari. Beautiful Katamari. I, I don't know if that was true. That's probably a C.
This is Chili Time. Uh, Chili Time is probably an S because I remember being hurt. I hurt myself
on this stream. Like an hour after that stream ended, I like actually, my, my, I hurt myself.
Uh, and I do remember that being unbearable. Dark Souls, I beat it. It was good. The game was fun.
I would say that's, no, Katamari is higher than that. Dark Souls 3? No, not really. Dead Rising 2
was not really a meltdown. It was just, that was fun. I had a lot of fun in Dead Rising 2.
Uh, these are up here. I think I specifically started, I remember specifically talking about
how the games are getting way too hard and how much I hate every video game or something during
this, right? Hotline Miami 2, way more than Hotline Miami 1. Jump King is S. I remember that was
horrible. No, I wouldn't put Lifeline's probably around B. Ario Tennis was one of the only times
really on stream ever that I was actually angry. Truly angry. Upset. Very, very angry. And not
like, oh, like, like tonight, right? Tonight. It's like, oh, watch dogs. Hey, what the fuck?
Oh, that stream was, oh, that sucked. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. I was like, I fucking hated
every second of playing that game. Every second of it. I was like, I hate this. Uh, I, I hated
being on, I hated the stream. I hated the fucking game. I hated the, the Switch or whatever dumb,
whatever it was, the Wii U at that point, whatever it was. Shit, this is up there too. Lord of the
Rings, the two towers. I mean, this, I think this has to trump this because this is the
longest stream I've ever done. This is 13, 14 hour long stream. Yeah, that's probably the
longest. Oh, Dom was just stupid and broken and hurt everybody's ears. I don't know if Sekiro is
over Hotline Miami. It might be. Especially that last boss. Hmm. I'm going to leave it there for
now. Monkey Ball was, hmm, probably more than, no. Probably, nah, probably more than Katamari.
You spent two hours on it. On the ape? Yeah, that's true. I did. Uh, the thing is S. I always gauge
on how high up on a list like this, that this has to be. If I like talk shit about the developers
of the game, that's very important, right? The amount of times that I was like, why did they do
this? What were they fucking thinking? Like that's how I can tell that it should be up here. Stuntman
Ignition was just fun. Okay, now I have to, I have to get this right. Simpsons was definitely worse
than Hotline Miami. Simpsons was definitely worse than Chilly Time. We have to, we're going to demote
Chilly Time. Hit and run is S. Yeah, it definitely is. Uh, was hit and run more of a mouth down than
Jump King? I don't think so. Was it? I feel like these two are on par with each other.
Have you seen the stream? I lived it, bro. Why did my face look like it just was like going like
this? That was weird. I think this is accurate because this is just, this was not really meltdown.
This was anger. Yeah, I think that's correct. Now it's correct. Now it's good. There you go.
There's, uh, there's the, me ranking the times that I've, oh, and where would I put the Watch Dogs
Legion stream? Probably like here. That was just the bad. I didn't have like a meltdown. I just,
my computer crashed like five times and I had to download drivers. And this whole stream was like
a fucking mess, but this wasn't a meltdown stream. This was a mess stream behind you.
But you think that opened? Shelf is collapsing. Oh, make sure you get a good view. All right,
there's the next one. This is a Ubisoft tier list. It should be pretty easy. Uh, okay. I can't even,
what are some of these? Assassin's Creed Origins. I didn't play it. Assassin's Creed Reincarnation?
I can't read that. Assassin's Creed 3. Assassin's Creed Rogue. That's like an iPad game.
Assassin's Creed 2. Assassin's Creed. Assassin's Creed Black Flag. Assassin's Creed Revelations.
Assassin's Creed. No, I didn't play any of these fucking games. Assassin's Creed Odyssey. None of
them. Uh, okay. Where's, uh, this is Far Cry Classic. This game is an F. I just want to make
sure everyone's aware of this. This game is not good. It's, I mean, at the time, at the time,
it was a very, it was amazing for graphics and fidelity and draw distance, but the video game
is actually really bad. It's not good. People wanted me to play this and I was like, oh yeah,
Far Cry. And then I remembered this is the game where people can shoot you literally that have
not been generated by the map yet. You can get shot through walls. Okay. No, I think it should
be there. It's probably, it's better than Far Cry. No, Far Cry, was Far Cry 5 really that bad?
Do I even like any Ubisoft games? Why do I play them? I feel like every single one of these I
would put like in D. Do I like any of these games? Although I have, I'll be honest, I never played a
whole lot of the Assassin's Creed stuff. This is like, this game was good. It's Beyond Good and
Evil, right? No, that was, this was good. You know, it would be really great to see Beyond Good and
Evil 2 and not Assassin's Creed 15. I played all the Rayman games when I was younger. I remember
really liking them though. I have not played a Rayman game in a long time. Where's Raving Rabbids?
That's S tier. Don't you think it's funny? Well, no, No More Heroes 2 is not. No. I'm sorry. I have
to be completely honest with everybody in myself. No More Heroes 2 is not S tier. It's, it's very
good. I think No More Heroes 1 is better. Let's make this right. Okay. Assassin's Creed Unity.
I didn't play the Prince of Persia remake. I didn't play any of these. I don't even know
what the game this is, but I know I didn't play it. I don't know what game this is, but I know I
didn't. Wait, this is Far Cry. Which Far Cry is that? Is that Far Cry 2? That's the good one.
Ends of Time is the only good one. Far Cry Primal. No, I didn't play it. I didn't play it. This is
Rayman. It's going up here. Oh, this is Rayman Origins, right? Rayman, no, what's the new one?
The one that came out not that long ago, like five years ago. This one, this was good. This was
actually pretty very, this is the good one. I think that's accurate. Uh, Watch Dogs. You know what?
Like, I'm going to be, I have to be honest with everybody. I have to, I just have to be honest
with you. I really don't, I don't think these are good. They're probably better than, the problem is
like these are like all the same, all the things that are on E right now are the same game with
just like some differences, like open world with like a bunch of random missions to do, but like
one is like a hacker and one you like drive around and like get shot at by like religious people,
right? Cult. I put these, these on the same exact category. Like to me, they blend together as the
same game. I think I just don't like Watch Dogs. Two was better. I actually do remember playing Two
and it was, it was fun for a little bit. It was. Yeah, I think I just don't like Far, I think I
just don't like Watch Dogs. What's wrong with me? I didn't really like Watch Dogs One. I didn't
really like Watch Dogs Two. So let me buy Watch Dogs Three and stream it on launch and be excited
for it. When the first two games I would put down at E tier. Why did I do that? Yeah, I gotta be
honest. I just don't think I like the games. I see there, I see how people could think that they're
fun. Backtracking Barry. He's back, backtracking. No, I'm not. This is a me. I'm forward tracking.
Okay, there's so many games in this list. I thought this was the list of things that haven't been put
up yet. Oh wow. Okay. What's next? Assassin's Creed? Oh no. Okay. Don't look at me. All right.
So let this be, let's be a future reference. Don't ever invite me to like an Ubisoft event
because very clearly, oh man, I didn't get invited to the Ubisoft party. What the fuck? They didn't
put me on the list of streamers, but I have played 1% of their whole catalog of video games. What the
heck? Why won't they talk to me? I don't play any of their games. What? You mean my name was glossed
over when I could have been like a VIP at like the Ubisoft like conference? Name one game you've
completed that was an Ubisoft game. No More Heroes and No More Heroes 2. Those are the only
Ubisoft games that I have completed. Every single other game on this list has been played
for a maximum of four hours. Wait, where's For Honor? Where is it? I'm sorry. It's like,
I can't even see, like, okay. I feel like Assassin's Creed, Assassin's Creed, which one?
These are all just different cards. You know, like the collectible Marvel cards. This is just
different artist depictions that you collect in that series. It's just like, I can't even just,
all right. This is like the Hulk, but like kind of metal. This is like
intergalactic Hulk. This is, this is She-Hulk. There's, okay, this is Deadpool. Like, I feel
like I'm just collecting fucking the cards of the same character. Where is For Honor? There it is.
Okay, it gets a D. Deadpool is the Hulk. Yeah, the only, I don't play any of their catalog. I've
never, I don't even, why would I play Ubisoft games? These two aren't even Ubisoft games.
And yeah, because every time like the Ubisoft does like a big press conference thing or like
an E3 thing, I just skip it. I just don't even, I just stop watching. I think the only time that
I ever watched a Ubisoft conference is when I was on stream with you guys. I'm roasting them.
I'm not though. This is just me. Is that Far Cry 3? Where's Far Cry 2? Wait, wasn't Red Steel kind
of good? Why do I remember this being kind of fun? I might be thinking of a different game. No,
I didn't play any of the South Park games either. Yeah, no, this list is done. No, I haven't played
South Park. Why is Black Flag so low? Black Flag is so low because it's the only Assassin's Creed
game that I've ever played for more than four or five hours. And I don't remember. It definitely
should be in front of, yeah, above Red Steel. Well, yeah, this has been an eye-opening stream
for me. Just got removed off of all the Ubisoft content creator email lists. Okay, this is
artificial flavors. What is the best artificial flavor? This is going to be really hard. I know
that for certain. I know the grape for certain. Grape and watermelon. Terry's up there too,
but I don't wear banana. Okay, when I think about artificial flavoring, I think of hard candy,
but I love banana cream pie. It's one of my favorite things ever. And there's just banana
flavoring that some people put in banana cream pie. Does that count? It counts. It's just like
an added artificial banana flavoring. It goes up here then. I know if I put banana up at S tier,
then like there's people buried under my floorboards. I get it, but there's not.
But I like it. Strawberry, eh, hit or miss. Second grape, okay. I actually don't really like
artificial orange or artificial lemon. Artificial lemon just tastes like heartburn. That's like the
flavor it is when you like burp up fucking heartburn. Blue raspberry, that's A. Green apple,
that's A. Peach, artificial peach flavoring is just kind of like battery acid. I don't like it.
It's trying to, no, it tastes like perfume. Artificial peach flavoring just tastes like
you're drinking, like eating perfume. I think this is good. How do you know? I'm just, I'm
just guessing, man. Watermelon sucks? No, it does not. You eat a watermelon Jolly Rancher right now,
son. And then you come to me and you come back to this stream telling me it was bad.
Watermelon's the only thing in the right place. Grape? You don't think that grape belongs here?
No? Grape flavoring? Like a grape popsicle? Grape is baste. Yeah, it is. Cherry's miles better than
grape. I'll tell you that cherry's probably better than banana. I think this is good.
Grape is B tier. How could you say something like that? All right, I like it. It's, yeah,
cough syrup. Maybe that's why I like it. Because when I was a little kid, there was that dimetap
had, it was grape dimetap. And I remember being like, holy shit, this is the greatest thing I've
ever eaten in my life. Whenever I had like a cold or a cough or something when I was a little kid.
You guys don't remember that? How it would be, oh, grape dimetap. And when you were a little kid,
it was like, oh my god, it's like candy! But it wasn't. You're leaning? You're a crackhead.
What? Because I said the artificial grape flavoring was good in dimetap when I was like 11?
No, I don't like put it in fucking Coke or Sprite or anything. I'm talking about just the flavor.
It was a great grape jolly rancher flavor. Oh, sandwiches. Oh, I'm gonna get attacked over these.
This is gonna be okay. Bacon, egg and cheese. That's S tier. It's fucking unbelievable.
A grilled cheese. That depends. Is this a sad grilled cheese that you make at two o'clock
in the morning because you don't have any food in your fridge? You just have slices of cheese
and bread? Or is this like a hipster restaurant where they give you a grilled cheese, but it's
actually a bunch of other shit that they pretend it is a grilled cheese and it's super super
like ritzy and uppity? Which one? Because I'll tell you. The one that I make at two o'clock
in the morning goes up here. The one that's from the restaurant where they make it, they like dress
it up a lot, is down here. Ah, that's pulled pork sandwich. That's S tier. That's a bon meat. That's B.
BLT, F. I wish I could give it an F. I wish I could say like put immediately into a garbage can.
BLT is a scam. It's a way for you to buy a sandwich without buying a sandwich and
somebody made it up. Somebody just was like, yeah, let me put like some of the shit that
people put on top of salad. Here's like condiments in between two pieces of bread. That sounds great.
No, there's not enough. You're missing the thing that goes underneath all that.
I'll never understand a BLT. What do you put on your hamburger? Lettuce, tomato and bacon.
What do you put on like a ham sandwich? I put lettuce and tomato on a ham sandwich.
Um, what do you put on a, what do you put on a tuna fish sandwich? Lettuce, maybe a slice of cheese.
Maybe, maybe, maybe a tomato. What do you put on a BLT? That's just it. It's just tomato and lettuce.
And then you put bacon on top of it. And bacon is supposed to be the protein part,
but that's just an extra. It's an additive. You have something else there. Cheese on tuna?
Yeah, a tuna fish sandwich. You never have cheese on tuna fish sandwich. It's good. Just like a
slice of American cheese. That's what a tuna melt is. How have you not had a tuna melt?
No, I just don't, I just don't think BLTs are that I would, look, I would eat it and I would
be happy with it, but I wouldn't be, I wouldn't order it. Because a lot of times a BLT is like
eight bucks and the large steak and cheese sub is 8.50. You're getting scammed. Just go and buy
a head of lettuce and go buy four tomatoes and a pound of bacon and you can eat BLTs for a month.
Move on. No, this is important to me. Holy shit French dip. Oh fucking get up to S. Are you
kidding me? Thanksgiving sandwich that goes up in front of that. Italian sub, they can be a little
watery. I don't know. They could get soggy. They're okay. Lobster roll? Uh, yeah. Turkey club? No,
too annoying. Too, it's annoying because you like, you have to open your mouth a little,
wicked huge and you end up going right on to the, like just the corner. You can only bite the corner
and when you bite the corner, every single thing inside just shoots out and you have to like,
oops, that's why they had the stupid little thing in there. This is baste. I'm getting a lot of baste
today. Uh, cheese steak. Fuck. I love cheese steak so much. I really do. Fried chicken sandwich. I
love sandwiches. This is going to be very hard. This might be the hardest tier list that you guys
have linked me. Um, okay. I just, I don't know what this is. This looks like a, this looks like a kit
cat bar with the chocolate taken off. I don't know what it is. Uh, tuna melt. Oh fuck. Meatball sub.
Fuck. A Reuben. Oh man, there's too many S tier sandwiches here. A, a gyro fucking S tier. I don't
know what that is. Oh, Cuban sandwich. Come on. Come on, Gwen. That's better than grilled cheese.
Patty melt. These are all, I, there's too many. Roast beef. Disgusting. I hate roast beef. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Let's hear it. I wrote, wrote what? Cold meat. Cold meat. No. Give me this. Give
me the French dip. Actually heat it up and put it in the sandwich like fucking real. I don't,
cold roast beef that you get. No. It just, it tastes like it came out of somebody's trash.
Every time that I bite into or smell roast beef that comes from the deli, it just smells like
old trash. You guys aren't actually using Arby's as a barometer for good roast beef sandwiches,
are you? Just because they say that in the commercial doesn't mean it's any good. Arby's
is okay. It's not good. Quiznos. Quiznos disappeared. Reviewers are dropping because of this. I feel
like my roast beef opinion is not an unpopular one. You guys want to talk about a boomer food?
A roast beef sandwich is like the ultimate boomer food. You want to be like a boomer?
Egg salad? It depends, but usually pretty good. Peanut butter and jelly. I'd put fluff on there
instead and I'd be happier. Monte Cristo. Too heavy, but very, very tasty. Torta. A. A standard
ham and cheese sandwich. No, I'm putting it down here at D, not because I don't like it,
because this is like the go-to when I have nothing else to eat. So I don't really want
a ham and cheese sandwich with just lettuce on it. But if I have to eat it, I'll enjoy it.
Nah, it's just, no. I'd rather it be like turkey, mayo, provolone. Ham is... I'm not a big ham fan.
I'm really not. A Cuban sandwich is way better. Egg salad is gross? Why is egg salad gross?
You have too many S tiers. I know, I'll work on it. I don't know what that is.
Falafel pita. I'd rather it be a gyro. Chicken salad. Fuck yeah, get up there.
A bologna and cheese sandwich. It's only gonna go up to B because it's what I ate every single day
from the ages of 8 to 20 during the hours of 11 to 2 p.m. It was eaten almost every day.
These two? Where's tuna? Just a tuna fish sandwich. Cucumber tea? It's a cucumber sandwich?
How have they made the BLT even shittier? This is just, this is just L. Wait, you just put two
pieces of cucumber between bread? Somebody like had to turn their homework in, in 10 minutes,
and they're in homeroom. And they're like, fuck, I gotta come up with a sandwich.
Okay, cucumbers between bread. Done. Fuck. I hope they're okay with it.
No, that's all the way down. Why would I eat that? How about a Kentucky hot brown? I don't know what
that is. Italian beef sandwich. Is it better than egg salad? It might be better than a, than a...
This is not roast beef. This is hot. This is, this is not cold. This is a hot sandwich. It's not cold.
Roast beef sandwich is a fucking cold. That's a cold fucker. What is this? Are these cold?
Usually it's hot. Croque monsieur. Um, never had it. Po' boys are okay, but this is kind of boring.
It's just fried shrimp between two pieces of sub roll. I'd rather just have you take it apart,
and I just want to eat the fried shrimp with like some, uh, dipping sauce. I don't want fried shrimp
between bread. I, this is kind of boring to me. Bagel with lox? That's, here's the weird part about
bagel with lox. I was just going to put it up here to pretend that, like, to be sophisticated.
I've eaten it plenty of times, but I was, oh yeah, of course, bagel with lox. I'm sophisticated. I'm
like cool and smart, but like, it actually is probably down here. Like, if I want to pretend
to you guys, I'm like, wow, look at, I'm like, look at how, how, look at my food eating habits.
I eat like salmon lox on bagels. Who cares? Like, doesn't matter. Yeah, it's down here.
Just be pretending to be, like, sophisticated when I'm not. Liverwurst, F. Veggie and hummus, F.
Oh, okay, veggie and hummus is just BLT. It's different, some other way, made a different way.
Veggie and hummus, this is, this is like the Mediterranean BLT. What was this? Bocadillo.
Is it bread rub with butter? I've never had it. Okay, let me, let me get this right. What is the
best sandwich on earth? I gotta be, like, dressed for this. I'm hungry right now. I'm very hungry
right now, so this is important. This is the best time to take this quiz. If you presented all these
in front of me right now and you said, Jeremy, pick between fucking any of these. You can have
any of one of them right now. And the, oh, and all the other ones disappear. Let's get that right,
right off the bat. Oh, feeling like fucking Reuben tonight. Oh, wait a minute, this is
patty melt. Sounds pretty good too. Oh, meatball sub. Actually, fuck, meatball sub has to go down
a full two letter grades. Because this is just the thing that's at school lunch every day.
It sucks. But I love meatballs. I love meatball subs. Ah, French dip comes up.
Patty melt. Thanksgiving sandwich is about to get knocked out. No, it can't. It's like my favorite.
It's my favorite. But if I was presented with all these right now and it just assigned my fucking
soul away to eat one of these right now, which one would it be? It wouldn't be, it wouldn't be,
it wouldn't be agiro. It wouldn't be tuna melt. That's too simple.
Hmm. French dip is creeping. Oh shit. It's pulled pork is on the move. Pulled pork is on the move.
Fuck. Fuck. Oh, I didn't got to knock him down. You got to knock some down. You have to. I don't
think it's going to be harder if I don't Reuben with fresh, fresh fucking like, oh,
sauerkraut. And with that fresh like corned beef, just like shredded up and just placed over like,
oh, with tender and just bite into it. You get that the hint of the sourness from the sauerkraut.
You get that Dijon must what's on it. Russian dressing. It's like my favorite sandwich. I don't
fucking know what's on it. I love Reuben's. No, but that's so basic. It's so easy to love a
cheesesteak. Everybody does. Is it weird that I don't think you're okay. If you don't like
cheesesteak, there's something wrong with you, right? If you eat meat, right? If you're vegetarian
or vegan, whatever, you're not going to eat these. But if you eat meat and you don't love cheesesteak,
I don't even know how it's possible. I've never met anybody in my life that ate meat
and had a cheesesteak and went, oh, no, thank you. That is awful. Yuck. Who's ever done that?
What if you're lactose intolerant? No, but I mean like if you are of the body of people that can
eat these sandwiches, if you can, if you're not lactose intolerant, you're not vegetarian,
you're not vegan, you eat meat, you eat beef. If you, all those things, if you do that and you
don't like a cheesesteak, who are you? From a cheese's garbage. What? I have digestive problems
and I still eat the fuck out of cheese. Don't eat a lot of it, but hold on. I know cheese is like a
meme. Like, oh my God, cover it with cheese. The ooey gooey cheesy. Oh yeah. Oh my God. Does it
have like a bunch of fucking nacho cheese on it? Oh, I know. I get it, but it's still good. Oh,
how can we make a, how can we make like a Caesar salad better? Cover it with ooey gooey yummy,
cheesy, cheesy, cheesy. I know people like that. And it's like, okay, we're like, that's funny.
Cheese, put cheese on everything. Stop, please. Please don't talk like this. No, this is, this is
fine the way it is. Now we gotta go to A. Chicken gyro. I love them. Chicken salad. Egg salad. Get
up there. Especially with a little bit of mustard. And if I want to make this even better, I could
put some ooey. Tortoise is better than grilled cheese. It is. Two in a mouth is better than
Italian beef. It is. I'm sorry. It's really easy to make too. These kind of are both the same in my
brain. If you want cold version, you know, if you want, if you're feeling like a cold sandwich,
chicken salad, hot tuna melt. Do that a sub notification with that. Oh, you know how we
could make this sub so much better? With a ton of, no, people would hate me. Grilled cheese is good,
but a grilled cheese with tuna in it is better. All right, enough with the pretending. I don't
actually like this that much. Cologne and cheese, it's just a childhood favorite. It has to be up
there. Lobster roll is 1000% way too low. What the hell was I doing? Yeah, what the fuck is wrong
with me? Lobster roll is better than Italian beef. I think it's good there. I think it's good there.
Get out of here. Okay. Okay. Ooey gooey. All right. Ham and cheese, turkey club, PB&J,
falafel pita, po'boy. I think this is fine. Ham and cheese probably comes up. BLT goes to the bottom.
Caprice comes up. This goes to the bottom. This goes to the bottom. Edgy and a hummus. Oh, these,
no, that goes, oh, yeah. I think that's a little bit worse. No, I don't really know what these
other ones are, but I'm going to stay sure. All right. Ham and cheese, better than a, no,
I'd rather have a po'boy than just a ham and cheese. Imagine going to a restaurant. What do
you have on the menu? Well, on our sandwich list, we have a po'boy with a horse radish mayo on it
and a little bit of a cucumber slice down the middle and butterflied over there with a little
bit of aioli on top. We also have a ham and cheese sandwich. It's just ham, cheese, and lettuce with
just a bun that you get at the grocery store. Get out of here. Why is cucumber above roast beef?
Because I think roast, I think cold roast beef sucks, but you're right. This should be at the
bottom. Why is bologna so high? I like bologna. Fringe. Germa is artificially inflating the price
of, what am I doing? Reubens. Stop watching the stream. Reubens are fan-fucking-tastic, man. I
might have to get one today. Why is PB&J so low? Because I would prefer if it was peanut butter
and fluff, marshmallow fluff. PB&J, I don't want it. I want marshmallow fluff instead. That's a
stupid reason. But is it though? I would rather have a turkey club than a PB&J. Fluff fucking sucks.
You've never had it, then. It's just this ooey gooey sweet. Am I trying to get you guys to not
like me? I think about some of the things that I say in the stream and I think back later, I'm like,
am I trying to make everybody hate me? Is that what I'm doing? Is that the goal of the stream
recently? Hey, what can I say that people are gonna hit the X wicked fucking fast? Oh, I know.
This ooey gooey thing that everyone fucking hates. All right, by the way, it's like a million degrees
in here and I have a full robe on. I'm gonna die. All right, anymore? You got any more lists
before I end this stream? I've done cheeses before. Jurassic Park dinosaurs? Oh, fuck yeah.
All right, we're gonna do Jurassic Park dinosaurs. I'm gonna save this. Control C saves, right? And
then it's Control V to paste. I'm getting the hang of things. Can we see the community rank?
Uh, view, yeah, all right, view community rank. And add. Uh, this is the community rank. Fried
chicken, grilled cheese. Where's Reuben? That's way too fucking low. That's way too low. Where's
roast beef? What? No. Roast beef better than a lobster roll? Okay, we're gonna do one more.
We're gonna do Jurassic Park dinosaur list of like my favorite dinosaurs. You guys ready?
What image is this? Do faces updated. I've already, I'm not doing a tier list of my own face.
That's just, that's so megalomaniac. Did that work? Jurassic Park dinosaurs. Do it. Do it. Do it. Oh
my fucking god. Fine. I'll do it. I'll do it. Where'd your link go? I'm not gonna do human organs.
Link it to me. Link me. All right, this is one, I'll do this one right now. This one's apparently
updated. German faces updated. So what, what am I, how am I ranking these based on
how ugly they are? Or how, or just what they look like? Or how much I like them? Just rank them.
Okay, that's F. This is A. This is a Pog. It has to be high. Uh, this is, that reminds me of the German
Rumble, so it goes up there. This reminds me of the carnival, so it, it's not that high. It should
be high A. This is what, I fucking hate this one too. I like this one. This is, I, look at,
look at how handsome I was when I was a young man. What could it be? That's just a Photoshop. It's
not, it's, all right. What about the ones that are just Photoshop? They're not even my face. Delete
that image off the internet. I fucking hate that image. This is just me looking, oh, that's fat me.
Okay. This one's fucking stupid. All right, I like this one. This one's going up to like A. This one's
probably A. This looks like, I, this is like the Roblox face. Like you made me in Roblox. There's
a lot of shitty, oh wow, yeah, that's up here. This is, okay, I thought this is a screen grab from
this stream. I was like, what the hell? This is, they are, these are screen grabs from this stream.
These don't even faces. You just took the, all right, hold on. I'm fixing the list. Hold on.
This is a picture of me in fucking high school. Who cares? Bottom. Oh wait, no, no, no, no, no,
you're right. Yeah, this goes up here. Wait, now we're going to close this out with Jurassic Park
dinosaurs. This should be easy. Pterodactyl. S. Triceratops. This is, this thing's just dead.
What is that? This is a goofy looking one. B. A. Selfie T-Rex. A. Weird little praying mantis
dinosaur. These things are cute. They get dippy. S. Spitter. A. Food. Food 2. D. T-Rex. A. Velociraptor.
What is the, what's like the Omega Dawn? Isn't that the thing from Jurassic World? What's the
thing called? Whatever it is, I'm giving it an F. What's it called? The new, they made like a
super T-Rex and it's just stupid. What was it called? He's so hungry. I'm gonna fucking try
to get a Reuben is what I'm gonna do. Taffy dinosaur. S. Brontosaurus is so cool. It's like
armadillo. Not even a dinosaur. This thing's, no, F. Is this just bones? Stegosaurus? Whale.
I don't know. I don't know. The thing's stupid. So is this. This is, I can't even tell what these
dinosaurs are. These are really shitty pictures. Wait, this is a pterodactyl with a T-Rex head.
That gets, it has to be up here. For a second I thought, I was like, why is there a human up here?
Uh, this is from The Hobbit. Mog. Food gets to be like all the way at the bottom. But I don't feel
like this is just German 985 faces. What's your favorite face? It's just the same dinosaur doing
other weird faces. Pterodactyl, the little ones, and a brontosaurus. Done. Halloween candy list.
Oh, it's ooey gooey. Don't say that. You'll get, somebody will fight you. This is me and my friends
tier list. Wait, what? Tastiest nuts? Okay, I'll do this one. Tastiest nuts. I don't want to, I don't
want to reveal it. I don't want you guys to see it too soon. Because I want to get a good look at
this first, okay. Uh, these almonds? Almonds S. These are pistachios D, C. I would put pistachios up
in B, but fuck you for being in pistachio ice cream. Seriously. If pistachio ice cream didn't
have pistachios in it, it would be so much better. It just, it angers me. I like pistachios, but when
they're in pistachio ice cream, what the fuck are they doing in there? I like the green ice cream
that pistachios ice cream sits in with whatever that is. I like that. I don't like the nuts in
there. Uh, walnuts. They kind of just, after you chew them up for too long, they get like dry and
grainy. I don't like them. Uh, what are these? Peanuts in the shell. Pretty good. Uh, macadamias.
Pretty good. Cashews F. Are these coffee beans? All right, I feel like that you, you, you, you're
duping me here and there's beans on this list. Are these chickpeas? Chickpeas are A. I don't know what
these are. These are like salted honey roasted nuts. And this is, um, a white plastic bag. Almonds
suck donkey dick. Okay. What are these? These are hazelnuts. Organs or riot? Oh my, all right, fine.
I'll do human organs. Stupid. Who, why, why does this even? Here you go. Uh, brain is A. S. Brain is S.
Otherwise, how would we have Fortnite without brain? It'd be impossible. If we didn't have brains,
there would be no, there would be no Twitch. There'd be no Fortnite. There'd be no driving
cars. There'd be no drivable cars. It's the most important organ. Without kidneys, we couldn't
drink our gamer fuel and play fucking Fortnite. And this is the dumbest tier list I think I've
ever seen. Lungs. You know, how would we be able to breathe in and rage when we get headshot from
across the map in Fortnite? If somebody builds and we're like, fuck you, how'd we be able to do that?
Without a, what the fuck is that? Without a second brain, without brain stem, we wouldn't be able to,
what is that? Without a heart. Heart, no, let's be real. What is this? The liver. Liver, I think,
would be higher up than, liver would be here. Intestines. Meh. Stomach, we need stomach to eat.
S. Uh, I don't, I don't know, is this bladder? Bladder and kidneys need to be together. Yeah,
I just made a person. This is a new organ, new organ. Pog. Imagine they discover a new organ.
This is a brand somehow. Science has discovered a new organ in the human body. Like, they never knew
it was there. They did? Well, here's the thing though. We have an appendix, but nobody knows
what the fuck it's used for. For all, seriously, for all we know, appendixes just like turn
like metal into fucking gold. How would we even know? We don't even know what it does.
They do know what it does. I thought they don't. I thought it was just a fucking thing that's there
for no reason. It was for grass and leaves and for turning metal into gold coins. We know what
appendixes are for now. It's there to explode. It's just, that's what it does. There's an organ
in your, there's a new organ in your nose. Is there? What's it called? The snipometer?
Nose two. Gooey gooey. All right, I'm fucking out of here. I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see,
me and Natalix are going to do co-op. That's the plan, unless like that goes all fucking wrong. I
gotta, my computer needs some serious work. Well, that was fun. I actually did have kind of fun
playing Watch Dogs while we, you know, we had, we were just chilling, talking. I'll see you tomorrow.
Round, actually, you know what? Tomorrow, I think starting around 4 p.m. Pacific.
Co-oping with somebody. Gotta, we gotta move some times around. I think we'll get burpee today,
too. What the fuck? So I'll see you tomorrow. Somewhere around 4 p.m. Pacific time. And then
on Halloween night, gonna be playing some more scary VR games. Got some fun stuff going on.
So that was Watch Dogs. And we can all just pretend that that, we can just burn that out of our brain
for a little while. Uh, here come the subs that subbed this stream. There were a lot of, there
were a lot of community subs. There's a lot of money today, too. We got raided by Ludwig, who,
I mean that was a huge raid. It was 15,000 people. If you stuck around from Ludwig,
thanks a lot. He's a really good dude. I would, I would follow that boy. Play Five Nights at
Bugleberry's. But yeah, we had a lot, there was like five $50 donations in bits today. And then
there was a hundred dollar, there was like three or four hundred bucks in bits today, so thanks guys.
That's a lot of fucking money to be giving somebody on the internet. You're not explaining
the cashews. Uh, they're the meat of the nut family. And I don't like it. Hey, Ludwig subbed!
I just saw it. They're the meat of the nut family. They're very earthy, very meaty. They get a very
deep flavor. Layers of Fear 2? I, hey, hold on, I have a question. Is Layers of, I heard Layers of
Fear 2 wasn't that good. It is? I heard it was like kind of not as good as the first one. Play it,
play it, play it. Both are bad. I thought Layers of Fear 1 was pretty good. I mean, we got some,
we got one of the most iconic video clips of the whole stream ever. I can't believe that was like
in my first, wasn't that like in the first few months that I even started streaming on Twitch?
It was. He peaked at his fucking debut. I did not peak at my debut. We haven't peaked yet. Don't
worry. You'll know when we peak because it might happen in 2021. Everything that I planned on doing
in 2020 had to get pushed to 2021. So 2021 is going to be loaded with something crazy every
probably two or three months because it just has to be because it's been, everything's been dumped
and delayed. Why do I have a fucking headache now? I have this like wicked bad headache right now
from, what is it from? From Watch Dogs? Did I get my brain hacked? All right, I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Have a wonderful rest of your night. Take care guys. See you tomorrow and good night.