Meltdown. Battle of Chistan Cliffs, Pakistan. One in the chamber.
Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here with One in the Chamber, just said the name of the game mode.
This is going to be a live commentary of me messing around on One in the Chamber, which if you don't know what this is,
well this is Call of Duty Black Ops 2, where you only get one bullet, kind of like the golden gun in 007.
One shot kill. If you kill somebody, you get your bullet back. And you get three lives.
So, let's...come here you son of a bitch!
You can also knife people as well. As you just...
Damn it!
Alright, I gotta be careful here. I only got one life. I'm on my final life.
I'm gonna get smoked. I'm gonna get smoked.
There's a guy right here. Get out of my face!
Come on, I got this guy right here. There's a dude right here. A dude right here in this door.
Come here you. Come here you.
What?!
Oh, he...
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Where they at? Where are they?
He's right here.
I'm scared!
Oh, get...
No! No!
Oh, that guy just scared the absolute crap out of me. He just like jumped in the air like...
And I missed. Ah, I should have aimed down sights.
Damn it!
Carrier. Location classified.
One in the Chamber.
Let's do it again.
Got my golden gun.
Four, three, two, one, go!
Who...
Who wants it? Who wants it? There's a guy right here.
It's this guy.
Oh!
What?! No!
There's a guy behind me!
What?!
Yeah!
Alright, gotta get my bearings here.
Get out of my face!
Excuse me, sir.
I'm gonna get you.
I got you!
I got you! I told you I was gonna get you!
Watch that UAV. Watch that UAV.
Behind me.
Yeah!
Oh, this guy.
You wanna play a knife fight?
You wanna play?
You wanna go for a knife?
No!
Oh, I saw that guy.
If I was a split second earlier.
It's alright.
That's only one death.
I'm good.
It's so nerve-racking.
This guy up here.
Be careful.
Don't make any noise.
What?
Oh!
Get it!
Where's he?
Come here.
He's right here.
Where's the son of a bitch?
Why is this guy?
Did he die?
Oh, now I really am scared.
No!
Freak out!
That guy got behind me.
Damn it!
Alright, I'm in like the...
I think I'm in like the leaderboard here.
If I can just stay alive.
Yeah, there's only one or two guys left.
Come on.
Let me pull this win out.
Where's this guy?
Where's this asshole?
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
He doesn't have a shot.
Can I end it right here?
Oh!
That's a question.
That's a real question at hand.
He's coming around.
Oh, no.
He's coming back.
Oh, this is so scary.
No!
He missed.
Yeah!
Oh!
Murder...
Oh, I forgot my name was Murder She Wrote.
If anybody knows what that is, Murder She Wrote was an old TV show in the 80s.
My grandmother used to watch it.
Oh, look at this knife right here.
Look at this.
Oh, side step!
Apparently, I knifed his back.
Or...
I don't even know what I just knifed.
That was weird.
All right.
One more.
One more run.
Let's do it.
One more time.
All right.
Let's do a repeat last time.
Let me get top frag like a boss.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Let's go up top.
Get in here.
Anybody?
What does that noise even mean?
That thing scares the...
What?
That didn't make any sense at all.
I knifed that guy right in his teeth.
Oh, we got a guy coming up right here.
What?
No!
That's not fair.
It's not fair.
I shot that guy in his wrist.
Boink!
I got him.
How did I get that guy?
Holy God.
I didn't even hit that guy.
I shot like 10 feet to that guy's right.
Behind me.
I'm on my last life here.
I've got to be real careful.
I can't screw around.
Up top this way.
Watch that UAV.
There's a guy right here.
See ya.
Anybody else?
Check that UAV.
Yo!
Oh, I air knifed him.
One guy over here as well.
Come here, you.
He doesn't know where I am.
What?
Ready?
Watch this.
Super knife!
Oh, it's all about the knife.
It's all about the knife.
Oh, I would've won it.
I would've won it right there.
Damn.
Oh well, well.
This mode is a lot of fun.
If you don't know how to do this if you have Black Ops 2, you go to party games.
And that was me that died right there, by the way.
You go to party games and it's one in the chamber.
So thank you guys so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all soon.
And of course, take care everybody.
Murder, she wrote.