I feel alive. Oh hey look, it's you again. How you doing? How's everybody? Has my brain healed?
Um yes, but no. Because I had a annoying headache yesterday and you get headaches.
Uh it sort of, it sort of like turns you, I remember I told you it turns you off for a little
while. So I feel all right. I feel fine and I rested up a little bit. But there's like a,
there's a notch up here that's like flicked off. It's hard to explain, but I feel I'm good to go.
If you got like seven notches in your brain that have to be turned on at all times,
one of them is like reading, one of them is like a arithmetic, one of them is like
arguments and debates, and the other one is playing a video game. That one's probably
turned off. I can read just fine. I'll prove it to you. Resident Evil 2. No, I just, I made
that up. I just, I got that from memory. I need, I need like a piece of material I haven't
seen yet. Uh what, at the bottom there. Capcom coal limited 1998. I'm fine. Go.
Oh shit, I have to tweet that. Let me get a quick tweet. You know, I don't think I even
tweeted last night, did I? No, I didn't. What kind of fucking streamer am I?
And I know that I have, uh, you can automatically have Twitter when you go live,
just send an automatic tweet. But I don't, I don't want to do that. I think you can do
that. You can set that up. But when you do that, doesn't it just, German 95 is now playing
Resident Evil 2 on the site twitch.tv. No, I'd rather write, like on my own, like RE2
coming at you, right? And then give the website link. But hope you guys are having
a good day today. We're going to pick up exactly where we left off. No, I didn't do
anything else after the stream. I kind of turned it off and just went right downstairs
and hung out. RE2 coming, yeah you can't, I can't do that with an automated system.
And if I can, then, oh fuck, I didn't know I could. Uh, let's adjust some audio here. And why
don't, hey! Why don't I bring the villain hair back, you know what I mean? That's too bright,
this is too bright. I should, I need to be like in a different spot. Okay, there we go.
Still light outside, but it won't be for long. Put on the sunglasses. No, I'm all right,
I'm all right. If I need to, I got, I have like an old pair of shitty gunner optics that I
threw in the trash. And then I went, ah, I probably shouldn't have thrown those in the trash,
because those were expensive. Those are expensive pieces of yellow glass.
So I took them out of the trash and I put it back on the table and I wiped them clean
with a little bit of, with a little bit of, uh, Lysol. I got a beard. No, it's called lazy
and annoyed, so I haven't shaved. Uh, he's using hair tonic. Hair tonic. Anywho, this
should be good. I'm going to drop the volume just a bit though, because I don't, I feel like it's
overpowering my little baby voice that's coming out here. Um, can I? Oh, these are unlock? I
thought this was chapter select. All right, eat this. That'll hold them. Uh, a new model
for the Matilda. Okay, bonuses. What's this? I don't want to see them all, but actually,
yeah, these things are fucking scary. It's a pretty good game. Yep, let's go.
Exactly where we were. I'm going to move this over here because Jeremy's face should not be
there, right? Jeremy's face needs to be somewhere else. All right, we're good. We're good. Let's
fucking go. Let me just check my fucking twitch ability, because remember I told you, like,
reading comprehension off, light detection on, smell off, FPS twitch shooting detection.
Uh oh, might have a problem. Might have a problem. Uh, so where are we? Let's see. I'm excited
for Resident Evil 2. So what's the, remind me the last thing we did, because I don't remember,
because memory, memory, memory has been turned off. That's a blue herb. I got a save point.
Engage the bionic boomers, please, sir. FPS shooting detection functioning at 75%.
Yeah, I have to go into the reserves for this one. I'm gonna bring the red jewel because
I want to, and I think it'll do me some good. Store that. Do I have any heals at all?
I have the one big one. I got one big heal, and I'm afraid to use it because it's the only
one I have. I have so many little toys now. The crank, I got the diamond key,
I got the car key, I have the box. Let me go out back to the garage.
Because there were cars out here. Wasn't there? Like, should I go look at the cars? Let's take a
look. Uh, car number is 7439. So, oh shit, did I just unlock the door? Uh oh. Oh wait, no, no,
hold on. What, it's, what's going on on the bottom there? Why are there little prongs that
are going, that are sticking in and sticking out? Do all the prongs need to be up? Prong one
and two. Look at prong two comes up. Probably some fucking puzzle. All right, uh, box electronic
parts. This is, I need two of these or not. Uh, a small electronic part. It sure is right there,
isn't it? Do I have to examine this cube too? So it's four prongs, a custom part for a power
panel. Yeah, I gotta, I gotta, I gotta like start to write down shit. You know what I mean?
I need a notebook that I can just write information down and save always. Okay,
let's just take a look and see what's in these things. We've got some gunpowder,
uh, a lot of bullets and how many of those am I going to destroy before it becomes, uh,
worthwhile? The magazine ammo. That's magnum ammo, isn't it? Electrical part. All right, let's
combine some shit, put some stuff in the storage. Shotgun shells. Uh, do I make more
shotgun shells or fucking boarded windows? I have too many items that I don't know what to do with.
Um, how about we have to have to put some of these away. We just do. I'll have to come back
and get them. How about let's make some more shotgun shells because you can never have too
many of these. Let's put the co, put the cocky. No, keep the cocky. Uh, store the
magnum bullets. The wooden boards. I'm still just gonna have the red jewel. Maybe just
get rid of it for now. I got the fancy looking key. Oh, combine the key now. All
right, let's go, let's take a, let's go back to the garage. My favorite game. Resident
Evil 2 inventory simulator. Yeah. It's kind of part of the fun though. I'm not gonna lie.
The last couple days, like yesterday and then today, it's been like kind of part of the fun.
So I need to go to, I mean, generator room is right here. Parking garage. So how the fuck do
I get down here? Straight and then down. I'm just getting back to the parking garage. Those
shotgun shells? No. You know what? I'm gonna board these windows up. Right? I mean like,
why not? I want, yeah, I want to be safe. All right. So this is gonna take us out here
and then we're gonna bring them right into the parking garage. I'm going to open up
car 7-4-2-7-2. Straight ahead. Oh, wait, it was a shotgun? What the fuck are the dogs doing
over here? Oh, no. Shit. Assholes. This is a loud fucking game. You know what I mean?
I gotta turn that down. Okay. We're looking for a car. Looking for, beep the, maybe beep the thing
here. What car was it? This white one right here? Which one of these cars is open? Is he
wearing a shower cap? Uh, no. No, he's not wearing a shower cap, I can assure you.
Oh, it's gun stock. Custom part for them. It's a shower cap. What am I, like a fucking
lunch lady? A custom part of the Matilda that allows the gun to fire three rounds
per pull of the trigger. This is, that's interesting looking. All right. Did it just
get bigger? No, it just now takes up two inventory spaces. Oh, god damn it. Whatever.
Okay. Well, I don't need the car on key anymore. I got my upgrade. It was foolish.
That's a terrible looking gun. Yeah, it does look like it was made out of like
nerf guns and Legos. Now what the hell does it look like? This looks like,
yeah, it looks like a nerf gun, like a nerf attachment. So that's that. So that we,
now what else do I have? I got the diamond key. Let me see. What? Back at like the main hall.
What was the shit that was over here? Some of these are diamond key. That's heart. Club.
Where's that diamond? Diamond queen, you know? Follow that queen. Follow that queen. Follow
that diamond queen. Second floor. Electronically locked door. Diamond door. There's a diamond
door over here. Five community subs from Great Canadian. Fuck club. Thank you. Thank
you so much, Great Canadian. Just consistently constantly adding to your tally. Thank you.
So, what the heck? A crank handle slot. I could go all the way. I could go over here.
Yeah, I'm gonna bring the crank back down to this area down here on the second floor.
I think that would be prudent, right? I think that would be prudent. Let's go get it. I
really don't want to use this, but I might have to. So I'm gonna keep the key just because
I get overzealous. So, you know. Let's do what we need to do. Oh, there's a diamond door right
here. Let's check it out. Oh, no. This is the shooting range. Where are you? Oh,
where is this person? Where is the person? All right, let's go. I'm just gonna blow
your head off. Didn't blow your head off. Unbelievable. Fuck me. What a waste of a
shotgun bullet. Can I like stomp on the head? Does film? I think that's it. That's it. I got
film, though. This is in dead space. Why not? Oh, fuck. Well, it's okay. What's that noise?
I, why, you should be able to run over and just step there on their head.
Come on, man. Step your game up. How do I get by you? You stupid. I can't really. You
just did that to me. I can't fucking believe it. I was gonna do that to you. You're not
supposed to be able to do that to me. I was gonna do it to you. Why didn't I shoot? I,
because I, I don't, I, I, she, the animation started when she grabbed me by the fucking
chesticles. She like pulled me in with by both chest areas. I started biting me.
Dammit. I just took so much unnecessary damage. All right, so I need to go, but I did get
some film. So I need to go back to turn around up the stairs. You go up here and
break room. Okay. So I'm gonna go back this way and then this way. He's doing the end,
end of the stream voice. What? End of the stream voice. No, no, it feels bad. Stream
over. The stream is not over. Would just get started. Okay. But I need to bring
this thing. I'm going to store this thing because I don't want to use it.
That's my rare Lucario Amiibo. I can't even take it out of the box. Okay.
So we're going to go store the film too for now. I need tool. Store the herb.
I'll keep this one. This is a full health restore. So this, we're going to get back
to the crank. I'm going to keep the key and I'm going to board up a couple of windows.
That sounds good to me. Say how many saves? It saves 24 different saves from
compulsive panic saving. I can't imagine. How many saves do you get in hardcore?
Do you get like eight the whole game? Well, that would make me just absolutely livid.
I can get the, no, let me get the electrical part too. You get 20
through the whole game. That sucks. I'm going to hold on to that electrical part.
Now I know I'm going to be probably rage quitting. I'm going to rage quit the game,
right? In like 20 minutes because I'm going to need that. So I'm going to hold on to it.
I got plenty of slots for all this shit. All right, let's go. Heal? No, no, I'm not
going to heal yet. I got a full heal in my inventory. I can get one more bite taken out
of me before I have to heal. So, okay. Down and then here. So we're going to go down
out of this way. Can I get in there? Can I get in? Is there a way for me to get over
there? I'm going to board up some of these windows. How did you not get fucking staggered by that?
What? Oh my, this is just a fucking choose your own adventure game where you turn the wrong
corner and you die. That was, you could go down this into the forest or you could turn right
and go down the, the in between the rocks into the alleyway. And I picked the alleyway.
Oh, well see what happened was there were three zombies there and you died.
Oh, looks like I'm going to have to go into the forest. Why didn't I heal? Because it was,
it was a waste. It was a waste of a heal because I'm not going to get hit by any of these guys.
Now check this out. I have, no, I made sure I remember this one. Okay, let's do it again.
Let me go down the choose your own adventure hallway, which, which would do it. This door,
right? Hello, how are you? That's one down and then there's you. What the? Put it in.
I don't know what's on the wall. Oh, fuck off. You, what the guy with the fucking
internal organs coming out is still alive. The guy in like the fucking pile of bodies.
All right, we're good. That brings us to exactly where I wanted. Did I forget about him? He
should have been dead. There's no, nobody can survive what he went through. All right,
so we got to go back into the main hall and then wait, where's the fire escape?
I'm actually right next to it. So we're going to go up that way. Oh God damn it. Just leave
me alone. Why is everybody spamming P? Yeah, what's going on? Why are people writing P?
You can't go that way, but it doesn't matter. I need to just go right there. There it is.
Okay. Is there, that's exactly where I want to be. Let's crank it up. I don't know the
secret meme. I don't know any memes. I don't know what any, half the time, I don't know
what the hell everybody's talking about. Let's take it slow. There's one of those dolls.
I do hear noises. Chiropractor. That is a heart door. I don't have the key for it.
So this will take me down or up. I guess I could go to the roof maybe from here. Where
does this go? More boards. I'll just take them. Free stuff. Magnum ammo. No, that's just regular
handgun ammo. Left eye. Middle eye. Right eye. Flashbang. Change equipped sub weapon.
Is there a way I can, I'll get, there we go. I didn't know if I could put anything else there.
All right. E storage room or balcony. Let's go to the E storage room. I feel like
there's going to be a safe point in here because this is a storage room. Absolutely not. Blue,
where the fuck are you? Where is he? Where? Okay, what's this? A large gear. It's huge.
A rusty old gear. It looks like it belongs to some machine or another.
It's, that's two slots. That's unfair. Two slots. I can't get out of this door either.
Bitch. I don't even know why I shouldn't be shooting this guy. So I gotta go out,
I can go out here. No, I can't. Is every door locked up? I got the gear. Whatever the hell
that's for. There were two guys in here. Let's check the balcony. Running out of room. It's
completely gone now. But I got the gear for, what is it? What is that for? Oh, this is done.
All right, so I have one more spot. I could go down from here. I'm good playing ammo. Let's go
down. There's not going to be a monster just sitting right here, is there? Get rid of your
handgun. No. And why does Leon have a little BB gun? He's shooting little rocks out of this
gun. Not even bullets. Water? Okay, well, obviously missing a pipe. Is there a pipe lying
around here? Do I gotta come back later and get the pipe? Water valve lever. I'm gonna have to
come back here and stick a pipe up there. All right, so this is a door I have not. Let me
know. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me check. Because I haven't been out here right now. I'm
like on the roof. I can go that way. Hold on. So many branching paths in this story.
Well, this would not be here for no reason, so. I guess I could combine. I'm gonna combine.
Is it poise? There's a poison monster here. There's gonna be a poison enemy.
It's gonna happen. It's gonna be like, fucking acid's gonna go on my face and then it's gonna
be the first tutorial. This is a thousand people over there. Oh, there's like five people.
Is that just one very, very, very.
Shit. Okay, quickly, quickly. What's in here? Gunpowder. What else is in here? Quickly,
before they get up. Anything else? Nothing else like right here? Quickly, hurry up. What's in
here? What's in here? What's in here? What's in here? Ooh, a key. Club. Oh, thank you.
That's okay. There's a, this box right here. Red herb. Combine. Please. I got two super duper
ultra heals now. Okay, so I also now have too many amiibos and I'm not gonna use them.
This is a full RGB heal. I have three of them now and I'm not gonna use them. What's
going on with the happy, happy face? Combine GRB with H with B. I can't, I'm sorry guys,
I can't, I have no idea what that person just asked me to do. Combine these two and I get
an ultra super mega herb. No, I don't. I get like a super. No, that's not true. Don't F-U-C-K
with me. You know what I mean? Don't F-U-C-K with me. This knife sucks. I'm just gonna stab
somebody with it. I'll keep one of these large gear. I'm gonna store it for now. I don't
know. I don't know where any of this stuff is supposed to go. I still have doors to open.
I gotta open up all the doors that need a key so I can just throw them in the trash.
You're gonna get the boulder punching ability. I can't wait for that. Somebody said he missed
X, he mixed, he missed Y, he missed Z. No, I didn't. Not yet. I just wanted to get in here.
I'm going back. I'm turning back. No, I'm going back upstairs. So we've got,
do I have any? I do. Three flashbangs, the two keys. I got a couple of slots now. All right,
good. Thank God this is a little point that they could save for me. Yeah, I missed Z's all the
time. Going to bed at 4 a.m. These two are gonna get up so let me go out. Water valve,
that can go up around here. Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me. Left to right. What the
fuck did that do? Well, I don't know what that did. Panic. You don't actually come all the way back
up here. All right, so wait, would that do anything with this? Oh! So what does that,
what did that do for me? There's no item in here or nothing in here? How could there not
be something in here? How could there not be something in there? That's bullshit. Jesus Christ.
Okay, um, so like Jermarumble Rorschach is now facing me. Fucking Dick Tracy is coming after me
now. What am I supposed, is this an edit, what do I do about this guy? Does he just fucking chase
you around? No, of course they had to add like a nemesis. Oh my fucking God. Should I shoot
him? Okay, well he's there, so that's why they put the auto save here. Okay, because
fucking Slender Man and Dick Tracy had a baby. All right, I gotta bait him out here.
Jesus Christ! Come on, climb up the broken ladder! Okay, hold on, wait for him. I'm just
gonna run by him and then run by the helicopter. All right, does he have any
stretchy powers or anything? He doesn't have any stretchy powers, right? Where the fuck am I?
Ah, straight through the waiting room? Because this is open, right? Lose him in the main hall.
He does, he does not follow in here. All right, I lost him. Yeah, this is like a sanctuary. He
can't come in here. Okay, so I have the club key. I got some jewels. I have some healing.
You're safe in a horror game. I don't think I'm fairly safe right now. I could flashbang him.
That puts us here. There are some, there's a club key over here in the records room. What's with
my hair? What's wrong with my hair? You can't even like see it. I mean, it might be, maybe
it's a little messy today. So that's this way. Up here and then the first club key is
down, and then run. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What? What? What? I just uh,
open the door. Damn it. What the fuck? It's that guy. No, it's not. Fucking idiot, I am.
Get away. Please. I thought it was the fucking guy with the hat on. Oh my god. That would
have been the worst, that would have been one of the scariest things ever in a video game.
it still kind of was and I'm gonna die I need to heal no but this is my I this
is my Lucario god damn it that's a jack okay so the records room is blocked off
currently by a heart door that was the worst thing that was the worst thing
ever like I'll give you a point I'll give resident evil two points they did
the guy breaks through the fucking door and you think it's the guy okay
I think I need to go back in here but what am I supposed to do about this what
do I he's made out of stone I can't even hurt him he's made out of like fucking cement all
right wait a minute I need to what do I have I I need to I got the what is
this it's a jack I got a jack this up that's in the second floor I need to
look at the map to see where are the keys are that's a locked door heart door
anymore clubs that are in the vicinity no but I do have the jack which the
jack I'm gonna throw up the jack is for here so that's second floor I'm on
the first floor right now I gotta go into the operations room through the
safety deposit area through operations room over the corner there up the
stairs and then into the library ready one two three you go I go the right way
well he's so fucking fast isn't he was a secret exit was a secret exit oh go
go get away from what the hell are you doing over here okay so stop
fucking haunted house I gotta run by him straight around I'm going into the
dark room I got the film I got the film around throw it so holy shit I'm like
two this two lickers I'm too wound up I swear to God please please don't kill
me here please don't kill me please don't kill me please don't kill me
please just get in the dark room get in the dark room they can't get you
in here it's a safe zone fucking God can't come in the dark room right but
he can't come in here and like crash my photo creating party oh my god oh
ooh third floor locker DCM DCM nice I thought I had a fucking headache
yesterday I was like this is not gonna be like calm he's just out
there he's just waiting outside for me I fucking can't even possibly
comprehend I'm gonna have to I don't know I gotta get like flame bullets I
don't know what to do but we're gonna have to deal with it so I need to
bring out another one of these because I'm almost I'm very hurt I need
it I have I could do some more gunpowder just still I don't need it
right now let's reload the guns I'm not I don't think I'm gonna run into
any of these keys so let me see let's reload the guns try giving him a you
need directional audio I almost I almost cried okay I need to go I'm not
I'm at caution I can take another hit so the jack goes so now I'm in here
good get out here and go up the stairs get out go up the stairs and
then figure it out from there are there any more things I need to take I don't
think so although how the fuck am I supposed to know oh here we go up the
door up the stairs crotcher thanks for five community subs thank you so
much no that was just you guys okay then I got to go I need to get to
the I need to get here I don't know if that's the no I went the wrong way
didn't I I gotta go I can't go around can I I gotta go back to the main hall
I think through the shower room through the lounge I just gotta go I gotta go
all the way around wait this was a third floor no that's the it's a
third-floor locker which is right there I'm gonna go up there and get
that locker yeah there it is what was it D it was like DCM or something
right is it somebody coming behind me is he like here no he's not stop
uh guild here I'll thanks for the five community subs thank you so much five
community subs just Magnum ammo that's all right I guess okay left left no
that's got I got an achievement for that I don't know what it was I got I
got an actual achievement for doing that so I have the jack right did I
not bring the jacket my me know it's there so the jack needs to go
there I gotta take care of these monsters how am I gonna how the hell am
I gonna do this I have to let go all right just like four zombies down here
we're gonna make the shots count that's not doing it that's not doing
it Jack it up all right what did that do watch out watch out so he's
behind you somebody's behind you right now what the fuck is in here when it
what when is it where what door is he in when it where is he I don't
don't know where the fuck he is is he right is he right next to me fucking
daffy duck motherfucker get away from me I need to try to get I need to eat
he's his slow ass needs to get up the ladder okay it's just as simple as one
two three you just get down and then what what am I supposed to do with
this oh my god this is so the one all the way to the left has to be pulled out
so this one pull on there's gonna be like a secret passage right here hurry
up Leon you don't have any time out of time out of time okay so now I
should be able to get through this wait are you still looking at me oh
god you dick what hold on okay is this gonna work is that gonna do
anything I don't know where he's going upstairs one two three four five know
that I can I can oh my mouth okay I can run across that I just unhinged my
mouth like a snake about to eat a goat I got it I did it I can go in this
door where the fuck am I going okay east storage room clock tower all the
clock that's gotta go to the clock tower you know what I fuck with
I don't care okay I'm so he doesn't still follow you across the whole
fucking game how long does he do this for that's a dead end here ladies and
gentlemen where I supposed to go oh I need the stupid I need the handcrank
what the hell is this gun a large gunpowder and a rocket raccoon okay
through the clock tower locked door I don't have any goddamn keys what's the
what's the over under that it's a 50-50 chance that it's a it's a
fucking diamond or club oh man unbelievable this game is fucking
terrible no no but no no no this game is fucking great but oh the the stress
and anxiety he heard that no this is great this is this is fucking
terrible in like the best possible way he's not gonna be right behind
here right I'm still I'm getting residual shock waves from when he
first opened that door and I what is that thing all right I need the
double I need the big wheel to turn that what's this repair plan okay police
station west side clock tower due to the high cultural value of the bell
I'm calling a specialist and to make the repairs we'll go over the details
once they're on the scene but in the meantime I'll take steps to secure the
bell since the yoke is threatening to break okay well this is also another
thing that I have right what the fuck was that noise that I just heard I
can't get over there that's another electrical part I think that's how I
get it right I have to turn the clock tower and everything all right
straight left right east storage room it better be I better be able to open
that or it'll be I'll be livid go no no no no not right now not right
now not right now I need to heal right now where's my heel no
unnecessary I could just no just do it go okay this is gonna bring me down I
need a box room we gotta go back down to the first floor this'll all the way
down all the way bathroom break room just board it up you know just board
it up I have a bunch of them wait interrogation room opposite I haven't
been in here I need a safe point right now it's a heart room and this is a
this is a club there's also a locker I am OOM box I need a jewel don't touch
anything he's coming he's coming he's coming he's coming he's coming he's
coming he's coming okay I gotta get out I gotta I gotta get to a safe point
okay well I wish she wasn't here oh okay when confronted by an officer he
tried to escape by attack acting confused but was arrested a note he
had him was confiscated it's not like everyone doesn't know who it is but
it's Justin Hanson age 39 or city resident I'm frozen right now right
6 to 11 this is a safe key for second floor waiting room 6 to 11 there's a
safe gunpowder just that would do it all right all three of them and that
would give me some Magnum ammo I don't need the club anymore the key
these pick up box and then I gotta get the fuck out of here so I need a I
need a plan out up the stairs again which will bring me to here and then
out here through fire escape fire escape into watchman's room into break
room no what's right there roof where am I right now
fuck am I second floor right how do I know how do I get over there I think I
have to I have to go that way I have to go from the fire escape right
because there's no way I can get over here from here unless like this
doesn't leave me there I don't think because that goes down to the the
garage and then this would go up to the roof but then I could go down
okay so I'm gonna go up to roof no shit I think I have to go up the
stairs anyway so we're gonna go out we're gonna go upstairs so left
right upstairs how did this turn into the best horror game I've ever played I
don't but I need a fucking plan observation room I need to do I can't
open this door I don't have the part this is fucking unbelievable I have to
like go that's just a reflection he did make a hole so press room and
then to the main hall I'm just gonna give you a heart attack it
I have to go for it through the hole he made in the wall
there down and then into the main hall get the box the box I got I got I got
the box right this thing with the jewel in the middle I didn't miss
anything right I got to just go for it okay and the left press room
sometimes you gotta just fucking sprint and if you take a hit you take a hit
left straight right go leads us to out right left and then right into the main
hall oh what is that noise and why is he in the main hall it's a sanctuary
you're not allowed here no what damn it I just need to save the game both
of them I just want to save my game Marvin Marvin do not Marvin I'm sorry
I'll stop this lieutenant promise I just just want to go over there and save
and I gotta take the jewel out this must be stopped just in case I fuck
myself over somehow it's saved right here I gotta get in that box his
weakness is his hat shoot it off that was funny that was very funny but I
can't I don't have any comedy in me that was very funny okay I'm gonna go
in the box now does it freeze it when I go in the box at the time is
frozen right red jewel large gear he's not allowed to move in the stop time
we're gonna make another herb combine this with a red I gotta do another big
one red and then blue maybe not though that's a full heel I don't know
if it's I don't it's not necessary I need to save these for like poison
um that's a waste because this is already a full hill no I'm holding
on to the blue ones that would be a mistake it just would okay combine this
with this what's in it stars badge a special badge for our PD special force
sufficient stars right okay there's ammo I'm not gonna use it and hold on
to that key I need the large gear let's make I'm gonna make some I'm
gonna make some of this gunpowder I think just cuz I have a can right
might as well just do it get a shitload of it okay so I have to like look at
that let me bring this back out so I think that's good power plant power
panel part no no I don't think I need this yet make sure our inventory is
not stupid looking let's move this over here this over here and I can be
up there that's fine you get to heal this way that down there miscellaneous
items will go down here like quest items oh I'm throwing up okay back to
where I was before one two three okay now what the hell is this clip USB
dongle key that's for the armory which is on the second floor there it is
there's the PC I can get the lightning hawk if I open this door with the
dongle but I need to I'll go I'll go get it in a minute I just I need to go
to the clock tower gearbox am I gonna what else do I need to bring up here
is that gonna do it all it's also this room too yeah I gotta get rid of this
guy is that like the joke of this whole game here is like you're gonna do the
he doesn't know thing and I he's just gonna follow me for the rest of the
fucking game can I can I shoot him I shot his hat off hold on Jeremy I can
hurt him I can go into punch him better get moving does this do
anything okay all right all right all right okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
he goes down on the knee um I'm gonna go to the linen room I'm gonna get the
gun we're gonna do this first I need this shit so we're gonna go second
floor library lounge linen room out of linen room stars offers armory gun
out shower room no out down right in here we go up wait I have a diamond
key still yes I do and I have the dongle yes let's go so that bring us
into there and then we go down to the lounge into the linen room across this
way he's back he's back already this motherfucker is back already took this
guy 15 goddamn seconds to come back to life what's in here there is gun
powder and a portable safe okay what's in here shit there's too many
things to do it's there's too many things to do because that goes back up
that's the security deposit room and then that's there's a I think there's a
pouch down in there okay so I gotta make my way down there so fucking
cool okay so what's the plan right now the plan right now is to go out
of the linen room into stars office PC dongle oh motherfucker no way are
there any more right he's right right now face fuck face I gotta go in that
just put it in the fucking computer already that's a loud noise oh fuck
he put right he probably heard it I can hear him running I can hear her
running he's fucking sprinting how you doing in that drab old station
hanging in there against all irons me I just got back from a date with a
hot chick but you can guess what yeah Europe is amazing one month is in no
way enough to even scratch the surface maybe I'll extend my vacation for another
six months Barry don't even think of joining me I wouldn't want to make all
the cute girls cry yeah so you just leave the babes to me Jill if Claire
tries to contact you please let her know I'm okay just give me that's why
I don't lose it give me the gun so this is the Magnum nothing else in
here right okay got it do I need the key don't you take the key out
is there another computer I don't have any room that's it okay no I do
because of this is this keys done so grab dongle key leave the office take
up right through the shower down and then back to the main hall no wait no
back up to the clock tower I can get up to the okay perfect perfect plan
out of the armory right through the showers up the stairs around the West
storage into the clock tower I think I think one shot can blast his face and
then I was in this room because I'm never come that was the is he just
opening doors he's gonna find the right one eventually and I'm gonna be
in it he's right outside is there a crouch is there another door that he's
coming in from here why the fuck this turn into like amnesia he's gonna
check in here right to the shower there's a liquor up top I can't run
anything else the shower I don't know where he is I'm gonna open the door and
he's gonna be right in front of me all right I'm ready he's holding the
liquor on his shoulder he may as well be for the love of God out right
straight game time okay oh straight through I don't have a lock I don't
have to dial lock for this so I have to go out and then up what was that I
don't know what that laugh was straight and then out I don't have the dial
lock I missed it I made a joke instead well I'd sell somebody's cheating so
I'm cheating I'm gonna open it cap I'm just gonna cheat who cares are
there any liquors in here tell me yes or no straight ahead it's all
just video game sound effects it's not real out that door this is it's
not real it's just video game sound effects it's not gonna hurt you it's
just it's designed to sound like this out and then bang a left and then go
up the stairs I think now I'm gonna go down the stairs because there's a
save point right there up down the stairs into the dark room and okay
sounds good to me out left downstairs okay time to go you idiot
you're in my way get it get it get it oh my god this game is incredible
ten out of ten acting okay I'm gonna store the magnum for now I have in
here ammo oh I'm gonna make some more bullets maybe no I'm gonna save them
this game is making my back hurt so I have this tool I I'm not gonna do
I don't think I'm gonna do this dongle key I'll store it I have a
heal I have my knife I'm not even fucking using thank God I have save did
I have any more film I thought I did apparently not imagine this game had a
VR I'm fucking bearable so now because I ran downstairs I can go into the
locker terminals and put the next key on I have a save point right here so
I can just save scumbag if I get hit in the face by like a wrench or
something and then take the stuff out to or whatever they are I have to look
at them I'm ready let's go put the other key on and go get the other
items that are in this room left left okay what you say many the same
idiot holy shit what a mistake what a mistake this it's all
liquors just all right so don't run down that hall I'm gonna throw like
a flashbang and get in yeah save scum you can call you call me a scumbag if
you want I'm going for it that was this one right here right yeah guys
sorry you can call me a scumbag we're gonna go out there get out there
flashbang this thing will die hey hey ugly oh he's like peeking in the
room hey call me a scumbag all you want get shit and I'm sick of dealing
with you you're done I'm gonna make you dead forever how am I gonna get out of
here I don't have any more flashbang clip I'm stuck here how am I gonna get
up he's too big to fit in this room I'm safe in here okay so what do we
need to do we need 203 that's a pouch get it fucking velociraptors shut up
good playing this on hardcore can you imagine running into this guy for
the first time on hardcore and maybe you didn't save for like stream still
we good imagine not saving for like two hours and then fighting then if you're
seeing that guy for the first time that'd be living hell all right we got
two two oh eight there's nothing there's one of what there's one oh
three right one oh eight one oh three is knife just open it and they look
like a little flash of internet issues I think we're good so just like
replace this one I'm gonna slash somebody with that one what is it
equipped that this one's currently equipped I need to heal in a minute
here I got the pouch I'm good to go everything's loaded now what on earth
am I going to do now I'm gonna have to try to get back to the dark room I
think how audio isn't synced there's my what my mouse go would mean
should be I'm gonna I'll piss my pants if I if I don't do this right now so
I'm gonna pee for the first time I'll be right back pee break I needed that I
need that just glass of water and just whoo hello welcome back they need a
box of wine no I'm glad I'm done having it I don't have any wine
tonight you know are you kidding me that would just slow me down I would
probably die like five times to this guy so I have I gotta get back up let
me see back to the dark room because I want to save it because I just got
those items and then that part of the mission is completed for me so out
around the corner left I don't have I don't have any flashbangs I could
run straight just try to run straight through and through the
office it might be worth it cuz look at this yeah I didn't I ain't gonna get
out here they're both just sitting here waiting to open the door like
what the fuck I miss variety Jerma not normie Jerma what what does that mean
we just played the dreamcast like two days three days ago the heck all
right here we go no for normie Jerma here we go damn fuck I gotta kill
them I have to shoot them this is not gonna happen they have to die
they're blocking my path the door just shoot him did I hit him dead are they
both dead okay what I think what I gotta get through that door here we go
one two three bag of left in the main hall let's get a save perfect
pretty good driving directions I think yeah okay we are back in the main
hall with fully loaded weapons saved game now we need to go up what was that
safe the safe is right here isn't it what was that combination sick I got
it yeah I'm gonna get this safe so we're gonna come up main hall into
this room up here open the safe with six twelve nine or something right and
then from there fire escape up no I can't go up from the fire escape can I
from there up from roof through to clock tower I'm ready it's time oh I
can't wait to this motherfucker leaves me alone flies around this time
frozen when I use a safe if it's not it's gonna be bad like you see
kitty get in here so it was left what was it have it right here somewhere
left six right two left eleven so six two eleven six two eleven one two three
four five six one two one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven open up film canister no custom park for the Matilda that
reduces recoil and muzzle rise by redirecting propellant gas up and
away from the barrel all right the tilled is pretty decked out right
now he put me can't believe that worked when you use a safe you they're not
telling me the numbers to go to they're telling me how many notches in a
direction all right so out through here just all the way down through the
whole hall up the stairs through the storage room let's just get off the
stairs first here we go here bang a left go through I thought he couldn't
get in these rooms what oh you asshole somebody's gave five community subs I'll
stop panicking just shoot him down to one knee there we go let's go
somebody just write envy aim like Nevada what do you what and a would
like what you know now we're picking a states out now first it was like oh
and a oh you now we're picking actual states out oh like oh it's you
he's got real like fucking like ma we're gonna pick the state now what are the
what are the top players in Nevada what's their aim like he's down on
one knee just get out that takes us up to where I want to be I have all
the items I need right all right here we are we should go get East storage
room now and then there's the hall into the clock tower you better not
I knew it it was him no it's not him look just like him I don't care I don't
care I just need to get to where I need to go I don't care I don't care
okay he's there's nowhere for him to break through a wall right there's no
walls he can break through get it in there turn it do whatever you need to
do turn and then I need to do it here too right right here doesn't fit
I guess I can I just to go up then where did that drop down there's like a
ladder thing that came down here where the hell did that drop down is my
just dumb there it is well all right so here's this thing small gear well
now that I guess that makes sense of what it put the large gear in here
turn that one what does that do I'm not entirely sure it looks like it's
running it's it's turn I've turned it on okay so now this goes in the other one
and I should open and drop it down maybe so now that works well if I was
gonna attract somebody over here that's how you do it
there's the electrical part I now both of these I was told to get them both
I don't have to write a report on this you break through that door I
swear to God should be two there's an electronic part two of them okay
obtained electronic part obtained power plant part and now I can go back to the
parking garage and give me a second I need the other one so how what's the
fastest way I could go through here through and then down which would
bring me here put me in the library and then plus two for Leon did he make
he made a funny joke yeah I guess he did so that would put it would put me
down here I need to go from there to this library down that brings to the
West office and I need to go down from there's only one way to go and that's
is not through the main hall can I go down from the main hall or is it
easier for me to go through like for instance from down here so like from
over here I'm pretty sure I can get down there yeah I can get them from
here right maybe I can't do it so I'm doing some tuber commentary looks at
yeah okay because yeah that's what I thought so down here so I gotta go I'm
gonna get just get back to the main hall I've done what needs to be done
so down the stairs into the library and then out to the main hall let's
go for it I'm so nervous right now because just no no I gotta go this way
I need to go East storage room down down down okay East storage room it is
and then is there okay there is the break room is right there all right
straight left straight left I'm just gonna go out through there here we go
he's probably gonna be right here just load up the guns just in case
something happens straight all the way down left right I wish I could peek
don't break through a door don't break through a door don't break through a
door don't break out through like a door straight through don't break out
through this door and down down brings me here down again fire escape down
here is here and then I'm going out to the main hall so from here I can
yeah no I can't I can't I need because this is gonna bring me here
and this is gonna press room bathroom break room I can I guess I could do it
I could do press room through but this but there's so many aliens over there
we'll do that fuck it so press room so left straight left straight left okay
I'm so compulsive right now around the corner hello all right I made it I
made it I'm good okay we're safe oh I got my storage unit in here I got the
safe point right there now it's time to finish this give me the power panel
parts I have a heel I'm all right just reload I need some more handgun ammo I
might just make it yeah I'm gonna make it why not just sitting in here
okay any more items I don't think so maybe the dongle don't think so so
I got the two pieces I got the two power pieces game is saved now let's do
another part of the map stream let's go I need to go down so I
have to go from here this is not gonna do anything for me is it can I
go down from there would you look at that would you look at that I made
it here now where did these go I this two of them there's the parking
garage there's the card reader there's the electronic door panel so I have to
go all the way down back into the jail get that guy's key card and then leave
through the parking garage it seems like a lot is that guy like I can't go
underground right he can't he he'll get stuck second floor basement yeah
it's through here because remember that isn't the panels all the way down
here and then he has like that reader no okay it's down here there it is
all right get key I gotta get out of here okay put in the power devices put
them both in and then we have to play one of these games so it's got to
light up here here it's gotta come from here not these already lit up
no it's gotta go across down from here it can only come from that side so it
has to come from this side so the question is how to get this okay
there's one I gotta get the other one to do the same thing there's time to
run toilet Ben's memo the station's swimming with monsters even here I can
hear their cries but it's not the zombies I'm afraid of code name tyrant
the ultimate bioweapon developed by those bastards in the utmost secrecy to
think that there might be the thing might be wandering around here chances
are they've ordered to wipe out the witnesses that would be our friend
first aid spray good and this is gonna activate some kind of event so I
could be ready to run the hell out of here and read the card and get
the fuck out of the parking garage cut off the interview interview
transcript we just heard it so parking garage key card take it and escape the
parking garage what are they after this is where it gets fucking hairy probably
because these are all gonna open right they're gonna open turn it off turn it
off what the fuck am I do I have a grenade
get the fuck down lady which way is it this way how's my health I'm okay
oh shit come on Ada kill him get rid of this guy he's not gone he's gonna
come back and it's the same shit over again this is getting old saving your
ass that's twice I didn't realize you were keeping score look this isn't a
game see he's alive he's unkillable we didn't see him die on screen it
means he's still alive yeah and this I was hoping you could explain what's
on it maybe after I hear it ridiculous oh okay I need to see him dead no guys
that's not how this works what else we got I need I'm okay with healing we
reload I need shotgun bullets I need an upgrade to the shotgun it's just a
standard shotgun that's crazy oh at least I can have like a side
relief I didn't have to worry about that guy following me everywhere I go
for the last hour how do I talk to Ada Ada Ada can we talk is that the intel
you needed being outside just feel so good Ben didn't come through well what
exactly are you looking for more info on the people responsible for this mess
what about you trying to save the world consultation told lieutenant
Bren I'd bring help good luck getting that is the gun store is he gonna be in
here all right this stage he's probably gone where the hell are we going roads
out going through that gun shop looks like the only way yes yes come on who
are you and what are you doing here shotgun what a mess no I don't think
he's in here he stops you at the door we're supposed to be looking
investigating sure I will that's a grenade I'll take a grenade that is a
long barrel I did just mention shotgun upgrade and how I haven't found one and
now here's a shotgun upgrade custom part of the w8 70 that ups its max
capacity to 8 less spread makes each shot more powerful well that sounds
pretty good to me and it gives you eight shots good nice okay fancy
can I take up my flashlight only five rounds in the gun store no I'm not gonna
hurt you I said don't move who are you I'm just passing through I'm gonna ask
you to lower that weapon I kill you on turn around go right back out the
way you came in I think your daughter needs help sir tell me how to deal
with my daughter what are you doing here no wait step aside we need to
terminate her before she turns terminate it's my fucking daughter she's gonna bite
him in the back just let them be by the time I realized something that was
wrong the entire city was infested with
zombies I told you to stay put no original voice actor either but the
fuck you're supposed to know something how did this happen huh and by the
way what are you doing here by his fucking ear is gonna rip off see I'm
gonna I'll get away from the for the touching moment here you know it's one
thing to keep the truth from me but why him no it didn't happen I want to
oh wait oh fuck okay whoever's behind it oops helping people like them that's
why I joined the force I thought I was gonna get bitten eaten behind the door
my mission is to take down umbrella's entire operation we may not make it
out whatever it takes to save this city count me in I did that was
poorly timed with me do I thought it was gonna be him screaming because she
like we muffled screams from behind the door like he like she ate him
all right listen okay what are you doing here I wasn't trying to make that like
a joke I'm going to look I'm going off the original game in the original
game that happened to that guy so there was no daughter it was just the
guy I thought that was gonna happen again this is supposed to be remake
of the second game that games older than most of chat yeah it is now it is
and that's why I'm looking for a net Birkin she's the one at umbrella
responsible for unleashing the virus I'm going to bring her down okay I
thought there was a I thought she just walked off the edge I was looking
over at Chad Nick I glanced over here based on what you said the sewer
seems fitting well said after you gee thanks now let's go we have just gone
all the way down can't imagine a real scientist being down here come on
second sewers are run by the city how could they have a facility without
the authorities knowing I why do I have to take the lead the whole time
first impressions of the game I think it's fucking great no sorry about the
upward I meant to say Jesus that an earthquake it's gonna be that guy the
tyrants gonna be back that's why you check every corner I told you if you
don't die on screen you don't actually die
okay well that was a I think that was sick trash moving somebody dumped some
trash down here I told you I played the first second game you know you
have to say it like that now I played the first second one okay I got heels
I got two full heels I wonder if it's worth taking up the lightning hawk for
this because I only have 11 bullets for maybe although I kind of feel
like I'll need these at some point later ancient Greek German what are you
talking about no no don't even take it let's go I can kill this thing and not
take one point of damage so is Ada still with me what did she end up
leaving it's gonna like snowball down the whole hallway isn't it well
there's nothing else here Ada coming all right you you're filling me with
ammo she's still coming right again no chance you're stuck with me to the end
all right here comes that was a safe checkpoint so this is definitely
something going on right now it is I got two full heels you sure this is
the right way nine shotgun shots unfortunately she's gonna wave by and
I'm gonna have to fight this thing wait there
oh I'm controlling it now holy shit watch apparently can I shoot behind me
or something shoot it yep load up does it hurt you chew on that
oh yeah son of a bitch got two grenades looking good so I've made
kind of stuck down here what the hell was just get up here hey thanks for the
ladder was that the I was kind of expecting a fight there I guess it was
just a fun interesting thing to see on the virus and turned people into
monsters not reptiles their point I'm just impressed you made it in one
who flushed a grenade in the toilet somebody trying to pull like a prank
where's he down in the underground lab so let me get this straight
umbrella sells monsters like that to who our military somebody oh it's not
looking that's fine that's just a stain and Annette is who makes the
viruses scary as that alligator was Annette is far more dangerous to me
all right so we've made it underground so what do you want me to do now Ada is
this where when this is where part waves when we're gonna part waves the
safe point two in succession no box though interestingly enough new
character yourself she's who we're looking for my grain doing yeah my
good need to dispose of it just a little tired from it I'm good that's not
gonna happen I'm warning you doctor oh yeah hey she did cause like a little
fire didn't expect that from a scientist yeah I'm gonna burn this it
didn't do anything Leon forget about me just go you could have stopped her
before she gets away I play as Ada we character switching here we are
character switching now I'm right outside the facility in pursuit of a
net it's not on her it must be in the nest my guns once it's in hand I'll
call for extraction time to play as Ada what do you have run Annette but
you can't can I just steal all the stuff on my character because I mean
for real nine bullets in a nine millimeter you're essentially this is
the worst weapon I could possibly have right now so this is broken messed up
let me just check around because down here is a lead ladder but wait wait
wait wait wait wait go up I don't want to miss bullets especially at
this stage in the game here nothing right nothing okay we're just gonna go
up the stairs just throw a blanket on him he'll be fine no a price
scanner compare prices use the EMF visualizer track wiring and hack
electronic equipment hack electronic equipment okay it's secret weapon time
well it says on my app this is $15 less a target you turn it off turn
off am I not supposed to climb that well I was supposed to turn it on why
would I want to turn it on wouldn't want to climb up there oh I get it
I can do both I get it I thought I could just climb up with it off
candy from a baby what you're don't burn yourself wait hackable object oh no
listen just bugs no there's a buyer there we're gonna get hackable not
hackable hackable okay now what we are in there's only one way to go
straight but there's probably stuff there is something September inspection I
already put in request last week but we absolutely must have a replacement ID
wristband we need one to gain access to certain areas of the main facility
in other words me and my crew can't get to the places we need to in order
to do our job so I don't want to hear anyone accusing us of slacking
off so we got to get an ID wristband to get in certain rooms I
think certain doors nothing else here I'm not even gonna fight this guy why
would I checking for items I can't hackable door it is sir you're
annoying all right okay it looks like I can go through here let's explore a
little bit handgun ammo good who are you and I must say what are you
doing here where's the box I want to play find the string get me oh no it's
good can use it now okay definitely pick that shit up what else is over
here flashbang all right I have activated the lift you just did my god
you want me at the same time really damn it okay back out here okay let's
go you know wiggling does nothing it doesn't matter I have to just try she
is this lady's got what she what she's looking just disappeared she wants to
move all what's everything where did she go what the hell that's a new that's
music that's music that that's he's back I told you he was back I told
you he was back I told you he was back we didn't see him die hack it fuck
is this thing get Ada oh oh no bad oh god why does he have to be back again
deep why do you have to be back again I have to like hack shit I need to go
down and follow the stupid string to I don't know where over here does it
work pull it just pull it pull it pull it pull it pull it pull it pull
it pull it pull it go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
oh my god Ada your aim sucks all right ventilation fan where's the box turn it
on hurry he's gonna get up come on Ada okay anything in this room to pick up
and he's healing or it's shotguns or machine guns or ammo or anything no I
have to just go like I knew he was back I don't have any heels do I I
have a flashlight how am I supposed to get anything done around here thank
god there's a save point follow the box to what the hell hold on so I need to
this door needs to be opened so the box I'm gonna pee my pants again like
as if I had done it already so this is connected to here with the new
wristband that's just arrived we can finally begin our survey of the
demolition area as to the report from the other day about the
incinerator it's nothing really probably just a large piece of left of
trash I'll go take a look myself after I wrap up the report wristband we can
finally do our survey the incinerator so can I turn this on that's
activating this that's the incinerator all right I know what I have to do I
have to incinerate the timer I have to burn them I'm gonna get them in
there and close the door and burn them so let me take a look I got to
lock them in there that's an ID wristband
gonna burn you live now you'll never get your filthy hands on the G I'm not
the only one after it you realize that and you won't die alone where's
the box to do open oh fuck I gotta do them all I gotta pee okay I'm sorry
when I get like nervous and I'm playing a game and I just sit by to pee
just develops it just does so uh same I gotta just go in there and it's not
that big of a deal just go in pick up some items first though so I have to
do the incinerator unlock the door puzzle which I was wondering I knew the
wood I've what the hell these were here for oh it's Chuck E cheese how
many of those do you actually have to destroy before you get something
let's go ahead and get it open which it was which one was it how the hell did
I open this last time how the how the heck did I even know how the heck did
I open that it's up here I was standing right in front of it wasn't I
yeah I was my wave is a lever right hello he asks and it doesn't look in
Chad I'm looking seven okay this time I'm gonna be ready I'll get them all
I've got what five or six so far here we go skip one two three go what's wrong
with my brain what why can I not do this I just have what isn't it right
there and then you go from there to here where is it going what the fuck am
I doing I did every puzzle in like 12 seconds and I can now I'm stuck on the
fucking find the strings one I'm gonna lose again yeah I lost again Leon oh
what so I'm looking for orange and it's not orange you know I mean like
I from my brain is like oh the one it's orange but a yellow whatever it
it's not it's the one that's the blue still but it has the yellow in
it I know about the inspection let's go don't listen to your brain I know I
shouldn't all right come and lock the door again then I'm gonna play shoots
and ladders with myself it's not there you'll never get your filthy hands on
the G I'm not the only one after it you realize that and you won't die
alone I'm going to shoot this lady let's get the hard one first all
right let me out bitch knows what she's doing now I got the ID card but although
scary guys still around why did I say that say what oh shit okay so this is
where I need to go your ID is authorized until October not gonna
all right through this way watch out for scary scary man
tyrant oh wait I need this though don't I I took I took I took me longer to
put that in and do some of the puzzles in the game come on Ada let's
go shot in the face he shot me right in my mouth
the game is over you lost tell me is your husband still alive or did you
kill him so you could take credit for G interesting theory you don't walk
great a sample from the nest over my dead body you try to stamp me out
hurts what are you supposed to leave it in until you get to a doctor now I
got to stand up as Leon all right I've got my HP recovery jacket on now I
have to fight tyrant again Ada hack complete find Ada so I just got to go
through up there and the incinerator sounds like Ada where are you what do I
have to help caution I'm okay I got plenty heels well I need the wristband
don't I just to go through the exact same thing that she just did now this
is broken I don't have a hackable weapon all right she activated this
again okay I do not just show I need that save okay good perfect so I just
realized something I'm getting to like the end of the game right like I've got
probably maybe like an hour or so hour or two left in the game right no
about two yeah like about two hours probably maybe I have didn't poison
right toxins I have where's the toxic enemy interesting all right let's
get it saved we're good I don't think I have to take anything not no I'm not I
know I'm not the end of the game right now but I'm just saying as as of how
far I progressed I'm surprised has been it's either about to happen or it
just might not happen no toxic enemy so far in the sandbag dick heads
gonna be down here all right well bullets good just progress through
watch out the pleasant snow monsters are gonna come from the ocean and
already tell tyrants gonna show up two paths we got left or right I guess I'm
gonna just look left first and I'm gonna sneeze and I'm sorry I can't I've
got up and there's something here oh shit I thought that was a monster right
here and everybody in the laundry don't think so I knew I'd see you
eventually it's hunk I found hunk USS digital video cassette sure I'll take
it is that actually hunk all right we up here I can bang a right I think
let's go right treatment facility is locked let's try this door over here
electronic part well okay well I guess I'm gonna have to kill this shit shit I
kind of need to go over there don't I unless there's no plug the socket I'm
gonna go down there but that's where I came from put it back in I need to go
across this fuck to lock door to go this way eventually I'll probably find
another one of those plugs that's a knife no I want to know grenade knife
take the knife out items new coming down here lower waterway sure just
exploded when he went in the water death one of those valves wasn't that
I need one of these earlier didn't I yeah I need okay those t-valves maybe
I'll get one to be able to keep it and bring back the hell was that did
you see that there's something right here what is that that's a new enemy
type I don't know what it is it's a blob what is that shit bye see you
later I want nothing to do with you toxic no this is where Ada was right
no cable car interesting umbrella corporation logo she took search not
completed yeah well there's a giant monster over there I can't search over
there yet more okay I desperately needed those this is where Ada fell
and that was water down there so I'm gonna drain the water where'd she go
what this is another door combination copy of emails there are alarms going
off all over nest I don't know what's going on but I can hear gunfire and I
can't reach my section chief we're trapped please send help as soon as
possible the situation here is dire nest has been contaminated with the
virus it's unbelievable failsa system didn't activate at all is this the
work of outsiders I can't imagine who else could be but why mayor and Kim
are dead I can't stop coughing why won't you answer me you it was all you it was
you all along yep okay let's take a look anything else in here that's worth
taking it was me no me I don't like the sound of that she is Ada I'm
coming Ada save Ada bullets in here all right is there a safe point
anywhere yes there is thank God do you like when I look at you I mean what he
wasn't right you like when I look over here and look at you look you right
in the eye yeah no sewers pamphlet greetings from the CEO thank you for
your interest in Knights construction company we believe that just because
our work is subterranean doesn't mean our designs have to be subpar or
refined between yay yay we meet all field someday okay sewer company cool
nice sick cool sick nice sick dude put it in let's see all the company secrets
there is again oh the rats are in it now so that's got the eyeball on his
shoulder virus how interesting rats spread it we can watch more TV shows on
here more found footage horror movies okay video player typewriter item box
let's just open up the item box I don't have a green herb I'm gonna hold on to
that just delete this keep this on me keep the grenades on me get rid of the
tape save it again put away that VHS tape they're not gonna use it
anymore so I can go out here but what's this nice and bad thank
goodness treatment monitor room garbage room treatment pool room let's
just keep going I don't know if I can go down here yet this needs to be
drained no access to this area unless this takes me to across this way
treatment full room let's go although let me check another safe which I
don't have a combination for and a guy that's gonna get up that's it you're
wasting your bullets I got I got plenty of bullets looking good I got plenty of
bullets what are the kids say I got bullets for days right fucking kids say
oh he was dead ah fuck another guy nothing over there nice water and I
got this gate open now which will take me back I need to keep what oh that's
the t-bar let's check back here the grenade rewind to safe what what is
going on here I was every freaking out where do you want to go back every
what what what what what what happened where the code was on the safe what
did you know was it no it wasn't what what the fuck are you guys
two twelve eight a piece of wood custom part that stabilized the gun allowing
to be fired and reloaded in one smooth action oh yeah not cheating at all well
sometimes you have to chat Chad I don't hold a chat cheating is not the
same as regular cheating it's not I'm gonna save it I don't want to do
that shit again if this was regular cheating I would say yeah you're
probably right but we're not talking about regular cheating I'm gonna call
it helpful guidance helpful chat guidance you know you like what I love
it all right got the improved shotgun these guys should still be on the
ground where do I go if I get down yeah yeah yeah to the water here yeah
they're up still on the ground good water has already looked down there
there's nothing this just brings me back out so I gotta go I don't have
that item yet damn it do I have to go that way or can I just stay there eat a
great yeah are you actually still alive no it's dead all right so now this is
taking me back around I don't this is the lift the dot no I got a win I
got what about to go here I have no idea I haven't gotten any new items
that I can bring me where where have I not been no no no no I want to zoom in
I don't want to change oh my god okay workers break room it's locked locked
door is there an electronic part there's something I can do over here
treatment pool room Ada has to be saved mmm I really just kind of don't
know I walked around a circle and I didn't get any other useful items
a lower there's the t-bar slot I didn't get it can I go in here maybe I gotta
go through this way maybe let me just see if that's possible is that
possible German sounds like he's getting a little rowdy I mean rowdy
this brings me down to here which means let's see if I can go through
this then I might be able to walk it this way this motherfuckers back to
shit yeah I agree this way this is open and then is there a way I yeah down
here all right I got it damn it I need a I where is that thing all right I'm
gonna go back up because this is where I was before this is where I
ended up last time so there we go bingo right there all right straight
down there all right I got it but let me save it maybe I know I shouldn't even
why save it I just walked in a circle why would I need to save it well there's
another full heel if I a full poison heel I'm so inclined to do it there's
the plunger well now I know where that goes ID wristband required more
documents delivery receipt the item below has been delivered to the
location specified in your order heat resistant safe times one combination is
written on the side of the safe and shock please remember to erase it
before you use it it's okay because chat guidance mode helped and now I got
it today what I got it anyways now I can go plug that thing in and use it
in the two places I know where it needs to be used we're gonna go to
the first one which is out here and then around and down down down down
I'm gonna save it Chad is spoiling the game I wouldn't call that a spoiler but
I guess it's kind of hard to spoil a game that technically released like 18
years ago and that I've seen like I knew what that was I'm gonna store
these I guess I could do another maybe just another red and green no I'm not
I don't I don't even know I'll just hoard them for a little while that
leaves me with time to go out and now I need to go I want to go to that first
one the original one all right electronic part any three of these well
that one has to go over here is it gonna do anything when I do this like
will it activate no I'm gonna take it cuz that can I can use that in
the bridge pretty sure the rook and knight are on the same wall and the
bishop and Queen aren't next to each other the Queen and rook were opposite
each other too that's how I feel the rook and knight are on the same wall so
when I get all these pieces they all have to be okay I see what you're
doing I see what you're doing here yeah yeah I need to get the other one
though so I'm just gonna put how am I gonna get the other one I'm gonna
take this one with me because I can use it unlocking the you area door I
lost the thing that tells you how to unlock the door in that last mad dash
but if everyone remembers which plug goes where please be a pal and share by
posting info on the board find the plugs so three of them are here I
need the I gotta go back to that how the hell am I gonna get that I got
a lock on like a shortcut or something whatever let me go back to where
the valve was t-bar handle slot is down there's so much going on in this
game is there anything else like no I'm just gonna go from here I want to go
wait that's the door that's locked all right the ladies and gentlemen I'm gonna
find my way to that t-pose which is down here someone's probably gonna get
the fuck up hope not alien slug is still gonna be here which is not good
for me but I need to get to right here I think do I have any like
flashbangs on me I don't know if I can't make it across here though
distracting him that's what I wanted
turn it yeah I wanted to stuff the grenade his mouth so I could get in
here I didn't get rid of it right I still have it yeah so what is in
here shotgun sick lift I can turn on work room you can't you come on you
whoo awesome roll of film gonna need it later he's gonna get up he's not all
right new roll of film which I could eventually get back to the main
building fuck now what is this bleeding plug socket whoo wait wait wait don't
take it yet what I got them all right this one's a lot now I got all now I
can turn around and go back down cuz this is yeah that's I got them all this
can't be opened I'm gonna go back up the elevator there out of the way
possible time let's figure it out let's dead oh shit you got a knife I
stabbed him like an hour ago all right let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go take me across into the monitor room I would I
need five pieces or three bring it over here one two three four five eight six
but how many do I have now missing one more shit I am missing I'm missing two
more one two three four I need two more broken the night are on the same
wall and the bishop and Queen aren't next to each other damn it there's
more can go ahead and film I got the tool for the other twisty and then it's
probably gonna be done no I have enough I'm gonna have enough I have enough
what do you mean I have enough enough what the hell am I talking about do
have any regular gunpowder no okay looking good thankfully I've not been
hit so I haven't had to use any of the heels that's a good that's a
good thing so where is that other valve there it's right here right so
this is back down again into this area and then down there okay so let's
just fucking go this is boring give us mr. X well I mean you can't you
kind of need that was like a full hour straight of just intense blood
pounding pressure you kind of need like a you got to come down a little you
gotta have a put the chess pieces in the slot minigame for like 40 minutes
after that I don't mind the slower kind of portion here kinds kind of needs
it like I was gonna die for an hour straight I need to go this used to
be a mr. extreme so I'm gonna go that way wait so this is the stick it in a
soda I want to get like a coke like a sprite most last time anybody here
purchased like a 12-pack of sprite I don't know if it's ever happened but
I want a sprite right now about ice key okay there's a locked door I know
that I can use this on what about a piece some kind of peace I guess I got a
let's look down here first right where it's kind of dying what are those what
the hell is that thing no no no more enemy types it's like face huggers now
oh my god this is getting worse where's Ada oh Ada come on I gotta get
you out of here Ada no not one of you oh come on step with
the knife knife oh no fine here great I'm wasting
no not I need them these exact shit waste a great what the fuck okay now
I gotta heal now I gotta heal you're gonna show your eyes all right why
you don't show me your eyes run by stab him I have a knife in the mouth
items and shit man I can't miss them yes I can just where what what the
hell oh my god get away from me is there anything over here what's that
fucking noise where am I in regards supplies storage room is where I am
right now combine them I need it anymore shotgun shells where the hell is that
guy mr. X he showed up to Ada okay it isn't like okay oh shit okay so I need
to get them both out of here right this three plug sockets in here so I
gotta do this in the right order apparently which sure we'll figure
that out grab from here whoo I can get that hold on asshole all right so let's
pull this out of here this is then drop down then I can blow his head up
you ain't getting up good so now I'm gonna grab the item whatever this is
what is this like a grenade launcher chemical flamethrower hold right
you're gonna fire the flamethrower the longer you torch a target the
bigger the flames you'll create can I open this yeah that's now open give me
these pieces so I can pick up this one three and then I gotta get back up
this one blue herb shit wasn't there three in here I just kind of locked
myself in here wasn't there one more up there am I still missing one no
matter what oops sorry that's closed this is closed now too did I just fuck
myself there's not one in there right I don't I don't think there is one in
there I'm just making sure how the fuck do I get out of this I just like
had it and I'm like looking around I like was on the way out too so
speaking of on the way out this is the way to get out of this so I need
I just like screwed myself so bad because now I can't leave this door is
open but this one's not oh I hate shit like this this shit drives me fucking
crazy because I have to get out of the door over here oh and I did it in
reverse and now I have no fucking idea I had pretty much had it done
and now oh I hate I hate shit like this with a passion like where's the
actual fucking exit do I actually have to do this again and drop down no yeah
I literally have no idea what's going on I'm not gonna lie like I have
absolutely not a single clue what's going on because now I can go this way
but I can't leave I have to ah and it's so dark too it just causing my
brain so many problems the way is the plug that I just plugged it in I
wish I could turn a light is there a light in this room I can turn on oh
the darkness is killing me it's I'm every the room is spinning around in
circles okay I have to go through god damn it I have to unlock this door
okay so to unlock this door I need this one because then that will let me
give the opportunity to I don't think this can this even open it okay so
now this door needs to be unlocked which where can I get that fucking plug
from so I can take this from here now and then open this is the heart this
is the struggle it's just spatial awareness and darkness is just it kills
me so I have to take this one out and put this one but this one that
will close this door oh I can't I can't do it I literally can't do it
my brain is too small just click on the fucking screen and show me where to go
I like I my brain literally cannot do this puzzle I'm no I'm okay you guys
are gonna guide me because seriously like the darkness in the in the in
the plugs and spatial awareness is it's actually impossible for me to do
I am brain dead so here's what we're gonna do am I go direct me
straight straight left okay left okay take King grab no take other piece okay
take King taking put King in this slot fucking with me now yes please yes
yes no does anybody else know what's going on now take this one yes this
is the one I'm taking now straight through this door take this one take
Queen yes okay I got both Queen and King now put Queen in here okay now put
King in here yep okay now take take now um not take Queen take Queen
Queen take go through take King and then leave room I got them all that was
not a funny joke I thought it was a pretty funny absolutely not a joke I'm
really that stupid I can't do it I can't do puzzles like that they're
impossible for my brain see how fast it did like that did that in like eight
seconds no gates closing dark I can't no no way I was pretending it
was a joke so now I gotta get the hell out of here and I have to go
god I gotta go back through the I thought that just had bottom Weasley I
was like why does it say Weasley I can now open that door I still want to get
hit by the stupid thing all the blobs are dead besides this one right not
this one the one in the middle wait what the fuck did it go there was
one it was just right here did I make it out of there are you serious
nothing else right just get the hell out of this wait did I try dropped
it down my climb over this fuck did I make it over here no no no that's
where it was okay this give me the fuck out of like another dark soul
swamp
ruin you god let's go do another puzzle they got all the pieces what
difficulty is he playing on normal this is just normal I'm gonna go back
up right what would the laugh laugh at me you're you played it on normal too
didn't you on your first playthrough ever finally how we doing on box space
I got this chemical flamethrower no regular I guess I could make a super
heal not really necessary at the moment so I'm gonna store this
because I don't think I need it right now so now I have one two so let's
just let's take a look let's take them all out what does it say pretty sure the
rook and knight are on the same wall okay so this pawn I know where the pawn
goes on goes in here and night goes in here so it says the pretty sure the
rook and knight are on the same wall the bishop and the Queen aren't next to
each other Queen and rook were opposite each other so let's do it
pretty sure the rook and knight are the same wall let's put the rook on
here just just to have it on there this is a rook just put it in that leaves
one space here bishop and Queen are not extras of the Queen and rook were
opposite each other so Queen and rook opposite so the Queen has to go on
this side that's the Queen Queen the bishop and the Queen are not next
to each other okay so that means the this is not the
bishop this is the Kings the Kings over here and the bishop is over here
and then maybe but let me walk around in a fucking circle doing the open the
gate puzzle for like 18 minutes all right let me save it I'm gonna do it
on everything so shotgun no not a whole lot of bullets I'm gonna keep
the chemical flamethrower I'm gonna store the key for now no wait isn't
there there's a lock somewhere over here it's right here is that key
for key to a section of the sewers sewer no entry zone I don't know if
that's a waste of my time to go all the way back here water injection
chamber or workers break room because right now I'm down here and that means
I have to go up I don't know if that's worth going to get if there's
like five shotgun shells there I'm gonna be pretty pissed off because
that means I have to go out all the way through here again and then up
there why not up there up here like socket I guess I don't care now I don't
think I care to be honest no I want that all right heel of not that great
on the ammo department at the moment I got two good full heels it is
important it is it is in this all right fine I'll do it let's just go
open it this five shotgun shells in here you're all in big trouble so
that means I have to go out here and then down or maybe can I go up from
here you need a plug doesn't matter which plug here just just a plug so I
need to this door stays open I need the rook okay so I have the rook I'm
just gonna go open the door now the question is what's the fastest way to
get to that door here's the upper waterway I have to get I have to
get here so I have to cross this right see if I can get there from here
maybe it should go up up from here and then I have to walk all the way
around oh that sucks that's so far hold on let me see see if I can
reliably get there fast from this way if I go left I go from there I
wonder let's see I don't want to use a bunch of bullets I don't waste a
of bullets can I get there from here no I can't get there from here shit so
confirm this with my brain here because I want to make sure I'm not
gonna do something stupid if I go down here and then to the lift that takes
me up to here and then from here to here right I just want to make sure
that that's what's happening it is called the workers rift don't get up
all right open that door I hope this is worth it or you're gonna see me go
like this I'm gonna make a fist and I'm gonna squeeze it so then that opens
the door up here all right I hope it's worth it
shit from all right let me in all right we got gunpowder not impressed so
far empty nine handgun bullets a jazz festival flyer SZF that's the password
to somebody's locker okay interesting so what's this what the hell where am I
going special weapons case underground stairs what the fuck I can't open
that this is this is the bottom all right this leads all the way back up to
the police station yeah weird so now the whole thing is connected I guess
that wait this is the badge will fit in there I gotta get that badge then
all right so now I'm gonna go into here up still go upstairs what is that
an upgrade for don't forget the film I mean is it okay all right film USB
dongle oh shit what is that for wait hold on nice okay this thing's probably
already this goes back out to the main hall it still can be used
somewhere excellent so then now here's the main hall that's pretty cool all
right eight is probably dead well we we didn't need her anyways we're on our
own mission let me go open this shit up actually wait what about the film
as we go develop it saved all right dark room so I'm gonna go through
here and then bang right which will bring us to right there oh shit the
lickers I forgot no no no don't die here don't you die here don't you die
in here okay film hiding place with desks where are those desks like the
the offices yeah but I mean which one up here hidden well what's even hidden up
there cuz he talking about that that's quite that's a journey for me to go on
right now hold on if I go up from here I'm gonna get myself fucking killed
so I'm just gonna try I'm gonna go up the stairs from here and we'll go
to the stars office stars office straight through thing left wait
lickers I didn't how did I miss this hold on a second no I can't go so I
could go to the showers there are lickers all over the place here I'm
gonna walk through here and then through the door I know there's at
least one up here I've shot this thing ten times straight and it's on
the left is don't all right so where was that it was somebody's desk with
coffee on it let me take a look there's a stereo player and then a phone with
some pens phone with some pens on it okay right here wooden box a slightly
heavy wooden box all right that's all I got a piece of wood come on I can
open this red dot sight for the lightning hog a custom part for the
lightning fast aiming all right pretty cool oh so then from that's sick but
the other one is what the boom box I gotta get back out to the main hall
and then the first floor it was like down here right East office or press
room what did I just got more film oh what kind of wild goose chase is
putting me on this is like a treasure hunt I get the USB to go in the
computer I've got to go check the press room I got to watch out for the
liquor all right so I got back through back into the dark room or maybe not
yeah so I gotta go back to get to the main hall again it's gonna mean
keep keep searching the desk what there's like hidden prompts
everywhere or something I don't get it search desk search the desk again
there's nothing here missed desk one you just you baiting me all right I'm
gonna do the same thing it's gonna go down from here and we're gonna develop
this film so we just have to slowly make our way away from the liquor
through the shower I mean wrong way I'm just going just back down to the
USB USB USB I already got the lightning forgot that was mean don't
going down I already did it yeah I know I have I have it and then I'm gonna put
that in the secret room downstairs no I know what's going on I got it so then
let's just go just start running fuck it run out of time here downstairs
that'll bring me to first floor dark room develop this film how did that not
hit didn't even need to do it more film to develop my I'm gonna get more
like treasure pictures okay that it's just a that's it check desk so that's
good I got that now I gotta go out here I'm gonna go through the West
office back into the main hall we're gonna go to the press room yeah yeah I
think that's I think so yeah so left left straight all right check the
press room under the boom box and then from there I can just go right through
there and we'll see if I can find over the hell this thing is these stupid
enemies are just gonna be right here aren't they with a lickers here I
just don't know what I've killed everything comes back to life in this
game okay boombox boombox boombox boombox son of a bitch where is it boombox boombox
got it ooh fuel times 400 that's pretty great actually anything else in
here that's it right I got that's a lot of ammo that should take us now go
back up to the main hall down put the USB in there's no I can't there's
nothing else here there's no other I can't like I can't do it nothing there
all right Ada Wong is fucking dead she'll be fine I'm just gonna go bang
bang bang out back to the main hall down the stairs dongle let's go get
this secret item there's so much to do I'm surprised they were they were
able to fit this much even little secrets it's really really cool so I
have it in my inventory right I do I'm gonna come actually I'll do it right
now for the lightning Hawk in here so this is a laser scope with the
lightning Hawk nice okay let's go get another little piece of whatever it is
stop stop stop what show us the gun I will once I put the dongle in here
because then I'm gonna save and we'll continue okay nice what is it what I
was gonna say did I get baited here okay it's a pedal and break long barrel
and is that it those two clips no all right so I this is great custom part
for the lightning Hawk this ball barrel reduces recoil and it imparts
extra speed to bullets increasing damage so this thing is decked out now
it's two slots let's see it this is the kind of gun that you have to
actually be very careful I only have 11 bullets that's a last boss weapon if
it is you know if I've ever seen one this thing is now done goodbye all
right let me go save it combine this shit get things in a box wait no
I'm is there anything else I just know where this is so I wonder
German no what what's matter you look extra cute tonight hey thanks thank you
that's very nice yeah the flyer too right was like ZZSF or something all
right it's time to make something happen here I'm gonna I'm gonna load
this gun because I want to be okay seven out of four store it store it
store it store it maybe I should store the shotgun for now look at all these
blue herbs I gotta bring these back anyways um what do I do with these
herbs this is anti-poison I could combine three of them again but I'm
not sure it's even worth doing that it can't be used as it has become
can you do red and blue red and blue does like Constitution right what does
red and blue actually do for you so I've got two complete superheels red
and blue I'm gonna do red and blue I'm just I want to know what it does
okay so this is like a guard so it's a defense boost so I'm just gonna do
it again no no I'm gonna wait for a green I'll wait for a green to do
this I am so slightly ready to go let me save and we'll go back to what we
were doing which I honestly it was so long ago I don't remember what the
hell are you doing you know always add the green after idiot but I like
the way it looks in my inventory I like the way it looks in my inventory
there's also the other door that I need to open it's on the other side
of the plug-in down all right so well was it this way yes it was was
it that was it's an interesting shortcut though Ada is fucking dead no
she's not she's gonna be just fine she texted me she said lol spike
sticking out of leg help I said be there soon she said how soon with like
a kind of a slant like mmm said 30 minutes text it back can you stop at
McDonald's I'm like fucking hell yeah what do you want oh you're gonna stop
cool I'll take a number one and a large coke and in two large fries all
right man so where's the heel not heel all right I gotta go out here
this way plug in so it's the rook right what's in this room hopefully
something worth spending about the last 35 minutes doing it looks to be
well let's super bullets gunpowder gunpowder that's the only thing in this
room so not terrible I could make some more bullets with the miss
something what I miss in this room I don't see anything too bad that's not
spray I like those back up back through let's go take me back to where I was so
I can go save Ada do not attack me the slug monster is gonna be right here is
it alive I keep thinking these things are alive that one is but I don't need
to even go near it you get out of the way time for progress save the
game through the door I'm ready that guy wasn't a zombie imagine that poor
guy excellent it's just triple check okay so should I make more Magnum ammo
because what is um what is high grade and large gunpowder no that's how do I
make the mag in the memo you can't so this is just gonna be a bunch of
shotgun shells then which is actually probably better two yellows or
should I just make six well what six shotgun shells I feel like I need some
shotgun ammo and this is done so it'll be three shotgun shells wouldn't it be
six so just wait for another one to make another yellow okay these I am
kind of running low on ammo though so the do I need to bring one of
these with me does it even matter what is this I'm done with this this
is just done I'm not gonna regret not taking one of these whatever all right
destroy that the key is done let me take a couple I feel like this is
something coming up here you know something's coming up I might as well
just forward everything I'll take it I'll take it I'm not gonna take the
fuel though I'll take it mr. X would like to know your location what
about grenades mr. X would like to know I don't have any cool another blue herb
I should just go deposit it yeah just go deposit it into your bank you're
gonna need it good sorry left is the flamethrower so is this the anti mr. X
gun is that what people are saying here oh god damn it I have mr. X is
in chat wait wait wait wait wait wait I need to save it again oh god
damn it I found more healing items fucking stupid game forward all right
Ada I'm here do you have any blood left are you out of blood main power
room wait what about the what about the garage room damn it need the power
on first okay all right God damn it more healing items shit let me check
make sure I don't miss anything it's gonna be one of those switch flipping
minigames I'm pretty good at these powers back on if I'm able to make it
back I'm gonna say oh my bump into me body oh what the fuck am I supposed to
do um power what am I do shoot I have to make his hand hit something my my
chest hurts out where the fuck is it
where's the wall there's a one against a wall get out of the fire I thought he
was gonna go down how am I doing on help okay holy shit goodbye oh uh turn
it on hit him knock him off the table what the fuck it didn't go the
correct way what did I just take take them take them come on hit up so
I'm not even gonna you okay that's good it's good thing that happened
because I'm not gonna use any bullets I'm just gonna walk I'm gonna just smash
him I'm gonna save oh I can't save any bullets all right hit him do it do
it do it do it do it do it do it where is it hit up fuck you know what I
mean you know that yeah Jesus Christ crap I missed crap crap do I have to
shoot his eye okay watch out free up get out of the fucking fire oh crap get
to keep all my ammo guys I heard I heard somebody I heard somebody call me
a scumbag now I got you goodbye farewell it's been nice knowing you but you're
dead you're not dead why are you still alive here back the eye back of the
eye what am I hit I don't understand what's going on
why is he still alive I don't have to do it again I actually have to do
it again go down he's not down fuck no don't fall over here okay push him let's
do this bye-bye there I maybe I should redo it let's hope that's the last of
them no I'm good I'm good I'm good I just had it's fine I got plenty of
other ammo plus speaking of ammo there's some right here where the hell
this is magical handgun ammo okay let me take a look out of shotgun shells I
got some Magnum ammo my health is fine I made a little bridge for myself
and all right Ada you still alive did I grab the knife but there was no
knife but there's a safe now I'm in a little bit of trouble because no
shotgun ammo I have plenty heels I'm gonna have to conserve ammo here
somebody's get fit stormy to just get $50 stormy to thank you so much for 50
bucks 5,000 bits from stormy to streams been great so far lots of laughs
tonight question for you what would you do in a Resident Evil scenario you
gotta try you know I wouldn't use any I wouldn't use a gun because guns are
unreliable you need to have ammunition for a gun so instead of having like
ammo for a gun I would just get a baseball metal baseball bat I wouldn't
be dead we talking about a metal baseball bat and you just swing as
hard as you can for their heads it never runs out of ammo it will never
break and zombies are slow and stupid you just have to hit them as
hard as you can possibly swing double crow hop into the face they're not
gonna get up it's just not gonna happen not a knife no no no that's too small
or probably even a better weapon of choice would be a an or like a rowboat
or it's made it a solid wood it's got length and you can just or somebody
in the back of the fucking head that's probably the best melee weapon
you could probably have in a zombie apocalypse what about a spear no not
a spear spear that it's a point a rowing or it's a big flat spatula like
this big you don't have to aim very much you could really just just double
crow hop huge reach and crush skulls I would last and then I would go to a
grocery store I would just sit at the grocery store I would just take all the
Campbell's tomato soup and I would just that's what I would eat every
day I would live forever let's go what about a two by four two by four
is that's not big enough and it's not that strong either how would I
reach it on the shelves I haven't or either are you nice try to get worried
there for a second I can't get it out I don't know if I should just do it I
can't walk like this okay that's definitely in fact it's been there for
like an hour and a half I can do it myself just relax okay what is that
magical oil he's putting on so what do we do now get yourself out of here
well you still can I'm not just gonna leave you not like this you don't
understand the situation's worse than I thought you're not getting rid of me
that easy it was antiseptic that's my turn just get yourself in a work
keeping score grab my shoulder push it rookie just trying to help watch your
step but long story short we have to get to the nest anything that requires
resources is bad in a zombie apocalypse right beneath us and that let it slip
that's where the virus samples are you up for this I think I could fit in
my schedule come on we got work to do food is but food is necessary to
survive a shotgun shell is not necessary to survive if you don't you don't like
eat shotgun shells and by the way Campbell's tomato soup is a great weapon
nice where'd you get that you have a backpack with like 40 of them and you
can just take them out and just club people with them you can throw them
they're heavy as shit they weigh like they will take six and a half pounds
one can of Campbell's tomato soup it's got six and a half pounds of
tomato in there there's six and a half tomatoes inside of one can I need to
save the game let me carry you no that only make me feel worse I feel
pretty bad too come on Ada we both uh in dire
straights right now it's not just you how's the shoulder worse than it
looks what a pair both got one foot in the grave getting blinky here all
right her little tea card wrist watch will open the store right you would
think there would be something up there this may be a one-way ride so be
prepared are you prepared huh I just saved it so how are we doing on time
you know what I was thinking I can't wait for the FBI to raid Umbrella
headquarters and take those bastards to justice I agree but to be clear
you're not working in official capacity this is a federal case once we get the
g-virus I'm back on my own hey Leon trust me trust me honestly if I
didn't you'd probably be dead I thought I might need your help and I
was right if you can secure the g-virus I can make sure what happened
in Raccoon City never happens again can I make myself look fucking huge in
yourself it's a federal case I don't have the authority look at me my ability now
if I'm gonna finish this case you're the last hope I've got I'm not just
gonna leave you here what if you're attacked what if you need help that
just said what happened what did that just happen I'll be fine don't worry
about no I got to see this through and I want to see you again I got
plenty to live for trust me now arriving at yes please we don't have
much time you're gonna need this okay Leon I know I can't do that for very
long what happened give me a TLDR what a Leon sucks a to sucks t-virus sucks g
virus sucks FBI now involved CIA okay we have we're at the final save point
I'm just kidding why do I still have these I don't know you got an item
but no save point why it's kind of weird leave them now I'm not taking the
magazine I was just kidding map is the shape of a gun yeah items I'm just
doing an item check do we drop some frames no it's all right it's not as
bad not even close to what it was like yesterday it was horrible
yesterday sweat check now I'm just gonna Dexter's lab or is this you know I
think I will receptionist let's see no that's on herb okay I wonder where the
g-virus is nap room will be entered 1203 and Wayne Desmond I have to
remember this shit I have to remember this so I'm gonna write that down
the fruit that's in order to ensure employee safety in order to enter
you must use an ID wristband visitor general staff and senior staff
authentication is granted based on an electronic chip inside the wristband
the wristband access level can be changed by simply inserting a different
electronic chip visitor wristbands can be given to family members of
employees please inquire at reception for the details now I'm just skin
well what was the part of that item box I just saw all right hmm more
stuff that's good when's the local t-virus gonna come get me research lab
north area map so we have cafeteria kitchen nap room which is we have to
do a puzzle in here seems pretty good not doing so hot on the ammo
department I'm gonna have to use some of these items I've been hoarding
and speaking of hoarding this does they use a yellow liquid substance
that has been building up inside of my body and I gotta I gotta get it out
I'm telling you scary games make me every like hour and so does my
terrible old person body I've peed three times in five hours I mean I've
been drinking I've been drinking like a water of an hour but and every
hour and a half maybe feed three times in five hours it's just it's the
it's this I'm getting this all the hydration is sapping out of my body
because I'm screaming that's two-third as much as you need well why am I peeing
so much anybody in here a doctor I'll be right back if there's a doc if
anybody in here is a doctor but why I have that I've had my kidneys checked
I've had blood work if I have my kidneys checked why am I peeing every
like fucking hour and a half what the hell so all the doctors that I
mean this is all this 3050 people watching right now I my viewers are
incredibly intelligent I think there's at least 1500 doctors here so among
the medical community maybe you can come to consensus yourselves as to why
because I know that you know it is there so I'll be right back
I got myself a Coke I need something to sip on way better than Pepsi way
better par out the wristband now if you
blindfold taste tested me I'd probably say I would probably say Coke
was a little bit a little bit less acidic Pepsi's like acidic it has
you can taste it in your nose it's like a nasally acidic flavor where Coke is
like a back of the tongue sugary deep flavor back here Pepsi is up here Coke
is like back here like back here I was already in here
does it say he seems fatter what are you talking about he seems fatter I
think one of my eyes just crossed I definitely just one of my eyes just
crossed over the other like that it actually happened out of the time I was
gonna jump out of the boxes no liquor not quite
there's a lot of people here now I gotta get in there there's like super
gunpowder right there oh shit no don't throw grenade die oh damn I got
achievement more fuel okay how do I get across there just like bullets in the
where the fuck are they there God access denied just keep it you can have it
keep the night for all I care you can have it keep it what did I just get I
just got somebody else's watch oh just eat a grenade and everybody explode
I'm so sick in this room turn around turn the fuck why would you do the
quick turn what the fuck was that he wouldn't quick turn all right let's go
other side of the kitchen there's the large gunpowder what is too large gun
part is get you anything good the knife good I'll take it nice back
gives you two large bullets speaking of bullets I'm going to need some
thank you I don't want to use the shotgun yet there's a new wristwatch
and regular regular flame regulator for the flames or a custom part of the
flamethrower restricts liquid fuel making it possible to fire for much
longer chemical flamethrower I didn't even use it once so I get to use it
for much longer good in there muff I don't think I don't have the
necessary item for this I don't although you do have a new watch here
electronic chip you're gonna combine that come in handy so where does it
let's see what I can do with it general staff so my security clearance
is general staff which I think I can go through this door and then
probably probably this door okay let's go someone's gonna this they
wouldn't just let you gather straight away here no way something's
gonna be here no good save it
still people here the hell is still here fuel for his max so I have two
large gunpowders now so I asked a question and then didn't look at chat
does it to combining two gunpowders big ones do anything interesting or
it's lots of ammo it's 50 pistol rounds Wow okay is that worth doing in this
stage of the game do you think it's worth having like a really good supply
of pistols it literally says it on the screen we'll see if I get
desperate I can do it but I still have plenty of ammo in this that I
haven't even used so anyway I'm gonna store it I have plenty of I got
a heel here don't need it just yet I still have that tool why didn't I get
this for PC this this is on PC this is PC fill up the fuel yeah that's a good
idea I'm playing with yeah I'm playing the controller and it's not so good
for aim but it's alright for I like moving around a third person with the
controller feels more organic to me well this is different main shaft
special forces recording target moving to West area must be going over to the
dream virus an antiviral agent this is ghost
rendezvous at point w3 this is alpha I've got eyes on the target he's gonna
open the safe awaiting signal got eyes on the g-virus we're going in dr.
Birkin you'll come along with us quietly g-virus is in the West area
got it all right I need to go to the West call up the elevator thing
that was neat at East East West that ain't correct I go this way I'm facing
south yeah but I mean look why would you build the facility like this why
would where we you come in that door that just seems strange you're looking
from the cell yeah but this is how you this is how you come in some idiot made
this place not as smart as me I would have made it a little bit cooler than
this I would have like streamers in every room streaming to their twitch
channels nobody thought that was funny that's okay an NV design and you're
talking about a place that has like the Las Vegas strip design is pretty
damn cool Ferris wheel you see the light up Ferris wheel I'll take a Nevada
design well now I can make another one of these I still have one of these
already made but I'm just for some reason not doing it look at how many
of these I have one two three four five full heels more gunpowder good
that's four never make fun of me again that goes for all of you that
goes for all of you there's two there this is a this is a full heel so that's
one full heel in here I have one two three four full heels so that mean I
have five full heels isn't that interesting that's not interesting
well it is okay I touch the mouse and now all of a sudden I can't use
my controller all right let's take it with the map we are here they can go
lobby let's go straight through straight through never mind how about over here
oh no okay that thing's gonna break out of the glass flower astronaut thing
ah that's so creepy don't just go activate it need to upgrade my wristband
yet shit ah okay I got shotgun shells here oh here they come you got to shoot
them in their hostiles that's kind of hard to do with a controller in my
damn hand all right poison them shoot left posture shoot right posture a
cartridge for dispersing various solutions in the greenhouse okay anything
else in here there's a map of the whole area input code what Tetris I have no
idea I will not know for at least probably a little while so I got the
greenhouse thing solution sprinkler control room can keep moving this way
Jesus I'm gonna have to I'm gonna have to start burning stuff let's explore
nothing this way here I got four bullets watch out somebody in the vent
all right so I got to the minecraft shoes best piece in Tetris minecraft
shoes best Tetris piece that's the first two herbicide synthesis plant 43
herbicide synthesis place an empty cartridge into the solution dispenser
add the required amount of UMB number 21 cool it immediately I was just
fucking drank out of this the wrong way and dumped it on myself thank god
I stopped okay so I need to place an empty cartridge add required amount of
UMB number 21 I'm assuming I'll probably get that so I need destroy
plant 43 looking for a chemical more large gunpowder all right I gotta start
making bullets next box that I get to because I just have so many good gun
powders I have to use them okay let's see the map out here back into
the greenhouse control room can't go out of here yet what's going on why
is everybody why is everybody copy pasting what happened nothing I can do
over there so I gotta go back out take a look whoa whoa whoa hold on F H
minecraft shoes okay Lego paws minecraft shoes Lego Lego paws minecraft
shoes Lego make them count make them count really burn oh burn I think that
was pretty good use of that didn't use very much all right computer no where's
the Lego machine thing I guess it was Lego paws minecraft shoes Lego okay
that was unlocked so I gotta go back over there is the safe point I'm gonna
save it no I'm not no no I'm gonna say I can't leave is he blinking now
oh fuck Jesus that's the wristband so I can I not take it I think I have to
destroy it to get it yeah make sense good back through there I unlocked that
thing very good watch out I don't want to take an
unnecessary hit here kind of just blocking the whole way aren't you
unnecessary unnecessary do it necessary I go to where I was and then there
should be a ladder here now right mm-hmm here we go you have 700 flame
BF I'm gonna need it when I fight like a huge mr. X research lab East good and
then what's this more gunpowder fuck oh fuck I have to take care of this I
have to make ammo I need to have my hoarding mentality just be destroyed
it's not good in the lounge you're right Leon calm down server room won't
open probably need to open it with some unlockable thing I don't the music is
doing this thing it's stopping I got so many items the hell is this trophy
all right when you find yourself in a scenario like this I think I have to
make the herb good okay give me the trophy so what the hell is this trophy
in the shape of a DNA helix and there's another code I can look at it
again so I have another code for that I'm gonna walk over here in these
fucking assholes are gonna get up Murph Murph it was muff that Murph I'm
just not sure what the hell it all means an herb right behind me all
right I need a box pronto what is it what is it what is it where the fuck did
you come from a great document to brain dead why did you not die from that
explain it to me somebody there's like 30 people in this room what do I have
to do what did you even come from you gotta be kidding me man just
get me the fuck out of here Jesus Christ are you coming out of a fucking
portal what the what did unbelievable why the fuck even am I just gonna dump
like five enemies on me at the same time with two lickers oh you can fuck
right off for real anything even over there fuck you stop dropping people out
of portals Capcom what the hell is this you can't tell me that that guy
didn't reliably come out of a fucking portal no no somebody's note everybody's
turned vetrified they keep going back again and again burn them all burn them
all until their body is black as ash there's no other way oh god this is
the Murph thing I get through this locked door what that's not effective
that was like one was 50 flame throw ammo burn them all burn them
I'm dead I'm so mad right now oh I'm fucking furious somebody returned
sticks I'm let me let me console aim for a second here I had so many heels
this was my decision yes and I'm gonna sleep in my fucking terrible bed that
I've made I'm gonna shit in my bed I have to clean it up eventually do I
have another heel in here that's not okay so unfortunately I have to use one
of the super heels so I'm gonna do high grade high grade yellow and yellow is a
bunch of shotgun shells right no it's Magnum okay right but that's important
Magnum is like what I want now what I'm gonna equip the Magnum and I'm
gonna make sure I use console aiming to hit precise fucking shots with the
Magnum let's do it now I'm gonna do so gunpowder and large gunpowder
doesn't matter I think I want like some pistol ammo look at how much I have in
here I have too much I could do console aiming and precise it's just
oh it's alright it's fine I think I want some more shotgun so I'm gonna do
shotgun and then I'm gonna do six shotgun I think I want pistol as well
so too large gives me a bunch of handgun ammo which I'm just gonna do
it I don't think there's a reason to hoard this I really don't think there
is it what if we drop in frames oh we did oh well alright let's uh let's do
we're gonna double I'm gonna combine these two and make a shitload that's
actually very very good so what do I have now let's take some inventory I
need to get a better look at this so hold on don't get cocky at least
now I have ammo to use let's get some fuel 400 that's good
got 12 magnum ammo and seven in the chamber I need to take a couple of these
actually because I'm almost dead bring the signal modifier wooden boards so
that leaves me with this I think I'm gonna store these for now let's move
some shit around so we got that I don't have any more ammo for the
shotgun there's eight bullets in there for the modifying signal okay pretty
good I need to heal but not yet not yet take the bring the wooden boards to
fix the indoor windows so I have another thing to punch in here so there's the
sprinkler there's the control terminal I do I have to go to the where that
thing saying muff with Murph what where was it Murph muff I don't think
it was it down here I think was somewhere else there's not one in
here requires senior staff I got to go to the the nap room
it's not moving so much all right let's go I don't even heal yet so that
brings us to here what was the was on the trophy what was it it was what the
heck was it I don't remember it was I don't have the trophy with me burn
plants are you burnt are they burnt that one is come on burn got it okay
gotta get a nice and crispy yeah they're pretty crispy so what was the
minecraft password here it was somebody remembers I it's okay go by numbers so
imagine it like one two three is up top four five six in the middle seven eight
nine involved it was wrong I don't want to go get the trophy Lego paws boots
Lego Lego no I did that one already is that it all right I did this one
I already did that one what was in the bottom of the trophy I'm gonna
have to go get the trophy okay so people were writing random numbers
let's see what it actually is so it's boots which way spinning around just
take the damn thing with me I'll throw it in the trash when I'm done he
he hates us I that one that's the correct one drug testing lab is now
open excellent now can I get rid of the trophy yeah now I gotta go to the lab
which I need do any I need like a solution or something right so
through here I didn't burn these guys so unfortunately I probably have
to fight them again I burnt some of them didn't I I just think we remember
burning at least a couple of these guys this drug lab all right time to
make a potion so we're gonna put this in and I gotta do the double dare family
challenge thing where you gotta get the milk over the line you gotta get a
little bit and then I gotta get a little bit which one has a little bit
only I had it I think I had it right actually the first time because one of
them pissed out I got okay I gotta fill fill this up all the way and then what
happens if I do this okay there's a little bit left in here so I need
hold on so I need a full one of that and this little one that's not
enough it needs to be those two so the one the middle one on the right
one are I'm ready to go but this one has to be drained that's is that
gonna do it no it's too much okay that should be it stop messing with the big
gulp machine the freezy machine dude I'm doing I'm doing the cray I'm doing
like fucking coke Pepsi Sprite 7-up I'm doing all of them fuck it um it's
awesome how's it taste pretty good man all right so now I have that so
put that thing I just made into the machine which will spit out the
poison and I'll get the wristband that we can get on and I'll get on with it
right cartridge for dispersing various solutions with the greenhouse it's full
of solution taking precautions here I still have the signal modifier no it's
one of these listen to Cheeto thank you oh it's muff okay I get it muff I
gotta stand in front of them and do them I get it all right I have the
solution I'm gonna go back out here into the greenhouse room sprinkle
that shit where it needs to be sprinkled call it a day from there well
not it's not call it a stream but call it a day in the lab because this is
gonna destroy everything right this is the solution and this is this is this
correct hope so I'm gonna save it first just in case I didn't do it
right all right I gotta chill it oh yeah that's right I gotta I gotta cool
it down first so now the question is where was all that shit I cool it
all right here's a circuit breaker down here so from here I'm gonna go this way
and I want to find one of those like muff circuit breakers this one in this
area right here I got live I don't think so this one doesn't work it's
not turned on now there was a couple of enemies still down here I think both
the Lickers are probably still alive because they come back to life so I
gotta be careful but I want to find Murph so straight through here there's
a circuit breaker at the very end of the hall here all right no alive
Lickers please they're both dead I think I'm safe all right Murph son of a
bitch so Murph examine let's do it on Murph Murph
stick it in what did that do turned on the lights that really all that
did was there no reason for that besides just to turn on the lights no
okay server room combat knife good I'll be sticking that in somebody's face
very shortly anything else in the server room ooh some paste and some gamer fuel
safe you can almost host a minecraft server almost what can I make I can
do more Magnum no I can do more shotgun which I think that's what I'm gonna do
yes it is more shotgun ammo store this fuel so I got some gunpowder fuel I
have do I have another gunpowder or just that's it 12 with 7 in chamber
that's a lot blue herb some boards I'm gonna keep I'm gonna hold on to
that cuz I probably need it very soon looks good everybody load it up what
playthrough is this this is just my first playthrough at Leon that's it so
I've done everything I can do it here what about this way though is that
door locked as well or did that open now because the lights are on let's
find out it is open though don't open that for this person come on what
you dumb low time cool it down there is where I can cool it something's gonna
appear in here I know it lady's gonna get up so what's in here I thought
that was a pack upgrade well can I not go in here I'm gonna get hurt if I go
in there Wayne Lee's inbox can you believe that bastard Cartwright cool
well I guess he's the boss for now anyway have you seen my helix anywhere I put
the secret on the bottom let me know if you find it put together the budget
estimate for the year after the next and get it done tonight we're under
attack people are dead the east area is cut off we can't operate the bridge
with the wristbands we have here where's that bastard Cartwright
hiding plant 43 is going wild the greenhouse is hell we need to send
someone in there before it's too late Wayne how do we stop this
thing you have to help us please reply remember Susie the cheerleader what a
great gal we were both into her of course she wasn't into nerds I still
have to give you back those comics and games I borrowed but you might have to
wait a while all right so I'm gonna go into the
chill room hopefully I don't get chilled out all right it is very cold
in here so let's just do it let's get it over with cooled it off it's
gonna take 30 or 40 seconds to do this and I'm gonna take a couple minutes
surprised I know drink it immediately just unscrew the cap and just pour it
down your throat herbicide good really selling the whole chili act I like it
yeah there is gunpowder in here something else though besides just the
random little gunpowder there's a little side room too isn't there no
that's it completely searched you know you know fucking though I'm waiting for
somebody to explode through a wall or crash a computer it's gonna happen nice
make our way back up I now have the herbicide I can get the wristband to
be able to go into the West
you're gonna let me come up here without a fight or an issue fucking burn the
body burn fucking hell you really he has great commentary not scared at
all just irritated just slightly annoyed at everything that he's doing save
it not like whoa well holy shit what the fuck is that thing no what the
fucking hell he's slightly annoyed at every enemy yeah where his youtuber
reactions come on maybe that's a decent stack cool ready to rock and roll um
I think it's time to bring out bad boy I'm fully stacked don't use this
unless I need it something's coming up here for sure I'm in the lab the
lab I'm about to I'm about to turn this thing into jelly and I'm gonna get the
wristband so this thing's gonna attack the giant tree monster is gonna fight
me and I'm gonna need to do one pinpoint headshot where's that thing
it's in here right yeah sprinkler system through here all right it's
time for you to die put it in let's see what happens
dispensing solution now Jeremy doesn't read chat I try to peek over there
every every minute or so I try to see what's going on in there just gotta
that did the trick gotta pay attention to the game you know all
right let's go upgrade the wristband you have dispersed a danger solution
without authorization your actions have been law and disciplinary measures
disciplinary measures oh no I'm gonna get written up so witty okay it's out
you fell out there okay you're gonna do this to me I you're not just gonna
fall flat through of course not I thought he was gonna go through the
glass let's clean it up there's only one I think that's alive here there
again what the hell whoa whoa whoa there's one coming up quick you know
what just
like I like electronic chip that guy looks normal what's with normal guy
shit him again oh no you don't all right I gotta get out of here out out
out out out all right hold on I need to go to the senior staff PC get the
fuck don't it's gonna break through a wall I know he is fuck I gotta
upgrade the dumb watch okay senior staff I don't read you guys emails
right now but I'm gonna apparently reading emails when did nest become
a nest for spies three month three last month for the for this month and those
that are just the ones we caught step up security cart right or do you want
to end up like your predecessor I'll be restricting access to the West area
from today ignore all requests from headquarters for information on G the
suits contribute nothing to this project autogenerate warning
unauthorized access herbicide dispersal by unauthorized employee
detected in the East area that's great that's really great good to know
so I need to go out we're gonna save the game and I have to go I can't believe
this guy's still here he's still following me around still trying to
kill me West area I got a full heal in my I'm gonna take two feel like we
could be getting somewhere here out to the West area so that's just bang
right and make it over cross and I have the access now he's gonna show
up right here wait wait wait wait wait what what what's wrong what's
wrong modulator modulator modulator modulator modulator modulator I still
need that thing I mean I guess maybe I'm kind of out of room let's go how did I
even look at him why did I open the door I what was the point of me doing
that I want to just make sure he was still alive and he was doing okay are
you still in there yeah he is West area yeah good luck I can't pull this
back oh all right the G samples up here go to get the G sample what do I got
for weapons everything loaded pretty good wait what's everyone freaking out
about use a modulator in the north room oh god this guy's coming to get me
and we're going to get secret items no I'm definitely not getting
debated because it's it is listed right there it is pretty close it's
right here I'll just save it right here anyway just in case mr. man comes to get
me so it's just left and then I'd leave with it there was enemies in here
wouldn't there no not all the way down here that was the I was a funny
zombie that was kind of a funny zombie muff what do I get nice hit
pouch I think that's the final upgrade son of a bitch was this Wayne Lee's
notes dear God blood everywhere what the hell's happening they're dead all
dead it was those men in black USS headquarters special forces but why
isn't their job to protect us white brains in a sea of red this can't be
happening dear God why didn't everybody say I was a genius a genius
like me can't die in a place like this I always got results they're
screwing me well maybe well maybe I'll screw them I win the Nobel Prize
I'm a hero a genius of God I will not die unfortunately you did and that's
what I came back all the way back here for was an upgrade to my pouch got the
pouch upgrade okay I it's time to go why do people always write in their
diary when they're about to die because you want to you want to leave
you the last thing right you want to leave at least I got to tell somebody
my story right before right the apocalypse you can hear like the
zombies closing in you're like I got I got fucking something to tell you I got
something to say whoever finds this you know so I'm gonna hold on to this
just because people probably get angry if I throw it in the trash let's go
West Hall what would I write in my diary something ridiculous something
really really cryptic and weird just okay you guys know you guys know
mr. Satan from Dragon Ball Z I would just pretend I was like a superhero
or something like I fucking saved the day and shit I'd write like a whole
story about it here we go video cassette and grenade one of the
videotape to go play oh good is it player right here what perfect timing
for a videotape player good thing I brought it us us and there's the
light good no save point but there is a box for some reason let's put that tape
in and see that's it modulator is done I can't really get rid of it but
we'll watch the tape quiet movie
you'll come along with us quietly you think I didn't know you were
coming this is my life's work I'm not handing over anything we have our
orders dr. Birkin I'll ask you one more time
what the fuck are you trying to be there
what the fuck were you thinking our orders were to bring him in alive
yeah come on hunk get with the program we're in we had a snafu target
resisted we had to take him on that's correct sir so they're gonna do
a hunk campaign I hope they do they've done it but with every other
game they've ever made besides like resident seven right resident six it's
already in oh everybody loves hunk so those were G samples so that leaves me
with the lab here the inbox of William Birkin decided to cease all research
on G which was ongoing at the nest underground laboratory all funding has
been cut and Birkin has been removed from his post thank you your
mail dr. Birkin top brass has expressed an interest in this
evolving bioweapon do not worry about costs our company is the most well
funded in the whole of the United States good news G is almost ready
strange you never thought to report to the research lab here at Umbrella but
I suppose I can't let that slide anyway send over the data would you
and don't worry you've done good work on G but we can take care of the
rest you're under suspicion of breaching your contract with Umbrella
that has become clear that you have claimed ownership of the G project and
unauthorized contact with the US military please respond to the
investigation committee summons within 24 hours okay anything else in this
room that I can do buy a reactor room okay get that scared me speaking of
storing stuff I have too much stuff in my inventory uh but yeah both these
can be destroyed don't need you anymore don't need you anymore who are
away still have a full heel have two full heels in my I've got full health
three full heels not bad F why is everybody saying F F well I don't think
I have anything else did no that this is an important room I'm going to go
back and just put this in the box I can't combine it with anything so I
still have this plunger tool thing I still have that well I don't know
what that's for must have missed something in the office or in the
police station all right here we go straight through what the hell is that
noise by a reactor room long way down okay do anything all right here's the
big reveal this is the before you get on the ride weird scary room where
they start to blast music and start to talk to you this is the pre
before you get in in the on the ride at Disney World I'm ready creepy
limbs brains eyes more emails after G embryo was implanted in the subject we
made a 50 centimeter incision from the chest of the abdomen and began our
observations subject's consciousness level was kept between 15 lucid in GCS
10 however the subject consciousness level deteriorated the further
observation was deemed unnecessary the subject was then disposed of the
G virus was administered to subject 501 they mutated into G form and was
introduced to a group of 30 test subjects after two hours 36 minutes it
was observed that all but one of the test subjects have been implanted
with the embryo all subjects were disposed of one subject broke down
during experimentation and took their own life G viruses 628 who had shown
slight resistance to the t-virus the virus was then introduced to subject
639 with whom 628 had a close relationship 628 showed some signs of
resistance but had it been implanted with an embryo up to 24 minutes t-virus
resistance does nothing to stop the mental deterioration caused by the G
virus a lot of numbers I'm tired that was easy all right it was back to
okay that was easy I didn't look in here there's like a okay this shit in
here save it right now hurry up okay uh I need shotgun ammo shotgun ammo
grenade okay save it here we go self-destruct sequence initiated let's
go out of just let me pick up all the shit first hold on not yet wait
self-destruct sequence will begin when lockdown is complete
let's go oh it's this guy again it's a deterioration gun I get it call this
thing William why your umbrella too you tell me you weren't involved in
this yes what you just fucking walking away you just tried to incinerate
somebody tell me everything like an hour and a half ago right from the start
yeah you don't you're at fault here sometimes the hardest decisions take
we made the g-virus but we never intended it's been in any way you want
you're still responsible
why did you make him stronger
he's super
three two one actions run and there's no way to run
okay got out of the corner Magnum time right not yet no yeah I don't want to do
it yet what are you doing shoot him in the eye he's in the fire too it hurts
him Magnum and his not yet Magnum eat shit
first aid spray get it that come on shotgun oh no no no no no no no no no
no no no no me oh you fucking got up and you fucking did that right when I got
up oh you're fucking bright when I fucking threw the thing got you you
go right the fuck up immediately damn it I'm in trouble now not quite no
yes I am I got one more heal it up Wow you still hurt and what you're
gonna pick up the whole tube whoa no no no the whole tube
give me that what is this first aid I don't know this is give it out just
take everything quick okay uh this bullets hand grenade it right there
burn his body what I won
Joel beat getting over it just tell me he'll destroy that G sample no no he
did no it's evidence did you act it's going to the FBI no man that welcome
everybody she's a mercenary she's gonna sell it G virus is gonna go to the
highest bidder I can't beat it I won't be able to beat it bullshit that's a
godly gamer I don't know what a godly gamer absolutely godly gamer you
are oh by the way spot spoilers for Resident Evil 2 if you never played it
before because this is the end of the game sorry for those that well there's
two stories though you might that don't worry there's two different
stories but uh that's the hope you had a good stream welcome everybody go
follow Joel if you haven't he's fucking awesome all right so uh how
do I gotta get out of here what if this still this still a loose end
here where's um where's the other guy with mr. X I have to another there's
another fight coming up here with mr. X give me my heels I got full
everything right two full heels like I still got six bullets did I save it
when did it save all right mr. X is gonna be in the elevator and I'm
gonna shoot him right in the head I was just thinking about you that makes
two of us I was getting worried we make a good team I gotta ask you
something ways clear please tell me you got it I got it
it's the ultimate babe right let me verify the g-sample we get the hell
out of here before we do that I ran into a net she's bad she claims
Wesker the guy with the glasses should have been so realized as much as I
wanted to trust you I didn't I really hoped it wouldn't end up like this so
that's all this was do we have this conversation on the other platform some
pawn to you this one's kind of collapsing my job and I'm doing mine
so drop that damn gun I'm taking you in hand over the sample Leon I don't
want to hurt you can you like email me the details here and you shoot me but I
don't think you can who's mr. X her fall let her fall let her fall you're
going to get shot see you around kid take care of yourself I lived though
see I grabbed onto the chair all right final battle with mr. X let's do it
escape the lab let's go 49 seconds no I got nine minutes to get out wait what
do you mean get out like I've nine and a half minutes to get out of
everything out of like the pepper what do you mean everything what do you
mean everything what do you mean get out get out of where where am I
getting out from can the elevator go any faster you should have jumped
okay here we go here we go here we go out out out out out out out out out
out 9 minutes until detonation who's that I was like oh it's clear Claire
what the hell are you doing here weird I've been doing the same shit you have
from a different angle the whole place is coming down listen you have ten
minutes yeah yeah there's a way out we can make it
claire you're still there leon hey leon you're breaking up
forget about me just get out of here damn it
wait okay first aid let's go come on give me that give me that
like tim burton music 8 40 does it just count time down i
gotta take all my herbs okay just no i got enough i'm ready tool tool tool
tool tool tool tool tool take the tool tool let's go
pump room excuse me what is wrong with this door
combine it with this one we're on the dock jump jump jump jump jump
until detonation is he waving to me he just waved to me what what
okay thank you let's go what a cool shot of my proton pack
almost gotta keep going seven minutes i'm fine everything's fine let's go
just keep giving me this shit okay um shotgun shells take it reload high
grade i don't need it what is this stuff
bullets joint plug i don't have time for this
shit i don't i got i got plenty of handgun
uh i think it fits there tool too i know i have the tool that i have the tool
everything's fine i got the tool is there a safe point right there
somewhere nope no don't pull it i gotta fight him on
here final battle great seven minutes until
even the ball sack he has like a large ball sack
in the chest right in the chest let me see it
uh-oh reading he's getting greedy no i'm still i got caution i'm still
fine you should have slow stamina
oh my just a small area i'm dead i'm fucking absolute
no first aid spray is gonna fix this one
okay so he has this like fucking chest thing
that apparently i'm not shooting good enough
i don't even know what the fucking buttons are
seven minutes until detonation why don't we skip this
use the tool it's not the tool
oh he was still there what is it with this thing
he says not good not good not good not good
i thought how did he do it i ran through his path
how all right so and i'm you shoot him in the heart
i'm supposed to be shooting him in the heart right like i'm doing that
right it's just the instant kill move just
watch out his arm seven
all right stop looking at chat it's definitely the heart it's not his flame
arm six minutes until detonation
all right well not good not good dead again aren't i i'm gonna die
again how do i get to the inventory i'm okay how do i throw flashbang on the
on the computer what is flashbang i don't know what
flashbang is space i'm gonna heal
all right get it i was gonna shoot him one time in the mouth
where did this go oh he's i got room it was very anticlimactic
he's gonna get back up right do i have any
all right okay hold on i have ammo i got four minutes to get the
fuck out of here exit no no i ain't dealing with this one
don't make me use a fucking rocket on you son of a bitch
don't make me take out the rocket launcher i'll do it
shit gotta get out of here mr rex to come back
i've got three more rockets with mr rex's name on it
so don't need that anymore apparently believe i actually miss her i'm not sure
who i'm referring to does it just be ada and that party was
crazy last night let me get that wristband off i can't
get it off you can never get those fucking things off comedy right
who the hell are these people hey we made it just like i said we would
who's the who's who's the girl that's abrupt that's a very abrupt
ending that was all right not even like a
ride a motorcycle into the mist all right no that's all right here's a go
here's my thoughts it's great that was that was great
that like two hour hour and a half period where mr x
the tyrant is just won't leave you alone as some of the most intense
terrifying experiences i've ever played in a video game it was fucking
unbelievable so there's all this is a clear
campaign too which takes you through the events of the story from a
completely different tv screen and you can see all the other stuff
there's a lot of other things that you places you go
with claire uh but the purposes of tonight's stream
and obviously yesterday's stream leon that was what seven
eight nine ten about like nine hours for the campaign
ten hours for the campaign total somewhere between like eight to twelve
hours for general playthrough i guess but uh i
don't know if i would stream claire i don't know is there enough
content to justify doing it all over again from another side
that there is there there actually is okay
it's the same levels but it's it's different
no i mean yeah the i would i would assume that
if they did the campaigns this way i mean in the first original game it
was kind of like that too right he played from two different
perspectives but that was great uh streaming wise we'll we'll see if
this is something that we'll always kind of have it in the back pocket
because i don't think i would we just we've done resident evil 2 for the
last two days in a row i don't think i would
want to do this like the like the next stream we do right
maybe i don't know it depends on how i feel uh
not tomorrow uh we'll be streaming next on what's today's date let me see
let me see let me see today is the 29th so the next
stream will be on uh thursday so nothing tomorrow
except we'll get back on thursday maybe i'll just do claire
or maybe i'll try to do one some of the bonus stuff if not then there's a
couple other things that are on the table
still but that was a fantastic game that was great even just seeing
you know maybe not even 50 of it that was very very good
it was worth the purchase for sure are we going to get a post credits
secret secret scene is that possible kingdom hearts three
uh i don't think i would ever stream that game you can skip
so if i skip this it's not gonna skip the cutscene you sure
is that for real it won't it won't always the c assist mode i don't
have assist mode on i don't have aim assist or anything
how am i i told you i'm a c or a b minus streamer so you kind of get
what you're here for less than 10 hours yeah just a
curiosity i want to see some uh concept art uh aida model
concept art uh survival a hero emerges game mode claire second story mode
costume leon model quick draw army bring marshmallows
bonaparte okay modeled new models new models
model g stage three packed pockets broom hc g adult
new game second run has been unlocked selected under story from the main menu
the ending and certain parts of the game are different in the second run
scenarios interesting let's do the models for a
second so we got trench coat aida right we uh look at all these
unlockables there's marvin william remember so
bloody the zombie dog g adult this is the one i was
okay right it's those weird monsters it's the tyrant why does everybody
call this guy mr x a leon calls a mr x
stage 3g really cool looking why would you a flash grenade oh cool
sla 60 that's a cool looking gun broom hc cool okay well
for the purposes of tonight that's gonna be it uh gone for about seven
hours now maybe like an hour post uh just about
for bits and subs and yeah that was fucking fantastic so
thank you for joining me on this tuesday night tuesday afternoon
and that's gonna be it we will gauge if that's something we're gonna do to
do the other side or to do some of the more of the bonus stuff
but i had a great time at least so far ahead so take care i'll see you
guys on uh not tomorrow the next day check
the sus be probably around 3 p.m pacific
three-ish p.m pacific and that's gonna be it
much love take care of yourselves those of you that came over from joel's uh
stream uh street that got caught down here
somehow uh those who came over joel's stream
thank you hope you enjoyed yourselves and i'm gonna get off the camera
am i doing bits oh yeah yeah for sure let's get out of resident evil
two and let's scroll down to a little bit earlier today
we had uh from alec thank you alec for the one dollar
hello hello timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar i have no robot
conversations today but i like to say that i love your
streams and the worst part about having a good
sleep schedule is that i can only catch just about the start of them
yeah pacific time is really weird because when it's the daytime for me
sometimes it's like 11 to 12 o'clock at night for everybody else
so that is just the nature of time zones unfortunately and i live
across the world from a large amount of you but i appreciate it
nonetheless thank you thank you divas for the two dollars
thank you divas some guy thank you for the 10 dollars some
guy so i was going to post another meme
video yesterday but unfortunately i had a retake today
so i had to sleep to make up for it i'm going to make this a double
whammy what a double whammy what do you mean meme
why is that how is that a meme that's just the theme song to a
play it's just the fandom of the opera again you just gave me
you just did it both is it both the same video
well thank you i thank you for the 10 dollars some guy appreciate it and
the end of the opera thank you anonymous thanks for the one dollar
anonymous hey jerm i think the name you came up with last night for my
duckling is amazing i also want to say i wanted to say
stay still when shooting in this game the uh the recticle
to tighten for a chance of getting a crit headshot
yeah i figured i i did figure out somewhere
about 78 percent of the way through the game that there's like a
counter-strike aiming system you just got to stand still i did
pretty good no i only missed a little bit
hey beef one dough thanks for the one dollar thank you
ydna thank you for the 10 dollars ydna
hey germa addressing the pizza hut versus domino's chat a few streams
ago i just want to say that i've worked at pizza hut for three years
and that all the dough comes in frozen and nothing is made fresh
if you have the five dollar menu where you're at it's a big fucking steal
yeah but that doesn't mean that doesn't mean i don't like the pizza
it just because it's frozen doesn't mean i don't i can't you know what i
mean it still tastes good stuffed crust pizza but nobody goes
to pizza hut and thinking a stuffed crust pizza
is some organically made product i know it comes off of a truck frozen
you can't put cheese in a crust like that if it has to be manufactured
it's gross don't eat it i can't i have to
i i know it's probably bad he's so upset
i'm not upset it's just i love stuffed crust pizza and i have i've only got
to eat it like once every couple of years
but i love it i wouldn't say i don't think pizza hut's the best pizza ever
i would put it pretty far down on the chain of restaurants right
but it doesn't mean i don't like it hey we phone thank you for the one dollar
sorry for some things i say in chat i feel like i can make comments that i
think are appropriate but looking back they could possibly
sound mean-spirited or even just completely off topic and i just vent
sometimes i forget people especially you can read and it's not the place
for that kind of stuff i just get a little wild and don't
always think before i say things germapleudo that's okay see here here's
the thing if you do something that you maybe
shouldn't have done or you think back you have the wherewithal to
think back and understand that what you're doing
might not be right or it might not be appropriate right
so give yourself the credit that at least you're looking back
and are trying to improve on maybe some things that you might say
i'm not saying that i don't 99 of everything that's in this chat i know
is just for fun and a joke trust me i know it germa you keep
bumping the mic fuck i'm sorry but no i i know that people are just fucking
around so don't worry about that just know that
it's good that you have like i said the wherewithal to step back
and take a look at what you're saying thank you for the one dollar thank you
howdy i'm chad for the 10 bucks thank you for the 10 dollars chat
hey germa i'm so thankful for your streams in the community around it if
it wasn't for the germa discord i would not have met my amazing
girlfriend really we're both big fans and i'm happy we
can share these streams together you can add world's most compact
matchmaker to your list of records all right that's awesome
that's really really cool i'm i'm glad that that
worked out that's awesome and i didn't even do anything
matchmaker no you guys just you guys found each other
i wish you the best of luck thank you to the both of you and thanks for
the 10 dollars rumble legs thanks for the 30 bucks
hey germa i love you and keep it up by the way you have a hair net on
not rumble on numb i said rumbles that is not your name it is uh it is
numb legs nine but thank you for the 30 dollars
a hair nut i didn't have a hair nut on but i really appreciate it
i watched your stream with my ex and she didn't laugh once that's all right
can't make everybody happy can't please everybody right
uh thank you dingo for the one dollar somebody put a coffee cup in
your hoodie oh there are that don't do that to me
i get angry hey future gamer thanks for the one dollar hey everyone living in
northern america right now stay safe in this minus 50 to minus 60
wind chill weather yeah i did hear about that
that's insane that's the kind of weather where if you open up the door
and walk outside you movie like nitrogen freeze right
just be fucking careful guys be safe don't stay up there for too long
at all even that's absolutely bonkers hey lentils thanks for the one dollar
lentils hey germy really glad you're playing this because i'm too much of a
wimp to play resident evil hope your migraines go away soon
yeah i thank you i appreciate it i felt pretty good today
just been kind of headachy and slow the last like week and a half
some strange reason i don't know why maybe just to do with something to do
with my sleep but i'm good kind of back to normal
at this point but i appreciate the one dollar and the concern
uh thank you t dog red for the
crotcher thanks for the five community subs earlier guild hero five community
subs also community subs community subs lots of
them uh keith ward thank you for the
one dollar scariest funniest shit that i've seen
in a while nobody fucks with the jacks wait did i say that
when did i do that the fuck is wrong with me
uh dork cube thanks for the one dollar oh boy you made some fun sounds tonight
that mr that that was mr x shit i'm not kidding
that was not i wasn't like playing it up i was actually
in fear total complete fear they knocked it out of the park
this is a well it's a great game they did a great fucking job i hope
they do the same thing to resident evil 3
and hell may go back and do it to resident evil 1 do it to all of
them this was too it was this was very good did i play the original a long time
ago yeah but i was also kind of young and didn't
get it i was bad at the game well you still
are yeah i know but i mean bad enough where
i couldn't i just didn't want to play it i was too young to really
care i think i was like 15 or 16 when it came out and i wasn't like
that young but when did resident evil 2 come out how
old was i 14 i don't remember resident evil
1 and 0 remade already yeah but they were remade in that
same style of tank controls right i would love
for them just to go through the list and do them all like this
at least three at least do it at three because isn't three
considered by most fans of the game franchise
to be one of the worst ones in the whole series from my
understanding i always thought the three was three
and six i thought with just nobody really liked them it's six
it's just six yeah i didn't like six either
six was just it didn't even feel like a resident evil game it felt like a
it was kind of just shoot at other military guys right
at least for a large portion of that game but we'll move on
thank you smelly boy for the two bucks germa iq is such an underrated
emote oh i think it gets used fairly
frequently i see it all the time when i look over
but thank you smelly boy thank you jules for the one dollar chat says
uh save marvin germa shoots marvin in face
and then says save the game uh thank you rock
raucous spur for the one dollar i'm having a i'm having too good of a
time with this stream i usually don't pay full attention to
any stream but i can't look away from this i'm really happy you like
prison evil 2 no this i there's a blast it was
great i had a great time uh thank you david west for the 10 bucks
they just say uwu thank you uh dave vad for the 10 dollars
appreciate it 10 bucks smelly boy thanks for the one dollar germy please
wake up jerry please just once for your daughter's birthday what
freudian weapon thanks for the 13 dollars freudian you may have
single-handedly got me interested in survival horror again
resident evil 2 looks great watching you get scared by dick tracy
there was the highlight of my evening much love germa hart have a great night
you as well freudian i hope you do give it a try because it
especially considering that this is a great game to stream
i think and to watch because even if you watched me play the
entire leon campaign you can just do claire and you
hadn't even seen any of it before that's really cool it's very very
cool but thank you freudian for the 13 bucks
it's a great game and freudian again you had five community subs right after
that thank you uh also another dollar from
freudian who are you and what are you doing here
yeah wait hold on everybody got really upset at me
because like my favorite npc and resident evil 2 shows up and i like
start talking about it and all of a sudden
all of a sudden like i'm the bad guy thank you though
thank you uh t dog again for the one dollar can we get some
pogs in the chat for this intense gameplay
i bet that there was there's probably so many pog champs
dork cube thanks for the one dollar dork cube i know a weapon you could use
against mr x it's called uh you know that fire weapon oh
streamer i can't remember what it's called can you think of any weapons
that use fire oh yeah what happened with the tool
i didn't even get to use it was there was there was no
nothing i could do with it this is a debate oh
oh well it didn't have a red check mark on it though i could have used it
somewhere else you are a tool get him out of here
man thank you dork you uh thank you kinky for the five dollars i spent like
thirty dollars on you now but it's all worth it
i love you father also it's popo not poopoo
anyways check out this website you'll have to reload it like
once but it'll give some insight on your chat i'm not gonna click on
that that is just that's the gnome
headquarters why would you want me to click on gnome hq
thank you chicken parmesan for the ten dollars
thank you chicken uh i want you to take a deep breath right now jeremy you're
doing fine thank you chicken i got over it i got
over my fear hey robot mentality thanks for the
one dollar the cap david thanks for one dollar you look extra cute i caught
that one before but thank you uh creation the cyborg thanks for the
two dollars hey germa guess what's happening tomorrow
we shop and anything online related for the we will get shut down
forever will you pay your respects to the we
ps the we shop music will still be playable but you can't go to the store
itself and anything the we you features
online for the we is shut down too so basically it's the original xbox
live shutdown for the we i mean whatever
it's like what was on the we shop it's like
wow mario tennis you can but you can just get mario tennis
unstepping fuck you germa i'm just listen let me tell you something
i think is i think it's i don't know why companies decide to open up these
stores in the first place if they know that they're just going
to close them i like i don't i think that's dumb you know
eventually every digital store is probably going to turn off
but but for me personally i i did there's nothing on like the
we shop that i am like oh fuck i'm not gonna be able to
i can't do that anymore i kind of i got my fun out of the we
now wait this is important though hold on our if you bought a game
on the we shop is it still downloadable
just not purchasable anymore like let's say i i bought like
10 games on the we shop is it just is it actually
like they're not they're closing it down or all the servers are turning up
and you can't even download it you can only play the things you
download it you can't you can't even know the
servers are all shutting down all right like that's that's that fucking
sucks i didn't know i was unaware of the
details i thought they were just closing the
store not turning off all the servers i thought like i thought what
people have been saying is like this the store was closing i apologize for
that i'm sorry about that um yeah that's like a terrible
scary reality of everything being digital
you know 10 20 30 years from now if it's not profitable for a company to
keep what you've purchased online and they
have the terms of service just to pull the plug on it
then you know all the things you ever purchased are impossible to ever
receive ever again that's kind of the digital world
that's the scary weird reality we live in if steam were to turn
its servers off tomorrow i would lose out on
hundreds of games if i couldn't play them but the thing
with steam is you you just it's not those games would still
function but you just wouldn't be able to download them anymore
but still you would lose out on so your entire library thousands of
dollars gone potentially you think that uh
services like this would have some like emergency
sort of backup of everything and just have it available
even if there's not very many servers because like let's put it this way if
if you were going to go download like mario tennis for the we shop
and it was going to take you a little while because oh shit
oh that's right there's like 10 servers that are online
not like 500 it's going to take me a few days
you probably still wouldn't i mean it would be annoying but at least you
could still do it that's why you back them up keep copies on archives and
that's not a concern yeah unless you're using a service
that stores everything but that's unfortunate i didn't i
wasn't aware that it was not just a store that it was literally
anything everything related to we online the whole the whole shop the whole
everything that sucks but there's nothing i would really want to play i
played pretty much everything i wanted to
there'll be an emulator there's an emulator for the games anyways
yeah that's where that's why emulation is important
it is because there's backups of these pieces of media
that you would just get kind of lost forever wouldn't it decades decade i'm
talking like 100 years from now we need that library of video game
congress is the music muted oh no i just turned it down a little
but thank you peaceful hailey for the one dollar hi jeremy and chat
just want to say thank you for taking the time to read what i send
about my career problems sorry if i keep repeating myself but
thank you for the advice and giving me hope you're truly one of a kind person
love you germa and chat i'm really it's great that you're
going to get you're saying that to chat too
chat is chat's pretty fucking great but thank you
peaceful hailey i'm happy to give anybody any kind of
unprofessional advice but i'm not i guess that that's what you're
getting it from just some guy you know i don't want to pretend to
be an expert on anything that i'm not i can just tell you my
opinions that's pretty much it but i really appreciate it thank you
for the one dollar and stormy chew gave 50 dollars was
touched upon it one more time stormy chew thank you for 50 bucks
lots of laughs tonight stream's been great so far
and the resident evil scenario or or a baseball bat definitely
thank you thank you keith ward for the one dollar as a doctor my
prognosis is that you're urinating more than usual due to the hang on
my patients have all died because i've been watching twitch for five hours
thank you uh keith thank you ecliptic for the one dollar at one time i was
drinking so much coke i could clean the toilet with my pee that's
disgusting that is absolutely revolting and i'm
embarrassed and ashamed that i just read that out loud
thank you tar alacran for the two bucks derma you forgot to mute during
one of your pee breaks this is the new low for even for you
oh my fucking stomach i'm just sitting there going ah
oh yeah oh that's fucking funny thank you for that
thank you for the two bucks uh tar alacran and the great clip
uh palasonic thanks for the one dollar germa the entire chat was just
convinced you would
i'm not gonna read that thank you tar alacran for the dollar 25 why does
chat keep calling you a boomer i don't think you're that loud
ah thank you thank you for the three dollars and 25 cents
binary man thanks for the five dollars well i forgot to set my alarm and slept
through the entire stream until now germa pluto and there's a youtube
probably you know what the fuck was that thank you
binary man for the five dollars uh ethereal seth thanks with one
dollar germa my friend said you ate poop on stream but you seemed
wait no that didn't happen thank you yes is online for the three
dollars damn i've missed a lot of streams because of work but i'm glad
you're playing resident evil 2 i had so much fun with it that i had
to 100 percent it in two days thank god for vacation days i've been
in a massive creative slump for a long
amount of time and it inspires me to see you entertain a pretty
consistent basis uh entertain on a pretty consistent
basis thanks and i hope that the green
screen film my team's working on can repay all the entertainment you've
given us whatever it is i am i i have no idea
what i'm potentially in for it's probably going to be crazy so
looking forward to it and yes resident evil 2 is a great game
thank you for the three dollars why dna thank you for the ten dollars
leon looks like the main character from that quiet man game
yes yes he does thank you why dna for the ten dollars
and for the quiet man reference thank you the thrill for five dollars
the thrill long time listener first time caller 31 years ago
my older brother passed away the small the smallest things like watching you
streaming makes trying days like these easier to deal
with much love thank you the thrill for the
five dollars and i'm terribly sorry to hear that
if you can get anything from watching the stream that makes me
incredibly happy thank you we got a great we got a great thing
going on here and i'm really really just
absolutely just ecstatic that there's such a great community here
thank you so much for the five dollars take care and then we had the
demonic cucumber for a dollar i think it's really nice of you to
continue uh his streams of the voice changer and video clips italics it's
nice that you continuing it after his set in stone death
that would be something wouldn't it can you imagine if italics was just
doing this with a voice changer it'd be impossible he streams too
hey tingy thanks the two bucks i don't know what to say so germa pluto is all
why what be sad why thank you for the two
dollars though tingy uh pin thanks for the one dollar pin
germa i adopted two bunnies and i was wondering if you could help me think
of some names uh they are both twins uh brown with
black spots the brother rabbit has white paws and the sister rabbit
has a half black face if that helps thanks
scrawny a hug for uh okay so you have two rabbits one of them is brown with
black spots anyone has a half uh okay so how about
how about cookie and cookie and crumb which one's bigger the bigger one could
be the cookie the smaller one could be crumb
easy done you're gonna love them but thank you pin for the one dollar
demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar i can't believe germa stole
his english joke from inspector gadget his english
joke from inspector gadget glad to have someone with more integrity
in char- what stole his learn english joke from inspector gadget
you sure did i'm gonna get a fucking ad
hold on i have i have a full four and a half minute ad no i have like a
hold on i'm getting called out for i don't even know how am i supposed to
know what this is okay this whole tour was fabulous
never a dull month even a last minute rescue you guys sure put on a good show
penny you missed all the fun penny you missed all the fun
i could have been inspector gadget i do consulting work hire me
uh thank you demonic cucumber for the one dollar
hey 64 fanatic thanks for the 10 bucks you we screamed when x burst
through the wall germa old i'm sorry that was dust in my
throat it was i was too scared and it was too
much but thank you 64 fanatic for the 10 bucks
uh dr epic frag thank you for the one dollar
uh if uh papa papa murphy's is miles above every place near me
if you got one nearby use that money i donated the other day for a 13
dollar family size they're well worth it compared to other places
uh i've never heard of it germa deflates is this it
i have to go up the stairs anyway so we're gonna go out we're gonna go
upstairs so left right upstairs yeah that error just kind of came up
yeah what a youtuber but thank you dr epic frag something or other thanks
to the one dollar who's your favorite reasonable character and why is it tofu
it's actually uh it's actually leon no it's not
thank you anonymous for the one dollar sorry literally just found this out
apparently because the people you sent over to my rescue stream i'm about to be
viable to become an affiliate so thanks to you i might be able to take
in even more animals as i'm betting you know there's always more rescues
thanks again truly no that's absolutely it's
you're doing a good thing you saving animals should be commended
but thank you so much and congratulations and good luck for the
rest of the with the rest of the stream
hey creation the cyborg thanks for the one dollar the store on netflix
and youtube on the way is shutting down actually later today
at 1201 and whatever you downloaded from the we shop will be on your we
forever you can't get rid of them anything
online we related like i mentioned uh but don't worry x-link may get their
hands on the shop soon interesting maybe they'll back it
up be good uh not very many more to go
through thank you burnt muffins for the two bucks hey germa i'm back
from bmt it was nice welcome back burnt muffins thank you so much for the
two dollars welcome back uh i volunteer at a bunny shelter man
they really need all the help they can get
i have a bunny shelter when i worked at an animal shelter it was kind of
everything i didn't know there was a very
specific just bunnies that's pin by the way that said that
i was unaware but thank you so much burnt muffins uh clue the sniper
thanks for the one dollar hey germa your horror game streams are always
fun have you thought of streaming dead space yeah i
dead space is weird to me because i've seen half of it played
and then i've played like two hours and i've watched somebody play the other
like four hours it's just it's kind of all over the place to a point
when i'm not sure i'd want to do it
i don't i can't go in blind and oh wow i don't know what's gonna
happen because i know a bunch of the scares already i know a
bunch of the stuff already so i don't know if it would be a
great stream but they are great games they're very good thank you
creation cyborg again for the one dollar uh you said you're an ed ed and eddie
fan there's a game on pc you should get it
uh i mean i'd edit ed ed and eddie's cool
it was a good show i can't say i watched every episode of ed ed and
eddie but it was it was good it was good the
video game is awesome and there's also one for dreamcast
god uh you know me germa jeremy 985 that's me the guy that plays old
like cartoon video games we just play cartoon games well i
think i don't think i've ever played any cartoon games
why am i making that reference to myself uh demonic cucumber thanks to the one
doll i hate germa uh and then in brackets italics i
know we joke around here a lot but i just want to say that your content
genuinely gets me through the days sometimes
it brings so much to my day with your hilarious and heartwarming streams
and i know this is sentiment echoes with others in the community
from the bottom of my germa heart thank you mind how you go
thank you demonic cucumber and yeah i i get
showered with such incredible comments and such praise
i i wish there was more i could say you've heard me say this a bunch of
times i wish there was something more i could say or do
but all i'm gonna do is just continue to be here and hang out and
stream and try to do my best and that's not gonna change i don't
know why it ever will or ever would so thank you for being here
thank you so much you guys are amazing only a couple more we
have nick thank you nick for the one dollar you're probably the person i
look up to the most that's still that's i can't i don't
even know how to respond to that like that's
i'm so happy that you can take anything from this stream it's such a
nice thing to say to somebody it's such an interesting thing to hear
i don't know what i don't know what i can do i don't know what i
how i act or how i you know it's that's kind of
and i essentially am at that place for you
where i'm sort of on like a pedestal and i'm not sure i want to be
i'd rather i don't know it's a weird feeling
maybe the pedestal is not the right word but
i just i just want us all collectively
as a community and as a group to go as fast as we can
on the highway you know what i mean just like to go very fast
and then we slow down a little and i just i want us all collectively to
have a great time and i just hope that you can get
something out of the stream and i hope that
i i guess it's just and maybe i'm like a self-deprecating a little here
but i think i have to because it keeps me honest
it keeps me uh my head on straight and you know the nature of the
business here the nature of the online entertainment kind of world i
want to stay i want to keep my head on but
that's an incredibly fucking nice thing to say thank you
just say thanks yeah i know but you gotta look you gotta look at it from my
perspective though right uh i there's there's a very specific
thing that i want to do here and when people tell me that you
know they look up to me so much i i it's almost like i want to
do more and i do appreciate it that somebody would say something like that
about me it's it's incredible thank you
we all look up to you since you are the almighty tallest
yeah i fucking am but thank you shimmy shim sam for the shim
sank shimmy shim thank you shimmy sham for the one dollar germa did you see
this tweet it's very good let's take a look
germa found dead in raccoon city it's a jack
it's a jack that's fucking funny tag link that
peak mic did i peek the mic at all today probably like 30 times
but thank you shimmy shaman thank you tag for the for the clip
hey jushb thanks for the one dollar hey germa ha now that you're in vegas are
you a raiders fan also i second the dead space playthrough
that or some skate streams i'm not a raiders fan
not yet because they haven't really played the stadiums going up
but we'll see i'm more of a more interested in baseball
than i am in football once i play a couple of games maybe
try to get to one or two see how they are it's really interesting stuff
going on in vegas right now lots of development lots of stuff
is coming here it's pretty great hey creation the
cyborg thanks for the one dollar you looked on etsy with ed ed and
eddie there's a half-life exclusive half-life
grunt on on etsy there's an exclusive game
for ed ed and eddie that i didn't that i forgot
i don't have like any half-life stuff half-life exclusive half-life
grunt and half-life paranoia i'm not i'm not
entirely certain of what you mean by this
but uh thank you for the one dollar and gotta get some half-life figures
or half-life not figures uh exclusive games
but thank you thank you uh nick for the one dollar i know it must be so
weird to have people saying these things i've been thinking about that
but anyway literally just keep doing you because we love you for you
yeah sometimes i try to give you guys like an idea of what i
what i mean by these things and i don't want to come off as ungrateful
or uh rude or anything i really don't i like
to keep myself as grounded in at least somewhat as you know transparent
as i can with everybody here but you know it's it it helps
when we all talk about it talking about any of your feelings
right let's talk about our feelings i just hope you guys can understand
i don't mean it in a way of trying to be rude or trying to be
disrespectful at all but thank you and then finally cola man
thank you cola man appreciate it and how does that make you feel
you're always grounded because of your height get that guy out of here
uh let's do the credits resin evil 2 was awesome really great
wow that was loud i don't know why that was so loud
two dolls from creation cyborg uh two oh it's two half-life games for the
dreamcast i did not know they existed you
know who's got a lot of feelings blokes who bludgeon their wives to
death with a goth trophy oh that's a sniper yeah what a bunch
of what about great characters they ever gonna like do anything
else are they gonna make like a team fortress
telltale game where is that please don't
yeah we could get a tf2 telltale game
where there's only two choices that do anything
and each of the characters looks like they're on strings
and being danced around like marionettes it'd be great
that was mean wolf among us was good the first walking dead game was good
i've heard tales from the borderlands was good
yeah that was kind of mean they made a they made a lot of real
bonehead moves but then they made a couple of
like pretty decent games they did tails was fantastic
yeah i never played it i was not like a really a huge borderlands fan
thank you creation of cyborg two dollars tf2 was originally going to be a dlc for
team fortress classic so i could see that happening yeah i'm
glad tf2 took as long as it did because it was
going to be a completely different game good thing it took nine years to
make i clocked them at 85
85 is how fast you were going but thank you everybody all the new subs
and old subs there are still a shitload of people
that are subbed to this channel what an awful title this stream was
god this is terrible this is awful why didn't anybody tell me to change this
re2p2 it's been like this for eight hours
why didn't somebody tell me to change this this was a placeholder title
from when i was setting up the stream that's the worst title i've probably
ever had damn all right well i'll see you guys
in a couple of days nothing tomorrow take care of yourselves
resiable 2 is fantastic and we'll see what we're gonna do on
wednesday much love to you see you real soon
take care guys have a wonderful day have a wonderful night
oh my god t-shirts right fuck okay um hold on the oh man we take hold on
a minute t-shirts i have two shirts glue man is
returning permanently and the germa solar system
is the new t-shirt that's coming out it was going to be either today or
tomorrow but since i'm not streaming tomorrow
i'm just going to hold off on it and i'm going to launch it's going to
be a storefront on teespring and they will both be
permanently available at least for i mean we'll see how long that the
store can last but they're not going to be taken down
for a long time thursday at the beginning of the stream
i will link to the storefront and there they will be the shirts are
planning i'm planning on the shirts being 20 bucks
i actually was on the teespring website and they changed some of their
materials they changed the way that they made that you can design shirts
now they got rid of some of those shirts
from before but i still think that i can do 20
dollars with like the premium t-shirt because last time i did the premium
t-shirt and i was 20 was still fine for like
all the overhead so i they changed some things i still
think it's going to be possible so it should be one of those nice
premium shirts for 20 bucks thursday and then yes i will tweet it
i'm going to tweet it out there'll be a command in the chat for it
for it forever i guess or at least for the first
couple months what's it gildan what's it gildan
no they have what the teespring changed the shit
should i be laughing at that what is the teespring premium shirt
is that what everyone's laughing about everybody i mean like the one
the two one guys i have no idea yeah i'm trying to figure that out but
it should be 20 bucks see you on thursday we'll talk
about some more take care okay bye now for real