Seven minutes. Seven minutes is all I can spare to play with you.
We're up here!
I can't move! I can't do anything!
Can we please just shoot?
Seven minutes.
Dodge! Dodge! X!
I'm gonna grab those, make sure I get them.
Hold on, I have the poison. Let me just shoot them and...
I've been kicked.
I couldn't give him the poison.
Hold X to like...
Hold on. I forget what we have to do here.
Oh, it's a red herb.
What is this? It's broken. Something's broken.
Smash this.
Alright, this is a giant rifle here.
This is legitimately like...
We're not hiding. What do you mean there's no point in hiding?
Alright, I'm about to drop like a fucking nuke right next to you.
I need to get to like a good spot.
He's dancing. He's literally dancing.
I think we can like... Oh no, we can... I remember we can like turn off the lights.
And he's like, ah, where are you? I'm an idiot.
Okay, so we'll come over here.
Are these the lights?
Yeah, it's dark over here. Watch, he's gonna go...
Oh, what the... Oh, I can't... Never mind.
I think I'm dying.
I think I'm dead. You killed me.
Saturation.
I'm dead.
You're dead.
I thought that was for you.
There is no way we would be able to stand on this lava rock inside the volcano.
No, what are you talking about? It's probably like a cool, clean, chill 68 degrees right here.
We've got like a high of like 70.
Yeah, it's probably like 60, 70 degrees right now.
It definitely would not be like over 180, like three, five, six hundred thousand degrees.
Why am I on this?
I have to make my way around.
What the fuck?
Wait, me? What? Hold on.
Climb up. Climb up.
I'm having trouble doing this.
My hands getting tired.
I'm coming.
I have to tap this shit.
I'm punching this rock.
Oh my god.
I actually pulled myself.
Oh, you saved yourself?
You would never be able to do that in real life.
Just one arm, pull yourself up.
Dude, that rock is like 12,000 pounds.
There's no way you'd punch that rock.
I just spit everywhere.
You're like punching a fucking rock, like Rocky Balboa.
What the fuck just happened?
Get over there and start punching the fucking rock.
Here we go. This rock is a hundred times bigger than me.
He's like making his way over to you.
There's no way you're going to do it in time.
He's like right behind you, dude.
You're so dead.
Something tells me we would do it. Something's wrong.
But I'm pretty sure if we walk near him, he's just going to...
This is not good. He's just in the way.
Is there anything we can do? Wait, can you?
I'm going for it. I'm going for it.
He just fell in the lava.
Will you stop swinging at nothing?
No, no, no. That's a bad idea.
What is this dumbass doing?
Looks like he's painting a mural on the wall.
Oh, God. Oh, here he comes now.
Oh, this is over. This is it.
This is it. This is it. We got to go now.
We got to go now. We got to go now.
Ready, partner?
Locked and loaded. Suck on this.
Yeah, you didn't fire, did you?