Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Enlighten.
This week's Enlighten is going to be a live Enlighten. I'm going to make a park in RollerCoaster Tycoon 3.
Now you're probably wondering, Jerma, RollerCoaster Tycoon 3 is not that old of a game.
So why are you doing Enlighten on this?
Well, with the recent disaster of the SimCity launch, I figured a lot of people are trying to find different city simulators,
trying to find different ways to get their fix for micromanagement god simulators, and this one is my all-time favorite.
It's going to be a lot of fun to reminisce during the gameplay while I'm making my park, while I'm making my people happy,
getting them burgers, getting them fries, getting them cokes and soft drinks.
If you've never played RCT, go get it right now. It's on good old games, it's on Steam.
RollerCoaster this one's on Steam, I believe for 30 bucks right now. It probably will go on sale at some point.
But it is a filling of the void for a lot of you SimCity guys.
So, let's get started here. I'm going to clap into the microphone accidentally, I'm sorry.
I'm going to do just a live playthrough of me making a park.
If you guys like it, please let me know, show some support if you want to see more of this,
and I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care everybody.
Alright, well anyways, let's get these freeloaders out of here.
Nevermind, you can stay.
Let's start building this thing.
Park is closed, yeah. See you later people.
Let's go straight up here.
I don't want to go too far out because look at how huge this is.
So I made a custom scenario just to play.
I made just like, you know, no BS here in the beginning, just my own park. I can do whatever I want.
I think I made it a little too big.
But whatever, we're going to make this the best huge park ever.
So I want a ride to be here, here.
Let's just give some markers here.
I want more people to come in, I want there to be concession stands over this way.
So I want this to be...
So this is going to be the food court, right here.
This is where everybody's going to have to go to get food.
Whether you want burgers, fries, like I said in the beginning, this is where you're going to have to go.
So let's go ahead and make some of that stuff.
Food. Bison burgers.
Burgers. I don't want any weird, weird stuff.
Let's just get regular burgers.
So go right here.
We need some drinks to go with that.
Where are all the drinks?
Oh, actually fries, too.
Fries.
There's a lot of options here.
Oh, it's because I have all the expansion packs.
If you're wondering where like all this, like some of the stuff is coming from,
you can see I have like the wild expansion pack.
I have the soaked expansion pack.
Wait, is this like chocolate milkshakes?
Hell yeah, we're putting chocolate milkshakes in my pack.
Okay.
So that's all. You get burgers, fries, and a chocolate milkshake.
That's all you get.
I want shops over there, too.
Oh, here's the drinks. Here we go.
Oh, coffee. Definitely coffee.
If you want some coffee.
There it is.
That's a very odd looking place, by the way.
Look at this.
Is that where they get the beans?
That's kind of gross. What happens when it rains?
Floundering Ferry.
Merry-go-round.
Got to have a merry-go-round.
Oh, my goodness.
It's so dark in this park.
I don't have any lights.
Oh, no.
Nobody's going to be able to see.
There's the entrance and the exit.
Hey, welcome to the park.
Hope you like pitch blackness.
I need some lights.
Hold on. Where do I go to the lights?
Germaland.
Germaland is officially open to the public for eight bucks.
You get to come in.
You get to take a right, eat food, and then go on a merry-go-round.
And then you get the fuck out of here.
How disappointed.
How disappointed would you be if you came to this park?
This park sucks.
Come on, let's go.
Germaland's officially open.
We're like the thousands of people I want to get in here.
All right, now that that's open.
Wait, I need to make these.
I need to open these.
These are just all closed.
All right, there we go.
How much money?
I want this to be...
No, you can just do default for now.
Standard coffee is $1.
Roast coffee is $1.50.
Okay, I'll keep the default prices for now.
If they become really popular,
that's when I'll start to really jack up the prices.
And suck everybody dry.
I still don't have any guests,
except for this dude right here.
Are you about to go ride this ride?
Look, Grandpa's going to go ride the merry-go-round by himself.
He's not really going to do that, is he?
He really is.
What?
This is the park inspector.
You are wasting electricity right now.
Did he pay for this?
He had to have paid for it, right?
No, he didn't even pay for it.
This guy didn't even pay for it.
Look, $0.00.
You scumbag.
Hold on a second.
Let's see.
Oh, here they come.
Here come the people.
Here comes the one guy.
Nothing really for you to do down that way, dude.
He's going to get lost.
Come on, come on, to the concession stand
where we sell coffee, burgers, fries, milkshakes, coffee, milkshakes, burgers, fries, milkshakes, coffee, fries.
Oh, yeah, you know you want to go in there.
Take your little shit kids in there with you.
Dude, this lady's more excited than the kids.
She's like leaving her children behind.
What a psycho.
Let's get some more stuff built here.
Right there.
And regular path, asphalt.
There we go.
This ride is going to be $2.00.
Here we go.
Open it up.
Chair swing.
Oh, one of the really cool features about Rollercoaster Tycoon 3,
you can ride your rides.
You can get in your rollercoaster that you built,
or like this.
Ready?
Let's see if I can do it on the stupid friggin' Ferris wheel.
Let's see if I can ride it.
Oh, yay.
I'm having so much fun, mummy.
Why is the ride not starting?
I want to ride the ride, mummy.
The ride isn't starting.
Ah.
Okay, that's enough of that.
Oh, wait, wait.
I just heard, I just heard a money.
Who's going to ride the ride with me?
Oh, hey, let's go.
Which one are you going to get on?
Are you going to get on that?
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
So excited, guys.
I'm about to ride the merry-go-round.
Why is nobody riding this ride?
This is one of the only things you can do in this whole park,
and nobody wants to ride it.
You guys are assholes.
Is it because there's too much money?
That's it?
That's the whole ride?
That was 10 seconds.
Look at this guy again.
The same dude.
The same, the same guy that's supposed to be, like,
inspecting my park is riding the merry-go-round again.
He's on the merry-go-round again by himself.
This guy is a freak show.
What's wrong with this guy?
I need to make some more stuff.
What are people saying about this park?
Do they hate this place?
Let's see.
Is someone watching me?
I hope it isn't too scary.
Talking about the merry-go-round, I guess.
I'm not hungry.
I want to go on more rides.
I want to go on something more thrilling
than the merry-go-round.
What about you?
Where are all the rides?
I'm sorry.
I'm working on it.
We'll do another ride.
Here we go.
Thrill rides.
All right, you want a thrill ride?
I'll give you the disco.
I'm going to put the disco right here.
Yeah, right next to the merry-go-round.
That's not too bad.
That's not a bad place for that.
Wink, wink, wink.
And then what's with the flickering screen?
I don't think this game was meant to be recorded.
It's going, like, every few minutes.
Open this up.
Are we closed right now?
Yeah, the park is closed.
Admission.
I think these rides are too expensive.
I really think that's the problem.
People, like, don't want to ride a merry-go-round
for, like, three bucks.
How much did I make this?
Don't even have a bathroom.
Should I make these toilets, like, pay toilets?
How much of an ass would I be
to make these $0.10 to use the bathroom?
People would have to do it
and force people to have to spend $0.10
to go to the bathroom.
We're doing it.
Hey, if you want to go to the bathroom,
you don't want to spend $0.10?
There's, like, a Dunkin' Donuts
three miles down the street.
Yeah, good luck.
Not one person has bought anything
from any of these stalls.
Why?
What the hell did I do wrong?
What?
Are they too expensive?
Maybe there's not enough pickles.
All right, we'll drop the price.
Standard burger's gonna...
We'll drop it all by, like, $0.30.
I'm probably gonna lose money on this,
but you know what?
It's gotta happen.
People aren't buying anything.
Who comes to a theme park
and doesn't buy, like, a cheeseburger?
All right, that's right, everybody,
because it's always too expensive.
The only thing I ever buy at a theme park
is probably fried dough.
Small bag...
For $0.40, nobody is buying Hershey Kisses.
You guys, seriously,
that's like a stick of friggin' gum,
and you're not even gonna buy it?
All right, all right,
we got a pretty good audience right here.
Look at these people,
like, all ready to roll.
We got birds over here.
Look at these birds.
No one's riding this ride.
Do you people know this ride exists?
Maybe my pathing sucks.
With drastic, drastic measures,
we're gonna build a roller coaster.
The facelift or the fear slinger?
Let's do the facelift.
Look at this thing.
62 mile-per-hour speeds?
You better believe it.
Where are we putting this thing?
Holy shit, this thing is huge!
Uh, it's going right here.
It's gonna go over the swing ride.
Wait, where's the, uh...
Let me see where the entrance is.
It's over there, I think.
Bang, there we go.
There's...
Wow, look at those shadows!
Oh!
Those shadows are so ugly!
Entrance is over here.
Let's go with...
Let's do the exit first.
Just because...
People are gonna have to walk a mile
to get to this damn thing.
You don't have enough funds?
I don't have enough money?
I can't even open this thing!
How much was this?
Was this roller coaster, like, all of my money?
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, good thing...
Good thing Venom from Spider-Man
has taken over my park.
Look at this symbiotes suit
that's literally taking over my entire park.
Are you guys ready?
We're gonna do testing.
We're gonna ride my roller coaster, baby.
It's an inverted coaster.
Oh!
Whoa!
Look at this.
This is the coolest part,
because you can build your own coaster.
You can build your own coaster from scratch
with all these cool things,
and you can ride it.
You can look down at your park over there.
I know mine sucks,
but you know what?
Here we go.
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
The twist!
You're in the twist!
This is so cool.