So, this is RID Asteroid, and as you can see here, we've got plenty of different classes
to choose from. We've got plenty of demo men, we've got a lot of soldiers, we've got a lot of heavies.
There's not just scouts and engineers, there's way more.
What are we doing? We need to be killing the robots.
Don't pan the engineer. That's not what we should be doing.
Look, we have to go get the... Oh, there's an engineer over here.
Oh, great. Okay. These two centuries are so close to each other, I'm surprised that they're not going to be shooting at each other.
I got auto-balanced.
Hopefully, we will soon see the outcome.
Don't forget your bonk. Don't forget your bonk. Don't forget your bonk.
Oh, it's closing. The door is closing. No!
I wanted to get in there.
Don't you laugh at me.
Oh, shit. Oh, God. This guy. No.
Oh, what? How am I dominating somebody?
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. One second.
Give one second here.
What the flying fuck is going on right here?
What is this?
This guy's behind the glass.
Too many centuries versus a big... All right, here we go.
This is the real test of what's a better century.
Who's like the better engineer?
Two big centuries versus two minis blocked by glass.
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy.
What have we got? What have we got? What have we got?
Oh, look, a spy. I'm going to go steal your R2-D2.
You can try.
Stealth, are you on the other team?
I'm on blue.
Oh, well, I'm just making my way through.
Okay, I'm joining red. I'm on red.
Just sneak by here. Go by the hole. Anybody?
Oh, look, a soldier. You might be AFK. Oh, no, you're not.
He was an AFK when I shot him.
Oh, now I'm at their R2-D2s.
I can't do it. I can't.
I just can't shoot R2-D2.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa.
I'm going to get the intelligence.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Tom Hanks. I mean, Tom Cruise.
What are we going to do? We need to play his bets here.
Who is going to, like, actually not make it through this, do you think?
Oh, this thing is simple.
Oh, this thing is simple, huh?
Okay, now can you accept this?
What am I doing?
Can you accept that backflip?
I need to step back a little bit.
It would be really funny if you could get killed by that.
Whoa, that's going to be close.
All right, right here.
What the fuck just happened?
I definitely got killed by the laser.
Oh, this is so stupid.
I hope everybody makes it through.
So come to where, like, everybody is on a...
For, like, blue?
On, like, where we are.
Okay, on red?
All right, let me come to the front door.
I'm going to make this guy do a backflip.
And once, after, right when he's done...
Why did it take that guy that long to decide to do that?
Everyone's just kind of standing around.
There's, like, no objective for us to do right now.
Besides just, like, standing around.
There's one, two, three, four, five.
There's six people on our team, seven people.
Just chilling out right here.
Maybe we'll steal more points.
You got it. Congratulations.
Oh, shit, a player.
A guy on blue team. Look out.
Don't worry, there was only one of them.
There's ten people on their team.
We did it.