Okay, so I have a couple of options here that I think we could pivot to that would be fun.
I don't know which one to do because there's very real possibility that one of the two of these
things that I want to just throw in here are going to be so bad. I'm not sure which one.
I have Universal Studios Ride the Rides for GameCube. I don't know why I bought it,
I don't even know how I bought this. Or another Cooking Mama game that was on the Wii,
the Cooking Mama 2 for the Wii, and then go to Animal Crossing in like another couple hours.
I'm not sure which one of those I want to do right now, but they both sound very interesting to me.
Should we ride the rides at Universal? Universal Studios? Look, this just got caught in the wind
here. I'm just looking up GameCube games that look like they could be fun and interesting,
and I'm like, when am I going to have an opportunity to play this fucking game? Ever.
Because this game, this is a game that I will never play for more than an hour or two,
so it seems like a pretty good spot for it right now. And look, if this game is absolute dog shit,
then we can just keep moving around. I'm open today, I'm open to whatever,
but this is already set up so it's going to have to be something for the GameCube or the Wii.
We want to go on rides? Okay, let's go on some rides. We might have to do some changing of the
audio. Let's see. Do we have to do any changing of the audio? This game is not a true representation
of Universal Studios theme parks. What? I missed, oh, I missed 50 dollar bits, holy shit. 5,000 bits
from Phylacter Lich, that's 50 more bucks. Please play Gotcha Force, you sexy BLT clown. Gotcha
Force is probably going to be like a 10 hour stream, and that was not on the plans for today.
This is going to take too long. Oh, there he is! Wait, why is he in there? Why is he in there?
Are we going to get a, please be the person that takes us around the whole park.
There's no dialogue. Are you guys ready to ride these rides? This game is going to be very bad,
I can already tell. You know, in hindsight, I'd like to uncheck the box when this is in my cart
to remove it from my cart, but I can't do that. All right, you ready to test the audio? We're
going to do some audio testing here. Ready? Boom. Boom. Boom. Boom. Oh, shit. Boom. It's all right.
Just skip and play Cooking. How is this game hard? Rumble feature. I don't know, I hate Rumble.
Universal Studios theme park adventure. Name, what's your name? That doesn't matter. Me. I don't
care. It doesn't matter. Jeremy. Player select. No. Oh, there, there. Oh, please do it. Please.
That's all I care about. It'll be worth the like 80 cent purchase if we get like a
uh
Welcome to Universal Studios. I'm Woody Woodpecker. And today at Universal Studios,
we have exciting theme areas based on the movie world. Today in the marketing of stamp collection
contest. That's not Woody Woodpecker. This is not how Woody Woodpecker sounds. Let's begin.
Get lost. Do it. Holy shit. They couldn't even get somebody to do it. They couldn't get somebody
to go to do the it is it's it's about put those kids to sleep. Well, yeah, I can do this on this
thing. It's gonna take some thinking. You can do this on my sound machine right now.
All right, let's go. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't
wait. I can't wait. Come on. Come on. Come on. I want to get to the right. I want to get to
Space Mountain. How do I do anything? Oh, all right. That's not real. This is the kind of costume
man. Can I talk to people? Stamps are either red or blue. You'll earn a red stamp if you score high
in an attraction.
Motion picture magic. No, I don't want to watch a movie. I want to ride. The game is very loud.
Is that better? Oh, no, I'm quiet. That was my fault.
ET. Give me on ET. What's up, you fucking creep? Yes.
I didn't get any of that. I don't know how this works. I don't know how to play the game. All I
heard was everybody sticking a needle into my ear and hitting like the fucking right side of my
brain. Wait, I actually have to do... This is not how the ride works. I thought I was just going to
ride the ride. Wait, it like put me in ET the movie. Go. All right, can I stop bunny hopping
and go for these speed bumps? All right, to be fair, I do that. I used to do that shit all the
time on my bike, even when I wasn't rushing to deliver an alien through his spaceship. God,
this ride sucks. This is really... What a shitty ride. Hey, kid, just go ride down the street.
You have four minutes to ride a regular bike down the street. Cool. I left three and a half
minutes to get there. How do I speed up? At what point is there adult intervention?
He keeps falling down. But now they're trying to kill him. Crunchy. This is fucking terrible.
But I need to... Hold on. We're getting into the hard part.
Holy shit. They're dropping... They're doing like Bowser, every Bowser boss fight.
All again, Jeremy. It's funny. I'm just pedaling, dude. I'm going to get there.
By the way, somebody said they guarantee I don't... They guaranteed I don't beat the first
level. Somebody said that. I want to make sure that that's on the line now.
He actually did it. Yeah. We're almost at the end. I have two minutes to get like 15 feet.
It's not over yet. I know. I can see. This is a loading screen. Yeah, it was a loading screen.
Did it go over this? Oh, okay. I will tell you. I promise. If the next level is this exact same
level, this exact same game with a different coat of paint on it. It's a side scrolling racer with
a goal at the end. If that's the next game, I will take the discount immediately and I will throw it
away. Okay? I promise. I will recycle. I will recycle this, if that's the case. Eat the disc.
No. All right. How did it end? Is this a ride or is this a really, really, really rich kid's
expensive birthday party? This is all for me. Holy fuck, man. It took some of you motherfuckers
an hour to do this. 59 minutes. That's impossible. That's not even possible.
Some. All, actually. All. Did I get a stamp? Oh, we can do a quiz. All right. I got the E.T.
stamp. All right. I'm not done. Is there a map? Map. Where's map? Item. Is there a map? Can I go
in the mailbox? Go to Jurassic Park? I mean, I have no idea where to even go. I'm like a lost kid.
Most in picture. Magic. What's this thing? Can I do this one? Press tab, noob. There's no tab on a
GameCube. Wait, somebody wanted to talk to me. What do you want? Someone was handing out maps
at the park entrance. I mean, he looked. Looked at what? All right. There's the park entrance
right here. Where are the maps? Map. Do you have a cap? You can enter some attractions whenever you
want if you have a cap. This music not like this. All right. Give me a map. Hello. There are letter
tiles hidden inside the park. You'll receive a stamp if you collect all the tiles. You'll earn
points if you click. Uh-huh. All right. Woody, give me a map. Right now, every attraction is at
full capacity and nobody can get in. I'll give you this. E-pass. You can only have one E-pass,
but you have priority to enter any attraction that you want. So if you decide to use your E-pass,
choose the attraction wisely. What? I have to use an express pass? I want to exchange my points.
ET cap. T-Rex shoes. No, no. No, no, no. I want to come back. This is just animal crossing, yeah?
Where's the entrance to this park that somebody has a map for me? Over 40,000 points.
Get the fuck out of here. Unlock everything. I'm not gonna do that. Where do I get this map?
I heard somebody was handing out maps at the entrance. Well, where the hell are they?
Is there a sprint? Can I go right? No. I'm just gonna keep following the road. What's the,
what's the worst that could happen? Right? What do you mean? There? There? Right there? Where?
Who has a map? Nobody has a map. Who's going down the road? You're gonna get hit by a truck.
Do you have a map? No. Okay. I don't have a map. If you don't have a map, get one back at the park
entrance. The red lady? Nobody has a map. There's no, this lady? This lady didn't, hey, hello.
Nobody has a map, guys. Nobody has a fucking map. Red lady. This is a blast. I'm having so much fun.
I need an, I need an adult to help me do this. Where's there? I'm at the park. This is the park
entrance right now. Red. Do you know where you're going next? I don't know. I don't know where to go.
Help. Which attraction should I go see now? I don't know. I need help. I'm lost. Wait. I can go down
here. Wait. Just get this shit out of me. Map. All right. This is the park entrance. I'm supposed
to go into the fucking parking lot. Where is the map person? I'm in the parking lot. Do you have
maps? The weather is always nice. Don't leave. I'm not gonna just leave. You think this kid has
enough to like survive walking down? No, he's got like a peanut butter and jelly sandwich and
like Ritz crackers in his backpack. I'm not, Lee, I'm not going anywhere. This map doesn't
fucking exist. It doesn't. I just have to walk to the next ride. I'll just walk into the next ride.
I don't even care what it is. Do you have a Ritz sponsorship? No, but they're fucking utterly
delicious. When you put a Ritz cracker in your mouth, you can eat them by themselves. Wait,
you mean blind again? The guy in blue. What? Here, have a map. All right. We're going to,
we're going, here we go. When you put a Ritz cracker in your mouth, this shit disintegrates.
It's so buttery and flavorful and it just disintegrates in your mouth. You put a little,
one little like cube of cheese on it. You put a little piece of salami on it. Ritz crackers
are seriously some of the best snack you could ever have. You can eat them by themselves.
They're fulfilling. They're, they're, they're satisfying. I, I fully endorse Ritz crackers
for a snack president, I guess. All right. Where am I going? All right. Let's go this way.
I got it. I L. Oh, what's that up there? New ride. It's not even a ride. It's not even a ride.
Got it. Can I find something? Please? I think I found something. Jaws. All right. Let's get on
Jaws. You can't enter this attraction because there are too many people. Wait, you have an E
pass. Let me know whenever you want to try this attraction. Just wait in line. I can go once.
All right. Let's fucking go. A Jaws. This is going to be the coolest one. Let's go. I'm going to
Jaws. I'm freaking me the fuck out. I don't, I don't even know how to play. I have no fucking idea.
A and B. Wait, I'm Jaws. All right. Let's go pick up barrel and throw barrel at Jaws.
Hurry up. Get out of here. Oh shit. He took a bite. Uh, starboard, right? Get up, get up, get up,
get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up. Oh my God. He's
going to eat me. Oh shit. A kid fell down off the jaws where I turned it off. This is not even
hitting him. How do I open shit? Can I open these boxes? He's wrecking the boat. Yeah. I mean,
I have to hit him with these things, but he keeps. It was so dumb. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Do it again. Here we go. I'm running out of Donkey Kong barrels to throw at this guy.
Are the yellow ones worth more damage or something? Imagine paying like $150 million to license all
the shit in this game and you throw boxes at Jaws off the boat. I have 30 seconds to continue.
Wait, which one's selected? All right. Here we go. I'll get it. Now I understand the mechanics.
Well, I didn't know if it was like, it was like depressed or not. Please no more. No, no, no. I'm
not done. I'm not done. I'm not done. Please no more. That zoom in on his face. That perfect
zoom in with the thing in the fucking head. Oh, throw it. Look at Jaws in the top left.
Fuck out of here. Jaws. Please no more. Don't fall kid. It's only one guy saying no more. All
right. All right. All right. Okay. All right. That's fine. It's so dumb. It's so dumb. It's so dumb.
Only one guy said only one guy was saying no more. Wait, what? Only one guy was saying
only one guy was saying no more. You're going through too many layers of one guy. I can't,
I can't follow you that well. All right. I think I only have to do one more. There's only one spot?
No, there's like four. Let's go. What's he doing? He's circling the boat. Let's go, man.
Oh, oh, because he's, oh, yeah. Okay. Yes. Yes. I see what you're saying because there's only
one green spot left on the boat. The game is so stupid and it has to be here. Get boxed, motherfucker.
He just leaves. Yeah, you're done. Yeah, you're done. Got the stamp. Good job. Is that loud?
Wait, that was, oh my God, that is very loud. Oh my God. I'm so sorry. I didn't know. I didn't
realize I was going to be that loud. I just, I'm sorry. I'm actually very, very sorry about that.
I did not know that was going to be that crunchy and that extreme. Sorry about that. I really am.
I didn't mean to do that. My neck. Hello, guys. This game is giving me a stiff neck.
My hands are a little sore. That feels a little better. We have $50 coming. We had
a 50, a 50, 50, 50, 50. 5,000 bits from Goiki. Seriously, thanks for the 5,000 bits. Thanks for
the $50, Goiki. This game is fun in a stupid way, but it reminds me of the countless nightmares I've
had about falling into the Jaws ride and it being a real shark. I remember, here's a quick story
for you. I remember being really, really scared of the Jaws ride when I was like 10 or 11 years
old or something like that when I went to Universal. And I was, I hyped myself up so much
and I was so terrified of it that when I actually got on the ride, I kind of closed my eyes for the
almost the entire duration of the ride. But I heard my brother laughing and he thought it was
really funny and I didn't understand why he was laughing so hard. And he like kind of was like,
open your eyes, open your eyes. And the Jaws animatronic is so old. It was so old and so shitty.
It was just like a sock puppet going like this. And then it would turn and go like,
it was not scary at all. It was a, it was, the thing was on fucking strings at that. It was like
the thing was built like in the fucking 70s. It didn't even look like a shark and it's gone now.
Yeah, unfortunately. So I remember that. Me and my brother just were laughing. We were like laughing
and fucking high-fiving each other and shit. But I will tell you that the Alien ride at Disney World,
I did not fuck around on that one. There was a ride at Disney World, and I'm not sure if it's
still there, it was at Epcot. It was something, it was like escape, alien escape, whatever it was
called. This is back before they rebranded it. They made it a men in black ride. But before it
was a men in black ride, it was just like an alien escapes from a fucking tube, the ride.
And I remember doing this. So I heard how scary it was. There's an alien in the fucking tube and
it breaks out, right? And the whole, the lights go dark. There's like scientists all screaming,
like he's out, he got out, run. And they have these weird sensory things where it breeze on
your neck and shit. I remember going like this. Well, here's a strategy. If you're ever scared
and you don't want to fucking see anything that's going on on the ride, here's a strat.
It's the pinky and the thumb, pinky and the thumb, pinky on the eyes. Make sure your eyes
are tight and closed. Thumb in the ears. And you won't, there's no sensations. So absolutely.
And in here, I didn't see anything. It's a foolproof tactic. Boom, boom. Like this.
Because everyone goes, Oh no, no, no. Nope. You got the pinky and the thumb technique.
And I did that the whole ride and I did, I didn't even see it. I got out of there.
Professional coward, professional coward. I was, I was like eight. You guys act like I was there.
I was there like a couple of months ago being like a scary alien. No, I was like eight or
nine years old. I was like fucking 30. Although I probably still would use that technique.
Oh, this is the wild West world. Why are you giving us tips? I'm telling you,
okay. It's not even nine year olds that you had. No, you know what? I'm getting really into it.
I go like this with my hand like that. All right. I got it. Let's play. If you have like a little
brother or I don't know, like, I don't know. I skipped this line. You can't get in here because
there are too many people. How are you supposed to ride? Ride? Do I have to buy? So you tell me I
have to buy. People should throw garbage in the garbage cans. It's pure common sense.
Do the quiz. Well, I don't know what the quiz is. I have to go get a pass. Get another E pass.
Why would you gate this game behind fucking E passes? I picked up trash.
You have to deposit the trash into the trash receptacle. Oh, nice. Do you know where you're
going next? No idea. So I'm going to go buy. How many points do I have? So I'm going to go buy
another E pass and then we're going to go do the quiz and then I'm never going to open this game
ever again. Why is a kid picking up trash? You shouldn't be doing this. Oh, I got another stamp.
Go on Jurassic Park. It's going to be tough. You hear that? There's a big crunch up here.
Jurassic Park is good. Jurassic art. Omega lull. All right. Do I really need a pass to do this?
Why do I have to? That's stupid. Can I just buy it from Woody Woodpecker? Do I have to actually
go to the very beginning? I don't have to go to the very beginning of the entrance, do I?
Oh, why? You can't get in here because there are too many people. Okay, so why? I would like to
purchase a pass from you. Just go in. Just fucking just go in. Just go in. I have to go all the way
to the beginning of the entrance. This is so... There are two hour waits in most theme parks.
Not if you do the easy pass. Not if you do the easy pass. The E pass. Go get the Jurassic
Park hat. I need a pass first. You missed bits, coward. I did actually, right? That was from
another more fucking huge money drop. 5,000 bits from Yes Is Online. Another 50 bucks.
Thank you for your insane contribution. Remember, that was part of the great movie
ride. It was a compilation of movies with actors and animatronics. They tore it down.
PepeHands. They did a lot of... They changed a lot of shit, didn't they?
Didn't they replace it with like a Fast and the Furious ride or something?
Where the hell am I going? Is it like a... You ride with the screen or something?
All right, this map is so bad. I can't even tell you where I am. I have to go this way.
Where's the entrance? Why am I so far away? There's no entrance and no exit. No, I didn't
get a cap. Get out of my way. Okay, we're almost done. Now I gotta go this way. I can't even go
this way. Left? What the fuck? I have to go there. What is this Final Fantasy VII map? Yeah, it
actually is. Dude, where the fuck? Jaws is over there, so I have to go back from Jaws. But isn't
that what I'm doing? Go to animation or right. I can't go anywhere. Okay, we're all the way out
here. I need to go down that way. Back up and bang a left. This makes no fucking sense. This
makes no sense. So I need to... I'm just going straight again. I just saw in the chat the funniest
thing I've seen all week. The funniest thing I've seen all week. Absolutely. Without a doubt. In
like the last five plus fucking streams. The funniest thing I've seen all week. You ready?
They said Olive Garden music. That's perfect. That's fucking perfect. This is exactly what
it sounds like when you're in an Olive Garden. Why is that so fucking perfect? And you see they're
eating your like your fucking tortellini and your endless soup salad and bread bowl. And then they
give you that you're out of it. Oh, I'll take the fettuccine Alfredo. Our fettuccine Alfredo.
Whipping it up with the... Our fettuccine Alfredo. Whippered up with the most delicious cheese sauce.
And the best, freshest wheat. And don't forget about our soup salad and breadsticks. Only $11.99
at your Olive Garden. We're in the neighborhood. And you order your fettuccine Alfredo when it
comes out and then fucking half the goddamn thing is cold and it's enough to feed eight people.
Where am I going? Anime voice. Get me... All right. Up here and that way. That way. But it's good. Oh,
it's absolutely delicious. It's unbelievable and it's like $12. I didn't tell you it wasn't any good.
This way. That way. This way. That way. This way. That way. This way. That way. This way. That way.
Anybody feel like I'm... I'm going in... How did I even get here? Can I please ride this?
Talk to me. Talk to me. Yes. You can see the demonstration of the climax here. Here's your
seat to see the demonstration. It starts the climax scene when you are seated. Choose your seat.
The demonstration starts when you press A. Holy shit. They don't do that. When did I choose... I
didn't even choose my seat. When do we get to see the water world demonstration? This is the water
world demonstration. Oh, this reminds me of... So, you know, in some martial art movies,
when it shows the same thing, the guy getting like punched in the face from like 12 different
camera angles. It's like bang, bang, bang, bang. I love that shit. I love that. That's what we're
seeing right here. I used to love that as a kid. Yeah. But we only got one scene though. Somebody
said, Twitch is shit. Go back to YouTube. I think you're about six years late. Yeah. All right. One
more time. One more time. Okay. Get me out. I'm done. I'm done. All right. Do I get a,
do I get a pass for that? You picked the wrong seat. 100 points though. Wow. All right. I
seriously want to spoil our Jurassic Park and I'm fucking never play this game again. I promise.
I promise I'll never play it again. I promise I'll never do it again. Just let me get,
let me do the Jurassic Park ride once. And don't forget our seasonal minstrel, Olive Garden.
When you hear, what's it? Olive Garden. What happens here stays here. What's, what's their,
what's their quote? Olive Garden. When you hear your family, that's what it is.
That would be fucking weird if that was the actual thing. Get the cap. I would,
I would love to get the cap if I could fucking find the way to the entrance. Somebody just said
with a heart, somebody loves me. What? Oh, it's garbage. How do I get out of here? I just,
I can't see the left, that left road. I can't go there. There's no way to go there.
I can't get there. It's not, it's impossible. There's no way. I need to go there from right
there. Where do I go? I can't go there. There's nowhere to go. Holy fuck. It was a tiny little
area. Burt. Uh, where are we going? Over here. Olive Garden music. I just need to know.
Olive Garden. Start with our unlimited homemade soup or fresh signature salad and a basket of
our famous never ending breadsticks. Strike one. There's something you can't miss at Olive Garden.
All new giant Italian classics starting at $12.99. Choose from four new specialties done up in a big
way. Feast your eyes on giant. Strike two. With catering delivery from Olive Garden,
we make the food and deliver right to your door so you won't have to lift a.
This is definitely an Olive Garden commercial that uses this. I know it is. I've, I've heard
it a thousand times. We're going to get it and it's going to hold on. Never ending classics is back
at Olive Garden. Fuck. It's this like, it's this like warm acoustic guitar. No, no. I know what
you're talking about. They, they changed their ad platform in like, in like 2017, they changed it
from like snappy fucking restaurant to like warm. We're sitting around with an acoustic guitar.
Hold on. We're going to go back to like, we're going to go back to like 2006. Check the ad
playlist. Is there, there's an ad playlist for Olive Garden? Why the fuck would that exist?
From the home of never ending comes never. Spaghetti and meat sauce. So many of us make it.
I. Right. Put your feet up. Now get ready.
Why is it all Gordon Ramsay? Right. What happened? Why is what this playlist? Why would you have an
ad for? Okay. I'm on the official Olive Garden channel. I'm going to go back to like fucking
2009 or something. This, I know it is. Somebody's got it. You got it. You actually got it. Do you
actually fucking have this? Please tell me you haven't. Did you find it? If this is a no,
I'll never turn my stream on ever again. What have you done? What have you done? No,
I can't ever turn the stream on again. All right. Give me Olive Garden. Fuck. Olive Garden,
never ending breadsticks. Is that what it is? Olive Garden, never ending breadsticks. Why does
it, you can still watch this. They don't even, Olive Garden 24 seven 24 seven breadsticks.
Okay. There's spam going on. Friday nights with my best friends. We have one rule. Everyone orders
something different. Now at Olive Garden, new smoked mozzarella chicken sauteed and topped with
melted mozzarella and a sauce at Olive Garden. We have one rule. Everyone orders something different.
Now at Olive Garden. Why would that be a rule? Who fucking cares? Well, I wanted to get, I wanted
to get the crusted eggplant salad. Well, order it, you fucking weirdo. Why do we have to get
this different food? This has it. Hold on. Another one. Let me see. You know, I love our family
tradition. What's that? The one where we pass our plates to the right. When did that become a family
tradition? When you ordered that. Try Olive Garden's new grilled garlic shrimp, marinated shrimp topped
with a roasted garlic glaze or try new grilled balsamic glazed chicken. Both served over angel
hair pasta and homemade cream sauce. Two new grilled dishes with endless salad.
I love going out to dinner and ordering food and then just fucking handing it to the next person.
Why don't you just order the food you want? Why don't they make all these fucked up commercials?
But it's, it's accurate though. You ready? There's another one. 2005. Got it. Got it. Now you got,
well, I mean, obviously you're going to get it in every other commercial. Okay. This is like
family guy funny moments. What the fuck are you doing? I don't want to watch this.
Okay. This one's called, uh, we're all family. Now this is not, this is not it.
That's not it. You got it wrong. Why would you look? All right. Last one. Is this a good one?
Okay. We got, this is called. We'll treat ourselves a bit at Olive Garden.
Breadsticks. It's a chance for us to catch up. So is that Donna still in the picture? Maybe.
Enjoy Olive Garden's new chicken crostata grilled marinated chicken breasts with our tomato Alfredo
sauce or new steak crostata grilled steak medallions with a four cheese sauce, both with
crispy Asiago cheese crostata and unlimited salad and breadsticks. So is this, uh, serious?
Yeah, this is seriously good. Dude, this is like, this is like fucking 15. Are you asking if it's
a serious relationship? The dude's like fucking in like the, like the ninth grade. What are you
talking about? So, uh, are you getting serious? Like what are you talking about? Yeah. She asks
it twice. Mom, get out of my fucking personal life for a little bit. All right. All right.
What are we doing playing the Universal Studios game from? All right. Last one. Actually last one.
This is the final one. 17. Hi, can I help you? Looking for my date. He's very handsome and the
shoes are probably untied. Olive Garden's new stuffed shells with shrimp and a creamy seafood
sauce or with sausage and Alfredo. Starting at 9.95 at Olive Garden.
I'm looking for my date. Where is he? Oh, he's probably got his shoes untied. I'm a funny mom.
Only at Olive Garden. Holy shit. Give me a break. I can never hear this the same way.
This is the classic Ultimate One Guy moment. Yeah, it is. What's this on screen? No, I'm not. No,
no, no, no. I am not going to put on. I am not going to put on it. No, no, no, no. Talk to Woody.
Woody's standing there like this. No, no, I'm not putting it on. I'm not doing like a,
no, I'm not doing an Olive Garden app. Try this trivia quiz contest. If you win,
you can play two new mini games. Let's go. With our beer battered Cheez-Its and our
never-ending lasagna covered in cheese baked in the oven and then strawberries put on top of it
and then Luigi on top never-ending breadsticks that thrown underneath. You see, oh, I can't get
up. It's in my can't get away from it. Okay. You're going to take a knowledge quiz.
Try to do your best. Choose the correct answer from the four choices. To answer a question,
you control stick to choose the answer and press the A button. Okay. What kind of natural
disaster took Center Stage and Twister? A tornado. What natural power does Marty use to, uh,
reload my time machine? Lightning. Before he joined Sneakers, where did Crease work?
I don't know. At the FBI. CIA. Awful. I know. What was the name of the town setting for all
three episodes of Back to the Future? New York. I have no idea. What was Axe Adcox's real name
and backdraft? John Adcox. What color is the necktie worn by Lieutenant Columbo in Columbo?
Dark blue. Watch more movies. I have a confession to make. I have never seen any of the Back to the
Future movies. Not even one minute. I don't know how. I don't know how it happened. I don't know
how it's possible. It came out when I was younger, like in my heyday, to watch those movies.
I just didn't, I never saw them. In E.T., what did the hero do to be included in his older brother's
game? I have a confession to make. I've never seen E.T. I've only seen maybe 16 or 17 total
minutes of the movie. He has, like, the clothes on his head and he's like, and he's got these in
laundry and then obviously the flying thing and then the dog, doesn't the dog like sniff him?
Every time that movie came on when I was younger, I fell asleep. In The Mummy,
Imhotep has a human servant. What was his nickname? Johnny. The hero of E.T. was played by D. Wallace.
You need to watch more movies. I don't watch movies. I don't listen to music. I don't watch TV.
Where did the first trouble for Apollo 13 occur? In space. I know that one. In E.T., where did the
hero find E.T. after the alien ran away? At a factory. Who played the villain in the river
wild? Hint, he also appeared in Apollo 13 in Footloose. That would be Kevin Bacon.
In Back to the Future 2, the hoverboard that Marty borrowed cannot fly on...
it cannot fly on water. That makes no sense. The lost world takes place how many years after or
before the original Jurassic Park? It takes place four years after. What is the color of the coat
worn by Lieutenant Columbo in Columbo? Guess what? I know this one. It's beige. What was the logo of
the fragrance company owned by the father in Beethoven? Giant nose. What was the name of
the hero in the Back to the Future series? Hard... Ronald McDonald. Marty McDonald. Marty McFly.
What did the missing $250,000 end up as in charade? Stamps? In Meet Joe Black, what unusual act did
the company president do when he realized that he was dying? He ate cookies during a meeting.
Before he fell over, what did Doc Brown drink in Back to the Future 3?
Coffee, water, juice, whiskey, whiskey, coffee, whiskey. In The Mummy, where was the library where
Evelyn worked? Manhattan. I don't know. You need to watch more movies. In the 1999 version of The Mummy,
what made a Hooman optra visible? Ah, the full moon. When E.T. stumbled near the riverbank,
what kind of animal spotted him? A dog. A grizzly bear. A dog. A grizzly bear. What did Dracula do
in order to sneak into a young woman's bedroom in Dracula 1931? He turned into a bat. He turned
into a bat. What was the weight of the giant man-eating shark in Jaws? Definitely more than
a hundred tons. You need to watch more movies. I don't know. I don't. No, I don't. Any books I've read?
Woodpecker? Any books I've read? How many books have you read? What kind of device was the black
box in Sneakers? Um, it made the best coffee. It broke all codes. In the conclusion of Twister,
what was sucked up by the tornado while Joe was in the barn? Car. The parts are good. What was
different about Marty's girlfriend in the Part 1, 2, and 3 of the Back to the Future series?
Her dress was different. Doc fell in love in Back to the Future 3. What was the name of his special
lady? Clara Clayton. Clara McFly. Clara Simpson. Clara Sim- Clara Clayton. Those are all- Okay.
What inspired Joe to redesign Dorothy for flying in Twister? A whirligig. I weirdly know what that
is. What did E.T. take with him when he left Earth? Shoes. What? He's in like the shoes! Doesn't he
love shoes? In Dragonheart, what was Bowen supposed to teach King Iwan? Who played Bowen in Dragonheart?
No. What did he take with him? Didn't he like- wasn't he like a big fan of like, oh I liked
shoes! I wear clothes! He wore like clothes and shoes and shit. What does a hero's brother live
in Backdraft? What does his hero's brother live in? A car? What, he lives out of his car? No.
During school, Elliot painted a picture of his notebook in E.T. Who was the picture of? Who was
of E.T.? What was Marty's girlfriend's name in Back to the Future? Lorraine. No. Fuck. In his first
test, how many points did Patch Adams score? I haven't seen Patch Adams. This? 100? Who directed
Two Mules for Sister Sara? This is a million dollar question on who wants to be a millionaire.
Who the fuck knows this? I don't know. This person. Why did the boat sink in the closing scene of Jaws?
Well, it's because the shark had- the engine had a problem. The shark destroyed it.
Who directed Duel? It's this guy. In Dragon, the Bruce Lee story, what was the name of the
martial art style that Bruce Lee introduced? Watch more movies. Once exclusively an action movie star,
this actor tried comedy for the first time in Twins. That's a fucking- that's a good movie!
How many years passed between Jaws 2 and Jaws? Even if you're a huge fan of this movie and this
series, I don't think you even know this. Two years? One year? Three years. Which actor starred
in Hitchcock's Rear Window to Catch a Thief and Dial M for Murder? Brace Kelly. In E.T., the students
at school dissected something for class. What was it? Was it Frog? It was Frog. Alfred Hitchcock often
made cameo appearances in his movies. What role did he play in The Birds? Customer at a bird store,
owner of a general store, and elementary school teacher. Fuck! I was pretending to know what I was
doing. In Waterworld, the hero follows a map tattooed on the back of a little girl. What was her name?
You need to watch more movies. When a tornado- there's a lot of questions. When a tornado chase
in Twister went wrong, where did Joe and Bill seek refuge? In the earth. No, it was- it was like in
somewhere. It was like under something, right? It was like under the bridge, right? What kind of instrument
did Marty play at the dance in Back to the Future? Car. I've seen that scene before. Who let Marty
the hero of Back to the Future 2 ride on their hoverboard? That would be Biff. Which prize did
the 20-year-old picture of the hero win in Backdraft? Who directed Spartacus? Tim Burton.
I was gonna pick Stanley fucking Kubrick. I've seen that movie. I saw the Steven. I thought it was a
Universal Studios. Oh, in Back to the Future 3, Marty ordered something at a bar. What was it?
A coffee! Why would you order a gun? What did Denny's give to Karen in Out of Africa?
What does Aunt Meg break in Twister or leg her neck? I don't know fucking anything about movies.
I'm not a movie guy. Which color did Marty dislike in Alfred Hitchcock's Marnie? He didn't like the
color green. Uh, what was Casper a long time ago? Uh, he was always a ghost. He was just a ghost,
always. He was just a ghost. What was the name of the hero's dog in E.T.? I don't know, Harvey.
When Dracula left Transylvania in Dracula, where was he bound? Venice?
No questions have been repeated. This is insane. The Universal Studios are theme parks based on
what? Movies? Cars? What did the hero of Backdraft do when he was late for his job on the first day?
Jumped on the back. He jumped on the fire engine. What was the name of the princess that Imhotep
wanted to resurrect in the mummy? What was a very valuable commodity in Waterworld?
Well, that would be Glass. What was Mr. Kirby's real occupation in Jurassic Park 3?
I don't fucking even remember seeing Jurassic Park 3. These are all such like random movies.
I don't know, he was a fisherman? He was a banker? He was a fisherman. I lost again.
Where did the Mariner in Waterworld take Helen to show her dry land?
Just tell me. Bottom of the sea. Just tell me. Early in Jurassic Park, the Caged Raptors shared
dinner. What was on the menu? It was. Don't tell me about this. It was? Goat was the T-Rex.
Hold on. It was a chicken, I think, or a cow. I believe it was a chicken or I believe it was a
cow. It was a cow. Okay. Back to the Future 2. What was engraved on the stick of the biff from the
future? It was a fist. In E.T., the hero's mother read a book to his little sister. What was the
title of the book? New Japan. What was Evelyn's occupation in the mummy? She was a doctor. Hill
Valley, the town featured in the Back to the Future series, was located in the following state?
California. What was Malcolm's area of study in Jurassic Park? Chaos Theory. Genetics.
It was? I thought it was like he was like a biologist in the mummy. What was the name of
the veteran Air Force pilot? Alfred. I'm gonna lose. I lost again. I lost again. You just pick
him. You pick him. You fucking pick him. You pick him. You pick him. You pick him. You pick him. You
pick him. I'm done picking. I'm done. You pick him. You just do it. You just do it. You do it. I'm
just gonna wait and you tell me. There you go. Who delivered Doc's 70 year old letter to Marty in
Back to the Future 2? That would be a police officer. Just you do him. You do him. Before they
find dry land and water, what kind of bird visited the balloon? It was a sparrow. You do him. You just
do him. What mystical creature was the hero of Dragon Heart? You do this one. What was the
name of the fucking movie? Dragon Heart. What was the name of the dinosaur that ruined the
camp in Jurassic Park? The Lost World. You do this one. You do this one. T-Rex. While chasing
a tornado and twister, Joe watches as something falls from the sky. What was it? Snow. It was
definitely snow. It was snow. It was snow. I know it was snow. It was frogs. You fucking lied to me.
You lied to me like 100 of you. It was all frogs. What was the name of Doc's dog from the past
in Back to the Future? Einstein. In 1915, who founded the Universal City movie studios? Carl.
What was the name of the hero in Jaws? Bill. Tannen Grant. Bill. Bill. We have to get a bigger boat,
Bill. Brody. We've got we've got to get a bigger boat. Brody. Bill. Bill. It was Brody.
What cover did the mysterious killer, Solino, use in The Sting? You do this one.
Who directed Jurassic Park? Steven Spielberg. Where was Prince Inon injured in the opening scene
of Dragon Heart? In the head, probably. Where was it? In the chest. What was the name of the gang
in American Graffiti? The mummies, the pharaohs, the daldoms, the emperors. After you.
What year did Universal Studios Hollywood open? 1964. I believe that's accurate. I think it was
1964. What vehicle did E.T. and his friends use to reach the starship in E.T.? That was the
Okay, good. The author of Jurassic Park, The Lost World is Michael Crichton. What was the name of
the male hero of The Mummy? I don't know. Jason. The hero's son in Liar Liar had a special wish
for his birthday. He wished that his father would snot lie anymore. Stop eating. In which year was
Hatch Adams hospitalized in a psychiatric clinic? 1996. Because, no, yeah, because there's no way,
because the movie came out in like 1995 or something, right? When did the movie come out?
1699. What was the trade of the heroes in Backdrop? The fireman. It doesn't take the game.
In Back to the Future 3, Doc set up his own shop. What was his profession?
Oh, Marty, I'm a gravedigger. Marty, I make graves, right? Yep. Fuck. The setting for the thing was,
oh, we know this one. We know this one because we just had a large experience with this game.
We had a very large experience. That was Antarctica. What was the name of the mythical
place that everyone searched for in Waterworld? It was Dryland. What did the mariner buy when he
visited Atoll in Waterworld? He bought, and who would know this? No one would know this. What was
Helen's occupation in Waterworld? She was a nurse. She was a student. She was a grocer. She
was a gatekeeper. What does that even mean? She was a grover? She was a student. She was a gatekeeper.
Nobody knows these. Who played young Kara in Dragon Heart? Watergate. I don't know.
This, not many of you guys know. I just hurt myself. I just, I just, I had this in my hand
and I slapped it down a little bit hard, kind of on my, what I thought was my thigh.
It wasn't. It wasn't. It wasn't. Michael J. Fox, the star of the Back to the Future series,
is originally from Russia? He's Canadian. What was the year that Jo encountered her first twister?
1999, probably, because the movie came out in like 1996. What the fuck? Doc didn't like one
of Marty's expressions of Back to the Future. Which one was it? Cool. Oh yeah, it's lucky. That's heavy.
What did the mariner do to punish Enola and Helen in Waterworld? Okay, a lot of Waterworld questions.
Way too many. Did Waterworld come out like six months after, before this game released or
something? Cut their hair. What was the name of Marine's, Marnie's horse and Alfred Hitchcock's
Marnie? The name of the horse was, I don't know, telepathy? Telepathy or kamikaze? You, in the mummy,
what was the city who hung up or called City of the Dead? Has to be. Has to be. What was the price
tag for a flying car from the future in Back to the Future 2? Can you do this one?
What kind of dangerous phenomenon was described in the 1991 Firefighters movie with the same name?
Backthraft phenomenon? The movie's named Backthraft. What did Jo use to make the flying
modifications to Dorothy in Twister? I know that one. Who's empty cans? Who directed The Birds?
Have we Alfred Hitchcock? When Patch attended the university in Patch Adams,
what was the name of his roommate? Anybody know this? No, none of you do. I don't have any time.
Mitch? One more. Which actor starred in Out of Africa and The Great Waldo Pepper? Come on,
I needed a list of actors! Actors, actors, actors, actors! Starring Albert Breve. That was fun. That
was a fun game. What were we doing? Oh yeah, I want to ride the Jurassic Park ride and then I'm done.
I need a ticket. I need a ticket and then I'm getting on the fucking Jurassic Park ride.
Even no repeats. That's unbelievable. Did I learn anything? No. Yeah, I learned go watch the movie
Backthraft, Waterworld, and all the Jurassic parks and maybe re-watch Twister. You should watch
Waterworld. The only thing I remember about Waterworld is the guy does the piss in the
Berkey thing at the very beginning of the movie. He literally pisses into a water filter and drinks
it. That's like the first scene of the movie. Give me a pass. E-pass, please. Goodbye. Time
to go to Jurassic Park. Well, that's fucking cool. Wow. Wow. Wow, that's amazing. Jurassic Park and
then that's it and we're gonna move on. We're gonna move on to Animal Crossing. Small wow.
7k people are watching this. Why? You're one of them. You should ask yourself that question.
Oh, he's done. He left. He left. He's gone. Fuck. He didn't get my zinger. He didn't get my like,
got your zinger. All right, let's go. Oh, fuck. Losing viewers. Fuck. What do I do?
Maybe 7k people need more Olive Garden ads.
Jurassic Park. Go. Oh, here we go again with his fucking fantastic map design. Fantastic.
Fantastic map design. It's absolutely fantastic. It's the greatest map I've ever seen. This is not
even it. Stop. What? What? This is not even right. I want to go fucking to Jurassic Park.
Bernie Schwarzenegger? I don't know. I have this. This part is dumb because there's only, there's
like to the right of Jaws, up against Jaws. I don't want to ride Jaws again. I gotta go like
that way. You already did this. I do, but this is like so stupid. It's so hard to,
it's so easy to fuck this up. Universal Studios sucks. Hey, look at that. No. We need Bugleberry.
Oh. Oh. There he was. Here it is. Ready? This is exactly what I was talking about.
I'm walking up. Now I have to walk down. Un-fucking-believable. I lost 87 viewers.
What do you want me to do? Fuck me. What do you want me to do? What do you want me to do about it?
You lost 100. What do you want me to do? What do you want me to do? Pride?
If they attack, aim with the control stick. Press the A button to shoot.
I don't want to listen to this little weirdo anymore. I guess I'm gonna play.
Don't fucking sing. Oh, I hate it. Sorry. Why are we giving a kid a gun?
Something is coming from behind. Here. Fucking seven-year-old. Use the gun.
Hold button. Dude, this game's in the arcade right now. I played this game in Dave and Busters like
fucking like a couple years ago. I think I killed him. I think the T-Rex is dead. Why am I lying
down? Didn't the Velociraptor sound? Didn't they get like out of a toilet bowl or something? Like
they flushed the toilet and like changed it for a second. Why would I shoot the T-Rex air top?
Wait, I have a lock on? They're just hitting themselves with the car. Why do I have a laser?
Okay, that was fun. Panzer Dragoon. Panzer Dragoon. Panzer Dragoon Orta. Right? Stop killing
dinosaurs. What? They're killing me. They're attacking me. Oh my god, it's a million of them.
What? Are they all gonna combine into one giant Velociraptor? So loud. Well, somebody found like
the funny sound effects at the local Radio Shack keyboard. No. What do you mean no? Why
do I look over there? There's nothing over there. This is the longest fucking game. Like,
this is a long ride, man. Let's get out. Play City of Heroes. Okay, I'll go get it. I'll go
down water right now and I'll get it installed and I'll play it right now. It's gonna take like two
hours. I'll go get it today. City of Heroes. Let's go. Don't overuse that voice. That's just me talking.
Fucking City of Blasphemy, guys. Why are we driving up this dinosaur? Hold what button?
Hold. Hold what button? What are you? You're the fucking psycho that just drove up a dinosaur
instead of the road. What am I? What's wrong with me? I can't move. This kid's dead in the back seat.
The kid's dead. Oh. Hey, check this out, dude. I'm gonna fucking drive up the back of this animal
and then go for a huge jump instead of going on the road. What are you doing?
What the fuck is wrong with you? What are you stupid? What are you doing? Why did you do that?
At some point, you have to fucking just hit the eject button. Take a sword and get it.
Why are we doing this? Uh oh, there he is. The Tyrannosaurus. Did you guys know that the T-Rex
is a horn? It's a horn that they fucked up. It's like a French horn that it goes like
and they played around with it in an after effect. I kind of don't care.
It's not it. How's that not it? My god, that's not it. Okay. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. I'll
never please play in this game again. Wait, that's good. Ten community subs from Fries and Shine.
Thanks for the subs, dude. Fries and Shine. Ten fucking subs. Ten community subs. Ten community
subs. We did it. Hey, silver lining on this. We got the one guy olive garden moment from this
game. Now, that is worth it to me. Absolutely. A thousand times.
Matches. That's kind of cool. It like matches everything.
That's really cool. That's cool. It matches a little bit. That's pretty cool. It's a fun game.
Maybe we'll try another one sometime. Excuse me for just a minute. Excuse me just a moment. I have to