Today is a special day. Adventure is ready. It's Gomez time.
Yay. Anytime now. Just you wait. There you go. Yay. Hexagonal rocks. Hexafree.
This thing is vibrating on my peep.
I gotta like lift that up.
Please stop vibrating on Jerma's peep. He's just trying to play the game.
I just want to play Fez. I just want to play this dumb indie game that I heard was good.
Well then it's not dumb is it?
This is pretty dumb what's happening right now.
Is it still vibrating on your peep?
All right, we got 3D inside 2D. All right, cool.
Yeah, that's the plot of the game. You discover the third dimension.
We got like a weird like TV changer beeper that's up in there like telling me like directions.
Can you just enjoy life?
What is this? What is this like McDonald's french fry box?
I don't know.
I wish you could see this. Oh, it's a Fez. It's the Fez.
Yay.
Fezzes are cool. Why is Doctor Who 2?
Wow, all right. This is way more interesting than I thought it was going to be.
The game's breaking.
Why?
I don't know.
I didn't do it.
Like I'm just sitting here playing a 10 million.
All right, you know in regular Nintendo games when it when like the game crashes
and it has like those weird pixelated colored things.
It's doing that right now.
On purpose or?
Yeah, like on purpose.
Oh, you're making it sound so dramatic.
This is so cool.
It just pretended to like restart the computer.
I think you're spoiling the experience for me when I play it
because now it's going to happen to me and I'm not going to think it's cool.
I'm going to think it's boring.
Why am I at the menu again?
Maybe it restarted.
Did I like just did this like just fuck up something went wrong?
I need your help.
I was sent to guide you.
I am gut the hex of Fez.
You've got a fragment.
Give you give you a life story of somebody else.
I got like places to be.
Fuck face.
All right.
On second thought, I'm not sure how much of this game I could even play.
Why?
Because it's going to make me sick.
Stop complaining.
It's artistic.
Hey, honey, you want to kiss me?
Get up there.
Punch this like nerd in the glasses.
Where's the where's like the punch?
Where's the blood?
Where's the punch nerd in glasses button?
I can't open this.
They stole this from Zelda.
That's Zelda copy Zelda.
Zelda.
Twilight princess copied Majora's musk.
This game is a copy of League of Legends.
Why do I really gotta copy League?
See, there's like a person that you control.
This is a League of Legends copy.
Every game has Wukong now that League did it.
I just like fell to my death.
Whoops.
Wow.
League did it first.
What to do?
Should I?
I think I have to go open that.
Yeah, I gotta go open this door.
Scrub doesn't even know what to do.
Remember guys, this is a full let's play of this game.
I guess I got a key.
Hey guys, this is the final episode of this game.
It's funny because it's true.
Hey, this isn't a let's play channel.
It's a first impressions channel.
Yeah, this is my first impression of Fez.
And my first impression is pretty sick.
I bet you go in these doors.
Don't go in the doors.
Too late.
It's going to be something spooky.
No, I suck at fucking playing video games.
I like have no idea what's going on.
Hold on.
Can I spin this world around?
Oh, there's a chest over there.
Oh, I just do it.
I remember how I just said I suck at video games.
Yeah.
What a lie that was.
I just found a secret fucking chest.
Is it Harry?
Is it like a Harry chest?
No, I just got like my second stock.
Is this like a Mario 64 rip off?
What didn't this game rip off?
This game in reality is actually pretty like interesting.
Where are these last two pieces?
Where's my little Navi?
She goes, hey, listen.
Like from the Avatar movie?
Like Navi.
What is the name of the stupid thing from Link?
Legend from Link.
What is the fairy's name?
Navi, right?
There's like a different one every game.
What's the one in Ocarina of Time?
I don't know.
I've never played it.
You've never played Ocarina of Time?
No, I've never played any Zelda game.
The most I've played of a Zelda game was the one for like Nintendo.
Like the very first one I played like 10 minutes of.
Wow.
Oh my God.
You just pissed off every single person in this comment section.
That's either watching and or not watching this.
I'm taking so long to beat the first like tutorial.
It's okay.
It's a first impression.
Shit, I'm so fucking dumb.
No, I died.
Well, thank you so much for watching.
Let's play.
Where's this last cube?
Where's this little cube?
Okay, Star, I will give you a thousand dollars
if you can find where this last like little cube is.
I will turn the game on
and probably catch up to where you are in 30 seconds and find it.
I would probably assume that you would do that.
You'd be able to do that very easily.
This whole video.
Wait, oh, I used one of the keys.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, give me that map, you prick.
Why are you such a dick?
I don't know.
Just like the little virtual pixel guys.
That guy just told me I picked up a map
and he goes, oh, you found a map.
Figure it out for yourself.
I swear to God, that's what he just said.
Aren't you sick of like games holding your hand?
Play a game.
Dude, I'm almost 30.
I need my handheld for stuff like this.
Do you know me?
I know you.
Have we met before?
Yeah.
Do you know me?
I think your name is like Greg.
Still on tutorial level, by the way.
Oh, I found it.
I found it.
This door hasn't been opened.
Yes, there's the last one.
Fez, baby.
Hooray.
You did it.
Yay.
Get a cube.
Get a cube, cube, cube, cube, cube.
You did it.
Now you can unseal the door.
Let's go.
Hooray.
Oh, I died.
Oh, shit.
I'm so impatient.
I just want to drop.
Where's this door that I can unseal?
There it is.
Ladies and gentlemen, that's the tutorial.
Are you ready to begin your adventure?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, listen.
This is outside the village.
Be careful.
Use the world map.
That's OK.
I'm going to get there.
OK, bye.