Alright, have you guys decided on, let's see, potential elimination? Or do we just do Xbox?
I feel like 150 people would like to choose between these two.
So we could eliminate Tier List. Let's do another one. Because I could Tier List either way.
Alright, here we go. Add a neither option? Neither. Well then it's like, alright,
I'll see you later. Again, we're at the stage where it is so, it is too close that
streamer might, streamer, which is me, might just have to pick one of these.
262 to 262? 268 to 264? It's too split. Alright, here we go. I didn't vote? Well vote!
This is the only opportunity you're gonna get. Do both? Both of these things will take
more time than I would like to stay streaming. If I did both. Alright, we're getting close to
where I'm gonna have to turn this down here. Turn this off. People now, oh, every, all I had
to say was let's go. It's still too close to call. Looks like it's pulling away a little bit. It's
pulling away. It's pulling out. I'm gonna have to do it. Oh, it's, oh, we got about, if you haven't
voted, this is your last opportunity. I'm gonna count from 10, starting right now. 10, 9, 8,
wait, hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. People need to have the poll again.
Okay, just in case. This is it. Go do it. 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Thank you for voting.
Family Feud is won. We're gonna play Family Feud for a couple of hours. On the Xbox. So Family
Feud wins anyways. It's close though. Family Feud coming up. Uh, let me just set it up real quick.
I'll be a minute or two because I don't have my Xbox plugged in or anything. So give me, uh,
give me like a minute, give me like two minutes. I'll be right back. All right. Did it work?
Let's see. Where's my Xbox controller? That would be useful. That'd be nice if I actually had it.
I didn't shred this game, right? No. Stay mad. TT tears. Hey, a true champion does not brag about
his win. A true champion does a shitload of interviews and is respected around the goddamn
world, which is essentially kind of the same thing. A true champion does not talk shit.
I got a hopeless fucking captured. Hey, it did. Okay. Uh, all right. Hold on. I gotta change this
thing. I gotta change things to take disclaimer, everybody, just in case. Family Feud. I have to do
this though, because I'm going to be coming in. Hopefully that's enough of a delay. Yeah, this is
2012 Family Feud. We don't have any, but this is not a recent one. Change the title of the stream.
Family Feud 2012. Are you on the Twitch list? I wonder. I am going to do myself a favor here
and I am going to unplug the fucking connect because I just saw a like that's so Raven vision
of me sitting here with no clothes on. So I, I'm going to make sure that don't happen.
All right. We'll get my headphones in the burnout camera. The only difference this time is I, I
don't have a bathroom on. All right. I've updated the stream. All right. Who's ready to go find this
spy. You know what I love the most about anything is when monitors have touch-based fucking controls
on them that don't work like 60% of the time. I love that so much. I love it. I'm using the
Xbox. That's not the right controller. What, what happened to the other one? All right, let's go.
Ow. Let's do it. 2012 Family Feud. I want to do a test to make sure I've synced everything up.
You guys are going to have to help me here. I'm not going to play David. David sucks.
You're doing that thing where you can make me sit and look like I think David sucks.
Okay. You ready? Two, three, one, two, one, two, one, two, three, four. Boomer avatar. What are we
talking about? How are we doing? Good. Challenge. Beach party, high seas, rock and roll, fiesta.
Beach party. Medium. I pick the, do I have to pick my family? I have to, I'm assimilating myself
into another family. Who's the host? No host. No licensing fee for a host. I'm the only one in the
family. I, it's just me. Where's my whole family? Oh shit. Our flights got all fucked up, but they
still had to tape the show. Your score points for every top answer you give for these surveys.
If you give me an answer that's not on the board, I'll give you a strike. When you have three
strikes, the other family can try to steal your points. The family with a top score after four
rounds gets to play for a twenty thousand dollar prize. How do we do that with just me though?
The Kelps versus Tended D Rangoon's family. I guess I'll do it. Why do I have my avatar?
Answers on the board. The best answer gives you control of the board.
And how it works. In the buzzer to answer. We asked 100 people, name someone who might knock
on your hotel room door. Cleaning person. Quick answer. Clean. A clergyman.
Like that answer. A clergyman is going to come knock on your door.
It fills in the blank. It's like an auto correct.
All right, who could knock on the door? I think I'm going to play it. Yep. We're talking about
security. Room service. Pizza guy. All right, who might knock on the hotel room door?
We're talking about a security. A secretary of defense. What?
How could security? Okay, room service is another day on the one I was going to say.
Roofer. Room service. All right, some tiny answer. I don't know what it's going to be though.
One strike. Knock on your door. The front desk? Delivery? Like a delivery, right?
All right, that's... Plumber? Why would a plumber? Pizza? Wouldn't pizza be delivery? Like pizza
delivery delivery? Repair? Like maintenance. Why am I not getting an answer here? Repair guy.
See that answer. God. That's three strikes. There's a chance for a steal.
You can steal all those points just by giving me an answer on the board. I'll repeat the question
for you. So what is it then? I think pizza delivery person. Is that answer on the board?
I said delivery. I win, motherfuckers. Your family wins the round.
Why Beach Party? Bellboy. All right. The manager. Those two out of a hundred are the ones that got
complained on. I would think it would be more than two percent of people that had their radios too
loud in their hotel room. Six answers. Give the best answer and take charge of the board.
Buzz in to answer. Here's the question. We are your family. According to women,
what is the most beautiful thing you have? What do you mean you have? What do you mean you have?
Like me? You're in a hurry. You have. Kids. I like that answer. Let's check the board.
Kids, number one. The most beautiful thing that you have are kids. It's your choice.
I mean, I was going to say. Do you want to play or pass? 2018 Lamborghini Porsche.
That thing's fucking, that's a beautiful car. You'll let the other family take it from here.
I have no idea what these answers are. Oh, okay. What is the most beautiful thing you have?
I'd say dog. A dog. A dog. Dogs. Pets. All right. You got a beautiful dog. Okay. House? I'm just
trying to think of what people would say. Oh, you've got a beautiful home. You've got a beautiful
house. You've got a beautiful house key. Houses? Houses. You've got a beautiful kids. You've got
a beautiful home. You've got a beautiful dog. You've got a beautiful life? Car? Yard. You've
got a beautiful yard. Why can't I just do yard? Why does it have to be yard stick? You have a
beautiful, I was going to say smile. Beautiful smile. Look at you. What nice teeth. Two strikes
now. What nice teeth you have. What beautiful teeth you have. What's the werewolf grandmother?
What'd she say? Beautiful what? Beautiful eyes. My, what beautiful eyes you have. My, what beautiful
teeth you have, right? All the better to see you with. All the better to, okay, what is the most
beautiful thing you have? A ring? Hair. That's a good one. Hair. Your beautiful health insurance.
Good answer. Smile. And then I have no idea what one person said. No, it's not smile. I can't even
get it wrong. Muscles? Skin? Teeth? Did we do teeth? What beautiful, beautiful teeth.
Show me the answer. What? The board has it.
Only one answer left. Beautiful teething ring. That's considered jewelry. What's the last one?
Oh wow, everything like that. Your molars are coming in really good, Nancy. Beautiful clothes?
Clones? Cloth? Oh shit, I'm gonna run out of time. Clothes for the gym. Fuck, I didn't press A.
Time for the steal. Teething ring. They're not gonna get it. The points are yours for the taking.
Just give me an answer from the board. We're talking about. All right, there's no way.
There's only two people that said anything. One person. Dresses. Does that steal the points? I
don't know why you went cross-eyed. Nope. I'll take it. No, the other family keeps the points.
The other family wins the round. What are the other answers? It's less than three.
This was answer number six. Shoes. We're doubling the score for round three.
Let's keep this going. I need one player from each team. These animations are weird. It's
almost like they overly mo-capped them or something. The top five answers are on the board.
This is the type of way you're supposed to perform on a stage for a play.
You're supposed to over-annunciate, over-act so people can see you.
We asked 100 people if you hired a gourmet chef to cook for you,
name a complaint he might have about your kitchen.
No, you shitty olive oil. You're too small. Like that answer. Let's see. There it is. Number one.
That's the number one answer. Not enough tools, not enough ingredients. They're not fresh. You have
like frozen ground beef in the freezer. You have your pantries just full of the same brand of
spaghetti and it was like the get 10 for $10 spaghetti deal. I don't know if I want to do
this one. You're going to pass. They're not going to get it. A microwave. Is that on the board?
Nope. Because a lot of places use them. I got to be ready for a steel though. I'm going to say
ingredients. Counter space. I said small. Did I pick easy? This is medium, right? What do you mean
counter space? Because the counter space is small. What will complain? The light? It's too dark in
here? Holy shit, that was a dumb answer. Okay, the knives. Ingredients. Your tools. Your utensils
are bad. Your ingredients are bad. That's going to be tools. It's dirty. Dirty. Yeah, I think dirty.
Now you have to watch out. Fuck. Stole that. Show us the answer.
Dammit. All right, what's the one that one or two people said? Fill in the blank. Ingredients. It
has to be. Like low quality. It's warm in here. All right, this is the opportunity. What is it?
Rats and pests? No. That's your third strike. Oh shit. Okay, what is it? It's ingredients.
You can steal all those points just by giving me an answer. Low quality. Not fresh.
Ingredients. No. Quality. Frozen. No. Oh no. It smells in there. Spices. Is that answer on the board?
The other family keeps the points. Fine, we have our winner for the round.
The other answers are? You know, I really would like this if you didn't,
if you would just stop spitting in the food. Each answer is worth triple.
Let's keep this going. I need one. Stove. I don't like your stove. Isn't counter space in small?
All right, I got to do this. The top five answers are on the board. Give the best answer and take
charge of the board. The stove is a stove. They're all the same damn thing. Here's the question.
Name a word or phrase that begins with the word string. Cheese. Don't let me stop you. String
cheese. String theory. I'll get all these. Sounds good to me. I'll take that. String.
String theory. String. It's your choice. I don't know other than two of these. Do you want to play
or pass? String bean. String bean. Let's keep going. I'm going to string theory because I said
that immediately. Is it up there? Why is it funny? I don't know. The word string bean is funny. I
don't know why. It is. Excellent. There are no strikes on the board. String beans. Did that just
say string bingus? String cheese. String cheese. String. Like a violin. String violin. String
instrument. All right, what is this last one? String. Guitar. String. String quartet. That's
not a bad idea. Thank you, family. Is that right? Uh oh. That's strike one. String bikini. Is it on
the board? Uh oh. Guys. That's strike two. String bikini. String quartet. String instrument. String.
String silly string. Instruments. I already got instruments up there. String along.
String section. String along. Is that right? Oh. Good job, family. Clear the board. Show me the
link team. And that's how you win. That's how you decimate. You're moving on. That's how you just
absolutely fucking decimate, guys. Thanks for playing. Better luck next time. It's time for
Fast Money. Against me. Do I get to play with him? That was a pretty sick karate move.
That was a good like martial art move. I just did like a spin kick.
You have five surveys to answer but not much time. You have two chances to answer each question.
Chances. We'll add the scores together and give you fast money bonus if you have at least 200
points. Okay. The clock starts when I read the question. Name something a gardener uses that
you would be scared to see your hairstylist using. Shears. No, they use shears. A hose. Okay.
Name a type of food you'd buy from a supermarket's freezer section. Pizza.
Okay. Name a food people eat at a carnival. Corn dog. Funnel cake. Fried dough.
Name a bug that makes some women scream. Spider. Okay. Name a form of transportation you wouldn't
want to use in a rainstorm. Ice skates. A bike. A boat. A bike. A bicycle. Yeah.
Do it again. Fuck. You have five surveys to answer. If you hear this sound then that answer has already
been used. I know because I just used it. The clock starts when I read the question.
A lawnmower. Name something a gardener uses that you'd be scared to see your hairstylist use.
Lawnmower. Name a type of food you'd buy from a supermarket's freezer section. Ice cream.
Name a food people eat at a carnival. Hot dog. Corn dog. Next question. Name a bug that makes
some women scream. Scorpion. Name a form of transportation you wouldn't want to use in a
rainstorm. A um oh you motherfucker why
the answers are in let's see the board a boat because it's like a storm
first we have i'm gonna do it i'll be fine and the survey says not bad start the other answer is
that's gonna be high and the survey says what was number one then what
in the second question first we have pizza and ice cream with number one
what else are people buying in the freezer section that's not pizza and ice cream
that's all that exists there survey said that's the top answer that was do a backflip on stream
the connect is turned on i just did it also said corn dogs the survey says
now i don't think i'm gonna win fast money question number four asked over animated bullshit
70 60 yeah i still have a chance the other answer is a survey said nobody's afraid of scorpions
i am in the fifth and finals first we have bike survey says that was pretty high
the other answer is nothing a 200 point mark no i'll do it again though don't worry
oh
do it again it's time this is exactly like steve carell when he said this is exactly
send me one player from each team six answers i didn't unlock a family feud video we will this
time give the best answer and take charge of the board buzz in to answer we asked 100 people
who would you love to see host the next oscars oh why did i press this this is 2012 um who was
who was the biggest star in 2012 um i'm just i'm just gonna say tom hanks because like everybody
loves tom hanks right like just tom hanks tom and jerry like the cartoon
there's at least one person would have said tom hanks
who would you like to see the host the will smith damn it i'll take it tom hanks wasn't even born
yet it's your choice play this don't pass it to me i have what i'm just gonna name random celebrities
and i'm not gonna get any of these great um i'm gonna google top actors in 2012 no 2011 who would
you like to see the oscars really is that how you spell steve carell show us the answer that's your
first strike steve was shitting he was huge in 2012 jim carrey jim carrey no no who wants jim
carrey to host the oscars who's that who's that magician david copperfield that would be a pretty
fucking crazy show don't you think see if we can just cheat here the other team just trying to
pull any david i should have just said i've just done first names you're not gonna get it come on
conan o'brien is that answer on the board there's no way that's on the board the other family keeps
this family wins the round i got eight points good what are the other i'm actually intrigued
about this number one the number one answer was robin williams this was okay that makes sense
billy crystal is the number three rosie o'donnell look at number four whoopee goldberg
number five mike myers that was so much fun let's do it again it's round two let's keep
this going mike myers i could see it shrek was really popular let's put the top six answers
on the board the best answer gives you control of the board hit the buzzer to answer all right let's
do it i got a chance where to complete wash here name something they sell at a survival store
uh quick answer rope food cans rope no that they don't like that one food
canned food so kit like a first aid kit holy fuck thank god let's go with that
that's that low all right um the camping equipment
computer i'm sorry that they don't sell computers at the survival store fucking
imbecile in fact that was so irrationally awful that i'm gonna let you play
you're going to pass that was so bad a gas cooker no that's your first strike gone what's the next
one boots show me they better not get the the dumb algorithm answer yep they're not gonna get one i
gotta think of one though uh like camping like a tent camping yeah i'll get it a sleeping bag shit
that might be good enough no all right let's do it's gonna be 10
has to be 10 will you lose your points you can steal all those points just by giving me an
what do you say to this question 10s is gonna be number one is that answer on the board
oh yeah 10 points so what was so far up to number one your family wins the round
what is number one one answer was knives yeah canteen flashlight this was answer number six
compass yeah no i knew it was gonna be a knife for round three does that mean i've only won 13
dollars i passed it we didn't even need to know tent was you couldn't you can't tell me the tent
was gonna be at least a good enough answer next to knife tent and knife here's the question
besides potatoes name something you would find in a potato salad mayonnaise don't let me stop you
then a lot of it sounds good to me let's go with that okay in a potato people put all kinds of
weird shit in their potato salads i don't know if i want to your choice do you want to play
or pass we're talking like spices all right i'm going for it people do mustard they do onions
okay i'm gonna go must people do mustard mustard's like a big deal
mustard people so many recipes for potato salad is mustard
what are you guys am i gonna get question marks this whole stream or you're gonna listen to a
fucking chef you guys don't even know what you're eating look at the damn ingredients
let's say uh onions onion rings in there onions egg it's there okay uh some people do
do potato salad they do like salt pepper spices like eggs sometimes people throw some eggs in
there what is some of this but like i'm thinking some of the spices yeah like celery so i'm gonna
do salt and pepper just salt salt and pepper it might be dumb enough to be up there i mean
it's just salt it's gonna be it's people do salt is it up there no all right okay it's gonna be
spices now it's gonna be like dill um paprika some people do celery okay so i don't know how
i don't know how many potato salads i've had with celery in it i don't know about that
okay all right all right this is gonna be chive dill paprika try to chive dill chive olives what
nobody puts olives in potato salad disgusting i'm gonna chives
no not pickles paprika people to pap yeah i said i've said paprika like a hundred times
i've said it like 10 times i'm going for it paprika
everybody puts paprika in the potato salad everybody
you're not gonna steal it this person will say computers ground up video cards pickles nobody
does that no one does pickles i've never had pickles in potato salad before ever that's
unfucking real you steal the points i've never had pickles in a potato salad your family wins the
round it's the fourth round your answers are worth triple points let's keep this going pickles and
potato salad pickles and potato salad with like mustard and give the best answer and take charge
mayo and potato salad is disgusting that's the main ingredient of potato salad is mayonnaise
we asked 100 people name a foreign country whose films are popular in america
yeah france
france sounds good to me french films right yeah yes you got the top spot you're in charge
i'll take a number one answer all you naysayers that's good play or pass i have to play this one
keep going uh uh spanish uh i wanted to say spanish not spain what country fuck show me
the answer italy's also very popular excellent no do i have to keep getting answers before people
start to understand uh i'm gonna say it probably is spain let's see that answer yeah japan
uh japan japan everybody loves japan movies
yeah all those all the animes one strike on the board uh name a foreign country whose
films are popular in america besides france italy japan germany probably let's see it
no second strike united kingdom i that seems too easy though that seems too easy india india united
kingdom that it's gotta be a better i gotta have a better india united i'm gonna say yeah we'll do
united kingdom but that's like too that's too easy i think okay wait this is not like a test of what's
this is but it that makes sense or listen it's probably india it's either india or
it's probably i mean it it's probably india india or china i'm going with india final answer
show us the answer god damn it that's strike three the other team can steal
it's probably china if you have one of the missing answers you win the points our time
they're gonna steal it with they're gonna say china they're like canada
no i did all the work
so what was it this family wins the round i wonder what it was it then let's see not india not china
canada mexico let's see who has the best score it's you you're moving on i win that was a clutch
run for you better luck next time we're going to play fast i gotta win a fast money so i can unlock
a funny video of course you are this is how you can win twenty thousand dollars you have five
this is 2012 20 000 in 2012 that's questions twice that's like 85 grand now that's a lot
the timer starts when i read the question name a place game shows give away trips to
italy next name a bad sport for someone who is afraid of the water uh water polo keep going
me name something that chauvinistic males command their wives to do
uh it probably it's probably cook probably if i were to say okay
name a fruit you might find in a cake strawberry wait yeah next question
name an occasion or event after which you might be broke casino gambling casino the casino how
do i say like the casino gambling gambling uh i right it's time for your second pass
we've got five surveys for you to answer if you hear this sound
fuck then that answer has already been used you have to pick something else the timer starts
when i read the question they have a place game show gives away to hawaii next question
they have a bad sport for someone who is afraid of the water fishing right swimming
uh it's probably clean right fishing is a sport what are you talking about
a fruit you might find in a cake strawberry cheesecake strawberry shortcake blueberry
muffin peach cobbler cherry cake apple lemon lemon lemon uh lemon carrot next name an occasion
or event in which you might be broke slot machine um christmas uh ceremony wedding wedding wedding
the answers are in let's see our event occasion is gambling you're going to gamble with your
friends question the first answer was and the survey said zero they give trips to europe all
the time what the fuck and the survey says top answer well done for the second survey
italy is a huge just like a huge tourist destination and the survey says
you also said and the survey said in question number three we are first we have i'm gonna win
from these probably
the other answer is strawberries and lemon cake
here four eight 14 13 i gotta get like 25 and 25 or 30 30 i didn't even answer the fucking question
never mind the other answer is the survey said top answer well done you've got the answers
do you have the points 19 points no not this time but you still get five dollars per point
that's not too bad it's time to play this is the first round let's get things started
send me one player from each team no video i'm getting that video six answers are on the board
bite desk bite desk bite that's the best answer and take charge of the board buzz in to answer
here's the question name something kids need to take with them to camp let me stop you
um prescriptions like prescriptions i have to get their prescriptions packed
i didn't think of that well let's see your opponent has a chance is there a better answer
let's check the board
get the computer you backpack that's a short round we both saw this is round two
based computer poster what the fuck is going i need one from each team six answers are on the
board give the best answer and take charge we're both like on drugs into answer
here's the question pack a prescription and everyone kid has a prescription
besides a football game name an event that might be held in a football stadium concert quick answer
like that answer let's see now what the hell else do you have in the stadium
answer you're in charge besides concert and a sporting event do you want to play
or pass i'm not sure good luck there's too many answers up there you're going to pass
i would probably really get to and collectively maybe give you like a two or three of them but
there's like seven up there show me the answer the board has it you have no strikes
let's see i thought i thought it was like sports events not i thought it was collectively
ain't gonna be right the rodeo the what the fuck are you talking about rodeo
at the football stadium a graduation of the football stadium the answer they're not going
to get this middle one here you got it there's nothing else that's possible and you fill in the
blank convention in a football stadium let's see that answer good answer you found everything
this is round three each answer is worth double let's keep this going i need one player from ht
a football one six answers all right we're in double points now the best answer gives you
control of the board buzz in to answer here's the question name of famous david you're in a
hurry david copper let's try that on for size i'll take that oh good thing five people i got the i
got the okay david has it off david bowie david sideris i'll take it nothing there i'm afraid
who's david sideris you're in charge guys i don't know about this or i have to play it but am i
gonna come up with a bunch of daves i don't i don't know if i'm gonna be able to do it
david famous david you're going to play david has a lot david bowie david um david's david
david haselhoff show me the answer how is david has a lot david spade no david spade david bowie
is the other one i was gonna do where's that answer who's the number one of one strike david
ortiz no um that's like only like a new england thing uh david david letterman let's see it
you got it do david beckham oh i'm gonna recheck because i'm gonna cheat i don't have any family
members up here guys you are the family david bert there's no beckham david
david and goliath david left no it's not david comma larry it's famous david's not famous larry
david david david decovny how do you spell david decovny david decove oh fuck david famous uh
is it there that's your third strike will you lose your points david linden d
yours for the taking just david from wendy's from the board i'll repeat the question david
from wendy's i would love to say that on the air david brinkley does that steal the point
i'm gonna i'll accept the defeat if it does because i don't okay you steal the points
there's one chance here when i have to get a huge amount of points all right we have our
winner for the round david and busters missing answers the number one answer was king david
king david it's the fourth round your answers that wasn't his name his name wasn't mr king david
famous david it was it was david what was his last name answers are on the board david king
that wasn't his fucking name of the board hit the buzzer to answer we asked 100 people
who's in european country americans enjoy visiting got it italy quick answer like that answer
okay what you're on the board what you're okay we're just gonna name all the european countries
france oh shit ireland no thank no let's go that's not gonna be higher than italy
oh it's time to get all the points it's not on the board it's your choice ireland will you play
france uh england yeah france england spain you're going to play germany amsterdam uh let's do france
is it up there that's not a country i know i'm just saying like that's a place everybody goes
that's the number one answer no strikes on the board france germany uh all right let's probably
do i let's do england is it on the board there it is france england italy germany is it up there
spain germany's up there definitely yep germany and then spain the board has it i have done it
is it on the board and that's how you destroy it and win the game now i have to win
the fast money unlock the video who has the top score you got it get ready for fast money
that's the end of the game for you better luck next time no more stupid answers we're going to
play walk in and get it done are you x stop pretending the fast money okay stand right here
with me this is how you can win 20 000 you have five surveys to answer you'll answer the surveys
twice if your total is 200 points or more you'll win the fast money bonus the timer starts when i
read the question but i have to read the question which is stupid name a feature on your car that
would be nice to have on a supermarket shopping cart uh nitrous um brakes um rear view mirror
side view mirrors horns a horn keep going breaks tell me someone people might keep a picture of
next to their bed grandma grand grandchildren next question name something you need to bake
need something you need to bake a cake an oven next name something that a nurse usually does before
the doctor comes in for an appointment uh blood pressure okay name america's most famous department
store uh-oh um uh macy's walmart macy's k-mart k-mart it's gonna this is 2012 it's probably
k-mart it's gotta be up there now you have to answer the surveys a second time you have five
surveys to answer but not much time k-mart is huge this is 2012 remember this is like seven to eight
years ago something else k-mart wasn't what starts when i read the question it was 10 years ago
and feature on your car that we have tonight on a shopping cart i don't know
break up breaks up my breaks are your hands a radio radio okay the gps tell me someone people
might keep a picture of next to their bed grandchildren parents sibling mother mom mother
father kids just your kids your wife wife kids your kids okay name something you need to bake
a cake eggs name something that the nurses lead up before the doctor comes in reform it temperature
next name america's most famous department store walmart let's check the answers on the board
by the way macy's walmart's not a department store macy's i had it right the first time
everybody just fucking screamed at me i had it right the first time i said macy's
one guy no it was a thousand people survey said come on kids the other answer is
children that's number one
30 40 50 64 about 70 points number three we asked first we have
the survey said the other answer is and the survey says
question number four asked first we have
how do i keep this i'm gonna nail it here
what do i want to add the survey says what do i need the last one
sears it's not walmart and k-mart survey says no i can't i can't win
you also said walmart it could be walmart walmart with like 44 45 points
the survey says it was macy's and sears and shit you've got the answers do you have the points
not this time but you still get five dollars per point that's not too bad
get that video i guess the same family first round it's the same the kelps just kind of want
to go home face off board shows the top five answers the best answer gives you control
of the board buzz in to answer we asked 100 people name a famous howard don't let me stop you
oh
sounds good to me all right oh that's a lot of points yes you've got howard stern howard
but that's not a howard that's a do you want to play or pass no too specific
you're going to pass that's not howard guys this is not this is 2012 general family feud
not like twitch meme feud show me the answer good answer you have no strikes howard hughes
where is it oh shit the board has it i already told you guys the thing that i want to do
eventually after the carnival is that's not a that's not a howard that's a place
a disqualification that's your first strike uh i want to do a family feud where it's custom
the whole thing is custom where you guys i you get pulled we're bringing like 100 people at
a time to do we'll find a way to do it and have like a bunch of questions howard the duck there
you go there's everybody i've wanted to do that for a while but i just don't have any time to do
it on the board get like two families let's see that answer i wouldn't i would never have
ever guessed that you found the ball that was so much fun let's do it again it's round two
let's keep this higher five actors to be a different team that don't know anything about
me on my channel seven answers are on the board it'd be so confusing give the best answer and
take charge of the board hit the buzzer to answer bring in my family we asked 100 people
name someone who wears white gloves dentist chef dentist wait this could be anybody
this could be anyone white gloves mario super mario mickey mouse sounds good to me
all right you're right gloves oh this is gonna be how the hell are you gonna get this
forensic scientist the board this is gonna be tough it's not on the board it's your choice
i kind of need to pass this will you play i don't know if we're gonna get this shit
i'll try michael jackson there's this like i'm trying to think of other a mario let's see it
that's probably number one that's your first strike i was gonna go dentist doctor but they
wear like latex gloves don't they dorks uh doctor is that dentist
doctors don't wear white gloves they wear latex blue blue gloves no dentist wears blue gloves
no dentist not doing dentist um bugs bunny butler that's a good one butler it's not even on here
bugs bunny is it there second strike i have no idea um baseball players batting gloves are
white they can be golfers baseball players golf golf gloves golf gloves batting gloves
no baseball player what the fuck no that means it ain't up there
that's three there's a chance for a steal if mario's up there i'm gonna be
the points are yours for the taking just give me an answer from the board one more time
a skier does that steal no way not a not a chance thank you it's not fair you don't get the point
yes this family wins the round 39 bucks nobody found these answers here's the number three
answer nurse look at number four densest shit number five was band leader this was answer number
six police officer is the number seven answer we're doubling the score for round three
let's keep this going i need one player from each team the board shows the top five answers
here's the question name a space you might land on in monopoly oh i could get all of these
park place boardwalk let's go park place sounds good to me jail will i will destroy
this one let's run with it this is a guaranteed win boardwalk number one it's park place number
two baltic avenue number five your opponent can still beat that free parking oh i win let's run
with it it's there actually three points it's too low it's your choice i i'm playing because
you want to play or pass you're going to play railroads free parking even if i get one x it's
fine let's see it free parking that's the number one answer you have no strikes free parking
okay not free part that's all right first strike community chest chance railroads
you can land on go you can pass go golden no railroad is that right there's um the utilities
the electric company water only one answer left it could be any of these though that's
the tricky part it could be water works it could be um really uh water we're going to do water
works water park is that on the board shit okay it's either the electric company or community
chest or elect a community chest let's see if it's on there commuter train go but it's not go
chance it's not going to be up there it's not going to be up there
i'll try it i don't think it's going to be up there there's that answer i told you that's three
strikes there's a chance for a steal the points are utilities but it's going to be utilities just
the word utilities from the board one more time say something stupid like computer baltic avenue
fuck that was my answer on the board that was my goddamn answer yes take the points they're yours
all right we have our winner for the round this is round four each answer is worth triple
let's keep this going i need one player from each team
yes how do you not say the board shows the top five answers the best answer gives you
the one who controls the railroad the one who controls the railroads i can't run who controls
the railroads controls the game my father taught me that something a pro athlete might keep in
his locker you're in a hurry a suit gatorade water under a towel towel is a good one
i'm stealing that one from the crowd let's try that on for size okay this is unbelievable maybe
your opponent will do better is there a better answer an athlete an answer the pro athlete might
keep in their locker photos take that um this is not a high schooler so much for that round
let's see who has the best score it's you you're they threw that intentionally to win
oh you're not going to fast money this time they just took a knee they just ran the clock out
bastards all right whatever let's play a few two families are this is the first round it's the same
day still at the beach six answers are on the board the best answer gives you control of the
board hit the buzzer to answer here's the i had that monopoly one new york avenue tell me the
worst part about going to be two people sand sand in your underwear sandy sunburn sand
sounds good to me let's check the board it's there what's better answer all right
the smell no it's not there what beach are you going to you're in charge are you sure that's a
beach and not like a toxic waste dump or pass i feel like i'm not going to be able to get these
some of these are going to be really specific you're going to pass
dry the worst part about going to the beach is driving driving to the beach
all right there are no strikes on the board jellyfish let's see it that's one strike
yeah yeah you have to drive your car anywhere if you're going somewhere
parking at the beach let's see it that's not a bad one probably number one good work
one strike show me the answer all right they still missing too
i gotta think of number one then because if they don't get number one
then it may be i think it actually is sand is it up there i can't believe it
the worst part about going to the beach is the sand only one answer left so don't go to the beach
why are you there like electric eels i gotta think of something we're getting fucked up
it's water should we go for water sharks no no no no okay it's not it's water it's water
crash one of the missing answers you win the points leeches leeches are not in the ocean
question going to the beach what's the worst part is it trash is it birds is it the water
is it too cold is it too hot trash litter i'm gonna go with trash glitter litters does that
steal the points what trash is litter what the fuck is it then all right we have our winner for
the round you left out the water this was answer number six seaweed that was so much fun let's do
it again it's round two let's keep this going i need one player from each team someone said
the board shows the top five answers how did the kelps miss that one yeah i don't know
oh you think they would know that one we asked 100 people name something you associate with
eve from the bible you can take this one you're in a hurry let's try that on for size i'll take
that
i'm gonna say apple let's go to the board satan you're standing tall sin satan apple it's your
snake i we can do this one do you want to play or pass snake adam apple sin
eden where's that answer adam apple that's the number one answer there are no strikes on the
board uh it um nudity right let's see it potential yeah nudity adam apple snake eden
is it it's eden right like eden it's eden how does it not eden's not on here
the devil snake satan none of these are on here no satan no devil no even the garden of eden why
wouldn't eden be on here the garden is fucking eden fuck you game eden is the garden one answer
is left on the board naked nude naked feet is that right yeah well naked feet why this is round
three each answer is worth double let's keep this going i need one from each team
the top five answers are on the board give the best answer and take charge of the board
hit the buzzer to answer here we go here's the question name a kind of boat you do not have to
be rich to own let me stop you a canoe kayak kayak right like a kayak or let's try that on
for size let's go with that maybe your opponent will do that is there a better answer all right
a paddle boat and a kayak that's ridiculous your answer there's no way a paddle boat is more
it's less expensive than a kayak will you play or pass kayaks not a boat
but what the hell is it then you're going to pass a car canoe there's that answer
okay we got a number one what's an expensive boat there are no strikes on the board
a sailboat sailboats are like insanely expensive a toy boat is it on the toy boat toy boat toy boat
toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat you try that
um paper boat this is gonna be one paper boat boat a a rowboat a rowboat
rowboat rowboat rowboat row row row rowboat what is number three robot toy
boat one answer is left on the board a dinghy dinghy dinghy dinghy dinghy
how do you spell dinghy a gravy boat it's not gonna be gravy boat is it it better not be
is it a gravy boat gravy boat is it there gravy boat d i h d i h no something else quick a raft
is it there damn it right to raft dinghy an inflatable a d i n a a kayak i already did kayak
a a lifeboat life a life preserver life vest that's not a boat a life jacket a um a what else is there
answer it's strike three you might lose no dinghy what else is possibly up there if you have one of
the missing i tried to spell it d i n d i h a motorboat those are expensive this question
a fishing boat is that answer on the board a fishing boat what do you mean fishing boat
what the fuck are you talking about what's a fish what a fishing boat is a rowboat a fishing boat
is a canoe a fishing boat is a paddle boat a fishing boat is like fucking 75 grand
it's the fourth round your answers are that's like 150 000 dollars
let's keep this going what what do you mean fishing boat six answers are on the board the best answer
gives you control of the board it's 10k it's like 10k for an okay one here's the question who's got
fucking 20k 30k line around for a fishing boat and canoe is number one or number two
let me stop you um like that answer i'll take that a canoe is like it's just like a piece of wood
and fishing boat is on that list one answer it's your inexpensive things will you play or pass
i have to play it i have to try to go for the win let's take it from here skunk deer
i mean but deer no deers are but they're squirrels you have no strikes armadillo i'm sorry i've never
i've never seen an armadillo before so i don't think that's correct i've never seen an armadillo
uh skunk is that on the board skunk yeah good work what the fuck are you talking about
okay uh squirrel where is it let's see it there it is you're right uh raccoon where's that answer
squirrel that's making me laugh i don't even care all right one more left on the board rabbit
is that right uh-oh this is how i win the game it's not armadillo it's not going to be armadillo
please help me it's not armadillo it's not going to be an armadillo snake no is that right what the
fuck i know that animal may as well be in like you cleared the board like this the savannah i got
the safari i've never seen enough there's armadillos in the united states where better lock next time
isn't that armadillo like it's time for two eggs where the hell are they of course you are
stand right here this is how you can win twenty thousand dollars what you have five surveys to
answer but not much you have to listen vegas i've only lived here for like eight months total score
is high enough sorry i don't know all the fucking wildlife the timer starts when i read the question
name something names like people do right after they eat shit i do um lie down no um
i can't why is sleep not on here keep going sleeping those why
they have a sport where the fans might yell crush them monster cars uh hockey
football why it's sleep i can't believe sleep is not there got it name tv show
that focuses on gossip i don't know e where's exclamation point tms with tmz
okay tell me something the queen of england has a lot of chairs rooms in her house gold money
okay name something you would see a lot of in kansas uh open fields corn farms now you have
to answer the surveys a second time sleep what do you do if they eat surveys they don't know
no they don't sleep they don't take sleeping pills then that answer has already been used
you have to pick something else the clock starts when i read the question
clean the names of the people do right after they eat clean clean your teeth clean the pool
it's not clean your teeth dishes next uh crush them hockey that's i still can't get over
hollywood tv show that takes the folks in gossip no any tv show entertain it's e entertainment
tonight there it is next tell me something queen has a lot of go guards body guards
uh dogs t gar i'm gonna say guards next question name something you see a lot of kansas uh kansas
we're not kansas anymore my pretty i if i only had a brain tornado the answers are in let's see the
board for the first question first we have i tried to sleep that sucks the other answer is
and the survey says what the fuck is the number one answer then in the second question
first we have survey says that's the top answer you also said our survey said
hold on question number three it's still possible the first answer was and our survey said
what the other answer is survey said that's the top answer i mean tmz didn't exist it was an
autocorrect answer question number four asked the first answer was and the survey said the other
answer is and the survey says god damn it it's not even mathematically fucking possible
do question number five first we have survey said you also said our survey said
you've got the answers do you have the points but you're not leaving empty handed
i don't understand what this is are they electrocuting me here let's play let's make the families all right
it's the first round let's get things started send me one player from each team
everyone's cheering you're in the middle of a crisis there are four answers on the board
only give the best answer and take charge of the board no i'm not allowed to stop streaming until
i get that video we asked 100 people name a famous woman even oprah might be jealous of
let me stop you oh i mean oprah that's pretty high sounds good to me all right
you have the number one answer you're in charge do you want to play or pass
no okay you're going to pass famous woman even oprah might be jealous of the queen
my fuck is q i wish this was a fucking qwerty keyboard queen victoria what the fuck first
strike i have no idea it's not the queen it's not um oprah's like one of the number one people on
earth who could oprah be jealous of queen elizabeth i don't know guys that's thanks god
famous uh michelle obama was already taken 2012 who is the biggest it could be yeah
bianca's huge it's strike three you might lose those points the points are yours for the taking
just give me an answer from the board i'll repeat the question is that answer on the board
hillary clinton to be up there over over the number the other family keeps the points
your family wins the round i win you left out these answers this was the number two answer
here's the number three answer look at number four angelina jolie second round
angelina jolie let's keep this going i need one player from each team
angelina jolie is not even close and close to queen bianca the best answer gives you control
of the board buzz in to answer here's the question if there were a store called bodybuilders are
us name something you might be able to buy there protein powder don't let me stop you
protein shakes let's try that on for size all right
your opponent has a that doesn't make any sense is there a better answer
there let's run with it
is this like the 1600s
and we're gonna get like a fucking unicycle will you play juggle while i lift weights
you're giving the other family a check okay um weights let's see that answer good weights
spandex protein powder is not on there you have no strikes it's not gonna be it's
equipment um red mill um show us the answer shower exercise machine weights you're right
um like shakes or protein or supple like supplement is that right clothing spandex
is probably already clothing supplements exercise between rates spandex oil show us the answer
strike one gym clothes but that's like i think like that's spandex shoes vitamins supplements
would be vitamins wouldn't it a um towel towels shoes like gym shoes the answer okay shoes what's
this last one has it water bottle one answer left water bottle is that right oh shit that's
i already did shakes didn't work um weights is dumbbells isn't it it's gonna be deodorant
chalk yeah like the uh that's true chalk that's that would be pretty good
or is it that's strike three if it's vitamins then that's bullshit because supplements is on there
what that's the same is better not be vitamins by giving me an answer on the board here's the
question again i already said that answer on the board thank god the other family keeps the points
this family wins the round the other the kelps are just like let's sorry i just i want to sleep
look at number four it is vitamins supplements and vitamins two different answers
each answer is worth double what the hell is a vitamin what does it do let's keep this going
supplements i need one player from each team your fucking nutritional values and shit it's
vitamins the same damn thing six answers are on the board the best answer gives you
control of the board hit the buzzer to answer we asked 100 people name something a woman should
change after getting divorced i don't know you do this one you're in a hurry i like that answer
that's pat you do it let's go to the board look at how many there are oh i should have done it
and passed it in charge play it play it play it play it play it play it play it do you want to
play play it or you want to play this you know you do you motherfucker you'll let the other
take it from here that's 67 percent of the answers are gone we have to okay what do you change
your bank account is that you leave bank you change bank accounts
yep you change your house your dress no strikes on the board your phone number
number show me the answer your address
this one that's less than three it's going to be one person said something just stupid uh address
where's that answer okay name bank account phone number address
your ring change the but locks is address and you know what i mean like you change your address
let me change why would they have the your address so why do they have the locks the key to your new
address no it ain't on there it's not on there guys um yeah why would you change if you change
your address why would you change the locks on your new address change like maybe then change
your looks maybe change like your no that's not on there um change your passwords that's
this is 2012 guys no this is bad um your appearance that shit's not on there either
that's strike two okay insurance change your hair that hairstyle change your hairiness
hairstyle or insurance let's see that answer all right this is important this is the one person
or two people said this next one answer is left on it's either insurance job your job your
change your husband it's not on there i don't think no it's not fuck i'm gonna say job
is it oh fuck that's your third strike will you lose your points it's not insurance the points
are yours for the taking i'll repeat the question for you because no no it's the meme answer it's
the meme answer you motherfuckers you did the meme answer take the points they're yours we have
changed wedding rings
i even did change husband and they wouldn't let me write that no i didn't put in like the funny
five answers are on the board give the best answer and take charge of the board hit the buzzer to
answer here's the question you don't change your nickname for someone named elizabeth
you're in a hurry how many up there sounds good betty liz we can get this all right
number one answer you have the number one answer you're in charge lizzie beth i'm gonna play this we
have to will you play or pass let's take it from here okay uh liz lizzie we'll do lizzie
show me the answer that will do excellent uh beth you have no strikes
strikes bertha is it there liz beth uh lizzie betty betty betsy is that right eliz eliza eliza
right he's a shitty one answer left nicknames for elizabeth show me the answer no strikes
right good game okay now i have to do this i have to try to win fast money alone
show me the winning team come on you've got the top score you're moving on to fast money
that's the end of the game for you i have to focus next time we're going to play fast money are you
i'm gonna relax i can calm down over here do a pause buffer if i need it i will do you want to
win the twenty thousand dollars of course you do we've got five surveys for you to you'll answer
the surveys twice if your total is 200 it looks like i'm controlling him and speaking through
the timer starts when i read the question
in name something that is made out of aluminum can very safe keep going
name an animal that might charge if you get in its way a bull a bullfrog
name a type of program you see on tv late at night talk show and infomercial next question
not porn 2012 guys not no name a specific occupation in which you might have to hurt someone
a a bouncer a a bouncer a bong is a bouncer keep going name something a person might do if they
were having a hard time waking up in the morning something a person might do if they're having a
hard time waking up in the morning um coffee and then a cold shower is a good one for your second
okay don't fuck this up you have five surveys to answer but not much time if you hear this sound
then that answer has already been used those are pretty good answers for the first round
you can screw this up the clock starts when i read the question
name something that is made out of aluminum foil cook with it got name an animal that might charge
if you get in its way a rhino a rhino or i mean rhino is is like the big like okay it's a rhino
a rhino keep going name a type of program you see on late night tv infomercial right
name a specific option which you might have to hurt someone you might have to hurt somebody um
a a a a police officer you know if you like getting okay something happens okay now that
okay and right name something a person might do if they were having a hard time waking up in
the morning set an alarm shower alarm alarm clock those are fucking all good to go we're
gonna we're gonna get that video the answers are in let's see the board in the first survey first
we have luna can and our survey said that's the top answer we're gonna watch that video
and i'm gonna get copyright strike on stream survey says for the second survey
first we have balls gotta be number one has to be survey says top answer well done the other answer
is and our survey said all meaty answers in question number three we are first we have
and the survey said top answer wow the other answer is that's juicing is it gonna be 30 our
survey said the fourth survey said the first answer was a bouncer that's what the survey says
is how many points do i have said the survey says that's the top answer did i do it in the fifth
and finals first we have i did it the survey says top answer here it is well done you also said
and the survey said do you have more than 200 points you win 262 yes you just won 20
you unlocked a new family feud video let's do it i am so happy i'm ready
to do it
videos don't want to see a naked grandma what why is what is that uh thank you adventure mf dan for
the 10 community subs name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
naked grandma neck huh
i don't see that either i know you're right okay nobody wants to see a naked grandma
what are the chances of you breaking in the house and running up into your grandmama naked
looking for the naked grandmama in the house outside in the woods on the blanket
name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
rock naked naked this video is locked
naked all right we're going again this time we're going to rock and roll and we're doing it on heart
this is the final one naked grandma it's time for family this is the first round the game can't
until i get two players up here with me six answers are on the board give the best answer
and take charge of the board buzz in to answer
here's the question naked name something a man might do all day long if his wife let him
do you know in the man in the man cave watch football watch tv like that answer i'll take
that pass the number pass it pass it pass it your choice pass it is gonna be some specific answers
on here or pass pass you're going to pass sleep yeah okay where is it
oh i'm passing to hard ai that's true right on you have no strikes eat is that on the board
no strike all day you would you cook all day if you let me two strikes now do you work in a
restaurant golf all day now that one let's see that answer that's possibly up there
good luck with the other two strikes now you have to watch out fix cars all day right
what excellent why fry relax all day sleep is already up there i'm sorry but you lose
excellent one answer is left on the board read all day why would you be stopped from doing that
why would you be stopped from doing something gaining knowledge
you found the ball and reading all day so much fun let's do it again it's round two let's keep
this going i need from each team all right we have to start playing let's put the top six answers on
the board give the best answer and take charge of the board buzz in to answer here's the question
name something america is running out of what do you say bees um sounds good to me
okay natural resources what are you running out of you're in charge what are you running out of
will you play or pass you're giving the other family a chance is it up military powder
uh-oh that's strike one that's like the one thing that we aren't running out of what
that's like the number one thing that we are not right in short supply it's there one strike
is it there okay match money jobs you're right we got the okay the money running out of jobs
running out of resources okay now what are the other what are the other ones
running out of honesty is that right okay right on not no one would have gotten that
none of us would we would have lost anyways running out of time is it there that's a
bullshit answer though because everybody's running out of time fill in the blank doesn't matter if
it's america europe england any continent it doesn't matter at time intelligence excellent
that's not a time is not an american thing that's it nobody can stop time this is round
three we're all running out of time is worth double all right i gotta win this one let's keep
this going i need one from each team let's put the top six answers on the board give the best
answer and take charge of the board hit the buzzer to answer we asked 100 people i love how in the
middle of this is me a word or phrase jojo begins with is a bad show a phrase that begins with
heart what do you think word or phrase that begins with heart heart heart heart attack
like that answer let's go with that uh-oh good answer your opponent can still beat that
that heartburn all right okay i can play this heart it's your choice heart will you play heart
or pass i have to play because otherwise i just lose the game yeah heart rate let's take it
heart stone that doesn't work here heartfelt heart ache heart throughout they give him the
answers here this is great heartache is that right that's number one that's the top answer
usable there are no strikes on the board heartbeat uh heart drop let's see that answer
heart throb now we need heart rate excellent heart beat not on there heart rate there's that answer
uh-oh that's strike one heartbreak is it there is heart heartbeat one word one answer is left on
the board it's not on here heart transplant is it there heart rate no that's strike two uh-oh
uh-oh this is bad heartless i did heartache already heartless is that on the board
oh no that's strike three the other team can steal there's no way what what else you just
pick a random thing that is hard this is bad just give me an answer from the board we're asking you
this already did heartfelt did i already do i already did heartfelt that steal the points
what did i didn't already do it you made the steal huh your family wins the round
it's the fourth round your answers are worth triple points let's keep this two words
one player from each team let's put the top six answers on because i'm about to just take
it all right now give the best answer and take charge of the board hit the buzzer to answer
here's the question name a soup that begins with cream of cream of mushroom no something cream of
cream of chicken cream of mushroom cream of mushroom like that answer all right bingo
we get to play yes cream of mushroom cream of chicken you're in charge it's gonna be a soup
do you want to play or cream of wheat but that's what is that a that's not a soup cream of broccoli
uh cream of 69 community subs that phylactery which just came in but another like a cream of
cream of broccoli uh phylactery that's that's another is that on the board
it's there cream of corn no strikes on the board but is there is there a cream of corn
soup or is it creamed corn guys cream of celery is it there one guy said that and i like just
believe me i've never heard of that before uh cream of chicken but phylactery thank you
for the fucking insane amount of subs is it on the board that's a shitload of money dude cream
of chicken cream of cream of wheat is not it's not a soup it's like a cereal see cream of potato
is that right cream of potato good cream of tomato spinach is a good one
that's a good one no it's not on here cream of tomato cream of tomato cream of cheese
there it is excellent you cleared the board who has the top score you've got the top score
what you're moving on to fast money how's that make any sense better luck i thought it was worth
quadruple points i thought wait uh triple points where how's that triple points 36 that's 100
that's three what do i had zero triple triple 100 is 300 there's not 100 points on the board
i thought it was they survey 100 people top six out of 100 oh right because like i know what
happened here because this is the last one in the matter it's time for family this is the first
round yeah that's right they wouldn't have the single answers out there because it would be
like naked feet until i get two players up here with me because they think somebody would just
they'd go for somebody oh excuse me sir um what's your favorite kind of uh kind of suit yes you
signed the paper you are one of the hundred people yeah okay uh we're looking for cream of
something he grabs a fucking mic shit and then he fucking walks away and they have to use it
jar what do you say like that answer let's go with that so they do have trouble opening jars
yes you got the top spot cream of lettuce your choice will you play
oh fucking disgusting cream of lettuce soup you'll let the other family take it from here
we come in because we come in at the end we get 500 fucking points there you have trouble opening
up an envelope on the board why how is it how is it hard to open an envelope good work no strikes on
the board how to open a it's hard to open a window
you just tear the envelope open with your hands it's made out of paper it's hard to open presents
oh you're doing so bad right now i'm confident the door hard to open a can of soda
oh i can see that like two oh you want to avoid number i would say wine bottles of
course bottles you know you can it's gonna you get the algorithm's gonna get you with wine bottle
people have trouble opening the door show us the answer
one answer is left that's pretty that's pretty dense
there's that i don't open the door you gotta be fucking kidding me it's there breathing
this is round two i just can't pass ever again let's keep this going i wouldn't know how to play
the top five answers are on the board give the best answer and take charge of the board
buzz in to answer let's go here's the question name something a person might do
if they were having a hard time waking up in the morning what do you have for me alarm
set an alarm we get this set on fire set a flame what set alarm what is this this is
fucking throwing me off alarm clock sounds good to me i'll take that
it's there your opponent can still beat that coffee early bedtime let's check the board
you're on the board but not high enough you're late do you want to play or pass just go to bed
just go to bed earlier right in that email who the fuck are you uh name something a person
might do if they were having a hard time waking up in the morning coffee is it there request
that's the number one answer you have no strikes wait i need to focus shower is it on the board
cold shower coffee long card early bedtime um what's the one answer is left on stay up
just stay up names like a person might do if they are having a hard time waking up the morning
stay up stay awake stay home no uh eat eat eat eat bedtime eat eat eat cereal show me answer
first strike i don't know just wake up late exercise show me the answer uh oh that's two
strikes just sleep just go to sleep sleep in sleep in wait uh just stay with sleep yeah i mean
that's what remember this is like two or three people is it up there oh fuck that's your third
strike will you lose your points please don't get this the points are yours for the taking
just give me an answer from the board i'll repeat the question a person might do if they were having
a hard time waking up in the morning is that answer on the board it's not fair they would do
steroids when they got up just they would just start juicing wins the round let's fill in the
blanks number five was a rooster this is the third round all points count for double let's keep this
going i need so let me get this right it said what would you do if you were sleeping if you wait
what would you do what would a person do if they were having trouble waking up
a rooster answer and take charge of the board buzz in to answer we asked 100 people
what the fuck are you talking surely what do you think sounds good to me all right
give me some famous uh surely sir because i that's the only it's like famous surely
oh i surely i don't have any idea i should pass this one pass this one no you can't i can't ever
pass because the ai knows every single thing i can't pass i can't this is on you guys not me
okay you're going to pass is it on the board good answer you have no strikes there is it
well done is it you think we would have been able to do this we would have had to cheat
we would have just had to cheat at this game and google famous surely can you fill in the blank
is that on the board they got them all didn't even have to try it's there
you cleared the board this is round four each answer is worth triple
62 now this is this is still mathematically possible i need one player from each team
i have to be like naming some titles from the super mario franchise the best answer gives you
control of the board hit the buzzer to answer here's the question name a country that is famous
for fine automobiles what do you think real foreign tough germany i like that answer all right
eight germany japan the united states you're in charge oh this is just another like name
you want to all the countries or pass i have to play it i don't i mean does it just try to
get all the countries you're going to play italy what's an italian car what's that what's a little
what's a little the little gerbil car what's it called yeah yeah yeah good italy there are no
strikes on the board japan let's see that answer germany united states japan well done
um italy let's see it sweden korea show me the answer oh that's your first strike
united kingdom france united kingdom united kingdom united kingdom makes
is it there one of them okay england and well it's either sweden only one answer left france
i'm gonna say france we got two chances here let's see it and that's how you lose the game again
who cleared the board no i won okay let's see who has the best score it's you you're moving on
this is it this is a hard mode better luck next hard mode it's time for fast money whatever it's
called fast money of course you are unlocking new video and then come over here this is how you can
win twenty thousand dollars you have five surveys to answer you'll answer the surveys twice well
i'm gonna do it just to despite just despite what just despite that one guy bonus the timer
starts when i read the question name the noisiest room in the house the laundry room the bathroom
the laundry room the living room the laundry room the living room name a u.s state what people like
to drive convertibles california keep going name an activity you use your hips to do dance
next question without swearing tell me a word people say right after they have made a mistake
crap darn darn uh right dang name of famous jesse jesse uh jesse was that was that show
famous jesse jesse what's his what's his name jesse jesse oh no jesse jane you've got to do it all
again you have five surveys to answer but not much time when you hear this sound pinkman that
means the answer that's like the character's name it's not an actual person something else jesse
what's i'm gonna get i'm gonna fuck that one up the timer starts when i read the question
name the noisiest room in the house the kitchen kitchen like
kitchen okay people drive a lot of convertibles u.s state las vegas
nevada uh no like uh florida or name an activity you use your hips to do
it's not on there next question without swearing darn crap is crap a swear to like 2012 xbox players
oops right jesse help me jesse contura jesse a good one i need a good one
i'm gonna have to go with manjaro that's a good no that's a good one the answers are in let's see
the board for the first question the first answer was and our survey said that's the top answer
got it the other answer is survey says oh i knew it i told you it was going to be the kitchen of
the pots and pans all frying sounds and they'll smoke second question first we have
california's number one has to be our survey says that's the top answer you also said
the survey said we got this we're gonna get another video the third survey asked first we have our
survey said that's the top answer i've already got it it's almost impossible
and the survey says the fourth survey said the first answer was the survey says
not bad oops the other answer is or shoot are they crap the survey said that's the top answer
dang it darn it crap question number five the first answer was survey says top answer
well damn the other answer is and the survey says
holy shit this is a big one the 200 point mark no that's 357
yes you just won 20 000 in fast money you get video totally care about new family feud video
unlocked adventure mf dan thanks for the subs five community sub adventure mf dan ruin a kiss
shereka shakira shereka lady name something that can ruin a kiss a mustache
that is not a good answer the jealous lady looking for a mustache
oh don't try to fix it now i just go back down here talk to the other players
name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
naked grandma i have to say that one again look at this there's there are look at these moments
there are 22 classic moments going on we got naked grandma one more time okay name something
a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
one more i think we gotta get one more of those name something a burglar would not want to see
when he breaks into a house name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks
into a house name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
raw naked grandma neck huh i don't see that either i know you're right okay
nobody wants to see a naked grandma
what are the chances
looking for a naked grandmama in the house outside in the woods on the blanket
okay all right one more one more that's it name something a burglar would not want to see when he
breaks into a house naked grandma all right i got it i'm good it's out of my system
hey that's the end of this frame all right okay all right i'll do it again one more and then
then we're out name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
raw naked grandma name name something name something name something a burglar would not
want to see when he breaks into a house raw okay that's enough of that that's it i will see you
guys later i'll see you in a couple days i it is currently saturday i'll see you guys on tuesday
tuesday uh we will do name something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks into a house
raw naked grandma it's i turned it off it's the cds in my hand i promise okay
we cannot we're not gonna be able to hear that again let's see i've taken the cd out
so anyways uh thank you again everybody i know it's open it's not here you see do you hear that
sound that means it's open the disc is open in fact i if you really if you want me to prove it to you
look there's no i am on my dashboard right now do you see this is the xbox dashboard
so it is impossible for you to fucking hear that again thank you for watching everybody
close the tray it's closed see it's not something a burglar would not want to see when he breaks
into a house raw naked grandma oh shit it's in the house i'll see you guys on tuesday thanks for
joining me thanks for watching that was a fun stream tour area into a family feud i had a good
time we will come back to it it is a friend request and yes i'm gonna have to um i'm gonna
have to make my profile a private i'm gonna have to make a new tended d rangoon
but we'll do the bits and go over the subs too so see you guys tuesday thanks for watching
hopefully we see you again soon we had 10 bucks for a mini clip earlier 10 dollars they say look
at this sandwich this is now a sponsored stream i don't i didn't look there's enough i didn't see
a sandwich there's no sandwich thank you for the 10 dollars i really appreciate it thank you bake
me home for the five dollars uh would a geno me costume be enough to please you or does geno
literally have to be in smash now it's got to be the whole thing it's the whole thing but we got
sans yeah we did what i mean we i don't like that was that wasn't something i wanted i wanted
fucking geno yes you did i i'm happy that sans is in the game but i didn't i wasn't actively hoping
that sans was going to be in the game it's cool i mean i would have i would have loved scrooge
mcduck too but i don't think we're ever going to see that in fact i think we probably see that
before geno think about it but thank you thank you also to gnarly for the 250 when are you going
to play my favorite game you fraud caster have a good night well eventually i have to play every
game because by 2030 i will have i will have played every single one eventually i will thank
you amnestic ow for the 15 this is the song that is supposed to be intended for the devourer of
gods this is from that song mod yeah i never got this mod unfortunately let's let's give it a
listen though this is the song that's terraria calamity mod universal collapse is the name of
this actually plug this in again oh darn it okay dang it here it is all right i'm curious
that's a nice ring to it i don't know what that part was though seems like that was added in
somehow that's a cool song sounds good got a nice ring to it thank you amnestic ow for the 15
dollars it's a lot of money thank you sergeant mars thanks to five dollars please buy a rat
you know i've thought about that before you gotta get two though that's something that would have
to happen how you know i would probably have like a couple of rats i want like a cool bird too i
want like a nice like beautiful bird but i think those kind of things are when you you're at your
at least for me you'd have to be at my like forever home so and by forever home i mean at
least a house that i know i'd be at at least for at least 10 years so maybe i do love rats though
they are awesome uh thank you step step and ma for the five dollars hey germa long time watch
your first time donator i've been really enjoying your streams and second germa videos i want to
make some videos though one of my ideas needs audio where you ask a doctor and a priest
to drill your head for 50 dollars i can't remember which stream or era pre vegas or vegas can you or
chat remember when you made that joke you had headaches during them i don't i have no idea
audio where you ask a doctor and a priest to drill your head for 50 dollars it was during the demon
souls streams demon souls part two apparently hopefully maybe somebody can help you out i
really don't remember i say a lot of things sometimes i don't even have any any memory at
all of ever saying anything somebody will tell me i got show i got sort of clip before when i was
talking about like peeing in my face or something and it was me saying it on camera and i just i
was like when the fuck did i do that i think that's kind of just what happens when so i've
been doing this for eight years right i've been recorded talking and saying random stuff and
talking to you guys for almost a decade so yeah there's there's hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of hours hundreds thousands of hours of me talking so sometimes it's hard to remember the Alzheimer's
is kicking in but i hope you find it whatever you're going to do with it make it keep it classy
make it classy okay but thank you for the five dollars adventure mf dan thanks with 10 community
subs phylacter lich gave 69 community subs hundreds of subs from this person if you don't
know hundreds adventure mf dan 15 total community subs tonight as well actually i think more than
that too i know that might be from the other day but thanks seriously thank you guys some people
give an just insane amount of money to the stream i just hope that you can afford it number one
and number two i am floored that you would even think to give me any money that is even remotely
remotely even countable sometimes i look at the amount of money people give to the stream it's
just like holy shit that's a lot of fucking money so please if you do donate to this stream if you
do sub to this channel make sure that you are capable of doing that completely i should be
way down on your priority list i appreciate it nonetheless thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you speaking of subs uh there are at least the hundred gifted subs today let's take
a look at all the subs today thank you i'll see you guys on tuesday i will have by then so tonight
into tomorrow because i'm i won't be around till tuesday i'm gonna get some real this coming week
here probably i would i'm not gonna give you a date yet on tuesday i will give you a real
true date for a cut off for submissions for the activity book stream and then a date for that as
well it'll probably end up being this coming weekend so the cut i'm just gonna say it right
now here it is this is it has to be this way because obviously the carnival stream is two
weeks from now so what is with this spam what's going on with the spam in this chat room
what's happening with the spam in this room face do it piss on me piss it piss in my face
do it i'm fine i can hold my breath the second i start to smell some feet i can just
who knows if i've ever said that before i don't know um but on tuesday i will give you guys
real dates for this stuff besides obviously you know the carnival stream is the 21st
the activity book stream will be that same week it will end up being somewhere in the middle of
the week or the first the early week of that the week of the 16th so we're gonna get two
you'll get two pretty much back-to-back streams that uh might be pretty interesting well just
the one on the 21st is guaranteed to be so when's the deadline the deadline will end up being
probably this weekend probably like not this weekend but next weekend so either the 13th
or the 14th will be the true hard deadline for any activity book submissions and then after a
few days we'll compile some stuff i'll get some stuff ready and then probably like the i want to
say the 16th the 17th or the 18th or maybe even the 19th no no no no no it'll have to be like
the 16th because i'm going to be gone so it'll be later the 15th 16th or 17th i'll give you a
hard day don't worry you'll know at least a week in advance this is the where's waldo thing yeah and
the dot to dot and random little jokes and shit it's just a thing for fun just a little community
night where people submitted stuff and i do little puzzles on stream and little activity book stuff
that the community has made the where's waldo segment if you don't even if you don't know what
that means people have to make an image where they have i have to find me in the image where's
waldo's style and the only thing i get to do is i have to sit i will have a webcam on i'll have
to sit at least two feet away from the monitor but i get to use the windows magnifying glass
that's a stipulation that i get to have no two feet away from the monitor windows magnifying glass
where's baldo but thank you apple ship for the 250 uh hey who is your hero and idol growing up
uh jim carrey uh jerry lewis believe it or not and probably a few voice actors
there's a ton of them that i could list people like charlie adler tom kenney definitely if you
want if you want seriously if you want to know the the person that made me want to do
you like voices and characters and it's charlie adler it's if you look up to you'll know who he
is cow and chicken the big heads from rocko he's everywhere at least he used to be if you don't
like add big head oh it's me big head rocko all right he was he was incredibly animated incredibly
he his range could go up and down he was it was wonderful that's like my biggest probably
but it's like actual inspiration at least in i don't know if you want to use the words
who did you want to emulate when you were watching cartoons and tv shows it would be him
hopefully that answers your question and then finally uh permanent marks thanks for three bucks
the no message just three dollars from permanent marks thank you take it easy guys i will see all
you wonderful people on tuesday good night take care thanks for joining me as always see you soon
wait hold on wait no no no no no not yet not yet i missed one that just came in a few minutes ago
tyler mike thanks for the 250 germa sorry if this has already been asked but you mentioned a while
ago that you plan on playing classic wow and making a guild for us i wonder when you think
you'll set that up as i wouldn't mind playing but i need to know what server thanks for the laughs
we made a joke about that earlier and i didn't realize so i i try i it's a long time to go from
like one to even from like one to 20 in classic wow is a long ass time and i'm not sure i can
like put the necessary time into doing that it's an interesting thing that i want to do but i don't
like have time to do it right now maybe when all the dust settles i just don't i don't i'm not i
don't have like the really the time to play wow right now and i thought i was going to but then
that was also before some of these big streams came up germa lied about classic wow yep i do
sorry for adding you on xbox please don't delete your account i'm not gonna i just hit 20 the other
day and i had like 24 hours played yeah so it's a commitment especially if you want to do anything
that's you know not picking up squirrel blood hoarder alliance i always played alliance
and that really only is because i liked the way that the humans left the human laugh was like the
biggest dick move if you know if you ganked somebody or like you got in a fight with a
horde and it was you could just sit there you just typed slash lol when they died
it was just like that motherfucker nobody had a laugh like the human alliance ganking omega low
oh the gnome too the gnome laugh i based who i played on is how their laugh was the gnome that
like it's like you nobody can do it you can't replicate it but maybe i don't know i i can't
say definitively if i'm gonna do that if i really get into it i really actually start playing
what i'm i'm gonna be careful though because all things are playing classic wow
i'm gonna level up level 20 you know level 25 30 i love this i remember how fun this was
i'm gonna do this every day what are you streaming tomorrow uh i'm not uh nothing
oh when are you gonna stream again i have uh tuesday okay it's well it's it's tuesday now
yeah you you mean this next tuesday yeah i think you guys want to see wow i don't want to do that
i'll get sucked in but thank you a ap key or app key for the three bucks what's your favorite
power shell what's my favorite command um i i don't know um ip config slash all i don't know
or a trace route to uh i don't know all right i'm out of here see you guys on tuesday take care
good night have a wonderful rest of your evening and a wonderful rest of your next few days
let's see you guys on tuesday goodbye see you take care