Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Testing out stuff. Testing out the stream. Testing out the stream. Testing out stuff. Testing out the stream. Testing out the stream.
Oh, test it. Test it. Alright. Good enough.
Noto!
Oh yeah. Somebody gotta stop that bomb.
Alright, let me get out of here. Let me just get out. Oh, I got a new item. Sick.
Okay. Are we live? I hope so.
Pop this out.
Alright. Okay. Looks like we're live.
Should be. Oh, we are. There we are. Hey guys.
Pop that out.
Okay. There we go.
Let's lower this. Alrighty.
Okay. Hello. Oh, I gotta tell people I'm streaming.
Gonna play some CSGO tonight. Along with some TF2.
Oh, happy St. Patrick's Day everybody. I didn't even say that.
This is a second livestream on YouTube.
Hopefully it goes well. Hopefully nothing explodes.
But yeah, happy St. Patrick's Day. May the luck of the Irish shine upon you.
I'm gonna find a better server than that. I do live in Boston.
One, two, three. I'm reading it. Alright, let's get this going.
Alright, hold on. I gotta tell my Steam group what's going on.
Because I'm trying to do the transition from Twitch to YouTube.
So we'll see how it goes. I got a lot of
mixed responses. A lot of people are like, no, go to Twitch. And then people say, no,
YouTube is much better. It's torn between two different places.
But eventually I'm gonna be able to stream in HD on here.
So that should be pretty cool. And why can't I go to my Steam group?
Oh, right. I'm not even online. Whoops!
Let's get to an event. Saturday YouTube
stream. Oh, potty.
And play. Woohoo!
Alright, let's get a server here. It has nobody in it. Alright, zero out of
28. Arena Lumberyard? I don't know if I wanna go there.
One, two, three. Let's get zero out of 32. Here we go. Here we go.
Zero out of 32. That's what I'm looking for. Warmfront.
Casbah. King of the Hill Nucleus. Let's go to Nucleus.
Alright, guys. This is the server I'm playing on right now.
And here it comes. We'll let everybody go. Yo!
My stream's broken. My stream isn't broken, is it?
Try and refresh it. Give it a good ol' refresh. Alright,
join that. I just put an IP into the chat and that's where I'm gonna be playing.
Oh, using the Floggestinator. I'm not gonna play with that.
Play Soldier. Anybody even in here? Alright, Weston.
If some of you guys could repost the IP, I'd be very grateful.
Give him hell. What's going on, chicken?
So I have a new mouse. We're gonna see how well this goes. How did I not hit that guy?
I got a Razor Deathadder. Ow!
Yeah, Razor Deathadder. It's the blue one. The one that lights up blue.
Never gonna give. Never gonna give. So, a lot of
people can't load the stream. I wonder why. Everything should
be the same as it was last time. Is more than one person having stream problems?
Or is it just one or two people? Error, huh?
Hold on a second. That's weird. The people that are having problems,
what country are you from?
It might be because you're from a country that doesn't support it or something.
YouTube is still in kind of like the beta streaming stages.
Oh my God. I can't believe I...
How? Yeah, I guess if you're having stream problems,
just close out your browser and then come back or clear out
some of your cookies or something like that. I don't know. I wish I knew what was going on.
If everybody was having that problem, I would be like, Darn! I'd have to fix it right away.
Oh, that was so lucky. Oh, you're under the spy?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Let me just look at my own stream and see what happens.
Gonna pull it up for a second here. Just wanna see what it looks like for me.
Expedia. Let's see.
Why did I just get a double add?
I got a double add on my own stream.
Offer a sacrifice to YouTube. I mean, it looks... Yeah, I'll show you guys. We'll do streamception.
It looks alright on my end. I don't know.
I'm not sure, guys. I apologize if it doesn't look like that
on your screen. Oh my God, look at all these people.
High five, baby. Oh, we're gonna get spawn trapped. Everyone's
just in here hanging out. Oh, crit screen. Oh no.
Put a lot of pressure on me here. That's not a spy.
Oh my God. It's lagging so bad.
Oh God. I just hit like a lag patch right there. That wasn't good.
Oh yeah, I'll show my loadouts. Good call. Good call, Luke.
Oh, I just missed your name. Good call, Phoenix. So right now
I'm using the black box, the reserve shooter, and the equalizer. And
I got this stuff on, too. There we go. Let's do it.
Alright, so I'm getting a couple more messages saying the
stream is all screwed up. Now we're gonna do this, right? We'll do this.
I'm not sure if I can even restart it, to be honest. It might like
screw a bunch of stuff up. Yes. We'll go scout.
I got the mad milk. The stock.
Stock. Oh crap. No, die.
Well, the only thing I can say is if people are still having
problems, then this should be uploaded
to YouTube within the next hour or two. You should be able to watch it on
YouTube. I don't know. Maybe I'll try restarting it, because it looks like
more people are having problems. Control point enabled. Get going.
Yeah, it's a razor death adder. I like it. It's good.
I'm not a big fan of big bulky mice, but this is
this fits comfortably. Oh, damn.
Oh my god, they're right outside the door.
That just like scared the crap out of me. No, I'm going this way.
Let's get out of here. Come on, spy. Let's get the hell out of here.
I'm lagging so bad. Look at how bad I'm lagging
right now. Everyone's like a freaking slideshow. Streamception.
Did I kill that guy? I just confused myself.
I can't believe I made it.
Logitech all day.
Yeah, actually, you know what? If some of you guys will notice,
I have quick switch on now. I am not using the regular
non-quick switch anymore, because I can do stuff like this. See how I switch
that? Because I got a button on my thumb now. I can use the button on my thumb
to switch to the melee slot.
Cool, huh? No more slow switch for Jerma.
Those are the days of the past. Oh my god, so many people
up there. Chris Krieg, oh my god.
Hold on, I'm gonna go... I'm going Soldier.
No, no, no, no. Somebody said go Combat Engie. I will.
I will go Combat Engie. Oh my god, they got us like
spawn-trapped. We are spawn-trapped.
Anybody up here? Sentry down. Sentry down?
How am I... It's giving me a break. I got one
hit on that guy. Oh my god, I just realized something.
I don't have the gunslinger on.
Are you serious? Alright, well, whatever. This works.
Nice. Big sentry, baby. Oh no.
Oh no. Oh no, I have no metal. That's fine, take it out.
I don't care. What just even happened to me right there?
What is going on? There's so much lag on this server.
Jerma, the girl I have is... Do you have any dating advice?
Do I have any dating advice? The only
dating advice I could give is... I don't know.
I'm not really the best at... I gotta take this off.
I'm not really the best at dating advice, to be honest. If I had any, I would definitely give it to you.
The only thing I can really say is, don't pretend to be somebody
and not. Because after a while, people find out.
That's pretty much the only advice I can really give. Oh, stair stab.
Where did my sentry even go? What just happened? What even just happened to me?
No, I am not stoned. I am not.
I don't do that. Drug free up in here.
Dating advice. It's a trap.
We gotta get him away from the spawn. I'm going the other way. My god.
Get in the face. Wait, how did I not... No, I'm gonna die.
And that's a spy. Oh yeah, I got like a dozen extra eggs
here. I have two dozen eggs. No, I'm just kidding.
No more eggs for me. Not unless I make a stupid bet with myself.
Oh, did I make it? I made it. Alright, I made it.
Made it out of the spawn door. I'll probably stream for an hour or two.
Oh my god, that just scared the crap out of me.
Yes, I am playing in a window.
I am in a window. Get him off the port.
Punch him in the face. Eggs. No, I'm not from New Jersey.
I'm from Boston. I'm from the bean town. And if you're just joining the stream,
happy St. Patrick's Day. If you happen to be of Irish descent.
I am of Irish descent, so. Later on, after this stream,
I'm going with my family. We're gonna go get some corned beef and cabbage
at a restaurant. Should be a good time. Get to see some
aunts and uncles I haven't seen in a little while, so. Should be cool.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I can't, oh my god.
How did I survive that? Holy crap.
I need like health. I can't believe I survived that.
Come on, come on, come on. Just at least give me like, oh,
what am I doing? My brain just like exploded right there.
I'm trying to like, will I build something and just die with crit?
I idiot. I just ran into a spy. At least I think I did.
Oh, we really, we're doing this well? Overtime?
I'll take that. Oh, jump over the
rocket. I just rocket jumped with his rocket. Right now it is 6pm.
Eastern time. Do I like streaming on Twitch or
YouTube? I think they both have their own little perks. For instance, I think more
people can watch a Twitch livestream because Twitch is available in
more areas. Yeah, Twitch is available
in more places. I think that the reason why people are having problems with this stream
is YouTube streams are not available all over the
place in the world. I'm pretty sure that's the problem people are having.
Is there no damage spread on this server? How did I not hit him?
Don't get yourself killed. Run away. Oh, come on.
No, get that scout.
Oh, what? What is...
Oh, I thought I died from the flamethrower. Arby's
corned beef. You know what? There is no Arby's around here. I wish there was
an Arby's around here. I'd go there every day. Those of you that have Arby's
near you, is it any good? I always see the commercials and I'm like, God, I want one of those
roast beef sandwiches. Spy...
Sure, why not. Mission begins in ten seconds.
Oh, that's fine. That's fine with me. I'll just bump into you.
I'll just bump into you. Look, I am heavy.
Oh my God, that's such baloney. That is
baloney. Slow mo that back. I backstabbed him.
Did we lose? What? How did it...
Hold on, did you guys hear that? It just said, you fail victory. What was that?
You fail victory.
I actually hit him. Hit me with that crit rocket.
Oh, get out of my way. Oh no, get out of my way.
Look, I'm a heavy. A sick minigun.
Oh, boink. Oh, come on, get me behind all
these bastards. My gloves are running
urgently and I'm running wicked slow. That's not like a total giveaway.
You too. No, no, no more heavy disguise.
Oh, this guy's eating a sandwich.
Oh boy. Damn it. So Arby's really is terrible.
My processor, how many gigahertz is your processor? It is 3.6
gigahertz, I believe. It's overclocked. It is an overclocked
Intel i7950.
I'm a real engineer, don't worry. Oh, chaos stab.
Give me a chaos stab. Yeah, I do apologize if you're getting errors on here.
There's not a whole lot I can really do about it besides just not stream.
Come on, back up a little bit.
Damn. I got a GTX 470
NVIDIA. EVGA edition. I think that's also
clocked too. That's overclocked as well. I got a lot of overclocked
stuff. Not going to be good up here.
Get away, get away, get away, get away. Talking about like face
stabs, I still have not gotten a stair stab. Not once
in the entire time I've ever played Team Fortress 2. Never gotten a
Oh my god. A stair stab. Oh, now I did. Nope.
There's like 12 people in this hallway. How did I get killed?
Get that scalp, bastard. Oh, you're not
going to get away. Not going to get away. Let's go
I'm going to go sniper costume. Let's go sniper costume, baby.
Oh, I'm just sniping. Just sniping. Hold on, we got to like be careful
here. Like let me in the spawn. Let me in like the spawn door.
Damn it.
Run away, run away.
Oh no. That would have been my first stair stab ever.
Hey buddy. Damn it. That would have been my first stair stab ever.
I will get one of those damn things.
Damn. How did I not get that? I'm just going to
I'm going to get a stair stab. It's going to happen.
Today we're going to go stair stabbing.
I'll go heavy. We need a heavy. I'll go
Tommy Slav heavy. I got on the
Tommy Slav. What else do I got?
Crit Rocket. Damn. After this round
we're going to go to a new server. Get to a new empty server.
This is my heavy setup. Oh god, five seconds
left. Are we like losing or winning? I don't even remember. Oh, looks like we're winning.
Where's that guy coming from? We did it. Hooray.
I'll follow you to the depths of hell. Alright, new server.
The next server is going to be refresh. Oh,
stair stab with a heavy.
Let's go to
32. Here we go. Stop refresh. Gold Rush.
Control Point Kings. Looks like we're going to go here.
New server for stream.
Here you go. Putting it in the chat right now.
There it is. Everybody go there if you can make it.
I have not played Tribes of San Tony. I'm thinking about getting into it. Thinking about trying to get
into the open beta. I just really haven't had time to be honest.
I've been doing a whole lot of TV watching lately.
Plus I got that new dog and I've been kind of busy lately.
It's been tough to get into new games. At least the last week or so.
Let's go red. How can I keep getting defaulted
to the Pyro spray?
I love that. I want to do that too. Quick! No! Too late.
I'm going to play engineer. I'm going to play real engineer.
I'm going to be a weird engineer. Weird bastard.
Let's put it down. What's my pink?
I can see your comment. Help me build this Pyro. Thanks dude.
My opinion on the very controversial subject of bread.
Well, obviously bread is an incredibly, incredibly controversial
subject. I think that the best kind of bread
is wheat bread. But then of course the white bread will get really irritated
with that. And the rye bread might rise up and take over the wheat
country of Dylstalu. So I like to stay pretty neutral.
Bam! My brain just exploded right there.
What am I doing? I thought I was on offense for a second. Where the hell is
Shibby? Where is Shibby2142? Oh, he's probably working right now.
He's a real working man now.
Do we have six NGs? Oh my god.
Okay. Let's do it.
I'll help you with this at least. It's the least I can do.
Oh my god. Well, it looks like we crashed the server.
Don't worry everybody. We have every entrance secure.
All we need is one pointing down the stairs. And you're talking about hystericalness.
Oh my god. This server is laggy as hell.
Oh my god. Alright, I'm moving. I'm going down here.
I'm going right here. They don't even know I'm here either.
Excuse me, they have revenge crits. That's all I'm caring about right now. I'll change classes
after this. Oh, that's a spy. What?
What? What? What? Oh, it's cause every...
Oh my god. Look at these pinks.
Look at these pinks. Holy crap.
Oh, well it looks like we just broke this guy's server.
Hey, Mr. WLF. Sorry, but we
broke your server. Yeah, new server.
New server. Oh god.
Alright, time just to shoot people with a pistol until I die again and then I'm changing.
Oh, I'm going to go on a tirade. Yeah, new server. This place
is ridiculous. How about...
What is Casbah? Do another refresh. Yeah, somebody
in there had like 900 ping. Oh my god.
Forget that. There we go. We might have to go
into a 24 or a 30. Let's see, this one's 29.
We'll go to capture the flag well. Why not? More spots.
Alright, this is where we're going. This new server.
Here we are. Everyone head there. Hopefully this place doesn't
crash. Yeah, if you're getting the stream error, try closing
out your browser and clearing out your browser history
like your cache and all that and then try coming back in. That seems to have been
working for some people. Hot time!
I just wrote the IP. Oh, let me write
this. I don't think people can... Hold on. Let's try it.
I'm going to write this in the chat just because some people... There we go.
There we go. That didn't go through?
Oh god, this server is like no better.
Yeah, I posted the IP earlier. That's a spy. I like the black box better
personally in my opinion. Oh my word!
I just think the black box is just... I don't know. Oh my god, by the damn
drain!
That was heinous.
Oh man, I've never done so many cartwheels in my life.
Geez. Give me that elf.
Oh, bird of prey mode. I'm going to drill here.
Damn. Mini-saturn.
The enemy has dropped our intelligence. Whoa, what was that?
I just heard a bunch of noise going on over there. You can't use your flames in
here. Whoa. Nice dispenser.
Yeah, screw that train. Now I'm not getting hit by the train again.
That would have been two in a row. That would have been two train travesties
in a row. I don't want to kill that medic.
I'm on fire now. Good for that water. Gotta get in the water.
Where'd he go? Where'd he go? Oh my god. Chaos.
Oh, I'm so dead.
Oh, I'm going to drown. I'm making a run for it. Let's go all the way
to the back of their base. Now they got a big sentry over here.
Oh, not that I can take it out. Oh! No! God! Why did I
crouch? Why did I crouch? Oh my god.
Oh, what the hell?
That was B-U.
You know the rest. L-L. Could have taken that thing out.
Would I like to see TF3? I would love to see a TF3.
I don't think it'll ever happen though. I think they're kind of
going to stick with the community idea thing and let the community run with it and
I'm going to die. I'll play sniper. I'll play sniper with
the cozy camper. I got the coat. Let's see what it looks like. Yeah, see there it is.
Cozy camper. Are there really slot reservations here?
Oh, what am I doing? Why am I running in there like that? Oh, I got the cozy camper.
It doesn't even matter. I'm not going to flinch.
How am I missing this guy? Oh, how are they just
running by us all? Come here, you bastard!
What new items would I like to see in TF? A...
What? Run! Run! No! My friend! Oh, come on.
Come over here. Oh, come on! That would have been sick.
No, get that! A weapon I like to see in TF is a
new engineer primary that's not a shotgun.
I guess they kind of already did that with the Pomsom.
But it's still technically a shotgun. I'd like to see a total
replacement for the shotgun. Damn.
We'll protect that medic. Damn. I got to put all the... I got to put the...
So is it true that this works? The cozy camper works with the huntsman?
Yeah, there's probably some bug in the YouTube streaming right now, to be honest.
Because there should not be double ads playing. That just should not
be happening. Hold on. Are you stuck in an infinite
ad? Infinite ad. Watch it. Ow.
So is the stream... Was it in your sub boxes, guys?
I'm just wondering. Oh, that was sick.
Oh, lag. Because maybe that's another part of the problem.
I've had a couple people say that it's not. It wasn't in their subscription box.
Or it should have been. Oh, too many people attacking.
Oh, no. I don't know. I don't know what to do. Hold on. It is infinite
ads? Are you serious? Oh my god.
This is just a bug in the YouTube streaming. Definitely.
Infinite ads. Give me a break.
Just reload the stream. I have to reload the
stream. Yeah, if you're getting infinite ads, if you get stuck in
an infinite ad, just reload the stream. YouTube.com.
The best website in the world.
Anybody get by the train? Damn it.
I can't see him. He's the flames are blocking him.
Yeah, if you're getting infinite ads, definitely
just reload the stream. Or just come back. Because that's
stupid. That should absolutely not be happening.
Oh, add. Then add. Then add.
That's so dumb.
Oh, that medic is standing still.
I didn't kill the medic? What did I kill? That was weird.
Oh, god. Oh, god. No. Why?
Why? A wee by any car.
Who did I just kill? Can somebody in the
stream, right, that if you're getting like
just reload the browser, if you're getting an infinite ad, like two or three of you say it
because the chat is quite fast.
Because I wouldn't want someone just to sit there and be like, what is going on?
I got crits. Get that health.
No, no, no, no. Get out of the range. After this round I'm going to hop into some CSGO
for a little bit. Should be interesting.
All the things you're seeing are
YouTube streaming bugs apparently. None of this happened last time.
Those of you that were here last time, I don't think I can
restart the stream. That's the problem. The thing with YouTube is once you start
you have to either stop and like remake an event or
I think it's weird like that. I've got a critscreek right now.
Oh, my god. I killed one person.
Infinite ads. Oh, my god. Well, I guess the one
possibly good thing is this thing will be watchable on YouTube.
Hopefully, unless there's more bugs. When do I predict
Oh, he's going to fish kill me. No, he's going to fish kill me. He's going to fish kill me.
He fish killed me.
Alright, we'll go with three more deaths and I'm going to hop on CSGO.
I'll see if there's something I can do on my end. I don't think there is unless
I turn off the stream and then redo another live event.
It takes a little while to set these up on YouTube.
YouTube bugs for the win. Damn, if I only lowered that a little bit.
Where are they getting these crits?
No, that wasn't the medic. What was that? You're going to be
rolling that bacon, buddy. I don't think so. Maybe I'll get like banned.
They're probably going to be like, oh, we saw that you loaded 25,000
bats. You cheated. When in reality, it's just like a bug
on this site. Yeah, CSGO is the new
Counter Strike. It's in beta. Alright, this is my last life.
Last life and I'm going to hop on CSGO. Where am I going? Where is this guy going?
Oh, another one. Oh no, that didn't count. One more life.
YouTube premium. Only $30 a day.
$30 a day.
That's more money than my data plan for my phone is in a
whole month. Oh, I got him to kill himself.
First infinite ad, second...wow. YouTube.
Thank God for YouTube. And then not buggy site at all.
It works perfectly every single time you want to use it.
How did I not hit him? Oh, alright. CSGO time.
Alright, I'm going to disconnect from here. Hold on a
second. Let's figure this out. What the hell is going on? I'm going to...I'm playing my
own stream. Here we go. See what happens.
I'm watching...okay, here's an ad. Let's see what happens after this ad.
Alright, what do you got for me? You're going to give me like another ad? What do you
got? Oh, look! Another ad! Are you serious?
Wow. Alright.
Yeah, this is stupid. Oh my God, YouTube.
Oh, wait! It worked! Okay. I got two.
Oh, thank God for YouTube. Alright.
Can I like...hold on. Let me go to my video manager for a second.
I'm just going to turn off all the ads now. See if I can even do that.
Event dashboard. No, the stream is in good health.
Sure it is. Oh, sure it is. I don't understand.
See, there's like nothing...I have to turn off the stream.
Dumb. Alright, well, your stream is in good health.
Apparently not. Yeah, if you're still having the ad problem
or if you're just barely getting back from it, I apologize. That is not what was supposed
to be happening. Hold on a second. Yeah, see like the only thing I can do
is just like stop broadcasting. Which will turn off everything.
And then I have to like reset up a new event. Well, it should go
right to YouTube. This should be uploaded to YouTube without any BS.
So, I do apologize though. Let's go to
Counter-Strike Go. Oh, right.
The screen is going to go black while I load up Counter-Strike Go.
Counter-Strike Global Offensive. Hold on. Bear with me for
a second. Remove. Add. CS Go.
Okay. So, Counter-Strike
Go is all of a sudden 2,000 people quit the stream.
I wouldn't blame them, man. That's stupid. That's annoying. If I was just sitting there
wanting to watch a livestream and it was like, oh, here you go. Here's like 15 ads
right next to each other in a row. I'd be pissed off too. That's stupid.
How did I get a beta key? From a really
cool dude. His name, he just wants to, he wants to go by Anonymous.
If he's in the stream, if you're in the stream, Anonymous, then thank you so much. You are
amazing. Alright. It looks like we're on, what map are we even on?
I gotta buy stuff. Pistols, let's go with the
Deagle. Do I have enough money for that? I do.
Alright, let's do it. How much is CS Go? It's not out yet. I gotta turn,
my sensitivity is way too high on this. Gotta change that.
Oh, god. Oh, unsensitivity. Keyboard and mouse.
Mouse sensitivity, come down. There we go. Audio.
Bring the audio down. Resume.
Alright, we lost. Alright, that's much better. Dual Berettas, baby.
I need to start saving money. What am I doing?
Click, click. D-Dust is dustier.
It's alright, I just unloaded a clip on you. Whoa, they take a long time
to reload. These things take a long time to reload. Bang.
Bang. I actually like these. I'm gonna keep
these. Let's get a, how much money do I have? Kevlar and helmet.
I'm gonna stick with these. I'm good with these.
Long range pistol attack. Let's get up there. Oh, god.
What am I doing? What did I just pick up? I didn't want that. What was up with that?
I didn't want to pick up that weapon. That was BS.
Is that the P90? Or the PPM, whatever it is? Let's watch this guy.
Let's see how good this guy is. Oh, you just got smashed.
You just got smashed. I think this is coming out in
a couple months maybe? I don't know. There's no release date for it yet. It's in beta.
Let's go PP. Check the PP out.
If I get one car for free, I would want the most expensive car you could ever bake.
I would want like a Lamborghini or like a Bentley. Give me like the
absolute most expensive car you can buy and then like, then I'll just resell it.
Oh, drop zone. Damn. I got one guy. I got
one guy.
Abyss Lord.
Am I like, what's going on? Why is this guy just like sitting here? Is this guy camping with a
deagle? How you get a copy of this isn't it?
You have to go to, you have to take Valve's survey.
They have like a CSGO survey. Oh, the FAMAS and
Kevlar and Hellman. I've been invited to join the group. Kills free gaming.
So is this a burst? This is a lot different than it is in Call of Duty, I'm assuming.
Where is this guy? He's down there. Oh, no.
No, no, no, no. Run away. Ah, I almost got that guy.
He's right there. Ah, damn it.
Boston's good. Boston is good. I like it.
It's kind of cold out here now though. The survey is
if you just type into Google, type in like Conner Strike
Go Beta Survey. I'm sure it'll come up. It'll be on a Valve website or Conner Strike
website. I think you can do it through Steam as well.
Maybe they aren't even doing it anymore. I'm not sure if anybody knows.
Where is the, is it the MP7? The one from
Conner Strike, the original, that I like? I think it might be. I forget.
Oh yeah, they're not even close. Two totally different games. I'm gonna go this way.
I had more luck going this way before. Oh lord.
I'm gonna get flashed. I am gonna get flashed.
Damn, how did I not get that guy? Come on, that's ridiculous.
That is redonkulous. I'm gonna turn my
heat seeking missile thing up, or black screen for a second.
Resume game. The beta ends probably when the game comes out.
A scout asks for a dispenser. Will you give him one?
Actually the questions were kind of weird. It was like,
let me ask you something. What does more damage in a round? The M4A1
or the AK-47? Which one do you think is more powerful?
They ask you like actual real questions about it, so. That's not how
I got into it though. I got, somebody gave me a beta key. I'm gonna go, let's go Terracid.
Would I buy a Ferrari? If I had the money
like to just throw away, I absolutely would. Go to
Berettas. Oh! Yeah, I need to buy a frag.
What am I doing? I'm like not buying anything. Oh, they're behind us too.
Yikes! I'm gonna go around this way. I'm gonna surprise this bastard.
Can I even go around this way? I don't think so. I would love
to hear a joke. Who the hell is everybody? There's only two guys left on the team. There's one.
Oh! I just totally gave myself away.
Oh my god, what an idiot I am. I'm so
stupid. Firing around in the air with dual pistols equals
MLG Pro. Yeah, I wanna buy, I wanna get a rifleman.
Oh, that guy. That guy's unloaded. Oh, you're taking
the survey now? Good, good. I love potatoes. They are unbelievable.
Alright, let me get a, what do we got for heavy?
Lenovo. This thing is 5200 bucks, oh my god.
The Galil, okay. We'll take out the Galil. Nah, I want a grenade.
I want a Molotov. We're doing Molotov right now. How do I
switch to it? Is it, what is it, three? Oh, it's four. Okay, four.
I'm gonna throw it down the hall. Let's throw this down here.
Molotov out!
Whoops. Hey, oh, sorry, I just like totally ruined everything, teammate.
I apologize for that. I thought there was a guy right there next to him. Oh my
god. Oh my god, no. Ah, huh.
Mr. Cammie, I'll say your name. Counter-terrorists win.
I lost all my money. Hmm. I want something with
like a, this thing's got the highest fire rate, huh? None of these are that accurate.
This thing, oh, it's a sniper. Oh, the AWP is
back. I'll go with the Galil. I like the Galil.
I need some more money. I gotta start killing people. Not like running around like an idiot.
Alright, this is where the action is. Oh my,
oh, I knew it. Why did I go around so carelessly?
If I had a frag grenade or if I had a Molotov, that would have been game over.
Super Taco, well, I'm glad to be your hero. If there's
anything I can do to protect this country and this world, I will do it.
This guy is, this guy is so dead.
He had the right idea right there.
Leprechauns. Oh, come on, pull it off. Oh!
Oh, damn. Look at that.
He ended up, he pulled it off. I bet you I will see that comment, TheAwesome.
I bet you I will. Alright, I want to go, I don't want the
shotgun. Let's go with the 5.7. Kelvlar
and I want high explosive grenade.
Alright, I'm not messing around anymore here. Read the word
in Arabic? What word are you talking about? Alright, this is the
magic, magic area. Boom, get blown.
Damn, don't breathe in. Damn.
Reflex just like a cat, baby. I'll take your, I'll take your
PM290, whatever it is. Ah! Every time I start
talking, I'm like, I just get annihilated.
Alright, I'm definitely buying that again. Cause that's like, I did good with that.
And I want, I'll take a flashbang. You can buy more than
one grenade, I think. I don't know why I'm only buying one or two. Be
prepared. What's that from? 15 German
points, what's that from? Be prepared.
Get flashed. I just flashed myself.
Oh,
what an imbecile. I'll take you down too, where are you at, buddy?
Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it.
MLG Glock. I like this gun.
I need to start to stop being a turd and like, do well.
And grenades. I'm gonna go with another Molotov and a high explosive
grenade. I'm gonna have two different grenades. We'll go with the Molotov
first. That's right, Lion King. Lion King, you all get it.
Molotov, baby, what do you say? Let's light it up.
Light it up, baby. What just happened? Oh god, oh my god, no.
No. Oh god, this guy's so mad.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I just killed all my teammates. Oh my god.
Damn it. Damn it, damn it, damn it.
This guy is so mad. I have my voice turned off.
But that guy was definitely screaming at me.
I can guarantee you that. Is this a scope?
It is. Ooh, I think I might like this thing.
Alright, this time I'm not gonna flashbang myself.
Oh, for the love of god. Damn.
Be prepared. Jerma, why was there fruit punch on the floor?
I don't know. People need to stop eating so much fruit punch.
Well, that guy just totally, this guy Killroy just killed the entire team.
He legit just killed every single person. I gotta start using
the SMGs. I am absolutely not one of those guys that can sit
back and do well by aiming. I just need to go like this.
Oh, shit. This guy is so, oh, he's a bot.
Okay, nevermind, he's a bot. And these are all bots?
How come my team has the bots? Alright, let's go. Spray and pray, baby.
Oh my god, how much does it take to kill the guy? What just happened?
Where was that guy? What in the name of god?
I can, can I really? That's pretty cool.
Alright, I'm just, I'm going with just straight up, I want money. Should I? I got money.
What about the shotgun? I'm gonna use the shotgun. Just because
I feel like it. I did play CS Source. I played 1.6.
I wasn't really that good at it though. My brother was really good.
My older brother was really good at Counter-Strike.
Me, not so much. Let me get somebody to just play.
I was trolling for a headshot.
Damn it. That guy's good.
It's not fair. That guy's like too good at this game. I was using the shotgun.
That guy killed Roy. I want to get on his team.
I'm 4 and 9 right now. How, wow, I'm doing the best
on this team? No way. I want to, what's the most expensive
one? MP7. And grenades.
High explosive grenade. And I want a Molotov. Can you put a silencer
on stuff too? Isn't that possible? Alright, this time I'm not going to light
the entire team on fire. I promise. I have played some MMOs. I played
World of Warcraft for so long.
How am I, I can't believe I didn't kill that guy. That headshot of me.
How did I not land one shot on him? That is
ridiculous in my opinion. Ridiculous.
Unless he's like aimbotting. No, he's definitely not.
He's just really good. I'm 4 and 10. Oh, if you die
one more time, you need to eat an egg.
I had the most success, to be totally honest, with the
5.7. Kevlar. Forget about the stupid
grenades. One Molotov. Let's go. I've
only killed people with this weapon. Alright, let's get some area denial down there.
I didn't want this. I didn't want this. I didn't want
that weapon. Dude, this guy Kilroy, seriously, is just like
destroying everybody. Kilroy.
Look at my team and look at their team. Look at how many pros
are on their team. Look at how many scrubs are on my team, including me.
You've got the ultimate scrub, which is me. And then like two of those guys
are like 8 and 2 KDR.
Alright, I'll definitely do that next time, CN. I'll take control
of one of these bot bastards. Oh god.
Hey, white screen. Watch out, watch out. Get out of my way.
I'm so dead. I'm going this way.
Wow, we won. Cool. I shot like five people.
An awesome pro 360 controller user.
I already got the Glock. No, the
R7, sorry. Let's do it. Oh, max
out the pistol ammo. Okay, let's go.
There's going to be somebody right here and I'm going to get frigging headshotted.
And right here. That Kilroy, god damn it, headshot.
Range quit. I'm going in a different lobby.
I'm going somewhere else. Watch me get put right into the same game.
Oh, let's go right into the same game with freaking
Kilroy, the guy with 40 kills and like three deaths.
Yeah, I'm going to get my first Moab in this game.
Why am I not making commentaries about CS? I just got it.
I just got it. I got CS go
probably three or four days ago. Alright, good. Good. This is a
new lobby. Oh, new map too. Very cool.
New map. No, this is Italy, right? This is CS Italy.
Hi, Mexican Koala. How are you? Good to see you.
Need backup. I'm going this way. There we go.
Let's clear this place out, gentlemen. Well, that's how you
win. That's how you win. Alright, I got one.
That's 24 away from a Moab.
Yeah, I don't know when the TF2 update is going to come out, to be honest. I'm not sure.
They've already started rolling out some changes, so probably in the
near future. I'd say in the next, probably in the next couple weeks
you'll probably see some more stuff in TF2. Hopefully, at least.
There's going to be a bunch of people around this corner. Oh, right there. This guy.
If only my reactions were better and I didn't think
that was a teammate. I use a Razor Death Adder.
That's the mouse I use. Oh, take control of the bot. Oh, hey,
what's up, hostages? Oh, no.
I got the hostages. What do we do?
Those poor hostages. Oh, apparently my stream is
just starting. That makes perfect sense. Oh, get away from me.
I got one. Oh, my God. Look at all this fruit punch.
Something happened here. He's right there. He's right
there. Oh, Wayne.
We lost. Oh, that's right. I got my kills when I took control of
bots. Whoops. Oh, we're going to do some sniping.
We're going to do some straight up legit sniping. Oh, yeah, this is going to be
sick. Hell, yeah. Why did the chicken cross the road?
To go meet his family for supper.
Oh, bastard. How am I not hitting you?
Oh, quick scope. What? What? I was going to say,
how did I miss that? That was going to be like, oh, I just die.
I go walk up five feet away from you. Actually, this guy over here.
Where is he? Oh, get
get dominated. Anybody else? There's two more
guys. No, no,
no, no, no. Shoot. Come on, come around the corner.
Where's he going? That scares me. Where'd he go? Where is
that dude? Where the hell is he? Oh, it's what?
What the hell was going on? He was just sitting there?
You bot. All right, we'll do another two or three
rounds. I want to buy... Let's go with
the PP. And I didn't buy the Kevlar. What am I thinking?
Kevlar best. Oh, look at that fire rate.
To get a MOAB, I got to kill more than like one person in a row.
Two of them. Two of them. That's ridiculous.
I can't believe I didn't kill him. That's ridiculous.
I got a GTX 470 from a video. That's the video card I got.
Desert Eagle. Kevlar and helmet.
And a high explosive. Oh, yeah. All right, this
probably would be the last round before I end the stream, because I want to go back and look and see
what was going on. See what kind of errors were happening. This will be
on YouTube if you just came, if you missed the beginning.
Oh, give me the whole line of people.
Oh my god. I didn't kill the whole line. I just killed like four people right there.
Oh, look at that. Ammo conservation. I was just
aiming down there, aiming near heads, and I just killed everybody. But yeah, this is going to be
uploaded to YouTube, so if you missed it, or if you couldn't watch
it or something like that, this will be in your sub box as a watchable
just straight through video. At least I hope it will. Have I
used this gun yet? I don't know. I'm going to go up here. I'm going to go up the log
cabin. Oh, never mind. No, I'm not. It's too much work to do.
This guy stopped talking? Listen to me. He's like, got another flare,
hostages situation. Got it. Yep. Roger.
Oh my. I don't even know how that, I don't even know how
that happened. I don't even know how that happened. I want to watch
that again, because I had a Kevlar...
I don't understand. I don't get it. I'll take control of you,
buddy. Alright. Alright, hostages.
Let's talk business. What do you know about the operation?
Too late, you didn't answer fast enough. What about you?
You like seeing your friend get shot like that? What do you know about the organization X?
Oh, I don't know. I'm so scared, please just let me get... That's not the
right answer. Oh, they rescued them.
It's alright.
Don't ask me
how that happened. I don't understand. I don't understand.
Oh, this is the Og. I didn't even see this. I used to love
the Og. The Og. A-U-G.
The Oggy. Come on, show yourself. Another here.
Get out of my way. Get out of here.
What am I doing? What are you doing? You're a bot. You listen to me.
I can't kill him.
Oh, look. I'm going to be the only one left. What's going on, random vids?
I was going to shoot the chicken. I was going to shoot the chicken.
How come these are all just bots? I just went to quick
match. It's not like I said, please play with bots only.
I just went into quick match. I don't understand.
I kind of want to just die. Ready? Oh, this is going to be funny.
Do any of those guys have grenades?
I hope they do. I just went so high.
Alright, let's see. I want this guy. Where are the hostages?
Where are the hostages? Oh my god, the entire team is right
there.
Come on. Ah, damn it. Alright, guys.
That's enough for me. See, watch. Ready? Exit to main menu. I went to
quick match. Did I do quick match or create a game? I think I just did quick match.
I don't know. But yeah.
Thanks everybody for coming. If you missed it or if you
were having problems with the stream earlier, this should all be uploaded to
YouTube so you can watch the whole stream if you want from beginning to end.
Thank you guys for watching. And I do apologize. I'm sorry for
the shenanigans that happened earlier.
I don't even know what was happening. Everyone was getting like 50 ads in a row.
That's not how it was set up. I apologize if you were having
problems. But yeah, thank you guys so much. I'll talk to you guys soon.
And take care everybody. Next stream is going to be next
Saturday probably. Or, you know, I might do one during the week. I'm not sure yet.
I don't know. I'm not sure. I assume
that I'll probably do one, if not this coming Saturday at six,
then probably like Thursday
or Wednesday, something like that, if I end up doing a midweek one. But I will check you
guys soon. Thank you everybody. Goodbye. See ya.
Actually, how do I turn it off? I don't even know how to
turn off my YouTube stream. Hold on.
I can't stop streaming.
Oh, let me just go to YouTube.com. What if it was just locked forever?
Like, oh sorry, you're stuck on YouTube for the rest of your life.
What is going on? Why can't I? Oh, I gotta open up a new tab.
Here we go. Okay. Here we go. There it is.
Alright, yep. Thank you guys. See you soon. Take care everybody.