Hey, what is going on guys? It's Jerma with a gameplay commentary.
This time I'm on King of the Hill Badlands as a Soldier, and I'm using the default rocket
launcher, the buff banner, and the riding crop, making this heavy run frigging a thousand
miles per hour, getting them right up to the front lines.
Kill a Soldier and I get murked in two seconds by these hippies that were here.
The only thing I changed from the Uber update is the riding crop, the disciplinary action
is the only item I took from the Uber update, because I can't use the other, hold on, this
is really funny. This spy is AFK the entire match, and I use
him the entire match to run really fast out of the spawn.
I'm not sure if it was a good idea or not, because I could probably have just ran out,
and I don't know if I was wasting my time or not, but I figured that if he was watching
at some point and just see it happen, I thought it would be funny.
Kill this heavy medic pair with an instant crit rocket, I am a jerk for doing that, I'm
sorry, whoever that heavy was. But back to what I was saying before, this is my default
setup usually, if I did not have the riding crop, I would have the equalizer, and I'm
so glad I could change. Speaking of the buff banner, here it is right
here, and oh, I killed two engineers with one rocket, but the sentry kills me.
If I had known that sentry was there, I would not have taken that route, obviously, but
I love the buff banner. It gimps you a little bit when you don't have
the shotgun, but it's something about giving every single person around you many crits,
and even for you, it's gotten me out of a lot of trouble when I'm stuck in a corner
somewhere and I have it, and I use it, and I kill four or five people.
So I like to use it, I couldn't use the new rocket launcher, I tried, I know I said in
a previous video in the uber update item demonstration video that I was going to try really hard
to use it, I did, I tried using it in about six or seven different servers, and I just
couldn't, it was good, I liked it, but that third rocket, sorry, that fourth rocket not
being there, they were like at least four or five times, I counted, where I would have
killed somebody with the fourth rocket and it just didn't happen, and I just can't use
it. Hey, what's going on, Spy, how are you? I'm
good, thanks. So I don't really play Soldier that often, Soldier's not really like one
of my classes, quote unquote, but I figured I don't have a Soldier gameplay, and some
of you guys probably will ask for it, so here is one of the probably few Soldier gameplays
I do, and I do okay, I do pretty well, I think I'm the number one scorer at the end of the
round, but King of the Hill maps are a lot of fun, they can get a little chaotic though,
as in most King of the Hill maps, the spawn points are really, really, really close to
the point, and you can get into a lot of trouble with spawn camping and stuff like that, like
as in right here, I kind of back off, I would have died definitely anyways, but you never
know what people are going to consider spawn camping, so you just let people come out,
don't spawn camp, don't be a jerk. So I have the buff banner now, and I blow the horny
horn, try and get a few of my guys to get crits, I kill this Heavy with another random
crit, I think that's the second time that's happened, again I'm really sorry, but it probably
wouldn't have mattered, I hear an engineer building, I couldn't find it, I find it here,
I eventually get killed, I think, no, I come around this corner here and I do a super swing
shoot, and I kill that sniper, I thought that was pretty cool, because I'm not really, I'm
not that great with Soldier, I, that's to me to do something like that, I was like,
nice, that was a pretty sick thing I did, kill that spy, come up around the corner,
we got a minute left, trying to get this Heavy, don't get him, he gets me with his default
minigun, which you don't see very many of those as of today, after the Uber update,
so anyone that's not using the Tomislav, good for you, because it's good to have it spread
out a little bit, not have every single person use the new things, and that's another reason
why I could be using the Liberty Launcher right now, but everybody and their grandmother
is using it right now, same thing with the Tomislav, pretty much all the new items, it's,
I mean, I understand people are trying to get used to him, me and the Soldier sprinting
up here, we both take out this Heavy together, see how unbelievably useful the riding crop
is, so stop using the Equalizer, use the riding crop, so they get on the point here, and I
only have three health, so I'm trying to just sneak over here and pick somebody off, I get
one person, but it doesn't matter, and this screenshot is great, according to the kill
feed, it didn't turn out so well, so they get the point, and we're stuck in overtime
now, and this is kind of how King of the Hill maps go sometimes, you know, you'll be down
to the wire, you'll win, essentially your team wins, and the other team at overtime
gets it back, and a lot of times, from here on out, they will win this match, that's why
King of the Hill is interesting, because you never know what's really going to happen,
so this is kind of embarrassing, I kill this Soldier, and then I get destroyed by a Medic's
Bonesaw Crit, and I was saying when that happened, I was like, oh, maybe I can like cut that
out and nobody will notice, but, I mean, I left it, but I'm not going to take it out,
I promise, this is the last time I'm going to use you for my own gain, so get out here
to the last point, they only have one minute left, and thanks to this guy up here, this
Soldier that was up there firing, doing suppressing fire, we got to keep the point, we end up
getting everybody on it, and we are the Weenas!
So this next clip here, it's kind of like a bonus clip, I guess you could say, it's
me as a spy on Nucleus, I don't use the Eternal Reward at all, it's an Eternal Reward gameplay,
but I figured because I was showcasing the Soldier, which is something I don't do that
often, I would just put this in here, I was a little late, as you can see, it's about
two minutes on each side right now, and I managed to get to the top score position,
so I think that was pretty cool, I have to come in late, so I get a couple kills here,
I get this Soldier, I get this Sniper too, and just to talk about what I don't like about
the Eternal Reward, why I never use it, I think it's very counterintuitive as playing
a spy, I think you should not have to run behind every single person to get your first
kill, I don't know, it's not a philosophy I agree with, this is a cool headshot right
here, I'm the Scout, I get the kill, but it's something that I don't agree with, I think
that as a spy, you're supposed to, the core gameplay as a spy is you're supposed to blend
in and fool people and use people's ignorances to your advantage, I think with this knife
you just can't really do that, because right now I'm just running around as a red spy,
and it's right there, everybody knows it, and spies are a red flag in this game, spies
and medics in this game are red flags, if you see a spy, you kill it, and you do everything
you can to kill it, otherwise you didn't do your job, oh spy, I didn't kill that spy,
same thing with a medic, if you see a medic, it's just a big red flag, and I know a lot
of you guys use this knife on offense when you're playing in a control point map or a
payload map, I just don't understand how you guys can do that, it's just too hard, see
king of the hill maps, it's easy to get behind people because everyone's all over the place,
by the way here's a quick tip if you guys don't know, if you sap a building and no one's
around, take your revolver out and shoot it a couple times, it will die ten times faster
than if you just sapped it and ran away, and you shouldn't sap it and run away if no one's
around because you'll look in the top right corner of the screen in the notification area
and find out, oh the engineer just came back and got rid of the sapper, so give it a few
shots and I guarantee you that the engineer will not even have time to react, even if
the engineer happens to be ten feet away, you can take out a full sentry before he even
realizes what's going on, even if he gets there, don't freak out, still do it because
you can really take down a sentry like that, see right here I didn't have a disguise and
I ran out of cloak, so I'm a red flag like I was saying before, but it doesn't matter,
our team handles it pretty well, we end up winning the round and as you can see I made
it to the bottom of the chart there when I came in, about half way through the match,
so that's pretty cool, I want to announce this right now too, if I get 500 subscribers,
I will do a video showcasing me in real life, you'll get to see me in real life, finally
the man behind the mask, and I'm going to do a workout exercise video to try and pump
some of you guys up, so you'll be able to watch that video and go listen to what I tell
you and you'll get fucking huge donations, but anyways for real though, thanks a lot
guys you guys, all this means a lot to me, it's awesome, so shoot for 500!