Hello ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, it's me Anthony Wimbleton here with another German 9.85 shoutcast on his Shadow of a Team Fortress 2.
I got a lot of requests to get back into this and do another shoutcast, so I'm gonna start it here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, let's do it!
Playing right now is the Soldier with the black box and the shock and the default shock and actually it is strange, I'm sorry about that.
And I have on the frying pan, I think I do.
Playing with the black box right now, when you use the black box, when you shoot somebody and you make direct contact with them,
you get plus 15 health added to your total health.
It is amazing, unbelievable Soldier item.
Playing on King of the Hill Harvest Final right now, one of the more fun maps in Team Fortress 2, especially for King of the Hill maps.
Getting this started now, Jerma comes out here, shoots a rocket to the right side and look at the point capture, it is almost capped for the red team.
Spy almost gets the backstab on Jerma, but he's not smart enough to get behind him, so Jerma's okay.
Sniper right here, Jerma gets a couple of rockets on him, gets the final shot on him and kills him.
Jerma is fine, ran and dandy.
Unfortunately, the medic went down and Jerma is very saddened by that, but Jerma is now trying to defend the point.
We got a couple of people coming on here, Scout gets on the point, Jerma gets a malpiro coming on here now, Jerma is okay.
He may be on fire, but Jerma has the confidence of 15 balls running in the ball parade.
If you've never seen the ball parade, it's a very, very interesting thing, funny to watch.
If you want to check it out, go to www.BallParadeIsAwesomeAndFun.com.
That website does not exist, I just made it up, please do not go there and waste your time.
Jerma gets the health back and is now on fire again.
When I say that, I mean that metaphorically, now he's on fire with the shots.
Prime example right here, Jerma turns around, sees an enemy pyro, shooting a friendly pyro.
Which one's the right pyro? Just like a mystery movie on TV, he makes the right decision.
Enemy Spy gets blown up as well, and now he got a soldier on soldier fight right here with Jerma versus this dude.
We don't know his name, I'm not sure, I'll find out.
He gets a couple of shots and exchanging fire.
What's gonna happen here? He's getting no more shots, that pulls out the shot, can equalize and run away.
Does he get the- he gets the shot right in his back, unbelievable display of athleticism.
I gotta bring in one of my colleagues right now to try and explain what just happened.
Everyone, please welcome David from the mail room.
David, how can you analyze that situation? What just happened?
That was pretty cool.
Yeah, I'm sure it was pretty cool, David, but the real reason why I invited you up here was because I'm actually firing you.
So you're fired, thanks for coming, your performance has been pretty lackluster, et cetera, et cetera.
See you later, thanks for coming.
Take a look now at the bottom portion of your screen.
You will see that the enemy just capped the point, which is bad news,
cause Jerma and his medic could have been out here protecting it, but they were in that choke point the whole time.
Getting a couple of shotgun shots on that soldier, and he gets a blind fire shot on exactly what I'm not sure,
but he kills whatever the hell was in there.
Medic now has a hundred percent uber charge.
Jerma, this pyro, and his medic trying to find a way back onto the point to take it back to square one for the blue team.
Scout gets on the point. He is not a factor because he's on fire and runs away, frankly.
They got the point captured right here, and this is where things get really, really rocky for the blue team.
Here comes the entire red team. Here comes Puff, the uber.
Kaboom! There they all go, everyone's dead, absolutely fantastic.
Trying to find somebody to shoot at, they're covered in the uber charge goo.
Looking to the left, Jerma sees a sniper and a scout,
but he doesn't want to go deal with him because, as we all know, he wants to find the heavy medic pair again,
straight ahead towards the spawn area.
And sure as sheep's milk, he finds him, shoots the heavy, and shoots the medic with a couple of shotgun shots.
That was exactly what he was looking for.
Jerma and his medic now come out to the courtyard area, get lit on fire by a pyro.
He's going for the extinguisher kill. He does not get it.
Jerma gets him with a shotgun kill.
Treading backwards now, Jerma does not want to get shot in the face by anybody.
Lots of people around here on the red team.
Jerma finds a way backwards, and here comes another enemy pyro.
Jerma gets the lucky shot on him. Unbelievable.
Whipping around this corner, Jerma sees a disguised spy, gets him with a lucky crit.
Not sure if he's a dead ringer or not, but it doesn't matter because he checks this demo man behind him anyways.
It's not a dead ringer.
Runging now down towards this heavy, Jerma's being a really risky bastard.
Is he going to get the shot? One, two, three, oh no!
Jerma dies, and that is going to be the end of the shoutcast because I'm...
out of breath.
So if you're wondering why I decided to do this, I wanted to put a one-life gameplay
and a shoutcast together because I got a lot of good responses from both of those two things.
People like the shoutcast, people like the one-life series, so I figure why not combine them?
And technically what you're seeing now is not any more of the one-life gameplay,
but like you all know, I do not like to have gameplays that last less than three, four, five minutes.
So I'm going to talk to you about one more thing here.
So if you are familiar with my Facebook, then you already know this and I don't have to tell you again,
but for those of you that do not know, I am now a Machinima Respawn Director.
I mentioned it in my Q&A answers video, maybe for a second or two,
but Grandpa is going to have a show on Machinima Respawn now.
I will let you guys know whenever that happens, whenever it's going to be up there.
I can't wait to get started. I can't wait to get my first upload on there.
I am going crazy right now. I'm going to work so hard on this, guys.
Thank you, everybody.
This is to every single one of you out there that subscribed, that liked, that favored,
that do everything, that do anything you guys do to support this channel.
I'm totally grateful and I always will be grateful.
And for the first person that subscribed to this channel, the first guy, you rock, dude.
And the guy that just subscribed two seconds ago, all you guys rock.
You guys are all amazing and hopefully that this series will take off
and maybe get some more support, maybe get some more channel growth.
Who knows what's going to happen, but thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. I will see you all next time and take care, everybody.