Alright, let me change this to just chatting. Well, they were going to fix it tomorrow,
apparently, so let's really hope that they do. Rage 2 stream? I don't need any more rage.
I'm at like rage 10. I'm not at a rage 2 out of 10. I'm at like an 8 out of 10 for rage.
Use transformer to complain about cocks. Alright, we might as well.
We just need like audio for that anyways. I told you not to do cocks. This is the only
company. There's two companies here. It's cocks of CenturyLink and they're both dog shit.
There's no, you can't win. You don't, you're there, you cannot win with North American
internet. You have to roll dice. Just start your own company. I have CenturyLink. It's dog shit.
Like Google Fiber and there's like, why do you think everyone's moving to one
fucking city in this country that's a streamer? Because it's the only place with like real
reliable like fiber and they're not even doing that anymore. Didn't they can that?
Remove shirt. Jerma's next up to be Sibyl's boyfriend? I don't know about that. Oh,
Jax net. Oh, it's because I'm right here. I see what you mean. I'm willing to let this
try to work itself out before I completely, you know, throw in the towel here.
Jax net. I need to move this camera. Hey, let's just stretch me out. I'll just look
bigger. Oh, that doesn't work. Alright, so what do you guys want to talk about?
Ask me anything. Ask ask me literally anything. What is that shaped hair? It's called ice cream
melting over the side of the cone. Ask for that next time you go there. You got a job as a
substitute and any tips for a substitute teacher job? Um, yeah, it's I would pass that down to
any generation that wanted it. Any generation? Would you consider yourself a 90s kid? I mean,
I was born in 85. I got to change the title here to like frames are depleting. Oh, is it already
there? I think we're there, right? Would you watch this clip earlier in the stream? What did
I do earlier in the stream? God, you're so old. Yeah, I don't claim to be young. I don't
claim to be like a young man anymore. Straight frames depleted streamer defeated. I like
that. That's a good one. I like that one. Frames depleted streamer defeated. This has
to be from like the wind we've been getting lately. And just like I could sit here and be like,
I can't I got to just did it just go down when I did that?
Watch some videos. Maybe we'll watch some videos. All these Fortnite streamers are hogging the
good internet. Capitalize the D and depleted right now. Oh, fuck, you're right. I got
pants on. Rank the Star Wars movies. Star Wars. Two. Star Wars. Four. Star Wars. Seven. Star Wars.
Three. Star Wars. One. Star Wars. Are we going from best to worst? Why did I rank
episode two as the best Star Wars? I thought which way were we going? What am I gonna do
the sequel to Otto's Big Adventure 2? Never. Never. Unless it's a joke for like 10 seconds.
He's calling football plays. What would you sacrifice for a perfect internet? The top of
this pinky here. Like that would see that with this this top of this knuckle. Just take it off.
I don't I don't need that. Do I I don't need that. From like here down. I was born.
Break out the red blend. No, I'm not drinking. I'm not. Why would I'm not going to start
drinking right now. That's not a sacrifice. I wouldn't even that's not a sacrifice. You
said I you said what would it take? And I said like the top half of my pinky. Well,
I don't know. Maybe like that's a sacrifice because it would be hard for me to grab stuff.
Break out the whiskey. No, no whiskey. No booze. No, I'm not like that upset about
this. I'm just like mildly irritated. I'm pretty upset by this. I'm actually very upset
by this. Don't let them fool you. Don't let me pretend. I'm like very upset by this.
Play Mario Yahtzee. We might. Maybe. Maybe. Why is your face cam so noisy?
Yeah, that's right. Why is this so shitty looking? Well, it's because
it's because of this. It's like in a weird resolution. Yeah, look at this. This is what
we're what resolution even is this. It's great because I'm like sitting down on it.
Here. There you go. How mad am I on a relaxed to Hotline Miami 2?
Maybe maybe like the first the first like four pages of Green Eggs and Ham. You know what I
mean? That's where I'd say I am on a scale of like upset. Clean the closet. I will tomorrow.
Have I seen any celebrities in Las Vegas? No, I mean, again, no. Again, it's not a
uh I've seen Criss Angel go like this. It's huge. It's like on every building.
How mad are you on a on the Richter scale? Like a mild. He still exists. Yeah, and apparently he
does. What's what's what's what's this? Let's watch some old videos. Yeah, let's watch some
old. Let's just chill. I'm defeated. 30,000 drop frames. That's too many. We've been
live for an hour. All right, let me set this up to get this to work. Let's um I had a friend
who believed everything Criss Angel did was actually magic. I mean, what is magic though?
Magic is it's just fooling and you know subversion, right? All right, let me put this
over here. What do you guys want to watch? What like you want to watch a video of mine?
You want to watch an old video? Should we like vote on these? I don't know how we would
vote on them. Put on a rat movie of Otto's Big Adventure. Watch yesterday's stream.
I'm not gonna watch yesterday's stream. That was a lot of fun, but watch death to spies.
Oh yeah, the with the graph. I forgot about this. This video has a million views.
Holy shit. Watch your least liked video. I don't know. I don't want to do that.
Your least liked video. Let's see. I don't even know. Can I even sort on a channel for that?
It's a little bigger. No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop it. Stop it. Okay,
I stopped it. So now let's put this on here. I should be able to turn it on.
Hey, this has this video has the same amount of likes that I have dropped frames today.
Let's full screen this death despise. This is an old one. Can I, I got to give myself a spot here,
right? This is the video that got you into the channel. Really? That's this is some of the
funniest fucking shit I think I ever saw in a video game. Can I not like just make this be
the whole screen? Why are you doing this? Come on. Come on. What are you doing? This is killing
me. All right, let's watch. Let's watch death despise. It's been a while since I've seen
this. In fact, I think it's been years since I've opened this video. Let's watch it. Okay.
Here we go. That's as loud as it can get. I feel like this would be louder.
And I'll make that louder. Guys, I don't do this. I never like do like videos on stream.
Is that getting louder for you guys? I think it is. Yeah, it is. All right, there we go.
That's better. Where am I supposed to bring this guy? This is a gigantic base with people
in it. How am I supposed to sneak him out? He's extract captive. Oh, the body can be
hidden in a truck. And that makes sense. Okay, well, you stay put. I'll be back.
I killed him. I've been sitting here for at least a few minutes, trying to figure out what exactly
this fucking guy is doing. Well, yeah, what the fuck is he? He's like cleaning down this
old rusty cabinet with his hands. Or is he looking for a stud? That's a good one. That's
a good one. Stop. Stop it, please. I had to do that. You had. Pause it. Pause it. I'll
give you some insight information here. So this is there was a spot here that I tried to go into,
like, probably 30 to 40 times. It took a long time to get in this exact area where I couldn't
get shot. And this is where I figured out that people were just dumping into the room.
And I died so many times here trying to fit myself in this one spot to go underneath.
Because your head is underneath and they can't hit you. Yeah, it was like a pixel that you could
step on. Oh, he found me. He found me. He is trying to figure out how to shoot me right now.
Oh, shit. That you like that fucking hat over there. I can't seem to hit it. How do I hit
this fucking hat that's on the ground? You guys are so stupid. You can't hit the fucking.
All right. So here's another thing, right? I was trying to like set this up because I
thought this was funny. And the grenade coming into the room is something that I never prepared
for. There was no way I could have ever prepared for that. It was like no fucking way. I have
to do this a bunch more times. So I was trying to get them to miss me while I was the hat
on the ground. And it turned into this. So the hat on the ground. Is that what you're saying?
Flying by and dropping missiles on this place. Stop with the fucking.
Are you kidding me? Are you guys kidding me right now? People are all out of their minds.
They keep coming in here, realizing where I am. And then somebody throws a grenade into the
room and they have to leave. And some of them actually die. This shit was so fucking funny.
There he is. I found him. Oh, wait, Jerry, did you just throw a grenade into the room?
They all run out. They all like scatter. How much one of you morons is going to throw
the grenade? That's the question. We got the whole troop in here. Who is going to be the
finger moron that does it? Oh, get him. The hold up. I don't understand what the hold up is.
Was it you? Was it you? Somebody comes in and fucking throws it at her.
What's going on? Oh, put this gun over. He's like, what happened over here?
This dude, this guy aiming the gun that way. Throw it. Throw the grenade. Here we go.
This is my favorite one. Somebody comes in and throws it after I throw one, I think, right?
Yes, this guy went in here. He's sitting there standing looking.
You threw it into the wall. He throws it in and then he walks in the room.
I've just been reloading this over and over again. It's true. I was.
That guy didn't even attempt to get out of the way.
I forgot about that one. Something interesting. If you take a look at the guy that just stands
there and just goes, this is the best game ever, man. Like this is seriously one of the
funniest fucking, they don't make them like this anymore. That guy didn't even attempt to get
out of the way. Oh yeah. This next part too. I don't, I could like stream this game. I
probably could. But the next part where you're the chef and that's like a super disguise,
apparently. I don't know when nobody can see through it, right? Oh, no, no. Only one guy
could see through disguises. It was the chef. That's it. Something interesting. It was unfucking
real. Take a look at the mini map. You see all the green blobs. Those are all the people,
all the guards, all the hotel staff, all the people here cannot see through my disguise.
There's one red blip. Do you want to know who it is? The chef. There are other chefs in
here that can't see through. Right. So explain to me why other chefs couldn't see through my
disguise. One chef, everybody else. I don't get it. Throw a fucking plate in this guy's face.
This guy grabbed my leg. What is going on? What is hurting me?
Did I freeze in the freezer? Oh, don't tell me you can freeze in the freezer. Do not give
me that kind of power. Hey, Gary, just the man I wanted to see. Hey, look, can you go
ahead and grab me some extra kebabs from the fruit? What a fucking idiot. What an idiot.
I know. Do me a favor, Gary. Freeze. He's not freezing. Bullshit. This guy immune to cold.
This was horseshit. I was so mad about this. Why do I freeze in here, but he doesn't?
That's bullshit. Gary. I was hoping that that actually froze. The internet froze it.
Um, what I was actually hoping was going to happen there was that I could fill that freezer
with people. Just like have, just keep like throwing coins or whatever, throwing stuff in
there and they would just keep going in there and it would close the door and they would
just be in there. Would it feel weird recording a game for a video without a live audience
anymore? Yeah, probably. Because honestly, people say, oh, you don't, you know, I don't
make videos anymore, but this is the, I did this same shit off stream when I'd stream a game.
Now I just, I treat it the same way as if I was going to make a video on it essentially.
So it's, it's different, but it's also kind of the same. Now there's live feedback for
everything and I don't edit things out. I don't put things like in like graphic layovers
or sound or music or something, right? So it's, it's a, it's different, but it's also pretty,
it's very much the same too. So I play games off stream sometimes, not that much anymore though,
but here we go. The guy in the chair, he won't even suspect the goddamn thing. Oh yeah,
that's the guy that I was supposed to save. I was supposed to like go bug that guy or
something, right? I'm not even making sounds. I'm not doing anything in here.
Are you seriously wondering how that guy died? You opened the door and I did it.
Don't fuck with Jeff. Oh, $800. This part. My mission is to find the mole.
I've got to be quick. I've got to be silent and unseen. I find my target. He's this guy.
I throw a piece of china right in his mouth. Mission accomplished.
I can now escape undetected. This game was out of control. You know, I really wish they
would play something else. You're right, Jerry. And I agree. I think this piano player really
needs to shut the fuck up. Get some rock music in here. You know what I'm saying?
Was I spawning spoons? Where did I get these from? No, I was just taking them off the
tables. Right. I'm just being annoying right now. That's all I'm doing.
Just ruining these people's dinner. Oh, I forgot people just came in and pissed on you.
Excuse me. Are you serious? Occupied. Get out of here. What are you doing? Get away from me.
Oh, good afternoon. Yeah, there's somebody in this one. Yeah. No, somebody's still in it.
Thank you for understanding. Second time. Third time. He doesn't. He's going to piss in my
face. He just comes in. They don't care. The AI doesn't even know you're in there.
They just fucking pee. Grab that auto. I almost died making grab that auto. That last part.
It's been, I haven't seen these in a long time. It's been a very long time.
Grab that auto. All right, we'll do grab that auto. Oh, subscribe for more.
Four years ago, we've decided to tell you to do that, you know.
Role playing duck gamers. Oh, I forgot about that one too. I forgot about all these
videos. All right, give me, give me one second. I want to go grab, I want to grab
some water. I'll be right back. Also, again, thanks everybody for your patience and shit.
I'm sorry that we had to kind of dip out and do something else for a little while,
but I do, I really appreciate it. Let's move on. I'll be right back.
Oh fuck, it's getting worse, isn't it? Holy shit, it's getting worse.
I left at 40,000 drop frames and now there's 47,000 drop frames. Shit.
It's, we keep, we're hitting this like critical mass right now. All right, let's uh,
let's put on grab that auto five. Grab that auto five. You know what's one thing that's
interesting is the, is the view counts on some of these videos. Like I, grab that auto
five is four and a half million views. That's fucking crazy. I, that's, how? That's a lot.
It's interesting to go back and kind of see just how these videos have grown in a way. Fuck.
Guys, guys, this is not looking good. This is bad. This is like, I don't even,
this is not good. This is not good. Fuck. People watching more than once. Yeah, no,
that's, that's awesome. Like, I'm glad that people have been able to watch these videos
more than once and still like them and still watch them. It's, that's fucking cool. I'm glad
you like it that much. I had some of the most fun I've ever had in my entire life
was making some of these videos. Most of them actually. So it's, don't give up. Don't give up.
Um, it may be time to give up.
It may be time to give up. Well, I'm going to stick it up for a little longer,
but it's getting worse as we go along here. We get, grab that auto on the screen.
Um, so if, if, if I might, I might get cut off completely here. So let me just tell you the
plan. Uh, if this does happen. So the plan, they're supposed to be like really looking
into this and fixing this tomorrow. So I'm going to take tomorrow off, let them just do
what they need to do. I'm going to stay on top of it and we're going to get it settled.
Right. So, but because this stream is going to be really all over the place and like
barely a stream, uh, after Monday, I'm going to try to come back on Tuesday
and we'll just go Tuesday, Wednesday, right? Like I'll just take this one day while they try
to fix it. So that plan is to come back on Tuesday, Wednesday, and probably Tuesday,
Wednesday, Thursday, I would assume. But I've been, I was told explicitly that they like,
they were really going to get like to work on. And I think they know what the problem is,
but let's use the finite amount of time that we still have and watch another video.
So let's put this on the screen. Hello. I'm John. Hello. Hello, John. Uh, I actually need to
go like this. I got like an ad. Hold on. Let me let the ad play out first. This is a
nine minute video. I didn't even realize that. Okay. This should be it. Hey, look at that.
Is that in the right spot? I think it is. All right. Hi, grab that auto five chin cam
incoming. It's also been a very long time since I've seen this one too. Let's go ahead
and type in grand theft auto into the app store search bar. Don't do this if you have never done
it before. GTA type GTA legit, right? Looks pretty San Andreas. You got vice city.
And you got all this. Let's what is all this? Grab the auto five type in GTA into the app
store and accidentally download me grand auto gets good and a thumb stick is right on an ad.
So we're off to a great start here. Do I have a mission to do?
Or is this just pop in the game? This this engine, whatever it is, can't even load
15 feet in front of me. I'm not even sure there's anything I can do here.
Besides just drive around in the city and just walk around.
Doesn't like Apple have to approve. Let's get out and walk. Does this actually have a radio
like GTA as well? I want that bike. Give me that bike. Yes. Thank you. Thank you
for getting off of your bike and dying. No, he doesn't. He didn't. He kicks my ass, doesn't he?
Oh my god. I have to unlock. Everything has to be unlocked. Money and diamonds and shit.
Let's get back in my burger car. One of the only cars I can fucking drive.
Hold on. 15 diamonds. There it is. The best one. They take a very long time to load.
This one has graphics. This music is so annoying. I've memorized this whole song.
Is anyone driving this car? No, there's not. Nobody's driving the car. How do I shut this music off?
Can't get over this music. Oh, this is like the Fred Flintstone one.
I probably got so many viruses. Camera. I probably got put on so many lists.
Why is it just singing to me? Is that a police car or is that a bird like a chickeny?
Cops found you. Get rid of them. Sounds like Kirby.
Holy shit. What am I supposed to do? How do you beat that?
See, the greatest part about this is these two guys that-
Riding a star. That's right. Don't care at all.
This is pretty normal to them, apparently.
Just a normal day in Shitsville. Two guys shooting at each other through a bunch of
fucking bricks. Oh my god. Why can't you make a full game like this?
What was in those guns? You can't be in that car.
Those were Chad's next car game.
Well, we know this guy really likes this song. That's good to know.
At least he's got a favorite song. This one's real bare bones.
One. There was no loading screen.
There was no menu. It's just one.
I wish I could explain how hard this was to move.
Mapping in the corner was so bad.
Holy shit. That's a lot of money.
That guy was holding a bank vault worth of money.
Go get it. 20 bucks.
That was a stack. Pretend to play it?
Psycho. I can follow that guy.
Get out of the window. Just rip him out of the windshield.
What is going on with- That guy just turned into a bunch of luggage.
Mack truck. This guy's gonna-
Oh. Pull him over.
Time paradox. Same game, same engine, same music.
The only difference is this time they decided to make you a robot Spider-Man.
Forgot the script. I guess this one's a slot machine.
I'm gonna give it 15 seconds before I get run over.
Somebody behind me? Somebody's just throwing punches at me.
Get out of here. Are you serious?
Is he still behind me? He died.
This is another goal-less game.
This honestly was one of the top five funniest things ever.
I literally turned into a cackling witch at the end of this video.
This went on for so long. All right, hold on. I gotta pause this.
You know how you've asked before the differences between streaming and YouTube, right?
Well, the differences between something like this.
If I streamed this, if I streamed this game and streamed doing this like
ran the thought oh kind of bit.
This went on for a very long time.
Went on for fucking like this would have- this never was going to stop.
We could have sat here on stream and watched that for like 30 straight minutes.
And the differences I guess were because I didn't- you don't-
I didn't even want a video to be like a 20-40 minute long video.
I cut it down.
We would have been able to see this live happen in complete and total present reality.
And we could have- I could have gotten up and I would have just left it on the fucking stream.
I would have left it there for an hour.
So that would have been the difference is we would be able to sit there the
whole time and let it just play out forever.
But nevertheless, it was still fucking hysterical.
Ruby, you fucking idiots.
Where are all these people coming from? Why are they fighting?
Oh my god.
This shit was so fucking funny.
This guy was in slow motion.
Two people were like, why?
This dude is gonna stop fighting them?
Why would you start fighting this guy?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
Is there a reason why these people are all doing this?
Consider what?
It's a conga line of people punching each other in the back.
And then flying away.
Oh, this went on for so long.
Just wait till you see.
Like if you haven't seen this.
Oh, I'm gonna need a minute after this one.
I was dying.
I was fucking crying.
It's never gonna stop.
This is never gonna stop.
Listen to that.
I'm like dying.
I'm gonna die.
I'm seriously gonna die.
I'm gonna live through this one.
This is the best thing I've ever seen in any game.
Just never ending spawn.
Just flies.
I don't ever want this to end.
I don't want to hit pause.
I don't want to hit replay.
I don't want to stop it.
But you know what?
It's...
I gotta get out of here.
I have to stop this.
Wow.
Is it first ever I gotta get out of here?
Holy shit.
That might be first ever.
Four years ago.
Because I'm seriously gonna throw up if I stay here any longer.
As amazing as this is.
So I'll talk.
Hell yeah.
Of rewards.
30.
29 actually.
29.
I think I was like 28 or 29.
29 I think.
29 by the way.
Now we'll play role playing duck gamers.
That's an old one too.
Uh I think I can...
Can I...
I think I can just get it through here.
Can I?
I'm like interacting, right?
Or do I have to redo this?
I should be able to...
Can I not interact with it?
Interact.
That's why.
Is it because it's full screen?
Why can I...
Come on.
Apparently not.
No!
Why are you doing this?
Well I will try to pull it from here.
Role playing duck gamers.
This video was not that long ago either.
2015.
2015 was a good year.
Alright no ad.
That's good.
No ad.
God!
There wasn't an ad on here!
There was no ad!
Alright here we go.
This is uh Star and I jumped into duck game and after...
I don't know maybe like 20 minutes of playing it we figured out that
it was fun just to pretend to talk through the character's voices
by pressing the button that makes you quack.
And nothing else mattered at that point.
Nothing mattered.
Only that.
So here we go.
Role playing duck gamers.
You dropped your burger on the ground there.
Hey have you ever seen that movie Super Mario Brothers 2?
It's pretty cool.
You see the main character Super Mario he goes like this
and he gets in and he rages the game.
That doesn't even hurt.
Where's the gun?
Give me that gun.
That's a lot.
Give me this gun.
Give me that gun.
I win.
That's like more fun.
You got me.
Today is your unlucky day motherfucker.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Gotcha.
Gotcha motherfucker.
I don't think that's gonna stop being funny.
What's wrong?
Having some trouble?
Come on now.
What do you got?
You got a pistol.
I got a pistol.
I'm gonna shoot you with this pistol.
Duck.
Jump.
Get ready.
I mean get ready.
It's actually kind of hard.
It's hard to like hit B and make the mouth open and play the game at the same time.
It's very hard.
Watch out I got a shotgun.
I got one too.
I'm gonna blast you.
You're gonna blast me?
I'm gonna throw it.
You think you're gonna blast me?
Well I'm not gonna now I don't have a shotgun.
Come chase me.
What?
Come chase me?
I don't know.
Come chase me.
You're the one with the gun.
This is so fun.
What a fun thing.
We're gonna do it just like they used to do in the old times.
Back to back ten paces.
Turn around.
Okay in ten paces.
Go.
One two three four five six seven eight nine ten.
Die.
My die was like eight syllables.
Look look this is the gun from Earthworm Jim.
Cool huh?
Cool.
Duck game.
On Steam.
Currently part of the Steam sale.
Pick it up today.
You're gonna have fun with all your friends.
Like this guy.
He's my friend.
But is he really though?
I don't know.
Could he be?
I have no idea.
Friends.
I love friends.
Fuck this video.
Fuck this whole thing.
This whole thing sucks.
Fuck this video.
When I sit up here and stare at this red beam.
I think about my life.
And where I've been.
And where I'll go.
And what?
Aliens.
Are we the aliens to aliens?
We just want to watch the world burn.
That's a Batman quote.
Some people just want to watch the world burn.
I wonder how long this recording has been.
Hello there.
Welcome to the shoe shop.
Okay so I have this pair of shoes for only 12 dollars.
Wait are we dead dead?
We good?
Dead dead?
Doesn't look like it.
Almost.
Close.
That was really close.
I'll rewind.
I gotta rewind.
Okay.
I just want to watch the world burn.
That's a Batman quote.
Okay hold on.
I need to pause this.
I feel like the like this this was the just both of these characters are just
uh what are the what are the kids saying now like mood right like oh like mood
like mood is fuck right for like the both of us I feel like that just captured both of our
who we were completely like fucking mood you know what I mean is that what people say
yeah oh by the way you know that I spent I spent like 45 minutes the other night on
knowyourmeme.com trying to and just typing in things people have written in like bit donations
I actually was doing that trying to catch up
I wonder how long this recording has been.
Hello there.
Welcome to the shoe shop.
Okay so I have this pair of shoes for only 12 dollars.
I'll take them.
Okay good.
Yes my old nemesis.
The hamburger head.
Those of you that know who he is.
He's a dastardly villain and he must be destroyed.
You have to come down here.
Yeah I know.
I will eventually.
I'm doing my monologue.
It's incredibly important to the story arc of my character.
I don't I seriously don't know how.
Go get him Glenn.
I can even I could tolerate as a person.
That's the gun from uh that's the moon gun.
I'm gonna catch it in my mouth.
Hold on.
No no don't die don't die.
There he is.
Ladies and gentlemen that's the guy that had my character.
I have to go to kill that guy.
It's part of my character story life.
All right you got all right do you know you know when somebody's having too way too much fun.
I'm having like so much like too much fun.
I don't I seriously don't know how many more of these I can.
I can't tolerate as a person.
That's the gun from uh that's the moon gun.
I'm gonna catch it in my mouth.
Hold on.
No no don't die don't die.
There he is.
Ladies and gentlemen that's the guy that had my character.
I have to go to kill that guy.
It's part of my character story life.
Catch it in my mouth.
All right so your first day on the job here at Edwards construction.
You got to be careful.
Told you to be careful.
And that's when she told me to go to school.
She wanted to see me.
Well you're really fucking this up aren't you.
This turns into animal.
Are we the aliens to that planet?
Makes sense in my opinion.
Although a more existential way to look at it is probably like this.
Can you believe Carol?
Carol in accounting.
Man she really gave me the ride.
I have to get back to work.
Yeah you do.
I don't know why you've been doing that.
Seems kind of expensive.
All right I'm ready.
Okay I'm gonna catch it in my mouth.
Didn't we just do this?
Okay I just want to say congratulations on being number one.
You don't talk to me.
You deserve that trophy.
Your second place I win.
You don't talk to me.
This video is so much fun to make.
Oh speaking of Star.
You'll be pleased to know that we're probably going to play something fairly soon.
I actually just talked to him like a few days ago.
So Jerma and Star.
Everybody wants to see this fucking happen.
I'm not playing that video though.
That's an embarrassing, that's an embarrassment to me video.
Yeah we were talking about just playing some ram stuff so this should be fun.
Do it!
No I can't do it.
We've got them dropping too many frames.
You wouldn't even be able to see it.
Tactical intervention.
That's another one that was...
I want to like...
Yeah we got to watch the tactical intervention video.
That video is fucked.
That game is fucked.
That game is insane.
If you type tactical intervention.
It's Star and my videos of what happens here.
All right let's load it up.
Jerma is mad.
Part three.
Now let me open this up.
Which this should...
What's this on here?
How many of those did he make?
He made a lot of those didn't he?
I got it.
I caught it before it could happen.
We I saved you from watching the ghost recon breakpoint explode inside of your ears ad video.
Why am I getting two ads back to back?
What is up with this?
Since when?
All right here we go.
Three two one play it.
It's just it's just showing us the scenery.
Yeah why isn't it just...
Okay here we go.
Oh god this is so loud.
Why is it so loud?
Every game is loud.
And now you're you're wicked loud again.
This siren.
You are so loud.
I guess I'm ready.
This siren does not stop for the entire video.
This is the loudest game ever.
Oh my god I'm driving.
Are you driving?
I'm in the car.
I'm in your car.
Are you behind me?
Yeah I'm behind you.
That shit's fucking so stupid.
This is a secret highway route.
But everything is so loud and you are so loud.
You are so loud right now.
I'm sorry.
Your microphone is so fucked.
Hey look at this car.
I can't control this.
What is the objective?
I'm passing out dude.
The world is closing in.
It started to see black like I was fainting.
Do we get out?
And we won the game.
All right so something really important because the thing with making a video
after the fact there was three tracks right?
There was the game audio, there was my audio, and there was star's audio.
So every time you'd make a video you'd have three different audio timelines
in your editing software.
So to be able to have this video actually play audibly
in any video, it didn't matter which one it was,
you played with the audio levels to make it so the tracks
weren't too overbearing or too horrible.
This video, what you're hearing does not do justice to how loud this actually was.
This had to be dropped like 75% to not be completely blowing out
every single person's eardrums that watched the video.
So like how loud this was.
He is, and not just the game, for some reason his microphone was like
I'm gonna peek and break and be loud as fuck too.
It was just, listen to why when he says we win you can hear his mic crying.
Do we get out?
No, no, don't get out, don't get out.
I can't, I can't get out.
No, I'm driving.
Do you hear that?
It's so bad.
Peek your mic, peek your mic.
Yeah, we're off, we're off, we're on, we're off, we're on.
Highway mode was so good.
Some of these first experiences in these games,
I'll never forget that.
I will never forget how funny that was.
We didn't even know what we were playing.
It was just like, let's play this.
This sounds like fun.
It's by the guy that made Counter-Strike, right?
That's what you knew when you went into that.
That's all you knew.
So guy that made Counter-Strike made this game.
Oh, let's play it together and maybe we'll record it.
And this is what happens.
It's just, it's wonderful.
How's the, I actually, I haven't played it in a long time.
Didn't they do, they redid it.
Didn't they like remake a bunch of it?
But that's the thing people say like,
oh, video games and playing with like people
and your friends and getting them calls.
Like that's the kind of shit
that you want to take away from that.
You know what I mean?
Even when I'm like 80 years old,
I will always remember that first,
like 25 minutes in Tactical Intervention.
I just will, I know I will
because it was fucking so unbelievable.
It was so ridiculous.
Is it, did it shut down?
Yeah, sorry, the server shut down.
That's too bad.
But let's continue through the video.
Here we go.
Oh, what the fuck is this, Jay?
Hold on, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready.
I need to fix this audio.
Deep fried star.
Audio, jeez.
Bring the master ball.
You're the driver.
I'm wait, I'm driving.
Watch out, there's guys behind us.
How do I drive?
This car drives like a piece of shit.
Yeah, it was pretty bad.
Why do you get arrows pointing?
Yeah, why do I get the GPS?
You didn't get the GPS.
I'm getting out.
Somebody was still in the back, I remember.
Like the VIP is in the back seat.
The guy in the back seat wasn't even in the call.
He's just like, what am I supposed to do?
The game just released.
I don't know what the fuck to do.
I'm just watching some guy drive his car.
He was sitting in the back seat, just sitting there.
You are a fucking asshole.
This is the best thing ever.
It really is.
How's this guy doing?
He looks like he's-
Oh, boo!
He's just like looking at me, just beeping.
He blew out of the car and then back flipped.
He's alive.
The VIP is alive.
That makes no sense.
He's sitting on the dash.
This game, I can't take it anymore.
I got to get out of here.
Wait, what the hell?
That's the first, you got to get out of here.
People just gunned him down, surrounded him, and just started firing.
All right, I'm driving.
I'm going fast.
I got the need for speed.
Get out of the car.
There's two of the same guy holding their feet on the car.
There's two of the same guy with the feet on the dash.
I seriously am passing out.
You see the spoiler on the back of that car?
No, I'm too busy blacking out.
It just threw us into this game.
I remember, I remember I had to like go to bed after this.
This is one of those scenarios we played.
I don't know, this is like five minutes.
We probably played for like a couple hours, two, three hours maybe.
Maybe a little bit more.
And I distinctly remember like being hungover.
That happens to me.
It does.
I don't make that shit up.
Like when I laugh to a point where I fucking like start crying and shit.
Like I like start to fade out.
I get like streaming video hungover.
I get like comedy hungover.
I really do.
Seriously, we were at the ready screen.
It got wicked loud.
That was just too much like too much stimulation.
The last time, the last time I faded out for real.
Actually truly faded out was during the Sims 4 mod night.
During the dog peeing shit.
Like the guy on drugs with his dogs.
That is the last time that I actually like got fucking video game hungover.
I just, the dog rolling around in its own piss and the guy on drugs
walking and walking the dog in his own house.
Like I was blacking out.
I came pretty close a few more times.
Like recently.
But then like that, I don't know.
Then like later on that night you just kind of,
you just like fucking god it feels like you just got run over by a car.
The farts and screams.
I didn't black out during that.
I started like welling up a little bit here.
But those mods, the first handful of those mods.
Oh, I'm about, I actually had eject, but I wasn't blacking out there.
I have a distinct memory of taking my headphones out.
So I think I said it a few times.
Like I have to leave the room.
I turned around.
I like got out of the fucking chair and I like walked over here to just get away from the desk.
I love this shit.
Like it, it's got, it has to be constant laughter for a little while.
If you expel like enough laughter and you laugh enough and then you, you like get back.
But if something else happens that you see when you're in the middle of desperately trying
to come back, that's where you get like comedy injured.
You see something or something plays out in your head over and over again.
We, you think about it over and over again in your head of why you think it's so funny.
But it's, this is just reminds me and even from streams too.
This is just reminds me just how much fun some of this shit just truly is.
It, I fucking, I love this shit.
It's fucking so much fun.
Hyperventil laughing.
Yeah, the laugh just keeps punching you.
How does this one end?
Of the brain.
My old screen.
Subscribe for more like if you did.
If you did.
I only like if you did, if you liked.
If you didn't like it, then you didn't have to like it.
But I like if you did.
I hated that one.
Well, I hope you didn't like the video then.
Have I watched all stars videos?
Oh, I've seen every single one of his videos.
All right.
What's next?
German, no, no German rumble.
I feel like we've German rumble has been seen plenty of times.
I want to kind of revisit some of the old ones that like I don't,
I haven't watched in a while.
Raven's cry.
Oh man, that's an old one.
Raven's cries.
Crazy.
Which one though, I did two videos on that game.
I made two Raven's cry videos because they've remade it.
Wait, did I Raven's did?
Did I make two videos on Raven's cry?
Yeah, I say, yes, yes, yes, I did.
Okay, I tell you, I did.
This is Raven's cry is a finished game.
Be brave.
Oh, internet.
How are we doing?
Ooh, not very good, it seems.
All right, let's add this.
Doink, doink.
Raven's cry.
What?
Why is this not playing here?
Oh, here we go.
That was weird.
All right, let's watch Raven's cry.
Three, two, one, action.
This guy looks like he's waiting for a bus.
Get out of my way.
There's no need to be rude.
I was just.
It's the same person talking.
I didn't even do that.
Why?
Yeah, half the audio wasn't recorded.
Uh-oh, there's pirates here waiting for me.
And there's no, none of them.
None of them.
You let them have the flag and here you stand.
Mind telling me how that's possible?
My name is Christopher Riddle.
My name is Batman.
Touch more ass.
Remember that drunken asshole?
We all know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So what's next?
Turn it up.
All right.
This really does sound like it sounds like somebody was just at like a bar
drinking with their buddies and held a microphone in front of
some one of their friends was just like, hey, can you
can you do like a fucking shitty pirate voice for me?
Of course his asses.
All right, this swear guy is seriously driving me crazy.
This is all he does.
There's a guy on this boat that's just saying a variation of the same insult.
He's telling us to be brave and at the same sentence he's calling us names.
Which one is it?
We're sinking.
He's sinking.
Sinking into the sea.
We don't die today.
You bitches.
God damn it, man.
Well, first I'm going to stand and then I'm going to put them
and then we're going to put them again and then I'm going to put them again
and then I'm going to stand and then I'm going to stand.
Why does he keep telling me to do the fear skill?
I did not mean to shoot that guy.
Didn't mean to kill that guy.
I really didn't.
I'm trying to do the fear skill.
Nobody seems to care though.
Apparently that guy.
Nobody cares about that guy.
Everyone's cool.
We're all right.
We're good.
Look, a guy sleeping on the dock.
What do you know?
Hey, who's got a gun here?
You're going to put a gun on me?
Are you crazy, man?
Let's see if you can put somebody's eye out.
I'm tired.
I'm going back to bed.
I think I'm good.
No, wait.
You've got a gun still.
Oh my god, dude.
You're going to kill somebody with that thing.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going back.
I'm not tired anymore.
You think I'm tired?
No, I am tired.
No, I'm going to wake up now because you've got a gun.
This guy's crazy.
I'm tired again.
No, I'm not tired.
You think I'm tired?
Fuck you.
I'm tired again.
Oh, hey.
I don't want to fight these guys.
You quacks.
That's my favorite one.
My favorite one.
Be brave.
You quacks.
That's the best one.
That is absolutely the funniest one.
Dingy boat.
Why quacks?
These guys are shooting like 300.
Oh my god.
Be brave.
Shit.
There's no way I'm going to be able to fight these guys.
I just like 2%.
I did like not even 1% damage.
We're like instantly getting killed.
I can't even turn the wheel.
It's all your fault.
You numbskull.
No.
Who's saying you need me?
Why is that the fucking reverse of yeah?
No.
Oh shit, there's a prisoner in here.
Get me out of here.
That's not a very secure prison.
Excuse me.
Just go the other way.
I don't even know what that means.
You just said a nonsense statement.
Just please go out the door.
Get on your way.
Go.
I'm going to block this side of the door so you have to fucking go this way.
Turd sniffer.
You just call me a turd sniffer?
They're all like bumbling all over each other and like saying excuse me and I go
I don't want any trouble.
God dude, this is I can't beat this.
I can't beat this like hen house.
That's all I hear.
Somebody just said discord voice chat.
There's literally only I that's all I fucking hear right now.
It's making me want to die.
Go go go go go.
Oh discord voice chat.
Please tell me I got out of that nightmare.
That's so fucking funny.
You cannot be serious right now.
Hey I'm going to try.
Hey let's go to voice one.
Voice one.
Anybody in here?
Crash my computer.
My computer is locked up right now.
Mine too.
Who crashed all of our computers?
My discord I my computer is locked up right now.
I'm still stuck here.
I have I have I can't do anything.
Okay anyways.
That's so funny.
No joke dad somebody fucking broke the discord with.
Serious right now.
I can't believe that somebody just broke the discord.
What if it just shuts down forever?
What if we never get it back?
Wait a second.
Don't even tell me.
Oh yeah people just peed.
People just pee in bushes.
No I forgot about this.
Yeah this is a lady pissing into a bush.
I completely forgot that people would just pee.
God they keep tempting me.
Stop tempting me with this.
Come on.
I like people just peed.
They keep putting them in the perfect spot
for you to push them off the giant scaffolding.
Do you have any idea how hard it is to not do that?
Look again.
And this guy this guy's pissing.
No he's not.
What is this guy doing?
He's puking right.
Oh he's throwing up.
He's throwing up into an invisible ground.
That was mean.
That was me I got sick.
He was ill.
Wait was that the guy I was supposed to talk to?
You guys notice something?
Anything seem a little off to you guys at all?
Just listen.
They patched him out of the game.
The last clip you saw was like two and a half days ago.
They removed this is all new dialogue on the boat.
Anytime you go on the boat now it's this.
What were the patch notes?
Did they say like oh we removed these scream swears be brave guy.
We apologize for his uncalled for insults.
And he has been removed.
I want him back.
Where is he?
He was an integral part of my crew.
He was he was like the bet they just they patched him up.
I remember because I was recording over like a few days here.
Like it's probably like I typically would play the game for like a few hours.
Take out some things that I thought were fun.
Play for like another hour or two the next day.
Or take edit some stuff together and be making the kind of the video as it went along.
And it just they changed the game like halfway through when I was making the video.
It was really weird.
Scare Saturdays.
Let me go over here.
Rat Burger.
We'll do we'll do Rat Burger.
Rat Burgers and I haven't seen that one in a long time either.
Let's see.
Welcome to Rat.
Five more than five years ago.
This was May March 18th 2014.
This is five years ago now.
That's a long long time ago.
I was just a young man.
I was just a young boy back then.
This like that.
Okay let's take a look.
Rat Burger.
29 is still young adult.
Haven't you guys played Alter Ego?
I know haven't you played Alter Ego?
Hi.
Where do we make the cheeseburgers?
I love how we each have a different.
All right wait wait wait wait wait stealth.
No no no no no do not just stop.
This is what he's doing.
That's not me.
Oh shit.
Why are you star's girlfriend?
No no.
I thought we were doing the tape.
Oh yeah.
All right.
Something important to note here is this game was so early in its development.
It was like a super alpha.
There was no restart.
There was no redo game or put the do a do a reset or you had to physically everyone had
to close the game to get these cheeseburgers back up here on the shelf.
You had to close everyone had to close out their games.
Everyone had to restart their games and the process to get anybody into a server was
this crazy roundabout.
There was like three servers that existed I think in the whole game.
It was a unity browser game that was hard to get people in multiplayer.
So it was this was very hard.
This took us like I remember like this like two hours had gone by at this point
and we finally fucking got it and got it to work and we were all ready to like record.
Remember if you fucked it up we had to do the whole thing again.
So like that's why I'm like don't don't don't what the fuck are you doing please.
Just because that we would have to start over.
Didn't star wake up in the middle of his sleep.
Yeah I I we needed a fourth person.
So I just like hit up star like I texted him.
I'm like hey dude come play this burger game it's gonna be fun.
He was asleep and I was like come on play this game please.
And I woke him up I didn't dead sleep.
And within I don't know maybe like 30 minutes or 20 minutes of being awake.
I was like we're trying to multiplayer just get in here's like the server is
what you have to do and he was just barely awake at this point.
Start over.
Hi.
He just didn't want to be here at all and he didn't give a fuck if he was
gonna fuck it all up.
So what's the first thing he does.
I love how we each have a different.
All right wait wait wait wait wait wait stealth.
No no no no no do not just stop this is what he's doing.
That's not me.
Oh shit.
Why are you star's girlfriend?
No no no.
He's just doing his own thing.
So I can't control.
He's just okay star is just doing his own thing this whole video.
He's just like not even in this video he's just doing his own thing.
Hold his mouth sensitivity.
You have to turn your like DPI down.
I can't fight my mouth.
So high.
All right you are seriously you are seriously messing this whole thing up you guys.
We were supposed to build burgers you guys are just taking all the ingredients
and throwing them all over the place.
We got people coming on the floor.
We have customers.
I'm going to say hi.
Look you need to look at like the note board to see what we have to do.
I'm just watching star like literally just hold his hands out and just hold left to right.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to fix it.
You have just like single-handedly destroyed what we were doing.
Can we actually make a burger or are you guys just going to be dipshits this whole time?
Look at come out here you sprint you can sprint.
I had this grand idea that we were going to have like a burger contest and
do some maybe like some light RP right.
They were just fucking throwing shit on the grill.
I had this like this grand idea.
Girl are you guys just going to be dipshits this whole time?
Look at come out here you sprint you can sprint.
I figured I'd just change the field of view.
There are people out here looking for cheeseburgers.
This guy wants a bacon burger.
All right we gotta we gotta set this up.
This guy wants.
There's so many people in here.
There is a burger patty.
She's not happy.
All right who wanted the lettuce?
No nobody will all right seriously meeting team meeting team meeting.
Oh the manager is displeased.
I am not happy.
You guys one of you guys is getting fired.
Hey look at all this stuff on the grill.
Yeah it's all burnt.
Go to the front desk go to the front.
I got a burger.
Wait what do you mean what are you talking about?
He took the patty.
Catch it someone.
Catch it.
I caught it.
She's still there.
Where's my burger?
Oh he snagged it.
Oh no this look at look at this trail of rats.
They're all it's like a rat fight.
They're all going after this one piece of meat.
This one guy.
Don't let them get away.
We are chasing this rat all the way down the street.
Come here you son of a bitch.
I got it.
I don't think you can.
I got the rat.
Look at all these people just watching.
I caught the wrong one.
Can we actually play this game?
We're not.
Hold on.
Everyone get in the back.
These rats are burned.
They are crisp.
They're not even they're dead.
They're black.
Hey guys it's okay we can finish the rat burger.
I found the patty.
These rats are burned.
Get the rat and put it on the bun.
I'm crying right now.
This is so stupid.
Okay can we please restart this and just like I don't have any
fucking rats everywhere.
I don't even know how you draw.
Like how do you like even control this?
I think it screws up in multiplayer.
And then that's did I just.
It looks like that's two-year-old drawing.
You're holding two.
All right so.
All right no no follow me though.
There is a prisoner back here.
There's a person back here.
Oh my god you fucking idiot.
What are you doing?
We just remade this game.
Remember keep in mind.
Keep in mind we just started this again.
This was like a all right three two one let's go right.
Immediately the first thing he fucking does.
We were been this not even two minutes.
A prisoner back here.
There's a person back.
Oh my god you fucking idiot.
What are you doing?
We just remade this game.
You're fired.
There's a person.
What's this a guy in here?
I know that's what I was saying.
What's wrong with this guy?
Can we like punch him?
He is the rat mama.
Can I pick him up?
What if you could pick him up and like.
You make like a person sandwich.
No I oh no.
All right you can lock people in.
No we all conspired against you.
Yeah it's just like all at once.
I am completely locked.
There's no way I'm getting out of this.
We did that very silently.
We all knew.
You dicks.
It's just me and like.
Is it like let us bricks.
I don't know what that's supposed to be.
He's like fighting through the trouble.
I'm fighting through.
Also we're wearing bandanas and.
Again take three.
Okay star you're not allowed to look.
Not allowed to look.
No because you're the burger judge.
There's people coming in.
There's customers.
Do you see what I did here.
This is some fucking 4D chess.
Star you're the judge.
You have to be on the other side.
Not in the kitchen.
That's some yeah.
I made sure to get him out of the kitchen.
No because you're the burger judge.
There's people coming in.
There's customers.
I'll talk the people down.
You got to show them to their seats.
I'll lower their expectation.
Lower their expectations.
Because they're going to probably throw up.
After eating one of our burgers.
I'm going to go.
You look mad.
Oh I picked something up.
Yeah still we have to make burgers.
We have to make our own delicious cheese.
You must be proud of yourself.
All right my second rule.
Start with the bun.
And hey I have everyone get away from each other.
Because we're just going to knock into stuff.
I'll take my stuff into the bathroom.
So here's my burger station is going to be right next to the sink.
In the bathroom.
Yeah I'll be I'll be in the bathroom.
You can use the bad controller.
Oh well the cheese is completely.
My cheese seriously is just like a black tile.
You don't put the cheese on the grill.
I wanted to like melt it.
You don't put the cheese.
You can put cheese on the grill.
Hey well get out of my station.
You.
No you can't.
Can you?
Sick.
Son of a bitch.
He just dropped my burger in the fucking sink.
Hey hey you don't got to you got to play to win.
Oh my.
Star just pretend like you didn't hear that.
It's a Krabby Patty.
What are you doing back here?
How are you like multiplying these bacons?
Star come back here.
One come back here.
What's going on?
I know how to break everything.
Where are you?
It's like duping the back room.
He's duping.
What the hell?
How did you get all this baconator?
I'm the baconator.
Who's under the ground?
Jerma you're under the ground.
What the fuck?
Oh no.
We didn't get to do the thing I wanted to do.
I'm so hard on this.
Where am I?
Somebody else fell.
You're gonna see the tiny little guy fall.
Who just fell?
You went whizzing by my screen.
Yeah.
I wanted to make like cheeseburgers and have a cheeseburger contest.
Apparently not though.
Jerma is he's reliving his frustrations.
He's doing it all over again.
He's seeing why he was so angry.
Spy party.
What about the New Vegas time gun?
I haven't seen that in a long time but that one that was fucking crazy.
Fun facts for everybody here.
If you're a new viewer to the stream that is
that is one of the first streams I ever did moving to Twitch.
Very early.
I think that was had to been the first five to ten streams ever right?
It's another one of those where I start to not be able to breathe.
I can't control myself.
Let's try.
Let's watch it.
Didn't you stream Minecraft in like 2012?
No I had like a Twitch account.
I had like an old Twitch account and I would use it sometimes.
I streamed on YouTube sometimes but it wasn't until like 2014
that I moved and started doing Twitch seriously.
Like taking it very seriously and streaming three or four times a week
and that was like late 2014 I think right?
YouTube streaming.
Yeah it wasn't very good when I was doing it.
That's why I chose to do Twitch instead.
Internet come on.
Let's close this.
My title changed right?
Yeah I'm just making sure the title actually changed.
All right what was it gonna do?
We're gonna do this one.
Stop.
There we go.
Stop wasting my time.
All right here we go.
This is all streamed.
So this is gonna be so I'm so I streamed this at a low bit rate too.
This is back like 2500 I think bit rate.
I stream now at 6000.
So this is old bit rate that was pulled and made into a video
now being streamed through through Twitch again
with like shitty internet problems today.
This is gonna be interesting.
We'll see how this looks.
Here we go.
Ready?
Oh wait I know you're gonna hear that line like four times
but hold on let me is this god damn it.
I knew it was frozen for I knew it was frozen.
I knew it was frozen.
There we go.
No don't be frozen please.
Sorry sometimes when I interact with a browser it freezes the whole thing.
I don't know why.
Okay all right there we go.
Finally put it on the screen.
Geez that took fucking long enough.
Here we go.
Go waste Jason's.
Fuck you I came here for a mission and I'm gonna do my mission.
You fucking ghouls.
So should I just fucking kill this guy?
You got it.
I missed.
Oh don't don't don't don't go sir.
I was just playing with you.
I just didn't want you to know that this was coming for you.
You can run but you can't hide.
Let's get in it.
Also very important to note.
This is important to note.
This is the first time I've played Fallout New Vegas and I just I was just fucking killing people.
I just was like slaughtering people.
And I didn't know I never ended up finishing Fallout New Vegas.
Because I got to a point where I was spawning 500 easy peets and I couldn't play it anymore.
I couldn't do I could I can't play Skyrim anymore either.
I've said it before of any time someone's like hey cheat like put that add this do this.
At some point you just you've ruined the whole thing and you can never play the game normal ever again.
Step in that asshole Larry.
Step inside that asshole Larry.
I'm so lost in here.
Where the fuck do I go?
Everything's the same.
God help me.
Derma blind.
Blind.
My computers.
If I touch a computer it'll save me.
Oh my fucking god I'm just gonna throw everything in the trash.
I don't fucking even care.
No I need that.
I need my space suit back.
Did I lose the space suit?
Where's the space suit?
Where'd it go?
Fuck.
Did George Washington take shortcuts?
Did Bill Gates?
I couldn't think of another person.
Took me that long to think of another successful person.
No they didn't.
Did Christopher Columbus take a shortcut?
I should have taken this shortcut.
Fuck George Washington.
I should have taken the shortcut.
Should have taken the fucking shortcut.
I'm scared the fuck out of here.
Oh I had no clip to the door.
There it is I found it.
I think I found it.
Yeah I think it's this way.
Where is it?
Uh oh it's down that way.
To the left.
Up into the right.
I think it's right over here.
How do I get a better view?
Oh I know.
See I already lost it.
It's over.
I can't play the game the same ever again.
I can't get a better view.
The first step is always no clip.
That's true.
That's always the first step.
Yep let's go.
Yeah give him a speech.
Dynamite joke incoming.
Oh you couldn't even interact with it.
Holy shit that's wicked loud.
Look at how loud this is.
Are you serious?
That's so loud.
Holy shit.
Wait what?
No it's no cheating.
No I just I saw it.
I just want to see.
I want to look.
I just want to take a look.
I just want to see what's in there.
This is where it goes off the rails.
This is an odd picture.
Why is this behind a locked door?
Some random guy singing to one person in the audience.
And his clone is sitting in this seat smoking.
What a secret.
What a fucking secret huh?
Is this right?
Here it comes.
Somebody just put one in.
I'm gonna believe this guy.
Spawn this Jerma.
Spawn this.
This will help you.
And then it's just it's always easy peeps.
Oh this is where.
Didn't I notice that they're funny?
This was so funny.
I cry a lot it seems.
Oh look at the guy in the back.
They turn like they get torn through like four dimensions.
Look at his eyes.
Look at this one's fucking eyes.
Why is this happening?
Why was this happening?
I lost all control.
Oh my god.
I forgot how heinous this was.
Why are they exploding?
I don't know.
I don't get it.
Stop.
I don't it's too laggy.
It's a little too laggy.
They're hurting.
That hurt.
Stop.
What was that?
That's not easy Pete.
This is not easy Pete.
Oh fuck.
Who is the flamethrower?
That's not easy Pete either.
That's not easy Pete.
Oh god he's naked.
Nudity.
Oh god nudity.
A second time and he turns.
It's almost like.
It's almost like this is a weapon.
You remember the Bart Simpson game where you had that thing to show that people were aliens?
It was like that.
It was like I had to hit that guy twice with the show me you're an alien weapon.
That's not easy Pete.
Fucking not funny.
I swear to god if this guy turns into like a fucking cheese pizza when I kill him I'm gonna die.
Oh no I'm at zero.
Are we good?
Oh god this is.
Uh oh.
Have we reached the end?
We may have reached the end of the.
We're at the end of the line here.
I think we're okay.
I think we were right here.
Oh god.
Yeah we're right here.
Nudity.
Because I said this thing.
Ah nah nah nah.
Hold on hold on.
Uh oh.
Well if we go out completely then they're supposed to fix this tomorrow
and I'm gonna let them do it.
I won't be live tomorrow.
Let's just let them do it.
And we'll come back again.
I'm hoping that I don't have to.
We're getting a lot of red.
I'm sincerely hoping that I don't have to spend more than one day trying to get them
because he said that they were gonna get on this tomorrow.
So hopefully I can go Tuesday.
Just in case we cut out completely.
Here we go.
Okay that was not easy Pete.
That was not easy Pete.
It's never fucking not funny.
I swear to god if this guy turns into like a fucking cheese pizza when I kill him I'm
gonna die.
They do don't they?
I forget.
Oh yeah they oh yes they do.
They just turned into a fucking museum statue.
Look at this.
Look at this guy's face.
Oh yeah.
He's like oh fuck.
He can't believe it.
He can't fucking believe it.
This is unreal.
This shit is fucking unreal.
It's a time gun.
I just don't I don't have any words.
There's no words to explain it.
I'm freezing them in time and ripping their bodies.
That's fucking crazy though really.
They look like dead space enemies.
Like gum people.
Like jello people.
Taffy people.
I made this person in dreams two weeks ago.
Whoa what I think I found the secret.
If you turn uh-oh I think I might have broke it.
I don't think it's gonna happen anymore.
It really never it's never not funny.
Come on.
Kill the other one.
Fuck.
Why are you so good?
Are you seriously this good?
Fuck you stop being such a good shot.
What?
What the fuck?
No way.
No fucking way.
Here he comes.
Come on.
Moment of truth.
You know typically I would be upset about this but you earned it man.
You earned it.
Look now he just wants a drink.
You earned it dude.
You earned your drink.
Bottoms up.
I think there's more.
Sark.
Oh yeah Sark came in.
A lot of closed casket funerals.
God it's.
I'm so happy that since that was like one of the first
so that was one of the first real couple weeks of streaming on twitch
and I'm like I still have that much fun like that's I still do that.
I still have that much fun in game still and that makes me happy that I can still have fun.
Hopefully it's still fun for you too because I feel like I'm just I love
being able to um to like because I don't really watch these.
I don't.
I watched like maybe maybe like a year or two ago.
I don't really watch old videos anymore.
All right let's do another one.
We spent seven hours watching you play a DOS text game for seven hours.
What do you think?
Well that makes me happy.
That's fucking I'm glad you still enjoy it.
All right let's do another one.
Let's do um it's always the monopoly guy.
That's a good one.
That is that's a good one.
That's a really good one from what I remember.
Stars Mike I think was also fucked during that this video as well.
If I remember correctly.
So let's get it on here.
It's always the monopoly guy.
This is this game out did this game ever really get completely bait?
That was an easy p jupiter.
Holy shit is this game should we play this again?
Should is it worth playing again?
This just this is the flashback episode in the sitcoms.
Oh you know now I gotta make it bigger.
All right let's do it.
Full screen HD 720p back when 720p was a big deal.
Back when 720p meant 720p.
Holy shit you got a video in HD.
I remember.
All right here we go.
Now that needs to be bigger.
Why is this not come on three two one let's go.
Oh you know you could be this guy with the book too.
This like monopoly man.
You're the fucking monopoly man.
Nope it wasn't me.
What?
And here comes the intro.
I'm pretty good at I'm pretty good at these things I think.
Well um you know I'm going to know what they are.
Yeah I know that's fine.
I love these N64 graphics I kind of miss them.
All right I'm ready.
Are you?
Because you're gonna pick the monopoly guy now.
I'm gonna see the monopoly guy.
We why why would I be that stupid?
Oh yeah let me pick the guy that you would just what I yeah that's a that's a great idea.
It's so scary it's so scary because I can see the the the laser.
Is it on your head?
No I can just see it.
I can see the laser.
I know well if you see the laser on your head of the monopoly.
I can see the laser pointing into the room.
That's all I'm telling you right now.
Does he get me here?
I'm just kidding.
No don't shoot me.
Don't don't shoot me.
Play in the psychology role.
Oh yeah well I'm gonna get you.
I think I've already got this figured out.
You should be scared right now.
You should be whimpering.
Fuck!
If that's the case these guys are all suspected double agents okay.
So that means you're over here somewhere.
You're in this crowd somewhere.
Of course I'm in this whole room is a crowd.
No no no you're in this crowd like over on the right.
Because these guys were suspected.
They were suspected criminals.
And you're over here.
You're one of these four people.
How could I possibly be one of these four people?
You're always the guy in the mustard jacket.
I think you're the guy in the mustard jacket.
Mm-hmm.
Why I think you're the guy in the mustard yellow jacket.
Who wears mustard?
I got my eye on you.
I got my eye on the mustard jacket.
Okay Nissy now you said I'm out of here.
Which means you have to be one of these people.
Because how would you have known he even walked away?
Oh oh that's right I just figured you out.
Thinking about that one.
You're one of the guys in the mustard colored jacket.
Okay I don't know which one of them you are.
But I know or you're the lady.
All right gray everybody else out.
I know which one of these guys you are.
You're that guy.
You're definitely that guy.
Say your prayers.
No!
You're not good at this.
He was the lady.
You were the you were the lady.
You were the I totally knew you were one of those guys.
Or you were the lady.
Oh no.
I had it.
Did I pick it again?
You're the fucking monopoly guy again.
I picked monopoly guy again.
You're just gonna play with the monopoly guy every single time.
This is a poker game.
I'm not gonna give you any tails.
Ha ha ha yeah that's the major tail.
Are there 16 different party goers?
I don't know.
It looks like there are.
I'm taking the shot.
I was the monopoly guy.
Busted jacket.
You thought it was busted.
I should have shot the monopoly guy.
Yeah you really should have because it would have been like the monopoly guy.
Like it is every single time.
You seriously better not pick him again.
It's not gonna work.
That is why you titled it that.
Yeah that's true.
Hmm this is tricky.
I don't want to get it wrong.
I have my suspicions.
Mustard jacket.
I'm standing right next to mustard jacket.
That's a mistake.
My suspicions are squabbling.
You don't have very much time.
I made it real easy.
You haven't completed your missions.
There's no way you have.
Okay okay screw you monopoly guy.
I don't think it's you but screw you.
Are you kidding me?
I was moving so obviously to yeah.
Like I wasn't doing the correct like NPC world of warcraft walk.
I wasn't doing like the world of warcraft wolf walk.
Really?
Yeah someone's already and oh that's not even that can't be you.
Because that's the double agent as well.
You can think whatever you want bro.
Wow he's a wow clicker.
You want to know what I think?
What do you think?
Let's see it.
I think I think there's a lot of statues here.
There are a lot of statues here I guess.
You know what Jerma?
What?
Safety is off.
What do you mean the safety is off?
He's just got it was so it's so nerve-racking.
Shoot that guy.
Do it shoot that guy right now.
He's the next best thing to the monopoly guy.
Shoot him shoot him right now.
Shoot that guy right now.
No shoot him in the head.
No I'm taking my time.
Blow that guy's fucking head clean off his shoulders.
Who's this lady?
No you pay attention to the other guy.
That lady didn't do anything.
That lady's going the other way.
See he's going this way.
I did like the voice like it's me.
I'm just staring at you.
Why don't you shoot me?
Does he get this?
I don't remember.
Does he get it right?
No what is about to happen.
He he does.
Oh every everything is about to happen.
No monopoly guy this time.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Okay.
You have to hit accept.
Hit accept.
I was stretching.
The stretch.
You gotta go for it sometimes.
You gotta go for it.
You didn't it wasn't the wrong idea.
No I'm not having this guy show up to no more parties.
Are you sure it's not him?
I'm not.
Okay okay you're picking him this time though.
I know you can't resist.
Can we please play around?
Yes.
Where you do not instantly kill the monopoly man.
You could just watch my laser.
That's fine.
That's perfectly fine.
Fucking monopoly man every time.
He's gonna take the shot.
I know he is.
What's he doing just standing over there.
He's just standing over there.
He's not doing anything.
Too suspicious.
All right I I'm not shooting the monopoly guy.
I'm not going to shoot.
Oh it is the fucking monopoly.
You can tell it's 2012.
No.
I tried to shoot.
Hold on.
Yeah I tried to shoot the monopoly guy.
I'm not going to shoot the fucking monopoly guy instantly.
I would have had it.
You took like a turn too quickly.
You had one job was to kill the monopoly.
Oh did you like that video?
That was a classic one.
Ah reminiscing of yesteryear.
Watch my curls video.
No we already watched that like 50 times.
Skyrim sliders.
Oh yeah that is a video isn't it?
Extreme body sliders.
I forgot yeah I'll put that one on.
Let's put that one on.
Three no three to four.
Four years ago.
Just about four years ago this video was made.
And then we'll yeah then we'll watch like a couple of videos.
On um maybe like an old star video.
Death to Spies already did it.
Did it.
That was the first one we did.
Let's get it on.
So those of you that asked me to play Skyrim.
This is the video.
This is the reason why I cannot play it.
I just can't.
Hold on.
Don't start yet.
Okay so this is the reason why I cannot play Skyrim.
Because I did this.
And away we go.
My child the task is at hand.
You must go under cover to stop the human dragon conflict.
Father I'm not ready.
Silence.
You've always been ready.
You must live among them.
Be part of the human race.
Find out what it's like to be human.
But what if I fail?
Take the magical cloaking cloak.
It will always disguise you as a human.
Our ancestors used dragon wizardry to create the spell.
It's extremely strong and powerful.
As long as you wear this.
Oof that was we went to zero.
I paused it don't worry.
All right let's go back to here.
Take the magical cloaking cloak.
It will always disguise you as a human.
Our ancestors used dragon wizardry to create the spell.
It's extremely strong and powerful.
As long as you wear this you are safe.
I love you my son.
I love you too dad.
Be careful.
First day go in meet a few people.
Good day folks.
A dragon.
I saw a dragon.
What?
Oh shit.
Cloak doesn't work.
Dad a magic cloak.
Really it was probably just shit faced.
Please stop hitting me with the sword.
Please we can live together in harmony.
Don't you see.
Maybe a tad on the large side for a head.
Longer neck.
We put his head forward a little bit.
You know he's real perceptive.
He sniffs around a lot.
He really really wants to get to the bottom of stuff.
He's a private investigator.
What?
And I think uh I think that's all right.
I like it.
A little bigger.
Yeah that's good.
That's good.
We're not going to go any more extreme than this.
It's a dreams character.
It's a dreams sculpture.
Excuse me.
I just was wondering.
I can't even see anything.
It looks like I seriously took this guy's face and molded it out of clay.
Good old clay.
This is an art project that I did.
I found out that I had to do this art project 15 minutes before it was due.
And it was to make a person's face.
I can do better than this.
Dero Pop that's right.
It's like bullfrog person listening to this guy.
Sitting on a park bench.
How can you keep a straight face right there?
How would you not be scared of this?
The hamburger guy.
He like looks over like what the fuck are you doing here?
You walk away.
See how big my arms are dude?
Do you have any idea how big my arms are dude?
Sometimes you just gotta run.
You know what I mean?
Sometimes you're really going to build up that CO2 in your body and breathe it out.
You just kind of go on a little jog with your hands.
You know what I'm saying?
Get up right behind this guy and do our stealthy little secret technique.
And give him a little small sword.
Fucking sword.
Get right in the back with the backstab.
No I mean this is the little cubert right?
Who's trying to make cubert?
The fucking lady's dead man.
Wow.
What a sicko.
I remember being sick for this video.
I have some bad news honey.
Yeah I had a cold this week.
I accidentally backed over the cat this morning.
It's okay he's still he's in high spirits.
He's still all right.
You'll make a fine rug.
This little cat please leave me alone.
You old bitch.
She goes crazy.
You know I actually thought I was gonna have way more to say about this.
This is a cat riding a horse.
I'll see you next year when this is a Disney Pixar movie.
Back away you foul humans.
We have every right to go through this tunnel.
You can't stop us.
Well you never seen a cat riding a horse before?
Get cultured.
Oh shit the fucking Thanksgiving turkey's on the loose.
This is the best character.
Hide the women and children.
The Thanksgiving turkey is the best character I've ever made.
I'm just gonna run my meat shop.
I'm doing well for myself.
I don't have to be concerned that there's an evil Gumby behind me.
Could be much worse.
Just don't let them know that you're afraid and everything will be okay.
So the Thanksgiving turkey is just the gum ball.
The gum from the fire pro wrestling.
This is the Dark Souls game.
What Dark Souls boss did I make?
Yeah shoot to the arrow.
Go shoot me right in the penis.
Good job.
Hey Jerma play Skyrim.
Play Skyrim.
I think you should like Skyrim.
At some point yeah I kind of can't.
It'd be such a good stream.
Yeah that's the thing about like video versus stream video versus stream.
So that that was like five days worth of just recording stuff and making stuff
and coming up with things to put on the camera and record it and edit it.
It's like we do that still but it's like in real time over seven to ten hours.
So it's it's interesting to see how it plays out like that.
Who is uglier?
Saints Row.
Kung Fu chroma key.
Ask nicely for crits.
I haven't seen that in a long time either.
Come on don't crash on me now internet.
I haven't seen that in a long time.
In fact I don't think I've seen that video since it was uploaded.
Maybe.
Let's watch it.
All right let's get this off for a second.
He's gone.
Ask nicely for crits.
This video is long.
This is like a 12 minute video.
What even is what's the what's the concept in this video?
Oh didn't he have to he had to scream right?
If he didn't scream as loud as he could I wouldn't give it to him.
Let's get it on.
Two ads in a row.
What the fuck YouTube?
What is this bullshit?
All right this is this is very much this is a trip down memory lane for sure.
This is old Team Fortress 2 content.
I don't know what is going to be in this video.
All I know is it exists and we're going to watch it.
It's been a while.
Here we go.
Ask nicely for crits.
All right we're all right we're going to play hide and seek.
That's how it starts.
Let's play hide and seek.
Hide and seek come on.
Two minutes ago the idea was let's play Team Fortress 2.
Yeah but don't you want to play hide and seek with me now?
No.
Look don't do not turn around because I don't want you to know where I am.
Understand?
Yes hide and seek.
The probably dumbest thing you could ever think of we're doing it.
This isn't like you know normally people would just go play prop hunt
but prop hunt's too stupid for you.
You need you have to take it to the next level of stupid.
Okay I'm ready.
Okay.
Wait is this where that comes from?
Does that come from this video?
Jerma, Jerma how's it going buddy?
What's going on?
What are you doing over here?
What's up with uh you know defending the point.
Waiting for my buddy star to come on over.
So context I'll give you context of what just happened there.
So there was always like that running joke where like three two one time to start the video.
Like here comes the start of the video three two one.
Hey what's going on Jerma?
What's going on?
You're oh what are you doing over here?
Oh nice to see you.
Oh I'm just playing around just hanging out here waiting for you to come over.
It was it was the here comes the YouTube start of the video thing.
We did it all the time.
We thought it was funny.
Jerma okay I'm ready.
Okay.
Three two one.
No no no.
Jerma, Jerma how's it going buddy?
What's going on?
What are you doing over here?
Hey what's up?
Hey what's going on?
I'm just hanging out you know defending the point.
Waiting for my buddy star to come on over.
Hey looks like we got some crits you can you can uh come with me right now.
We're gonna be using these crits against uh enemy gamers you know.
You tell me when you want me to do it.
You want me?
When I want you to do it you're gonna know because I'm going to scream.
No he does though.
And I'm really going to turn this down.
All right sorry I didn't get a lot of people there.
I thought there'd be more closer than that.
What the hell was that?
It was so loud.
See he turned I don't do that usually.
See here's the thing again he turned his timeline volume down to five percent.
I didn't get five percent.
I got a hundred percent.
So that's I did I did snort right there.
That was like a that was a pig.
That was like a little piggy.
He's like he's more closer than that.
What the hell was that?
That was uh actually a pig snort.
That's not a typical one that I do.
Snorted I don't do that usually.
You don't do that usually.
Thanks for clarifying.
Hey guys guys German doesn't do that usually.
It's still relevant right now.
It's not it's not a common thing.
Yeah I don't do it usually.
Okay.
I just said it again.
Please tell me you're gonna scream again.
Well how else am I gonna get you to crits me?
You're gonna have to build it up first.
Hold on I'm too like busy laughing.
All right.
All right so when we build these crits up.
We need to take we need to take it real careful.
And his hit sound is me doing something.
Whoa whoa whoa easy easy easy.
Hide hide.
Hide why are we hiding?
Because there was a guy there that looked like he was going to shoot me.
I killed him.
Oh you didn't okay let's go.
With the power of Kratos.
With the power of the golden rocket launcher.
What are you going on about?
Talking about your golden rocket launcher.
How it's like a family heirloom.
I was doing a whole thing there and you just cut me off.
No no he cut me off.
Do you have the crits?
Yeah I'm about.
Watch out for the sentry.
I can't I can't all right.
You are turning into the judge from who framed Roger Rabbit at this point.
No the worst thing is I heard one of my neighbors coming out of their apartment.
And they without question a hundred percent certainty they heard me screaming.
There's not a single doubt in my mind that they heard that.
I just don't know what their thought process was.
All right this is also this is also somebody that shit their pants.
While I was playing Overwatch with them.
He shit his actually shit his pants.
And I think I was streaming.
I was either streaming or making a video.
I forget what it was.
I was streaming it right.
He pooed his pants and sat in it for like a fucking a long time.
I still I can't fucking believe that.
There's videos about that.
Yeah this dude shit his pants.
And he didn't want to like fuck up my stream.
He didn't want to like run away from the stream right.
So he or with the video or the round.
It was something like that.
Yeah we didn't even win the game and he was trying really hard to end it.
So he could just run away after the round was over.
Oh what a truce friend.
Imagine just shit in your pants and you don't care.
You're gonna play the round out.
No that's not like good friend.
That's like video game like addict.
That's like that's like game that's like ultra gamer.
That's like video games psycho.
Dude they need to start like DX racer makes those chairs.
Maybe DX racers just start making diapers.
Have like the logo on them.
Would you shit in a DX racer diaper.
It meant you'd be cool.
No.
All right let's keep watching.
You can like this guy either won the lottery.
That was like that was a happy scream.
That wasn't like a like a bad oh boy watch out watch out.
He's so fucking good at this game.
Can you teach me how to shoot people in the air.
Dude I'm telling you people you guys think.
You guys think that I'm like I don't make it up.
Like I would that's like I just was saying I have the same reaction.
Oh he's so good at this game.
Like I wish I could.
Hey I'm you're wicked good at that.
Can you it's like I'm reliving the past.
I'm going back.
If I went back in the past I'd be fine.
There would be no paradox.
I'd be perfectly fine.
I could meet myself and we would have the same.
We'd say the same fucking thing.
You know like don't ever meet yourself.
No I'd be like what's up dude.
Hey how are you?
We're gonna be fine because we're gonna say the exact same fucking thing.
We're gonna what what store do you want to go to right now.
Let's go.
Alright let's go.
Let's go to the store and just walk around.
Wait but no then the government will find out.
And then one of us will get captured.
Will we both get captured?
Or would only one of us get captured?
They would take us both right?
No they wouldn't get me.
They'd get him.
Twins exist.
If you were yeah that's right twins exist.
I'm having like a panic attack in the store.
Oh shit what if they think we look the same.
Oh no.
One of us is gonna get captured by the government.
Tim this pipe is him in the air okay.
Alright that's what I do.
I miss when I do it.
Hey I'm just trying to help.
Alright I'm getting attacked.
Not anymore.
But hold on.
Hold on we're losing frames and I want to what is that sound?
The sound was it I'm getting attacked.
Attacked.
Sound from an old video.
I was like when did I do that?
Not anymore.
Look.
Oh man.
Easy easy be careful there's a sentry.
I'm being easy.
I'm being very easy.
Nice nice.
We can walk our way out.
No this sniper is gonna headshot me.
Alright no more oh no stop.
Wow you got like six people.
I think it was four.
Slam and frothy milkshake.
Is the scream thing really necessary anymore?
I don't know how else would you have known?
No no no just get on the point just get on the point just get on the point there's a pyro on top.
We're good we're good.
Excellent.
You did great right there.
Can I just say this has got to be peeking my microphone so bad.
Yeah you got a little quieter that's for sure.
That's for sure.
For sure.
Medic.
Alright stay right there.
Alright we're gonna play hide and seek again.
Where did he go?
Alright come find me.
Oh god he doesn't know where I am.
I'm gonna go play the game.
He doesn't know he doesn't know.
Forget about you because you're obviously an insane person.
I made it up.
I made that up.
Where is he?
So can we change the crit sound from you screaming to like you making a different sound
like what's crits me doctor can we change it to that?
That's expected no because usually what usually when you call for crits with someone they're
like oh I didn't know that you were saying it no just you just yell and there's no way
you won't know that I wanted the crits you know what I mean?
But what if it got hurt?
Yeah well I just fed him so many kills take that get back stabbed.
He just got back stabbed.
Why did he slow my voice down?
Why did he slow my voice down for that?
Right in the stomach.
Oh I was taking my time killing him because I thought that they wouldn't shoot
me but they were shooting at you the valuable target.
I'm sitting there just like preparing myself for the real scream I'm like sitting
there clenching like he's gonna scream.
We got a screamer on our hands.
All right well I'm waiting for you.
Back stab.
A burger sign?
Yeah near the dead spy.
Is it really a burger spy?
Yeah.
A burger a burger spy is that what I did?
No a burger right here let's go.
Oh whoa grummies burgers.
That was like the most fake excitement I've ever heard in my life.
Oh whoa burgers I had no idea can we go?
Was that a you was that a youtuber excitement?
Was it was I need to see was that youtuber excitement?
Like tuber excitement was it?
Oh grummies burgers.
Why is that what I did?
No a burger a burger right here let's go.
Oh whoa grummies burgers.
Yeah it was yeah it was that was a pretty tube that was pretty tuber of me.
That was like the most fake excitement I've ever heard in my life.
Oh whoa burgers I had no idea can we go?
I'm healing this guy he needed help.
No he didn't.
He needed health he needed an over heal.
That guy is mad and chat that guy.
Mad and chat mad and chat.
Nice you just nice pop.
Pop and shot.
This is a is this a spy no he's just holding his friend.
Pop and shop.
Hold on I need to heal hold on hold on hold on.
All right.
I need to heal I was on fire.
You have you're gonna have to quit soon.
Dude there's a health kit right over here.
72 percent.
I want but I want this guy to give us.
He doesn't keep screaming right he gives that up.
It helps to get your uber watch out for that pyro.
No it's the same pyro who only walks forward he won't reflect don't worry.
To get this health give me one second just chill.
You're taking your time.
I have the crits I have the crits.
Going out the window and going left going out the window going left.
Don't scream don't please don't scream.
Why would I not scream?
Please just just say just say Jerma I would like for you to give me the crits creep now please.
Okay Jerma the crits.
Jerma.
Okay I really didn't need it but I thought the comedic timing on that was pretty pretty well done.
Who's that person gonna be?
That person that comes and heals you.
I've heard that audio clip like a thousand times before.
The danger.
And look see this guy right there I want I want you to take I want you to take notes on this one.
I want you to take notes on this one.
Hold on we're not done.
Well yeah you got him.
I want you to take notes on this one.
I didn't even kill the guy.
He's a gamer you need to you need to heal me.
He like rocket jump market garden pulls somebody.
And I'm trying to get an ubersaw on one hit on one guy.
I don't know.
Hold on hold on I'm I hold on I need to fall back spy behind spy.
Spy dead make sure you heal yourself you are you dead.
He got me.
No you're bad.
I was saying spy to you and you were too busy.
I was fighting the spy.
You were not fighting the spy.
Your eyes were forward and you were looking at like some pyro.
Why does he keep doing that?
He's dead he's dead.
Why does he keep slowing?
What's going on?
You see this?
You don't you don't you know you don't see a beam at all.
No I don't.
Can you just re-click on me?
Like medic has been broken in this game for like seven years.
Watch it come on I watch it.
Oh lord it's true.
I watched him hi don't don't peek.
I knew you were going to do that and you took so long to line it up.
Is this the magic medic amulet thing?
I was just waiting for how long is it going to take German to peek?
Is this where I talk about the magic medic amulet that I wanted?
Is this the same video?
What video do I describe the magic medic amulet?
No okay.
I'm sorry I'm really sorry because I was like we were getting we were getting close to winning that.
Yeah yeah I mean we were right up there you're you're building crits.
You shouldn't have even mentioned it.
I shouldn't have but I.
How do you take that hit sound?
There's a soldier that hat he's behind us.
I don't know if he's gonna rocket jump up here.
Wouldn't that just get on your nerves?
He might rocket jump up here.
No no we're good we're good.
Oh get that 70 percent.
Get that get that last 30 percent.
Let's climb up again let's climb up again let's climb up.
I gotta say everything like four times because you're an infant.
You could have just said it once and I would have understood.
Uh-oh uh-oh not good not good that was that was a big one.
I think the stream turned off for like five straight seconds.
Okay um again I want to make I'm gonna make it really clear again.
Oh if if we turn off I'm sorry.
I'll just I'm gonna try to get this fixed as soon as possible.
Thanks for hanging out regardless.
Thanks for chilling out watching old videos.
I have a few more times you didn't.
Oh my god this is not I'm not doing this on purpose I promise you.
That was no you're knocking me off that's what happened.
That's yeah that's what happened.
Can you seriously what I used it.
Is that what you wanted?
Not right back step.
Are you joking?
No okay that I looked real bad right there.
Let me just like let me just clarify this for a second.
Yeah I mean guys come on he doesn't usually snort.
All right I want to say is that you used it at a time that was not opportune for me.
And it's because I didn't scream and you were unsure if I wanted it that time.
He doesn't usually snort.
All right it's a hundred percent flawless.
You know crazily enough like really truly crazily enough you are correct.
I thought you will I thought you said use it.
No I was gonna say like we're getting like we're getting ready to use it like
I want to let's wait until we turn around the corner climb up here again.
Fuck.
Can you do it can you do it?
Look I'm gonna do it don't worry just don't knock me off.
If we keep getting defibrillated.
You think we can win this we've had them at their last.
It's like.
It's been right here this is a win.
Watch out for those spies.
I have I'm don't worry I'm I'm looking back I'm checking the perimeter.
This guy's just building a sentry.
Oh we're capping the we didn't even do anything.
We did it we won nice job.
Yeah great excellent stuff excellent stuff great showmanship of shows.
Who even capped that?
I don't know some dude.
Can I get you uh french fries can I get you anything out anything at all let me know
anything I am here.
Can you just get me to mid with 300 health.
Buffer size creeps is zero yeah that's why I'm 99 please.
Okay well I'll give that to you right after we we get there.
Okay okay we're about there um let me check my my pants.
Okay there's time oh spy what what what what.
Well you made the joke and you got the spy so that he had plenty of time to stab you.
It was very scary.
Okay let's go let's go let's go let's go pick up the pace pick up the pace.
We want to win this in under one minute.
This is the speed run under one minute.
Are you sure we're gonna be able to do it?
Yes I think we do it.
I'm up this is a climb strat we're gonna we're gonna keep doing the climb.
I had trouble getting up.
I had trouble and we got scouts.
I always had trouble in the source engine jumping.
Got it I understood I completely understood.
Jumping and crouching and landing on stuff in the source engine was always just hard.
Okay okay it works a lot better when I scream.
I'm dead no there's just engineers everywhere.
You got it did it did it did it got it got it and we did it.
Seven I why am I saying these 10 I'm really impressed with the 10 points.
Ten is a number seven's also a number two.
No no no no no no no no end of the screen.
I am back here.
I have to sneeze the sneezing doesn't mean use the crits.
Knew it.
You screamed you screamed.
You told me if there's a scream use the crits.
I said I'm gonna sneeze and the sneeze doesn't mean to pop it.
I wasn't here I was out of the room.
Handball showdown the funny part about handball showdown is that
he didn't want to upload that video he thought it was it was a terrible video.
I remember we watched it back and he was just he was just saying himself
well handball was really a bad game battle of the executives.
Let's see what we got for time here.
Hold on give me one moment.
I have to check my phone.
The frog video the like that the that amazing kind of frog video whatever it was.
Okay just want to because I got to pick up Kim.
And that was one of the reasons why I started a little early.
Unfortunately did not know we were going to run into this bullshit
which is the internet stuff but it's all good.
So let's do the battle of the executives that sounds like a good one.
I remember that one also there's a second one didn't they come up with two of them.
There's another one of these that's available isn't there.
I think star wanted to play I forget what the name of the game was it's like something like
dwarf like left for dead dwarf game.
I don't know what it was supposed to be looked fun though forget what it was called.
No not vermin tide it was something else deep rock galactic I think that's it yeah.
He was talking about playing that and then we really should play
the we really should play the battle of the executives too.
Sorry there's an ad get that game now.
Well I mean I will when me and star are going to play it left for dwarf.
All right this is battle of the executives.
Thank you for joining us on impromptu watch old video night or watch old video day.
It's fun to look back though it is here we go.
If that scumbag thinks he can take us on if he thinks he's going to destroy our will and
take down our pride he has no idea what he's dealing with.
Sergeant truffle top you are my leader of the command unit.
You must take it forward and you must find him and destroy him.
Puffle duffel say hello to the missus for me of course who could forget you.
Bill ball baggins copyrighted character that I've just said when you're done with this
joke explain to me if there is anything else we can build besides these drones forever.
And you Anthony Wimblestein you have been my number one companion ever since we were two.
Maybe we had that birthday cake that time if we shared that birthday cake.
You have to meet me in the middle like like diplomats come forward.
All right so diplomats come forward.
So stop having them following you.
They're not close enough diplomats.
I don't remember any of this video.
They're going to start shooting.
No they're not.
See very stop.
They're not stopping.
How do you make him stop?
Was there a wait?
There's no way.
Technical difficulties.
Where are you?
I didn't put that on there.
With my executive right now.
Oh I see you walking.
I'm coming off.
Oh yeah you're technician.
This little guy with a gun to watch you run.
What an insignificant little like shit you are right now.
I zoom out to like the normal view and it's like there's an ant coming to get me.
In this?
Yeah.
Derek stop building me hallways.
It's gonna take me too long to get around this.
Just get inside of it.
This is never gonna happen if you keep building sections.
You just added like 10 minutes to my trip.
All right there you go.
Oh my god.
It's so long.
Oh well okay.
All right here I come.
This is so funny that you could do this.
I'm coming to your corporation right now.
Can you do this in the second game?
Oh yes you wanted to see me.
No no no put the gun down put the gun down put the gun down.
I can't put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
Look at this shitty douche smirk on.
Like yeah I'm gonna shoot you.
Yeah you think you got me in this what does your screen say?
CEO neutral login screen.
Why what did I do?
I got startled.
I got scared.
I thought you were trying to kill me.
I went back.
I sat down at the computer right now.
But I thought you were using like telekinetic powers to try to kill me.
Your executive is dead.
What?
This person's not alive.
They're just not alive.
I'm tapped into the link.
No you're dead.
Your guy's not even breathing.
You're just sitting there as a corpse.
Easy easy easy.
Whoa why are you in here?
Your guy's face is so fucked up.
One of his eyes is open and one of them is closed.
You are deep in thought right now.
That thing has taken over.
You've done that too many times.
You know what I mean?
Like you've done this so many times.
You like shouldn't be doing this anymore.
Where the hell did you go?
Oh dude that was rough.
Oh wait no.
I have to do one more thing before I head out.
I just got one more thing I need to do.
No!
What is going on?
This game is fucking so much fun.
He's beef raving.
Organ playing.
Don't look over here.
Whatever you do for like the next minute do not look over here.
Did you just make a unit that is playing an organ of death?
Nah.
You can turn around in 10 seconds and like notice that there's a monster behind you.
Really?
Yeah.
So you're telling me in 10 seconds I can turn around?
You might have to.
I would turn now.
Turn now.
You can't stop me.
He thinks he's so big.
He thinks he's so goddamn strong.
Do you think he's strong enough to take on the march of the C-3PO's?
I doubt it.
Oh shit.
Oh we both get them don't we?
I think we both get them.
Jack in the box.
Yeah we built some hinges on our warehouse.
Hey what are you doing over there?
Nothing much.
I'm just coming over here to kill you.
Yeah that's fine just get over right here and stand like right there.
Right over there?
Yeah stand over right there.
Okay I'm coming.
What is this wind?
What a waste of 500 billion dollars.
My grandfather told me this is the button.
My grandfather.
When you know you've been defeated.
The final stand.
Activate it.
Let him come.
They killed themselves.
What is this guy?
Oh yeah you can breach the other person's base with units.
I didn't.
I won.
Well how did you get out there?
Help.
What do you I don't understand how you did this.
Let me in.
Oh I'm gonna let you in.
Just be careful.
How did you get stuck out there?
He wanted to discuss something.
Yeah what did you want to discuss?
We're a military compound not too far away.
You've been yeah you know.
Didn't even want to come up with anything.
What did I do again?
You gave up halfway through.
You know what it doesn't matter.
We were playing for two hours.
Two fucking hours of this.
What the hell have we been doing?
It's true.
It's true we didn't even play the game.
We had a tendency to do that though.
We would just not do anything for like three hours.
And then be like you know what that was kind of fun.
I think that would be a pretty good video.
Damnation.
I think yeah Damnation is a good one to do too.
So we'll do we'll do Damnation.
We'll do Damnation Dying Light.
And then we'll see where we are from there.
Let's do Damnation.
Oh I remember this one.
This is the Pop Tarts thing.
I remember this one.
This is actually this is the video where Star laughed harder than anything he's ever done.
For my what I remember.
He almost threw up laughing at like the stupid motorcycle I think right.
I believe this is that video.
I've never heard him laugh as hard as he did here.
No I've never heard him go harder than this.
All right here we go.
Let's get it on the screen why don't we.
Okay three two one go for it.
Extreme content.
Yeah on.
What is extreme content?
What does that mean?
It's not blood or gore.
Usually they the blood or gore is a checkbox.
Watch first scene of this game.
There's just gonna be tits everywhere.
What's I asked you a question.
I don't know.
I know she told me.
Rourke.
Joaquin.
That's the that's this person's name Joaquin.
That's something that like.
I want to move this way.
I'm not able to separate.
Oh well I want to move this way.
It's more comfortable in this seat.
Yeah that's better.
It's more comfy this way.
Now I got like a good I can like sit over here and your chats over here too.
So I got chat and I got the video.
There you go.
All right here we go.
Nice rat tail whatever.
That's the that's this person's name Joaquin.
That's something that like Chung Li would scream when she shoots a fireball.
I'm able to separate.
Joaquin.
Many of this old boy's basic controls.
Holy shit.
This is so loud.
Loud.
This is the loudest thing I've ever experienced.
Let you come alone.
Joaquin.
I hear that in my dreams.
Does it seriously have to be this loud?
I told you he was gonna die.
Ten bucks.
Is he gonna get run over by a motorcycle too?
That's been the best.
What?
What an awful shot.
And you're not shooting him.
How was you missing that?
How did you miss those three shots?
I could do that.
Shoot him.
He's already gone.
Star.
Yes.
I didn't want to be the first one to say this but I truly think
I truly think this weird agency is poisoning the water supply.
Oh no.
Where is he?
Breakfast is almost served.
Honey.
I have your favorite Pop-Tarts.
Pop-Tarts.
This is the one window though.
No, you broke it.
Did you see me trying to come through it?
You fucking broke it and you messed up the joke.
Honey.
I've got your favorite breakfast snack here waiting for you.
It's Pop-Tart.
Pop-Tart.
His head hits the top.
Honey.
You know there's Pop-Tarts down here.
Huh?
What?
Pop-Tarts?
You fucking idiot dick.
Get in there.
You know I've got all these breakfast toaster strudel things here.
They're they remind me.
Toaster strudel.
I got it in.
Off of Moria.
I remember this shit.
Don't we drive it back?
All right, I got it in.
I got it in the house.
I don't know what to do.
I don't.
I'm stuck.
Well, get off.
Get off of it so we can do this joke.
I kind of can't do it.
I can't.
Didn't you?
Yeah, I did from this.
Once we start to actually drive it on the road.
All right, I'm gonna get off.
I almost passed out.
You got this on the second floor?
Honey, I have your favorite breakfast food.
Pop-Tart.
Yeah, that was so cool.
This is lagging so bad.
This is it.
This game just got so much better.
You can't take that.
You cannot drive like that.
The walls.
Riding on the walls.
Look at that.
That's fucking sick.
Listen to him.
No, don't go.
I'm dead.
I thought I died.
I was dead.
I was like, I'm like gonna burga please throw up right now.
Why would you be able to do that?
Oh my god.
Listen to him.
Yeah, he's fucking going nuts.
What is extreme content?
What does that mean?
This was such a boring game.
And then they added this to it.
Oh, you're in another room.
Watch out for this guy.
I'm gonna die.
No, what?
I think you ran me over.
I'm dead.
All right.
Here's your last chance, honey.
They're nice and piping hot.
Pop-Tart.
Please give me the Pop-Tart.
Yes.
Oh, fuck.
We got it.
Oh, he spawns in the room, right?
I'm gonna use my superpowers to see where he is.
I'm not climbing up.
This is like on all those movies you watch with like the
Oh, the school bus is just hanging by a thread.
How much it's going.
I'm stuck perfectly.
Like I have no traction.
You cannot move at all?
No.
You cannot move this at all.
He just fly off?
Oh, yeah.
Sure, you can't.
No, no.
Hitting the jet booster on the back kind of help.
All right.
I'm done.
I'm out of this fucking game.
Chalk it up for games that you kind of wish that you played more of.
You kind of wish that you played that way more than you actually did.
But someone was asking why are we doing this?
Why are we doing?
Wait, where are you?
You're over here.
What camera are we looking at right now?
Because I have dropped just about 100,000 frames.
So I couldn't really do anything.
So we're just handing it out.
Figured we'd just watch some videos for a few hours.
It's bad.
But let's watch Dying Light.
Yeah, I think I actually have to go from here.
This is fun.
Yeah, I'm glad we got it.
I'm glad I didn't just like turn it off.
I'm glad we got to at least stream for three, four plus hours here.
So let's watch the Dying Light video.
I mean, we salvaged the stream.
It was salvaged.
If we can at least hang out.
Dying Light.
Is that, I think it's the star.
It's a star video, right?
No, we both made one of these.
It, oh, okay.
So I have one too.
This is Legend of the Tunnel Troll.
They're both good.
Let me get this on here.
Legend of the Tunnel Troll.
That, oh, the, the tunnel.
Here, here's another one of those.
We tried to do something over and over again.
It just doesn't work.
We did that quite often.
We tried, many times.
And sometimes you guys are only seeing like 20% of the attempts.
Okay, let's get that out of the way.
And let's get that back on the screen.
I'll get back on screen too.
Why not?
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Okay, so that's what that does.
Its head came off.
Yeah, interesting.
Okay, interesting.
Sir, you appear to be on fire.
Just dead.
What?
Why?
I thought I had more health than that.
You just instant died.
That fake laugh.
Funny, funny, funny, funny.
Skip, skip, skip.
It's going in my video.
Yes, it is.
What's your response to what you just did?
Very quickly.
Well, I want to hear like, what's your response.
I'm bored.
Here's another funny tidbit for you.
We used to be recorded saying all kinds of fucking weird shit.
And it would always be that.
You would always be like, no, no, no, dude, don't put that in your video.
And it would be fun sometimes to put it in anyways.
Like, don't, dude, don't put that in.
That's not something you should put in the video.
No, dude, I'm gonna.
No, don't, don't, don't.
Dude, like, what about my reputation?
And sometimes you just put it in.
Sometimes you just put it in.
Got my gun.
Oh, what do you guys got?
What's going on over here, boys?
Put your hands up.
Put your fucking hands up.
Hands in the air.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Doesn't need to fucking ruin that guy.
I destroyed it.
That was like.
Psycho.
I wasn't the psycho.
I didn't do it.
The guy threw a fucking axe in his head.
And he looks left and right.
Like, what the fuck do I do now?
Yeah, he was like, still.
All right.
This game was so fucked.
It was just so all over the place.
Like two seconds.
He was just like, oh, shit.
Okay.
There's an action.
My fucking head.
What am I doing?
Do I run away?
Got real dark, real quick.
Oh, no, no, no.
No.
Somewhere.
Can I eat these trees?
No.
I don't know.
I really just don't know anything about where I am right now.
Who goes there?
This is the tunnel and I am its troll.
What do you want?
I just was looking for some food, looking for some supplies.
I just wanted to find something.
When I come in, I have food and supplies.
I have both of those.
I have a lot of them.
Is this some kind of trick?
No, I'm not a troll.
All right.
I believe you.
Come in.
What do you got back here?
Do you have any?
I got this.
What happened?
Just you wait 30 or 40 seconds.
Something real bad is coming.
Didn't work.
You got to do it again.
Can I eat these trees?
Maybe I can chew on the bark and get some syrup.
I really don't know.
I'm just...
What is that?
Who goes there?
Who tries to enter the tunnel of the troll?
Not me.
I was just looking for some supplies and maybe some food to eat.
Well, hey, I have supplies and food all back here.
If you just want to come in the tunnel for a second.
Some kind of trick?
No, I'm not a troll.
Oh, okay.
I believe you.
Just come in.
It'll be everything.
I really hope you have...
I hope you have pizza rolls.
What's this?
What have you done to me?
What have you done?
I just wait like 30 to 40 seconds microwave.
What are you talking about?
What am I waiting 30 or 40 seconds?
This joke is so bad.
It is.
It really is.
This is not like this.
This is worse than the fucking jump through the glass Pop-Tart joke.
Oh, call back.
That was a call back.
Why can't we not get the fuck off this stupid troll joke?
I'm dropping out.
We have to stop this now.
Hey, it's me.
Stock scream.
That did sound like a stock scream.
That was a stock scream.
Fucking hate troll.
I'll get this troll secret.
They're my secret.
Get away from me.
I'm sick of it.
I have to troll.
I have to fucking hate troll.
I can't, man.
Oh my fucking god.
Stupid troll joke.
I'm dropping out.
We have to stop this now.
Hey, it's me.
Made it onto one of the towers.
You know we're both jumping off, right?
Edit that part out.
There's a fucking zombie up here.
Hold on.
Don't do anything to him.
How would you have ever made it up here?
She doesn't even have a arm.
This zombie is armed.
One armed climbed up here.
Are you telling me that's what happened?
No way.
What if she got up and just fly back up?
That's where this came from.
That is where this came from.
Hurry.
Quickly.
Whoa.
It's a spitter.
That cut scene just healed me.
I'm shouting because this fucked up infected motherfucker
with guts hanging out of his mouth just spit a bunch of toxic snot at me.
Motherfucker.
Toxic motherfucker was fucking snot in his mouth.
Turn your light off.
Uh.
Oh look there's like a door here.
Oh whoa I thought it was real.
All right I want you to go through my time travel machine
as you see here my lovely assistant head on through and I'll see you in a year 1900.
That's not as funny as I thought it was gonna be.
What the fuck?
Hey it's okay.
Are you all right sir?
Hey you just dropped like 10,000 feet.
Forgot that happened.
Hey what were we doing earlier?
Let's say go let's go go let's do parkour and jump.
Oh what are you doing?
This is such a fun multiplayer game it really was.
I'm pushing the boat.
No what is he doing?
You don't know what it looks like for you guys.
I just want to ride the boat.
I just want to go.
That's like somebody just learned unity and this is what they're they didn't animate anything.
They just learned how to like rig somebody in unity.
I got it.
He got it.
Got it.
I got it.
He got it.
All right my turn.
How did you even attempt to do that?
I have no idea how you even tried.
There's a place you can stand where it's like completely it's really really easy to do.
All right what if I like start to if I start to fall and can I grab it maybe?
Oh I remember this.
No I wouldn't do it that way.
Going for it.
Look what I just did.
You want to talk about like falling and grabbing onto something?
Wow Jermis is the master of falling and grabbing onto things.
I'm fucking the man.
Back to square one.
Everyone I want all the actors.
No shit no dude.
Hey just wait just wait like 30 seconds.
Yeah guess what I'm they're gonna.
Come on.
No get the fuck out of here.
Oh god damn it.
We have to watch the other one.
We're gonna watch the other one.
We're gonna watch Star's video.
Here's the thing that this is the thing.
Star and I when we played the same game.
Some more little youtuber lore for you.
We never made the same video.
We always made it a point to make completely different videos.
Because we didn't want it to just be.
Oh here's the same video from another perspective.
We wanted to always have completely different videos.
And it would sometimes would cause lighthearted arguments.
Because we would get into these little.
Oh that was really good.
That was a really fun clip.
Who's getting that one?
I'd be like oh well you got like.
You got the guy like the car flipping and crushing the guy's head.
Yeah but I like the.
I think I should have that one.
I should have that clip.
That should be my clip.
That's where like need a clip or need a clip.
We would talk about what.
Who was going to have what and what in their video.
And sometimes I remember specifically watching a video of his.
And there was like a clip that I thought was really good.
And I was like damn I really wanted that one.
And he did the same thing though.
He did the same thing.
He'd watch videos of mine and be like.
Oh that was like that's better from my perspective.
It should have been mine.
So but it turned out pretty good.
Because you never watched a video twice.
From just a different camera angle.
It was always a different video.
So let's case in point.
Let's watch it right now and you'll see.
I think we would share like maybe like sometimes it'd be.
If there was something really really funny from another perspective.
Typically it would be different though.
Very different.
His video is titled Zombie Jackass.
Tubers that care.
Well I honestly I just.
I just didn't want and neither did he.
It and this is obviously I don't want to.
You know throw unnecessary shade at.
Hold on it's talking to me in my ear.
It froze on me again.
But what I was saying is it.
Typically what you'd have you know.
Let's say let's say two or three people are recording together right.
And then they all upload the same exact footage.
It's just from a different angle.
And sometimes it wouldn't even be from a different angle.
Sometimes it'd be a game that was not a separate angle.
It was just here's the video three more times.
We just came to a conclusion together.
That it was we didn't really want to do that.
We didn't want to have that kind of scenario play out.
Because then if you've seen stars video.
Then you've already seen my video.
You've already seen you've already seen it.
What could we add to that to make it so it was different for you.
And but also to you know backtrack.
Some people were uploading like three or four times a day.
We didn't do that.
I uploaded like twice a week.
Maybe two or three times a week.
Here we go.
Three two one zero zero.
This is Steve and this is the fish tank.
Run run.
Hey friend.
I did put it down.
He's gone.
This one.
There is this one.
It's a zombie.
You have to go on this bowl on the outside.
You fucking god damn it.
What did you.
I'm gonna make it.
I didn't make it.
You can't sleep now.
Yeah I can't sleep.
Yeah we just have to make our way to.
Where are you?
I'm down at the bottom.
Okay I'm coming.
What what I just zipped on what.
How do I do that?
I just wanted to jump to my death.
Oh I'm coming.
Oh wow.
Skip.
They won't come in the door.
Oh yeah this.
Come on.
Come get us.
Don't shine the light on it.
It hurts them.
Let them like run at us.
Oh it's almost daytime.
They're just gonna like start dying.
Is this gonna be like Minecraft?
Are they gonna just sound like burning?
Come here you.
Knight survived.
Yeah he's just running now.
Chase them.
Oh yeah follow this guy.
Follow him.
Do not let this guy get away.
We need to find like the hideout for where these guys are.
Get out of the way.
You don't want to fucking shoot her.
Oh my god I'm gonna get a burn.
Damn it.
Oh which way do I go here?
I just my mom's gonna be so pissed at me.
How is he not dead yet?
Like what are you scared of?
I don't know.
Oh he jumped up here.
Go go go.
Oh no he can't get away.
Coffee.
Cheetos.
Chicken.
Hey can we help you?
Can we find your house or something?
Do you need help?
Uh yeah I could use a little bit of help.
He's on the run.
Hold on I need to see that again.
Do you need help?
Uh yeah I could use a little bit of help.
He's on the run.
He just hit his face.
It looks like he tried to slide under the fence.
He hit his head and died.
No we like cut him up now.
Who's Kratos?
Is that is that my name?
Did you just call someone on the phone?
Oh god I hear that and I don't even care.
He edited this like making it look like he fell for like 10 seconds.
It was like 5,000 foot drop.
I don't even know what we were trying to do.
Good joke.
Great joke.
That was a real good real good joke.
Your favorite pop tart cereal.
They're like come on let's go.
You think you can take me on?
You're just a bully.
Stay in there.
Another propane tank.
Stay here?
Yeah.
Why am I staying in here?
Hold on stay in there for a second.
We also would trade footage to each other if somebody had something funny.
Stay in there for a second.
Jerma I was never in there.
Yeah I know it's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
Hold on stay in there for a second.
Stay in there for a second.
All right Jerma I was never in there.
I was standing right next to you the whole time.
I'm dead.
Okay this thing seems to be going well.
She's not gonna hear us coming.
Here comes my super stealth patented ninja kick.
Lagged.
Yes I'm a badass.
That actually happens in the game too.
Essentially that character only.
Why why why did I do that?
I sat here and I did that.
Okay that's what you have to understand.
Foliage is pretty fucking cool dude.
Look at all those.
Is that fucking hailing out right now?
Thank god.
Run.
There's like a bunch of birds.
First impression.
First impression of the birds.
They're pretty cool.
First impression of the zombies.
A little bit buttery on the hit there.
A little bit buttery.
And a little bit cream cheesy.
You know first impression of the zombie?
Cream cheese.
Somebody's throwing rocks.
No it's just I think it's like a hail or something weird.
All right we'll do a couple more.
And then I do have to leave.
Not because of the internet.
I mean it's been a pain in the ass.
But because I have to get Kim.
So we'll do the bits and everything.
We will.
But this stream was going to be a little shorter than usual.
Probably about like five-ish hours.
It could have been potentially longer.
But you know the internet problem.
You know.
So let's do a couple more.
What else are we going to do here?
I have to do the definition.
Add the definition of the German joke.
I mean we just watched the two of them.
I guess I'll put it on.
Just because we just watched them both.
It's an unlisted video right?
It's a hidden video.
Was it ever publiced?
Mods linking the good version.
What do you mean the good version?
There's been the good version.
Why is there a good version?
No I'm not going to watch me watching Star watch definition of a German joke.
No I'm going to watch me watching me in.
This is going to be ultra compression.
All right.
I'll watch it.
So you're going to get you're going to get dual commentary from the both of us.
I'm getting like a flash player error.
What the fuck is going on here?
I don't have flash anymore.
But not a flash.
It was like a little thing.
A little puzzle piece.
All right.
I should have it.
And here's the thing.
A lot of people have probably haven't seen this.
A lot of you probably have not seen this video.
So I guess we're going to have to give you some context.
Context is check it out.
All right.
I'm going to give my context and he can give his context.
Okay.
So when I play games and this is even like off stream or on stream.
Doesn't matter.
I just kind of say stuff.
Even when the camera's not even on.
I just talk.
I say anything.
I repeat something over and over again.
I'll just like a song.
I'll just say a song.
I'll say a line just over and over and over again.
Just because it's my brain just functioning and working overtime for no reason.
So it's just like a stream of consciousness.
Yeah.
Just it just flows out of my brain and I just do it.
So when we record these videos like you've been told before.
We edit a lot of shit.
And you cut out like all the times when you're like.
I believe I can fly.
I believe I can touch the sky.
And you do it like a hundred times.
You're just like, ah, that's not I'm going to get rid of that.
Because why would anybody want to hear me do that a hundred times?
Right.
Many of you guys may not have seen the definition of a German joke.
I wanted to watch this earlier and I forgot about it.
Oh, Star Chat.
This was one of the secret videos apart with the zombie jackass.
You can see zombie jackass 666 dude zombies amount of views.
The secret video 45,000 views.
I wish I had made this public.
This is one of my favorite videos I've ever made of me in German.
And it is so insanely bad.
It is so stupid.
But this is German in a one minute, 37 second nutshell.
This is like who he is as a person.
Got it.
What's in the crate?
Oh, dude, there's a fucking knife.
There's coffee, cheese, it's chicken.
Hold on.
This is what I'm saying.
Like we're compressing it like four times.
I got to turn this all the way up.
I'm not sure I can even turn this up.
That's loud.
But I don't think I can turn this up anymore.
All right, here we go.
I tried.
Stupid.
But this is German in a one minute, 37 second nutshell.
This is like who he is as a person.
Got it.
What's in the crate?
What am I gonna get?
Oh, dude, there's a fucking knife.
There's coffee, cheese, it's chicken.
Coffee, chicken, cheese, it's chicken.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
It is like triggering me to do it.
We're gonna assume, we're gonna watch out.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
Stop talking about coffee, Cheetos, or chicken.
He's like enabling me.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
I didn't even realize this.
Holy shit.
Wow.
I didn't even pick this up.
It's been years.
He is enabling me to do this shit.
He's like triggering me to like do it.
He's like keeping me enabled.
Listen.
Eat Cheetos, chicken.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
Oh, coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
Chicken.
Yeah.
Oh, coffee.
Whoa.
Cheetos, chicken.
Coffee, Cheetos.
Perhaps I should take both.
I guess I'll take both.
Might be getting some Cheeto.
Might be getting some coffee.
Chicken, Cheetos, coffee, coffee.
Fucking coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
Oh, really?
Because guess what's in here.
Coffee, Cheetos, chicken.
There actually was coffee in there.
I know.
Yes.
I fucking loved it.
I laugh every time I watch it.
It is so bad.
I'm sitting here like I didn't mute my mic.
I'm like trying not to laugh to like not go over the video.
I want you to public it right now.
Did he public it though?
I don't even know if that works.
This is from January 30th, 2015.
What's going to happen next?
That's a great description.
What?
Yeah.
What's the next part?
Is he going to keep doing it?
Again?
God.
Listen.
Don't tell Jerm I've ever said anything nice about him.
But he is so good at making absolutely nothing funny sometimes
that for a while it was actually discouraging me from making videos.
At least that style of video.
I like my basically series because I feel like that's where I'm good at.
He could just go ahead and fucking make coffee,
Cheetos, and chicken funny for no fucking reason.
Well, hey, hold on, Star.
Before you let me interrupt you there.
His videos are some of the funniest fucking things I've ever watched.
Some of those edited videos are like 11 out of 10.
So friendship isn't friendship.
Just wonderful.
No, I think that, you know, whatever, I'll say it.
I think that I think that Star had some of the best videos on YouTube.
You know, I still think he does.
And I uploaded two.
I thought I uploaded some all right ones over the years.
You know, isn't that right?
Isn't that right, Star?
I cut the shirt on to prove it.
No, but for real, I will forever cherish how much fun this all was.
I've been 90 fucking years old just watching Family Feud in a bed.
And like somebody will say the word like Cheetos and I'll be like,
I remember that one.
That was a much slayed.
It's true.
That's fucking amazing.
But yeah, that's me being fucking strange and I just say words.
We will do, oh, mood.
Mood.
Oh yeah, mood.
What's the, because we're reaching over here about,
we'll be at about five hours after the bits probably.
Public that video?
I, that's his video.
I don't have, I don't have control over his channel.
Intervention.
Bargain Bin Beach Party.
Bloody Trapland.
You mad, bro.
You, what's this?
Why are you doing the you mad, bro thing?
Oh, yeah, we did Intervention.
We did Tactical Intervention already.
Zombie Penis.
Yeah, Zombie Penis is a good one.
Battle of the Toys.
That's also a good one too.
The, Battle of the Bots.
Battle of the Brainless Bots.
That's another good one.
All right, all right.
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna do, we'll do Battle of the Brainless Bots
and then I'm gonna have to get out of here.
And I'm not gonna be live for at least tomorrow.
I'm gonna try to come back on Tuesday.
But I desperately need to get this fixed.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes over the next 48 hours
to make sure it works.
Because 100,000 drop frames is just unacceptable.
It's just, it's, it's unacceptable.
It is.
All right, let's get this on screen.
Do whatever, anything.
Okay, this is Battle of the Brainless Bots.
This is a TF2 video.
I might as well do, go out on a TF2 video.
All right, here we go.
Battle of the Brainless Bots.
This is when I pretend to go back in time to hydro.
No, that's another video.
All right, here we go.
Battle of the Brainless Bots.
End on Jerma is mad.
We've, I think we've already watched Jerma is mad.
At least once on this stream before.
Whoops.
No, go in full screen.
Hey, what are you doing?
No, it crashed.
It crashed, it froze and crashed.
I guess that's a new word.
I mean, if you guys like this,
if you guys think this is cool, we can do this again.
The only reason why we started to do this in the first place
is just because of the internet.
That's the only reason why we did it.
But if people like this and people think it's fun to,
um, keep doing this.
I think my, like my actual browser keeps crashing.
Damn, yes, come on.
It brings in the bucks.
Nah, it's just fun to, I would only want to do this
if it was, um, like I hadn't seen them in a while.
I don't, I want to watch ones that I haven't seen
because it's almost like, I forget some of the shit
that's in these videos.
A lot of these things I forget, actually.
It's been so long and I've put together,
I've seen so many clips and I've seen
so many timelines, right?
That it's almost hard to remember.
All right, can I please fucking interact with this?
Finally, Jesus.
All right, took long enough.
All right, here we go.
Battle of the Brainless Bots.
Three, two, one.
Jeremy, I'm already just so exhausted
from even trying to put this together.
There hasn't been an ounce of enthusiasm
in my voice since we started talking about this,
but now we're ready.
I sent you the info, let's do this.
You like do not want to do this at all.
That's like makes it, I was like threw up.
Did you hear that?
A little bit, yeah.
So here's the, here's what the deal is, right?
So here's Star, he's the soldier right here.
He's on red team, I'm on blue team.
This is upward.
We are going to both have a team of easy mode bots.
That means our bots are at the lowest difficulty
they could possibly be at.
And why is there a tank?
This feels familiar.
So easy, easy mode.
No, no, don't break your own fucking server.
They kept training into him.
Can you give me one second
to like just explain what's happening?
Look at this mess.
I can't believe you made like a trail to yourself.
Okay.
Yeah, even in really didn't think
you were ever going to be able to do this.
You brought the truck punchline over into team fortress two
and your server is going to crash.
There's no way we're making out of this one.
This place is shutting down.
Shit's like flying by my screen.
Oh no, we invested our money poorly.
We didn't put it into a 401k.
It's disappearing.
All of our money is disappearing.
Quick, somebody make a German and Bitcoin joke.
Quick.
You wanted to invest in a lollipop company.
It's all gone.
All right.
Come on out.
They are not leaving.
Oh yeah, they were one person is.
It seems two of them has left.
All right, there we go.
They're making some progress.
Don't worry.
We have our sentry set up in a very optimal situation with a scout.
They're actually pretty smart.
I think my guys are pushing it.
We got it.
We got a heavy medic combination coming in through the front control point here.
Pyro coming out here.
It looks like you see your spine.
No, I'm watching them.
What are they doing?
What is he still doing?
Oh, okay.
I'm going to pay attention to something else.
Why is they doing a melee fight?
Are you kidding me right now?
What the fuck?
Did you seriously make every single person a spy?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
What are they doing?
What is your team doing?
What are?
Why are they freaking out in the corner over here?
That's just what spies do.
This is what you should be aiming for.
Oh, make sure you're disguised.
Yeah, they keep jumping and jumping.
I just heard like 10 seconds.
I wonder why they're trying to jump through the boards.
That doesn't work like that.
You're not like made out of taffy.
Here we go.
Here they come.
They're just all disguised as the same person.
Don't even tell me.
Please don't tell me they're all going to keep coming out of this door.
Where else would they go?
I don't know.
There's only one option.
I am a spy.
I go out this door.
All you a spy is an enemy.
I think you like broke them.
Hold on.
Let me see where they are.
I forget where they are.
Are they done?
No, they're all going out the front door now.
They're all going out the front door.
That spy is an enemy.
Okay, this is stupid.
Nobody's even attacking.
You don't want to tell me what stupid is.
No, they're going after each other.
No.
Did you get backstabbed?
I got backstabbed.
There was one too many of them.
No one's even going to go for the point.
This is going to last exactly three minutes and 32 seconds
because there's absolutely no way any of these brainless son of a bitches
are going to go for that point.
Okay, this one engineer is really just going for gold.
We actually capped it.
How the hell did that happen?
I don't know.
Maybe it had something to do with the tank.
They just crushed that guy.
It's just bad.
It just starts running people over.
They're all going to get stuck on it.
Blocking the door.
Yeah, this guy's freaking out.
Let's get trickstabbed.
No, no, no.
Is it actually making its way in?
No, it's not.
Is it?
Please crush them.
You go like crushing them.
No, it didn't kill them.
They got in.
It's fine right here.
It's just getting fucking run over.
It's trying to like shoot it with a shotgun.
I'm going to die.
This should not have happened.
They're actually doing enough damage to it.
Here are some engineers on the back of the tanks.
Yes.
I'm going to kill it.
Oh, you didn't think this could get even dumber.
Elders react.
They just keep getting run over.
All right, redo, retake, redo.
I need like a second before I throw up.
Why are they all taunting?
They don't even know what to shoot yet.
Why are they not shooting you?
Because the round doesn't start.
I'm not supposed to be on here.
Oh, they're that confused about the round not being started yet.
That they refuse to shoot you.
What?
What are they?
This doesn't make any...
Wait, oh, I want to see what happens in one second.
How is anybody on Blue Team going to get anything done?
You have such a huge advantage.
Because you're allowed to build your sentries first.
My guys are being like dumbasses trying to do like leapfrog in the spawn.
Hey, you could be a little bit more respectful.
Just wait.
Wait till this 12 seconds counts down.
I bet you every single one of these guys just walks out and just gets eaten alive.
Eaten alive by what?
We barely have a defense.
The sentry mosquitoes.
All right, here we go.
Why do you need a catchphrase for everything?
Here we go.
Let's see what happens.
That's better than anything else is going to work.
Because they all backed up.
Why do you have to have a catchphrase for everything?
Let's build it back here.
Let's start getting these teleporters up.
They're so confused.
Fioritizing the teleporters over sentries.
Yeah, they'd rather build teleporters than sentries.
No, seriously, this was done.
The joke was over.
That joke ended so long ago.
Why do you have to fucking ruin everything?
Good times.
Good times, man.
I'm just in the corner over here hanging out.
Good times.
All right, guys.
I have to end the stream.
Oh, back when I was in my prime.
I was so, I was so handsome.
I do apologize again for the extreme internet problems.
But I'm going to try to get them fixed.
That's all I can do.
I'm just going to try.
Hopefully we can come back strong here without any problems at all on Tuesday.
If for some reason it's still really bad on Tuesday
and I can get it fixed on Tuesday, I'll let you know.
At this point, I don't know.
I'm shooting for Tuesday.
So just keep an eye on the sus over the next 24 hours and we'll find out.
But yeah, this was fucking fun.
It makes me happy that we can kind of just go back
and watch some of those old videos.
You guys are fucking awesome.
It's been a long time.
It's been fucking almost 10 goddamn years.
Holy shit.
Oh, but let us say good night for now.
See you again possibly on Tuesday.
I will keep you updated.
I will probably make a tweet about it just to make sure everyone knows what's going on.
Thanks for watching.
As always, at least we salvaged it, right?
So let's go to the bits from earlier today.
See you soon.
Take care.
If you thought that was fun, we can do it again.
I just, I don't really do a whole lot of kind of react
or watch kind of videos on stream type of stuff.
But every once in a while, it's fine.
You know, do that like once every couple months or something once a month.
We'll see.
That was fun.
So let's head back to four or five hours ago here.
We had, we had a lot of community subs.
We had a bunch from, we'd five from Kazzy.
We had five from soup store.
Thank you for those.
We had three dollars from, from thanks for the FAMAS.
Thanks for the three bucks.
It's been, I've been watching you for so many years.
It's needs to do with retrospective.
Yeah, that's the first time I've watched those videos
since at least a few years.
So it's cool.
But thank you for the three dollars.
First time I've ever seen a stream.
Thanks for being, thanks to being British.
But thank you for helping me through a lot in the past few years.
Much love.
Thanks to being British, British.
Oh, the time zone, right?
The time zone.
Oh, I was like, wait, what?
I was like, I'm British, am I?
Multi trip, thanks to the three dollars.
Have some money to make you feel better.
No, I'm sorry.
I can't, I can't let it get to me anymore.
You know, I can't like, it's going to happen.
I'd rather just relax and just deal with it, right?
That I, what's going to happen if I get fucking angry and furious?
No, I can't believe that shit.
It's not going to do anything.
So just make what you can with what you got, right?
That's what you can do.
I'm not going to let it bother me.
And it turned out to be a fun stream anyway.
So that's fine.
Sam and Max though, that's a, we got to figure out where I'm going to put that.
Because I want to do Garden Flipper DLC.
When I, the first stream when I come back is probably,
we'll probably have to make, I don't know, it's going to be hard.
I'm going to, I'll put it somewhere next week.
So we're going to do Garden Flipper when we come back.
And then I want to play those episodes in Sam and Max,
because we just kind of get screwed over today.
We'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out, don't worry.
But thank you to some guy for the 15 bucks.
Thank you, some guy.
I got screwed by the last course of this semester last Friday pretty hard.
I probably failed it as well.
At least you put a smile on my face
due to the fact that you are screwed even harder by cocks.
But thank you for the 15 dollars.
I'm not sure what, what course it was,
or what classes are, you know, fucking with you.
But all you can do is, you know, if you have, you know,
some bad grades or bad GPA or had something happen,
you just got to keep doing it.
Keep, try, you know.
Do what you can.
I had a 4.0 semester.
Well, aren't you Mr. Smart?
I had a couple of spots in college where I didn't do very well.
I was just borderline above what's it called?
Probation, right?
Academic probation.
I was like maybe, I was like,
I was probably two or three tests away,
or one letter grade away from being on academic probation.
But then I, I kind of got myself situated.
I started to do better.
I had like a 3.0, I think, total,
or like a 2.9 or like a 3.1 or something, whatever it was.
But all you can do is just keep going.
There's no secret formula, right?
But yeah, I've had my fair share of troubles in school.
But thank you for the 15 dollars.
Wish you luck.
Hopefully you can figure it out.
Thank you.
Son of Genova, thanks for the 250.
This was one of your best moments.
This was one of the best moments.
Oh, this is the...
That's true.
You will quiet, everyone will be quiet and say,
what is he doing?
Because you're the teacher.
You're not supposed to do that.
The teacher is not supposed to make the weird noises.
The kids are.
So that's just like, why did he just do that?
Silence.
Okay.
So now that I have your attention,
but thank you for the 250.
And that like shitty mic,
like was so bad.
That was the pre-move mic.
Thank you, Frost, for the five dollars.
I hope chat doesn't bother you too much
when internet stuff is happening.
I watch no matter what
because you are quite a comedic talent.
Thanks for the five dollars, Frost Tro.
No, it...
Chat doesn't bother me when that happens.
It bothers me that I want the stream to be fun
and watchable and I don't want it to buffer
and cut out on people.
And when it happens, I get frustrated at that
because I want the stream to be good.
I want the stream to be...
I can pay attention and we can go through something
and you don't have to worry about some other force
negatively affecting your stream.
So no, chat messing around.
And no, that's not...
That's not the issue.
The issue is I want the stream to be watchable.
And if it isn't, then I have a problem
because that's what I'm doing here.
But I expect it to be fixed in the next couple of days.
I do.
I really do.
I have somebody...
I have a supervisor at Cox that every time there's a problem like this,
it takes like a week or two, but they get it done.
They fix it.
It's over and it's good for like three months.
So I'm confident that they will get it done.
I am.
At least I hope so.
Otherwise, that would be bad.
But thank you, Frost.
Thank you, Mr. Atigan, for these six dollars here.
Jermyn, when he's upset and angry,
don't forget about the baby running into the cabinets
in layers of fear.
That's true.
That was unbelievable.
That may have been the strangest thing I've ever captured
in front of my face.
And then they say, go box italics.
Why would I do that?
That's not...
No.
Thank you, Heldrich, for the five dollars.
Hey, Jerm, I've been watching for years.
Thank you for that.
I'm so happy to see how much success you've had.
You're an inspiration, my dude.
Keep up the good work, PS.
Alter Ego Mail had me crying laughing.
I'm glad it did because it was fucking crazy.
But thank you so much.
Glad to have you for that long.
Thank you so much for the five dollars as well.
Mentosium, thanks for the 250.
Any updates on Movie Night 2?
No.
I don't really have an update for you.
There's a lot of things
that I'm trying to do at the same time.
And that kind of fell backwards
behind a couple of the other things
that I am putting higher on the priority list.
So there are other things that have taken priority
from that second Movie Night
to like set it up.
Play Monster Rancher DS.
Yeah, I got to figure out how to cap DS
because there's a lot of games on DS to play
and mess around with.
Jerma lied about Movie Night 2.
Here it comes.
Make another one.
No, we'll eventually, we'll probably,
I think we'll eventually do it.
That was the most viewed stream ever.
Yeah, I know.
But it's important to me
that even if something,
let's say something really works
and it's really like, for instance like that
and like the Jerma Rumbles,
there's a lot,
there was probably eight,
9,000 people watching the last Jerma Rumble.
Just because an audience is there that's large,
I want to make sure that it's done right.
And I don't want to just keep doing it just to do it
because I know that people will come and watch it.
I want to make sure that it's fun
and that it's worth doing
and that people will think it's fun
and it's not just something that I'm pumping out
on a, just to get it out there, right?
That's my philosophy for a lot of things.
Jerma lied about picking up Kim.
So maybe it would be easy
just to throw together that Movie Night
It's almost like I want it to be
the way that I want it to be.
It's weird to talk about.
When are you going to stream with Joel?
I'm not sure, there's two Joels.
Talking about Joel,
like the Joel that I just hung out with
or Joel the trash talking wrestling.
Yeah, we talked, he got really busy.
So yeah, you're talking about,
you're talking about Varg.
Yeah, he got really busy.
And he said, I'm really busy.
I'm sorry I was working.
He was working on a bunch of stuff.
So we just said, all right,
we'll figure it out some other time.
But he had a lot of projects going on at the time.
So I'll probably throw the line out
eventually here soon.
We were thinking maybe,
no, I'll keep that under wraps.
But there you'll probably see something interesting.
Co-op penis stream.
Why did I read that out loud?
And second of all, what are you talking about?
I don't know why I do it.
I'm telling you, I'm so unableable.
People could just say that.
I don't, did some stuff.
The coffee cheeto, like I just,
it's just, I have to say it.
I am like, so you can lead me
like with a carrot on a stick into a cliff.
I will fall off of it.
I'm very unableable.
But yeah, we'll see.
We'll see what happens.
Cad, thank you Cad.
BTV, resident video game developer.
Thanks for the 250.
Look at this ego maniac watching his old videos
in front of 4,300 people.
I bet he stares in the mirror for hours
talking to himself.
Yes, I do.
Yes, that does happen.
I will just have full conversations
with myself in the mirror.
I do it like all the time.
Full.
A full, into the mirror, full frontal.
And I just do a play to myself.
And I'm the actor and I'm the audience.
I knew it.
He's insane.
Thank you though.
Hey, thank you Lula Moore for the five dollars.
Please do the layers of fear video.
Um, not right now.
Not right now.
I've got to get out of here.
Save it for another time.
Thank you to Frodeon Weapon for the 350.
Thank you, Frodeon.
Not to be an attention hog,
but you taking my stream name idea made my day.
Dear my heart.
Plus, as much as I love Sam and Max,
reminiscing over some of your greatest videos
is even better.
Hope your internet issue gets resolved.
Happy Sunday.
Happy Sunday to you as well.
And yeah, I'm good.
I'm good.
It'll get fixed.
Just got to deal with it for now.
And we'll get back to normal.
As of hopefully Monday or Tuesday or so.
Or if Wednesday, Tuesday,
I'm going to try as hard as I'm going to.
I'm going to get up as early as possible tomorrow
and make like three phone calls.
I'm going to be phone call businessman tomorrow.
Just juicy.
Frontal mirror stream.
And then I will be removed from the platform.
But thank you, Frodeon.
Thank you, Hans Beets for the five community subs.
Thanks, Hans.
Five subs on top of all the other ones
that we're on tonight.
Thank you.
CadBTV, again 250, would you?
Who would you shit your pants for on stream?
Nobody.
No, but no one.
Maybe my mother.
If my mother needed me to stream with her
or something, it would be my mom or...
That's probably it.
Not Kim?
No, I...
No, there's context here.
There's context here.
There's context.
Thank you for the 250.
Appreciate it.
But thank you, Sticks Renegade for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, with your permission,
I want to custom order one car sticker of your Jerma J
to put on my sticker bombed Corolla
from those sticker maker websites.
Is that okay with you?
If so, I can show you the car when I get the sticker.
If not, that's completely understandable.
Oh, you want to have...
Oh, I see what you're saying.
I'm going to call my lawyer
to see what he says about that.
No, that was 9-1-1.
That's the wrong number.
That would not be who I would call.
Hey, nobody was going to steal my copyright.
Oh, this is the...
Yeah, you get...
Well, let's forward you to that department,
the copyright police.
Yeah, I mean, I don't have any stickers or anything.
I might actually make some stuff like that for fun
because I have that teespring store
and you can make hats, mugs, socks.
Stickers, you can do that.
So there probably will be more of that added just for fun.
I don't expect thousands of people to be like,
I have my merch, buy it.
But it doesn't cost anything for me to do that.
So I'm sure I would do it at some point.
Pins?
I wonder if they have pins.
I'll take a look.
Does Teespring do pins on their stores?
I don't know.
Dr. Clay, thanks for the 250.
I did some research for you.
Here's the origin of that sound.
Really?
This is from the BattleBots.
That is where that's from.
Why would you make that a hit sound?
Of all the things, why?
It was just me going, oh,
there wasn't anything spectacular about that.
Thank you to Talos for the 10 bucks.
Talos03, thanks for 10 dollars.
As soon as you gave us that heartfelt speech
about streaming still being fun after all these years,
I went out and got some bits.
You've got me through some tough times, Jerma.
I can always count on you to make me laugh.
It is still fun.
That's why I tend to get upset
when something gets in the way.
We have a pretty large community here now,
and I want it to be fun.
I don't want it to be like,
oh, here we go.
Look at this.
Look at me.
120,000 drop frames, cocks.
And yeah, it's a joke.
I know you guys don't mean half of it sometimes,
and it's not a big deal,
but it is to me because I want it to be good,
and I want you to enjoy every second of the stream.
I don't want it to be,
you know, well, you know,
15% of that stream was fucked.
Couldn't even watch it.
So it means a lot to me that I'm able to do it,
and it's able that I can do the things
that I want to do that day.
But it is still a blast every time.
I still have a great fucking time,
which means that I'm going to keep doing it.
I'm happy that you find the streams worth watching,
even when there are problems like this,
like that happened today
with the technical internet kind of stuff.
Even still, that you're able to stick with me there
and stick through that.
Thank you.
It's worth the pain.
I hope so.
But thank you.
Thank you Skeleton Toast for the $5.
Hey, Jerma, I don't you remember,
but nearly a year ago I asked you
for some words of encouragement, of courage,
before I went into surgery for my brain condition.
Due to my meds and constant doctor's appointments,
I've never really gotten the chance to catch your streams.
So to say thank you and let you know
that everything went fine.
Not cured, but hey, not dead.
Thanks for helping me get through that day.
And whenever it gets too much,
I'm pretty sure the Fat Engie
was the first video of yours that I ever saw.
Well, I'm fucking incredibly happy
that you're all right.
And that video was, that game was so good.
I'm so grounded and thankful that somebody,
that I'm helping you through that.
That's, I'm glad you're fucking all right.
Thank you so much for the $5 and stick with it.
Much love to you, for real.
That was Skeleton Toast.
Thank you so much to Zalaski for the $2.50.
Hey, Jerma, why were, why were you the friend
who shows you their favorite movie
and says this is the best part during the whole movie?
Oh, yeah, I was, I was going like,
yeah, but here's the thing though.
But like most of us have seen the movie, right?
We've all seen the movie.
So you and I are looking,
are looking at each other and we're both,
yeah, here, yeah, here it comes.
You know, you've seen the movie too.
So we both like are like,
yeah, this is it, right here, man.
And I complained about that person like two weeks ago.
That's fucking funny.
Let's get the credits on the screen.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, oh, there they go.
Hey, Easy Peep, Easy Peep 81.
That's a, that's a pretty good subscription
considering we watched that video.
Oh, that's fucking fun.
So we had a few more bits that came through.
Thank you everybody.
All the subs, all the gifted subs,
all the resubs, everybody.
Might see a redesign of this as well,
if it's possible.
I might have this be changed
on top of all the other things
that Ballordow is in the current process
of making right now.
And we got a couple more bits here.
We had a brain just froze.
I'd ever agree for the five dolls.
Do you have any tips for streaming?
You're hilarious, dude.
Tips for streaming would be
make sure you're doing it for fun.
Make sure you're doing it
because you want to do it.
Make sure you're doing it not for money,
not for power, not for fame,
but because you want to.
It's very important.
And do something that you're comfortable doing.
Find your zone.
Find your spot that you know
that you'd like to do
and see what happens.
Power, power.
All you can do is see what happens
and just make sure you're
realistic with your goals.
Make sure you're realistic with yourself
and do your best
because at this point
there's a lot of people that stream now
and trying to kind of
poke your head above the crowd
can be very difficult.
So just stay true to yourself.
Do what you know that you like to do
and that you're good at doing
and try to have as much fun as you can
and see what happens.
Power hungry.
You must accept the power.
Trust Jermo.
No, then you wrote he's short.
And there are plenty of cases of people
that start streaming
and then they just they grow
and they grow and they grow.
It's not like, oh, it's impossible now.
There's a lot of cases.
There's always cases of people
grabbing some audience.
But I've had kind of moments like this
where I've talked about before
but it's hard to give advice
because I know what I do
and I know the way that I like to stream
and the way the things that I like to try.
It's hard to give advice to people
that might not be the same.
We might not have the same ideas.
We might have the same things
we're trying to do on stream.
There's not a whole lot of real good
like just advice
like blanket statement advice
on how to be a streamer.
You kind of have to make that on your own.
You have to figure out what that's going to be.
Kim is sitting in the hail at soccer practice
waiting to be picked up.
No, she's not.
But I wish you the best of luck.
Do it and have fun.
Is it still hailing?
No, that was really weird.
It was just hitting them.
Smashing into the windows and stuff.
It was crazy.
Dr. Clay at the very end here.
Thank you for the 250.
Even though the stream
was the result of bad internet
I just want to say that it was fun watching this.
I always enjoyed hearing the comments
from the perspective of the creator.
Nonetheless, hope everything is fixed
and you can go back to streaming without issues.
Take care.
Me too.
I hope it's completely gone
as of the next day or two.
Yeah, I had a lot of fun on the stream.
I'm surprised that we were able to go
like five hours.
Kind of just melted.
The time just sort of disappeared
for a little while there.
Do I like sand?
Yeah, sand is cool.
And then finally right at the end we had Spooge.
Thanks for the three bucks.
Nine months sub now, Jeremy.
The baby is due.
But in all seriousness I want to let you know
that I had gotten a 30 on my ACT the first try
and I almost broke down about it.
I'm super excited and I appreciate you for being here
for all of us who have been stressing
about finals in school.
Love you, man.
I'll always be here and love every stream.
First try.
Holy shit.
Congratulations.
I, thanks for the nine months in a row.
30 out of 36.
That's pretty damn good.
30 out of 1600.
Oh, that would not be good.
Who doesn't like sand?
I don't know.
But yeah, congratulations on that.
That you should be pretty,
you should be very proud of that.
So thank you everybody.
That's my time.
We just, just over five hours.
Okay.
That's our, that's good then.
I'm okay then.
I'm all right with this stream.
I'm all right with it, I guess.
I'm okay.
I was scared there for a minute
that we were only going to get to
be live for like an hour and 10 minutes
and I would have been really sad about it.
So I'm all right with that.
I will see you guys hopefully by Tuesday.
If that is not the case,
I will make sure to let you know.
Just keep an eye on the sus
as of Monday night, Tuesday morning.
I'll make a tweet.
We'll probably on Tuesday morning
you give an update on how things are going.
Take care everybody.
Have a fantastic rest of your night.
See you very soon.
Ta ta for now.
I believe it is currently too early for legends
because I streamed less.
Yeah, I streamed yesterday.
So I did that late at night.
So no stream legends unfortunately.
Sorry guys.
See you real soon.
Have a great night.