Oh, I don't have it. Where's my intro video? Oh, that's right. I cleaned up. I cleaned up. Hey,
go back to talking to each other. Sure, hold on. Go back to talking to each other.
Shit, I think I deleted them. So, all right, I do this thing every year where I clean up my computer,
delete a bunch of old shit, delete a bunch of old temporary documents, and I think I deleted
my intro videos and my outro videos. How did I do that? No, I didn't. Why would I have done that?
Because I just tried to play it and it didn't work. Hold on. Oh, shit. This is the new intro.
Wait, wait, wait. I'll get it. I'll get it. Where is it? No, here it is.
So, where the hell is it? Oh, all right. Why is it over here? Well, fuck it. All right. Well,
hey, guys. Today, we're going to play a game called Black and White. Black and White. It is a...
All right. I don't want you to... I don't want you on camera anymore. All right. Here we go.
Here's the real intro. Where the fuck is it? This is actually annoying me. Where is it? Okay. Hey,
all right. See you in a minute. It's pre-manning and on yet. Bye. Okay. So, the plan today. Yes,
I'm not 100% recovered from being sick. I remember a few days ago, I started to get a bad migraine
and I was like, ah, fuck, I got a migraine. And then it just turned into a full blown just head
cold. I had a bad sore throat. My head was hurting. Kim now has it. So, it's not... It's just the
season. But I'm feeling all right now. I'm coming down from it. It's been a few days
and my head is not as hurting as much. So, I can spring. Good to go. With that, we're going to play,
like I said, Black and White. You've never heard of Black and White before. You're probably like,
wait a minute. And if you have heard of Black and White, you just... You just pog to your pants
right now. You shit your pants. Because this is... This is one of the most classic old
God simulating games that existed. Everybody that had a PC back 10, 15 years ago loved this game.
It's a lion head game. It's old lion head. The problem is they never ported it anywhere. They
never did anything with this. This series is just lost forever, apparently. They made a second one.
But it's just one of those games that everybody's just... Where's the third one? Give us a new
Black and White, please. It's one of those games. So, without further ado, welcome back, everybody.
I cannot promise you a, like, 12-hour spring today, but I can promise you a 10.
Let's go. Black and White. Why did I just... No, why did I just say that?
I'm not doing a 10-hour spring. This is probably going to be, like,
five. I got a headache. Okay, I got a headache. I got a headache. I got a headache. I'm doing it,
and I'm not doing that. Liar. Liar. Here we go. Black and White on an HD screen. That's right.
Wait, hold on. I gotta do this first. All right. You get one... You get... You get one more second.
Make it count, because you never... This is never happening ever again. Okay. Somebody
Pogged their fans already. Pog... Oh, that's so stupid. All right. Here we go. Black and White.
Open it. Uh-oh. Did it just insta-crash? Wait. I tested this, like, a thousand times. I tested
this a thousand times. This should not have insta-crashed. Okay. I tested this a thousand
times. It insta-crashed. Hold on. Okay. Jesus, man. Gonna give me a fucking heart attack.
I was gonna say, no way. Black and White, ladies and gentlemen. Lionhead Studios. Peter Molyneux.
The greatest video game developer to have ever fucking lived. In his own words.
Please choose from one of the following options. Start the game normally. Skip straight to the
creature select. Skip all of the creature to keep your... All right. I did open... I'm gonna...
I'm gonna be completely transparent here. I did open this, because I wanted to make sure I could
get it captured and in full HD texture. Uh, what's gonna start the game normally? You ready? What
the fuck is this game? You'll see. Is it gonna be a smash hit? I knew it. I knew it when I... I knew
it. It's gonna be a smash hit. Remember your favorite stream of, like, the last 10 years?
Add this one. Smash hit. Here we go.
Jinxed it. I'm just kidding. Am I though?
Don't go in the water! Wait, why? Why can't... Oh, because there's sharks.
I'll handle this.
That kid was fast. So those of you that wanted me to play Godhand, this is close enough, I think,
right? This does two birds with one stone. I read this script already. Yeah, we talked... We did...
Pre-stream gets a couple of jokes that happen on stream, all right? And somebody said, hey,
I saw that joke four hours ago in pre-stream. Yeah, it's fucking easy joke to make. Everybody
wants me to play Godhand. I'm playing a game where you play a literal hand of a god.
It's the easiest comedy ever. This kid just got hit by a fucking meteor.
Thank you, God. I did.
Thank you. Thank you for your mercy. We praise you. I require
all three of you to do a Fortnite dance. There it is. Okay, good. Good. I like that one. That's
the one where you go up and down with your hand. Good one. Greetings. We're your conscience. Good
and evil. Chaotic evil. Black and white. As part of you, we'll guide you through this world.
Chaotic evil. Okay. Good and evil. Should I be good or should I be evil? What do you think?
Our people will want to worship you. Please come with us to our village. Be evil? Why would I be
evil? I'll show you how to follow them. How to move. Let's see. You move your hand in the direction
you want to travel like this. Then you click and hold the move button. After that, you move the
mouse towards you to drag forwards. You grab the ground and drag backwards. You click, hold, and
pull again to cover more grounds. Sorry. Yeah, you actually have to grab the hand and move.
He's got sticky keys on. No, I don't. Follow your new worshipers to the village.
You'll have to grab the landscape several times. All right, let's go see their village.
I actually love this game and its sequel. Me too. All right, here we go.
This, this, you don't think this is going to be scary? What's the thing from Adam's family?
Cousin It? This thing's just running next to you? Not cousin it. What's it called? Not lurch.
Lurch is the tall guy. Thing. I'm right, I'm literally just right next to you.
The thing, thing, yes, thing. I'm right. I'm literally in my field of view.
How far away is your village? What were you guys doing out here?
I was foretold. The prophecy has come true. We can now finish the temple.
Let's go. Let's move to the temple by clicking and dragging or double click the move button
on it to go straight there. Same guy. All right, let's move to the temple clicking and dragging
or double click the move button to go straight there. Ooh, the move button. Temple. There it is.
We're, I think we're almost at the most important part of the entire game and that is
who do I want to be? Hey, it's not finished. Who do I want? And you'll, what's he, what's he
talking about? What do you mean? We're talking, you'll see. This temple will be the focus of our
power. Okay, good. But now it's time to learn how to look around. I'm going to do a poll.
Yeah, we'll do a poll. You move the hand to the side of the screen until the rotate
arrow appears like this. You hold down the move button. Then you move. I can't wait
to play this. Rotate around and see things from a different angle.
Certainly circular motion. Hold down the move. You can rotate either way.
Do a smart click instead. I actually, my smart clicks are broken.
They're all fucked up. You can also use the keyboard to rotate.
Okay, yeah. Now you try looking around. Just dragging around. You can go like this. You can
go like this. Not middle mouse. What was it? Not right mouse. What was it? I wasn't paying
attention. Shift. There it is. Wait, what? Is it not shift? Shift what?
Yeah, I was, oh, edge of the screen, right? Edge of the screen. Yes. Yes. Yes. That's right.
Okay, cool. Good. Now let's learn how to- How do you look up and down?
You move your hand to the top or bottom edge of the screen until the pitch arrow appears.
You hold down the move button. I don't want to have to do that. What's the key? Then you
move the hand to look up and down. You can do this with the middle mouse button.
You can do all this with the middle mouse button. I don't even need to know this.
But we have to do this tutorial. You can also use the keyboard to pitch.
Now you have a go. Yeah, middle mouse button's gonna do this. Splendid. That's it. That's it.
You've got the idea. But I know that doing tutorials, it's just a thing. If I just blow
through it, I don't care. Oh, now time to play and I don't fucking know what I'm doing.
You move the mouse towards you to zoom out. You know what I mean? Like that. It's gonna make
people angry. And you move the mouse away from you to zoom in. Zooming, as you see, is extremely
useful. You can also use the keyboard to zoom. Now you try. Yeah, I know how to do this. I know.
Yeah. And see, I told you, I didn't even need to do that. That's it. You've done it. All this moving
around is giving me a headache. I think we may need to practice a bit. We can go to the God's
playground by pressing F2 on the keyboard at any time. Wait, what? Now we've learned how to
move and look. We can help the villagers build the temple. I saw somebody resident sleeper over
there. I want you to remember that resident sleeper in 20 minutes. I want you to remember
that. I want you to wake up and go, what the fuck have I written? In 20 minutes, I want you to
remember what you've written. I want you to look at it. I want you to look at the screen and go,
I wrote that 20 minutes ago. All right, let's take some food and wood from the store to the
builders. First, you move the hand over the food or wood like this. You feed villagers by pressing
the action button. The longer you hold, the more you pick up. You can still drag while holding
objects. See, I helped. I'm just a big hand. You press the action button while holding an object
to drop it. All right, here we go. So let's get some wood. How much wood do we need? How much wood
do they have? All right, I'm taking all of them. I sure don't need to take this much. All right,
I don't need to take this much. Okay, I have 5,000. How much does it need? All right, I got it.
Wood required zero. Very good. He's the wood god. See, look at him. And it's got great music too.
I'm not picking him up yet. You guys, this is, this is, if I pick up somebody and like
yeet him into the ocean, I'm going to get negative god points. You want me to be good, not evil.
All right, do I need more wood? Yeet the non-believers. Oops. Oh, no, there we go.
I don't know. It just takes time. It just takes time. There we go. What happened? Oh, they said,
wow. There it is. They're trying to best straw poll for good or evil. No, I'm going to decide
there's no good. There is no good and there is no evil. This game's called black and white. I know.
But sometimes good people do evil things. Sometimes evil people do good things.
This is the entrance. Click the action button on it to take you inside.
Ray. All right, let's go inside the temple. Incredible. The tribe built all this.
No good or evil. Only checks. And to think it's a monument to you as a god.
And us as your conscience, don't forget. The workmanship is amazing.
And what a symbol of overwhelming evil. Death's in your region. Birth's in your region. No, it isn't.
Sacrifices. This here must be a map of the homeland. What about all these doors?
Each leads to a room. The rooms are extremely useful. Let's try some.
Okay, let me take a look at this. Check out all the writing on the scroll, boss.
Percentage that believe in you. It's showing lots of information about your followers and
your villages. Unbelievable. Only 59 people live here. Yeah, look at this.
Death's in your region. Births. Number of sacrifices. Buildings. Wonders in your region.
Disciples in your realm. Builders. Breeders. Fishermen. Farmers. Foresters. Missionaries.
Craftsmen. Traders. Well, let's see. All right, that's cool. Let's take a look at the other rooms.
This is the save game room. Okay. Here's the library, which I don't think is gonna happen.
This is the library. The scrolls contain a whole bunch of useful information.
Village help. Help with village life. Yeah, this is just extra documentation.
You know, it's just documentation. What does it say? Story history. The evil conscience said the
scrolls contain a whole bunch of useful information. One line ago the good conscience said this is the
library. Two lines ago the good conscience said... Am I playing? Is this AI dungeon?
This is a transcript of what everybody has said. It's a lore scroll.
All right, what else is in here? I don't remember. Challenge room. I think there's a creature cave.
Game options. I don't want to touch that. The future room. What is the... Okay, the creature cave.
Oh, this is an expansion thing, isn't it? Yeah, it is. Yeah, this is like an expansion room.
What does the challenge room do? This game has like two expansions.
You can get information on each challenge. Also, if a challenge is unfinished,
press the button underneath them. All right, so this is challenge room. Let's take a look.
I'm just trying to get the info. There are no challenges right now. It's just a bunch of empty
frames. All right, it's time. It's time for the most important thing of the whole day,
because this does not change, by the way. I think we have to figure out what each one does.
Daza, thank you. Daza for the 10 community subs. 10 subs from Daza. Whoa. Thank you.
The future is uncertain. Yeah. So what? More DLC. Yeah, I know. Don't save. I'm not going to save.
I've read... I've got all the patches that I need. The game can only be saved when it autosaves.
Yeah, I will actually break it. All right. Who do I want? Who do I want to be?
It's tough. It's a hard choice. Let's explore. I'm dying to know what these signposts are.
No, not yet. Not yet. Not yet. We need to learn. No, there's so much we got to do. I say we hunt
out the gold story scrolls. He just wants to go. He wants to skip. This is
you. The devil is you guys right now. Oh, let's learn more about the world. No. With Nancy Drew.
A gold story scroll looks like this. Clicking on gold story scrolls with the action button
will lead you through your quest in Eden. That's right. You can activate the scroll
or you can explore. It's up to you, leader. Okay. I'm going to do the right thing.
You know, I'm going to do the right thing and that's I'm going to make sure that I know what's
going on. I get a lot of shit for this. I get a lot of shit for this. So I'm not going to go.
What's the lumber mill do? What's this? What's this do? What's that do? What's the tent do?
No, I'm going to be good and I'm going to learn. You can scroll through some of these info signs
to read all the text. Hold the action button. No, no one's dying yet. Any information you
read on one of these is added to the library in the temple. No one is dying yet. I'm not going to
have bad points or good points yet. I just want to, I just want to remember how to play the video
game. The village quiet. Somebody shot a gun. Okay. You didn't think there were guns in this game?
I think I just saw a bunch of people pog instead of another fire. All right, mute the chat. Mute
the chat. I don't want to look over there right now. Centrist Gray NPC Jeremy. That's the last
thing that I read and that's the last thing I'm going to read for the next like 10 minutes.
Store contains wood and food. You can add either resource to the store. Right. I can,
I'm still looking over there. You guys are in my head. The villagers will also gather them
unless they are worshiping. Right. Okay. So this is the store. You can store wood. You can store
food. It's grain. You can add either resource. The villagers will also gather them unless they
are worshiping or they are assigned as a disciple to another task. Right. Surrounding flags indicate
the level of need. The higher the flag is raised, the greater the need of your villages. Place your
hand over the red of, why did I say red flags? To gain more information about it. Okay. Yeah. So
here we go. So children desire is what? Food desire. What does, that means they want to have
children. Well, go for it. What's, how's that stopping me? No, don't put it in emote only.
Emote only makes it easier for them to be mean to this classic. I can't even believe it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Imagine resident sleeper ring like Half-Life. Imagine. Just imagine. Like
resident sleeper ring. Half-Life. Because that's what you're doing right now. This is one of the
most classic fucking top 10 PC games ever existed. I mean, it might be like number nine and Half-Life
might be like number two. Right. Or whatever. But like, you know, come on. Disable the chat. No,
I'm moving on. I don't even, whatever. They'll, they'll see. They'll just let, let them resident
sleeper for the next fucking 40 minutes. They'll see. They'll see when the first boulder rolls
through the town. They'll see. They're doing it for the jokes. I know. So am I. Backtrack and bury.
Did you know you can hold the action button to draw, to drown, to down, to pick up increasing
amounts of food. Yep. You can also drop trees and wooden objects into those stores as well
as food from the fields or fish from the sea. Yes. So you can just drop food in here. I got it. Okay.
Relax. Did you know that signposts always contain useful information about the world? Once you've
read them, their knowledge will appear in the library inside your temple. Yes. You can scroll
through some of the info signs to read all the text using the action button. Oh, that's cool.
That's right. All right. If I didn't, imagine if I didn't know that. Imagine resident sleeper ring
half-life. Did you know you can use the mouse wheel to zoom in and out? Yes, I know. Oh my God.
You can use them. Yes, I know that. Yep. Okay. All right. We're good.
I love this game and I'm going to play it. That's all that needs to be said. So. All right. No,
don't give it to them. Don't give it to them. Don't give them. Don't just pick somebody up
and whip them into the ground. Don't do that. That's what they want. That's what they want
you to do. And I'm not doing it. You could press the following key to show you the name. Oh,
that's cool. And make tracking their movements easier. That's actually really, really good.
Interesting. N. That didn't work. N? Yeah. N, right? No, I can't. It doesn't work.
If you see a house with smoke coming out of it, it is occupied. Okay. To eject the occupants,
tap the house. Oh, did I just do that? Oh no, there's nobody living here. Let's try somebody.
People are in the house and green people would show free spaces. All right. Well, get out.
Get out. I think it's the tutorial. That's why I can't do it. Oh, that's cool. All right. Read
this one. Placing a man or woman next to someone of the opposite sex turns them into a disciple
breeder whose only goal is to breed and produce children. Drop. Disciple breeder.
So we have breeder. Okay. We got breeders. Somebody. I keep hearing like a sniper rifle
in the distance. It's like freaking me out. You can plant forest by picking up a tree and placing
it upright in the ground. That's cool. If you place a tree in a village, it becomes a scenic
addition and will please your people. Foresters will not cut these trees down. All right. That's
good to know. We're almost there. We're almost there. Every time you activate a gold story
scroll, you start the next chapter. Okay. All right. Let's. Okay. Here we go.
I just, I wanted to get that info. Greetings, Holy one. You've activated a gold story scroll.
I have. My name is Sable. I am a trainer of creatures. I challenge you to open these gates.
Creatures. Behind them are three wondrous creatures. That's right. Every god has a creature.
Every god has a creature. Tall as a mountain and can perform miracles. But you can't open
the gate unless you find the three gate stones. Each stone you find must be placed on this platform.
I'll get them. Throw her into the ocean. No. The villagers were dancing around a gate stone
when you arrived. No. Once you place this gate stone on the platform, I will tell you of the
other two. Throw the ocean into her. Now retrieve the first gate stone, Holy one. Okay. Let's go
get the gate stone. It was over, where was it over here? Right. It was like on the beach.
Who lives here? Where was it? Wasn't it like when I first got here? It was like right here, right?
Yeah, it's right here. Here's the stone that people were dancing around. Pick it up by
clicking the action button on it and drop it on someone's house to please all the people
resident sleepering half-life one. Get it? Drop it on her. Excellent. You found a gate stone.
You'll need to search for another now. Try looking for a gold story scroll in the village.
I'll find it. Easy. Oh, that's not a scroll. That's a moon. All right, looking for a gold scroll.
Anybody see a gold scroll here? What's going on here? Oh, Holy one. I kneel before you.
Nerd neck. My brother suffering a fever has left his sick bed and become lost.
All right, we're gonna find the lost. He's so weak. I'm frightened he'll die.
If you find him and bring him home, I'll give you one of the three gate stones.
It's in my house. Kill him. Hey, I got a plan. Why don't we trash the house?
We can get the gate stone that way. I heartily object. That's just malicious.
What do we do? That's kind of the whole point.
The lost brother is in some trees through the pass.
What's in the house? What's in the house, lady? Any gold in here?
Fields are where you people plant crops, which are then harvested and carried to the store.
Yes, to add to the food pile, you can harvest crops yourself.
As can your creature. You can also make dedicated farmer disciples by placing villagers in these
fields. Trash the house. No, if I'm God right now, I go find the lost brother is in some trees
through the pass. I didn't see this skipper out. Well, there goes the skipping God hand
on his way. Where is he? No, I can't let them. I can't let them dictate what I'm going to do
as my as me. I'm bringing them back. There you are. I've been so worried. Do as we command.
Thank you for your benevolence. Do you want me to go against the title of my own damn stream?
Now steal. All right. You want me to drop this on somebody and watch them explode?
Is that what you want? Is that what you seriously want me to do?
Yes. And everyone calls me the psycho. Holy shit. You're a psycho. I crushed that guy.
Good. You have two of the gate stones, but the third could be a problem.
The villagers say the final one was destroyed eons ago. All is not lost though. The village
sculptor can carve a new gate stone for you. You should see him. All right. Village sculptor.
What do you got? That's not big enough. It's gotta be way bigger. Holy one. I hear you're looking for
a gate stone. I am a sculptor. Burn the gate down. If you provide me with the right rock,
I'll carve one for you. Okay. You'll find the rock I need in the old hermit's quarry. Please
bring it to you. Smash. I can't. I'm not going to smash and kill people in the tutorial.
All right. There it is. Go get the big rock. I'm definitely the best sculptor in the village.
That's why you can't die. You want me to kill the best sculptor in the village? What? Why would I
do that? Oh, pick up rock and throw rock into people. Okay. Yeah. That's fun. There's no going
back if I do that. You understand? All right. Where was it over here? Where was it? Right here?
I thought it was right over here. Wasn't it right there? Over here? Where's this rock?
Where is it? I can't even go this way. The old hermit's quarry. Yeah. Well, wasn't that like
right here? That's not, I thought it was right here. Um, which, which one? Does it matter?
Is this, I can't pick this up. This can't be moved. Um, is this what? No, I need to be bigger than
that. How do I, I can't move these. Maybe does it matter here? Use this one. I guess this is big
enough here. Right. That's big enough. Actually, this rock isn't right for the fucking serious.
Why? No, no, no. Oh shit. No, no, no, no cat. I want to pick them up. Now. Now you believe,
huh? Now you all start to believe, you know, I didn't believe in that God until he bowling balled
that rock down the flip. All right. So why can't I pick up? Like I don't, I want to pick it up.
Am I, am I insane or is it like this one? Yeah. It's this one, right? No. Keep going.
Nothing else here. It's up the hill. Left, left, left up here. Here's the stone you need.
Found it. If you press F1, when your hand is over something information on it will be displayed.
All right. Let's see. Gate stone. I actually have to be careful. I don't want to kill anybody
accidentally. All right. Let's do this. Here you go. Here's the stone you need. Yeah, I know. I
just put it down. That's excellent. Exactly the right kind of rock to work with. Dude, Half Life 1.
Thank you. Come back later and I'll have it finished.
Come back later. How, how, how much later? The sculptor is still carving the gate stone.
What am I supposed to do in the meantime? We should speak to the sculptor about the gate stone.
Hurry up. I don't got all day. I don't have time for this. Oops. Go back to work. Breed with,
all right. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's breed. Oh, this person's already breeding. How much breeding?
I say some are jigging about on here. What? This village is just chilling. All right. Hold on.
People are just having sex with each other and stuff. What is going on?
This village is just chilling. Hold on. Wait, what? That lady, that lady was already pregnant.
All right. Let's go. The gate stones are together. Pass through and claim your creature. That's the
Oh, because that's a resident breeder. What? So hold on. Did I, did I designate that person
to be just a breeder? Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. There they are. There they are. You see them? Look at the corner. Do you see?
I don't see them. I don't see what you're talking about. Oh, I see them.
Yeah. Look at them. Just look at them. These are miraculous creatures indeed. They certainly are,
but not quite as big as I expected. Not yet, maybe, but they can become powerful creatures
in the world. Now that I'd like to see, we must have one. What should we choose? They're all
special. That makes me like the monkey hearing that like, like that makes me like the monkey,
but all that we do have nerd neck tiger. You know what I mean? Like this, this is a hard choice.
There's nerd neck tiger, there's funny monkey, and then there's just absolutely just, just,
what do you, I don't even know what you call it. Superhero cow. Good luck. You have to pick.
It's not going to be up to me. They, they all have their own personalities, by the way.
Monkey, tiger make, this is a really important choice. Okay. Let's see what you guys do.
I'll get you. I'm going to put them on the screen in full HD so you can see what they all do.
Oh, come on. You don't look at it. Did you just superhero cow just did a split for you?
That was very impressive. Whoa, boy. And the superhero cow, unfortunately is going to lose.
Oh, that's unfortunate. That's unfortunate. I just,
monkey is going to win. I can't believe it.
The cow just did a fucking split.
You have to veto. I have to veto. I have to veto.
Oh, what was that? I like, like you now. Okay. Cat. I like the tiger now.
I want the cow. I want the cow. I don't care. No democracy today.
Are you sure you want this creature? Click on him again if you are.
Oh, but he just laughed at me.
How about the ape? Intelligent and quick to learn.
This is, I can't change this. Oh, it just did no split.
Chosen a creature.
He was surprised. The cow was surprised by this, by this. He's like, holy shit, it actually worked.
You're a dictator. This is your creature's new home.
He's small at the moment, but look after him and one day he'll be big and powerful.
He isn't comfortable in his new home yet. In fact, he's a little frightened.
You can stroke him to reassure him.
Let's, let's pet, let's pet cow. Can you pet cow? Yes.
Click and hold the action button, then move your hand to stroke him by holding the action
button and moving your hand over him gently. Stroking tells him you're approving and it makes
him happy. Okay, scratch his belly.
So I'm not trying to do that. I'm going really slow.
All right, good boy. See how he likes that? He feels much better now.
Okay. I'll leave you two alone for a while. I'll return later to teach you more.
He's going to pog. Did he pog? Where are you going? One percent damage.
Fuck. All right. Let's see. This is your creature's home.
It feels, he feels safe here and when he rests, he'll grow in size faster. That's right. They get
fucking huge. You can place interesting things in the pen for your creature and inside the temple
is a creature's cave full of useful statistics about him. Look at that. Look at that side eye.
Yeah. Okay. So we can get him toys and stuff. What else can I do?
Space bar is a shortcut key to place your camera. Get out of here. The space bar is a shortcut key
to place your camera in a safe position. Press it again to return you to the temple. Pressing it
again will return you to original. All right. So if I go like, I see. Okay. So you can just like,
you can have it focused and shit safe, I guess. I see. What do you want? Is he laughing?
Oh no, he's going, hey, over there. Hey you, go over there. Oh, I love him.
His voice is kind of annoying. Your creature is getting hungry. Let's eat.
I suggest you find him something to eat. Choose carefully though. Some things are better for him
than others. They eat people. All right. We're going to find food. What do you, what do you like
to eat? Hunger. 100% tiredness. All right. Hungry. What do we eat? If you want a creature to eat
something, rub his tummy when you give it to him. He'll eat it even if he's not hungry.
Hungry. Okay. Um, does he eat people? I don't know if you should eat people.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge...
Does he eat wood? Oh, there's a, wait, there's a reward scroll.
Oh look, a silver reward scroll. Let's see what it...
Okay, let's get our projectile skills up the scratch.
What do you suggest? I presume it involves killing.
No, not at all. I was going to propose, uh, we, uh, I know...
I'm gonna feed him. Let's see if we can hit that
pillar over there. It's a test of our godly powers and nobody gets hurt.
How nice. And I guess we use this everlasting pile of stones.
Hmm, handy that. Move your hand over a rock.
Yeah, all right. This is teaching how to throw.
Press the action button until the rock is in your hand.
And we're gonna knock down the rock. Hold down the action button.
Put momentum on the throw by moving the hand in the correct direction.
So you can actually...
Throw the rock by releasing the action button.
Yeah. Try throwing a rock now.
There we go. Okay, I need a little bit more.
Not enough weight behind that one.
Now that was close.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Go back to work. Okay.
I will feed the cow. Just wait.
That hit. Wait, I have to hit the top thing off?
Oh my god, this is gonna be...
You're doing well, but you have...
I know. Holy shit, that was too fast.
Oh my god, this is hard.
Here we go. All right.
The cow's starving. The cow's gonna be fine.
We've been given a chest.
Oh, it's a toy. It's a toy for the cow.
Awesome. All right. Okay. Look what I got.
I know you're hungry, but look.
Where are you? There you are.
Give your food by putting your hand in front of him
and then holding the action button.
Look at this.
Hey, you.
Where are you going? All right. You.
I know. I know. I know.
I know you're pointing at me. Eat.
All right. I need food.
What is this? What is this?
This is a... I don't know what this is.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
He seemed to like that.
Try feeding him some more. I'll be back later.
Oh, no. Now he is insufferable. Just lust for food.
Here. Play with this. See? He's like, oh.
Hey, good job. Here.
Yes. What about? What do you want?
You strong? How are you doing? You're okay.
Good boy.
I was rubbing his tummy. I was rubbing his...
I was rubbing his tummy. It said rub tummy.
It said rub tummy for food stuff.
All right. Let's go.
All right. Where's the silver scroll?
Silver reward scroll. Where was it?
I don't remember where it was.
Oh, fuck. Who's this motherfucker?
Oh, no. It's a rival god.
It's spying on my base.
All right. He's spying on my base.
Your creature already has his own personality.
What is his personality?
But you can alter and shape it by...
Oh, I thought he was going to eat her.
Punish your creature to stop him doing things like that.
I thought he was going to eat her.
Oh, that just gets shit out of me.
Punish.
Hold down the action button over the creature to zoom in on him.
Now, slap him by moving your hand quickly from side to side across him.
There it is. Good job.
You want to encourage him to do things like that, do you?
Well, it's up to you.
I'll return when your creature is behaving a bit better.
He's like, haha.
I can do those things. I don't even care.
You're a little weirdo, huh?
All right. Feed.
Play with your ball.
Wait. No, no, no, no.
This is the fucking...
Okay. That guy is the carver.
Okay. Let's go find another scroll.
He needs to grow up, too.
They get older, actually.
They actually grow up.
All right. How are we doing on food?
Feed him. Feed him. Feed him.
All right. Do we have any more...
Animals?
Here. I have this.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
All right. Well, hold on.
Hey! Sable, the creature droid that is trying to attract our attention.
Eat. Eat.
It says rub his belly to make him want to eat.
Stop playing and eat.
You're going to lose the ball.
I'm not going to get it.
I'm not getting it for you if you lose it.
Yeah. You can't even hit it.
All right. Well...
Hey! Sable, the creature droid that is trying to attract our attention.
All right. Eat.
Eat this.
You're hungry. Eat.
Eat!
That's the stomach.
What? He thought about that.
He had like a moral conflict there.
What was that?
That was weird.
Sable, the creature droid that is trying to attract our attention.
Yeah. But hold on.
Where's the silver scroll on the beach?
I want to get more toys and stuff.
Is it on the beach?
What did he say it was?
There it is.
Hi, man. Neat stone circle.
It's a bummer that some are missing.
Sounds like we can help there.
What?
Help test the loaded sack of burnt-out neurons.
The stones have to play a scale.
That's what we need.
Tap a stone to hear its note.
Okay. It has to play a certain song.
Cool. Okay. Now what?
Let's find the stones to put in the stone circle.
Let's find the stones.
That's going to be a pain in the ass.
Kill that guy.
Let's find the stones.
Good luck with that shit.
I found one.
Does it play?
It's one, two, three.
One, two, three.
All right.
Well, no, I didn't.
I just have to find them.
It's not Simon Says.
I just eventually have to find them all.
All right. That's fine.
Let's go back to the scroll over here.
Wait. Find another one right here.
It's an omega symbol.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This guy's freaking me out.
Who are you?
What do you want with me?
Can I throw a boulder at him?
And what does this one say?
Silver rewards scrolls are not vital.
Yeah, I know that.
You can throw in different ways.
A long smooth throw sends the missile low along the ground
and a quick hand move release will throw the object higher.
Yeah. All right.
Let's go do this.
It's time to take him for a walk.
Okay.
This is the leash of learning.
Please click on it
and I'll show you how to use it with your creature.
He's going to like stuff it on people and shit, isn't he?
All right. Here we go.
Good. Now click on your creature.
Now you've got some direct control of the little beast.
On a leash.
You didn't wait. Where's this other pig?
You can pull the creature about with the leash.
You see that tree over there?
Yeah.
Try pulling your creature towards it.
Click the action button on the ground to hurry him up.
Okay.
So let's go.
Come over here.
Good work.
You got it. Very well done.
Excellent. Well done.
Did you know that you can use a leash
to make your creature interact with objects?
Oh, I can try getting him to pick up that cow over there.
He loves picking up.
Wait, that's a hand with the leash over the cow.
Then click the action button.
Uh, yes, she will be doing this.
I didn't have to.
Well done. You see the leash is very useful.
It'll do him good.
You can drop the leash by shaking your hand left and right quickly.
He's like, bye.
Shake your hand.
Okay.
What do you want to do?
All right. Let's go for a walk.
Let's go for a walk through town.
Take him to the sheep.
No, look at how small he is.
Do you see how big the sheep was?
Wait a minute.
Holy fuck.
The sheep is like 500 times his size.
Uh, I don't think he's...
I'm not, I'm not going over there.
Let's go in here.
It's a friend.
I highly doubt that shit.
All right, let's go.
Look, everybody's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
Look who's here.
Look, he's getting smarter.
He's like, whoa, these people.
What is this stuff?
Oh, who's just chasing them around?
Just let him, let him, let him learn.
Let him think he's getting, yes, that's a person.
That's correct.
He's getting brain power.
Are they all running away scared?
I don't think so.
Where's he going?
Where are you going?
What is he doing?
He's, oh, he's just running around the perimeter.
Uh, all right, all right.
You don't, you really don't need to do laps around the building.
But maybe you do.
What is he doing?
He's getting exercise.
He's doing cardio.
He's going to get big and strong and he needs to do his cardio laps.
Give him a name.
I don't know yet.
Let's see.
Ooh, what happened?
Oh, I, he, oh, I deletion.
Oh, he wants to go home.
Okay.
All right, we'll go home.
Will he eat trees?
Hold on.
What can I get?
Hunger.
He's hungry.
He's tired.
He doesn't, he's not going to eat wood.
Yeah, you're doing great.
Okay.
What about like just trees?
Will he eat this?
Here.
Do you eat trees?
Oh, I guess this is, oh, oh, wait, hold on.
Hey, I guess you don't like it.
Okay.
I'll get, I'll, I'll get rid of it.
All right.
Jesus.
He thinks he's so funny.
That's fine.
He's spoiled.
There's more to learn about leashes.
I didn't tell you that you can attach the leash to objects.
Try leashing the creature to this tree.
Make it so he can't go anywhere.
With the leash attached to your hand, move it over the tree.
Okay.
Double click the action button to attach the leash.
Attach your creature to the sparkly tree.
What did he do?
Did he eat?
With the leash attached to your creature, double click on the tree.
Why did he do that?
Double click the action button to attach the leash.
It wasn't funny.
It's not funny.
It is funny.
Fuck it.
Who cares?
Like he leaned out and did this like dance.
Okay.
Whatever.
Good.
The leash is very useful.
Your creature is tied to the tree now.
You interact with whatever his leash to as well.
If you click on a leash when the creature is attached to something,
you can adjust its length.
I didn't, that was, he did it like four times in a row.
This is the leash of aggression.
It encourages your creature to get angry.
This is the fluffy leash of compassion.
It makes your creature behave nicely.
Why not experiment with these leashes?
They're powerful tools.
I'll bid you farewell.
You now know as much about creatures as I do.
Legends tell of an ancient creature somewhere on this land.
We've seen him already, but I've never seen him.
He hides from us humans,
but he has great knowledge, I think.
It's a giant sheep.
Hey, Mini Clips.
Thanks for the five subs.
Appreciate it.
It's the sniper.
There are advanced techniques for using the leash.
Find them on this signpost.
No, you can't go that way.
All right.
Don't do it.
Oh my fucking god, he ate her.
Can we not get quests anymore?
That was bad.
No, that wasn't good.
Not funny.
Don't do that.
Here, let me just...
I don't want to...
Is there any way?
Can I scold him?
How do you scold?
I don't want to...
There's only one way you can do that.
It's like, all right, he's...
He's going to start to become unbearable.
You know what I mean?
Like he's going to eat quest givers and shit.
I don't know if we can handle this.
Don't do that.
Let's stop.
I'm...
Okay, I just didn't...
All right, all right, all right.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I don't want to do that.
All right.
You can restrict the area in which your creature...
Jesus Christ.
First, what is he doing?
You can restrict the area in which your creature can move when he's on the leash.
First, you attach the leash to an object and...
Okay, that's area restricted.
He's thinking about...
What?
Look, this motherfucker just ain't the quest giver.
Okay?
All right, click on...
Click on...
All right, we're fine.
Pull to stretch the...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
First, you attach the leash to an object
and click the action button anymore on the leash to pick it up.
Okay.
You can pull to stretch the leash to the length you want it to be.
I see.
So you can do...
Okay, that makes sense.
All right, let's go find...
You're encouraging him to eat people.
You're fucking fused.
I was fucked up the second she was done talking.
Did you know the creature pen is where you'll find your creature's leashes?
You can also use different leashes to directly influence your creature's mood.
There is the leash of learning, which makes your creature mimic your own action.
The leash of aggression, which will make him angry and the leash of compassion.
So he's on the leash of learning right now.
Okay.
Does he want to sleep out there?
Let's get rid of the leash.
Go to bed.
How does he have to have that, like, big ass bruise?
Like, I didn't even want to do that.
All right.
Go to bed.
Good.
Okay.
So I got the leash of learning on right now.
All right.
Here we go.
There's a silver reward squirrel on the beach behind those huge gates.
I know.
There's a bunch of reward squirrels everywhere.
There's one here, too.
Remember, he ate a person.
I know.
It was an important person, too.
By the great gods, I've been asleep.
I was just counting my sheep when I dozed off.
Please find my strange sheep.
Well, they were going to be slaughtered anyway.
I say we waste the wandering mutton.
But if we find and return them, we'll have a diet in the wolf follower.
Wow.
The saintly one made a joke.
What is that?
Ooh.
Okay.
So we're going to find you sheep.
Found one.
Here.
Is this what you're looking for?
There's one right there, right?
Many thanks, higher power.
Keep them coming, please.
Well, it's your problem.
This is your problem.
What is this place?
Did you know children stay safely in the creche until they reach adulthood?
The creche is a settlement.
It encourages people to have more children.
All right.
So this is like a little daycare.
Makes sense.
If you drop a person by a job, they'll become a disciple and do that job indefinitely
until you stop them by picking them up and shaking your hand to release them.
Okay.
You create as many disciples as you like.
Shake your hand when you've got the leash and you release it, right?
You can leash your creature to any object by double clicking the action button on the object.
Pressing this key leashes attaches the leash to your creature.
Right.
Oh, what are you doing?
Why are you going over here?
Not over by the children.
Not by the children.
He's on the loose.
What's he doing?
He's just like sprinting around.
He's completely, completely out of control.
I mean, he's not doing it.
He's all right here.
Stay over here.
Just like relax.
Just chill.
He's the worst.
He's really, really the worst.
All right.
Just don't kill anybody please while I'm doing this.
Look at the sheep.
How are you doing actually?
He wanted to kick down.
Stay.
No.
Stop.
He's just shitting.
Stay back here.
Stay.
Don't move.
No.
Relax.
Don't.
Just quit being such an asshole.
Did I do this to you?
All right.
I gotta find video over here.
Sheep and...
Okay.
We need to make some jobs.
Uh, you...
Let's have you be...
Uh, okay.
Disciple Breeder.
Some breeding maybe?
He just killed somebody.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
Where are you going?
I don't even know what to do with you anymore.
Oh, he was thirsty.
All right.
Please be good.
I can't attach you to this.
Just stay over here.
Just look.
Play with your ball.
See?
Cool, huh?
Good.
All right.
Now let me continue the game, please.
We got sheep for you.
There's another one over here.
There was another scroll.
Where was it?
Okay.
There's this right here.
There's a huge creature in the valley beyond.
We're all terrified.
This must be the creature that Sable spoke of.
Let's investigate.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Look at the size of that.
Ah, okay.
We're dead.
We're all dead.
He's gonna come get us.
What is it?
Where is it from?
It doesn't seem to be aggressive, though.
If it is, we're all dead.
Even our spirits.
Dead.
You too, boss.
Pick up a rock and throw it at it.
It's dead.
This giant is communicating.
It's telepathic.
You have a creature.
Bring him to me.
Oh, no.
No way.
He'll eat him.
But this giant looks friendly.
Let's bring our creature over with the leash.
I am not proud of my son.
So I don't know if I'm gonna like this.
Please use the leash to bring your creature to me.
What if he just starts farting and kicking things
and eating people in front of him?
It's gonna be really embarrassing.
There you are.
All right, come here.
Over this way.
He must be judged.
Derva hates him already.
I don't hate...
I think he's funny.
But he's not...
He's not wholesome.
He's just...
He's just mean and weird.
All right.
Please use the leash to bring your creature to me.
This is an important weird God interview.
Don't embarrass me.
I do hope they'll be friends.
Another creature?
Is it true?
Are you real?
I've been doing the same...
You're doing the same stance.
I thought I would die without ever seeing another God.
I like you.
Or another creature.
Am I mocking him with this person?
I don't understand.
I once belonged to Nemesis, the most powerful of gods.
But his power kept growing
and soon I wasn't old enough for him.
So I was cast out, banished here
and I've been alone ever since.
Until now.
Well, you just...
I'm not...
I'm not hiring.
This being is astonishing, but what a sad tale.
In return for your friendship and that of your creature,
I will teach you both.
You will both learn the ways of the gods.
When you are ready for the first lesson,
meet me at the village through this pass.
There's another village.
He's like, wait, where are you going?
I want to go see the big guy again.
I'm gonna let him do it.
He needs to learn.
He's got to be on his own.
He's so dopey.
Should I be bringing him over here?
Maybe I shouldn't even be doing this.
Derma, I fucking hate this cow so much.
Well, I'm sorry, but this is our child right now.
So it's too bad.
Wait, you don't want to go over there?
No, no, no, no.
Come on, let's go.
Follow me.
There he is.
All right, now let's learn.
This cow is better than bugleberry.
Oh boy, I can see that.
All right, here we are.
This is the Aztec village.
I will teach you the first secret here.
It's not going to be like burn it down.
These people do not yet believe in you as a god.
To grow in power, you and your creature
can impress them until they believe in you.
Look at the village store.
The flag shows that they need food.
Hmm.
If you give them some, they'll think it's a miracle
and will believe in you more.
They call the signpost to find out more about desire flags.
Yeah, they need food and yeah.
All right, I got some extra food.
Imagine if the cow just turned over and picked him up.
This is a food miracle.
You can cast one food miracle.
You can pick up such one shot miracles with the action button
and activate them by tapping them with the same button like this.
What animal is that?
I hear that all the time in random animal sounds.
Things like this really impress the creatures.
If your creature is on the road, he will learn this miracle.
I need to know exactly what that animal is.
I hear it all the time.
If your creature is on the rope leash,
he'll learn this miracle when you cast it.
All right, so this is the teaching one.
Tap on the miracle and click the action button on the Aztec village store.
Okay, let's get a leash on you so you learn this.
Yes.
You picked up the miracle instead of tapping it.
Drop it and try again.
Well done.
Now click the action button over the village store.
I can't be on a leash.
Didn't it say if he's on a leash?
I thought it said he'll learn if he's on a leash.
Come here.
Get over here.
Stop chasing stuff.
What is that?
Is it a bird?
Oh, he's eating.
Okay, he's eating things.
Come here.
No, stop sleeping.
Why are you sleeping?
I just casted the miracle on the ground.
Well done.
Now click the action button over the village store.
I'm trying to get him to move.
Get over here.
Let's go.
What an embarrassment.
All right.
They believe.
That's a lot more.
Never mind.
Look at him.
Look at Adam.
Good.
He's like sizing him up.
I have created more food miracles for you to practice with.
At the village center, you can see your symbol.
When it reaches the stone hand there, the village will believe in you.
My symbol?
Holding your hand over it shows how much belief the people have in you.
I need sleep.
Wake me when the village believes in you and you are ready to continue your education.
Okay.
When it reaches the stone.
All right.
Cool.
So let's make them believe.
He just lies on the ground over here.
All right.
Should I drop a rock in his head?
I'm going to throw a huge rock and drop it on his head.
Should I do that?
All right.
Let them sleep.
They can just hang out.
I'm going to do some more food miracles.
X will worship you now.
You have not investigated many silver reward scrolls, leader.
Try a few.
It'll be worth it.
You really want me to do the side quests.
I know you do.
Hold on.
All right.
They believe in me now.
Good.
Villages are impressed by the actions of gods, especially when they fulfill the people's desires.
Do impressive things like throwing objects around, use creatures in the village,
and cast miracles.
You'll see.
You will see the belief in.
All right.
Let's get some.
Disciple builder.
Builder.
Disciple forester.
All right.
Let's have some.
How many people live in this village?
Can I tell?
This is the village center.
Placing your hand over it will show how much belief is needed before the village is yours.
As you do impressive things in the village, you will see numbers come up over the villager.
This is the amount of belief you have gained for your actions.
That's right.
I need 199 belief before this village is mine.
So where'd he go?
Where'd he go?
Where is he?
Oh.
How do I locate my creature?
Did he go home?
There's a silver reward for on the beach behind those huge gifts.
Where did he go?
He took off and ran away.
Oh, there he is.
Okay.
Yeah.
Press C.
How you doing?
You good?
Good?
Good.
Be a good boy.
Go do something.
All right.
Let me get this squirrel over here.
What is this?
What's all the fuss?
A freak wave has just struck.
My husband and four others are drowning.
Please help them.
Uh-oh.
Drowning.
Let's see.
Who do we know who's tall enough to wait out to him?
Don't muck around.
Let's get our creature as fast as possible.
What do you mean our creature?
I can't just pick him up.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Hey, come here.
Go help them.
This way.
Hurry up.
Go, go, go.
Oh, they're dying.
Quick to the rescue.
Go get them.
No, go.
In here.
Go in here.
Don't fall asleep.
All right.
Save them.
Get them.
Take them out of the water.
Over there.
Drop them.
Drop.
Drop it.
All right.
Do it again.
What did he just do?
Did he just push his head under?
Quick, quick, quick.
Drop it.
Good job.
Save them.
All right.
Do it again.
Back up.
One more.
All right.
Go.
Nice job.
You did it.
You actually did something good.
I like, I'm starting to like you.
At least some survived.
We're a little thankful for that.
I'm refreshed and ready to start teaching your little creature more.
He's out of control.
I'm sorry.
There's no, I, he did, at least he did a three.
At least he did three.
He may have like snapped a person in half, but he did three out of four.
All right.
We have to go teach him some more things.
He's using the tree now.
That's actually interesting.
Why is he using the tree?
What about her?
What about him?
What's your problem?
He doesn't like you.
Why do you, you don't like, why?
What's his face?
Did you see that?
Look at that frown.
All right.
Come look up to go back to the big sheep.
He's hungry.
All right.
Well, let me get him some food.
Oh, he's going home.
All right.
Let's give him some food.
He needs to eat something.
We need like a pig or something or a sheep.
And he's just, I know I can follow him later.
He's just doing his own fucking thing.
Whatever.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
We need a sheep or a cow.
All right.
Who cares about that?
We'll just feed this here.
Come here.
There.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's probably, I just heard him.
Go get this.
Come here.
He's like, oh, he doesn't know what to do.
Oh, good.
Didn't like that.
All right.
Let's go see the sheep.
Let's go.
I mean, he's a, he's a huge sheep.
You really can't miss it.
There he is.
Make him eat more people.
No, I don't want him to eat people because I don't want him to bet to be a
thing that he just does on his own.
He already, he's done it like twice.
Don't feed him meat.
That he can eat meat, but just not people.
I tried to give him a tree.
Remember he kicked it over and he looked at me and he pointed at me and laughed.
I tried to feed him a plant.
Feed him grain.
All right.
Yeah.
I see.
I mean, that's all right.
Let's learn another spell.
German doesn't know what cows eat.
This is not even a real, this is a God cow.
This is not even a cow.
This is like a God thing.
It was nemesis creature.
He often sent me into battle.
I foresee the same for you.
First, I will become your size to make things easier.
Combat training.
Be prepared to get bruised.
Don't worry.
In time, people heal.
I love the point though.
All right.
Kick his ass.
And during the time there is a fight.
You should know that your creature will fight without help from you.
He doesn't want to do it.
He's scared.
He said, no, no.
I just want to eat people and shit in bushes.
And kick balls.
All right.
Get him.
Firstly, let's learn to attack.
Click on a part of my body using the action button to strike there.
Hit him in the head.
A good hit.
You can queue up multiple attacks as well.
Try killing up several attacks on me now.
That's right.
Now you must learn to block attacks.
Click the action button on your creature to make him block.
Block?
Yeah.
You have to block.
That's it.
A good block there.
You'll stop blocking if you do another command.
Motocombat.
Let us concentrate on dodging.
There's a dodge roll.
Click the action button anywhere on the ground to move the creature there.
That's it.
You have learned well.
Let us try some friendly combat to test these skills.
You got these hooves.
Kick him in the face.
Fucking kick him.
Just offense only.
All offense.
Oops.
How do I un-queue a move?
He's actually pretty good.
Block.
Kick.
Willstruck.
Good dodge.
Block.
Double kick.
One more.
Willstruck.
You're gonna lose to Sheepwheel.
No, you don't.
What are you talking about?
I don't think I can win.
Yeah.
That was an important lesson, friend.
You show great potential, but work on your technique.
Oh, it's because it's nighttime.
Right.
Where's he going?
No farewell?
He just...
Okay.
Oh, he just gave me power.
I have a secret for you.
But I warn you.
This knowledge is dangerous.
And you're watching the Disney Channel.
But come only when you are ready.
What I will tell you is forbidden knowledge.
Dangerous even to gods.
It's gonna be how to create tornadoes and meteors and shit.
Why don't you try out what you've learned while I sleep?
How you doing?
Hungry?
You're alright.
Alright, let's go rest up a little.
Hold on, there's another squirrel over here.
What is this?
How horrid.
I think he's trying to speak.
Is it a bat?
This ogre seems to be guarding something.
He's guarding the pass.
He's outside our influence.
So let's send our creature to fight him.
We shouldn't resort to combat with the poor thing.
He looks hungry.
You want to...
What?
You're immune to rocks?
Oh, I can't.
I can't.
Alright, where's my creature?
Let's go.
Let's get you some food and then let's have you beat this guy up.
Matter of fact, let's just do it now.
He doesn't believe in you.
So?
Is this an evil playthrough?
I don't think this is evil.
Wait, why can't I...
The creature can't go this way?
That's why the momma getting the X.
Look at how confident he is.
Uh-oh, you've got a mighty rile.
Prepare for battle, boss.
He's not gonna kick the shit out of me, right?
Uh...
Oh, fuck.
Come on, come on.
Kick him.
Do a move.
Alright, nice, nice, nice.
Okay, I can do this.
Block.
Again.
Offense again.
Block, block, block, block, block.
Block, block, block, block, block, block.
Nice, good.
Shit.
And dodge.
Again.
Oh, I queued up a big one too.
Right in the face.
Oh!
Block.
Lose.
Come on.
It's my fucking...
I'm going like off screen here.
Stop.
Do I die?
Do you die?
I can't even get close to him.
I can't even get fucking close to him.
What the fuck was that?
How do I run?
How do I run away?
Hold on, leader.
Pull back from the fight and try again when we've recovered some strength.
I'm destroyed.
Jesus.
Oh, no.
He tried.
He was trying to be...
Oh, is he dead?
He's not dead, right?
All right, you know, he's okay.
I actually just got scared.
Oh, he got the shit kicked at him.
All right, it's fine.
He was standing there like, no, I'm good.
I'm good.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Just instantly does like the Mortal Kombat.
You got kicked on the ground with zero health.
Stood up and fell back down.
That's what his eyes...
Well, this is not good.
All right, come here.
Let me...
No, Jesus Christ.
Don't get up.
Lay down.
Stay down.
Lie down.
You tried.
You really did.
Just hang out over here for a minute.
Let me get you some food.
There's a silver reward scroll on the beach behind those huge gates.
Okay, here.
Have something to eat.
You look like...
You look skinny.
Here.
I don't like it.
He has a taste for meat now.
I actually do...
I don't want you going fucking anywhere.
Stay here.
How do I like attach you to...
All right, stay here.
You need to heal.
Rest up.
All right, beach.
Where was that scroll?
On the beach somewhere.
Now there's this one.
I remember that one.
What beach was it on?
All right, let's do this one.
This notion that we quite like to sail the ocean
So we're building a big boat to leave here for good
We're not keen on sinking
So we're all sitting here and thinking
Cause we built it too big
And we've run out of wood
I leave
We simply can't leave till we get some more wood
Not keen on sinking
So that's why we're sitting thinking
Cause we simply can't leave till we get some more wood
You're looking for a prayer?
You're looking for me to supply wood?
How dare they leave?
After all we've done for them
What have we done for them exactly?
Perhaps we should help them out.
It might be nice.
How much wood do they need?
What does it say?
The ark.
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't want to do this again.
This notion that we quite like to sail the ocean
So we're building a big boat to leave here for good
I can't skip it again.
We're not keen on sinking
So we're all sitting here and thinking
Cause we built it too big
And we've run out of wood
I leave
We simply can't leave till we get some more wood
Not keen on sinking
So that's why we're sitting thinking
Cause we simply can't leave till we get some more wood
Oh, you're not gonna leave me hanging
We're gonna do another verse
We need wood
How much wood?
I wish it would tell me
Let's go get some
Let's do it
I'll do it
I could smash up this thing right now
But I know you're looking at me
I know
I'm just gonna take wood
Let's go
How much wood do I have over here?
An absolute shitload
Like too much
Let's get like 5,000
What are they doing over here?
Are they praying?
What the fuck was that?
Hey!
What?
Did he kick that from all the way?
What did you do?
Why is the leash not working?
Hey, you're supposed to be stuck in there
What is going on?
Get over here
Wait a minute
What the fuck is going on here?
Get over here
You're in big trouble
You are actually in big trouble
Get over here
He did it
I'm gonna make a FIFA reference here
Because that's the only way I can make this reference
He just grabbed the ball as the goalie
And did a full power kick across the whole game
And for some reason you fucked up as the other goalie
Like you are on the other team
And they scored from the other side
That was ridiculous
Get over here
I need to be like putting
You want a boulder or something?
You can't kick that out, right?
I played like FIFA maybe once
But that's what it reminded me of
Punish him
It's been too long
I can't punish him
All right
I'm just gonna like
I'm gonna like just
Don't do that
Yeah, he can't get out
He just fucking like threw
Imagine if that was a rock
Imagine if he had access to a rock
That would have been catastrophic
Where's this stupid boat?
Look what I got
Wood
Look at that
Thank you for
Three guys, huh?
Now destroy the ship?
No
I couldn't read that
I'm not doing that again, by the way
I refused to sing another one of those
Like lazy singing is what I was doing
That kind of worked too
All right
Let's grain fine
Go
He's pissed
Well, don't just
Soccer kick balls into people that are praying
That's incredibly mean
Here
I'm putting this back
Oh, that's right
Ball
Yes, it is
Don't do that again
Dude, I'm not even certain
The leash does a fucking goddamn thing
Like how can he
Well, why can he do this?
He's not gonna do it again
This leash doesn't do anything
How do I make the leash work?
You're gonna lose it
You're gonna lose it in the water
Lock it with mouse, too
I mean
Isn't it locked?
It's locked to a tree
Like a hundred fucking miles behind him
Fish farms can provide food for your village
A fisherman will deliver his catch to the village
Oh, that's cool
Shorten the length of the
How do I shorten the length?
All right
Stop
Get up there
Just let him do what he wants
No, it's a problem
All right
So if I attach it to here
And then how do I shorten the leash?
I have the leash here
So how do I shorten it now?
Okay
Restrict the area in which a creature can move when he's on a leash
First, attach the leash to an object
Then click the action button anywhere on the leash to pick it up
Pull to stretch the leash to the length you want it to be
Then click the action button on the ground
To set its length
Is that going to work?
No, it's not working
I never understood this mechanic either
I mean, I should be able just to stick it, right?
Like that?
Because look, I'm just giving him slack
Pull
It's probably bugged
Well, pull it back into the building
I don't know if that's doing anything
Is it the scroll wheel?
I don't think so
Wait, hold on
Did that work?
Maybe that did work
Maybe
I'll check back later
I think it worked
You have to like pull it into the
I think that worked
Is he bigger?
Maybe a little
All right
I need to do a brain
Go get his ball
It didn't
No, it didn't work
Why can he just do this forever?
He wants the ball
All right, whatever
I gotta put this wood back
He's hungry
Stop kicking this shit
Stop
Go back up here
Dude, your leash is too long
Fix the screen?
What are you talking about?
Just reapply the leash
Here
Leash is on
Maybe choose a tree
No, he ran all the way over
Whatever, he'll be fine
Use a regular leash
Isn't this a
This is a regular leash
This is like the
Your
This is the neutral one, right?
All right
Let me keep
Let me go do the grains thing
How much do they need?
I don't know
2,000?
4,000?
Let's do
We'll just do like 4,000
A million grain
Well, that would be ridiculous
All right
Where the hell is it though?
I keep losing shit
All right
Here
We're grateful for the grain, holy one
Another thing
It's quite boring if that's all you eat
Need some flavor
So do us all a little favor
Because we ain't going nowhere
Till we get some meat
Why don't you eat Bob over there?
Draw straws
We can't leave until we got some meat
So do us a favor
Find something with a little flavor
Because we ain't going nowhere
Till we got some meat
Okay, found one
Thanks for all this meat
We need more meat though
Wait, how many people are gonna leave?
Forget you, you know
See, what they don't know
Is I'm doing that thing where I grab an arrow
And try to burn it down
It's like sending out a funeral
I just hate goodbyes
I just hate good
I got something
What is it?
This pedestal is a miracle dispenser
It charges up and generates one-shot miracles
Click on the signpost for more info
Is it rain?
Clouds?
What is it?
A handful of water
There are miracles hidden all over Eden
Keep your eyes peeled
A miracle dispenser gives a one-shot miracle
Wonders when it's fully charged
This is water
Okay, what's water?
Is this my village?
No, not yet
Oh, they have a stone over there
What's that thing?
All right, how about right over here?
Let's water the trees
Like over here
All right, nice
What do you mean the cow?
What?
There's no point of you even having this leash on
There's just no point
Here, just you go do you
Has he eaten anything without you looking?
I don't know
You have to restrict the length of the leash
Yeah, I tried to do that like five times
Just pull it and click the action
But it does it just I can't get it to do anything
Yeah, it legit just didn't work
It really didn't
I kept undoing it
All right, I'm gonna do this one more time
So we can be clear
Oh my god, that's a lot
What did you that's a lot of
All right, leash is on tree, right?
Okay, leash on tree
You hate this person
He comes up from points every time
All right, so no wrong
All right, so look
So grab the leash
I have the leash in my hand right now
I can't do anything
I mean, you've moved it
Don't do that
Don't don't click
Well, I have to okay
I have to hold right click to hold this
Right click I have to hold right click, right?
If I let go of right click
He just let you let it go
Like I can pull it
But it doesn't seem to do anything
I mean scrolling just moves in and out
And if I click you just let it go
He's just gonna roam around or whatever
Or he can just do that
And it doesn't even matter where the leash is
He's pissed
This is what
Hold on
Did he just do like the fuck you?
Why do you hate this person?
I don't understand what his problem is
Just go relax
Go sleep somewhere
I've got stuff to do
You are he's coming
He's coming back
All right, all right, right, right, right
The temple is like clicking right now
Why is the temple doing this?
Oh creature creature room
The creature cave
The screws display different attributes about your creature
Oh, that's cool
Is that a raid coming from lime lime malicious
Thank you lime malicious for the fucking raid
Welcome everybody
What's going on?
I'm playing black and white
An old pc game
Thanks lime malicious
Appreciate the raid
Lines pog
Miracle
This shows the miracles our crew chicken cast
Okay, not yet
Wow half a creek in time
All right
So he doesn't know how to do anything
Creature mind
This girl shows our creature's state of mind
His likes and dislikes
I am slightly greedy
I'm extremely tired
I'm very compassionate
I'm extremely frightened
I'm rather playful
I think my god is on the side of good
My deity has paid me quite a lot of attention
What do I think about the creature guy?
He's on the side of good
What do I think about creature slag?
He is black hearted
The creature god is the is the person that he ate by the way
I know about one temple
I know about two creatures who oh slag
Okay, we have to kick slags ass
More general information such as his age and height
This him
Wait, his name is god
Hey boss
You can change or add tattoos to the creature by clicking on him
On the side
All right, wait, how do I rename the character?
Amount of poop zero
People killed one
Animals killed eight
Twelve poops
So he's only killed one person and it was the creature trainer
How do I rename?
This squirrel shows what he's learned to do
Phil is praying with evil
Your creature has learned that he can take food from the field
Okay
Your creature doesn't know how to use the totem
Get him and watch you moving it
All right
Doesn't know how to use the village store
Get him to watch the villagers you
Okay
It's on the list
Your creature has learned how to fish
Your creature has learned how to dance
I haven't seen that
This creature is dumb
Yeah, pretty dumb
Pretty dumb
Let's check this
132 people living
96% believe
10 deaths
67 births
Okay
We need some more
All right, I gotta make some more people
All right, let's head out of here
There he is
What's with the heartbeat?
The do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do
Why what's why is it happening?
Didn't it say I can like do something to him?
I can give him like tattoos
Give him some tattoos
I don't know
How do I do that?
All right
Hold on
I got other tasks that I have to complete
So I can get some more miracles and shit
Because yeah like we got to
There are still sheep missing
What is this one?
Oh no
Some of my poor children are lost
They'll need rescuing
A stranger has been seen putting the children into trances
Who the fuck is this guy?
He has them imprisoned in a secret place
What?
This stranger is to blame
It's got to be him
But if he should die before we find the children
They could be lost forever
Oh my babies
Let's go
We must act
Tiny lives are at stake
Tiny lives?
Come on who cares?
I gotta get this heartbeat to turn off before I lose my mind
How do I shut this off?
Is this something that it wants me to do in here?
That I just to make it like a
Is that a notification?
The challenge cave or something?
Like hey it is a challenge you have to do
I mean I don't know
This doesn't look right
Uh this doesn't look right at all
The Pied Piper
All right well at least I
You must find the person behind this child stealing business
Uh we got it
No more heartbeat
All right come with me
We have to find the person that's stealing the children
Where the hell is that?
No the heartbeat's back
I can hear it everywhere
Go save the kids
I'm trying to find him with a
Wait
Hey come eat these mushrooms
Try that
Is it good?
It was good huh?
It was pretty good
It was all right
He loves him
Let's go
What's wrong?
He's like slowing down
Look there's more over here
There's a sheep
All right you go take a look over here
I gotta return this sheep
For the love of god
That fucking heartbeat
How do I get it to stop?
It won't stop
Where's the sheep guy?
Many thanks higher power
Keep them coming please
It's under the floor
All right back to the cow
How you doing?
Uh I think he might
All right I'm gonna just look for this
Cave
Not cave
What I'm looking for
Is this too
What is this?
As I see it there ain't no need
For me to bow before you son
Going right through the water
I ain't seen deadly from you
Which infesses me what it a bit
Gods have huge creatures
And that's what my mama always told me
And until I see a big enough one
You don't mean nothing to me
Okay
I need to have a big creature
Oh don't leave him as a lost soul
Show him your creature
Oh let him die alone
It's what he wants
The hick
You don't have to justify yourself to him
Oh come on
You've got better things to destroy
Believe me now?
Okay fine
You killed him you uncaring horrid mean god
Wait wait what?
Is he dead?
But why can I touch it?
Why can I pick him up?
Where was that?
Oh I got so turned around
Fuck where was that?
Where was that?
Right here
I'm gonna take myself completely out of the picture
I want to see
I want him to learn
I want him to see things
I don't be like what?
Dead you know what I mean?
Person
I'm taking myself completely out of this one
House you know what else is over here
He needs to see things
He notices
He's like where's dad?
Where's dad?
He's just looking at him
No no no
You didn't learn anything
Look you need to learn
Look you didn't learn
Learn learn
Learn learn learn
Hey look
This is okay
This is fucked up
This is really fucked up
I'm done I'm done
I'm done I'm done I'm done
All right just take it
I'm done
He's tired that's why
All right get rid of him
Get rid of him get rid of him
I just have to get rid of him
I have to get rid of him
I'm not gonna rub his belly
He has no idea what's going on
He's like oh I don't know what you want me to do
Okay
Just go do whatever you want
Sociopath streamer forces son to eat a corpse
No I didn't I'm just wanting to
I wanted to see
I just I need I'm I'm god
I need to see what's possible in the world
There's nobody home
All right well I'm gonna
Okay careful careful careful careful
Careful
Just go adventure and go learn some shit
No I need to teach you shit
Actually teach you shit
Come here
Look at this
Look
Oops
I want you to see me throw things
Look over there do you see it?
I don't know what he's doing
Wait okay come here
Look
You see this?
You see this right?
He don't fucking care
All right what was I doing?
Oh yeah I'm over here
He'll figure something out he'll be fine
I can learn new moves
There's still the sheep thing
Oh the guy oh right the
The guy that's the the guy that's stealing all the kids right?
There he is
I just found him
That's him right?
Actor
Okay wait wait wait I need to
Oh he's coming back more kids
He's coming back more kids
Come on
Where's he?
Where is he?
There he is
All right I need to know where this is
This green is cut at the bottom
It's like that on mine too
It's the way that the the game runs
Like this is the patch
Get away from me you big monster
What?
Found it
Tie him up boss
He's getting on my nerves
He's right
And he won't get away when he's leashed to our creature
I have to leash him?
Wait okay wait stay here stay here
Get away from me you big
Prod me I don't care
I won't believe in your creature
All right we have to sneak up on him
Come over here
Tie him up boss
He's getting on my nerves
He's right
And he won't get away when he's leashed to our creature
No stop you
He's gonna keep coming up
Get away from me
Prod me I don't care
I won't believe in you
Attach him
What the fuck?
Tie him up boss
He's getting on my nerves
You guys did off my fucking strength
And he won't get away when he's leashed to our creature
The guy is like four pixels wide
Zoom in
Prod me I don't care
I won't believe in you
Get away from me you big monster
I just took my fucking hand out
He's getting on my nerves
He's right
And he won't get away when he's leashed to our creature
Leash not
That's what I'm doing
It's you you double click
You double right click to leash
That's what I just did
Get away from me you big monster
Prod me I don't care
I won't believe in you
I thought it says he can't
Okay the leash bugged it
Because he'll he can just run
He can just run
Tie him up boss
He's getting on my nerves
He's right
And he won't get away when he's leashed to our creature
Stop going over there
That all doesn't work
Prod get help
I'm having a panic attack
Okay now
Go get him
You get away from me you big monster
Prod help
I'm having a panic attack
Go get him
I can't tell him to do anything
You get away Prod help
I'm having a panic attack
Are you actually gonna do it now?
You got me
Let me live
Don't eat me
If you spare me and take me to my cave
I'll release the children
Bullshit
I only wanted a family
But the village women said I was too ugly
Oh boo hoo
Let's turn him into a creature snack
But if we take him to the cave
We'll save the little ones
All right
All right get save the little ones
And then drop a rock on his head
Thanks for letting me go
I've released the children
From now on I'll be a proper normal villager
Spreading belief of you
And trying to forget how bad I've been
Wait are we allowed to believe that
You stealing and kidnapping children
Nice
Another of those cruel miracle dispenses
Oh no don't worry
No there's got to be some fucking jail time here
You know what I mean?
Like
I love the throw
Why does he always just go to sleep?
Disciple Forester
No I don't
Just eat him
Get it over with
Eat him
He's gone
Yay
Okay he's tired
What was that?
What happened?
What's going on?
Why is it running away screaming?
All right the heal spell
Maybe it'll turn off the heartbeat
No it won't
Oh they saw him eat a human
Ah that's right
Okay I think it's time to go fight
No I'm gonna do
Let's I'm gonna eat the sheep shit out of the way
What do you mean I ate the wrong person?
All right you just hang out here be good
I need to
Well I gotta do the sheep thing
It's probably like six or seven sheep or something easy
I might have to like reload the game though
Wait what is this?
Look I have these wondrous creatures you can choose from
What?
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa wait wait wait wait wait
You're just gonna throw this at me right now?
That's
I don't want this one because this one's annoying
Are they all horses?
All right we're gonna do click maps on this one
Yeah it's no I can't I don't have click maps
All right what's gonna we're gonna do by numbers
One two three four five in the order that they were from left to right
Jesus Christ okay don't pick the fucking horse
One two three four five here we go
Oh god damn it all right you know what you know what positions they're in
All right I'm pulling back
Oh my god that's because I said don't pick the fucking horse
Yeah that doesn't that doesn't that does that count?
You need to bring our creature boss
Do another vote for the top two all right fine it's four and two
It's either
I can't even talk to you guys
The fun funny gorilla guy or the fun funny horse guy
Horse or was it gorilla?
The gorilla's pretty funny the gorilla's pretty cool
The gorilla's like wicked funny probably
This horse sucks I'm so glad it's not gonna be the horse
He's influencing yes I'm influencing the votes yes I said gorilla
I'm not listening to this all day
All right it's done it's gorilla done
Thank you for voting we're gonna pick the gorilla
But not yet because I need to do more all right first of all I need sheep
And then I have to oh it's raining did I do this?
Should I like take should I claim this that I did this?
All right I think I'm gonna restart the game
Then when did it did it just say what next time the game saves
I'm gonna restart to try to get rid of the stupid heartbeat
Teach miracles to your creature okay yeah
Heal miracle I gotta be uh come here I want to leash you up
Right come here where's he come here all right come here come look at this
Okay look see this
How do I eat okay here come here
Like I can't I guess I can't do both what are you doing?
Oh he's eating look at what I have
Hey
He didn't like that do you learn that because I if he's leashed
So for instance I got a leash on him I can't pick up a spell while he's leashed
Oh there we go you have to link that okay come here come over here
I'm gonna use it on this guy well he's come here look what I got you see this are you looking
He's like hmm I'm interested all right look do you see that
Cool huh interesting you asshole you're supposed to eat him
I don't know if he learned that all right whatever I guess I'm let him sleep let him sleep let him
Sleep just fucking heartbeat all right can I what I need to say the game has to save
So I can restart the game here just I'll take a sheep from here and put it over here
Doesn't matter how many does he need is it not count still looking for sheep
This is still the tutorial world I mean from my understanding and you just do this for like a few
Hours and then you go to like the next level in quotes like level two so I mean it it is tutorial
Zone but it is like chapter one so all right can I be done with this now or does he did I
This whole thing fucked up because he ate one there's still sheep missing hey don't do that
Not nice he's gonna go in here and eat a sheep isn't he I'm never gonna do this this is never
Gonna end what are you doing this oh I can't do it to people so I can do it to sheep instead
I'm not doing anything bad it's a sheep I just can't do it to humans oh I understand
He's learning see that's a person I can't do that to you I can do it to sheep
I know all these things now hello yes you're an idiot all right come here learn this ability
Look what I got okay and we're gonna use it on the sheep that you I want you come
Over here and learn this come here you need to I'm gonna heal the sheep that you just threw
Game safe see oh I learned that was interesting wasn't it yeah you can do that too if you feel
Like it yes yes you can why don't you try yes try it yes good good very good good job oops
Good see learn the spell learn the ability learn the ability learn the ability good
I'm never gonna finish this quest I'm never gonna finish it don't do that no
No you can go to the bathroom you can go to the bathroom you can go to the bathroom just don't
I I no no no how do I make it so he knows he can go to the bathroom he's gonna hold it
You're fine all right I have to okay I gotta get this fucking heartbeat out of here
Okay I'm quit I'm gonna come right back and hopefully the stupid noise is gone
I just had it just saved it let me don't quit no it's it saves it okay now hopefully we go
To the heartbeat and no it's because my wait my what's villagers are starving look at look
At all this food what it's the other village the other village has its own heartbeat look
Wait they're fine look there's something going there's something wrong with this village
It's like oh you there's a huge problem here what's the problem
Disciple breeder no no I meant no no I'm trying to get you to breathe
I'm trying to get you to breathe I'm trying to get you to breathe I'm not trying to
Disciple breeder disciple breeder no stop all right now you work on wood cutting
Dude this fucking heartbeat I don't understand why it's here
So all right somebody look it up why does my temple heartbeat sound keep happening
Can you collect the orb on the cow statue I don't think so
S going to village S nothing to do nothing to do no is it because everyone's bored
What is it at 31 87 87 71 make them work going to farm
All right chilling out let's get to work
Disciple forester disciple forester disciple forester
Okay now what about a grain mover wait we have we need some farm stuff here
Disciple farmer yeah we need some more farmers
Oh people chilling out go do something disciple farmer
Disciple farmer okay all right you know what time it is
It's time for you to it's time for you we're gonna go to the big uh the big guy
Where's the big guy here we go
Please use the leash to bring your creature to me
Use the leash to bring your creature let's go kill slag
Should I kill slag first let me okay hold on let me walk the creature around in here first
Because they're I gotta they don't believe in me yet that much
And then I'm killing that orc what route are you taking
To start eating people no get the cow to carry rocks to increase strength does that work
Yeah actually all right well let me do this first
Oh well never mind we're doing this instead
Come little one the most important lesson of all awaits it's the key to this world
The heartbeat it's the very secret of gaudliness
Please silence it the way you'll triumph follow me to the mountain I will tell you everything there
Let's go
Silence of the heartbeat I hope
All right what is it I must tell you the secret of the cream it's the source of godly power
Creature speak no more nemesis my old master has returned
Come close my friend and listen well this guy doesn't sound like somebody I want to listen to
What is it silence treacher you must surpass all the secrets of the creeds
Nemesis is so determined to be the only god to destroy all other gods and their creatures
He wants ultimate power
Silence you will die for this no find the three parts of the creed which are aligned
This is the only defense against nemesis
Now run get away from here
Leave you got me seek an ally to help you find the creeds seek an ally
Okay
Oh
Oh, no
I got struck too though
No
Um, i'm like cooked
How much oh i'm at 98 percent damage
I can't leave
Your creature is feeling curious
All right run
Okay, I don't like this
Hey
Yes, we must see if there's anything we can do for them
Look like they need help water
the water spell
All right, you just
All right
Where's that water spell? Where is it? So i'm gonna be somewhere. Where is it?
Yeah, get the fuck out of here
dickhead
Oh
Where's
Where's my cow?
Where's the cow?
cow
Let's go get over here
What can I do?
heal
I healed
Um, oh my god, this is horrible. I don't have any more spells that it's not recharged is it pick it up. Oh my god
This is hopeless wait, what's this gold this guy's trash in the place
What's this some trick some new miracle?
It looks like a portal of some kind. It looks like a trap to me
Look it's sucking stuff in try throwing something into it
It'll come out wherever this vortex leads to
Oh shit
Where's the cow?
Where is he? What is this camera camera, please?
Let's go follow me
Oh, there's a whole new world through there
That's it. I'm going through for a look tutorial over than I thought he's gone through
Beligio was right. There's a new land through there and we should send plenty of food wood and
Followers as well. You really aren't afraid of this thing, are you? I say we throw things through
Try clicking the action button on the scroll what the hell do we want to live forever? Well, actually
Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I gotta stop throwing shit in. All right. I gotta start throwing people in
Wait, hold on grained and shit
All right. Hold on
Take everything
I have this 24 000 grain here
How do I make this go faster? All right, you're good
Get his toy ball. Oh fuck. Where's this ball?
Got it. Okay wood. Is he alive?
Oh, no
Oh, no, you need to eat. You need to eat. You need to eat
um
He is he's gonna he'll he'll he doesn't eat he'll die
Eat all right villagers. How do I get villagers to get in there?
I have to just start throwing them
Oh fuck. All right, let's go
Um, i'll take a take a few trees. Okay. Um, where's the cow? What is that?
Oh, he's oh, okay. We need livestock. We need livestock. You're right. Good call
What else do I need the ball his ball his ball? Where's his ball?
He booted it somewhere. I have no idea where
I have no fucking clue where that ball is
I don't know
Get the gorilla
But wait, can I take both?
I can't wait. I can't take both
Keeping the cow
Here pick this up
Quick throw it in
Throw it in do it
Look, see we need some rocks
Wood pile. Oh fuck
What about the vote?
Well, I I didn't know that you couldn't have more than one
I was under the assumption that I was gonna have two friends not replace the cow
Where's his ball? Is he gonna go find his ball?
He'll find it, right?
What about take the spells?
I don't know what I have no idea where he's going. But uh, take the spells too
Does it work? I don't think it does anything
Take it
It actually went in. Yeah, it did
All right. I'm just going i'm i'm fucking I don't care. I don't care. I I don't care
We'll just take this like one more person
And then where's the cow? I need the ball though. Where's his ball?
Fuck his ball
It's so important
Uh, what about the other spells?
Give me the one on the one on the beach
Anything else I missed i'm looking at the ball
Anybody see a ball?
Oh wait, I could do this
No, I can't it's too late. I'm out. I'm out. It's too late
What is oh?
It's too late. It's too late. It's too late ball top left. Did you are you serious?
Fuck the spells and and and fuck the ball
Yeah, fuck it. We're gonna go it's time to go
Yeah, I gotta go. It's over
It's over. It's over. I gotta go
It's over. I don't care. It's over. Whatever. I'll
Where is he?
Any more people I can throw in there?
No, everyone's dead
I don't know where the ball is
I see the ball. No, you don't
He kicked it down here
a long time ago
Like down this way
What about the aztec village?
These people are fine
Look at all this wood for free
He kicked it around the shore around the portal
Well, we'll get one more good look at it
They worked hard for that. Yeah, they worked hard for that for me
That's how this works
What do you mean ego?
I am an all-powerful
God that can do anything
I required 20 000 wood
And I got it. All right, it's time to go
Let's go
Ball right there. I did not miss the ball
Wait, should I take the fence?
Sure. Why not?
I'm done. Wait, is this this is the stuff that I brought?
Okay, I feel all inside. I got like 10 people a fence. Yeah, what a butt
Look someone's approaching
Someone
I greet you as one god to another. I am kazaa
It was I who provided the vortex to save you from nemesis. I declare war come with me
I need your help in return. I will help you
What do you need?
My very existence is threatened by lethis another god from the snowy realm and an ally of nemesis
This could be a lie, but you and I together can turn the tide of this war
There is much to do though
Firstly, you need to build up a village and look after your worshipers
I'll take you back to your village and place down scaffolds for you from my village's workshop
Okay
These create blueprints which indicate to your people what to build and where you want it
He's what a god, but he has to scroll wheel all the way over here. He can't just teleport it
He has to hold his mouse all the way to the edge of the screen
I will give you my finest builder. This is a disciple who works single-mindedly
I don't eat you can create your own disciples by placing people at the locations of the jobs you wish them to do
Here is some food wood and water for your tribe to help you start
I must leave to defend my realm, but I shall return when I can
With the coolest creature in the game the funny gorilla wait
You didn't
You didn't pick the funny gorilla
Oh, wow, that's that was a mistake
Kazaa has provided us with so much. He's a true ally. He's desperate still on the cow, huh?
Let's get our village built. Yeah, and we gotta get the disciples working there
All right, so we gotta get some stuff going here
Oh, I had the heel miracle. It did come with me. Wait, he's throwing shit over here. Wait, what is he doing?
Oh
He's helping me build. All right, we need some workers
you
Come here build this
4200, okay
Everybody make your way down here
We need some wood cutters
We need like a farm too
Where'd you go? Did I just kill that person?
Disciple builder
Grain, where's the grain?
Uh forester
Come here cut some trees down
What do you can you not work?
Why can't you work?
work
Work
That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid
That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid
Oh, okay. That's a kid. That's a kid. That's a kid
All right, we need uh with my where's the wood that I brought with me
I didn't bring a shitload of wood
It like landed somewhere
I brought like 20 000 wood
Where did it go?
This is it
You can drop trees on top of buildings. Oh, that's cool
How much is over here?
How much wood is this? Oh, that's a fence. I hear it all is
Your temple is built
Excellent. Thanks
Let's get this built
Let's fly the wood
There you are
Wood required none
That one's ready. Then this how much wood does this need?
3,500. All right
Wait, what?
Disciple breeder
Is it what is nobody working on this?
disciple builder
3,500
Disciple breeder
What the fuck is going on? Wait, what is the cow doing?
He's making people he's making people breed
He's telling them to breed that's okay
No, that's uh, that's that's all right
This is even our village. Where the fuck is this?
This is a different town. This is not even our time
We'll keep doing your thing
Good. You have built much
But there is more for you to construct
He's building faith. Oh, all right. This is a different, um village. Okay. Hold on
Get my grain
Do they did they build this shit yet? No, not yet anymore wood
Like I got like wood spells and stuff water miracle wood
Come here. I want you to see this cow
Come here
He's like, yeah. Wow. I did that. That was me
He's like shitting in somebody's house
All right wood. Look look what i'm doing. Don't you guys think it's cool? Don't you guys like me?
Wow
Interesting, huh?
All right, you come here. I want you to do some stuff. You want to impress somebody. All right
Well impress this person
Didn't even care
Didn't even care. That's unfortunate
No, no, no, no
Do some do something cool dance
We need more influence
Wait, pick up pick up a rock
I have no influence over here. I can't do anything
All right. I'm gonna put his leash on the town center
I like on their town center
Okay, have fun. Make me proud make people like me
All right, he's just a this is just a fucking roller coaster tycoon mascot at the queue line. This is what he's doing
Wow
All right. Keep doing your thing. He's not killing anybody. He's I think he's changed
I think he's changed. He's not hurting anybody. He's just dancing for people and making jokes and stuff
All right. Hang on here and keep influencing
Pet him for good behavior. Yeah, that's true
You're right. That's a good idea. That's true
You are absolutely correct. Okay, how can I move?
All right back to my temple. Let's fill up the how much wood does this need?
All right. Here we go. It's done
Let's do some wood miracle
Fill it up
Oh fuck you need food, right? Uh, we need do we need we need like a granary
Oh fuck i'm going that's I can't even do that you have to do that
What does this need how much wood do you need over here zero so let's go build it
Disciple builder you got plenty of wood. Let's go
Make the cow watch
uh
Cow's busy making people like us
Actually, you know what get back come back here
Look pick up like a rock or something make make do something cool
Pick up the rock
Pick up this rock
Cool now do something fun
Yeah, good work
Now roll it over there and something show them our power show them our strength
Roll up rock over there
See nice
Yeah, there it goes
Now they know our fucking strength
All right back this way
Uh, come back over here. I want you to look at the stuff that's happening so you learn it
So you're not an idiot
Oh a food miracle. Come here
Are they building crops over here? I feel like they should be doing that
Oh, they don't have any houses come on get over here. Where's the gorilla?
Well a gorilla
Uh, can I not use these?
What does it say?
Do you know that you can hold the mouse button to pick up more food from field? Yeah, I know
You need more buildings
right, um
Stop stop stop
Okay, so this is a what is this? There's a house
So how do I get you to build a building? How do I get you to do this?
Should I water over here?
All right. Well, let's build some houses then
Oh fuck
I have given you an expert builder of worship sites
This building is of great importance
I shall return once you have finished building the worship site
Ha boy, oh boy, oh boy. Oh, we're gonna cause some havoc now havoc
No, but it would be good to cast lots of lovely miracles when we need them
How about houses
worship site
Create some disciples. All right. Hold on lots of fucking food here lots of fucking food here
I can't do everything for you. Look look at how much food they have now
If buildings are not lived in they will deteriorate over time who lives here
People live here, right?
Yeah, look you live here
Why put your stuff away?
How do I get these motherfuckers to build?
All right. I got numb the builders are up here. I need some more wood though
Do I have any more piles of wood? There's one here
Okay, that's done. Now we just have to build it
Where's my buddy? Wait, what's this?
You can water your fields to improve the speed of crops grow the water miracle will water your land superbly. Yes, it will
Although I want him to watch this
look see
Interesting, huh? The creature's learning how to use the storm. Oh because he's watching them move around
The creature is getting curious
Cool, huh?
76 he's almost there
Learn this he's hungry
Okay, I need to you need to eat something
What happened to the livestock?
Didn't I have livestock?
Oh, here we go. The power you wield grows
There there's your food. Eat it
here
All right, so he's good
Uh creature will pay more attention to you from now on
Good, that means maybe he'll learn damn things
Uh wood miracle i'm gonna use it
The creature messed up that miracle. He's still inexperienced
What the miracle of going to the bathroom?
I don't understand. What what did he mess up? I didn't even see it
All right, let's put
I need some workers over here. Oh, we tried to cast water. Okay
It's all right. It takes a while. You can't just know magic immediately. All right, we need some workers over here
disciple farmer
He did it
You did it
You actually casted water. You know how to do it
very good job like
Phenomenal
Good work
The creature will be more inquisitive
He's doing it again
Slapping or stroking the creature determines whether he can and can't do something. Yeah, that's good. Keep at it
He just knows water now. He's so smart
You are the smartest creature ever
Your creature wants to be kind and generous. You guys want to be to get rid of him?
All right, let's go
We're here
Your creature will be kind and generous as he does the fuck you symbol and points and laughs at somebody
good
must build homes
He thought about it he thought about it he's thinking about what he wants to do
I want to be kind and generous. I'm gonna figure out put you down. He's dead. I'm sorry
I'm doing that voice a lot, but that's all I can think of
That's like that's what that's what I hear
He's prepping them
All right, well get some sleep he's tired all right, well here go to bed
Go go in your bed. Is this done? Oh shit. This is done. All right. What do I do about this?
Your worship site is built now. Let me teach you how to create miracles
Your people will worship you at the temple to send them there. You must raise the totem at the village center
You move the hand over the totem
Then you hold down the action button to grab the totem
You move the hand up and down to raise and lower the totem
I've raised the totem. So your this is come worshiping to the worship site
The higher you raise the totem the more people from your village will go to worship you this is emergency prayer
Look at your followers
Okay, they are dancing worshiping you this gives you power
All right
It's a rave
So what every single person in town comes here? All right
Then look, this is gonna be a we're just gonna make a bunch of people braiders
These are the miracles that your people offer you
the miracles of grain wood and water and water
To activate one grab the miracle with the action button and it will be charged by your worship it
You'll see the energy rings flowing into your hand
When the miracle is charged it appears in your hand and you are ready to cast the miracle
Remember worshiping comes at a cost the needs of your worshipers can be seen on these flags
So it's good to satisfy these needs and keep your villagers in good health
I'll leave you now to experiment with miracles and expand your influence by growing your village
So you just have to have grain to stick it outside here
Uh, that's a lot of they just took it all
All food desire 100 each tribe has its own worship site constructed by village of the race
each village has
Miracles at its village center, which also can be its worship site
Worshippers need food and rest which can be seen on the needs flag
Worshippers will swap with less tired worshipers from the village if they're available
You must use the action button to activate a miracle for charging
Yeah, okay
Did he just shrink he just shrunk uh worshipers can die chanting
In the middle of worship site is a chant store if no miracles are charging the worshipers will chant into the chant store for later use
One-shot miracles may be added to the chant store. You can also give your charged miracle energy to other gods
All right. Well, I don't want them to to dance to death
If you make your worship site look more interesting than you'll get more power trees rocks and placing mushrooms. Okay
I'm gonna put the heal miracle in here
Is not doing it, right?
All right
All right. All right. All right. All right. Hold on
Oops
Um, i'm gonna heal you
The creature wants to be kind and generous
Is he bringing flowers to somebody?
What's going on?
He's somebody's dead. Wait
What's he going with this? He wants to be generous
Oh, he's planting. Oh, good job
I I think he's making a garden. I don't know what he's doing
Uh
He's planting trees
Good job
It took four hours to make the
Your creature will be more kind and generous. Look he's gonna do I I would say I don't think you should put them over here
You're you're kind of gonna make a bunch of it's gonna be annoying trees everywhere. All right, whatever he can do let him do his thing
We got wood here comes the house
All right. I don't want you to get I don't want you to all right. How do I stop this?
All right, i'm gonna put the totem down because I don't want they're gonna die
Here everybody relax go back to work
Okay, we'll get another scroll
The cow god of trees the secret of using miracles
Come with me. I have set up an area where you can learn more
Here you can violence about defense
And here you can learn to attack
That one activate the scroll of your choice
Yeah, it's time. It's time to learn about learn about violence behold free huts
We shall use these as our targets
Here are some fireballs to use
You hold the action button down
Like this
You then move the hand to put momentum on the fireball
You release the action to cast the fireball
Devastating you missed fire spreads and causes serious
You can't do it
That's not what I did, uh
Well, okay, I hope they don't do I get more oh man, none of the huts got posted have some more practice
Here are more fireballs
I
Can I get closer
Oh, yeah, you hit one of the huts fire spread. You see a village can be torched in minutes
My fireball challenge is complete
I have given the knowledge of the fireball miracle to your oh nice
I actually get it on your people can worship for this miracle at your worship site
Wow, we can create these now
What about this town over here?
What did they do?
What was that for? What did they do?
They were heathens. All right, let's uh
I don't think i'm doing this thing, right?
Oops. Well now I don't know ever wait, maybe I can maybe I can he could where is he?
Come here
21 he just said he started to learn
That upset him
And it gave him gas. Okay
You can tap on a you can tap on a miracle seat to break it this place is in your hand. Yeah
to burst
To burst the bubble of a one-shot miracle will you quit your attached leash to the miracle itself? Really?
Right. Well, come here. Let's try that. There's more stuff to do over here
By combining up to seven scaffolds
You can create the following structures. One is a small house
Two is a big house. Three is a civic building
Four is field five is a village center
soccer a six scaffolds at the soccer field
All right, how do I get how to make it how to make a scaffold i'm sure it's about to tell me
But wait you come here
Come here, I want you to do this. I want him to uh to open up this thing
All right, see all right, he knows it's on there now
30. All right. He's learning it. Maybe he can figure it out
Here's the food miracle
Look watch what I can do
Not cool
Oh and you can eat it. Well, don't stand in it. You can eat it
look
rain
That's time. I'll pick it up. Whatever. Fuck it
Okay, let's uh, let's figure this out
Kazaa sent me I can help you build your settlement up
right
People are sleeping outdoors as they don't have enough buildings to live in
This is the workshop. I make scaffolding here
It allows you to decide where new buildings should be constructed. All right, let's go you can supply me with enough wood
I can build a scaffold
more houses
Feed he's not no, I need this person
So you get scaffolds you can do I get it
How much wood do you need?
Oh man in the workshop wants some wood
Okay
I can do that
How much like five grand ten grand
Well, i'll give you ten thousand
No, let's do five dollars
Don't make the soccer field it's bugged
I think there's an actual patch to do that right here
Look, there's a lot of
All right
How did I get this game?
I bought it
and then
I installed it
And then I had to do a bunch of tweaks to get it to work on windows 10
Because if you don't know this game had some of the shittiest drm ever made
Give me a little point where turn the wood into scaffolds
Uh went like windows actually removed the ability to use the drm
Because it's such a vulnerable piece of shit
so
You have to like essentially
You have to either disable
a feature in windows and put your computer at risk
Or you have to go around the drm is the only possible way you can play
It looks like your scaffolding is ready. We just need to move it to an area where we want it built
That's a lot of wood to place a scaffold down on the ground. All right, let's get it
Scaffold value one
When you're happy with its location and angle click the action button. All right, let's make like let's let's not be stupid about this
How about um
Down here. Yeah, this looks all right
right here
Oh, this is such a worthwhile cause planning homes to be built for the homeless
There is another way to solve this homeless problem. Oh, yes. Yeah
Kill him
These two guys are fucking wild
You're gonna do some more miracles you're gonna practice your water
Practice your water
I know you can do it. You need more buildings. You just scared him. Thanks a lot dickhead
All right, let's do um still homeless people in the village. All right, let's do more houses more wood houses
Oh fuck. I need a lot more wood
All right. I gotta make people do tree cutting
Because we're almost at wood they're building this one, right? All right, when he who's who is not doing anything right now
Going to a building going to a building. All right chilling out
Not anymore
You now do this chilling out not anymore
You're a woodcutter
Chilling out not anymore
Where they going where they're holy shit, oh that they're taking
All right. We're good
How many are here too?
Should I all right? I'm gonna put more scaffolds on top. I want a bigger house combined scaffolds. There we go. It's two, right?
Two is a bigger house
Yeah, that's what i'm talking about. Let's put this one right over here right next to this one
What just happened? That's not what I want
There we go. Okay. All right build it
Raising and lowering the village end of turnip is used to get into the worship. Yeah, we know that already
There are still homeless people in the village. You need to build more houses rotating automatically. Yeah, that that actually is
sucks
all right, so
What am I gonna do about trees?
And anybody even work here
The creature is hungry. He'll he eats sheep. He's fine
People need to work over here
I mean, there's a lot of food
Let me put this over here. All right, i'm gonna do a uh, i'm gonna do a wood. It's time to worship
It's time to worship
Because we I need we need wood
Miracle wood miracle wood. All right, everybody gets fucked up here
Oh, I already own it. Let's go
How much wood is it a lot?
We still need
Oh, there's another scaffold right there
All right, we'll put this down here
Okay, maybe it doesn't matter. Maybe they just go and I don't know
All right
This is so much food
Children desire. Oh, we need to okay. We need to
All right. We need to make kids
We need some all right. Who's
you
two
Are there any?
Can anybody even breathe here?
Oh shit. Is this a is it all men?
Oh, there we go breeder
Whoa
disciple breeder
Must build home is there any of the
Where are the women?
Disciple breeder. Okay, that should be all right
People still want to lose people in the village. You need to build more houses
We'll get it done
What are you doing over here?
Your creature is dehydrated
He can't just make water and drink it
But can't he just make water and just put his mouth in the air?
Your creatures third. All right. We'll
Go drink some water or I guess
Don't go too far
All right. How am I doing on influence?
I gotta start to move people away from this. We have there's too much food
disciple forester
Yeah, the grain there's too much grain we need some more builders
Yeah, more builders there's so much grain over here
What does everybody do for a living?
building building building building right building breeder
Going to dead person
What do I do with them?
I'll just
um
No, no
No, uh, who's who died? Who is this?
Somebody will all right. Somebody will do it
Still need more houses
Is anybody even in this one?
Yeah, okay
These ones are done. These ones are done
Still need some more wood or is it done? Okay, do we still need more houses?
There are still homeless people. All right, i'm making a i'm making a huge one more houses
I need more wood
You're making babies, but people are sleeping outside. I'm only focused on making houses right now. That's it
Where's my wood miracle?
All right, everybody get over here
To the worship site all of you
Go on go on miracle wood
Keep giving me wood
I missed big bits. Oh shit. I did. All right. Hold on. Give me one sec
How much wood did I just put in there?
All right, it says fiddy 5 000 bits from fiddy. I did miss that fuck. That was like 10 months ago fiddy for 50
Thanks a lot fiddy. They say hey look I found a hilarious but out of context video play it now or i'll get angry
What is it?
You just take them down spark plugs out in the down there just like bobby says it's like it go boo boo just like
It's pretty good
This boom howard drum
thing
They say just kidding only wanted you to say you're a cool dude germa harper the video is pretty funny watch it though
What is it?
What's going on here going to what what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with them?
age 34
What wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on
What's wrong?
Miracle wood just put wood fucking all over the place. Oh, he's he's he saw that. All right
More wood another one
More one more
Miracle wood
Okay, that's good
That's good. That's good. That's good. How much wood is in here? That's not enough wood
But wouldn't be foods in the wrong place
Foods in the wrong place
It wasn't it sitting right out here
All right, you guys can stop
What in the tutorial that was just sitting out there
They they they come out here and they they suck it all up
Yeah, see
Did you just eat somebody?
You have to put it in the bowl
Oh, but he in the tutorial he put it outside here
All right. How many do I have? Okay. Good
What is it three for? Uh
What's that one?
Three makes a civic building
Good i'm doing a civic building. Oh, it's got to be where can I put this?
It's going to be down here
Oh fuck
You do you do?
It is that that is what happens god damn it. All right
How do I get rid of this?
What?
Fuck it. Whatever. I don't care. Uh, thank you james o burn for the five community subs. Thank you james
I know it's a sideways house, but what do we want to do?
How are we doing?
We have a lot of food still no wood
Even how far they have to go to cut down trees. I need more trees
Is this stealing?
Like is this considered stealing?
I went to the gym. Is he still a dick?
Uh, not anymore. Actually, he's he's actually a pretty nice person now
um
He just ate somebody. I don't think did he though did he actually eat them?
Make more breeders. I spent 1.2k on this
Well, I still need
You need to build more houses
I need more wood is what I need
Somebody said let me see how much if I what happens if I do this
Okay, I can do that
I'm gonna do one more
How many people are homeless?
Get over here
I need to go take a look at some shit. I gotta I gotta get a good idea here of what how many people are doing what?
No, this is the influence, huh?
So this is whose influence?
Is this me which one's me?
That's a that's a monkey
Also a monkey
And a monkey I told you they're all using monkeys. I'm gonna get made fun of
It's the war room. All right, let's go back here
toggle influence
toggle miracle activity
And let's pull back
How the hell do I pull back?
Zoom zoom out
How the fuck do I get out of here?
And you don't
Click the map
No, no, but i'm gonna let this realm by taking his villages
I have to conquer this guy's realm
He's got a turtle
Can I can I can I pick up his people?
Oh, I can
Did I just was that like a so should I not have done that?
Please please stop murdering people
Wait, am I gonna get like uh, oh
Am I gonna get like a a nuclear bomb or something dropped on me?
Wait, no, that's my friend. This is my friend. This is my friend. That's my friend. This is my ally. Oh shit
Right, right, right, right, right
Well, he said conquer this area conquer lethers and will I thought I was on that guy's map
All right. Well, i'm sorry
It's this guy. All right, give me the fuck back to where I was, please. I want to see how many people are
408 percent believe in you five deaths in my every only eight births
All right, eight builders. Okay less builders
What the fuck? Uh, I gotta pee
Like really badly actually
I'll be right back. I don't have a brb screen because I moved it
That's great
I'll be right back
Hello, he was muted. I know i'm eating something
Something quick
We can't hear you. I know i'm eating i'm trying to eat silently because people hate that these houses suck by the way
All right, do I have enough?
Our village now truly has more room for people building more will encourage growth
This is a village. I want to be part of in my own village. I held the knowledge of the forest miracle
Follow me
forest miracle
planting trees
Constant worship is needed to maintain it, but the wood it provides is a blessing to the people
Didn't I already have this?
What is it?
constant
Forest. All right, let's do it
Yeah, right
Yeah, he's all right
I went home. Did I just eat the silicon gel bag? No, okay
I thought I did I
I I think I might have is this silicon gel? I got no it's not I hate these fuck get these things out of here
God damn it
It was really sandy
Okay, so who do I have to destroy?
blue
What do you got?
Oh, oh we got lightning and thunderstorms and shit over here
Whoa, what?
You can wait you can tell them you can tell what i'm over here. What do you got lightning?
Can I steal a lightning spell?
Sure, I can
uh
Oh i'm not in one of these again
The stones hold the spirits of the ancients each has its own voice
It is said that when a correct tune is played special powers are unleashed
When the stones are tapped the spirit sings
Few people know the melodies you may meet them or discover the melodies for yourself
Okay lightning
I just fucking learned a melody god damn it
Expand your villages
He's like hey, I don't really mean to be like in your face here
But uh, you need to fucking work on your village quit ticking around. I am lethys leave my territory
Fine, i'll just launch a fucking fireball. I'll just launch fucking fireball at you
Put them over here
Can I reach from here?
Oh ricky, i'm just gonna launch fucking fireball at you ricky
Should I do some fun? No, no, no, no, not yet. Not yet. We have to expand
Forest barricade, let's uh, let's just do some prayer
Let's wait. I need uh grain. You said put it in the thing
The bottom is cut off because it's 1080p. This game was never designed to be 1080p in hd
So and you lose like a tiny amount of the bottom of the screen
Sorry about that
Uh, let's get some forest
Come worship me
A hundred percent of the whoops. I just pulled speaking of windows
There we go. Let's go
I want the forest
Give it to me. This is the most beautiful game ever made
Huh? I don't know. What should I plant the trees over here?
What is he doing?
Go to bed
Give it to me more
Forest miracle. Okay. Okay
Over here over here. Okay, that's what that does
I really wish my um
Dog could have seen that
Do it again
Do it again loud chair, I have no idea what the fuck you're talking about. All right, I'll do one more
Miracle forest
It should be close enough
This is crave
Jerky, it's the best jerky you can buy
Full stop
Okay. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What are they doing people dying?
All right enough enough fireball
Um, all right, everyone watch out get out of my way. Nobody come near me
Where's this motherfucker?
All right. Give me give me another one. Give me another one. Give me
Home run give me one more one more everyone get out of here last one
Fireball, okay. Now everyone leave leave leave leave leave leave. I don't want to work everybody to death here
can I
Pull this down. Am I gonna act don't tell me i'm gonna actually throw this am I?
Can I pull this down?
All right. Come on
Imagine seeing that the gods like oh here comes. Oh, that's how you want to play, huh?
Oh, that was pathetic
You missed
All right, everybody go this he's chasing birds. All right, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop
People will die if I do this shit still I've got more forest. This is why they don't fire. Are they burning?
No, they aren't right
There's another thing to do over here
Soon you will need to protect your villages and their buildings
The physical shield protects against objects which are not of a spiritual nature
When you have the miracle, this is how you cast a shield
The shield
You move the hand to where you wish to start the shield
Why then you hold down the action button and trace the perimeter of the shield?
like this
and the shield
I'll throw these rocks at the hut and watch the shield
All right, it's protected the shield deflects the rocks
Now you can try
Shield the hut and I will attack it
Tap the shield medical and wait hold the action button
This is black and white
The shield is ready
Is there a throw rock spell or something that i'm missing
The hut survived my onslaught. Well done
Different sized objects to different levels of damage to a shield
It will disappear after taking excessive damages. I have given the knowledge of the from now on your people can worship
Thank you
It's really hard to obtain and to install
Yeah, it's a pain in the ass
But I got it running
And I got it running in 1080. So i'm happy about that
Whatever that's protected good
All right, I need to
What are you up to?
I think it's time
Is he watering good job. All right, so we need
What else do I need?
I'm sure this will probably tell me you have become well established
Our combined strength is becoming greater. We're gonna do an attack near lethys
It will become more essential to have your miracle skills in top form
For this you must experience the benefit of gestures
Can charge miracles without having to return to your temple to select them
Here comes a fight move your hand in a spiral like this
Now select the miracle of your choice grain is selected like this
Oh god
I can't see the symbols in the bottom right rise to the bottom right of the screen. They're cut off from me, too
Damn it
You try it now. Okay
um
Oh for the love of god, I can't see them
I can't see
You should practice your gestures go on and press this town over here, okay
fireball
They look like they're in a bad way
No food or wood
Why don't you create some food for their village store while I supply them with wood?
Hmm that's a good idea you have people worshiping at your worship site
I have to get rid of the fallout wait
Wait, hold on
Did that go straight up and straight down? What?
Why did that happen?
Is everyone all right?
Oh, thank god. I didn't hit a building. Okay. I need to get I need to go to my worship site thing
Like 50% of you get over there
More what buildings?
My grain is I don't know a circle. I can't I don't know what that's doing
Fucking help you do it
How many times do I have to do this dude
Did I not do it you need to fill up the village store with food
Food
Give me that food you creatures getting tired we'll let them sleep
Hey look at that they like us you need to fill up the village store with food
Excellent we have filled the village store. I was ahead of you are easily impressed
I
Time is not kind. You need to gain influence in the direction of our common enemy. Are you winning?
I strongly encourage you to gain this town
Before I leave to defend my realm. I must tell you one more thing
You will notice you cannot do anything even cast miracles outside of your influence
However, there is a way using the power of belief
You can reach outside the edge of your realm for short periods of time
But your influence is soon lost until your hand is returned to your realm
Hey, who's winning?
All of us are
All right, so make these
I was spicy. That was really spicy. Why?
Uh, okay, and I know I know what happened. I know what happened. All right, so this is the this is chili lime crave
and
Uh, all the chili lime was not on any of the pieces of meat
Uh, I just did the thing where I opened it up and tilted the rest of the crumbs in my mouth and got every single
Chili that was in the whole bag
Okay
Right. That makes sense
All right. So I gotta let's go
Do you believe do you believe?
Do you believe?
Here believe now. What should I do?
Teleport miracle. All right, i'll give you some food
Wait, how far away is this? Not too bad
Give him some wood. Yeah, let's give him some wood
What is what a three? I have no idea
Here's some wood
Everybody love me
Everybody love me any more belief
Uh, i'm sending the creature over there
He has he's been doing he's always he's been shitting behind the same bush
Come with me
He has been going to the bathroom behind the same bush
for two hours
Go do stuff over here
Go for it. Okay. Now I also the people still worshiping. Let's stop that
And
Do I need anything?
Here he goes. Let's go see what they'll what they think about him
We'll see if we have to eat any people
All right, we made it up here
Okay
Yes, you found a rock very good
Now go into this town
Have you ever seen a creature before?
Look at me. That's right
Have you never seen a cow this big before?
All right
entertain them
Don't leave stay
No, stay stay stay here and entertain them so we can take this over
All right, stay there
Move scroll destroy his temple to eradicate our belief and let this
Let's move in and enlighten these poor people enlighten them or destroy
What do you think I say we drum up some faith from these people?
We gotta take this place boss. I can't stand the waiting
All right, so I have to go in there and entertain them and make them think i'm cool
Or destroy them. I don't know. We'll see
Maybe i'll destroy one of the towns with fireballs
nice moves
All right, only 360 belief needed in fact, let me um, hold on
What do you guys need wood let's get some wood in here
All right, let's go back to the town
You can stay there and hang out. You can sleep there, too. It's all right
All right. How many people are worshiping here? Is there any food in here?
Not really. That's good
How we doing on houses?
People got places to live people eating
How come they only kind of believe when I give them wood extract more buildings? Jesus. All right, what am I going to do?
make a field
The five scaffolds is another village center
Or seven make a wonder
Or make another civic building
I'll do i'll make a wonder
Let's try it
And then just have people breathe the fuck out of each other. Yeah
You don't really have your villages desire flag
People need stuff
Badly what are we talking about?
For good desire. I have plenty of food wood desire more civic buildings civic
They still believe
Why don't you do one of your spells? Wait, what's this teleport miracle?
Whoa, what can I do?
uh
Wait, what am I doing?
How do I disable that?
Where are they getting get teleported to?
I mean it looks cool
They're not gonna get sucked in right?
No, what is he thinking?
Oh, you need two of them to be activated. Well, that's not good
All right back over here
How many do I have one two three?
I need more wood. How do I need more wood?
I have 10 000 wood over here like why can't I can't supply it production? Why is it just halted?
I don't understand
Oh, it's because there's only space for three. I get it
Okay
Okay, seven, right?
There's four
Four is a field
Let's see what the wonder does
Five
All right, we got let's let's I gotta start moving people around
All right. What do you nothing to do?
Well, you have something to do now disciple forester following mother following mother nothing to do. Yes you do
Following how many kids do you have?
going fishing
Following mother how many kids exist in this town? They're like
50 kids and like 10 people
Going to farm
following mother
checking animal for slaughter
Following mother following mother following mother following mother
Breeder breeder. Okay, these these guys they're making all the kids
All right, forget about the farm for now. We need more wood
disciple forester
We're at six
Okay, let's any more wood over here
must build homes
How come there's designated breeders? It's just the nature of the game
Uh, yeah, it's it's a little weird. I know
All right, where's cow? How you doing over here sleeping? He's hungry
All right. Let's go get some food
You can come back home
A faded hand cross over the hand gets the players outside of influence. Yeah, I just was told about that
I go chill over here. Let's come back eat something now. These people these are not my followers, right? Not yet
Well, we got to change that
200 more belief
My town sucks must build homes
Here we go wonder
This is going to be somewhere where it's not going to get in the way down here
We're low on
Shit
Why would you build your house in the side of a fucking mountain?
No one's going to visit this
How much wood does it need to be built?
Well, here we go. The norse wonder increased the yield from fish farms and increases the strength of weather miracles
What a waste of fucking money
okay, so my
my
Rain is cooler
All right, I gotta start stealing shit. I gotta start pulling trees from somebody else
You don't even how you don't have any trees left. What is this weakness creature miracle?
I'm gonna hold on to this
Hey, nice to see you letting the people's desires go unheeded. What?
Am I being evil how?
Oh because right because they're building a fucking they're building this for no reason
Uh, all right, I need wood
civic center
Wait that
Why is it not being built?
The cow is starting to look like a demon. No, it's not
I need three
All right. It's time
I gotta I gotta start taking matters into my own hands here
I can build the forest back up with the miracle. It'll be fine. All right, let's build it
I just got back from kissing what?
What do you mean you got back from kissing?
Yes, i'm still playing this
Yo, I just got back from like kissing girls, okay
Why is he playing farmville?
I have to destroy this first town. You know what I mean? Like I I need to I have to destroy it
I have to beat this first campaign
I have to
All right, here's another scaffolding
Oh, i'm starting to run out of room down here
Is this this isn't a I want to say I need a civic center
Wait, what?
Isn't it three for a civic center? Am I crazy?
Three civic building
It is a civic building
Oh, all right
Put it over here put it right there disciple breeder. Did they build the wonder yet?
21 000 wood. Oh shit
Uh, uh, how do I stop them? How do I delete this?
There has to be a way I can just delete that right?
I don't want to do that
Throw a fireball at it. No, i'm talking about like refund my money
All right, i'm gonna get another one
What do they need?
Wood and food, but there's a there's a shit little food right here
Well, so get working then what?
All right, start breeding
Start breeding
What do you mean food? You don't know it's right here
You're standing in it
Disciple farmer disciple farmer disciple farmer
disciple farmer
There's fucking 6 000 food in the coffers. What are you talking about?
It's literally in front of you
go eat
It's actually right in front of you another civic building
last one
All right, build that shit up. I can't fucking believe I need more wood than that. I need 20 000 wood
And then i'm gonna build these last two houses then i'm gonna make everybody a breeder
Everybody is going to breed
We're gonna have a party up here
And people are just gonna all breed
All right. So what's the problem? I don't understand what you're talking about
Food design there's food in here
Do they just not know it's in here?
The village store is nearly out of food
Do you need more food than that?
this like
15 people that live here
Well, there's more than that. All right
Where's where's where's my buddy?
I need to put you on like a quest
He's thirsty. All right, go fucking drink water from something
He's gonna go drink water
Speaking of water. All right, it's time. It's time. It's it
Let's go
Everybody get up here. I'm gonna do a bunch of food miracles and shit
Do I have enough to do it or do we need to do we have to dance for me get up there everybody
Everybody that's able to this person looks like shit
I'm gonna fill both of these with food. I'm gonna do water. I'm gonna do it. It's gonna be great
miracle food
Actually, I need some of this
You're currently on a plane make a joke for me
Um, I don't know. Will you hear it?
How big how good are your headphones? It doesn't matter if you have the best headphones in the world
It's hard to hear anything on an airplane
All right, let's go food food food food
Food
That wasn't the joke that was me explaining that you won't be able to hear me saying it
I don't even know how he can hear me talk right now
What are you guys talking about miracle food?
Miracle food
How much food is in here? How much food do I get per miracle? Not very much
This is not gonna work out the way that I think it is
Miracle food
Leashed and is dying
All right, one more the cow's not leashed I just saw him walking around
The cow is not leashed
Oh, he's real leashed. Oh, he doesn't shit
He doesn't do anything
He just shits. All right, everybody stop this food here
All right, one more food
And then miracle wouldn't and then everyone go back to work and then just start breeding
Miracle wood
What's that other one?
What is it? What's the seed one?
I can't even fucking see it stupid ass screen. I can't even see it. Just shake it. Give me this one
Miracle forest
Okay, everyone can leave
Let's put everybody on
I really shouldn't water too. Shouldn't I fuck?
Right, some of you go back some of you go back like
Like 10 20 you go back I need the water
W right
I gotta water these crops, you know
You know who learned water
But for some reason
Is doing it anywhere anymore. He was doing it
Everywhere
He did it everywhere. He was practicing and now he's just shitting in the ocean
He's not doing anything
Okay, it's time to breed
He has to watch you. I've shown him like a thousand times
All right, let's do some breeding
Who wants to breed?
disciple breeder
breed
Disciple breeder, okay breed
Disciple breeder we need some more people here
Disciple breeder
Okay, they're good
Disciple breeder 57 and 54. That's all right
All right. Where are you at?
How are you creatures hungry? Let's go. Let's actually go do some shit. I want you to learn how to do things
Come with me
I'm gonna do miracle of water on the crops and you're gonna watch
Miracle shower come here
So see this
Over here. You see what i'm doing
Interesting, huh?
Cool, do you get it?
Hey, he gets it
He did it do it do it again
Yes
Yeah, do it again. Look at how smart you are
Yeah
You're so smart
Now get him a ball I can't get him a ball
You could be more kind and generous to those sorts of guys
All right. Good job. Good. Keep doing that. Keep that up. All right. What are we doing for breeding? We good?
I need to go. All right. It's time. It's time to fucking assimilate this uh, like into my land
Where's my buddy?
First of all, is there food up here?
This food up here, right?
Are these people like gonna die if they just
They're not just gonna
Come with me. We got some stuff to do
down here
It's time to make this village believe and we're gonna make this village believe we're gonna have to start
We're gonna start going hard here
I'm gonna cast some spells. I'm gonna water their crops. I'm gonna put we're gonna do a bunch of crazy shit over here
This village believes in you. Well, but how come they won't do anything for me?
How come like how come they can't do anything for me? All right, here we go
Watch this shit guys
Hey, look what I can do
cool, huh
see
Look at that
uh
Now they're gonna think that I did that now they're gonna really believe
All right, how much more belief do I need?
Doesn't it say if you hover over how much belief do I need stop?
293 belief left i'm adding belief. Oh fuck. I just almost exited again
It's already mine
Well, let's go to the other fucking town. Let's go
Why can I not control anything?
What's going on?
Why can I not zoom in now?
What did I do? I leaned my hand down and pressed a button
And I now i've lost control of the game. Was it like z?
x
I elbowed a button. I don't know what it was caps lock
shift
control
alt
c
V b it had to have been like q w which what the fuck was it?
I can't zoom in and out now with my mouse scroll and I can't turn
What the fuck did I just press?
It's tab. Give me a break
Okay, come here. No, it wasn't tab. Something's wrong
And what is going on?
y and z
I didn't fucking press what?
God damn it
The top right corner. I like okay, let's go
I have to make this town believe I was in a chat room
these people
Uh, i'm about to no, should I drop a fireball in these people?
No water there shit
Be nice
Uh, so he knows how to make water 100 now
Very good
I kind of want to teach you
fire
stone. Ooh
I want this
What do I do with this?
can eat
Okay, um
Come over here and learn this
Learn how to do this
Is it will this hit?
I can't do it over here
Oh fuck. I have to do this in a random place then
I can't cast. Oh, I need to cast it in a circle
All right, do it like here
Why did he do that on the rock?
All right. Look see what I just did
Don't stand in it
Just look
Yes
Wait, he's doing it
Is he doing it?
Oh
He almost figured it out. Look at this
You see?
Okay, you ready?
Interesting, huh?
You try
Yeah, you try it. No, he doesn't know. He's just stupid
He's too stupid
He needs to learn fireball. He does
Look, there's another one right here
Come here
Take a look
Do you see?
Why wait? Why do I have this stupid leash on? Why is this leash on? I've never equipped this leash once
Why is this on?
I've never put this leash on. Why is it on?
Why is this leash on?
I'm serious. Why is that leash on? I didn't equip that
Give me a break. What? I pressed V. Oh, give me a fucking break
Oh my god, he learns 10 percent
You're feeding it nutrients through the umbilical cord
All right, come here fireball. You and I are gonna learn
You and me
Come here fireball
No, no fireball
Is it queuing up? It looks like it should be
Uh, I don't want to go in this guy's territory yet
Stay over here
Oh, it's because worshipers and there's no worshipers, right?
All right, well get back in here and
Get these people entertained for now
That was 39 belief points. All right
I gave them wood. I gave them fire
It's all right. Is this fireball still not ready?
Oh, whatever. I'm just gonna let go. I'm gonna go back this way. How are you guys doing on fireball?
Fireball's made? Wait
um
Why can't they make it? Is it enough people or food or?
I don't know
Sacrifice somebody
Uh, what's why can I not select fireball?
Why is it not getting any uh
Teach the cow that I don't think I want to well, why can I not select any of these?
Okay, there we go
All right, come here
I'm gonna practice
We're practicing over here
Yep, that's a fence you can go around it
What's he eating?
Did you eat someone?
Who did he eat? He ate somebody come here
All right, you see you're paying attention
pay attention
Interesting, huh?
Oh god
Okay. Well, that was
My fault that was my fault
That was my fault. Let's do water
Ready look i'm not even throwing it to the left. You see that man like i'm not doing that shit
How much belief all right 88 what believed go in here and just do some dances
Uh, okay water
Miracle shower
Cool
You can do it, too
How much more belief do I need?
35 belief. Oh my god
Is this a god game or a cut you know what?
That's much easier
That's just easy. It's I mean like everyone can like what the fuck face me but
This is what I like to say
Yes, I knew you'd be a wise choice to ally with
All right. It's time
It's time to attack
Kill why would I kill yellow?
All right, everybody can chill out for now
I'm gonna take back down to like 20
How much wood do I have not enough?
All right, let's do 25 percent
Teach it offense
That's what i'm trying to do with the fireballs, but he's stupid
He's got like 20 fireball learned
One of your villages has very high desires. This isn't what news leader
Dude, that's like fucking
This 10 000 food here
must build home
That's a crock of shit. This was the stupidest thing I ever did
Seriously
All right more more learning fireball
He apparently doesn't want to do it and you make too many kids
No, I made a wonder of the world that took like five houses worth of material
I'm not gonna ever learn fireball without a bunch of people
Can I take anything from them? No, I mean, yes, I can like just I don't care. Give it to me
You've 20 000 wood give me 10 000 of it
disciple breeder
Disciple breeder disciple breeder
Wait, this takes a worship energy
All right fireball come here
Oh, he's making them breed he's remember I didn't do this shit he did
He's doing this
Not me. So everyone's blaming me for this, but the cow is making people breed
Yes, you do not not good
Not a good job
Not good
Come over here. Were you even looking?
He was yeah, he's 20 try it
You have 20 fireball knowledge use it
I didn't teach him this that's why there's so many people that's so so populated
There's so many kids running around because in the very beginning when we first got here
He was casting the offspring. He was knighting people
Give me another fireball
He was
masturbating
Okay, I need another fireball he's gonna learn it
Come here
Look at me. Stop
You need to learn this
Learn it
learn
Learn fireballs. No, I didn't want to tap them
stop
Learn fireball. I have to like burn something in front of them. Let's okay. Let's do it on these trees. Come here
Look yes, he saw that. Okay. Good. He's like, all right. I see
You do it
Fuck
Right there duck you looking? Oh fuck. I burned him. Oh fuck. I burnt him. I burnt him
Okay, he almost knows fireball
Do it
Do fireball do fireball, please
look
Look 45 give it a try do it. I know you can do it do it
It's okay
It's okay. You're doing great
It's okay. You're trying you're trying you're trying try harder
Fireball
Come here. Is he paying attention? He is
Hey, look over here. No, no, no, no, no, no, don't get distracted
Are you looking?
Look go eat go be a t-rex for fuck's sake. He almost knows it. He's at 56 go eat
Cast him the water spell
He almost has it
Yes, good work
Uh, he this pig apparently thinks he's real cool
The really cool
Look at his stomach
His stomach is getting like imploded
He wants to impress somebody well good because it's time for your final lesson
It's time for your final lesson fireball
Are you listening?
You want to impress somebody impress me?
Oh my god, i'm not trying to do that. You know that
I'm trying to throw it
Fireball look there it goes you try look at him. He's like, hmm. Let me think
That's okay. All right, you you've you've worked really hard time to go home. All right, let's go
You did really good
Go rest over here
Go rest
I gotta get rid of this fucking dumb forest
It's taking a belief point
Rest him in his pen. Okay. Yeah, I will
Look at him watching
Oh, that was interesting
He's paying attention
He looked away at the last second
Well, he's gonna just relax or he's gonna shit on somebody. That's fine
All right. Let me go back to see what the hell's going on in my town
What's going on in my town?
No, we need to build homes
What do you want?
What did he just do that for? What do you want?
You'd rather have him cast fireballs than masturbate
Um
I mean, yes, one of those things is productive and that one of those things is not even what he was doing
All the time and energy it's taken to learn him fireball
You'll see it's gonna be worth it
Come here
All right, we're gonna do keep going
Just build them. I don't care. Just build them
Build them sacrifice somebody
Not yet
All right. Fine. I'll sacrifice somebody
Uh, how about it? Who's the oldest?
Eight eleven six thirty seven six
Ten eight fifty seven
All right, fifty seven
Okay, you need to go you need some rest
Here eat some of their food
Eat it
It's food. You'll like it
See
It's good
See you do it again. Eat it again
You like it
You just tried it
Okay, good now you need to okay go back to your pen and go to sleep we'll practice again tomorrow actually go in your pen
Do not stray over my territory
Shut up
There's a way till my cow knows fireball. He's gonna torture your entire fucking city
What are you doing?
What's he doing? Get out of here
What are you looking at?
He was like looking at where the kids stay
All right, buddy fucking
After my after he's ready
This is gonna be it
Just fucking wait
Let's get rid of this
I still need food somehow. It's almost full
70 food desire my god
Like do I
Let me just help you out here then
Who has food I can steal
All right, is he sleeping?
He's asleep. Let him sleep. Let him rest
We're gonna learn he's gonna get to actually 100% fireball tomorrow
Am I gonna play the sequel? Yeah, that's the plan
The plan was to play this until i'm thought it was not fun anymore
Until like that. I saw most of what I wanted to see and then do the second one at some other time
Food miracle. Yeah
I feel like it doesn't
I need to put food over here, too
All right, how you doing you ready to learn you look ready to learn
Take a look paying attention
Yes
73 percent
He's almost there
He almost knows it
Are you attentive? Would you like to see another one?
Look look at me
Okay, are you looking he's looking? Okay, good
Don't hit the fucking village
Okay, we're fine. Good. Yep. He's like, oh, oh, yes, I can you can do fireball. I see
All right, come over here before how could you be tired? You just woke up
I don't like the way you're you don't don't stand over there like that
see
Try it
try
Just try
Look you lazy lazy. You just woke up
No, no, no, no
Come here he has grown though. There we go. The creatures learned to cast fireball. He learned it
Yes
He knows fireball
Yeah
finally
Nearly not. Oh, all right. Well, let him go to sleep again
Okay back to bed. Okay sleep. Yep
a lot of learning
Uh, let's get food miracle food
Come here 80 something percent
Here it is pay attention
This is gonna be what you just get you flip me off
Is that what you did?
I'm I don't want to use this over here. Come over here this way
I'm not casting this into my own city
He needs his beauty rest every five seconds
All right. You ready cow?
The creature doesn't have much to do
Look
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, listen
Hey
Hello. Yeah
Nope. Okay. Come here
Okay, come here turn around
Fireball look
Look at it
He saw it. It's okay. It's okay
It's okay
I just want him to know how to do this so he can fucking shoot a fireball when we attack the village
What are you looking at?
the tree
You paying attention?
Uh, I don't think he's gonna learn this
Is that what you wanted?
What did you want that for?
That you were looking at it for a really long time
He probably fears fire for his life
Oh
I've traumatized him
Here. Do you want the tree?
Okay, here we go
He's curious
Scary look at him. He look at that curious face. Yeah
Okay
He's not even tired look at his stats he's not even tired
Okay when he wakes up
The gorilla would have learned meteor by this point
He's depressed because you beat him. I did not do that
Okay, look
Interesting stuff over here. Wait. No, no, no, no over here
Just look you just yeah
Yes, oh he's 88 what the fuck how do you get to 88 percent
He's so angry he can't learn anything he's stupid he's really stupid
You did okay though. Nice try
Come with me. Come with me. This is the last fucking time i'm gonna do this
We're gonna go destroy your foot this this come here
What do you mean food?
You got food enough
This is a big open field
You should have picked lemmonkey
Fireball
Stop look he's got it. He's got it. 98. He's at 98. He's at 98 98 98
He did it
Yes
You did it your creature's angry. Why are you angry? No, you did it
Now he knows fireball
You did it
You know fireball
You wait your creature's learned to be more angry distraught. Wait, he's gonna burn stuff
I tried to um, I don't want him to
Oh, no, he's look at his mean face
I gave him too much power. He's he's mad and mean and angry
Yes, good work, you know fire you know water you're ready for battle let's go he's dehydrated well
He's ready for battle here. If you dehydrated just sit fucking right here for a second
Okay
Here open your mouth
He's mastered two elements
Yeah, look at him. Look at him go
Now drink it
All right, you're doing a really good job
Good now you can rest relax. You know, he's mastered fire. He's mastered water. He's ready to destroy an entire village
We're going to put on the angry necklace and we're going to send him to the yellow village
I'm ready
By taking his villages
He's learning this too. Somehow. What are you learning?
This twelve thousand fucking food man
Play doom when he goes in
What's he doing?
All right. Are you guys ready? Fuck it. I'm going in
What what is it? What is it? He wants to be kind and generous. All right, we'll do it
Okay
What's he doing?
What is this?
Is
He's pointing he's like I am just pleased not enough dancing for my liking
Oh my god
That was ridiculous
Well, he got what he wanted. Your creature's hungry. He's thirsty. All right, let's go
Give me the mean one
Where's the mean leash?
Here it is. He's got he's now got the destruction leash on now
Someone gave birth and died at the same time. Yeah, that was fucking ridiculous. All right drink
Well, you're so goddamn thirsty like go for it. Yes
Drink the water
What the fuck are you doing?
Wait, you just picked it
That was incredible skill
All this water and nothing to drink
He won't there we go
He wants fresh water. No, he's fine
All right. He's good
All right. Where's this bat? Where's this guy? Let's go over here
How's he doing on food? Let me take a look
All right, he's ready to go and he's aggressive and he's angry
I'm crossing the plane here
It's time to fucking destroy
All we gotta do is just cross the way. Yep
Let's start our reign of of absolute terror right now. We'd better get the settlement
Let's go look at you his hearts and minds
Does your like waluigi wolf no fireball? I don't think so. I want this village now
Wait, there's a quest
What's got into him?
What the fuck we've been poisoned we can't work we can't pray and we can't worship you please help us
Poisoned we should stop this plague from spreading. Let's find the source of this sickness and heal the ill
All right, stay out of here cow
What is he talking to?
Don't go in there. Don't go in there
I found the source
Poisoned food
All right, stay there
Watch this
The village store is nearly out of food
The poisoned source is the village store. We can heal them now
Wait, was it the right guy?
It was right. What do you mean? No, no
That was a neutral village
Oh my god, there's so much food here that I poisoned
Kill the undecided ha
Oh, there's so much food in here
Blue whiz blue. I need a blue settlement
blue
All right, i'm gonna throw it over there. What's he doing?
Stay away
No one crosses leth is ground
What?
All right, i'm throwing the food over there you think I can make it
Where'd it go? This is his place
Look, he's floating around right there. There he is. This is his
That's him right there. Yeah, fuck it. Keep this poison
All right, whiz cow
Why don't you come all the way back?
All right, so that was the source
So now what the fuck do I do heal?
You got rid of the poison, but the people need to be healed loving creature miracle
All right. Do I have heal? I don't think I know heal
I don't know heal
Don't eat anybody don't eat anybody. I know you're curious. Don't eat anyone though
Um, how we do this?
Not that damp and sick
I don't think there's anything I can do for these people right now. I don't have heal
I mean I could learn this one
loving creature
What does that do?
As it were
Oh, what did I do? Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
What what just happened?
He's different
Wait, what he's different. He's like, I'm not this cow. All right, let's go
Wait, what what?
No, no, no, no, what happened?
You creatures no longer nice
Oh, it was just a temporary thing
It was bullshit. It wasn't real
The village stored is nearly all right. I don't know what to do about this. I really don't
I I don't have a healing spell. I don't know how to do it
Just got to go buy them. Sorry guys
Now he's evil again
Give food from the other village. Yeah, but they're still sick though
I don't have a heal spell, right? I don't think I do
Like this. No, there's no key. What is whoa? Whoa, wait, hold on
Wait
I do have a heal
Oh shit. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. The second town has the heal
All right worshipers need food. Fuck. All right here
Okay. All right. All right. All right
Where are they?
go
Give me that heal spell
Stop coming back here. You have a job to do
You want to mess around with me? I'm trying to pet him
All right, give me a heal
But well, I don't have access to it
All right. Don't eat anybody. I need to just stay just stay attached to this fucking rock
Don't go anywhere
Literally just stay on that rock. All right heal mirror miracle
That's charging. All right. I'm fucked. Who cares about this other town? This is just give me heals
miracle heal
All right, let's get it
Uh come with me
I need you to see this
Here we go. You're healing more now leader
Excellent
All right, who else is sick? The poison source is gone and the people you heal will survive
And those survivors can get a little worship done
Okay, now they'll be fine now
another all right another
This sounds horrible. All right. All right
Uh go stay attached to this
I'll be right back
Um, is there I I think there's gotta be a way I can go back and forth between these two easily, right?
miracle heal
Changes leash fuck. Okay. There we go
Come here
Where's the sickest people over here? Come here
Take a look
Nice you watered the tree come over here
That's not what we need you to do over here
Okay, let's drop this here
Have you saw that?
Can you try?
Try it
I'm gonna try poison source lovely
And the people you heal will survive
Miracle heal ours to redo the last miracle
Well, that's fucking useful
miracle heal
More who else needs it?
over here
Miracle heal people outside here
70 he almost knows it
Come over here miracle heal
79 you almost know how to do it
Try it
No wrong
wrong
Miracle heal it was close enough. I will do one more over here
Okay, is everybody healed yet?
Who am I missing? The poison source is gone and the people you heal will survive. You're gonna try it
Miracle heal over this way, maybe
97 he's almost got it. There's one guy by the town center. He just flipped me off right here
Does he know it?
What did you just what?
What did he just do?
He just what did he do?
He threw food
Stop doing that
miracle heal
What are you doing?
Wait, did he is he throwing food into the store?
I have no idea what he's up to
All right. Come on
This is another person to heal somewhere
I don't know over here
don't
I get what he's doing. He's actually pretty smart
He is going over to the fields
Pulling the food out and throwing it over there and going eat this this is food. He's understanding
You look ready and he's like hey take eat it. I don't see anybody else that needs a heal
He's just gonna keep doing this
This is ridiculous. I can't believe he's doing that
You should eat some of yourself
Wait, I see him. I see him. There's one guy left. He's right here. He's literally in this building. He learned it. Is that it?
I he's
I don't see anybody else to heal
The poison source is gone and the people you heal will survive
Give these people jobs
disciple farmer
All right breed disciple builder
disciple builder
Fine press s to find the sick ones
Hey, there's nobody sick
I don't see anybody sick
Oh, there we go
I think the last one died to you godliness. We're going to make it although we've suffered our faith has endured
Um lightning bolt a lifting item I feel lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt
Lightning oh get over here
Get over here get over here cow. Come here. Look what I got
Holy fuck you see that
Weird huh? How am I doing that? Oops cast spell cast spell cast spell on yourself cast spell on yourself
Consolidate your position by building more
I need water. I need water. I need water. I need water water water
I need water right now get water happy
Okay, he's alive
Holy shit
I couldn't cast anything over there because it was in the other guy's territory. I don't want this
I don't just keep him in there
Increase your power by impressing lithis villages
Okay, where the fuck was that village over here?
Everything's good. All right, give me water
This is my see like I could all right, that's what was I
Look
He's
When he's outside of my influence, I can't do anything
Okay, we're good I just wanted to learn lightning, okay
Uh, let him sleep for a little bit. He's learned enough. He's done enough
It's my territory. But see I can't like I can't cast a spell out here
Wait, what the fuck is going on then? Why couldn't I do it?
What is lightning? I can't see it from down here
I don't know what it is
Okay, how's he doing
Okay, I gotta put this down all right just come over here for a second. I can't I have to put this down
I know they do but I can't let go of this
All right, he's good come this way
Over here. I just want you to look
Sorry about that. I didn't mean to I couldn't save you. I usually when you get on this
People are dying at the worship site what?
All right. I need fucking food. All right, just get over here so I can do this
good
It's got a heart when they hit the dirt
Who who's who's dead who did I hit I didn't hit anybody
Where's there a fire?
Where's there a fire? I didn't did I hit somebody? I'm trying to just do it in like a random location
Come here. All right. He's he's good 32 percent. He's feeling curious. You're gonna try it
Oh almost 41 just keep learning
Yep
40. Oh fuck it. It's torched my own wood
Yeah, I know I did that. I'm an idiot. It's okay
Almost
Yes, do it weird it's really cool, I know
No, he's trying
All right, you're good you tried I I need to eat like I have to get food right now get over here
Ah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I need more food
How do I not have any food? How do I not have food?
It's ridiculous
All right here. I'm making food
Food
One more something's wrong with your minions. Oh, did they finally finish this miracle food
miracle food
It's necessary
The critters are under attack
That is the same person you're right
All right you it's time
Let's go
lightning
Looks like reach back on the menu boys
You can't see the rest of this
Okay, look 54 keep going keep looking keep trying watch out for that person don't kill them
Do it oh
Don't worry. It's fine. It's fine. I would pet you but I can't
Try it. I want you to be the most destructive spell caster ever
So
Fucking wrong leash again, you can do it
Yep. Yep. Shit. It's okay
See he's not in the woods. He can do it
Ah
You're so close
lightning
74 come on
Fuck he's almost got it. Okay
Every time I hit him with the lightning bolt. He learns how to do it
He only learns when it hits something
Is that real you know
He's like no I didn't want to do it
Oh, I had to
Job good job. Seriously. Good job. Good job. Good job. Nice job
You learned lightning bolts
Oh, he just okay now he's a destructor
Go get some water
He knows fireball lightning fucking strike
He knows all these insane spell. No, he knows heal. He knows
What was that look for?
That was an odd. Look
All right drink
Okay, just relax
You're doing fine. You're doing good
Go check out the creature cave
Yeah, well, that's a good idea
Ridiculous
That's a rare rumor
creatures mind
Okay
I'm slightly greedy. I'm tired
I'm compassionate. I'm frightened very rarely
I'm playful. I think my god is on the side of good
He's paid me some attention
What I think about creature god he is on the side of good
Okay, he's lying
Your creature has learned to cast fireball lightning bolt
healing miracle
And the rest of this who gives a shit about the rest of this water
general attributes
Four years old his name is god
That's not even real
Alignment decent and true
three percent strength
96 energy
zero percent fatness
31 dehydration cold
completely healthy
amount of poop in system one hundred percent
People killed four animals kill. He just killed four people right now
43 animals killed 88 poos
He's a hundred percent pooped
All right, we're gonna feed him
He was gonna make he's he can just eat as much as he wants
Well, there it is
100 your creature needs to poop
He's desperately looking for a bathroom
Name him. Okay, I gotta name him
uh
Hmm. Yeah, okay
You're you're good. How are you doing?
Your creature's angry
Well, uh, let's give you some food
Go take out that anger on this motherfucker up here
We're gonna go have goddamn battle
Something with a moo he needs to eat
You need to eat
This is this shit ain't poison, right?
Didn't have any uh
livestock here
Eat it
Why would you throw it? He's angry. He's angry
Kill him and grill him
Oh
Take that leash off. Take that leash off. Take the leash off. Take the leash up
He's like fuck you
You did this
All right, get out of the village out out out out out
Get the hell out of here
Here you go
Eat a shitload of this food
Go on eat this whole entire stock
eat
Yes, you can eat it
You can you can eat it eat it no eat it
You've eaten this before
Okay, eat another one it's good you just liked it
Good okay eat another one
You don't have to wait for me
All right, one more
Cannibal that's a pig
Wait, is that a cow or is it? Okay. Wait, that is a cow
That doesn't look like a cow
Okay, we're good
He's full. Yes. He's actually getting fat
All right. Come on. Let's keep going. What do you guys want doom ost?
All right. Fine. We'll put on doom ost for this
Let's go it's time to take over the fucking world music let's go your territory, huh?
Let's go
Yeah
What are you gonna do about it
What are you gonna do about it?
Oh
Oh shit
Get him go for it. He's like you motherfucker. You and me are gonna at noon
Get him
Get him help me save this land from lettuce. Oh, he's huge. He's huge
He's fucking huge
He's huge
No
Get in there
Wait, can I can I influence?
He's not keep him up. Keep the offense up
Good kick him out of the circle. Holy shit. He's casting a fucking fireball
Oh, no, i'm on fire too. I'm on fire
Do it again more fire
My god, he's
Heal heal
Heal yourself. Heal yourself. Heal yourself
Heal yourself
This ground is mine do not go near
I would have had it too. You must convert lethis villages ally
Yeah, well, let's go use your power by impressing lethis villages
You believe in me now?
What is the move for the electricity I don't understand it's like up over up over
You believe yet stay away, let's do another no one crosses lethis ground
My strength is being sapped by lethis what
Well, you haven't done shit this whole time
Wait, what if I hold on?
Look what I got
I got wood here. What do you think about that? Cool, huh? He's coming back. He's like i'm gonna make you proud dad
All right, how did he had spells to cast and he did it I don't know how he did him
All right, what do you train his strength?
Go get a rock
Pick up that rock
Yeah, pick that rock up and carry it around
Oh god
Do you have to you have to go?
Pick up the rock here carry this
No, no, no, I just crushed somebody I just fucking killed somebody pick this up
What are you what are you doing?
He was about to cast something
Pick up the rock
Pick this rock up. Are you you can't even pick that one up here?
Okay
All right, walk around with that rock. Oh, wow. That was pathetic do that again
Pick it up
He just is absolute disregard for the human life
I didn't raise him this way. He needs to carry this
All right, walk around with it. Will he walk around with this if I leash him?
All right, come with me
Don't throw it runner
This is even doing anything no stop just throwing it you just broke it
Oh
Stop stop stop you're killing everybody stop
Oh stop
He's look at his eyes
You don't do that
Control
He's killing children he's killing children
It's a leash it's a
Oh my god, my fucking stomach hurts why did he just go on a fucking killing spree like throwing rocks at people?
I just want him to be stronger
He just hates these fucking people. Look at him
Look, he hates this town
Look at that sass. Look at that anger
What is his problem?
Oh my god
It honestly the the rock at the end it hit like 10 people
That was like the most perfectly placed rock not wood
Where is he?
Where is he going now?
He gave him too much power
Go here eat something
Okay
I need to teach him defense or strength training, but that's all I was trying to do. You know that you all know that
He doesn't know any better
You literally force fed him a dead guy in the first half an hour. Yeah, but that's
He needs to chill come up here and relax
Get in there and go to bed
This still dancing and shit in here. Oh my god. My fucking whole body hurts now
Cancel that shield. I don't know how
miracle food
What are you doing there he goes you gave him the power to kill yes, how do I get rid of the shield
He's not going back over here to this part. Is he look at his face?
I don't know what his problem is
He's making friends
This has to be rebuilt. I need more wood and shit. This is a disaster. He's got to go take out the town
I know I'm working on it
Like how do I get rid of this shit? I need to get rid of this shield
Physical shield how do I get rid of it? I just made a fucking another one. I'm sure how do I get rid of them?
Oh, hold on. I
Okay, I can pick it up
Where's this one? There's nothing for me to pick up in here
I can't pick it up
Disaster what another god is about to take over your village
What are you talking about? Who?
where
Which village you must expand your realm
Okay, i'm going up
Uh, we need ah
Give me this food
Give wood too. I'm taking it all fuck you. I need it over here
I'm working on it
You're eating the wood. This thing needs to be rebuilt
Don't do anything stupid
Villages are looking towards other gods because of this
Well, here he comes again, I really could have beaten that big purple wolf thing
I'm certain of it
All right. There we go. Wood required build it up get everything back to normal
Where is he going?
All right. I need you to be stronger
I need to be stronger. I need you to be stronger
The creature is thirsty. I know but I need you to be strong
Del is picking. I'm your followers are giving up worshiping you. They better not
Wait eat the rock
You won't eat a rock really
Why did he just eat a rock?
Carry it go in there go in you need to drink
I gotta go back to the village. We're running out of wood. Yeah, no shit
miracle wood
Well, he did he did just destroy this place like he fucking torched the place that's the
Well, I didn't do that he did
miracle wood
Okay, is this how much wood does this need zero, okay good
It's because you put the hole i'm gonna sneeze
You ain't got so many believers
It's because they're he killed them all
He fucking killed them
I'm trying to put oh i'm trying to put you over here to build not to die
Why
We need to breed because he killed everybody he fucking torched the place
Disciple breeder
He actually torched the whole place he destroyed everything
You stay the fuck away from here. Do I regret not having the ape?
Not really
more breeding
Disciple breeder
Okay. Now I can build my town back up
In fact, i'm gonna drop the let's drop these two totems a little bit
Miracle heal heal everybody over here
That were hit by a fucking fireball
You know
I need to get rid of that. I don't know how to get rid of that
miracle wood
Okay, we got food
Uh, we need more
We need more breeding. We need more everything actually dear
Few of your people are believing in you. Well then i'm gonna fix that don't worry
Yeah, I gotta drop some of this
these totems a little bit
let's do like
15 on this one
and then let's do like
Let's do like 20 on this one
All right, everything's good
You know what to do. You know what to do. I know what you're doing
Your creature's thirsty. He doesn't he doesn't know he doesn't care about anybody
He's just going to the ocean. All right, I need to do water
miracle shower
Everyone good look at look what I can do cool, huh?
nice
He's just going to get a drink
I think he is
Creatures dehydrated. Well, there's water all around him
Like is it my fault that he won't go over here and drink water
Drink you can lead a god to water, but you can't make him drink
That's true. All right homes are being built right this builder is working on them
There is
uh
There's another home going up here
What a waste this is
That's that's really where the whole playthrough went diarrhea on itself
All right. We got food. We got this is all right. Let's put some people in here
disciple farmer
What are people doing?
Going to the village store for drop off going to the building site
Uh peters schnitzel or something. Whatever
Breeder breeder breed. We need more breeders
Going to no you're gonna breed. No, you're a kid. Oh my god. Damn it. I'm trying this to
Okay, you're
You breed
disciple breeder
You're you too
Uh, you too
You too
You disciple breeder you too. Wait, is he doing it for me?
Good work
What is he doing? The fuck was that?
Keep it up
Okay, not bad
Not bad
Getting back into it
Let's do
Uh, let's get some food miracle food. I'm gonna put it over here for the worshipers
Same thing on the other side
No, we'll get in a minute
All right. I have to figure out how to make him do his spells
In combat
Ally come here tap the cow when he does something good
I've been doing that
Your creature will rest more fuck
All right pick up a boulder
Come here
Can you carry this not yet?
Can you carry this one?
You can
Take it
Okay. Now come over here
Training let's go
Run don't throw it
training
Play rocky music
fine
Is it playing?
30 minute workout music motivation rocking rocky training medley
He's gonna i'm taking this town over but these guys don't believe anymore. Do they?
Oh, yeah, I have to make these people care about me again
Don't put it down. Don't put it down. Don't put it down
This is home depot music
Is this I feel like this is not even real
This is not hold on
That's not the one i'm thinking of
How about motivational workout music?
uh
Okay, this is arm workout music
No, this is I don't want this is I don't want to listen to this. Um
How about uh
gym motivation music
This is just regular music with like electric guitars on it. Um
This is like this is real songs
I can't work out to this stuff
Yeah, that's a better one
That's that's way better
Oh
All right, he's doing good
How can I tell how much strength he has?
clown workout song
Come on get over here
school
clown school
All right. Here we go. I'm getting this village over here
All right. I have stand before you a god. That's me your new god
Hooray
No, no, stay here
Uh, let's do do some stuff
What's this storm?
Uh, what do you have food?
Shedding on the rock. All right. All right. All right. What do we got? Let's do
Let's do um
Wood
All right, I get this off how much do I need they have a windmill what do I need
How much do until I can take over this 399 belief let this villages are ripe to be taken. What do you think i'm doing?
I don't have a windmill. I know
But don't do that though
I'm just trying to get them to believe
Okay, how much more I need like what?
233 okay
Uh, let's do a storm
Take a look at that
Don't stand in it you idiot
They need to believe
How about some food? I got that and i'll be stealing it from you, too
Help me friend. You must help me. What?
What do you mean help me you own this you own almost the whole
Is being attacked?
Wow. All right impress them
impress them
Be like cool
146. All right
Okay, cool
How much more belief do I need?
Wait, he's gonna do he's gonna do the water thing. He always does
Here he goes
Yeah
Everybody loves him
And look at how nice he's being
This is an ally's village
Is it though?
No, it's not
No, it's not it's neutral
He must be kind and generous good
Do something kind
Well, i'm gonna do with some what's that?
What does he have?
The game crashed
What why did it crash
What the fuck happened?
I want to do something kind
When did it save?
No
I'm so sad right now
We're about we're about to get really get rolling
It was pretty recently, right?
He wants to do something generous
Your temple is built excellent. What the fuck are you talking about?
What this is my land leave?
Save
Load the auto save this this is the auto save
What happened?
It can't be hold on
No, what the fuck was that?
What? Oh, no, no, no
No, it's did it just save it right there?
Oh, did I just fuck it? Is it over?
Because I I exited the game and it saved it after I exited the game
No, it it it loads up the auto save every time
That I I exited the game once and came back
Oh, no, that's so horrible. Hold on
Let me see if there's like more than one
Because no, I mean you remember like an hour or two ago
When I open I reopened the game and it put us back in the right spot with an auto save
so
Let me see
Let me just see if I go back in what happens
I want your saves folder. I don't know the hell that is
Let's see
black and white
profiles
saved games
All right. I have what the hell?
8 56 pm
and then
No, this is all wrong
8 56 pm was literally two minutes ago
I don't think this is correct though
Let me go in in the temple
Hey, the 8 56 pm is the one that I just did when I exited
No
I'm gonna back up the folder
This is fucking weird though because all right. So the last apparently saved game I have
Is from 6 pm
That's why it went back that far why
There's been at least four or five different times where it's auto saved
That's unfortunate. Hold on. Let me just go in and see if I can pick something else
Oh, I was just getting into it, too
Let me see what happens. Okay, let's go in the temple
Yeah, because look at this. This this is completely wrong
This is literally the beginning of the level
Not even close like I we've
I've auto saved like 10. I've I've this is wrong
Like completely wrong unless the whole thing corrupted and broke
Which I mean, that's pretty possible. It's a fucking like almost 20 year old game
Um game options room. What do I try and look at it?
save game room
This is the room where you save and load the game the problem with this is though save the game now boys
Don't save the game click on a picture to zoom into it. I was told by the yellow that this room doesn't work empty frame
Then type in a save game name
I was told this crashes the game. What's up here? Hold on
8 42. Wait a minute boys and girls. We're fucking good to go. That's 8 42 pm on wednesday, january
Hold on. What's the other one?
8 54 pm on january 8th
That has to be it
8 30. Yeah, it has to be that one. It's it's 8 54
That's the one you want to load this game. Yeah
Here it is
You're crazy. Yes. Oh, i'm so happy. Thank god
Your creature wants to be kind and generous
Hooray, but i'm gonna take this time
It's been about seven hours
Don't please
All right, wait, wait, they love me lately. They love me. They are wait. Here comes like the five nights at freddy's character
Hold away. Wait, wait, wait
This creature's tired. All right, come here. Come here. Come here. We're not ready for this fight. Come here
Miracle what?
All right, everybody loves me get out he's coming
Wait, hold on
Get out of here
Oh shit. Wait, wait, wait turn around turn around turn turn turn turn run get him get him get him get him
All right fireball. Did I do it? Fireball sucks
Make them suffer
I don't know how to I don't know how to do zap. I don't know what the move is because I cut off all my fucking screen
What is it? It's a u that ain't a u
What's going on?
Oh fuck heal heal heal
Get out get out get out get out get out
heal
He just struck himself on fire
Water stupid
Die die die die you must help me die. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Fight all right shock him you do it
Stay away
Across his left his ground
All right, get him
Knock him out. Um
What are you doing? Get in there
Look, he's like freaking out. All right going for the kill. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. Let's go
Let's go
You want to go?
Fight him
No shit
Fight him. What is that?
What is he doing? What is he doing?
Fight him
What is he doing?
Pick up a rock or something pick up a rock
The creature has refused your creatures offer a friendship
What is going on?
Don't throw it. Don't
He tried to be his friend
I'm not using the friendship leash. I have the aggressive one on
Oh my god
lightning
Look at all the burn marks all over this guy
Where is he?
Oh
What do you mean? That's not the enemy
That's blue
I have to go to blue blue attacks me. That's blue. That blue is the enemy
He's coming back over here
That is the enemy. I know it is you can't baby increase your power by impressing lithis villages
All right
What are you talking about all right heal
Look, i'm good. I'm you like me, right? You like me a lot
Who's the cow? He's coming back. All right, this is where i've got to fucking kill that thing. I have to kill that motherfucker
D for heal that's a heart
I don't understand what the fuck
I don't know why he's walking all the way over here on his own
Who draws a heart like that? What are you talking about?
heart
Uh, what you understand from trying?
To
All right, he's good he needs to eat
Should we do some more strike training?
Take this. Oh dear
Fewer of your people are believing in you
Whatever. I got this
Now don't throw it walk. Oh you idiot. Actually he threw that pretty far. He must have better strike
All right, let's see. I need I need to he needs to eat
Go eat
Take off the mean lash
Leash whatever the fucking damn thing is hang out in here for now
Uh, you need to eat eat something have some grain
Eat it good. Okay, take a nap
And then we're gonna go we're gonna go take over that fucking village. We're gonna go kill that guy
We're gonna kill that guy
You have food
But I will give you more
Good all right, he's just going did you sleep yet?
aggressive
Let's go
What is this?
Thank goodness. It's you you're the only one who can help me my temple here keeps getting flooded during heavy rain
The building consists of separate rings which you place over these columns
Please I beg you move the sections up the beach to rebuild it on the furthest column where it'll be safe
But the temple has to be moved correctly the architect left an explanation on this signpost. All right, I don't care
That's that that's not what I care about right now. I care about killing this guy
I want to do moves
In the middle of a fight and I did it once
I wonder if he does it on his own or if I have to command him to do those moves
All right, let's go
What we got over here? We got some shit over here create melodies on these stones to awaken the spirits of the ancients
Few people know the melodies but who knows we may be able to do it
Meet them boys free storm
There it goes free storm and free heal
Gonna use it right now
And then also free lightning
Where's that fucking cat?
What's he doing?
Nice. I mean we both
We're both not really doing much
All right, get in here take it over
Did I do it with this my allies have failed me my nemesis have arrived to take control
Hey destiny, I will be the only god. What is this?
What about the turtle?
Oh, no
Can we save this?
You have defied me for the last time
nemesis no
Because uh, I know your creature hides a part of the creed inside him
I do not need it. I already have the power that three combined queens bring
You and I will use it to destroy you
What about all these people?
No
We didn't get to meet this turtle
But I still feel sad
Retrieve the creed from gaza's dead creature. You must not fall into our enemies hand. I have to get it
As always I will do as you command. I'll send my creature for it now. Oh shit. I gotta get it, too
All right, go get it
Okay, uh
Where's the creature?
I'm in game. I am not in game
What is this creature across the whole game?
Did I fuck it up when I started? He's got an element of the creed. Oh, I must have screwed it up
He was really far away from when I was fighting him
He had to run from across the whole map. He's doing the terrible walk
I can't believe it cuz you're wiped out like a bug
I understand what the old guide meant now the power of three creeds must be combined
But nemesis said he has three creeds. Yes, but he's after the others to stop us getting them
We've got to get them then
Absolutely
We need more wood
What the hell do you want me to do about this?
What am I? What do you want me to do now? You creatures? What am I? What the fuck am I doing?
Do I have to go through like the portal?
What is all this shit?
Head to yellow
All right. I'm gonna go to yellow
Take over the land
I mean am I
Just keep taking blue
Where is my creature?
Pick that up
No
Good throw though
An enemy is trying to influence your village. Whack him
um
What the fuck are you talking about?
All right, I need heal. Do I not have heal? Oh, I lost heal
Yeah, look
Look at me believe in me
cool
Is anybody even still alive here?
You have a lot of food and i'm taking almost all of it
Go through the portal
Where the portal even open?
Look at how much food is in here
What are you doing with that rock?
Why are you carrying a rock? It's just killing animals
Okay
He's going cow bowling
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Stop stop stop
Thank you
What what?
What
Where's my original town over here? Everybody has food and shit this
Where's my temple?
Okay, let's go
Apparently we need wood
I'll take it from
I don't even fucking know. There's so many places right now. I don't know what my goal is
Just to walk in the portal
I have to get the rest of the towns
Do I have to capture blue? Oh, okay
All right. Um
Where do they need to bring this to over here?
Here's your wood
look
Like me now
Here start working on stuff
disciple builder
Disciple builder
Our followers are annoyed with you
Oh are they?
Okay, so this is good
Now, where's this other blue village?
up there, okay
Let's go take this one over
food
Oh
Oh, I see
It's these people here
Oh
Wow
I can't believe it
interesting
Get angry get angry and let's torch this place
Do you think get in there be aggressive be mean be angry get in there
Yeah
Yeah, he is angry
Be angry
What are you holding?
Is that a dead body?
What is that?
Is he holding a dead body?
Fire put yourself up put yourself up put yourself up
Okay, now heal yourself
Did it just bounce
Do it
nice job
Okay at this time I don't you just do it because like I fucking can't apparently like I don't understand the trajectory
Go in here and torch this place
Are they kicking this are they beating up this bird?
Eat eat the bird eat the bird eat that bird
Eat it. All right, take this place up
He's realized he likes the taste of birds
burn
There it is
All right, do you think?
He's pointing and laughing. Do you want to?
Put yourself out
He's oh you just ate two fucking birds
What are you sum up?
Heal
Fuck fuck watch out. Watch out. He's doing it again. He's doing it again. Watch out. Watch out
All right, heal do a healing spell
Eat just eat a shitload of this here eat eat this. I don't know. Where are you going eat this?
What was that
What was that?
Did he heal what was that?
Okay, eat eat something you have 95 percent hunger eat don't leave how could you be this hungry
He needs to eat
Is there any livestock?
eat it
Eat him heal heal him. I don't I don't have heal anymore
I don't have heal anymore. See it's like I don't have it. I think I lost it
Got it got it get it again do it again
Burn it down
Stop pointing at shit and burn something down
There you go. Good job
Kill him and grill him. Keep going good
Lightning yes
You're doing a fantastic job. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. God damn it
You got nothing keep torching it kill everybody
Just get it. You don't go up here
More destruction. You know what to do do something burn everything kill everything
Okay, all right did I win take it out
Yeah
Where did that go keep going fireball so hard to use I need him to do it
All right, unleash
Unleash him. Let him do whatever he wants
I need 322 belief. Oh my god release release him again. He's gonna he's gonna get some fucking killed. He stands still
Kill you're attached
Do something
Do anything
We sorted them real we didn't actually because they're still they're still here
There we go
More more do it again
Bingo right into the right into the heart. Nice job
torch it
Again, pet him to keep have him keep doing it
He's hungry
No one crosses left his ground
Fuck I didn't mean to do that. I'm trying to pet him
You don't be so destructive. Oh my fucking god i'm trying to pet him and it just hits him eat
Eat again. All right kill
Dude this is taking a fucking long time like not stray over my territory
Well, how many times do I have to burn this thing down?
How much more belief do I need?
Okay
All right. He's he's full health. You don't fuck it. Go up here
Go up to like the temple
Burn this fucking thing to the ground take it out get up there. It's out outside my influence, but it
It's not
Uh, my red circle is right here. I am lefis
All right heal
Destroy it do it. I don't understand what i'm supposed to do here
He's like not even alive. I'm supposed to destroy the temple. Well
How much mana do you have you don't even have any shit left you've
All right, this dude doesn't even have anything left
Where is he getting the ability to do that?
I swear to god this guy has no towns
Yet he can cast a lightning bolt every five seconds. We're getting toasted here boss
His other village is unharmed
This motherfucker doesn't even have another village
This ain't his village
This is mine
One of your villages has very high desires this isn't good news leader
This is my land
Oh my god, i'm never gonna take it
Yes, i'm gonna okay i'll give you wood i'll give you wood fine sure here
How much more until you just you cut the shit out
359 fucking believe
So I have to dump like 70 000 wood over there or burn it to the ground
Light a rock on fire time for cheats
I have all these followers. Just give me a
Just make them love you give them food
Yeah, that just gave me 11 belief
For almost 7 000 wood
Here I am let this is 10 000 wood territory
I almost got it. I almost got it. I almost got it do that one more time
Send peeps and missionaries over there
I I didn't I didn't even like do that tutorial
I don't even know how to do that
That was that even an available tutorial to do
That's it
Did I win you are truly a powerful god, but you failed to defeat me
Let's see how powerful you are without your creature
Look, he's heading for the vortex. He's mesmerized what the creature get him on a leash quickly
The leash isn't working
No, he's gone through and so is lathis lathis has taken our creature. What are we going to do?
It's to get him back. Let's go through. Yes scripted. It's scripted. Let's think about this. It could be a trap
No, there ain't time to think the vortex is closing but we don't know what's on the other side
Our creature is on the other side. That's all we need to know. Let's go
Is it actually closing get it go go
Wasn't a trap, but we better find our creature here. He's going to be around here somewhere
What was that?
It sounded like a creature
What look he's trapped. No, they got him trapped agony
This creature is torturing him. Why is he gonna play for this?
It looks like those statues are holding him in place
Oh
Only the prayers of many villages could be that strong. Oh, no
Oh boy
well
Uh-huh
It's our village store
That's it right there
That was fucking so fun though
I love that little cow. All right, how do I um
Do I have any abilities?
I think we need to get this village built. Yeah, but I don't have yeah
We gotta be strong for when we get our creature back. This place will give us a foundation to fight from
I I don't do I have any actual villagers though?
you guys
Are you?
Guess you are. Okay
Come over here and build this
disciple builder
Oh, they're building up a temple right now. I see
All right. Yeah, that's it. That's it. I'm gonna call it for tonight
We may depend tomorrow. We may come back tomorrow. It's been seven and a half hours
Uh don't want I didn't want to stream for more than seven eight nine. I don't want to stream for like 10 hours
So we we may do this tomorrow. If not tomorrow, then i'm gonna probably do uh katana zero tomorrow
But we'll see
I might play this tomorrow
He lied about the 10 hour stream kind of
But this is like really I love this game
Some of this shit was so stupid
Oh
What what a great game?
All right, it's it's saved
Uh, yeah, it's just it'll save right here
Keep playing it. Yeah, i'll get better at managing stuff, too
We'll we'll do it again tomorrow. We'll do it again tomorrow. And if it gets a little stale
Uh after like a couple hours, we'll uh, we'll move on to something else
But uh, let's do the bits and subs and everything
Thanks for joining me as always
We'll see you tomorrow
same time
Uh around one to two pm pacific
We'll see you tomorrow
first stream welcome
Do the other night's bits
Yeah, i'll pull those up. I'm gonna do them very very quickly though
just because
We have uh looks like a lot to go through tonight, too
So I don't want to have everybody sitting here potentially for the next two or three hours
Because then it will be a 10 hour stream
It will be a 10 hour stream, but we'll see you tomorrow. Let's go back a few days ago
uh, this is when
I got cut off
It was this one here doctor officer fireman. Here we are
All right, we'll go through these
I'm gonna do them quickly and we'll move on to today's pizza tier list. I don't think I can do that whenever
We had 50 dollars a few days ago file is remember this is all from four days ago
So some of these things people might be saying might be completely inaccurate
for today
But uh, they say germa is the police. I was playing the police fire and emt game
So they say germa is the police munker s thank you phylactery for the
Almost it seems like every single stream you give more than
50 to 100 dollars in bits. It's crazy or subs
Thank you
300 bits from the p cent
I've been watching you over the years since 2015
But i've really gotten into watching your stuff in 2019
I watch your vods to sleep often because I got insomnia
I've made friends via your discord and I visit it daily
Love you in the majority empathetic community. You have genuinely made my life better
Thank you
I really appreciate that
Thanks for sticking around
Thanks for watching t yick. Thanks for the 500 bits
Crow rad thanks to the 500 bits. This game is kind of quiet without music. Could you play happy rock?
I don't know. That is phylactery gave another fucking
5,000 bits again, like I told you before he does it every stream
It's crazy
We were trying to call ambulances seeing how many we can call it once
Now they say I need you to find out how many ambulances we can call it once. I think it was like four
I got out of that game though
Spliceable spleen. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey germa. I just wanted you to let you know
Uh how much your streams have meant to me over the past year. You're an amazing entertainer
Hope you feel loved and appreciated on the new year stream for everything you do on stream
I do. I very much do
Absolutely
Thank you
Trust me when I say I feel very very much
Super loved the channel crossed 10,000 subs on New Year's Eve. So it's like
What else can I even say? Like it's been a fucking wild ride
They all say I want you to let you know that I was indeed the nancy drew one guy
It started as a simple suggestion, but it blew out of proportion. I'm sorry
Hey, don't apologize. Don't don't ever apologize for fucking
Don't ever apologize for being the smartest person in the room. You know what i'm saying?
Thank you never electra for the thousand bits. Thanks for helping with my depression my dude
If you get something from this stream
I hope it makes you feel better. Thank you
Thank you never electra phylactery lich and velemi back to back 5 000 bits 50 dollar bit donations
Phylactery says get boots and velemi says germa if i'm ever dying. I hope to god you're not the emt that responds to me
Yeah, I think I actually read that one and never electra again. Thanks for the 28 dollars 2800 bits
Your bullshit helps i'm going through a rough time
Much loved you
The join the discord community if you haven't there's a shitload of people there that are just hanging out having a good time
And if you are going through a really really really rough time
I really implore you to seek out
somebody that can help you because it's one thing to be able to
Forget about it for a little while and hang out on a stream and just chill and fuck around with some friends and buddies and stuff
But it's another thing to try to make sure that you stay healthy and to actually you know, help yourself and treat yourself
Whether that's with somebody that's a professional or
Through a medical means, right?
Just make sure you're going through all the avenues you need to
I wish you the best of luck. Thank you
for the
2800 bits
Thanks a lot noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for the 250
Remember that dream is going to haunt me forever, but at least the wound from that splinter that sent me to the er is almost healed
Hope you had a great past couple days. Hope you had a great couple days, too
and
Eat eat eat more like fucking vitamin d or something so you don't have dreams of me having sex on stream
speaking of dreams
Hikiki hikiki kora most sunday gave 300 bits germ. I'm back with another dream story right after that
Uh, you were holding some big meetup concert event at his stadium and the tickets sold out in five minutes
So I got the stadium and had to fix my makeup. So I went to this huge
Unisex bathroom and saw some of the people from the discord sub chat were there and for some reason we were like
Let's have a pre-event party in here
So we had a rave in the restroom and I sent out a snapchat message to everyone
What the fuck is going on?
of rave in the bathroom
well, uh
bathrooms stink
I can't be in a public bathroom for more than two or three minutes tops
It just smells like pee. It smells like wet piss in every public bathroom
I've ever been a guy, you know what I mean? You know, you guys know what i'm talking about
It's it's like a wet humid pee smell
I hate it. Hey freudian weapon. Thanks for the six dolls and 50 cents
Happy saturday. Happy saturday. Well, it's not saturday anymore, but happy saturday when it was saturday
Swiggity swanky. Thanks for the 250 possible one guy moment here. Okay
This game nostalgically reminds me of the of a sim copter
A sim city flight simulator where you do similar tasks like in this game, but flying in a chopper
I still have to play like sim city for real
Oh, what's the easy one what's the one that was easy
cities skylines
That's like the easier more that's the the better one the one that's like more streamlined and easier to like understand is city skylines
Yeah, maybe hamster the pie. Thanks for the 250. Hi, i'm from ireland, but I spent the last summer working in boston
I asked on one stream once if there was anywhere that I should see and you said jillions
Had a great time there with friends after we saw there was a match starting
In fenway and tickets were cheap, so we got to know a confusing new sport
baseball
Baseball is like america's pastime been following baseball ever since back home now and we're setting up the first college baseball club in ireland
Thank you for setting off a chain of happy coincidences ps any baseball stories. I used to play baseball and softball
I haven't in many years, but the last time I played I played softball with a bunch of friends
We were in softball league in boston
And it was probably 23
24 was the last time I played
It's been a while. But yeah, it's a lot of fun
It is a lot of fun
but yeah, that's uh
The first baseball club in your college in ireland. Well, maybe it'll take off. It's a great sport. It's a lot of fun
We have frozen thor
Gave a thousand bits ten dollars from frozen thor
Jeremy i've been watching your content since 2012 and it's my favorite stuff to watch
I try to watch as much of your streams as possible, but it'd be difficult because of the time differences between new zealand and the u.s
You're my inspiration role model and I aspire to be as awesome and funny as you one day
Cheers for all that you've done for many more years to come. Well, you hope to be as funny as you will be
You know what i'm saying? Gotta give yourself some credit. Jeremy add funny
Hope to be as awesome and as funny as you one day
Well, I hope you're as awesome and as funny as you are. I hope somebody says that about you
I hope somebody comes to your stream or your channel or whatever your whatever you whatever you and they say, you know
You know frozen thor. I hope to be as funny as you one day and you go
People laugh is that people laughing me what you smack the table?
Uh, no, that's uh, but seriously, that's an insanely nice thing to say about anybody
if I am
your inspiration and role model I
I'm honored. I'm I I don't even know what to say. Like people say that sometimes
I'm just glad you're having fun
Shit and fart laughing, right?
Lesbian bigfoot. Thanks for the 30 dollars
3000 bits
Thanks for the hilarious content your streams helped me get through a really tough time last year and helped me to find the humor in things again
Here's to another great year
Thank you. Thanks for the huge money drop. I'm sorry to hear about you having not a great time last year
But let's hope 2020 improves and is much better than 2019
You know i'm saying
And then you'll depress thanks for the 400 bits derma
When are you going to finally take the moral high ground for once and endorse anthony bantony for president?
Uh your fence sitting and refusing to condemn his opponent dean dingus
Well, I might add strangled three people shows a clear lack of integrity. I don't I I my political endorsement was fucking benjamin franklin
There you go
There there you go anthony bantony or anthony bantony bantony bantony or dean dingus benjamin franklin
Motherfucker wasn't even a president and he got on the hundred. Okay
Whoa son of jenova. Thanks for the 250. Hi germa. Please consider cutting the last empty frames of germawalk. So it's a constant gif
Uh, I actually I did not make germawalk. It is a community emote
From better twitch.tv. I did not make it
And another germa pops up as soon as the first germawalks away from the screen
Um, I don't know. I didn't make it. I just enabled it
That is a community better twitch tv emote
I would direct that feedback towards the person that made that emote
How do I see it? You have to have better twitch tv
You made it on an alt account
Lizard amiibo. Thanks for the 1500 bits lizard
I could make this really long, but I just want to say thank you
You've had such a positive impact on my life this past year by inspiring me to be kinder and to pursue what I care about
Thanks for building such an incredible community and helping to convince me that things are going to work out in ways. I don't expect
That's true. That's the thing about life is
some things will happen
That you aren't prepared for
Some things will happen that you are prepared for some things will happen that you want to have happen
Some things will happen that you don't want to have happen
And some things will happen that you want to have happen that you didn't even know you wanted in the first place
so
Is it's a weird thing. That's five head. I mean, it's not it's not it wasn't a riddle
Break it down break down what I said
Pretty much what i'm saying is life is unpredictable
And even if you think you want to do something or you want x
Y might show up
And you go. Oh, wow. That's fucking awesome. That's exactly what I wanted happens all the time to people that sounds like a riddle
That's not how what?
Life is unpredictable. What's this riddle? The streamer is saying
Hmm
What is he?
Anyways, thank you lizard amiibo. Thanks for the 1500 fucking bits. Ooh, I must make stream what say what?
Sticks renegade. Thanks for the 250. I remember before that you were talking about your car months ago
Tell me how much do you know about your vehicle maintenance? I'm curious. None
If something bad happened to my car, I would not be able to fix it. I would have to call somebody
The only thing I know how to do
Is tell people that I know how to change a tire when I don't
And i'll tell me you guys can guys can sneer. Yeah
How many of you do that too?
Hey, dude, you know how to change a tire, right? Of course I do. What what are you an idiot?
Oh, okay. Yeah, I know. Yeah, I also don't fucking know how to change a tire and I i'm asking you but
Nobody knows how to change tire
The only people that know how to change a tire are car mechanics
And your dad if he's at least 50 years old nobody else does
It's so easy. No, it's not. It's very hard. It's impossible
It's too scary get a jack jacket change tire. No, it's too scary. That's terrifying. That's too scary
What if what if the car falls on my hands and it flattens like two pancakes? I'm not doing that
I need like a professional
That's a level one skill. No a level one skill is turning the shower on like that's that's a level one skill
No, I don't know shit about car maintenance I know about tire pressure
and
When the engine light turns on to take it somewhere
I also know how to put windshield washer fluid in a car and it's I mean that's not hard
Why don't I do my own oil? I don't know how to do an oil. Why I don't do my own oil changes
Why are we talking like this is some basic knowledge everyone changes their own oil
Guys, there are like burger king type shops
Every two miles to change oil
It's one of the biggest businesses in the country
What is an oil change is like 16 dollars
It's not like a thousand dollars to have somebody change your oil. It takes 16 minutes
Uh, all right this this I don't know. I I don't know. I don't know if i'm getting like trolled here, but I don't know anyone
Out of the dozens of people that I've ever come across in my life
None of them change their own oil. None. Not one person does not one
I'm talking to my family. I'm talking friends literally none of them
rich
rich guy
What i'm freaking out right now. How much is an oil change? It's like fucking 20 dollars
It's 25 bucks and 50 dollars being the most expensive like in the world. It's 20 dollars
You spent more money on hearthstone cards two or three years ago. Give me a break
I think I can go get an oil change
for 20 bucks if
I didn't spend a cent on hearthstone cards. Somebody did oil change. He's not changing his own oil
Yeah, i'm not lying on my I don't
I i'm i'm all right. I'm i'm moving on from biscuit. I just I don't understand how
I don't change my own oil
Is like the equivalent of me buying 50 packs of cigarettes every day
Same energy. That's what i'm saying. That's what i'm see you get it. You get it
You get it that guy gets it that guy gets it jackie. You get it jackie gets it
Do I drink the oil? No, i'm saying same energy man
All right, let's keep going. I don't change my own fucking oil
nobody does
I swear twitch chat is like they is
It does everything
Dude, I will call every single contact in my phone and say hey, when's the last time you changed your own oil?
Uh, I don't
Okay, hang up call the next person. Hey, when was the last time you changed your own oil?
I take it. I take it at jiffy lube. Oh, okay
Okay, i'm changing my oil right now
Yeah, I call somebody. Oh, hey, when's the last time you changed your own oil?
I'm doing it right now. Why do you not know how to do that? No, I don't
Ha serves you right you fucking dick
Sorry, this is my second pack of cigarettes today. How many of you smoked same energy? I like I agree same energy
I'm so glad this is confusing a lot a ton of people sick. All right, let's keep going. He's insecure about this
What percent of americans change their own oil? It's less than 20 percent
It's 18 percent of all the us car-owning population change their own fucking oil
The strong ones we didn't talk about strong or weak. We talked about how many people actually do the thing you think that everybody does
No, i'm getting i'm getting
I'm getting
I'm getting like gas lit. All right. I'm feeding into it. I gotta stop
You are the 82 percent. Yeah, okay
Oh, no, they they're doing it to me they're trying. All right, let's go. We gotta move. We gotta move
I know what I know what they're doing. I'm looking in the mirror right now. I know that that's what they're doing
You don't let them get in there. Hey mesa
Mesa rater
mmg
I had my 20th birthday the other day and I figured I'd ask if you had any tips on being old since you'd be the expert
Learn how to change your own oil. It'll save you
20 every uh, like fucking five months
There you go
Succomius, thanks for the thousand bits order pizza on stream right now. No, no pizza. I need to eat the healthy
Tingey, thanks for the 250
Hello jeremy, uh burkey gaming here to remind you to stay hydrated with some refreshing burkey filtered water
The purest and best tasting way to hydrate. Thanks tingey sad vega. Thanks for the 250
You can choose any fictional hero or villain and you resort to dinky brained comics
When we talked about who's the best superhero?
Any fictional hero or villain and you did dinky brain comics
What what?
What are the heroes and villains are that besides superheroes?
any fictional hero harry potter
Mario
Is mario a superhero?
I mean, I kind of I guess
What does that make luigi then?
Does luigi have any superpowers?
He's a loser
A sidekick. I mean luigi can jump high too though. Can he?
Never, okay
Um, if mario got into a fight with spider-man spider-man would beat the ever-living shit out of mario
Like if iron man and super mario got in a fight
Mario's dead in less than five seconds
Like dead fucking instantly
Oh, so like luigi can take on thanos apparently
the guy that walks into a ghost mansion
and goes
Ah
And is scared of little kids ghosts and as a vacuum cleaner can beat up spider-man
Am I actually hearing this?
He's so mad
Like you aren't afraid of ghosts
um, but
If you're a superhero
You don't he's not a superhero. He's like a fun. Cool
interesting guy that jumps high
and
Spider-man would beat the shit out of him
Spider-man would just have to like and over his mouth and he'd be like
And then spider-man would just do a roundhouse kick to his head his head would explode
That's what happens. This is what would happen
He's like fucking four feet tall
They have too many lives
This is a playground argument
Luigi would use his
spider-man is
This is yeah, i'm thinking about yeah, it's a playground argument. Fuck it. We're out here
a sad vega thanks for the
250 again
They say also happy new year's I didn't get a chance to say it at new year's because I didn't want to keep you longer
And you were gonna be late. Just know that the reason we donate so much is because we know you will do so much amazing things
That we don't see anywhere else
I've actually had a couple of meetings over the last week
There's some
crazy shit
There's some fucked up shit that's gonna be happening that will rival the carnival
That's happening this year
And when I it it might even be bigger than the carnival in regards to scope
It's gonna be fucking wild. I cannot wait until I get to really start to work on it
It is it is not not carnival related
But it's in that same scope
And it's not even off the ground yet, but I know it will be
It's gonna be a lot of fun
But yeah, happy new year to you as well. Thank you
Uh, yeah jack up. Thanks for the thousand bits germa say i'm the joker baby
I just did
I don't know why you want me to do that. But thank you though. Thank you bob boy for the 1500 bits
Please play through half-life series in preparation for half-life alex
for
Half-life one play on easy no joke the game could be too hard
I've played half-life
Before and the other difficulties. I think i'll be all right. I beat dusk on the hardest differ. I'll be all right
Thank you bob boy though for the 1500
Also, we're gonna do the end of a few days ago and then we can move on to today
25 dr. Pepper. Thanks for the 250 sure coke gaming is cool. But what about dr. Pepper gaming? You'll be our next sponsor
Also, are you planning on playing resident evil 3?
When the new one comes out? Yeah
Absolutely
I don't think dr. Pepper has anything to do with games or sponsors or anything. They're kind of they just kind of do their own thing
They just they do their own thing. They don't really
I don't think they're involved anywhere
You know what i'm saying?
But anyways, thank you to celestial ogia or logia for the 500 bits
I want to say thank you jeremy
I had the fortune to catch an upload of your new year's eve stream the other day
And while you've made me laugh my face off plenty of times in recent years. It was really your offense authenticity that charmed me
Well, you've been a joy to me in this chapter of my life. I'm even happier that you've been a joy to so many others
Thanks for being so mindful of other people's words
I never had a brother but i'm happy to think of you as mine take care of yourself and goodbye
It was really sweet. It's the first time i've ever been called somebody's brother and not
Their grandfather
Or their weird like scary uncle. So thanks for that
Thanks
Really appreciate it
Hey gnarly. Thanks for the 250. Sorry about talking about katana zero for like the 20th time
But I saw it on the pole in the pre-stream chat. I hope you end up playing it. It's good
That's the plan this week. I'm probably gonna play it before uh next week
Apple shift. Thanks for 250. Hey, do you have a set date for the next community content night? No, I don't
But let's take a look at the calendar might as well do it now
so
two three
Ladies and gentlemen, the next community content night is going to be
on saturday the 18th
There you go
Figured because I did say I want to do it the first and this first and second week
Somewhere into mid january. So that makes sense on the 18th. We'll do the uh, the next uh string of community content stuff
and then hopefully soon
uh, I can get
my shit taken care of so I can not be a
Broken body piece of shit and actually be able to get in front of the green screen and move around a lot
uh my old
body
Actually, I went to the memory. I told you I went to the doctor that was a specialist
and
we're probably gonna have to do
a
nerve blocking injection
Is what I was told
Because he he was under the assumption. He's like, I think you do have costochondritis
And there's not really much anybody can do for it
besides
doing steroid injections
apparently
Those of you that have no idea what's going on what i'm talking about. Um, I have a hiatal hernia
but every doctor I talked to said that they don't think that's
Really the reason why i'm in like pain all the time
They think it's because I have costochondritis, which is inflammation in your rib cage
In the joints that connect your chest and your back, you know, like where your ribs connect to your spine
And where your ribs actually your breastbone connects to your rib cage
Apparently there's inflammation in there and there's not much that can really be done
so, um
If that is the complete and total diagnosis from two or three different doctors
That you do injections you do steroid injections and sometimes you do like a nerve blocking steroid injection and it goes away forever
We'll see. How does it happen? Nobody knows
uh hereditary
Is just kind of just one of those things. It's just inflammation. I also have
You guys know, I mean apparently it's an autoimmune bullshit, right?
Because I have and i've been diagnosed with in the past
colitis and
the
inflammatory bowel disease shit and that's also autoimmune so
it's
Essentially, he said you probably have costochondritis because it's autoimmune and you already have autoimmune problems in the first place. So
There you go
for those of you that don't know what's what i'm talking about and what it means is
I don't my range of motion is
Limited tilting hurts bending over hurts
Leading backwards hurts
Um, and when I fell down in the chair on new year's eve
It was okay. Uh, the next day, uh, my chest was like in a ton of pain
Like I actually was like
Like the next fucking day
The ultimate fall joke
That wasn't a joke
But we'll move on we don't have to talk about it. Uh, i'm fine. I'm gonna be good to go
And I just have to do one more test and then maybe we'll be
Sticking a needle in my rib cage
Sounds weird. Okay, but anyways, we'll go
Locchio locchio. Thanks for the five dollars total if you stop playing this game right now. I'll give you the rest of my bits
Thanks for honoring my bits. Here's the rest of them. I did do that. You're right and that catches us up to now
Which we can go back
Let's go go go right here actually, it's not very much
We'll get through this pretty quickly
We had what did we have? What did we have?
today
I was just turned on the cam which would have been bad
Let's do this one. Let's go back to earlier this afternoon. We had 250 from peaceful hailey jeremy
I wanted to ask you what do you do for fun off stream?
What's a typical germa day?
Um pretty boring actually
grocery shopping
Do errands I get stuff for the next streams
You know most of the stuff that you see that just appears on streams randomly or things that I get are things that I do
It's usually set up a day or two before I stream
uh
Go to the dinner
You know kim and I will spend time together
Go see a movie
Sometimes it's nice just to kind of chill take a bath, you know
I contrary to maybe some popular belief. I live a pretty
boring
Private life
You know, I take take my dog out
I eat
I hang out with my girlfriend
I don't really do much else
besides preparing streams
And I sometimes like, you know go out, you know, if friends are in town or if we want to do something we'll
Oh, you know today. Well, we're gonna go to the strip today, right?
We've done I mean kim and I have gone out to the strip where you know downtown vegas a lot of times
But pretty basic normal stuff
No, the strip not a strip club another oil change servant. What?
Zeke thanks for the 250. I turned 22 today and spent my birthday eating microwave dinners and watching your old tf2 videos
Not like this
P.s. I know you get this a lot, but your stupid memes have genuinely helped me through stress and shit
More so than any other internet clown out there
Well, here's something else that I need to say about that
is
Sure, i'm the dude on the camera and i'm the guy that says the lines
But some of the funniest shit that had has come out of this community has come from people making the memes themselves
some of the most interesting stuff
comes from the community and the things that how you interpret the things that I say or how you
Create something out of something that I do or say
so
It's not just me
You guys come up with a lot of funny shit too based on this community, so
We should be the streamer
Jerma, you're the muse though
Hey potion dweller, thanks for the 250. I know exactly how today is going to go. Okay. Well, let's see
You will start out a very egotistical yet benevolent god
Then you'll accidentally kill someone and we'll all go d colon
Then someone will actually offend you
And you become a murderous psychopath petty god
I don't think it was that accurate
I didn't accidentally kill somebody
I intentionally killed a few people. I intentionally ate a few people
I ate that dead guy
Right, like that wasn't by accident. I
I ate the dead guy like that was not by accident. It wasn't on
Remember when he threw the rock at the crowd. Oh, does anybody have that clip?
Seriously, does anybody have the clip of when he throws the rock into the crowd? It's like
Fucking hilarious
Where is it?
Somebody has to have it
with the common psycho
It was so stupid. I was just trying to teach him how to like lift rocks
There it is
This is what I want. I need this in my life right now
No, not this
This is also funny, but not this one
Oh my god
Not this here I still will watch this still I guess this is fucking funny, too
Hey
What where's the other one where's the one from all the way here we go jerma's evil son
Jerma's evil son massacres innocent. Stop working. Hey, you're supposed to be stuck in there
Hold on. I need this. I
No, stop just throwing it
You just broke it
Where is it he goes with a rock?
You don't give a fuck man, oh he goes back throws it at the builder
Right here look at all these people
Stop
Stop stop stop it
He's killing everybody. It's not it. That's not it. Where's he throw the boulder?
He throws the boulder
That's not even it
Where does he he whips the boulder and it hits like 15 people
Somebody's got it. It's it's right after that. Yeah
Watch the full video
It's right there. No, wait, you see
He cries and he picks a folder
No, i'll find it some of it. We've lost control. Is that it?
This is the funniest shit i've seen like at least in 2020
Yeah, this is but this is by far the funniest thing i've seen in 2020
It's only been eight days. I know but still it's gonna be hard to top this for now
What's going on internet? Let's go. It's buffering. What am I buffering?
stop
Oh stop stop
He's looking at his eyes
Stop
Why would he do that
He's crying
He's looking at his eyes
You don't do that. Oh, that was so funny. What an absolute psychopath
Anyways
Thank you to potion dwellers
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Really appreciate it
also, we had
a thousand bits from
Suck your bus
And it was watch this on stream where no balls is salty swamp. So this is a great series. What are you talking about?
I mean, i'm not gonna watch it. It's like a 10 minute video
That's blordow's cartoon
It's old
But it's good
That's like 15 sick. That's like 16 years old
I think we've watched it on stream before
I'm certain we have
dermalore
Uh, watch this on stream. Not right now
No, watch joel's movie. I gotta we're gonna watch public domain movie night. We'll watch a bunch of movies queue them up
I promise we will watch it. We're gonna do a public domain movie night
But thank you suck your bus for the thousand bits. Thanks for the 1500 bits from bulbous swag desu
15 dollars. Thanks a lot for that. I'm so happy. I recommended this game like a billion times
I used to play it all the time as a kid
Yeah, it's fantastic
We'll probably be playing it again tomorrow
At least for a little while. I feel like there's still a little bit more to see
We'll see
Uh trampston gave five community subs. I think I missed it. But thank you trampston
phylacter lich gave five thousand bits again
again
Another 50 dollars name your god larry or we will riot. We'll get a proper name for the cow
I gotta have to really think about it. I didn't I was gonna say something but I didn't want to just jump on a random
Name and that's what the name is. No, no, no, I want to think about it. It's not going to be mega milk. Absolutely
No, sorry guys
Uh behemoth. Thanks for the 250. I I say it repeated
repent for being late
I just said it whatever and now I have to apologize for saying that i'm sorry
I just said that bulbous swag desu again 1500 bits again
On top of your 1500 to 30 dollars total here. Thank you bulbous way
I wasn't able to get this game to work when I tried a few weeks ago, but this tutorial goes on forever
Yeah
It is a pain in the ass to get to run on anything over windows 7
So those of you that want to play this game yourself, just be wary
It's a absolute mess to get it to run on new computers
Uh flinsenberg. Thanks for five community subs
Thank you flinsenberg
Germa put some chips in f germa put sun chips in f tier. Thanks for the 500 bits
I did
I just don't like them
I prayed I prayed this to you god germa so that you may show us your heavenly gigantic
Feet it's not what you guys thought it was gonna be also
Is there a chance that you'll play outer wilds in the future? Yes, it's on the table
I have a list over here with
50 plus games at this point that are all gonna get played. It's all early 2020 plans
So yes
I will be playing outer wilds. I promise
Topac thanks for the 250. Happy late new year couldn't send bits for the super late streams
Now that you're starting early, i'm so glad I can catch them again. It's been a wild four years since that i'm watching your channel
It's grown like crazy. I'm so happy for you. Keep it up. Everyone watches you for a reason
I hope so
All I can say back to you guys is
As the channel grows i'm gonna try to do more and more things that I wanted to try
We cross 10 000 fucking subs
I'm gonna do some shit that I may never have ever been able to do and may never be able to do ever again
You know i'm saying like i'm i'm I want to try new things
I promise i'll do even less imagine if I said that
So yeah
I'm gonna i'm gonna keep rolling
We'll see what happens. Right?
But thank you topac and yes, you can expect the streams to start pulled back where I
Was a couple months ago
around 1 to 2 pm pacific time
indefinitely for the foreseeable future
How did black and white go? It was very fun. It was a ton of fun
I told you it was I told you it was gonna be a hit
Do you remember the first like 20 minutes of the stream? I'm just saying
There was a lot of resident sleeper next game resident fuck and I told you you resident sleeper in half-life one right now
And I looked over and there was at least 100 people that were like good
I would do that for half-life one as well and i'm like fuck. Oh, how do I please this person?
It really starts to pop off when you get the creatures. Yeah
But thank you public for the 500 bits
And watching you as long as I can remember now i'm in my second semester of college and subbed to you for almost 18 months
Sincerely, thanks for everything. Oh and chat. You're cool, too
Chat is pretty cool. Yeah, I agree
Like some you know, sometimes they can resident sleeper of one of the best pc games
ever
You know and you know you let it slide
All right. I may I may have flown off the I may have flown off the handle there
Uh, this probably isn't the top 10 best pc game ever made
Um, the series is up there with some of people's most beloved cult classic video games ever made. I probably should have said that
I mean it might be
it paved the way for a lot of
Because lion head made this game and then everybody was like, oh wow
Having choices and and having powers and having ai control themselves and do weird things and people took it and you know, it was
It's pretty classic
Hey bulbous swag, thanks for the 1500 more bits on top of the already 30 you gave
Thank you bulbous swag. They said get the cow. I did
Classic doesn't mean good. But in this case it does
We also have to remember this is almost this is like 20 years old
It's like a six 15 16 year old game something like that
Can you imagine what this was like playing this?
When you could be good or evil and it was one of the first times you could ever do that
You still got the original box I got the original box too. It's pretty awesome
Came out in 2001
right
See
Show the box. I don't have any clothes on I can't i'll show it tomorrow. The second one wasn't as good, but it was fun
Yeah, I feel like we won't be spending as much time in black and white, too
Maybe like I said, i'm willing to give these games a good full two streams
I feel like we just opened up everything. So
Well, yeah, thank you. Pubble
Thank you for the 18 months in a row of your subscription. Thank you bulbous swag for the 1500
We did get the cow tar alecran. Thanks for the 250
The other day in chat people were telling you that bananas were radioactive
I went along with the bit because I thought it was funny
But I was watching a science video the other day and it turns out that not only are they radioactive but they reliably produce anti-matter
the most dangerous and volatile substance in the universe
On average a single banana will produce a particle of anti-matter every 70 minutes
This is as horseshit
You made the whole thing up
Thanks for the 250 though
Appreciate it. Look it up. Do I actually have to write this?
bananas anti-matter
This is real the average banana rich in potassium produces
Positron roughly once every 75 minutes. This feels like a fake website
Okay, the top two sources for this are the same website
Antimatter particle in bananas. Hold on. Is it maybe it is
quantum
Today I learned. Oh, here's reddit today. I learned bananas produce anti-matter. Let's say
Okay, let's see if somebody in the first comment goes actually you're fucking stupid. Let's see
Between this and the radiation thing i'm becoming increasingly distrustful of bananas and I really don't need that in my life
This and the radiation thing are the same thing
Wow, what a terrible sentence bananas contain potassium a small percentage of all naturally occurring potassium
Is in the form of potassium 40 potassium 40 decays through all three kinds of beta decay
Most of it is electron emission some of its electron capture and a tiny percentage is positron emission
It's a very small
arguably negligible amount of radiation the banana equivalent dose
Is 0.1
Weird usv in contrast you actually receive 10 usv background radiation per day on average
100 times more than eating a fucking banana. I said that to you guys
It's three weeks ago. There's this also you need potassium to live
so, um
You should be able to add this is a great quote from this fucking scientist. This reddit scientist
uh
You should actually keep your banana intake below
2740 bananas a day
um
To get below that radiation limit that you get just from it just existing a day. Okay, so be careful guys
Make sure you don't eat 3000 bananas a day to get the same radiation that you get by existing
Just standing in your room for a day
Like I said go in your basement and breathe in once
You just ate fucking 5000 bananas. Thank you. I'm so glad that we looked that up
So glad we got over that
Where are we here? Okay
Parasol, thank you parasol for the thousand bits
Hey jerma, just wanted to drop it and say I truly appreciate you. It's my dream to see you play my own game someday
until then
Love you
Until then though, but what game?
What game?
Never trust a redditor. Why not?
It's a porn game. You'll see
Thank you parasol for the thousand bits. I don't think it's a porn game
Come here. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey jerma, i'm pretty late
But just want to say thanks for the kind words on my xaraxos poster on the content night
Really made all the work. I put into it worth it. Can't wait for the next one. It was awesome. So thank you
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
But he said why not?
No, I can't play a porn game on stream
I can't i'm not gonna i'm not gonna play a porn game anyways. Why would I play a porn game?
Uh, thank you non a
Ha ar for the 250
Glad I can once again donate to the best streamer on twitch. I was so happy watching the award stream. You deserve every cent
Since you took me up on my black and white game recommendation. It was recommended a lot
So yeah, I told you guys how long till you give it and play dragon rampa probably never
Like black and white
This is my jam. You know what I mean?
I don't think i'll play in one of those. I don't think i'm gonna play dragon rumple
Probably never i'm just gonna be real
Stuff like I people say play dragon rompa play doki-doki literature club play
This game play this. I don't i'm really not into them. I really don't I don't play them
What's it called? What's it? What's it called?
Drag was it called?
dangan dangan ronpa
What am I saying dragon rompa?
I I like it that I I say it better that way dangan rompa
Probably not though. It's not doesn't look like it's up my alley
Hey invader z thanks to the 250. Hey jerem. I was wondering when the next community content night is
uh
18th
Also, here's a picture of my rats
Update a picture. You now have four rats
It's not good. It's actually okay
What the game?
Why you got him in why you got him in this bowl?
You got like rats in like a bowl. Yeah, look
That's a bowl with four in there
I know rats actually like to stuff into each other though, don't they?
I don't rats notoriously like to just get all on top of each other and like stuff on to into each other and stuff
That's a rat bowl
German can't say snuggle. Oh, that's true. That is what that is. Don't say it like that. I
Stuck I I i'm very literal
Yes cuddling sure. I'm I'm when I say like stuff into each other. I mean like pushing into each other
Hey kim mom is i'm not gonna read that
All right. All right. All right
But i'm talking in terms of like they press into each other and they roll and press and roll around and
All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done moving on. I gotta get rats
I want like a lizard too. I want a huge monitor dragon. I want a like a
Tegu so bad. I want a huge fucking lizard, but like I can't it's just not it's too much
Hey for raisin
uh
Frenzen thanks for the thousand bits
Thank you for all the laughs over the years germa. This is all I can give for now
one cent
Well, you can't even give one cent uh, 25 cents
Or 25 000 bits. I if you give money to this channel, don't ever think that this is all this is no
This is all I can give you for now
Don't feel obligated to give me money
Thank you for ever even considering it
Thank you for the thousand bits
Getting to the end here we have let's get the credits on by the way
Roll them up there and they come. Thanks all the subs everybody. There's a there are a lot of you now, you know the number
You know the number of how many people are subbed to this channel
It's an insane amount of people
it's
More than I ever thought that this channel would ever have ever
so
Thank you all of you
Regardless of I know it's a lot of gifted and community subs from new years
And if regardless if you stick around or not
This number here is fucking over 10 000 subs is fucking ridiculous. It's absolutely insane
I hope I use your money. Well
I plan to
next goal 20 000 subs
I don't know about that. That's uh, that's
At some point I at some point
You make a movie, you know what I mean? Like that's that's an absolute dick
That's an absolute shitload of money
You know at some point you hire danny to veto to fucking like come on streaming like throw an egg at me
You said dick. I was uh, this is just you know what I mean?
But regardless of where that number goes up or down. Seriously, it's we crossed the threshold here that
It seems impossible to cross
Thanks again guys. There's still a few more bits to do we have uh
mozzie connie
Mozzie connie for the mozzie connie
For a thousand this lot of ten dollar drops tonight a lot of thousand thousand fifteen hundred fifteen hundred. Thanks you
Seriously, it's a lot of money
Hey, germa got some bad news about my cat today
But your stream has been making it easier to cope just wanted to thank you for making everything a little easier
Whatever that news is
I'm hope you get through it. Thanks for the thousand bits. Thanks for sticking around
Uh, it's it's my pleasure to have you around
Sorry about the bad news
Whatever it is
Moving on to four real dough for 250
Is there a specific guide you use to get this game working? If yes, can we get a link to it?
Uh, okay. Let me go through the process here because it was weird
so
There is
This is an original cd
So it's black and white just the game
The original game no expansions or anything
And it I installed it I do I did not run it with compatibility mode. I just installed the game
Yeah, go to pc gaming wiki. That's a great place to do it. There is a fan patch
Because version the game patched up to version 1.3
I think is where the game officially ended and then some fans made a 1.4
And it fixed a bunch of the bugs and made it I think run better or run on um on newer hardware
Because I tried to run this game without the fan patch and it didn't work it crashed a desktop every single time
Yeah, bwf, uh, yeah bwf files windows 10. Yeah
I think there's at least a couple of guides on that website, too
But you you have to have that especially if you have windows 10
You have to have that 1.43 or 1.42. Whatever it is
Fan patch
And we've had a crash maybe once or twice and had a little scare about the save game
But for the most part it's been running
I would say flawlessly at this point
Uh, you also might have to get a dll, too
But cross that bridge when you need to
But that fan patch will help you. It's the only way to install black and white legit
big crash
I you know, okay
This is like this is funny to me, but also like I can't believe it. We're still arguing about oil changes right now
But I mean the others but I like
Somebody's saying it's a mess. It's a pain
I i'd rather just have somebody else do it. My time is valuable to me. You know what I mean? Like I
We're still going on that
Does luigi change his own oil?
Luigi probably can't even change his own diaper guys. Why am I so mean to a luigi?
Anybody why would I be this mean to luigi?
Jen ski flower. Thanks for the 300 bits
Hey jerma, i'm really glad you're playing black and white. It's one of my favorite childhood games
And when I bring it up everyone thinks i'm talking about pokemon black and white
I hope your doctor's appointment went well and you're feeling better from your illness
Or at least doing better than I am since i'm having an allergic reaction to my hair dye
And have sore itchy scabs all over my scalp
Holy shit, that's doesn't sound fun
And if you're not you better get some rest you toasted walnut
Yeah, i'm feeling all right
I I was coming down from my actual I had a head cold over the last few days and i'm feeling okay now
I'll probably be 100 better tomorrow
We can keep going
But thank you, uh jenski flower for the 300 bits
Mini clips. Thanks for 500 bits. What do you call a cow with no legs a ground beef?
Thank you bulbous swag again for five more dollars here. Just wanted to round up my bits for the night
But I gotta say you're a cruel and vengeful god
Uh, is it me? That's cruel
I keep thinking okay
Fuck, what did I think of this morning?
I was in bed this morning
And I started laughing just laughing really hard at something
What was it?
It was something random that I thought you guys would think was funny
I was in bed rolling around. You know when you get lost in your thoughts and you're in that half sleep
And you're not dreaming
But your imagination becomes way vivid way more interesting and way more vivid when you're in that halfway point
Something stream related happened that I remembered and I just started cracking up
Uh, what the hell was it? This is gonna happen though
I'm gonna randomly see in that half sleep the cow throwing the rocket though with those people and i'm gonna start cracking up
It's inevitable
That's so oh i'm so
I love this cow and if it wasn't the cow if it was going to be the the ape
The ape probably wouldn't have done that. I don't think so the cow like sucks. So I don't think the ape would have done it
I love this cow. We got to rescue him. Don't you understand? We have to rescue him
he's being
Captured and tortured right now. We have to get him. Thank you bulbous work tangent. Thanks for the five community subs tangent
The pc int thanks for 300 bits germa. It's not your fault, but my username
Is the point but the o is a c
Lol, the point was taken
Oh, so it's not the pc int
It's the point
I hope you have a good day missed most of the stream seems like it was both chaotic and boring at the same time
um
I mean, it's just it's a different type of game. You know, they take a while to do anything interesting
But when stuff happens it goes fucking crazy
That's another reason why I want to do this do the tutorial and like try to pay attention to a lot of things
Just to make anything fun happen in the game
You really kind of need to know how it works and I didn't want to just blow through it because I could skip the tutorial
completely
So I need to continue to learn
Level three requires you to use all the mechanics germa's been neglecting. It should be good. Yeah
We'll see the thanks them
Errorless thanks for the 250 when you're gonna do a collab a collab with uh lil naz
I don't think that's gonna happen. I i mean i'm flattered i'm flattered if if he likes
rat movie
That's where they got it from. I you know what I mean?
That's uh, it's flattering
uh
Just dm him and say you're the giant rat guy
I don't know if I want to do that
Hey, hey, i'm the giant rat guy. Hey, you you you tweeted that i'm the giant rat guy. It's me
You ret you tweeted something out with giant rat. I'm that guy
That's a little that's that kind of grasping. I don't i'm not into that
That's just cool that
He may have seen the video. That's just cool. I don't need nothing. I don't need anything else. No, that's enough for me
But you know if he did
If he was like, hey
Giant rat was really awesome. I'd be like that's me. I'm that guy
Uh, that's just cool. And that's all there is to it high tie. Thanks for the 1500 bits
$15 thanks a lot. This is my way of saying thank you. I've been watching your videos for over five years
Specifically starting with the pin cushion experiment. That was a that was a good one
You continue to be the funniest entertainer out there and I can never make up the countless hours of entertainment you've provided
Thanks man, I wish I'd been watching you for five years
Well, you you got five years from now, you'll be you'll five years from now
You'll look back and be like, oh, remember that was pretty fucking cool. Remember when the cow threw the rock at those people
your story
Begins now
But seriously high tide. Thank you
Thanks for allowing me to be able to do something like this
And wake up every day and go what do I want to try to do today that that might be fun
People like you allow me to do that. So thank you. Finally, we have a couple more we have kerbumble for 300 bits
We have for real dough for 250. I enjoyed the stream drummer. Here's to hoping this game and the sequel get a digital release
Re-release or a decent spiritual successor. That's something that I wish they already existed
If you took black and white
one and two and just remade it as just
Just remake it just black and white
Remake some of the systems take away some of the potentially more grindy frustrating systems that are in the game and put a bunch
New creatures in make the ai crazier
People would eat this up so much
But not very many people not many people know it exists and people that do know it exists
Can barely play it because it's hard to get to run
Mike it's microsoft microsoft is sitting on all this shit
Microsoft owns all these assets like what get on it
That microsoft owns all the all the lion head ip, right?
like
There's so much interesting shit that they could do with some of these lion head ips
ea owns it
I thought lion head was absorbed by
microsoft
Yeah, I thought so. It's ea. What?
Seriously
That's even worse. Yeah, that's that is that is kind of worse
I thought I always thought that it was it came with the absorption of all of lion head
Hmm. Well, oh well send it to bed then
Because that ain't coming back
Uh e cookie. Thanks for the 250 and our final bit of the night. Hey germa
I'm a veterinarian by trade and specialize in small rodents like rats mice and hamsters
All right. Let's get some info here for rats. They do actually enjoy being put in small piles with other rats
Like yeah, right
If I have a if I have a particularly anxious rat
I will place him with four or five other rats in a bowl then put that into a deep fryer you motherfucker
Right. Okay. Thanks veterinarian
Thanks the fucking fake veterinarian
That's the last bit of the night
I'll see you guys tomorrow for more black and white potentially. Well, we might do a split stream tomorrow
We might play black and white for a couple hours and then move on to like katana zero
Or maybe we get addicted and I just stay on it like I did today for like eight hours
See you guys soon
Have a great rest of your night
And I will see you
Very soon very soon very very very very soon
Very soon say sorry. Oh, wait, wait, wait e cookie just gave
E cookie gave 250 moments. They say sorry
e cookie
Apology
How dare you?
Uh, yeah, well we could see let's let's raid somebody
He's streaming right now
I've been trying to follow more people in ship and try to keep up with because we've gotten some really really
Great communities. We've had some raids
The box box has raided the channel like three times with thousands of people
Uh, we got that right from ludwig
with three or four thousand people a couple weeks ago
I really want to try to catch some of these uh
Some of these people when they're streaming
Right key wall key. Well, yeah, that's where key was streaming right now. Okay, what are you doing?
It's been a while
Yeah, let's break you up, uh, she's doing no pixel
Grand Theft Auto
I you uh, germa do no pixel do no pixel
I
I maybe one day maybe one day. I don't know
Go say hello to keyword guys
And i'll see you guys tomorrow
Take care
See you soon. Good night
That video is in a different spot as well
That video is in a different spot as well. I swear to god like that all my videos have moved
All right, joe
Here's the end here comes the end of the stream. All right, I don't know what this video is. It's not in this folder
See you tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye. We don't need it out. We don't have no outro