Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight, gonna be playing as the Engineer, Aggressive Defense Engineer, playing on the
big coil on Thunder Mountain, or the big snake, whatever you want to call it. It's, I think,
the last part of Thunder Mountain. But anyways, this video is not gonna really cover any of
the gameplay on the screen, but it is gonna cover a gaming topic, and that is competitive.
And what it now means to me, and how I feel about the competitive communities across the
globe doesn't matter what game you're playing. Because, as you know, some of you, most of
you, a lot of you know by now, we are going to E3. Now, if you haven't been on the channel
for a few days, or you don't know what I'm talking about, I'll try and break it down
a little bit here. So a few days ago, me, Ster, and MLC Stealth, we joined into this
Shoot Mania Storm tournament on Twitch TV. And the two people that were the top two
in that tournament move on to E3 to play in the Grand Finals. And we're one of those
teams. I don't know how we did it. I don't know, it really, it still hasn't hit me yet.
I'm still kind of sitting in this chair going, am I really about to get on a plane in like
less than 24 hours to go to E3? Is this really happening? My mind has not settled around
that fact yet. And I know it will. When I get on that plane, I'm gonna be sitting there,
the captain's gonna go, this is your captain speaking. We are now taking off to Los Angeles
International Airport. And I'm just gonna be like, oh my God, I'm going to E3. And I'm
gonna scare the ever living crap out of everybody on the plane. And that's not my intention.
I apologize if you're on that plane that I'm on, but I'm getting off track. The point is
we are going there to E3. We're all gonna be there. We're all gonna hang out. Shibby's
gonna be there or we're all gonna just, it's gonna be ridiculous. And I'm bringing my camera.
Don't worry, I am gonna get random footage of us being crazy in those hotel rooms. But
I do have to say this though. This is a massive thank you, massive shout out to anybody that
came to that stream that was supporting our team. Because we would look at that chat and
we would see people going, yeah, YouTube, money, crush them, let's go. And there were
so many of them. It was just so motivating. Whether you came from Shibby, Star, MLC Stealth,
my channel, wherever you came from. Thank you so much for doing that. You guys rock.
Well, freaking yeah. So now I want to transition from that to talk about competitive gaming
and sort of what I think about it and how I feel now, especially now after winning or
not winning, but coming in the top two of this tournament to go to E3. So competitive
gaming, the only thing, the only experience I've ever had with comp gaming is when I was
11, when I was 11 years old, I won a gaming competition at my local Blockbuster. Now that
might not sound like competitive gaming, but it was for me when I was 11, I was like, oh
my God, I'm playing, I'm going to be in a tournament. And it was exciting. But so the
winner of that tournament got to get free rentals from Blockbuster. I think for a couple
months or something like that, you get free video game rentals. That's back when video
game rentals were the big thing. And that's also back when Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis
were the big guys on the block. And now I feel old. Talking about Super Nintendo, I
owned a regular Nintendo and an Atari. That's how old I am. I'm pretty much as old as a
dinosaur egg. Well, not really. But that is the only time up until this past weekend
where I've ever competed in a game situation for real prizes or real notoriety. And I think
I want to keep doing it because it was so much fun, guys. This last weekend, it was
really tough. It was really competitive. It was really adrenaline rushing. And we spent
a lot of time practicing. We were prepared for this tournament. And even still, there
were a lot of good teams. And when you go up against a team that's evenly matched with
you, calling out strategies and trying to get in position, trying to really land down
those shots, my mind was in a tornado. And it wasn't a bad thing. It was a good thing.
And it really got me into the game. And I want to keep doing it. It was a rush. I can't
explain that a lot of you guys that play competitive probably already know what I'm talking about.
We were going up against some quake pros. We were going up against Counter-Strike 1.6
A couple other guys that had a lot of competitive experience. And it was just so exciting. And
my question for the video, I guess, is competitive-wise, how many of you guys have done some tournaments
or maybe won a couple things? And that doesn't mean Team Fortress. I'm talking anything.
I'm talking Counter-Strike, Call of Duty, Quake, Unreal. A lot of you guys are older
too, so you might have some of that experience under your belt as well. And I guess a follow-up
question is, getting into competitive, how do you get prepared? Because how I got prepared
is I drank like four coffees and listened to a bunch of music in my headphones as loud
as it can go to try and get me squared away. And then we just started playing. So I want
to know what your guys' process is, because this is really interesting stuff. And it's
stuff I like to know. So before this video is over, I want to bring this up again. Thank
you so much to everybody that came and supported that stream and came and supported us playing
in that tournament. And also a lot of stuff went in behind the scenes with Shibby2142
kind of being our PR guy to get our team straightened away, and Incredible Orb. Without Incredible
Orb, I would not have been in this tournament. Neither would anybody. So big, huge shout
out to Orb. You the man, dude. And I hope to see you at E3. I'm going to give you a
big hug. So thank you guys so much for watching video-wise for this channel in the next four
or five days. I'm going to have stuff schedule uploaded, so don't worry. There's going to
be content here, regardless of me being at E3. And if any of you guys are in the Los
Angeles area at the E3 Expo, I will salute you, and hopefully I see you there. So I'll
see you guys all soon, and take care, everybody.