Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Super Meat Boy Mondays, Chapter 6, which is going to be the end.
Now this is, this may or may not be the final Meat Boy video I make. I know there's the Dark World stuff, there's Cotton Alley, there is the Warp Zones, Character Unlocks, Band-Aids.
I know there's all that stuff in here, but I'm not sure if I'm going to do it or not. I might and I might not. I'm going to leave that pretty much totally up to you guys.
And I guess we'll just go from there. So if you want to see more Meat Boy, let me know in the comments and let me know with a like or a favorite or something like that so I can determine if you guys want to see more of this series.
So we're just going to keep going here. Super Meat Boy, Chapter 6, the end.
Dancing around like a freak show. Hey, quit dancing, you piece of crap. No, I'm not going to stop dancing. And I have your girlfriend too. What are you going to do about it?
The end. This is the end. Okay, there are only five levels in the end. So this hopefully does not take 60,000 years, but it probably will because this game is so goddamn hard.
Let's just go here. Let's beat this in 10 minutes. What do you say? There's no way that's going to happen. Is he here? Oh, it's locked. It's locked. Okay. Got to go around, I believe.
No, I don't. What was I supposed to do down here? Oh, there's the key. Okay. Oh, that's how you take down the wall over there. It's all coming back to me now.
Jump over, get the key over here. That opens up the wall over this side. This way. Okay, okay. Cheese, it's in gravy. All right there. Woohoo. So far so good. Oh, I can't do anything careless here though.
I, I'm, I, just go. I can do this. This level isn't even that bad. Come on, Meat Boy.
Epic music. Epic music is going to make me win. Over this way. It's over here. Be careful of the saw blades. They will kill you. They have been known to do that.
I just don't do anything stupid here like you just did. No, I got to stop jumping with it. And right now. Whoa, that was close.
All right, how many people died? How many did we lose? Only two or three. Here's the vector right here. Nice job. There you are. Woohoo. Schism. Schism. I don't even know how you say that word.
I will protect your honor. I will defend you to the day I die. My lady. My beautiful, sweet lady. I will complete this for you. Oh, jeez.
You just got to drop straight down this. I don't know why I'm trying to do something tricky with that. Same thing here. There's no need to be so nuts about it.
Now, if I remember correctly, it's easier to jump off of this and I could be totally wrong, but I don't think I am. Judging by me completing that, I don't think I was wrong.
Shoot me in the face with a machine gun. Just put like an entire god. All right, just be easy. It's only the second level. Be easy here. Can't freak out.
There we are. Super Meat Boy, baby. There's the key. I got to go back up. Oh my god. Oh my god. What am I doing? What did I drop? What did I drop down right there? What an idiot.
Oh my god. I can't believe I did. Oh my god. Just go. Just jump, you piece of crap. I'm going to drop a piano on your head if you do that again.
Am I talking introspectively? Am I speaking to myself when I say that? Who am I talking to when I say that? Okay, we're good.
Who's going to get the piano dropped on their head? Is it going to be like me? You? No, I wouldn't do that to you. Why would I do that to you? That wouldn't make a whole lot of sense.
No, don't go down there again. Just go down nice and slow like this. There we are. That'll do it. Okay, jeez. Here we go. There we are.
Okay, now just be careful here. You don't want to do anything ridiculous. Can't screw this up. Just like that. I'll take the pie and I'll eat it too.
How many died in the very beginning here? One dude? Who got the piano dropped on them? That's what I want to know. You don't see that anymore.
Nobody drops pianos on anybody anymore. See, back in the old days of cartoons, people used to get pianos dropped on their heads. Not anymore though.
Piano. Even the name is funny. Piano. It's so amusing. Oh, you get crushed by the thing, you elevator bastard. That was very unconventional how I just got that.
That's not how you're supposed to get that at all. But you know what? It works. If it works, then just take it. Get it and run. No, it's the exact same.
I'm doing a carbon copy of the same thing I just did a second ago. Okay, easy. There's only a few levels here.
You're going to spend the majority of the damn time on the boss anyways, because the boss is really difficult. Okay, let's think of it like a clock.
And you're going to get it right there. Freeze. You're good. Just be smart. Don't do anything stupid.
Let's keep it rolling. Just go. Speedrun. Speedrun. Oh, you thought you could mess with the speedrun. It's actually working. Speedrun's working.
Wow. Okay, I just went through half of that level right there in a speedrun. I did not expect to survive past that halfway point.
What's up here? You want to be able to see? Because I forget. And I don't want to have to speedrun again. Oh, baby, that was a beauty if I say so myself.
This is it. After this, we are at the blast boss of the game. Well, technically of the storyline of the Meat Boy storyline.
Now you and God's jeez. Trump down maybe. Oh, my God, that hurt. That hurt to do that. Yikes.
Oh, wow. Wow. I am. Oh, this is difficult. I remember this. You got to be very, very careful here. Oh, I did it too early.
God damn it. I would have did that in first try. Oh, no. Madden. I'm getting all over the place. Oh, back at the beginning back.
You know what? Just fall off. It's stuck from scratch here again.
And we're going to speedrun because last time I speedrun it worked. Maybe not. Just when you just get over there, you piece of crap.
Speedrun. It's all about just speeding. Forget the speedrun. Not going to work. Up, up and away.
No. What the hell? Will you? Will you stop doing that? Just get through the hole.
I had it the first time and I'm just a stupid idiot. And I got too busy scratching my ass or whatever the hell I was doing.
I don't know how I would scratch my ass with, you know, my hands on the controller, but whatever.
Now I forget how I just did this part. Now I don't. Just jump right through. Same thing here. Just this time. Don't be. Don't be a butt scratcher.
Key. Oh, oh, oh, damn. That was near the end of the level too. Time to be quiet.
We all know what happens when I be quiet. I complete levels that are difficult.
There we are. Just don't do that again. Oh, okay.
Here is the last boss, Dr. Fetus. Here we go, guys. Where is he? I'm gonna find him.
Yeah, yeah, you're not gonna come near me because I'll show you what a bazooka. You know what this is? It's a bazooka, you bastard.
Yeah, you're dead now. Maybe you're not. Yeah, he's dead. Wait, what? Get out of here. Now he's dead.
What the hell? Will you just get? God, he's gonna kill me. This thing is jammed. This thing doesn't even work.
Why'd I spend $5,000 on this thing? It's worthless. Come here. Let's go.
The whole point of this is you gotta beat Dr. Fetus. You can't get killed by his missiles or his rockets and you gotta kill him.
Oh my God, I am so nervous. Doctor? Doctor? Doctor? Please? Doctor?
Oh my God, I didn't realize what was happening. Okay. Didn't realize that was happening. Oh, great. Oh, great.
Come on, shoot me. Shoot me, doctor. Shoot me, el doctor. Danke, el doctor.
Make it over here. Gotta move. Gotta move. He's gonna start shooting. Oh man, this is bad.
Oh, this is bad. Whoa. This is bad. Oh man, oh man.
Oh come on, I'm almost there. Get up. Get up there. Oh no. Oh.
Damn it. I was at the end. I was near the end. I was...
Fotted my face and called me Dave Stevenson. Oh my God. I'm so mad right now.
I'm so... I am so mad right now. Just take it easy. This is not even that difficult. I can do this with my eyes closed.
That is an untrue statement. Let's pretend I didn't say that. Imagine playing this game with your eyes closed.
It would not be possible. I want to see a guy do a let's play of this game with their eyes closed and have a face cam. Whoa.
Careful here. He's gonna start shooting that stupid rocket launcher. This part was horrible. I can't believe I made it through this part.
I had it. I had it the very first time I tried this. I had it. Oh man.
Just go. You gotta stay in front of him. That's the major thing. If I can stay in front of him, I can do this.
Believe in yourself. You gotta believe that was why you...
Alright, time to do this. No more messing around. I'm doing this right now.
Silent. It's all about just memorization. I'm playing that game where you flip the cards over and you memorize everything.
Oh, somebody just texted me. Too bad. It's not as important as not dying in this level. It could be, though. That's the thing.
Back where I was before. Okay. Nice and easy here.
Oh! Hit that thing! Gotta hit that thing! Oh my god, I did it! No!
Oh man, that looked like it hurt. I know.
I'm sorry about everything.
Oh my, that was pretty morbid. Let's get out of here, sweetheart. Let's go get a drink. Yeah, let's go get it.
I'm not dead yet. F you. My final request is for you to die.
Oh, now we gotta get out of here. We gotta run. Come on, let's go, sweetheart.
I forgot that this was actually the last level. And it's really hard.
So, ow. I just hit my thumb. Man, this is very, very difficult. Time to be quiet again.
Oh, shoot me in the face. I've already said that, but still. Let's go, honey.
Oh man, somebody's probably texting me right now like,
Hey, Jeremy, your house is on fire. I'm standing outside looking at it.
And I'm just like, I can't talk right now.
Uh, Jeremy, there's a tornado about to come to your house.
How did I not die at that? Okay, let's go here.
Oh, now somebody's calling me. My duck call.
Hold on, I gotta answer this. This is like my mother.
Okay, so the house is not on fire, but my mother was just like, needed to talk to me.
It's okay. Let's get back into this. Go, go, go.
Nope. Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
God, I'm going to puke. Up, up and away.
If I could just get by this one stupid pot. Like that. Okay, now be easy here.
Oh, let me look at this. I just said I wanted to look at it and I didn't even look at it.
I just went, I didn't even think. I just went, just go.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Be careful. You don't want to freak out here.
Got to drop right now.
Wow. It's so long. It's so ridiculous. I'm going to throw up.
Once it goes around one more time.
I thought I beat the game. I forgot about this part.
This very long, very awful part of the game.
Okay, I got through that. I'm good with that.
This part's not that bad. I just got to go now. Jump over it twice.
Wait till it goes. Go. Go up here.
This part, you just kind of slug your way over this way.
Up here. Risky, I know, but I had to do that.
No more thinking. Just go.
Never made that noise before.
Son of a bitch. This is so hard.
Dark World? Can you imagine this on the Dark World?
Blood's going to come out of my eyes if I play this on the Dark World.
I should just, what am I thinking here?
I can just skip this.
Wow. Okay. That's good to know.
I'll remember that for next time.
Easy up there. These are just saw blades.
These are just saw blades. You can do this.
Just saw blades.
Just go easy through the saw blades. That's all you got to do.
And don't just skip those.
I did it. At the end.
We did it, sweetheart. I'm so happy.
Come on, hurry up. What are you doing?
Oh no, this thing's falling everywhere. I can't get out of here.
Oh no. Oh.
He's dead.
No. I got you, man. Just get out of here.
Go with your girlfriend.
Wow, thanks. You're the best.
No, just forget about me, man. I got this.
Oh, but...
No, man. Just go with her.
I love you both.
That's him dying.
Well, Meat Boy and his girlfriend decided to go to Paradise Island after this.
To see their honeymoon.
The Dr. Fetus was killed during the collapse of his lair.
And Pooh Boy saved the day as well.
So I guess we can say one earlier.
I'm back to kill you. You stupid bitch. I'll kill you. I'll rip your eyeballs out.
Super Meat Boy. The end.
Oh, goodness gracious. Oh my god.
Okay. Well, thank you guys so much for watching the series.
I very, very much appreciate it.
And like I said in the beginning, if you want to see this continue,
if you want to see some of the warp zones, more of the characters unlocks,
some Dark Zone stuff, or Dark World stuff,
then just leave me a comment, let me know, or leave me a like on this video,
and we will go from there.
So, I guess we'll just let this play out.
Thank you guys so much for watching.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.