Hello, everybody. How are you? Speak, speak, speak. I'm here. I'm here.
So today, we have been a night, saw you last night, but seeing you again right
now. We've got another co-op stream today. This one is going to be with some
familiar faces, Ster and italics. The three of us are going to play a game
called tools up. It's like a mix of overcooked and house flipper.
Who knows? The game might be good. It might not be, but it seems like it
could be pretty fun. We are currently streaming this through steam remote
play. So this is going to be a journey. We took a little extra time to get it
ready. So we have tested it. It does work. We are, but we're, we're ready.
They're both currently doing their intros because they're streamers. And
I'm just sitting here in outer space. Show us the hammer. Hammer. When is
halo? God damn it. You know, it's really, really awful. I feel like I need to
wait like a week to play halo again. I have such a, it's like eating ice cream
for the first time. You take a bite of ice cream while somebody stabs a knife
into your back. You are always going to have synonymous the memory of eating
ice cream for the first time with when you got stabbed. So I want to play halo
very, very badly, but I got stabbed while we played. It's all I, I got the
bad memory. Joel scarred him for life. Joel hates Jeremo. This is a different
co-op stream today. This is tools up. I wonder. Here's the funny thing. This is
what they know this and now you're going to know this. And it's actually kind of
funny. The way the steam remote play works is I am in total control of both
of their streams. I am broadcasting this to their computers. So I'm in
control. They have, they can't press any buttons. They can't change any sliders
or anything. So I'm in the driver's seat. So if I just start playing the game
right now, if they have their desktop audio enabled, this is going to start
playing. Let's find out. Let's see if anybody said, did it work? It should be
playing some music through there. No, hold on. I'm muted. Right now. Yeah, it is.
Alright, watch this. Yeah, come over here. Take a look at this. I'm in fucking control.
Alright, did I fuck up, did I fuck up the streams? He was muted. Yeah, no, they're
both muted right now. They're both doing their intros. Well, this is tools up. Or
are they both muted desktop audio and did I just do that to you guys? I wonder.
That's probably, yeah, that's probably what it was. But they're, hey, they're muted on stream, but they
heard it. There's no way they didn't. Impossible for them not to. It's impossible.
They heard that. Alright, I'm ready. I'm just gonna be in the
Discord call waiting for him. I'm just gonna be talking. Who are we waiting for?
Are you here? How's it going, everybody? What's going on? How's everybody doing? Yeah, what's up, man? Hey, dude. Hey, long time no see.
How's everybody doing? You guys all at the menu? How was your Thanksgiving? Oh, man.
What'd you guys, what'd you guys get for Black Friday? I got a table. You guys can't
both talk at once. Someone learn how to like... Oh my god, that's so fucking loud.
Are you nuts? He's doing it on purpose. I'm in fucking control. I had Jerma streaming a
game so that we can restream his game. No report. How do you report a player in
Steam? Well, you guys will be the ones getting reported because you're
streaming my stream. Alright, I had to turn you down to like 40% because you
just... You personally, your voice blasted my audio and now you're like quiet as a
whisper. Oh, dude. We've already played the game for 10 seconds. Fucking liars. Go back to our 10
seconds. I don't want to start over. Alright, let's do a new save slot. That one's
corrupted. Did you guys explain how this works to everybody? I don't know how this
works. Alright, Jerma is streaming this game to the cloud. The magic of the cloud
is enabling me and Stirr to connect and use our controllers as if we were
sitting next to him in the same house. Can you imagine being in the same house?
Yeah. It's called the internet. They just rolled out the internet this week and they're letting us try it as a beta.
Yeah. But this game is what I meant. I don't know how... I have no idea how this game
works. Alright, you guys... Here comes the cutscene. This game requires friends. You can be
anywhere on earth. That's us. How do you know? Hey, I'm driving. You haven't seen
this yet. Oh, nice. You almost hit that. Okay. Oh, yeah. Why can't they see the
cutscene? Wait, they can't see the cutscene? Hold on. My thing's bugged. I'm in control of the cutscene.
Oh, they can't see it. Wow. What? What do you mean nobody can see it? It's also showing the main menu. This internet
beta is not going well. Wait, what? Hold on. You guys skipped the cutscene?
Presumably. Hold on. But it's so cute. It's really not. Okay. I'm going to skip the cutscene.
So you guys just have to... I can see it now. You guys have the over cooked? I untoggled the
the cap feed and then re-toggled it. And that seemed to work. Okay. How does it look? You guys
good? We good? Who's player two? Who just did that? I am. That's me. I am. Okay. Okay. Hold on.
Because now I can't. Okay. Okay. I'm player three. Okay. Everyone remember that. No one
for the rest of any of our streams ask who is who or I'm going to be mad. Okay. First one ready.
Wait. What the heck? You just dropped out of the game. You hear me pressing? Okay. I'm ready.
All right. Are we ready? Yeah. First one ready. Let's go. Player one's me. Player two,
Talek's player three star. No, I'm player three now. What? Are you? Yeah. Oh, you are.
So no one asked. I'm player two. I just don't. I'm just like the Super Mario guy.
All right. I'm gone. I don't even know. I don't know who you guys are. I don't know.
I'm lady who is player two. So you got the hard hat. Left stick is elevator. What? No, it's not.
We're to fix this house. Oh, I just walked under a ladder. That's how much I did too. Hey, hey,
hey, hey, I'm the one in control. Don't tell me just did something and I'm supposed to be in
control. Sorry. I'll be here. No, I'm clear one. Okay. So we have to fix the house. Overall
progress. We're being timed. How are we being timed? What constitutes as a fixed house? Living
mom. The living room needs to be built. You're building. You didn't tell me there was building.
No, living room has to. What's that? The floor has renovating. We're trying to make this
a nice place to live in. Okay. Left trigger, right trigger. Oh my God. And Jerma controls the
camera. No, no, no, no, no, no. Whoever controls that whoever controls the blue camera has control
the camera. But what the hell paint the walls red. Okay. How do we do that? All right. I've got paint.
Okay. I took a door off. So it's X to do that. And how do you paint?
Um, we have to have paints to paint. I figured out how to take off doors. How do you pick stuff up?
We don't have any more paint. This is pain right here. Oh, okay. So you only can get
what you guys are already dead. I spilled it. How do you clean up this paint? What do you mean?
We're dead. All right. Well, you how do you recycle? What are you doing? Why are you riot shielding?
I'm beating the door. All right. Will you go take the blueprint? If we don't do this in two
minutes. How do we hook the doors up? We have 2.7 minutes. You press the bottom button. I don't know
what controller you're using. The A on the Xbox. You guys have Xbox? Yeah. I got an Xbox. Paint. I
asked for one for Christmas. And I got one. Okay. This is dumb. Oh my God. Okay. That's you doing
that. Oh my God. That's me doing it. I'm learning. We all had to do it once. Okay. So how do I get
new paint? Where's the tutorial? This is the campaign. This is the tutorial. This kind of
game that doesn't hold your hand. Are we out of? You need to turn it so we can see the other side.
Why am I holding a big milk carton? All right. Go. Oh my God. Don't let me have these. How do I
draw? I'm done. We have to paint. Okay. Okay. I have a new idea. I'll be the foreman. No. What the
fuck? There's three of us. Pick a room. Wait. How do you, how do you pick? Thank you. No.
Put it over there. This room needs to. No. Do we just have to paint the living room? When I go up
to either of you. Yeah. I think we have to flip so we can see the wall. Go up to the star. Come
on. Paint can. Hold X on the paint can. Which one? You don't know who you are? What are you
talking about? You've got a red hat. I've got an orange hat and German's got a green germ hat.
Yes. We did this. This is just a guessing game. No, it's not. You have red paint and you paint.
We just, okay. We went tidy up, get rid of all the trash. What about, okay. It says recycle,
but what are we recycling? How do you throw stuff and pick stuff up? My guy refuses.
Clean up, clean up, clean up. He just shakes his head. A throws. Pick that paint can up.
How? A and then use, that's how you throw. Why did you kick me out of the house?
Because no one knows what's happening. We still did it. Which one of these is you?
You. I'm the little guy with the German I'd hate five branded helmet on.
Well, then who's me? I don't know. I don't remember. You got to switch like five times.
Look, there are your controls right there. They're gone. I got a solid state drive.
There's not enough time to read those controls. All right. Let me be the one to help you here.
A picks up. Xbox controls. A picks up. B throws. X holding X does every option. B. Which one's D?
B as in bury. It's right there. There's only two buttons in the game. Just to pick up,
put down, hold to collect, throw with B. There are only three buttons. There's three buttons.
Well, now we know what they do. What are we supposed to do now? Now you. Okay.
Get the blueprint. I can't get out of this, by the way. You just can hold me forever.
You just hear a bully. Okay. Living room. Living room. Needs floors. Which one's the living room?
The living room needs walls painted. All right. We got to clean up the paint.
We got to recycle the rubbish. We got to use the buckets to put the rubbish away.
No, it does need floors. Yeah. Clean shit up. Okay. All right. I volunteer. What is this one?
I'll just be the foreman and I'll stand over here and make sure you're all doing it right.
All right. Pick stuff up and put it in the bucket. Just clean. Just help us clean.
No, don't throw it over it out of bounds. Listen, I've been playing with Nintendo
controllers lately. Who the fuck is this guy? This carpet guy. Oh, he's got the carpet.
All right. It goes in this room, right? Look, look, look. We can really speed this up
officially. I think we have to roll this. Are you awake? Yeah, I'm a foreman. I think he's
not playing. I'm playing. He's not moving. Have you ever been on a construction site before?
All right. Look, look, look. We're going to speed this up. Pick that up.
It's desperately telling you. What? I can't. No, I can't. Yeah. Yeah, they're still doing it.
You totally can't. That's what this is here for. Hey, which one's the living room and which one's
the kitchen? Put the bucket down. Yeah, they're still doing it. What? Okay. You're stepping in
your own dog poop. We have two minutes to figure this out. That's not a lot of time.
I'm going to be the foreman now. Yes. The carpet needs to be rolled in this room.
Stop. Just look at small Luigi Wario. Okay. He, Italics is a shitty foreman. Okay. I'm sorry. I
just had to get that out of my system. All right. Okay. We have a carpet now. How do we roll this?
I think we do. We need help. So you can order stuff. Oh, there we go. All right. You can see
progress. We're five percent done in the living room. Take, take. Oh my God. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Put it down. You can't tell what's happening when you're blueprinting us, you stupid shitty foreman.
Bathroom we were dealing with. Put carpets in the bathroom. Cowards. Why is, why is my character
just shaking her head? No, because you're standing on the square. You're supposed to
be styling. Because someone has to tell you no. Well, don't you have to stand on it and put it
down? I can't not stand on it. What button? All right. What color do the rooms need to be?
Does one need to be orange? Okay. I'll be, I'll be the foreman. I don't know what the foreman does.
The kitchen. It just tells you what needs to happen. Okay. So this should be orange.
Kitchen needs to be painted. Orange. The living room needs to be yellow. How do you tell what room
is what? So the living room is done, right? Yeah. Now it needs to be orange. Walls in the living
room too? Ugly. Oh, yellow. Yellow walls. Yellow walls on the right, orange on the top. I'm doing
the orange on the top. I spilled it. What kind of fucking McDonald's play pen house is this?
I haven't learned the buttons yet. Can someone clean this up? Play, play probs.
You're doing a great job, Star. Walking back and forth from room to room. You're doing great.
It's good. Now X, hold X and then hold X. I'm doing it, daddy. How come you can only paint once per
hour? Because it's part of the video game. We got seven seconds. What? What? We're 89%. Clean it
up. Just clean it up. Clean, clean. There's no carpet there. How is there no carpet in that
corner? We did it. One star. It was placed in blocks. That doesn't make any sense. That does
actually not make any sense. But you ever like malicious compliance? No. Just put it down. Who
cares? Somebody else's problem now. Oh, yeah. Yeah. That's my life. Let them put it together.
We'll just leave the paint cans there. The carpet. He's a Redditor. Shut up. Found out.
I can't believe we got 10 stars on that last one. Yeah. If you multiply by 10, I think I learned
the buttons. It scared everybody. I'm sorry. Let me go. I'm trying to shortcut you. Oh,
that's actually pretty good. Listen to me, everybody. We got it in the living room. We
got to put down the floor. But first you have to use the gardening tool on it.
The floor has to come in first through the mail. And then you have to paint the wall orange.
What do we have to do for that? Okay. So we need binding of Isaac damage plus what?
That's the binding of Isaac damage. No, that's like the gardener. You have to dig up
something to plant. Okay. The bucket is definitely supposed to hold access. Yeah,
it does. It holds trash. But how do you put it in there? Here, put it down.
It's A to put it in. All right. All right. All right. Here's the carpet. We haven't finished
moving this. Here, here, here, here. Yeah, there. See? Let's get it going. It's going to put trash
in here. Wait, look how fast this is. Oh, that is pretty fast. All right. So what this wall needs
to be orange, right? Uh, no, no, no, not orange. That's okay. This one's orange. I think so. Yeah.
Where the carpet guy go. Well, it depends which one is the kitchen and which one's the living room.
Get to the door. He's ringing the doorbell. Is he going to help? Okay. I'll be doing it.
He was about to leave again. Thank you. That actually helped. I'm, I'm the foreman. All right.
There's yellow paint coming in. Yellow paint just arrived. All right. This room's done.
I'm bringing you the yellow paint. Okay. Good. All right. In the carpet. Thank you.
We have to designate jobs. That's how this works. Well, I mean, we're doing that kind of honestly.
I can't paint this room. I'm willing to bet we get paid by the hour. Which room has to be yellow?
The top left one. Hey, but furniture delivery gets paid ahead of time. Oh, you got to peel the
wallpaper off. Shit. All right. I need that bucket. Throw that bucket in here. I'm getting it. All
right. I got the carpet done in the main room. What have you done? Trash bucket. I painted all
the walls. All right. Put it down. Trash. Trash bucket. Yeah. You have to peel the walls off.
Metallica. Get on it. I am already on it. He's already here. Get on it. All right. Get on that.
You're in the room doing the job. When you do that, it changes our controls just to let you
please don't do that. I'm doing it so that you can get the walls you haven't gotten.
I'm doing it intelligently. What about this one? You know nothing about.
Go this way. Hey. Wow. You spilled it everywhere. It's all right. It'll take two seconds to clean
it up. I really I didn't learn the buttons yet. I figured it out. I got it. I need to be very real
here. How how is it possible that you don't understand x and a dude? What this every time
I go to do something, I press the wrong one. Well, it's just it's a to pick up x to interact.
It's a pick up x interact. I mean, even I can figure that out. You're really downplaying yourself
there. You went to college. We got 91%. What are we missing? Of course you would know how to do that.
That the right wall, the right bucket, right wall. No, the right wrong with the right wall.
No, get out. I get my I want to get the glory. Oops. Wrong way. Right wall. No, we're good.
So what's wrong? We're missing the kitchen. The kitchen's all messed up.
It's the walls. We need to peel the paper or something. What is it? Yeah, it's not yellow.
Are we missing something? Spin it around. Not yellow. Spin the walls. Wait. Oh, shit. What the
hell is it? What? What? Oh, shit. Those are those are. Oh, thank God. They looked yellow.
They looked yellow. I'm with you. The people who they're just gonna have to pay us.
Like they're the ones that want to be shadow under 120 seconds. I think that's a little
extreme. Damn. One star Redditor. Hey, when are we going to get our first three star review on Yelp?
Not until Star figures out how to press X and A separately. I'm learning. You feel like this
should be on a 3D plane, but it's not. It's just left and right. We're gonna go in the elevator.
You technically can go forward and back. It's just I'm going in. You need six stars to reach
this floor. What are we getting Mario 64 right now? Yeah, we didn't do good enough. Get good.
You one started all three of the first levels. No, we didn't. We go. Yeah, we did. No, we only
got one star on every. We only got a single star. You know what? In this day and age,
that means we're willing to work for the least amount of money. All right. I'm on trash. I'm
on trash. I'm on trash. Do something else. I'm on trash. Get out of the way. Oh my God.
Okay, I'll be the former. Take that in there. I'm on trash.
Which button? You not know the button. Okay. Are you all right? Have you eaten today?
Yes. All right. I'm the former. We need yellow walls, rights, orange walls, top.
Is there any more trash? No more trash. Okay. I'm emptying this.
Hi. Did you just like smoke weed like an hour ago? No, no, I wouldn't do that. Oh, weed jokes.
Okay. You guys seeing what's going on here? All right. Good. I'm getting the carpet. Carpet.
Ding dong. Are we ready for carpet to go in the room?
Which button is the carpet? Pay no attention to it. I need two more walls.
I'll just start doing carpet. All right. Walls should be done. We also need to make sure that
it actually goes all the way. I know what happened. Somebody went like this last time.
That's what happened. Oh, that was 100%. I can't select the carpet. Somebody went like what?
If you don't hold it all the way, if you don't have enough carpet to do the whole place,
it doesn't, you'll miss a spot. Everyone loves holding the button. You're like a no man's sky.
You have to hold the button for every menu. Like, Oh, I want to change my brightness. Hold the.
Yeah. I actually, I agree. I disagree. I do. It should just be one input. All right. Tidy up.
We got that. That's three stars. Let's go. Who is who? I said, no one asked passively.
I was throwing away all this carpet. Tidy up for left.
Oh shit. Clean that up. There's like a Cheeto puff coming out of this can. That's it. Right.
You have to tidy up. Close the door. That's the carpet on left. Yeah. It's
a button is stun locked over here. Please. Got it. We unlocked a new character. I want to be Otter
boy. All right. When I asked my chat, what kind of gay animal I was, they said I was an Otter.
How do I change? What's wrong with you? Okay. Now everyone won't mistake that I am the Otter.
Okay. Okay. Ready? Yeah. Do we have enough stars to go upstairs? No, we have three and one and one.
We have six. So what is that? How many does that add up to? I can't, where am I? Three and one and
one. We three, four, five, six. Oh no. Oh, we do have six. Let's go. What are you guys doing?
Ooh, that was solid. We're going up. Why did it go back down? Going up because apparently we all
have control of it. I press down. All right. We gotta get a three star on this one. Okay. So it's
A to press up or put down or. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on. We have to dump cement or shellac,
whatever it is, into a bucket. And then we shellac the walls. Yeah. Stick the circuit boards in there.
Put your fork directly into the socket. Open the door. Oh, do you know what button it was? Yeah.
Talk shit. Get hit. I just didn't push the button is all. Okay. Here's the, so we go. So shellac
into the bucket and then hang on. Do you want to look at the plans first? Whatever we know what
we're doing. Yeah. Shellac. Okay. Okay. Uh, cause it's orange left yellow top. Yeah, but we got a
shellac first to get rid of this brick. Okay. I'm refilled the shellac delivery. I got it. Uh, do you?
Yo, what's this house? Why is this the neighbor? Do I just, do we steal our neighbor's fucking
sherbet? What is the, I don't understand. Yo, what's in the, uh, what's in the ice cooler?
What, what walls have to be, um, orange? These ones top right. Top right is orange yellow
and then left is orange. Is it? Yeah. Well, you can look at the walls. Yeah. Hang on.
Hold on. Wait, wait. I have to steal more ice cream from my neighbor. All right. You get it.
Fixed it. What is it? Just grab it out of his hand. Two spots up here. Embarrassing. There might even
be more. I can't see cause the person left the blueprints all the way outside the house. They're
saying we fucked it. You fucked it. You fucked it. What? What happened? All right. I'm doing some
rotations. Hold your pants. Who's going to get the carpet delivery? I'm going. Why did they deliver
to the wrong address? I don't know. Maybe that is the, why would this is, I have no idea. I think
this is the second house we're making over the wrong house. These people are just like on vacation.
It's yellow carpet in here, right? I hope so. All right. What is it? I need, I need this. I don't
know. Where's the trash. We also need to, um, kind of have to rotate. All right. I got paint orange
in here. Orange. Yep. I just make sure I shell act. Okay. We'll just paint over it. They won't even
know. The people that are going to know the people that own this house 30 years from now,
they're going to peel back three layers of wallpaper. Yes. And underneath it, I will have
signed my name and then, and we'll find the bones in the basement. I somehow knew that's where that
was going. I knew that's where that was going. All right. How are we doing? I'm flipping it.
That's a better view. All right. We need the, uh, we need carpet over here. Yep. No,
something else is better. We need carpet in here. Yeah. No, no, no, no. It's already here.
What's missing from the lip? What's missing from the living room? Uh, there probably is one wall.
There's one wall that's fucked up. It's one. You're like, it's right in front of this one here.
I got it. Oh, I got it. I got it. Don't worry. Don't even worry about it. I got that.
Man, I wish it would individually score us. You can see how good I'm doing. Wrong. Wrong.
Well, paint over it. Can I say I've got that three times. Then you just let me fucking get it.
I was, I know I did just, we were just playing baseball and I was a center fielder.
Cause I can't just repaint it. You called the ball and I just fucking ran in front of you and
tried to get it and we smashed into each other and it's a highlight reel on ESPN. I know. I
understand. Just fix it. That's it. The bones are going to be you.
So what is this? Like, uh, what's the ice cream bucket for? Uh, that was the shellac. Oh.
Steal their bathtub. And instead we had to do anything about them. All right.
There's only one door left. What is it? It's been us. Two left. Go shut all the doors. Three stars.
God, I'm working with amateurs. Really? Cause you just figured out how to use the buttons.
This level needs up there. How do you delete somebody else's entire Twitch account?
I'm working on it. Wait, did I pick the wrong same one? This is same one. Quit to desktop.
No, that would be bad. That would kill three games. That would kill three different streams.
I'm shocked that, uh, Cox is holding this. I know seriously, I can't believe it.
All right. Who wants to do what? Shellac. Wait, I got it. I'm going to blueprint. You blueprint.
No, I'm going to blueprint. You blueprint. What button is it? Hey, when somebody says they have
something. Okay. Look, look pink in that room. Remember pink in that room, orange in those left
room. All right. So we need to, we have things to do first. We're going to tear shit down.
We need a trash. The trash is right here.
No, no, no. That's the shellac. That's shellac bucket. That's the shellac bucket. We don't have
any other. Hang on. We did this wrong. What do I have in my hand? Shellac. How do I shellac?
The front room needs to be shellac. We fucked it all up. Just restart it. Where's the trash bucket?
I put shellac in the trash bucket because that we only get one bucket. All right. Tear down
and put in bucket. Do we need the sofa? Um, okay. You guys are doing a great job there.
Good teamwork. Okay. All right. It is a trash. Uh, star's only using one hand. So yeah. Um,
can somebody help me? I'm back. Can I get through? I, he blocked me in here. Can you bring that
garbage over here? I'm trying to dump it. Uh, it really used some garbage. Uh, all right. What's,
what, how are we doing? What's, what's going on in the kitchen in the kitchen is just orange walls.
You got it. Okay. Orange paint is hidden in the secret garden. All right. I'll take it. I'll take
it. No, no, no. I was already there when you called me. All right. Sorry. Ready for shellac
to go dump that bucket. And then we got to shellac that bucket. I don't, I don't remember how to
shellac honestly. I'll do what you said. I can tell you right now. It's, it's either X or a,
I'm doing what you said. All right. Bring this back over here. Here we go. Put it down.
Now we can, I'm getting a delivery. Is that a couch? That's a new couch. Is this a new like
Ikea couch we have to put? No, this is tiles for this front room. I don't know how to. All right.
This room's done. Um, what, what, what next boss? Um, I don't know. Well, what, what color do these
walls be orange? Paper is right up there in your room. All right. So yellow tiles in here,
carpet up top. We've read, but how do we do the tile? You just put it down. There's that red
carpet. Are you sure you just, how do we put the, how do we put this? How do we put it down?
Yeah. Well, it's either X or a J. It's going to be one of those. I can't get this might be like,
I can't remove whatever's in my hand. He's leaving. He doesn't. Oh my God. Every button,
I'm pressing everything. I won't get this thing out of my hand. Gotta shellac the floor. Gotta
shellac the floor. Somebody was just in the way. No, you gotta shellac the floor. Do you? Wait,
I can't walk over this. Oh, fuck. Here. What are we doing? No, we have to shellac the floor. Here,
take the bucket. See, it's Alex. You can't get this out of your hand. How do you get it out of
your hand? Okay. Put A into the bucket. Recycling full? No, there's shellac in that bucket. I can't
walk over there. All right. You need, wait, somebody get the door. We all run over to get.
I'm going to shellac you in a second. Okay. Keep in mind, when you shellac, you can't walk on it
for like 10 seconds. Why did you throw everything in here? God. Okay. Why is, why are the tiles up
in the top row? Because he's been, he's throwing them. All right. Here's what we got to do. We
got to, you got to tile. Corner out. I didn't throw the tile. What? Can't walk on that. Are you
picking this up from me? No, no, no. You have to shellac the ground and you can't walk on the
floor until it's done. I know. I'm being very patient. I'm just going to watch you guys. 40
seconds. I can't put this down. Oh fuck. Don't do that. It was the only place. Okay. Thanks.
Why is it in here? Why is everything blamed on me? But it's all italics. All right. I can't move.
Somebody has to do this. Cause you did it first. I just like fell down in real life.
I like slipped and I tripped and I, my control unplugged. All right. No. God damn it.
We got eight seconds. This is bad news. We can do this one. There was a new game mechanic. How
are we supposed to know? Wow. That's a zero star. I mean, you're only as strong as your weakest link.
I was the last to fall. I wish they individually scored us. Go that way. I could prove was he ever
heard he who smelted Delta. You are protesting quite a lot right now. Unprovoked. Pick a room.
Pick a room. Everybody pick a room. Pick a room. I'm just trying to do my job. And Alex is talking
about far. I'm in this room already. Did you not hear what I just said out loud in front of like
60,000 people? Hey, who's player one? I don't know. What button is it? Okay. I need that back.
Toss that over here. Thank you. Uh, is that couch actually supposed to come out?
Probably because you can make it makes it easier. No, it's not. I mean, it would make it easier.
Yeah. I think we just have to move it out of the way. All right. Somebody help me move the couch
out of the way. There you go. There you go. All right. Now we shall act. I will dump this
bucket. It looks right in front when I was to pick it up. I don't know what to do. This isn't
realistic. It's not going when you drag it. That's because there's good movers. We already put the
little cushions underneath each leg. I don't know what to do. Someone give me a task.
All right.
We have to show you to shellac these walls with the bucket of shellac. No, you don't. That's a lie.
I lied. Uh, you have to do that in the other room down here. No, no, no. That's also a lie.
Yeah. Do this in here. You shall lack the floor. Yes. So lack the floor. Use this bucket. You can.
Okay. We'll do it. Do it in an order that we don't have to walk. I need that paint door.
It's Alex door. Well, it's Alex. I can't move. Thank you. I was a fucking, that was a good play.
I locked you. I locked me out. I'm being, um, I'm being hampered. Sometimes it has to happen.
Okay. We're totally shellacked in here. There's a traitor amongst us.
Pick up the shellac. It probably works for a rival moving company. Oh my God. I do.
I took you. Hey, what are you doing here? Five missions to figure it out.
Did delivery guy just throw that? Or did you throw that? He walked into it and moved it.
Okay. We've got this paint that needs to come in here. All right. This couch is done.
Pink paint needs to go up on the walls. Carpet done. Yep. Let's get, I'll get this out of here.
Pink paint. And then we got to tile this floor. All right. Tiling is going to come last.
What about the orange paint? You guys already do that? I got orange in the left room.
All right. Let's let me check the blueprint. And I got pink in the top room.
Just the living room. That's it. Living room. We got to tile this room.
I didn't know that I couldn't walk over the tile. I completed it. We're good. Tidy up.
Start taking things outdoors. I got the tile. We got to move the couch back. Don't we?
Oh, I think it should be fine. Move, move, move, move, move.
Where's the red? Get him in the same room. That's you're walking pretty far to do that.
Now you can't get out. It's a 200 IQ play because we did two at the same time.
Yeah. But now he can't leave. Shut that door. Yeah. See, I got to shut the door anyway.
That's what I'm saying. Now he can't leave. He can't leave. He did it the wrong. He did it
from the wrong side. I didn't do that. Who did that? What? Wait, don't you left the tiles?
No, no, it's not worth it. Throw it out. Oh, almost. That was close. Look at my whiskers.
Can we go up the next floor? Are we allowed to go up yet? I knew that was the first thing I knew
it was going to happen. I'm supposed to be in control right now. It's not fair.
Oh wow. We all got an achievement unlock except only German gets it. The greedy guy that he is.
I think we just broke the game. I don't think we're supposed to be up here. So you need 15
stars to be able to be allowed up here. Maybe we have exactly 15 stars to be up here. We're
doing great. Oh boy. All right. Why are they delivering to us in a moat? All that stuff is
ruined. Important stuff coming down the river. Oh man. This is getting to the point where you
have to try, isn't it? All these sweaty try hard games. We have to try now. Wait, what did I just
do? I just wanted a relaxing game where I could chat with my friends and they have to turn it
into like an exercise. You know, games are supposed to be like enjoyable. It's funny coming from the
e-sports player. Who's that? Oh, I accidentally pressed the wrong button and now I have this
handful of paint that I can't do anything about until the paint comes around again.
All right. What room do we start in? Imagine your house is made of grass. All right. We should
probably just restart right now. This room sucks. It's the ugliest fucking room I've ever seen. We
don't have a single tool. All right. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it. No, you try hard.
We've been sitting around for a full minute. I was doing shit. All right. I have saved.
Just made a second pile. Okay. Trash, trash, trash, trash, trash, trash, trash.
We got to shellac this room. You got to put a carpet in that room. Which room?
Hang on. We got more stuff coming down the pipe. Bring some deliveries out here.
All right. House is clean. We got to shellac this patio. Shellac the patio. You got it. Let's go.
Tear it up. Which room needs to be yellow or orange? This one. This one, which also needs to
be shellac. I can't get through the carpet. I don't like this shellacking mechanic right now,
I got to say. Well, it's only going to get harder from here. So I, what did you do? Okay. Well,
hey, could you open the door for me, please? This is mine. And this one. Thank you.
What goes on the patio? The tiles? Have they been delivered by the moat yet or no?
Do tiles last? Go up there. Hopes. I'm murdered.
Delete the ladder. Make him suffer. Okay. One button. I love this.
All right. We need to turn this. Well, a secret carpet in here.
There's still a couple of things I need to throw in that bucket. Okay. Do it. Well,
you want the carpet to go. I think the carpet goes in on the patio where the pool is.
What? Living room, kitchen, patio, carpet. I think it's actually patio carpet.
How do I shellac these? What? No, you did this. No, you just have to pull them up.
Now. Okay. The shellac is for another room. Okay. I'm losing it, dude. The kitchen
needs to have orange paint and needs to be shellacked and orange paint. I will go start
that process. This is, I believe this is the kitchen. It is not the kitchen. There's one more.
You got it. All right. I'm going to take a look at the plants. Kitchen needs to be shellacked.
We need to hit these walls, paste. Does that mean this room's walls are not supposed to be painted
or that one more? All right. We got a bunch of empty blue walls in that bottom right.
What room am I standing in right now? What is it? Was this the, is this the bedroom? What is this?
It's, it's really room. What if I told you that any room could be any room, depending on what
furniture you put in. Oh, I, I accidentally brought all of the stuff into this room.
Sorry. Alex is the kind of guy to put carpet on a patio.
We got a shellac this wall. Shellac here. He'll put you to fill the shellac bucket.
So we're done with the orange paint, right? I'm going to start cleaning up. Okay. We got a minute
50. We got two times. That's fine. How do I? Oh, okay. You filled it up. Good job.
Now we paste. I'm going to check the blueprint. Make sure we didn't miss anything in any of these
other rooms. It's the kitchen is at 0% by the way. How's that possible? Hey, can you improve
your upload speed a little? Why is my upload speed bad? No, it's just, it's like, I think it's just
that screen. It's just being mean. Uh, I was getting like 480 P for a second. Can you make
you like, can you make, can you make our internet better? All right. What do we need to do? That's
not a yellow wall. Is it yellow? No, it's orange. Just paint. Yeah. Yeah. Every time you do the
blueprint screen to me, it's like taking on, putting off glasses, putting on, taking off glass.
Yeah. Putting on, taking off. This wall needs it for the otter spinning. Are we done? That's it.
Tiny up. And you thought this one was going to be hard. We have plenty of time. This one was an
easier one. Throw it all in the river. Would they know? I think they know. Do they know?
Four left. It comes around to the side. Go up top left, top right, go top right, bottom right.
What? It's in the river. I think it counts. Does it count? I got it. I got it. I'll grab it.
Well, it's on this side, the bottom right. It's not going to come around. It kept getting flipped.
Is it just you? Wait, am I the trash? Are you? Can you come out of here?
Just shut the door. Oh, it's me. I'm the trash. All right. We got three stars for that one.
When did we get our ultimate? I'm sure there'll be another game mechanic. That's interesting. Hold on.
See, unlike games with ultimates, this one's balanced.
Okay. Paints. That didn't mean anything. This game doesn't have ultimates.
Okay. Seriously. I'm going to take a two minute break. I don't want to be a...
Man down, man down, man down. I think I'm going to have a cigarette. I'll be right back.
Where's the junk? Where's the trash? I have the junk at the top left.
Hey, where's the trash? I have the trash at the top left.
Stop removing doors. I need it to be done. It was in the way. Well, I'm just manually
manually going back and forth. How do you put doors back? You just hit A.
Oh, there's three buttons. All right. So the top left needs to be painted.
Hey, just click their head. Okay. Okay. Where is it? Oh, I got a lot of trash in here. You guys
have hogged the trash bucket the whole... God damn it. I'm bringing the trash to you now.
You could just like not do trash right now. Or I could just mute and go like
cough for five straight minutes to get this out of me. It's like something in my body.
You brought the trash to me. You still walked outside. Can you take commands from anyone?
Don't tell me what to do. You're a stoa. Carpet. Carpet. Top left. So what goes on bottom right?
Green paint. Hold on. Green paint, green tile. Green paint, green tile. Got it. What do you think
this is? All right. This rich asshole who has a tree in his house. Who has a tree in their house
and a moat around the tree. I think it just is the tree's house. This is just where they live.
Do we have to do anything with the floor first? No, it's already. It's already been slapped.
Let's actually. Oh, I'm barred from entry here. Sorry. What's left? That's a trash bin right now.
All right. Let me see. How are we doing? I like how you're not supposed to walk on this,
but as long as you just walk on it first, you're fine. Just that bedroom. This just needs that
carpet. And then that's it. Then tidy up. Start tidying up. What needs carpet? The room he's in
right now. We're done after that. That's not carpet. That's tiles. That's it. Tidy up. Fix
that door. Bedroom. Is it a wall that's not painted in the bedroom? Are you going to throw that real
good? Stop. That's the word. So what are we missing? Which room is it? It's the green room.
There must be one walls. Yeah, that's what I was looking for. And he told me to stop.
One of them. Oh, it's that one. I mean, it looks great. It looks great.
Sorry. Sorry. The guy's in the way who's housework. Hey, I can't see past the tree.
Okay. Here we go. All right. It's five stars. Well done. I don't think you need to close the door.
Oh, dog. Anyone want to be dog? We got the dog looks overpowered. It does kind of.
I've overpowered you mean huge and probably in the way.
So how come I feel disproportionate? I'm the only one who can paint tall walls and reach.
Stop going down. Nobody's doing that on purpose. Yes, he is. What do you mean?
I'm not doing it. I'm going to get blamed and it's him. It's not me. There's no way that's not
being done on purpose. It could be German. He doesn't know. All right. What do we have to do?
It's done. Hey, let me move this. Let's move the chaise lounge.
That room needs blue carpet. This room needs tile and that's it. That's it.
Is it? Yeah. That's it. I mean, it's a huge room though. I think it's because it's so separated.
Let's wait for delivery. There's a big wall right there. We'll start pulling it up.
We got to like throw stuff. I got the chalacum. Get out of here. All right. So we have
to start pulling up tile. Oh, there's a secret slipper there. We need that trash bucket in here.
We need to work together ripping it up. Somebody said only one room in this house is actually
inside. What? Because he's a tree bathroom. It's got to be the case. You've got to set it down.
Not whip it. Everyone get prepared. Carpet. Get that excellent German on 85 branded carpet.
All right. We basically just have to throw stuff over the wall a lot. I think it's raining and
it's making random things on the ground. Yeah. This person's house is outside. Yeah. What a shitty
house. Nothing we can do to save it. All right. Do we need trash in any other room? I don't think
so. We don't have the green tile yet. We're going to do the other room. We don't have the green tile
yet. Can you flip it by the way? This is a dog shit view. All right. Green tiles here. Wait,
we got to do. We got to do shit. We have to shellac it. I'll get I got I got I got I got I got it.
Toss it on. Oh, all right. Put it in. Who said that I didn't do anything this whole stream? I did
that right there. I'm done. I don't think anybody said that. I think you're just like projecting a
little. Why are you throwing it back at me? I don't need it. Well, maybe I will actually.
I didn't realize that that's such a limited quantity. Oh, all right. Don't get out of here.
Ice. Oh, okay. Wait. Whoops. I can go down here in a minute. All right. Then we did do that carpet.
You're doing the tile up there. Good shit. I think I'm all tiled up. All right. I'm going to put this.
We're going to go what corner out. That was just returning. Yeah, I wasn't sure if I missed those
or not. But look at the power of teamwork, everybody. You just put aside your differences.
Can you imagine that this would take 100% longer if it was just me in this room and not you here
too? You think about that? Like I'm fucked up. That is I'm thinking about like why does it take
two hours to put one table together when you pay people to do it? Do they not know the instructions
ahead of time? Why does it cost like a hundred and fifty dollars? This is my favorite comment
of the night so far. Oh, this is going too well now. Resident sleeper. Oh, no. Now they like,
they get it. No. Wait, there's something missing here. One blue carpet and a little green wall
is missing. One blue carpet. Yeah. Where? In between the trees. Oh, that's it. Any wet spots?
It's going way too swell. Dude, we got to install wacky mods. Basically beat the game.
Three stars. Oh, mega low clap. No, that was resident sleeper clap. I just pretended it.
Look at how hard this one looks. Does the guy have clown outfit rooms?
Okay. We've got new type of tile. I think we have to shellac shellac. So shellac this whole thing.
It's only these. Honestly, you asked me to play this game with you and it feels like I agreed to
chores and I didn't realize it. Yeah. But didn't you also play this or clean up detail? Oh, and
he, he hated it and he left the, he left, he abandoned the game and left the stream.
Yes. So that did happen. Well, we played for a bit, but I mean, I mostly just dragged all
the dead bodies into one room. Refuses to do chores. Yep. Sounds like a professional streamer.
Definitely a professional. What are these barrio blocks? These are locked. I don't understand. Why
is this locked? It's like, it's a locked information block. I don't get it. Why do we have so many
flower packs? What's the new thing? Why do you, why are you carrying around gasoline?
We might have to mix this stuff. It might be glue because it looks like there's wallpaper.
All right. Well, let's keep, what was this thing for trash? Do I think we have to like sift the
flower in there? Let's find out. All right. It's supposed to, it tells you the instructions.
It's shellac plus paint shellac plus carpet. Carpet. That's it. Yeah. I think we're over
complicated. There has to be like a second step though, because we have like these big flower bags.
No, I think there's just, this place is full of garbage. I think it's just trash. Yeah,
it's just trash. All right. We do only have one bucket though, I think.
Yes. Pick a spot up here and just, you're going to throw like a 30% full bucket away.
Inefficient. Dude, I'm trying to use the bucket for the like paste. What we got,
we're on one job in here. Finish this one first. But the trash can's like right there.
Okay, just put it in. What, what is this? Hey. This is, Star sees how long it takes for us to
notice that he stopped working in the, I think. Sorry, I took a drink like one time in an hour.
Listen, you're only as good as you're weak as Link. Or so I've been told. I took, I took a drink.
I took like a sip of soda. Get back to work, you fucker. I just want this to be as realistic
as possible. That's not efficient use of your time. Listen, you only get one break a day. Get back in
there and go to work. Yeah, you're lucky I'm not taking all the fucking doors off right now.
I'll do it. Zip. Okay, so what do we actually need here? What are we doing? What's going on?
We're both trying to do the same thing. All right, we got a minute 55 to do everything.
And what do we have to do? We just have to, we have to paste all the floors.
All of them? All in the left. We got to paste them all? Start in the back. What the fuck?
No, we don't. What? No, we just have to roll the carpet down. This is the only room we had to do.
Which room do we have to paste? We have to do the hallway. We're at zero percent. You're saying
we're done. Look, look, look, look. We have the hallway and then the storage room. The hallway,
every single one of these walls needs to be done in a minute. You're going to do that? Yeah,
you got a minute. Take another sip of your drink, you piece of shit.
We're failing. Yeah, there's no way we're going to be able to do this. Well, we're at 20 percent
now. We'll get one star on this one. So what is the shellac? That's okay. That's all we had to
begin with. Why do we have shellac here? I think we're done with it. The wall in here needs to
just be pink. Let's go. But we have to tear down the wallpaper. What do we have for percentage?
45, 50. Where's the garbage? Down the bottom. It's just a shellac bucket right now.
Well, I'll take care of that. Here, here, here, here, here. We don't need the shellac
for anything anymore, right? Right. 20 seconds. Paint as many walls as you can.
Why did they spawn this back in the same room that I was in with?
Please just put this down. 10 seconds. We're almost done. Bottom left, bottom left, bottom left.
I'm going to throw all the garbage in the neighbor's house. One, zero. Wait, what? How
do we get one star? The hallway was at zero. How? Did we paint it wrong? Maybe it's because we
didn't finish. We'll do it again. Oh, I'm just going to start removing things. Yes, just throw,
just start. That's first. Start getting rid of trash. All right, trash in the left room.
I'm going to, I'm going to tear down these walls. Gorbachev, Gorbachev, Gorbachev.
This carpet is here. Trash upper left. Carpet is here. Ain't that the truth? Why can't I just
throw this into the street? Yeah, what button is it? All right, the peel has been peeled.
Have you guys seen this otter? Do you want another drink, Rick? They gave us too many
paints to confuse us. That's the problem. Yeah, they wanted to test your foreman skills.
What if your color blind? Do we have all these? Okay, we're going in here now. Are you having
fun in here in this bottom left room? How am I falling down? Stupid fucking Minecraft mystery
block. Get the fuck out of here. Does Minecraft have mystery blocks now? It's been a while since
I played. To clean this up. All right, all the trash has been removed from the house. Incorrect.
We have the trash in this room on the floor. This fucking wrapping paper up here. Hold on,
I'll get it. Oh my word. This whole hallway is full of trash. I'm going for it. I'm getting
everything. Wow. It was 200 IQ to put all the trash in front of the recycling bin. Now I can't
get to it. I can't get to the recycling. All I hear right now is milk me. Listen, you're not
getting any of this paycheck. All right, so what do we need? Do we need pink carpet? I think we
just did it wrong. Where's the blueprint? Give me that. With three minutes. Hallway needs to have
pink walls, which is almost done. There's one thing missing somewhere. The storage room needs
to be ground. It has to be orange, not pink. And these walls on the bottom left need to be like
purple. Do we even have a, what color was it? Purple? No, just the ground. Yeah, that's it.
Now we just, we have to just do the carpet on the, oh fuck my mouth. Don't do that. Which
character are you? He's the one that just fell and broke his jaw on one of the counters. Which one
am I? You scared the shit out of me. I'm sorry. There are five different paints. I wasn't even
looking. That was so confusing. People in tabs are just like, wait, what just happened? Don't
read chat. They don't have anything interesting to say anyways. There's two. All right. If this
is a one star, we have to turn off this game. It's not going to be a one star. If we one star
this one, this game, this game's getting turned off. If you're not watching at all, you just like,
what, did he like bite down on a colonel? Can someone help this guy? And particularly could it
not be me? We just, we just do orange carpet. Oops. Just fight over the carpet. See? Hey,
we did it. This is a dirty ass house. Not anymore. It's not outside. There's something else. Uh,
we're missing one thing. Uh, no, we're missing a couple of things. Is it the outfit on the wall?
I'm going to rotate. Ah, fuck it. You're two of them. Yeah. I count as one.
What's the other one? Um, is that wall supposed to look like that? I guess so. Two left. What is
it? It's not on the wall. Shut the doors. I don't know. I don't know. Oh, I don't know.
It's not too close to the front. Mop it up. I didn't see anything. Yeah. I didn't see anything
either. It was, it had flushed the toilet. I think he had to plunge to the toilet. I mean,
we all took a shit in there, right? All wait. All of us. Yeah. And that five minutes without,
oh my God, we powered through. Is it an outhouse? Hey, okay. Okay. Pay attention.
You have to paint a wall with glue and then wallpaper. All right. So shellac wallpaper done.
Oh, now it's a different season. Uh, yeah, that's a ice mechanic. I was trying to throw you in,
but it didn't work. You now slip. Do we have a bucket? All right. Clean up. Clean up. Clean up
first. I have a question. Yes. Why would you want your house to be ice? Where like a cartoon land?
Say that word again. Cartoon land. I'm done. I'm done. I don't want to hear it. Okay. So living
rooms. I don't, there's too many things. I'm not the four minute. I can't think. My brain is dead.
Just give me a task and I'll do it. All right. Give us both a task. Uh, we got carpet carpet.
Where's purple carpet go? Purple carpet goes top right, top right. And the walls need to be done
up with the currently existing in the same room, purple tubes. So top right is purple.
The top right is purple. Top left also needs to be purple walls, but they need to be painted.
So top right is not paint. I'll wait till you're ready. We also need green carpet at the bottom.
I got it left. Purple paint on the walls. It hurts. I didn't know how long it was going to take. I knew
it was going to, I didn't know how long it was going to take. Talking shit. You messed it up.
I'm the floor is ice. I'm sorry. Green carpet. All right. Now we do this on the walls.
So we need that bucket back up here. Okay. But can I like empty it first?
Um, we already did. All right. Now we do the walls. Ooh, I like that. That's um,
Oh God, it goes away. No, maybe that means it just dries. Yeah. So you have to like paste it and then
put the, Oh shit. I got, I got you. I got you. I got you. You paint. Purple's down here. Purple's
down here. I got it. All right. Bring the purple up here. I'm going to paint and you go. Hold on.
I'm going to bring it closer. Oh no. No, that's no. Okay. I don't know why I thought you were
going to paint over the whatever. All right. I got the top left room because you're dumb.
I didn't know how long it was going to take. I don't know how long it was going to take,
but you're fucking dumb. Got them. You're going to see a couple of E he's. It'll be fun.
Wouldn't that be so funny if you did like a Keck. All right. This room is done. Get out of here.
I'm looking too long. It was targeting the thing next to it, even though I was very clearly not
looking at that thing. What a dope. Okay. Here you go. You ready? No, no, no. I got to get
rid of this trash because you've spilled something. Don't mind me. Just sneak it in. Here we go.
One more on this side. There's two more over here actually. Get it together. Do you guys remember
the nineties? I'm pretty sure he still does that. Pretty sure he does too. He's still currently
touring. That's it. That's it. We've got the ice didn't even matter. Be careful what you wish for.
And five left. All right. What else? What else? What else? What else? What else? What else?
I can't wait to wait to the lava mansion. The sexy magma girl, new animal. What is it? A llama?
Sure. I want to be that. How do I switch characters like this? Oh, who's going to be,
you're going to be the llama. All right. Be the dog. Now this is even weirder. Wait, which one am I?
You're the otter. Oh, now this is a cartoon. You've been extolling the virtues of being the otter.
All right. We did this. We can go up another level. Isn't it cool how like the otter gets
bonus stats in the water levels? Wow. It's got an achievement for Game of Thrones. Yeah. I got that
too. A song of ice and fire or something, right? Song of fire and snow. What's this one? I told you
to be careful what you wish for. All right. I'm getting the couch. Quote, the ice didn't even
matter. I would spin this because like this is a terrible angle. What's that noise? I can't,
we can't get in there. It's messed up. We have to go all the way around. I think. No, we don't.
Where am I? Which one am I? I actually got lost up there. Okay. Okay. Ready? I can't pick it up.
There it is. Where does this even go? Outside? How do we? Hold on. Let me open the door.
All right. Turn. It's ice. Oh, yeah. It is ice. Why? Why? There's three people.
Just leave it in here. Just throw me. Throw me. I'll get it. Throw me. Throw me. I am pushing
the throw button. Throw me. Oh, my God. Reset. Okay. Purple carpet. Oh, my God. You just told
me to do that. He told him. I thought you could like read. You just said restart, restart, just
do it. And I'm like, okay, why wouldn't we? Restart. Restart it slow. Restart it slow. Well,
now I know you're being fucking dope. Facetious. All right. What's the first room we're doing?
Okay. Fuck the couch. We don't. Seriously. It's wasting time.
Restart. You didn't get a good enough job. Why can't you read sarcasm?
Okay. I'm going to start in. What do we even need to do? We have to. The couch is the only
thing to do right now, unless there's trash. Is there like a trash room? No, there's a
trash bucket at the bottom, right? We need to take the wallpaper off in this room.
How do like, I'm not even mentally present. All right. Trash it up. Oh, we have to move
that couch because it's blocking the door where the deliveries come. All right. What are we doing
with this? I'm going to dump this. It won't let me. I'm going to get any more trash I need to pull
up. I don't think so. So bring that. We need to paste the walls. Leave it on the front porch.
I'll get it later. Don't make me sign for concrete. Throw that glue over here. Which
one of these rooms needs to be purple? Where's the blueprint? Okay. Purple is probably. Check
blueprint. I got it. Purple's left. So this room has to be this room here. The bottom left is
striped. Bottom left is striped and this is just paint. Dude, can you guys deliver it all at once
next time? Or I'm going to, I don't, what am I doing? You're accepting deliveries. You're doing
a great job. What do I do now that I've accepted the deliveries? Now what you're going to do is
you're going to do, go to the, you're going to get the glue. You're going to fill a, this bucket
next to me. All right. Get that paint bucket up at the top and then go to the bottom right room.
Take that and fill that with glue. And then you're going to slack the bottom left and then shrink
it and then don't come to work tomorrow. Honestly, that's all very doable. Are we done with the
paint? I think we're done with the paint. Is this room supposed to be purple carpet? That's supposed
to be green paint on the walls in the lower right. Lower left is shellac and where's the carpet go?
Yes. You're correct with what you're describing. I'm going to, you didn't mix, you didn't even do it.
I didn't, I didn't do it. There's a lot of cleaning up. There's ice. I had to get two deliveries.
You just throw me under the bus after I had to walk uphill in the ice both ways to get to the
front door. I actually did. I actually did though. Fucking goddamn fucking idiot. Fucking stupid.
Fucking goddamn. All right. You ready? I didn't do this job before, so I don't.
Oh, this burst is too big. No, it's just trashed. I'm wearing one of those tacky
tourist outfits for Halloween. Okay, shellac. It looks like an inflatable. I'll clean this up.
All right. Okay. Can you help me paste the walls and I will put the wallpaper over the paste?
I don't have anything I can do, so I'm just going to clean. Star, you've made a real mess about
time. Pick up the paste. No, I need that. Okay. Sure. This room is so tiny and shitty.
All right. How about you can't target the things you want to do. Can somebody come?
Star, where are you going with that? Shut up. You're supposed to be pasting. I'm cleaning.
I'm cleaning this fucking room. Hey, you don't just put it in another spot. I'm ready.
Okay. You need me to paint. Yeah, I need you to do the paste. What do you think you're doing
down there? We're going to have to get a saline IV going in you. My brain doesn't work this late
in the day. This is like two more. I should have been bed an hour. Hey, hey, hey. What? There's
two more? This is not trash? Yep. What are you doing? I need that spit in your mouth like you
want me to do to you. Hey, can you come back and paste these? Where are you going? Why are you
running in a circle with a blueprint? I was getting it out and I was avoiding something in front of
you. Okay. Top two only. All right. Ready? 23 seconds. Get out of the way. Get out of the room.
Just get out of the room. You're just messing it all up. Go. Clean it. Okay. I got it.
I swear you were an obstacle for that level. There was a moving block that was just getting
in the way. 2.9 stars. That's fine. I tried my best. We haven't done this one. No. That was a
big one. That was a big one. That was a big one. This game needs a scoreboard. You know, I don't
like the snow levels. If that's supposed to be me, you're doing a very good job. Oh, wait. This is
a three-parter. Okay. We got purple carpets, strike purple walls, and then we need special
blue walls. Yeah. Wallpaper. I'll take that. Thank you. What do we have to do? I'll take care
of this. You guys wait for another delivery. Just hang out and talk. I need that puke bucket.
What do I have to talk to italics about? Yeah, right. Star Wars or something. Don't knock that
over. Don't knock that over. Don't dare. He probably likes the last Jedi, so it's okay.
I do not. Oh, boy. Oh, there you go. Oh, boy. Name a game that I like that came out like the last
five years. Name a game. Dwarf game. Dwarf game? Yeah. Dwarf Miner shooting game. That game was
okay. He did it. Yeah, you like that. I'm going to get that delivery, please. Minecraft. Did Minecraft
come out in the last five years? Yeah, I think so. Like 1.0. We got to get glue going in the top
left. Not before we have all the trash removed up here. That's not trash. Don't dare come in here
and start doing things. Is this not the purple carpet room? No, it is. Sorry. I really flew up
the handle there. Sorry about that. I just threw it in the garbage. All right. Now we can put paste
in here. Okay, we need to paste the top left room and we need to paste the bottom left room
different colors. That's like all we have, I think. Is there anything else to do? Let's check.
Carpet. There's only going to be one paste, so we can only do one room at a time. Yeah. Yep.
So one person is non-essential. So I'm just going to, you know, I'll not be the obstacle this time.
I just don't want to get yelled at. All right, we'll do this room first. I mean, you could just
put the paste in your mouth and just spit it into the wall and then do it. It wouldn't be too hard.
All right, let's start in the big corner. You know what? If you guys need to rotate, call in
the AC 130. Listen, this paste holds the wallpaper in place. If you put it in your mouth, maybe it'll
hold your lips in place. Alex, what are you doing? Are you happy with anyone?
I'm just sitting out there. You're sitting out there like the newspaper rolled up.
How do you live with him? You're trying to, you're trying to like,
wait, uh-oh, there's a little hoopsie over here. Wait, where are you going? I have to throw this
away because we have to use that bucket of paste and AFK player is just outside. I explained that
there is nothing for me to do. You know what? I did read that this game doesn't scale based on how
many people you're playing with, so it's not any easier or harder. There, I gave you something to
do. Okay, thank you. Which wall are we on? Thank you for any of them. What just happened?
Why is this trash now? What? Uh, I think you put the, I don't know. It must've gotten empty.
We got two men. Okay, we got playing time. Oh my God. You haven't even done this one room yet.
So paste. Let's go. There you go. Now put it on the wall. Don't look at me. Nice work.
We have just got to stuff in the corner and that's it for this one, right? You need to glue this
entire room down here with that. Okay. And then that's it. Well, how about you do that? There's
the glue. And I'll tidy up. I mean, I just want you, I want you to participate. So I'll fill it
up for you. Ready? See? There we go. Now I'm going to move over here and I'm going to be ready.
Wait, I'm, hold on. I'm working overtime here. Sorry. I took your job there. Uh, can we get a
rotate champ? What is that? Hey, champ, can you give us a rotate? He wants you to go pick up the
thing and move the thing, pick up the thing and move it. Oh, turn the camera. Thanks champ. You
guys need it again. Let me know. I think we're going to need it again here in a second, champ.
What are you doing? All right. Let's tidy up. All right. Everybody back it up. That's a day's work
all in a day's work. You fucking guys are so bad at this game. Like I'm missing dinner now.
How do you still have that from so long ago? That's so, you know what? I hope in a hundred
years, somebody digs up your XLR or whatever it is and plays that. It'll, it'll be on there.
Oh, we're not good enough. We need three more stars. Well, we can go back to floor one. Yes.
We were terrible. That's true. We could get, we did miss at least two plus stars.
Oh, these are, these are going to be the real baby hours. 10,000 years from now. That's the
only evidence of humanity. Don't alt tab is what I've learned. Why? Cause it like, if you're doing
this broadcast thing, it like freezes your feet. Oh yeah. This is, look at how dog shit this is.
One star. This is my bedtime. Did you know that? What? For third, five 30. It's five. Yeah.
On the West coast, but over here, it's six 30. It's so no, hold on. No, it's five 30 there.
All right. What do we have to do? Guys, we're supposed to get three stars. I'm looking at
the clock. It's, it's actually six 30 here. Oh yeah. It's, it's weird. It's still very early.
What time do you wake up? Like noon. You go to bed at six 30. You wake up at noon.
He's got six good hours a day. I was, I was going to say that's like left to yellow, not orange,
orange bottom. Looks like kicked it. All right. We start pulling stuff up. I'll get the trash.
I'll get this door. Grab that back to this. Back is the question. How did we manage to one star this
because this is still, this is one star. Didn't know how to X what's going on here.
Someone get the door, please. All right. We got this here. Any more trash, all the stuff on the
floor. Can I have that? Okay. Put it right in the door. Nice. How did we manage to one star this
Mr. Disruption? All right. Yeah. You just do it. It'll be easier. I think close the door. It'll
probably help. No, it's the door. Yeah. I'll just apparently we got paint. We got paint. Get the
paint. We got paint. Go get the paint. Let me go. Oh, this is not. Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding
me. Just trade you. Okay. All right. We got orange paint here. We need, we need that trash bucket
again. We need the trash bucket. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. Oh, you get it. You're going
down there already. You're closest. Doss it over here. I wonder how we didn't do this for the last
time. There's two minutes, but you calm down. I didn't say anything. I just replayed that part of
the screen. You fucking guys are so bad at this game. He didn't get a go XLR sponsor. So he just
has to do it for like by his memory. Have you even used that in its board's intended purpose?
What is its intended purpose? I thought it was for you to that wasn't what the joke was that you
play that while you were like mad at Overwatch. Oh, well, no. Back in the day, I was using it to
record other people who were mad at Overwatch. Right. So I gave you a I'm mad at Overwatch clip
and you haven't used it. I did use it during that was like a long time ago. We don't get three stars.
Okay. Can you peel this? Thank you. Now on your way out, just scoop that up on your way out.
Scoop. Did you not shut the door? Thank you. What are we missing?
What are we missing? We only have 42 seconds. We have 40 seconds. What? Are we stupid? The kitchen.
The kitchen wall? I don't see anywhere. Did we paint the wrong room? No. Tiny wall.
Can we get that paint that we're not going to get three stars. Where's the tiny wall?
Oh, I see it. Oh, I see it too. Oh, wow. Okay. Good.
It's two minutes. We got plenty of time. Yeah. We missed one, one fourth of a wall.
Quickly now. We got this. We learned nothing. Yeah. I know. I hope so. Well, at least no one can say
this is going well anymore. You know, that doesn't help very much because I have to set it down.
Shut up. I just now I'm looking at you with a shocked. Whoa. What the heck? I just threw a
bucket. It's like into like through a roof for you. That doesn't help very much. It's like,
where's the awe? What do you mean? Oh, like, isn't like, oh, oh, why would there be an awe?
No, like shock and awe, not like, oh, oh, I thought you meant like, I threw that bucket in for you.
Oh, you did that for me? No. Well, thanks anyways, though. Shock and awe. Well, you spelled something
over here. I did that. No, I. What button is it? Oh, I got it. Well, she's a real jack.
All right. We got plenty of time now. Seriously, like you didn't even paint this one wall.
Come on. This is where this is where we start making mistakes. No, you got the paint. I'm
going to get this trash. I'm bringing the mango ice cream. You may want to get the bucket that's
outside because I'm just. Well, it's all right. It's all right. You guys just can handle that.
I can handle it. All right. We get we got the small wall right off the bat. But good, good,
good. I hope I never see this level again. I hope I do. In fact, we might because there's still
another wall. Let me help you. Ninety five. I got it. I got it. I got it. Stop.
Stop. If we're just trying to go and do something and then the whole world rotates.
What's left? Would you guys leave up here? When did you leave this three left? Hold on. Wait,
hang on. It's well, there's only one thing left. Let me rotate the whole world.
Rotate the world. Rotate the world. Please don't do this to me. How does this keep happening?
Where is it? Trash outside. Does that count? Does it? It does. It does count. The trash on the
porch. All right. Do we have enough with thirty two? We need one more star.
We need a single. Yes, just one. Let's do level one. Level one. Level one.
This game's got a lot of replay ability. All right. I bet you could do this by yourself.
That's it. It just needs a pink wall. I think you know how much you've grown
in just a short amount of time. We didn't. We couldn't figure this out in
more than three foldments. It doesn't tell you the buttons.
How many furries does it take to paint a wall? As many as you want. One could do it probably in
a week if you skidded it kind of casually. What I want to know is how we finished it but
didn't get three stars. I see. That's how I think that might answer your question.
How much spill is there? It's a never ending spill. How did that? I pressed A to drop it
and it spilled. All right. We can continue and do the progression into the elevator.
We're about to unlock a new character, guys. What is it? I want to be an F-16 jet.
Oh. One too high. How could we all be facing the wrong direction? All right. We go this way. Wait.
To the left and then up. Oh. Unlocking number 13. Uh oh. Uh oh.
This is a real hotel. There wouldn't even be a number 13. What the hell are we supposed to do here?
I'm finding that info out. We are supposed to be... Oh, it's a mixy match. Yeah, it's a... And
there's slits and there's couches. Good thing we have plenty of time. Is there even a bucket?
Where's a bucket? We have nothing. There's no bucket. Oh, there's that bucket. Pretty brushes
to the door. Is it for me? Does it have my name on it? Okay, you joke but that's real life.
Which package is the opt? I have experienced that here in this house. Yeah, we just have to
peel off the stuff one by one. What a great treat, you know, for holidays to just do
repetitive tasks with your friends. That's what Christmas is all about.
Some of my favorite games are games where I just have to like paint a house.
Unironically, House Flipper is one of my favorite video games. You just like suck up bugs and
vacuum cleaners and stuff. You just clean up a house and shit. Viscer cleanup detail. That's
one of my favorite games. You just clean a house. I'm seeing a pattern. So would you say like the
big game companies are trying too hard and they just need to make like house cleaners? And that's
the next genre. Like it was like Minecraft, like Survival, Battle Royale, Cleaner. Yes.
Is next. Yes. I don't know. Are they trying too hard or are they not trying hard enough?
If there was like a hundred million dollar budget House Flipper type game,
I would, that's all I would do. And it's like an MMO and you get to flip your houses to other
gamers and then they get to live in the house. All right, are you painting the right walls here?
I painted one wall and it was the right wall. I'm just going to keep this up.
No, because then we can't. No, it just alternates. So how hard is it to alternate? I don't know.
Somebody, what about the walls we can't see? Listen, if our eyes are real. Okay. Okay. Got it.
Okay. Okay. Mirrors be real. I'm going to do a rotate. Is everyone ready for a rotate?
25 seconds. All right. Go. Somebody didn't kill this paint off. How are we ever going to get
you say someone didn't kill this paint off, which is like just an accusatory way. Like none of us
did it. It could have been someone didn't. It could have been me. Yeah. That's all right.
What do we do? Someone didn't get the door. No one. Do we do? You're trying to put the blame on
one or purple purple. Yeah. I'm trying to put the blame on one person. It could have been me.
I'm that one person that could have been me. That's no, that sounds like backtracking from
your PR department. No, no, that's some somebody didn't do this. We need to rotate.
I'm going to start cleaning up. Is there anything to clean up? You see one more purple wall, right?
Is that account for like, well, we're not even done. Our progress is not good. Are you sure?
I knew it was reversed. You were so sure though. I was. What do you mean reverse?
Yeah, these are wrong. I was so sure. What? But yeah, yeah, I fucked us. Oh, I fucked us all.
It's almost as if having the blueprint. One of us made a mistake here. One of us. Somebody
did something wrong. Not sure who it was, but one of us. Somebody made a mistake. I think then this
I think then this wall is also wrong. 94. I'll spit it. Got to be purple. Purple on the empty
spot on the left. If anybody wants to move, you could do it. No, I'll get it. It's fine.
Oh, you got it. Get those paint cans. One, two. Yeah. Three stars. Listen, if we got personal
scores, mine would be highest. That's I don't mean that's a koala. Hey, that last one on the
end. Is that exoskeleton buglionian boy? I want to be the outline. You can't just have the new one
every single time. Yes, I can. All right. Let's just make it confusing. We'll all be koalas. No,
no, no, no, no, no. All koalas the same color. Star. I know. As I said, my body type is an otter.
I can't be the one you are. Oh, you can't be the same one. Oh yeah. I can be any other one though.
You're just confusing people. All right. I'll be the dog again. Fine. I'll be this one.
I'll look at the vanity here. We need 37 to go up that floor, by the way. Of course.
Oh, there's a door open. Oh, there is? Oh yeah, there is. Number 14. We need 37 stars to reach
this floor. Why does it keep? Oh, that's to go up to the next one. Correct. Yes.
All right. Cool. What we got? Oh, this is a really nice island. Did you know that koalas
are really close to extinction? We don't have blueprint. Yeah, I was actually told this.
Maybe if they all just got jobs helping people move into their new homes like this koala.
What? Just start taking taking off the wallpaper because it's going to ask us to. Yeah. Oh no,
actually from what I was told and I did a little research myself, koalas have smooth brains
and they will not eat food if it's on a table. They don't get it. It's not like on the tree.
So they don't they will literally starve to death if you feed them their koala food on a table.
And apparently they like have they just have sex with each other so much that they just I'm
no this is not even a joke. Like there's so many like koala STDs. Did you learn any of those
meerkat facts? Why is this going outside? I don't know. I just felt like the appropriate place to
put it. I was just following your lead. All right. So what's the plan? Where is the plan?
The plan's in the dumpster. It looks like the plan's in the dumpster. I don't think we have a
plan. I think we might be waiting for a delivery either that or we just need to like trial and
error and that would be really fun. Oh boy. Okay. Well, do we have an info? Yeah. I'm going to
imagine that we glue these to this wall. I'm just going to, I'm going to, well, it looks like, yeah,
that's what the game wants you to do. We actually probably need to glue them to the top left wall.
I think that's the only thing we have, but what about the purple paint?
All right. Try top left. I'm going to try purple paint here. Oh, is it carpet? All right. Purple
top left. Okay. Let's give it a try. Progress is zero. I got progress for this. You got progress
for that. This is probably bottom left. Yeah, this is definitely bottom left. All right. So what
would be top left? The green? The carpet? No, where's the carpet go? We probably don't have
the ingredient yet. There it is. Yeah, that's top left. Let's try that. Hey, it worked. Look at us
solving this difficult puzzle. It is a puzzle. Now, if only they put like another
couple million into the budget of this game. I'm not kidding. If there was a game where you did
this, but it was not just like a fun little co-op game. No, no, no. Like you had to build a whole
house. How much was this game? $20. Okay. Only one of us had to buy it. That's true.
Okay. Considering that this is like $7 per person. Honestly, this game has... Oh no, I can't say that.
Never mind. Are you getting progress by doing that? Have you checked? Yeah. Okay. Good. Okay.
Just checking. Good. Good. Good. Good. Very good. I'm going to start trashing the walls over here.
I'm going to start throwing up. Why? Missing a wall in the top left room. We probably should spin it
to be honest. Honestly, you want to be really honest? Let's just... We can't spin it. Oh no,
we can't spin it because there's no blueprint. There is no blueprint. Oh shit. Okay. So we have
to... Get some pace. Do we have all the trash from this bottom left room? Oh, these bottom walls.
Also, don't koalas eat eucalyptus leaves, which is like poisonous.
Are you still on the koalas? No, no. Yeah. That's their main source of food is eucalyptus.
It's poison. But over years and decades, their stomachs have been able to digest it.
So we're doing... What? We need to do this bottom left room with the teal paper. Glue.
Hey, thank you Utopia Fox. Utopia Fox. Utopia Fox. For the five community subs. Thank you.
Utopia Fox. Thank you. You guys, are we getting progress on that? Yeah. All right. I'm going to
start cleaning. Are we getting progress on that? We have a room in the top left. We need the purple
wallpaper to be up there. Oops. I skipped one. This music sounds like Civilization 5 music.
Koalas can't eat eucalyptus at birth because they lack the proper enzymes.
They have to obtain the enzymes by eating their mother's poop.
Oh. What if they're like... What if they don't have a mother?
That's them. They were immaculately conceived and we might have missed
Jesus Koala at some point. No. No. There was a lab involved.
What are you doing? Thank you, Utopia Fox. Go get the fucking paper. I'm talking. All right.
Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I have a koala. Standing in the middle of the floor, not helping anyone.
What do koalas make for a noise? 27 seconds left, might I add, looking up Koala facts in his chat.
I think all you've done is move the thing further away. What do they do? Start cleaning up.
Oh, sorry. There's a wall missing.
Jera must just stand in the middle of the floor and I'm getting called out for helping you.
I don't know who is who. You all changed. Can I eat this? Oh, we do have four seconds left.
I'm sorry. Oh, yeah. Four seconds left. Oh my God. Now I can't. This guy. He went to college.
You keep bringing that up. Hey, not all of us are in the top 1% of the educated
elite that go to college for this shit. Oh, you're going to talk down to me now.
Hey, quiet, quiet. Did you say college boy? Yeah, college boy. Hey, college boy.
Are you my father on our weekly Sunday phone call when I was in college? Being considered a college
boy is a step up from being a boomer like usual. These walls need to come off. That door needs to
be answered. We have a blueprint this time. Which one are you now, Jerma? Are you the other? You're
the koala. I'm the koala. I've been the dog for like four missions. OK, that's supposed to mean
something to me. What do we do with the bag of flour? What do we do with a locked bag of flour?
There's a lot of locked ingredients. I've heard you're supposed to drink it and don't come into
work tomorrow. Oh, I have heard that too. Someone very wise said that. OK, this is our ingredient
room. Top left is that carpet that you just put down. Top left is that carpet. Which one?
Fuchsia? That one. That one. You got it. You got it. I'm doing it. You guys take care of that shit.
Do we have any more trash that needs to be peeled off walls?
I don't think so. Do we have a mix yet? There's a bag of that mix stuff in that right room.
Now, whatever that's for, I don't know. Oh, what's the box? Did I do this wrong?
What's this box? I don't know. I just have an indicator over here.
Take this box to the rightmost room. Hold on. You want this box over there? Yeah, that little...
Just you get it. It's right there. Can you knock it out now?
Hold on. I just got to put that... Oh, these are like the wall tiles. OK, I get it.
Here you go. We have to do the same thing, though. It dries. I need a second person.
I'm almost done here. Then I'll be in there with you, Chief.
I'm going to paint this top left room. You guys take care of that. Sounds good to me.
I'm with you, Chief. What do you need me to do? Just pick up the box stuff and then put it on the...
Oh, yeah. OK, Chief. It's one word catchphrase stuff.
Whoops. That was not... The top left room is done. I don't think we need this fuchsia paint anymore,
do we? I don't think so. I'm going to give you... You guys need to turn? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's it. After that, you guys are done after that. Then I'm just going to start cleaning
up. That's a three star. What do I have? I think I have tiles. You do have tiles.
There we go. He makes it up at the end. There's just some construction puke over here.
There's that one bundle. You want to put it on that final wall. Oh, oh. Oh, shit, dude. Oh, shit.
Jesus. Am I watching a college drinking compilation where somebody chugs real fast?
What are you doing? Get out here. Get outside. There's a minute. Put me down.
Just recording our royalty free party on beyond sound effects. You good? What if you say college,
boy? You guys have to finish that wall. I'm getting to it, dad. There's still one more thing. So
could we get some rotations? It's this door. No. You need rotations? Oh, there's another wall.
Right here. Right here. Right here. On me. There it is. Just you two? Yeah. Damn. Pretty
good. Nice work, guys. We need 37. Hey, good job. We don't even get paid for this.
How many floors are there? Well, the achievement was 999. 199. No, 999. This game is a testament
that a couple of, you know, a couple of farm boys can work with one city slicker.
You know what I'm talking about? We had trouble saying that for some reason. Why? Now we can
work together with the social elite. I think it's actually the opposite because I went to college.
So it's two college boys trying to teach one farm boy how to actually do things. We can't get this
out of this room. Free education. We have to move it around. Does the queen live here?
Where are you trying to move this? Just out of the way so we can start to do this.
It's in the way now. It's in the way. It is in the way now. I'll just restart.
We have. Yeah, this is going to be a pain in the ass. Just rotate it so we can walk by.
There. Diagonally. Diagonal. Diagonal. Stop going through the door. You're pushing.
All right. Let it leave there. Wow. Look at those two college boys work together on that one.
That's this floor up here. So that's it's already been shellacked.
There's no shellac. So just do it. Just click their heads. We need some couch movement I think
here in a minute. If anyone touches this couch, I'm screaming. There's one behind the top right
and the top left. If you touch this couch. Oh my god. Someone get the fucking door.
You have to scream twice as loud because we've both touched different ones.
Yeah, good metallic. Seriously, that's like a that's like a we like looked over and like
wink. You know what I mean? I want to hear the scream. That was a that we need to double scream
now. Boy, that was very bad. That was very bad. That was very bad. I'm sorry. It's my bedtime.
He can't scream because everybody in that city goes to sleep at six p.m. That wasn't even a
scream. That was like I just I just swallowed a whole wall. Can we get a blueprint boy out there?
Carpet right here. Oh, hold on. Doesn't that mean that all these are hidden?
Yeah, we need to be. This needs to be spun with the blueprint in my god. Oh my god.
He's joking. Somebody help him. All right. That room's all done. Now, this is for this room then
the tiles. Are they for the here? No one knows. No one knows. Yep. Tile that room. Wow. Get it
going. That's a lot of time. Um how do we thank you. That's a lot of time. We have to do. We have
to move all this stuff. Just do all these ones that are not inefficiency. Just do the ones that
are already empty that you don't have to move the table twice over. Now, you gotta move the table
again. Please don't worry. Don't worry about him. K.O. legacy. Thanks for the ten community subs.
Thank you for the ten subs. A huge drop here. Thank you. Ten fucking subs. Thanks a lot.
Uh something's on fire. That sounded like thanks a lot but I mean I mean like thanks a lot like
seriously. I'm sorry. I'm currently being yelled at so sorry. What? This thing's not supposed to
be up here. Okay. I'm just holding this up in the air while you guys do the tiles underneath it.
All the lactic acid is built up but I'm gonna like have to scream here in a second.
Okay. Now, we gotta move the table again after we get this. We gotta get this tile down. I'm going
for it. Always with the tile on this guy. Did you intentionally lock us back here?
We're missing tile for the bottom left room that needs to be done with. We don't have the
tile for it. There's tile in the top right room or something. What is it? Yeah, we need that tile
in there. Alright, chief. This you need this tile in there with that tile over here. Alright,
I'm gonna start clearing out. I'm gonna start clearing shit up. Okay. We don't need anymore.
Alright, chief. I can't wait till you progress. There's a large bed in here. To like buddy or
like guy or something. Alright, guy. Alright, buddy. What? Did you not hear? You keep just
changing words. You didn't hear the news? Alright, pull the bed. There's no genders anymore. There's
only sports. Okay, but pull the bed in such a way that I can get in there. Just place it on this
front one even though it's gonna block you. I'm trying. I'm gonna crush him. We're actually about
to throw it over the edge. Alright, there we go. Good. Let me out. I feel like I am playing
Minecraft again. I went A and K and when I came back, somebody boxed me in with no tools.
We have to put tiles down in the room. Just lean the bed up into the ceiling. This is ultra lazy.
You don't want to take the bed apart to clear the room. Alright, we got 50 seconds
and we're missing something. What are we missing? Kitchen. It might be that. Okay, it didn't drop.
Okay, we gotta start cleaning up. Oh my, he's getting it. Make room for the bed.
Can you just come out? Free bed. Free bed. Free bed. Are you seriously not gonna want a free bed?
Open that door right now. Are we stealing from them? That's just perpetuating, you know.
That's true. That is stealing. You said we weren't getting paid. That's a fee.
That moving people are just animal people like otters.
Now what do we need? This one is large, but I think it's fake large.
Alright, I think two people could do this one. You know what I mean? Fake large,
kind of like when I puff out my stomach to look fatter. Yeah. Or just sit normally.
Alright, what's the goal? Hold on, I don't think he processed it. It's alright. I'm muted right now.
I don't think he processed that. Tear down these walls. Okay, I gotta compose myself because I
can't laugh at that. Anyone want to do something? I don't know what the, what are we supposed to
restart? Tear down these walls. That was really mean. Okay, that's not what I was trying to say.
Answer the door. Answer the door. Alright, I got pizza. What is this? I think we, I think,
okay, next game. I think we're done. You do, hey, you do know what the next game is, right?
The next game is like this game, but different. The next game is like this except it's a train
instead of a house. Look, you guys are doing nothing. I know. Wait, wait. No,
I'm not done. I'm not done. Who's done here? Hold on. Who's done here? I was done an hour ago.
No. Alright. It was my bedtime an hour ago. We started an hour ago. You done? Two hours ago.
I'm not done. Taleks, you done? No. Alright, majority rules. You have to stay. Okay. Alright,
these are my, this is my swing vote though. If there's not a new mechanic by the next floor,
I'm done. Okay. Well, the mechanic, this floor is moving furniture. Oh no, we have,
but we got a backup thing. Okay, start tearing down these walls. Okay, tear down the walls.
Get the garbage can that you already put shit in. Oh, it's empty. There. Okay. The train one
actually, yeah, the train game does look pretty fun. Hey, you guys don't even know what the train
game is. Do you? I do. I linked it to you. When we want justice, when do we want it now?
Another backup plan. Okay, so we need to put these tiles on this wall. Everything turned off.
I, we need, um, different type of wall thing. Is it not here? Where's this carpet go?
I don't think carpet. I don't think the carpet goes anywhere. It goes in the kitchen.
This shit goes in the kitchen. What? No, wait. Oh wait. Yeah, it does. I got it. I got it. I got
it. I got it. Which one's the kitchen floorboard? It's got like a floorboard. Look, is it here?
Is this a kitchen bringing things? Which is what's the kitchen? So many things. All right.
Um, I don't know. I think this is a kitchen. Yeah. Wait, that's floorboard. What's this?
Yeah, that's not that carpet. Doesn't go there. That's the thing you're carrying
goes in the room. It goes in. Are you sure that's not it? Oh no, that way. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It goes in here. No, it's not. It's wrong. We haven't made any progress. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Kitchen carpet is right, but the percentage didn't go up.
Is this right? That's definitely right though. The percentage isn't going up at all. Maybe it's
because we smell. Uh, did we not tear something off? I mean, that's exactly the way it's supposed
to look. We didn't shellac. Uh, maybe there's so many things to do that my feeble wall painting
is not. Yeah, but the individual thing on here would show progress, but it doesn't. This one's
done blueprint. Are they different? This one's done. I know. Okay. Wait, no, we're going, I guess.
Oh, they're high. There's one high, one low. There's two different blueprints.
There's two different blueprints and one of them's false.
Oh, yeah. Fake blueprints. No, we got fucking tricked. So there is a rival company actively
trying to sabotage us. What the fuck? Well, that's a new mechanic, but I don't know if I,
I don't know if I like it. I don't know if I like it. It's just a time waster. You just restart
at that point and then you play the train gamer. You're like, go to bed. Right. It was frame game
time. Where's the latte wallpaper was like the latte wallpaper. Do we have latte wallpaper?
Holy shit, dude. That was, that was violent. What do you, it just sat watching him just keep slipping
in the back corner. He's just making a mess to try to get us to do the train game.
He wants to leave. All right. Train game. He wants to. All right. Fine. Fine. This was called
tools up. So we're going to do train game and I'm going to go to VRB screen and I'm going to go pee
and then we'll open it up. Just. Oh my God. He pees once every two hours. Not sure. I didn't
pee for eight hours last night. Last literally last room. I didn't go back in months. All right.
The first night you haven't wet the bed in the last month, mutable. I don't know. All right. I'm
going to go pee. What do you mean you don't have train game in you, dude? It's dinner time.
Why do you guys got to start so late? It's not even late. It was three. It was like four or five
o'clock. That's late. Then you have to do time zones and then consider what time it is in Europe.
Do you sleep apnea? No, I've just been waking up really early. No, he just, he just wants to go
to bed at six thirty seven o'clock at night. That's what it is. Do you go to get the early bird
special at your local diner too with all the other old people? I wish. All right. I'm going to go pee
at star. If you're, if you're still with us, then you're still with us. If not have a wonderful
early word judgment coming from early bird scrambled eggs. It's just going to be a full
plate of scrambled eggs. You're not going to order anything else. And then you're just going to be
like, this is what I like. And everyone is going to be like, what the fuck? Why are you doing this?
You're being really mean right now. Really uncomfortable. All right. All right. Are you
staying or are you gone? I'm going to look at the game again. I'm going to look at it. All right.
I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back in two minutes. I have zero brain power at this point in
the day. Non-canon week. Is this going to be another game where I have to like think?