Not that late, a little bit late. I just wanted to do a last minute check. I had to take auto out
and then I wanted to make sure these are all... I messed up the way the images came through,
so I had to re kind of put them in the right place. But we're live now. How are you? Good afternoon.
It is currently 2 1 2 Pacific. I don't know what time it is for you, but hopefully it's in a nice
time. Omega lull. Right off the bat, already got a couple of omega lulls. It's gonna be a good one
tonight! Uh yeah, we're gonna do a community content night. My throat's a little scratchy
because I've had a cold, but I've had a 20% cold for like 10 days. It won't become a cold,
but it won't stop. It won't leave me alone. Maybe it's the air. I started to develop this after the
slime stream. It's just like, get at it! Like give me the cold and let's get it over with.
He's turning. Not yet. Not yet. We'll see. You got slime-itis. No, but uh again, this is the second
time we're gonna be doing this. Expect this stream to be somewhere around a few hours, three or four
hours. This is what we're doing. Community content only. If you don't know what that is, go to the
discord. Read the pin on the community content discord page. You can find out what we're doing.
Art, videos, music, community themed. There were a lot of submissions. Tried to go through and get
as many as I could in for today. All right, so let's go ahead and move over here. We're just
gonna get started. Yeah, there's gonna be a cam today. I promise. There you go. You ready?
Um, there'll be a camera today. I didn't say which one though. This is the first one. This is the
first- we're gonna start with images. I don't know what the- I- is that pic- I don't know if
that's pixel me, but here's real me. How are you? Good afternoon. Uh, so make that face. I did that
face again. I'm never making that face again. I've done that face twice and it has become
just- there's a worse one. I look like it's gross in this picture too. I've talked about how this
is my least favorite photo a dozen times. Do it. Do it. No, the- the greedy grinner is not worse
than this. I'm gonna have to put like the evidence forward. This is the worst picture that exists of
me with like more than a hundred upvotes, but this is the one we're starting with. Derma face tier
list. I can't do that. Hold on. Let me just- everybody thinks I'm gross before drinking, like
I put blood in water, whatever. Uh, all right, let's get- let's go. This is number one. Again,
I want to make this very clear. Make sure you watermark your images. It's got to be on Imgur
and- or it's got to be on YouTube. Make- put- you got to put a little thing down here
that says like, Dan, you know, what- I do- whoever you are. What? What did I say? Imgur.
Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry, folks. Imgur. Imgur. That's too many things to say.
Imgur. No. Imgur. It's so much easier. Even if it's wrong, I'm still gonna do it. There are people
that say jup instead of jup. So, am I gonna change those people's minds? No. I say Imgur.
Fuck dumbass shithead. Oh my god. All right, let's take a look at the next- I gotta get this image
off the screen before it's like, again, the number one thing that comes up when you type in Derma
into any search. That's what it is. All right, this is the next image coming up. Fireman. Look
at this dude. Everybody loves Fireman. Of all the things, like, everybody just loves this character.
This is one of quite a few good Firemans tonight. He's awesome. Look at this dude. Very good
Fireman. I like the little rosy cheeks here. It's a nice touch. And I make that face. I do this all
the time. I always have this little, like, shit-eating grin on. I just did it right there.
Shito. I think we may have seen this one already, but it's still very good. Rest in peace,
Shito. What's wrong with Shito? Shito's batteries are dead, but that's all right. How do you zoom?
It's control plus, right? There we go. Shito's batteries are dead, but here's the thing about
inanimate objects. If you put new batteries in, they just wake up. It's like going under anesthesia.
They just get up. They're just up now. And they keep all their memories. Everything's fine.
Shito could sit in, like, a suitcase for, like, 10 years, and I just put batteries in, and it's
just like he opens his eyes from the last time he was turned off. And he's like, I'm fine. I'm
alive. I'm fine. Wake him up. Maybe one day. That's Toy Story 5. What a great idea for a Toy Story
sequel. That's fantastic. Have Woody just wake up in, like, 2060, and he has to deal with the
future, and he just, hey, all of his memories are from, you could do a whole future thing with that.
His batteries died. Yeah, that would be perfect. I would go see that movie.
The Wall-E future? No, it just had to be, like, a regular future. Not the Wall-E future. We're not
going to get, guys, we're not going to get that advanced. We've plateaued, I think, in a lot of
technology. It's going to take, like, a hundred more years before we get, like, a real new, like,
plateau of technology. I disagree. All right, let's keep going. That was Shito. Good. They watermarked.
I mean, it, that's me. That is me. Although I don't know if my, like, jaw is that. Maybe it was.
When I look at some of these images, I just go, like, is that, like, that's me? Man, I guess I
look like that, huh? That's a great style, though. I love, you know what I like about this one?
This part, right down here. I love this, this shadow. This, like, neon shadow. I love what you
do with the chin, because that's the extent of the amount of hair that I can grow on my face.
You nailed it. I don't have enough gamer neck. I don't, what do you mean gamer? I don't need gamer
neck for this. I can sit like that. And that's what my, look at my throat. That's what my throat
looks like, too. Like, bumpy and fucked up looking. I am, okay, I am such a bumpy person.
Like, what you see right here is what it looks like the whole way down. I'm just, like,
covered in, like, little, like, bumps and, like, loose skin. I do not look good naked.
No, I'm not kidding. Yeah, I do. No, not like a toad. Maybe it is kind of, no, it is like a toad.
No, it's not. Let's find out. Okay, what if I show you, okay, is it, no, that's illegal. I can't do
that. Just like, let me show you. That would be really bad. What do you think about this?
Illegal. No, I'm really, like, bumpy and, like, coarse. Like, when you touch my arm, it's like
sandpaper. It's like, ah, fuck, that's like, that's rough. I like this image a lot. It's very good.
Very, very good. Give me the watermark. Streamer go, well, there it is. Streamer goes insane.
I like this one here. I don't even, I don't even have to do anything. It's already there. Look at
that, like, in my stomach line, too. That is what it looks like. What is that? The old toothbrush,
I remember this one. That, like, that's the fart face? This, ah, this is the fart face, isn't it?
And of course, being bagsonic, I like the blue and the blue. That ties the whole thing together.
They pop, and then you add a little bit of, a little bit of green over here,
which your eye goes like this. This is how this works, guys. Trust me, I know how to, I know art.
Your eye, the artist decided to put the colors, pop it out like this, so your eye goes like this.
See what I just did? Oh, bang, bang, bang, bang, right there. Bang, bang, bang, bang, right there.
Your eye is one, two, three, four points across the paper. Don't you ask the artist. See?
Like, they're here right now? Yeah, that's why I did that. It's a good composition. I like it.
Very good. A lot of, a lot of moments. A lot of, like, a Twitter picture.
I don't think that, that many people are gonna like that photo, but they did. Your chin's not big
enough. It's huge right here. Like, my nose is, is, like, right outside, and then my chin, like,
touches the top of my nose, like, per minute. If you took a ruler and go like this, it'll hit
the bottom of my chin. See? Because it comes out. I fart like a banana. There isn't a ruler long
enough. Get out of here. Rude. All right, there's a, there's a, look, wait for this one. Ready?
So, this is, just watch it. Ready? Let's add the bottom teeth. Two submissions here. One,
one of the top row, and then finishing it with the bottom row. You gotta complete the photo.
My teeth aren't like that. Imagine you had teeth like that. Your mouth would just be constantly
bleeding. Blood would just be pouring out of your mouth at all times. It would just be like, ah!
Blood would just be filling your mouth, and you'd just have to spit. You'd have to carry,
like, you'd have to carry one of these around, and like, you just wouldn't, you'd have to keep
your mouth closed like this, and talk through here. Otherwise, you'd just get hurt. Blood bottle.
It's tea. It's tea. I'm drinking tea. But no, that's, I like these two because you,
the second submission has the bottom teeth. It's like, oh, fuck! I forgot to, I forgot the bottom
row of teeth! All right, I got, I got it now. It's there now. Let's keep going. This is when I won
the vine wrestle. It's the belt right there. You'd have to wear a mouth guard. Yeah, you just have to
have like a constant mouth guard on. CM Jerem. That was a lot of fun. I was happy to participate.
It was a great day. This is glue man. Who is this? What, what actual character is this? I don't,
I don't know who that is. What's the actual wrestler? It's glue man. No, behind the mask.
It's the dude, it's just a dude next to CM Punk. That's not a wrestler. This is like a fan. Wait,
is this somebody just getting in the photo? Like, leaning in? How would they be here?
They were just in the crowd. Oh, I thought this is like two wrestlers. Whatever. Oh wait, this is
awesome! I forgot this is like the Jupiter Storm. I should have, bye, I didn't, I wouldn't. Let's
just sit here for a minute. This is great. So this is a Jupiter Storm. Really a little screen saver.
I think it's great. You know what would be really awesome is if whoever made this, whoever programmed
this, to make it so it would count the Jupiters that are happening in chat. How many completed
ones happened? And that's the ones that ran down. That would be awesome. Oh, there's also gnomes
here, but who cares about those? We can remove those. Chat is feeding them back to the sky.
But yeah, this is really cool. It's just like a little screen saver. I think it's random too.
Seems like it is. Let's see. Is it random? They're just kind of, yeah, I think it is.
Different distances and stuff. No, it's not. Are you sure? I don't know about that. Let's see if
that happens again. No, it is absolutely just whatever, wherever they go. See? Look at that.
Here they come. See? They go down and then at the bottom and then they start at the top.
Watch the gnomes. Why do I feel like if I sit here for long enough, it's going to scream at me.
I don't think it is. It's just going to go like boop. It's really cool though.
This is a photo of a photo that somebody did I think in a class or something. Green light means
go. It's me T posing and then T posing J's. Is this a classroom meme? Are you passing this
like around in class? Don't get me in trouble. Don't get yourself in trouble. You better turn
that over and there better be flash cards behind there. I don't want to get you in trouble.
Get me in trouble. Oh, there's a flash card all right. There's a flash all right.
Why would you say that? Pretty cool classroom. You can tell. Look at the thumb. There's like
the thumb on the corner right here. Just like with like a camera phone right here.
Right there, the second you took that photo, you probably just got yelled at.
It was like Steven. Yeah. What are you doing? No, no, just flash cards. Don't get me in trouble.
I've been seeing this a lot lately. The lion from Madagascar. It does that thing.
I mean, I don't know. Did I steal it from Madagascar? I don't think I did. I've never
seen this movie though. I didn't see this movie. I've never seen Madagascar. Does he actually go
like this? Like bang. I don't think he does. Does he? I've never seen this movie. Maybe I like it
was all like in the background one day. No, I refuse to believe that I stole content from the
lion Ben Stiller character in Madagascar. I refuse to think that. I refuse. No, like my like father
used to do this. Like this is my dad. He would be like, Oh, look at me. I don't, I don't do that.
I got to say, I got to see it. I got to see it. I think we've seen this already, but this is crazy.
This is from the Simpsons hit and run stream. It's terrifying. Like they're melting and
it's scary, but it's really, really well done. Yeah. This is a thumbnail for one of the videos.
Yeah. This is the second term of thumbnail. That's why I was like, I've seen this before.
It's crazy. It's good stuff. Yeah. Look at how this is as a, as a thumbnail.
You can still make up pretty much everything. That's how you know a thumbnail is good.
When it's this small and you can still tell everything that's going on. Excellent work.
Excellent work. Just like you. Hey Carnival. Carnival, uh, German. I love the fact that you
put a watermark on it because there's, there's, there's the million dollars in bits. Frog,
just a well-composed fun image. German lied about Wailord. You sure about that? Wait, where is he?
I don't know where he is. I think he was being cleaned. He's not here.
Whatever. I usually just sitting right here in this chair, but not right now. He lied.
No, this is great. I like that. I like the teeth here. I like the crumpled up car run over hat.
Looks good. Very, very, very, very good job. Just all around. Good shit.
Here's Jax mix new bald coin marshmallows, low sugar. That's what I like to see.
I would eat this. What's the flavor though? Marshmallows, chocolate. This is like Cheerios.
Che, like kind of like Chex. I actually don't like, I think Chex are gross.
So I wouldn't want these to be Chex flavored because I find them to be absolutely abhorrent.
Don't, don't, don't give me that look. How, how, no, no, no, excuse me. You guys don't just leave
all the Chex in the Chex mix. Just remove the Chex from the Chex mix and you have like a really
great snack. I don't eat the Chex. I eat around the Chex, even the ones that are cheese flavored.
No, I don't, they're gross. They're just like too crunchy and they just taste like, like just
pure wheat. You eat the pretzels, you eat the fake Cheetos because heaven forbid we call them real
Cheetos and you eat the fake Cheez-It triangles and the rings and the rings and the little flat
bread pieces and the little weird gross white puff balls. I'll take those over Chex. Don't
eat any of the Chex. The rye, the rye bits. He's insane because I don't like Chex. He hates good
snacks. Like there's no way that this many people like Chex. I don't think that's real.
I think I'm getting like messed with here. Do you eat Chex in like milk too? Because like I'm about
to like, we're going to be going like a thousand miles per hour if that's true.
I'm not seeing a whole lot of no's. I cannot believe this. Chex are good as fuck. Chex are
amazing. This has to be a generational thing. Am I actually not in the majority when I say that I
don't like Chex? I can't believe this. No, like the old people eat Chex. You guys call everybody
boomers here. Old people eat the fuck out of those things. It's like their favorite snack.
They've been around for 150 years. You're the real boomer. Chex. Oh, even the word. I just think of
it. This is called streamer. Is this like doom? Old people eat wheat thins. Yeah, you probably
eat those too. I'm the real zoomer. I eat like Bucky Charms, Gatorade, and Beyond Burgers.
That's all I eat. This is really good though. You eat plastic bottles? There's no, what do you mean
plastic? There's no plastic in Lucky Charms. Maybe a little bit of rat shit, but that's
FDA regulated. This is great. So this is, I'm like a doom character. What, is this in doom?
What's the globe? Rat shit is fine if it's regulated. Don't make me do the you eat over
an inch of dirt every meal thing again. I will. I'll do it and people will be very upset with me.
Here he goes. Just pretend I said it. You eat over an inch of dirt at every single meal you eat.
Every single meal you eat over an inch of dirt. I don't know how people don't understand that
when you're sitting at a dining room table. He did it. He did it. He actually did it.
This is awesome. Question marks don't get it. Think about it. That's, that's on you. Streamer.
Very good image. I like the aesthetic. What is that image even of? I think it's from green screen.
Ooh, look! This werelord. How much of an inch of dirt is in grass? You eat food off of the grass.
So if you made a sandwich right now, you'd put it down on the grass before you ate it.
What are you talking about? I like the color back here. I'm asking, I'm talking to one person here.
One person said they eat like on the grass. I forget that there's like four, five thousand people
here. I'm talking to one person. What? Uh, werelord. I like the face here. This is really good. I think
that really captures me. Flat and then like, it's very good. I don't know how people draw.
You have to have a ton of patience to really actually sit there and do all this.
Cause I will get to the first stage, the first step of drawing and you start like blocking
out what you want and then it's all wrong. My legs are too big and it's like I have to,
I've made them like these big parachute legs and then you erase it but then I,
I screwed it all up so I don't even want to do it again. I have a lot of respect for people that
can do shit like this, that can draw and design. It's very, very, very, very, very cool.
Just draw for thousands of hours. Yeah, that's kind of how you do it. People are very, very
talented in their craft and everybody draws differently too. That's like the best part.
This is really cute. I'm liking it. Nice. This is kind of how like a dog will look at you.
And I mean if you like, or hey, like hey Otto and he's like, like huh? Like come over here.
This is a very like dog looking over at something that they're interested in.
The side eye. Yeah, the dog side eye. Let's get in a little closer.
God, rats are awesome. I wish I could just actually pull the trigger and actually get a rat,
two rats. I always get two. I just think I was gonna get a lizard before a rat. Can you guys
believe that? I was gonna get a big ass lizard before I got a rat. It's tricky. Lizards are good
too. I know. No, not an iguana. What if I just got like a huge monitor lizard? They need a whole room
in your house by the way. They need, it's like having like a guest just there permanently,
like in a bedroom. They have to have their own room. Imagine having a fucking like lizard live
in your house. So it's like a kid, yeah. They are so cool though. They're not like main either.
Some of them can be, but there are some monitor lizards that are just, they don't give a shit
about anything. They're like, are you feeding me? I guess you and I are really good friends.
Get a lizard roommate. Maybe the lizard roommate will strain too. Give its own office.
That would be fucking crazy. Nah, too much. Too big. Maybe one day. Maybe one day.
But I do want a lizard though. I want like a bearded dragon. Just like a, like a, at least,
I want a bearded dragon that's at least as big as my head. As big as like by hand all the way down,
like all the way down my arm. But that's like, I don't know. Maybe, maybe like another time. I don't
know. Great photo though. Great pic. You guys nail eyes, can I just say? Like, I don't even know how
you do that. I do like that you have the fact that there's two in, two earbuds in. This is,
I know what shirt this is. This is the Aquaman shirt. I know what stream this is from.
Let's get in a little closer. See the real detail here. I like the shine here. Nice shine on the
hair because that's for real. See? You've got that little shine coloring coming in. That's not
turning white, is it? No, it's not. Is it white? No, it's just like a lighter blonde, right?
Uh oh. I look in the mirror every single day. It's just the width of the lights hit in my face,
I think. Cover the eyes and it looks like the TF2 soldier. It kind of does. It kind of does.
That's pretty cool. That's century. Get a haircut. You guys act like my hair is down to my ankles.
It's not that long. It's like not down to here. It's just like a normal hair.
No, I like it. It's staying. I'm gonna grow it on my face too. No, I would never do that.
This is, I remember this one. This is somebody did. This is from playing Jackbox, I think,
and this is what they were able to do in the drawing game. Dr. Swiss Cheese getting papers
from Dr. Rat. You have like a tiny little cube to work with in Jackbox. How do you even make a
fucking volcano? Don't you only have like 40 seconds to draw this stuff? It seems very hard
to do this. Dreamy live streamer. Caption Twitch streamer. What if you have a 43 inch tablet?
This is Drawception, not Jackbox. Right, okay. Blue Guy with Fedora. This is German Neptune.
Does that emote still exist? Did I delete that emote? I haven't seen that emote in a long time.
Oh, it's German Egg. Right, right, right. I feel like that's an emote I never see anymore.
We'll get rid of it. This is great though. Classy Egg. You can't remember his own lore?
I know my own lore, but that was, what do you mean I don't know my own lore? That is German Neptune,
but it was just so bad that I just uploaded it and called it an Egg. That is the lore. That's my own
lore. I know my own lore. I know my own channel. That's, that is German Neptune. Let's keep going.
This one scares me a little. This one freaks me out. It's Lil Germo, number one clown streamer.
It's just like, this is like, unsettles me. This is for Halloween, it seems, like the last few weeks.
Pretty relevant. Apparently I am a rat puppet, but it freaks me out because
this is typically what I wear when I stream. Except maybe like shorts, or the other way around.
This is like, it's too real for me, including a diaper. That's not a diaper. That's a pair of
underwear. That's not a diaper. I get like, yeah, I get huge hands. That's not a diaper. That is a
pair of underwear. Yeah, those are tighty whities. There's a difference. Not very much of a difference,
but there is. Tighty whities really are just thin diapers. I don't wear tighty whities. Nope, sorry,
not on this guy. I don't wear tighty whities. Actually, there was one time where Kim and I,
I think we're on vacation somewhere. I think it was, she came to, whether it was E3 a couple years
ago, I don't remember what it was, but I ran out of underwear on the trip. And it was like,
I just have to get underwear. Let's just stop at like, a random store. I don't remember what the
store was, but I got a package of, I got a package of just tighty whity default underwear. And they
were huge, even though they were my size. And they just, they would like, cartoon tighty whity
underwear. And I remember just her laughing hysterically at me because I just had on this
tighty whities and I walked out of like, the hotel bathroom and like, brushing my teeth.
I just looked like a fucking idiot. And they were just like, bulky and all. They really probably
did look like a diaper. It wasn't the underwear she was laughing at. Oh, all right, I see what
you're doing here. Nice. You bastard. Ban that person for life. But yeah, I don't, I don't like
just tighty whity underwear. And they always show people in commercials wearing them. There's this
weird propaganda campaign with like shitty default, just tighty whity underwear, where they show these
like huge, handsome, like Chad guys wearing them. Nobody wears those. I don't, nobody buys those.
It's like, like tighty whity commercials are like the Switch commercials. Like they, it's the
equivalent of having like a big strong Chad guy in tighty whities in front of a camera is the same
thing of having a party on the roof with like 30 people all hovered around one Switch. So I don't
know who's buying it. Not me. Not anymore. Not after that trip. Box of briefs are where it's at.
Absolutely. Yes. You only buy tighty whity underwear, in my opinion, in like an emergency
like that. That's like emergency ration underwear. Not for any other purpose. And it does what it's
supposed to do. My name is, this photo is very, very good, but it's very creepy. Like who are these
people up here? Are these supposed to be you guys? But you guys are in here. Why are you in my house?
It's creepy, but it's very well made. Nice job. I, this one, I didn't mean to put this one up.
This is, I, I didn't, I, I, that must have stayed. This is me as the Joker. All right, when, okay,
when I go through all these images, like there are hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of them,
right? Sometimes I save a bunch. I put like a bunch of tabs up and I go like, what do I want
to put that here? Maybe we'll put that over here. Uh, that's a good image. We'll put that. And then
I go, maybe this one too. Maybe. And like, I have like a bunch of that. I, they have kind of a rough,
like go through them all and like kind of condense them. I mean, it's, it's good. It's good,
but I'm not, it's, I'm not going to have this as an emote. No, you know why this is not,
I'm not going to have this as an emote because when this is small enough, it's just the Joker.
When this is at like 10%, that's just the Joker. That's not me. That's just Joaquin Phoenix.
It's still you. No, but that we're, that's not as small as it's, it's going to be. It's going to be
like 50% smaller than that. No, I'm not the Joker. I'm the Riddler. Get it right. Something,
something, something, something, Jim Carrey, something, something. It's because it was Jim
Carrey. I'm not going to do that face anymore. I already said I wasn't going to do it. I love
riding the frog. This is awesome. What is it? I like, I just like this. It's frog in the park too.
Tell us a riddle. Did you know Batman? Did you know that you eat over two inches of dirt
every single meal? What are you talking about, Riddler? Well, if you can't get it, then I'm
sorry, Batman. That's where you die. Good photo. How's that a riddle? That's a riddle.
It's a puzzle. It's a puzzle joke. It's a joke puzzle. That's a riddle. You have to think about
it. A joke is a riddle. A joke just is a riddle. That's a humorous riddle. That's why you have to,
what are you talking about? A joke is a humorous riddle. Oh, you, God, did you think you know
comedy? You think you know comedy, Batman? It's a humorous riddle. Oh my God. I'm sorry, chat.
Yeah, I might as well get off camera and just play this. This is actually pretty good.
That wasn't a joke or a riddle. How is a joke not a riddle? You set up a punch line that the people
don't know what it is until you tell them. Three guys walk into a bar. One sits down and asks a
question. Like, it's just a long drawn out punch line. The punch line is the solution to the riddle.
You don't know the answer to that until you hear it. Come on. You know, it's a question that you
don't have the answer to until it's given to you by the fucking master puzzle creator of the joke.
So you are the joker, not the riddler. They live in the same house. They live in the same house.
Who cares? Oh, God. They all share, like, the same fucking flat. The best part about this one
is this is, uh, this is me kissing Kim that she took a picture of and they omitted it.
And it's just me. There's an image floating around of somebody, I don't know if we showed it before,
of me kissing myself with different clothes and different hair. And it's really, really fucking
weird. But Kim is supposed to be here. So this just looks really strange. This is called Mini,
Mini, no, that is it. That's Mini Man instead of Gemini Man. You motherfucker. Gemini Man. Oh,
you're embarrassing me now. What is this? Oh, is this it? Hold on. This, I need to put this on
camera. This is fucked up. Oh, this is so, this fucking weird, man. Hold on. Let me get this on
camera. It's fucking so weird. It's just so, oh, it's because we're making the same face.
What an egomaniac. I didn't make, I didn't make this, I didn't make this riddle.
Let's move on. Disgusting. It's the same, like, and look, I know, I got criticized for that image.
Let me go back. I got criticized for this image because, yes, I look like a corpse. I look like
somebody in a casket. I understand that. But the photo was taken. The photo was taken right when,
like, we first started kissing and it was just like, oh, it started there. I mean, like, I look
like, I look like I'm just asleep. I look like I'm sleeping. Another one. I'm not clicking it. This
is community, that is community content. You're right. This is community content. That's correct.
Click it. Hold on. We can't just get stuck. We got, like, another three hours of footage.
We haven't even got to the video section. All right. Whatever. All right. That's it. That's it.
That's it. Okay. That was good. Let's move on. This is, I like, this is almost like clay. Like,
I've made it, like, it's been molded out of clay. I need Dead Rising today. I already beat it.
I'd be Dead Rising all the way through. We're going to start Dead Rising 2.
Don't say tomorrow. Hold on. No, no. I don't know. I don't know. I have no idea.
Maybe. No. In, like, a few, no. Next week. I'm going to do something else. We just did Dead
Rising. I just streamed it, like, the whole thing. No. Not tomorrow. Not the next day.
Maybe another time. Next week. You'll see. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. I got to talk,
we got to announce this because, like, what the heck? I, over the next couple days,
there's going to be a new channel that gets opened up in the Discord.
What do you think it's going to be? It is going to be green screen DLC for free discussion.
Over the next, like, probably few, probably, like, in a couple days. It'll be up there.
And then that stream, green screen DLC for free, will be probably in, like, two or three weeks.
And then for the next community content night, we're going to see, we're going to see what you
come up with. But that'll be probably in, like, two or three weeks from now. But this is great.
I like the background of this one. This, was this brush? Like, take a look down here. You know what
I mean? This is brush stroke, right? Looks like it. I like when, like, the canvas shows up in the
background. You can see. Because then it adds, like, you got the white and then you got, like,
the maroon and then you got, like, the face. It's really, really good. Excellent work.
Here's the, look at those yellow teeth. There's the egg. This is unbelievable. Yolk teeth.
Nice work. You captured his essence very well. He, this is kind of how he is all day. And there's
blood in his mouth. Yeah, because look at how sharp his teeth are. We went over this already.
Now what are you guys linking? Uh, nice job. We haven't seen very much egg. He's been in two
videos ever. So, then why would we ever see him again? Click the link. Hold on. I'm in the middle
of something. No, no, no, no, no, no. That's not real, right? That's not real, is it? No, that's
not real. Is that real? That's not good. What the fuck? God damn it. You gotta be fucking kidding
me. How long does those stay there for? How long does it stay up like that? Oh my god damn it.
Okay. Well, excellent work on the egg. It's gone now. Imagine seeing that shit. There's, uh,
Jerma Myers. How, so we're going to get a lot of Halloween themed ones because Halloween was,
like, two weeks ago. So, it's still there. That thumbnail is so bad because it's,
it's a just chatting and it's somebody with their webcam in the corner, which is obviously
the person that's in the photo reacting to them, like, hooking up with themself. That's not,
that's fucking bad. I, you scroll right by that and you don't even click, you go, no, no, no.
God damn it. Uh, this is good. I like how it's the, it's the mask is what it is. Like, that's
not even what I look like under there. Nice touch. Jerma actually looks like unmasked Mike
Myers. I don't. Wait, I don't even, what does unmasked Mike Myers look like? I mean, true.
There's been like 30 Halloween movies. I don't know which one. I've only seen like 10 minutes
of two of them. This is really good though. This image will haunt me forever. This is like, okay,
you know those cursed videos that you can watch and it's like, don't watch this video. You'll get
cursed if you watch it for more than 10 seconds. There've been, there've been reports of people
who have, have watched this video and then they died. Like that's what this is. Don't watch,
don't look at this for more than 10 seconds. Actually, it's like, this is like actually scary.
I feel like it's moving. Look at it for a while. No, no, no, no, no, no. Next one. Next one.
Cause I don't want it to be on the thumbnail for the live thumbnail. That's a huge clear image of
like a gross face I've made, but let's go back and look at it one more time. So it's not the
thumbnail. Okay. I always thought that hair was probably the hardest thing to do. All you artists
out there and nice job. Love the watermark. Hair seems impossible. Every strand. Do you have to do
every strand? I have a crooked, somebody said crooked nose. Yeah. What about it? I have a crooked
nose. I got hit, I got hit in the face when I, when I was like fucking 12 on a trampoline.
I jumped on a trampoline and I landed on my back and my knees, I landed with my knees up and my
knees came back and hit me right in the fucking face. And it like for life. And then I got hit
with a baseball, like right here. And then I got hit with a recycling bin right here. And then I
fell down some stairs and like bumped it hard. How did you get hit in the face with a recycling bin?
Taking out the recycling and I was flipping it around. I was like doing like flips with it
because I was fucking 13 and stupid. It's a garbage truck accident. Like trying to like a
water. Okay. Remember the water, you remember the water bottle thing where it's like, I'm going to
try to flip it. So it like lands on it's like this, right? Imagine you doing that with something
that's 20 times as big and like throwing it up in the air and trying to catch it in your mouth,
like a popcorn kernel. When you, when you're a kid, things seem like they're fun and interesting.
They're dangerous. Don't do those things. Oh, it's going to be the thumbnail. It's going to be the
thumbnail. Not anymore. Says the guy that's probably done enough stupid shit, even the last like two
years on this stream. You can't ignore this forever. Oh, I can and I will. I can and I will. No,
it's not. Is it the thumbnail? It's not the thumbnail. Stop it. I have to, I'm in the middle
of something. All right. I got to, I got to go. I thought that was auto. That's not even fucking
real. What? This is fake. This is a fake image. This didn't just happen. Okay. Goodbye. Goodbye.
Lost stakes. Wait, what, what category is this supposed to be in? Why are there like stakes and
like stews? Chill your mind in the dishwasher. What the fuck is this stream? And is it still
live? Because if it is, I hope it's, I hope it is. Chill your mind in the dishwasher. What a great
stream. Oh my God. That's funny. All right. See, if they're still live, give them a follow. Barbecue,
smoked brisket and lamb. Holy shit. These channels seem fucking cool. I should watch all these.
All right. Let's go. This is a compilation of work from Gen 2. We can't see them because I'm in the
way. So let me get out of the way for a second. So you see the watermark. Good watermark. Excellent
watermark. The thumbnail is the face. Whatever. So here is just a compilation of things they did.
I like the rat. Let's get in close so you can see these. So we can see them all. There's a really
nice render of bald coin. I like that one. Here is, does that mean like vaping? The pumpkin. What is
that? Is it like a tray? Like a dinner tray or something? Like a plast, like a keychain. It looks
awesome. Chill your mind. Yeah. I mean, I would rather have, you guys know this already. I would
rather have a coffee and fried chicken with like, I really would rather eat this meal. This meal is
way better than this. Steak and, no, this is a better meal for me. Save the line. I can't, otherwise
we won't get over it. There's coffee here. There's fried chicken here. And there's also a puffy
snack. That's Cheetos. Coffee. No, no, we've moved on. We've moved on.
Hold on. Okay. They're gone. This is cool though. I want to do this. Let's see if I can find one.
Compact word search. There's coffee right there. There's coffee. There's Cheetos. There's coffee.
Cheetos. And there's coffee, Cheetos, and chicken. There it is. Got it. Okay, I want to find a
Germacraft right there. Got it. How about, uh, pee pants? Pee? No. Pee. Can you go diagonal?
Pee pants. There it is. Nice. Got it. He's going all out. No, just a no. There's a nice, uh, rat
painting. Click here for your free iPod Touch 5. The fake ad on this page. What the fuck? These
are great though. I like the compilation. Click it. It doesn't do anything. Okay, it doesn't work.
It's an image, guys. It's not a website. I'm clicking. Do you not hear? See? That's fake.
What? Let's keep going. This mouse sucks though. Don't ever buy this. Like, I'm going to give you
like, anti. Don't, um, just don't buy this ever. Let's keep going. Oh, Jojo's Bazaar Adventure.
Germa 5 foot 8. Featuring the Haunt Single QRS. Rat Records 5.98. This is a nice touch.
This is hard to emulate. What you have to do here is you have to actually get a photo of this with
that price on it, because that font doesn't exist. And you have to doctor it up. And then you got to
make it a little dirty. This is some work. It's just a pose. No, I'm talking about the price up
here. That's hard to emulate that. That's like the exact font. I'm sorry. When I, when I go to like,
font, fontditty.org, whatever the hell it's called, they don't have grocery store price tag font.
That took work. fontditty.com. Featuring the Haunt Single QRS. This is great. I like the,
how it's a little washed out here at the bottom. Excellent job. And you've got a, you've got a
watermark. Nice job, Cold. Good stuff. Very well edited. Demonwood Zaraxos at the Germa Rumble.
One night only. New Year's Zoo 2014. Doors open at 5 p.m. This is great. It's like those bar photos,
bar posters for random events. One night only. This is like the great photo. This is what great
on a wall. Make this a poster. Make this a poster. Make it a shirt. Make it a poster. This is so good.
Make it both. Make it a coffee mug. Man, there's too many things. Make more merch. Merchandise,
merchandise, merchandise, merchandise. I would consider purchasing this. I would, holy shit,
this is like unanimously, oh my god, you guys want to buy this. Merchandise, all right, well,
all right, hold on, wait, hold on. Just wait, let's, well, just hold on to that. Make this an emote.
This doesn't work as an emote. Pay the art. No, if I was going to do this for like a poster,
they would get a majority of the money. 51%. That's still a majority. 50 point, 50.1%.
It's technically still a majority. No, I'm fucking kidding. Or is he? Pay them an exposure.
We'll figure this out because there's also, there's also like, people have made stuff in this
community, like fireman, like this type of stuff. I would want to do that right. You know what I
mean? I really don't want to just be like, oh, thanks for the image. Yoink, and now it's a poster.
Thanks for the money. Actually, we've talked about it once or twice about doing another shirt,
doing like community shirts. But I would, I would want to make sure that it was like fair. I would
want the person that actually made it to be happy with it and happy with what they got. But that's
a process though. That's not just as simple as one, two, three. I would want that to be them
then to be happy. Regulations. Just make this a hoodie. But that, but there's another thing too
here is, I mean, let's get real. Ready? Let's get real. No more riddles. Okay. Like forget about the
riddles. When you take stuff from the community, for instance, like this, you end up, it's like,
there's been hundreds of images that have come through that people were like, oh, well, that was
awesome. That was really great. But one of them is the shirt. It's like, well, mine, what was wrong
with mine? What was wrong with that one? What was wrong with that? We should have that one and that
one. You have to, I just, you have to be careful just because I never want to have anybody think
like, oh, well, this one was the shirt. Cause it was the fucking best. Yours wasn't any good.
It can get a little weird sometimes. No one cares about that. I know, but still it would have to be
something that we unanimously thought was a good idea. Cause I wouldn't, I don't want anybody to
think that like their images or their art as great or incredible as it was, is in like a competition
for a t-shirt or for a poster or something. You know what I'm saying? It would just be as simple
as this is, it just happened this way. I don't want this to ever be a competition of who makes
the best art. That's not the point. And if something like this, if that ever ended up happening
for some reason, it's not because this is the best image that ever was put through,
it's because it just happened that way. You know what I'm saying? No, you know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? He did it. Slot fucking slime on me. He did it. Um, we'll see though.
I'm open to it, but I would want it to be done right. I'd want it to be fair to whoever was
given the image and I would want it to be the right thing that we all thought was a good idea.
Okay. All right. Back to the riddles. I don't know if this is supposed to be in this.
What am I getting, like a windows update? Am I actually getting a win? Don't you fucking dare.
I saw the ring. Merch. Get this on a poster. Get this on a pizza box. Make this a shirt.
How does somebody already have that ready to go? No, not everything is merch.
There's a good potential fun emote though. I need emotes too. Derma, but it's me. Germ yourself.
This is supposed to be like a fake, like Snapchat filter.
What is this? So this is a fake Snapchat filter thing. It's me at the DMV? I included it. I've
been looking at a lot of images. Derma, but it's me. Germ yourself. This is like a take on the
Snapchat. Look at me. Today, the change of faces. It's like Brad Pitt today, right? Why the DMV
though? I don't understand that. Here's Twitch chat versus Germa 95. Rob versus me brawler.
On day four, carnival. Insert text here. This is cute. This is cute and has a lot of layers.
Nice job. That's cute. This is you guys. And it even has, look at this. So it's Rob,
but look at that little piece of paper. That's the smile that just was tacked on there to be you.
I love it. Excellent job. Everyone's going to say emote, but when it's shrunk down,
it just looks like a car with hair. I don't even know what this looks like.
It's better like this. It's much better like this. This is not emote. This is desktop background.
It's perfect. Make it a B-T-T-V emote. You know what's going to be interesting? Can you imagine
if eventually Twitch and streaming and stuff is so normal that they start teaching these things in
class like at college? It's like how to connect your B-T-T-V and enable emotes. There's going to
be like Twitch stream college classes and they're going to look, I'm going to be in a book somewhere.
You're going to be fanning through like a hundred years. There he is. Ego maniac. What? I was the
first person to ever sing on stream. That happened in like 2011. I was the first person. I was the
first person to get in a rowboat and row down a river on stream. Remember we went over the
waterfall and I was like holy shit that's like 400 feet drop and I like I went down it was like
it was like holy fuck the camera panned back and it showed me going all the way down the waterfall
and then like I bursted out of the water like a shampoo commercial and it was like
and it was like pogchamp. Everyone freaked the fuck out. I was the first person to do that.
I'll be in that book. Oh look at this. They're in the same family. Shito. They're so cute.
I just want a video game with what's it called? What are those actual? They have an insanely long
name. The face flute. What is it actually called? I want a face flute video game where you walk
around and like make noise and stuff. Automaton. An automaton. Right. The face flute. Don't you
just want that to be like an item in a game? It's in Kirby? No not that one. Don't stop.
Holy shit. What the fuck? Watch this. I look like a different person. Watch watch me chameleon into
a different person. Holy shit that was kind of weird. He really does do it. He actually fucking
does this. What the fuck. Look at me. I need to like look up a clip of if this is real.
I need to see. God damn it. I hate seeing this in reality. Give me a link. I want to see it.
Give me a link. I want to see this once and for all. The lion roar. Fuck. It is the same thing
that I do. God damn it. But it's not though. Fuck. It really is the same thing. Hold on. I need to
get this on camera. I'm gonna go to the bathroom. I'll be right back. I'm gonna go pee. I'll see
you guys in like fucking a minute. Hello. Sorry it took a little while. He's chilling his mind
in the dishwasher. You scared me. Get jump scared. It's still going? The dishwasher is
actually still going? Wow. All right where were we? Oh right. That's right. We were in the middle
of doing this. It's even like the right elbow placement. Like god damn it. Whatever. It is what
it is. I was just like in my room. Just had my pillow in my face. Just going like. It's a cool
pose. It's a really cool pose. Why can I not go forward? You know it took me like I it was like
a double take to see if like this is like a real photo of me. Like when was it? Oh no no no no no.
Very clearly it's not. You're too tall. Djerba. There it is. Of course we got Yen Wen with an
insanely. This is the type of shit I'm talking about when I say art. I don't understand. How do you,
how do you even make that happen? This is when I was showing you guys how I shave.
But seriously it's it's like it's like it's really happening on the screen.
The pressure at the the trajectory of the fingers going into the cheek. The wrinkling.
This is some like renaissance style. Like the like old school like paintings of people. It's
unbelievable. Uh Alamanda just gave five community subs. Thank you. It looks like there's uh some
line work going on down here. This is like Michelangelo type shit. The hands. You can see
you can see the skin folding. That's like that's what my hand looks like. Yen Wen again just
unbelievable work. Egomaniac. Me talking about my my my skin folds on my fingers.
It's kind of gross actually. Egomania at its finest. Oh link and chat. Link and chat. Link
and chat. Link and chat. Link and chat. Not right now. But awesome yet again. Yeah Yen Wen.
Awesome yet again. Well written original structured joke. No emotion for two minutes.
Oh shit. Um but there was a reason why oh shit was so funny. It wasn't just somebody said oh shit.
It was every single character had a different way that they said it and they all said it.
That's more that's well structured original riddles. I'll take a loss on this one okay.
I'll take a loss on that one. Not on the first one. Absolutely. I'll take a loss on this one.
Whatever. I did cry laughing at that. But there was but that um but hold on. It was the it was
the the first part with the gym and the loud song and like the if that was what that person was
listening to as like a remix. That's what was funny to me. It wasn't the human biology of going
to the bathroom. No it was not just that. Shito man incoming. Look at this Otama dude. Look at
this Otama dude. This is so cute. You've combined you've evolved Shito into a new character.
Or is it just Shito with hair? With with beautiful hair might I add. The fusion to Anne is singing.
And I like the this. Look at this. This is good. This is like just odd sounds coming out. Just like
just broken. Oh it's a shirt. Oh it's a mug. Oh it's a car keychain. It's very very good though.
By Groove Wizard. Nice watermark. Put watermarks on your stuff please. So people know who it was.
Watermark it. Uh excellent excellent job. A Shito Otama dude.
That's crazy. Oh no fire man got gobbled up. That's not good. What's what's with all the blood?
That's blood. Is it? Or is it ketchup? Oh that's the dork cube. Okay right right right you're right.
It is it is blood. It just was in a box and shipped to you. Very good. I like the corner.
Just like oh this is bad. This is bad. Just say it's ketchup. Yeah that's what I just did.
Good stuff. I think there's another one. There is. I don't even know where half these photos are
from. Oh there's Otto. There's you. See if I can recognize all these. McChicken. Turbo Raptor.
I'm not sure what that is. I think that's just in the game. There's a rat. Turbo Venus. Of course
we've got the uh the poses. Beanbag Sonic. All rolled up by me who's crying. I'm apparently not
happy about doing all this. This is good and fire man's is still good to go. Not even rolled up.
A lot of sad faces in here. And no what about Otto? Got the worst emote on Twitch. It's currently
rolled up. That's good. There's somebody's doodle of umjammer Lammy from that stream.
Pretty good. I like the fact that it's just a folded next part of your scrapbook there.
I need to make a face like this because that's like a really good image to have for a planet.
Pretty good uh pretty good Lammy. Floating in outer space. Lammy emote. Oh emote? Yeah let's
make this an emote. When it gets that small you can just see. It's just a piece of paper at that
point. It should be German notebook. Good shit. Uh this is the quote that uh a senior yearbook
quote. Uh I was taken out of context for this one but we'll read it anyways. This is uh keep
your eyes on the prize. The road to success is always under construction. Pretty fucking goddamn
good if you ask me. Boring boring boring boring boring boring. That's what my mother used to say
to me. That's a that's a quote from my mother. You what are you why are you going to make fun
of my mother? Are you making fun of my mother? Mrs. Albertson huh? I didn't say end quote.
That'd be a really really strange quote. I don't think that would be I don't I think there's like
a Twitter amount of characters you can have in your senior quote. It's like under 150 characters.
I don't think this one would fly. And then here we go. Uh remember the last time we had somebody
give an interesting Imgur gallery of their created characters from Soul Calibur. They have some more.
So this first one is uh grandpa. Grandpa entered the ring with a kendo stick. His doctor said
to not participate due to heart problems but fuck that. Watch out for this crazy old bastard.
Pretty good. There's uh the ring master. Straight from the carnival comes the victim
of chat abuse himself. He had to change from his glue man shirt to his night sky shirt after a
dunk tank issue. He's weak against wind type and frog type. That wind was nuts. I'm surprised that
half of this stuff is even in the game. Do you can you bring in custom images into Soul Calibur 6?
You can? No. So how did you do the planets here? They're very clearly there's planets right there.
Or is it like a sun? Is that just really really good replacement of something? It was kind of
hard but they're all suns. Oh all right. That's still really cool though. This demon grandpa
from Jerma Rumble Live and he's the scythe. That's awesome. Oh there's a Louie Anderson.
Is it just a nightmare? There's Jex. Can you tell I like that shirt? That's pretty close too.
Jerma Louie. Holy shit he's here. He's here right now. There's the egg. Everybody loves the egg.
The egg the egg has okay you know when a character steals the show but they were
a cameo and they were on screen for like only like three minutes. It's like the egg has like a
collective like 0.0002 percent screen time but people just love him. He's great. This is good.
Jerma Craft. That's so that's so works perfectly. It's perfect.
Here comes the coffee pasta of course. I wouldn't have it any other way.
And then here is HHH the headless the horseless headless horseman from TF2.
There's a Tertemus. You even got the like the cage right. Do I I really should probably play
this game for like an hour just to play it. There's a 30s milkman. There's Star. He ain't
that jacked. He's not that jacked. Look at that arm. He shrank that a little like 30 percent.
Unrealistic. Demon Lord Xeroxos with the you got the sweater. Oh my god.
The apple. It's just a turtle shell but it works. See the mind of a creator of a character creator.
You got it. You make those sacrifices. You make those compromises to figure out how to get the
character to work on camera. Good fucking work. Seriously this is like yep you get it. Oh you get
it. Pinwheel. Papyrus. Jesus. There we go. Fireman. You can paint too. Captain Crunch.
Giant rat. It's just got this nose. There's like what is it like there's a there's a monitor lizard
character in Soul Calibur. That's that's what I want. This is what I want in my house. That's
awesome. This Sonic the Hedgehog and you fight with a ring. Of course you do.
Super Jex. Super Jex is just barely bigger and stronger than Star. These are all so good and
then of course I don't think you can watermark Soul Calibur characters but these were made by
gnarly 62. Good shit. These were fantastic. That's my favorite. Just shows what you have
just shows what you're willing to be able to do to get what you want on screen. The apple.
All right let's keep going. WWE superstar Roman Reigns reviews wrestling scenes in movies. Vanity
Fair. Oh there's context to this one. This is I think my bitrate dropped to like 500 one day
and then somebody posted this image and everybody thought it was real.
It was. I mean it was. This is not a real image. This one's real yeah because I remember looking
over at chat and everyone was like your bitrate is fucked but this one is a edit. Get this on a
mug. Good stuff. Oh here's the official from apple shift. This is I think we looked at this the other
day but we'll look at it again. This is from 2k20 I think. Pretty accurate. Let's get let's get let
me set up a little bit here. Good stuff. That beautiful hair too. It's almost as good as mine.
Mine's okay. That's the full tire. Mine's like the flat tire but it's the same. It's the same tire.
That one has a little more air in it. What is this? This is this is a sandwich. Is this a picture of
a snake? I think it's supposed to be me. Is that my eyes? I think that's me. You don't remember the
snake. No not new. We already have this as an emote. This is somebody made the emote in real life.
This is Bogdanoff, Germany. Good shit. Me as the joker again. And it's that same image. I can see it
from a mile away. You can always tell because of the eye. One eye goes right completely forward.
The other guy the other one guy goes this way. One guy okay. One eye is normal. The other eye is
buried into the socket and going this way. I can always tell when it's in that image.
You know which one I'm talking about. Oh and like the whole face too. It's pretty good though.
Nice stuff. I I've had this movie spoiled for me. What? That's not good. And Shito. Very good
Shito. Very clean. A very clean Shito. The happy face with the little sheen on the top. It's
beautiful. It is beautiful. It's got good lighting. Yeah it does. Good shading. Give me a watermark.
Give me a watermark down here. Gotta give me that watermark. Otherwise like otherwise like who made
this? Could be anybody. Give me that watermark. Up here. Down here. Right here. Just right there.
Small. And I'm gonna zoom in. You'll see it. It's fucking fantastic. It's fantastic. I love it. I
love this one too. This is with pencil. Pencil smudges and shit doesn't it? Do you use cloth
when you do this? I can imagine. Okay hear me out on this. When you are drawing something,
doesn't matter what it is. If you have pencil, pen. When I okay let's say I draw a circle or
even if I'm writing like a check or something. You write out whatever it is you're writing
and then there has to be more done to what you're doing and you put like your hand and arm on the
paper and you like lift up and like your sweat from your arm has ruined the picture and like
smudged it and smeared the ink and smeared the the graphite and how do you how do you do stuff
this detailed without like resting your like whole fucking body on the table? It must be so difficult
to do that because think about it. If you if let's say you you were working right here right?
You have this whole area down here that could be smudged by your hand and wrist and arm.
You put paper under your hand. Do you really just like put like a towel or like a paper or
something on underneath? You paper on top of the drawing and then you kind of slide it down while
you work. That's cool. They wear a hazmat suit. That's cool. You're drawing. Why are you sweating?
I've run hot. I'm one of those people and you're gonna know what I mean when I talk about this.
You know when you are in the car like let's say you pick up somebody or you're you know it has
to be fairly cold for this to work too. So I'm the person that gets in the car during like a
40-50 degree day and after about five minutes the windows start to fog because I'm in the car.
It happens every fucking time. That happens to me. Good right and I know it's me but I don't you
don't say anything. What if I go oh sorry guys I uh I have like the internal temperature of
fucking thanksgiving turkey. Sorry. I just see the corners start to fog up because I got in the car
and then I just sit there and I go oh whatever I'm just I'm just in your car
and they know because there's two other people here. There's two other people in the back seat
and this the car was not fogged up. I got in close the door. Windows are up. Let's go.
Here we go. We're going down the road. Fog. Well that's weird. This didn't happen for any other
reason. Just open a window. Yeah that and you crack no but if you if you crack the window
if I go just so it goes down like a half an inch and let out all like the fucking human steam
everybody knows that it's I did that. Why do you think I fucking why I think I'm always naked?
Well that's a little weird that you never have clothes on when you're streaming. Yeah because
like I'm I weigh like a thousand degrees and that's right I said weigh because it's heavy.
Anyways if I were to draw this I would lift up and this would look all nice and this would be
as if it was like a three-year-old with watercolors just smearing their hand all over the paper. I'm
just I run hot. He's melting. What did you do in your art minor? I don't know. I got like a bunch
of clay and hit a baseball bat 20 times and then like I gave it eyes and a mouth and it was just
like another face. Great. I just saw that happen in real time. I forget that people can just press
the button. I always forget that that like yeah this is live. Remember I grew up with like TiVo
was like a thing that just came out. I was like 18. I was like probably 20 when TiVo was like a
thing that at first came out. Click on the link. Never. I'll never click on the link. Look at how
awesome this is. This is somebody made a plush toy of that dude fireman. Merch, merch, sell it,
sell it, sell it, sell it. Now you can't just sell everything. I can't just I can't just sell
everything guys. Like you can't. No no I don't I don't like no no no I'm not I'm not going
corporate. Had to reply. I'm not going corporate. You're the greedy grinner. All right fine. We're
going corporate. This is fantastic though seriously. It's just love went into this you can tell. Very
very good job and we are all currently looking at him. Something's gonna be bopping real soon
and like I'm weirdly drinking that because like I know you're watching me.
It's the same thing like a being on the date. Like you I I know you're watching me drink this so I'm
like get this on BTTV. This is not mine. I didn't make this and none of you made this either.
Just yoink it. Anybody yoink this? No this ain't mine. I didn't make this. Yeah nobody did. That's
really cool though. Boom. Here's the B. If no one made it then you can claim that it's yours.
That's not how that works. I like how how like jacked I am. Sometimes I think about how big and
strong I used to be and I go damn imagine if I was like that still and then I go no
because that took like five days a week every single fucking week. Constant constant care every
day for like two or three hours a day. It takes a lot especially when you're my size and I don't
mean that as like a I mean that as like a when you're like under like five ten when you're like five
eight five nine and below it's hard to keep on fucking like 160 170 pounds. It's hard to do that
especially when you have metabolism like I do. Those of you guys that are under six feet like
under five ten five eleven and you have like like fast metabolisms you putting weight on is
impossible. It was a full-time job for me to keep an extra 25 pounds on. Damn. Just eat forehead.
Oh I did. I was eating tuna out of the can just right out of the can just as a snack in between
meals like a fucking cat. I just turn upside down onto a plate and I would eat it or I wouldn't I
would just open it and eat it out of the fucking can. That's nasty. I did what I had to do to get
strong. You know how much protein I'm looking you right in the eye. Do you know how much protein is
packed in tuna fish sir or ma'am? You look pretty full right now. I do not I've lost I I have I have
lost like 20 pounds since 2012. I was like 170 in like 2012. I was a I was a fucking cement brick
of a fucking man. Seriously I was oh I was just made out of cement and then I just you know
stopped. I started going less and less. Started my priorities started changing and I'm sorry I
just bumped you. Sorry I bumped you again. Now he's a little squishy. Yeah you get a little older too
and it's it gets harder to do. Contrary to popular belief I think once you cross like 30 35 years old
it's kind of hard to at least for me it was hard to like get to the gym like four days a week five
days a week and like lift. I just was like it's like kind of not what I want to do right now.
Jesus you're old I thought you were 32. Keep thinking that. Now we'll be 32 up here for a
long time. Down here though from here down it's like a turtle shell. As long as I just keep a
fucking long sleeve shirt on and a turtleneck on I'll be good. Excuses. Hold on a minute hold on let
me let me drink the rest of my life like water and cigarette ashes. He's fragile now he is. I'm not
going to tell you that I'm not. Here's a an album apparently that I am. Albertson the debut album.
Did you take this from eBay? Oh like this is an eBay photo right? Like this is an eBay photo
that you that you yoinked. I mean it's I get this is like pretty good like editing wise.
Parental advisory oh yeah I can't listen to that. No he's just saying yoink now. I don't think it's
edited. What are you talking? No no of course not. It's wait it's printed. Somebody printed this.
No they didn't. Did you? It's printed. Well let's hear it. What's in there? What's the CD?
And there it is. The first album I ever did apparently. Something of a scientist. Nice.
Oh look at this. Lots of fireman stuff. I love it. Now this in particular. We got the one guy in
there. Got the slug. What else is in here? He got the watermark. Beautiful. This is great too. What
else is in here? My favorite emote is in here. That emote will never be deleted. Term of chomp
is the Saturn. All neatly packed into fireman's face. Fantastic. Very good with the
switching between. I'm not even going to pretend like I'm going to like talk about how what I
think. It looks good. I make myself probably sound stupider and stupider the more that I talk about
the line work. It just looks great. But I like what you did with the white on the outside.
It really makes it come out of the image. It separates it from the paper enough
where it almost looks like a 3D image. You said my piece. You got an A. This is me scared.
He's an art major. Why does Jex have to be like three inches taller than me? That's not fair.
We're the same person. If anything, Jex should be smaller because Jex is like a spirit that
comes out of me and goes in and out. Shouldn't they be like a spirit that's like smaller? What
do you mean stand? He's stronger. Stand. Like you want me to stand up. I don't understand. I don't
know what that means. It's a JoJo reference. Well, I'm sorry. I didn't know that everything
that was pink and blue is a JoJo reference. I didn't know that. I just I thought this is me.
No, this is me. This is me and Jex. I know what this is. He doesn't get it. A stand is a some like
a summoned person. That's the worst noise of 2008 and 19. No, it's not. Bullshit. Bugle Boy
screaming into the urn is the worst noise ever on this channel. That happened like three weeks
ago. There's no contest. There will not be a contest for that because that will beat it every
time. Bugle Boy is like jeans. Bugle Berry. Bugle Boy. Bugle Boy is like clothes from the 90s.
Bugle Berry screaming into the urn is the worst noise I've ever made while live on this channel.
Son of Bugle Berry. Bugle Boy. Streaming hot. Streaming cheesy.
Cluck cluck is just cheesy chicken. New character. Bugle. I think this clip is too quiet. Hold on.
I'm going to warn you. I have not heard this in like three weeks. I'm going to play something
very loud right now. So I'm sorry, everybody. I need to hear what this sounds like. That's not it.
This is so much reverb. I was fucking shitting myself laughing at this
because the reverb is insane. It's insane. I didn't know it was this much reverb.
Did you guys know that during this segment? Okay, listen, this is real. We're talking real talk
right now. I don't know if we talked about this already, but we may have. During that stream at
about 8,000 to 9,000 concurrent viewers watching, there was like 8,700 people watching before we got
to Bugle Berry. When Bugle Berry came on screen, almost 3,000 people left. It was like a catastrophe
of viewers dropping. It was so hard to fucking not laugh at that. Oh my God.
Everything that I saw was like, dude, it's so loud and I can't hear fucking anything.
When I watched clips of this, there it is. There's the eep. This is going to be really loud.
Loud, a loud warning coming up. Very loud. Seriously, I'm not kidding around. This is
going to be very loud. When I was told, hey dude, we dropped like 3,000 viewers,
I was just like, are you fucking serious? Oh my God. Holy shit. Oh my fucking God. That's so bad.
Holy shit. That's fucking loud. I can see it on the monitor.
There's more? 3,000 people left. If you want something funny about that stream,
I'll give you another little tidbit of information. No joke. My actual reel, my mother
watched that stream and she said she watched it all. Right? So I'm just sitting there going,
holy shit. And she didn't say anything about Bugle Berry. The slime part was really funny.
Wow, that was really interesting. Oh, thanks, mom. The trivia was really funny. She didn't skip
the middle 22 minutes of Bugle Berry. She even turned it off. Mom saw you in a diaper.
My mother saw me in a diaper when I was two, okay? Who cares? This is great, by the way.
This is why we have to vet submissions. That was up for a very long time.
It's okay. No, it didn't even say what you think it did. It said whatever. Okay, this is sticks.
This is Sticks Renegade saying, Sticks, I'm going to draw your fursona. I said it like four years
ago and I just never did. I never did it. And spoiler alert, I never will. Reapplication.
Because I will butcher it. You're not going to like it. You're not going to like it. I'm telling
you, you think you want that, but then you're going to get it and you're going to be like,
this is so bad. And it'll turn into merch. That's right. Chat will never let you forget this,
Jeremy. And this is breaking news. The drawstrings of my pants just flopped directly into the urinal.
What the fuck do I even do now? I've been walking around like I'm wearing a diaper
because I don't want the drawstrings to touch me. I don't care. That's fine. That's a real problem
that people can have. If you're wearing comfy pants and you go into a bathroom and you pull
your comfy pants down and your underwear down to pee into the urinal and then you have these
long fucking strings that are like this long and they just went into the fucking urinal.
And what do I do now? What are you supposed to do? What do you do? You pull your pants down at
a urinal. No. Did you hear what I said before that? If you're wearing comfy pants that don't
have the hole that's in the middle of the pants, what do you do? Just pee through your pants?
How are you supposed to go to the bathroom if you have like comfy pants on that do not have the
hole in the middle? Why do people think I'm talking about like dropping my pants to my ankles like
butters from South Park? What? Just use a stall. That was like a shit in there. No, I'm not doing
stall. I'm not doing stall roulette. If you go to a very, very public bathroom with a bunch of people
in it, people, you never know which one's going to have a person in it. Look, if there's like six
or seven stalls and there's like 40 people in 30 people in here, I don't know who's in there
to lock. I don't know, but you don't want to walk up to a closed stall and be like,
go, go, go, go. Oh shit. Hey, I'm in here. No, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. I'll try the next one.
Look, no. What? Is somebody in there? No, cause stall. I'm talking. Look, I'm not talking about,
they need to do, and this is an American bathroom problem because everyone's like,
what are you talking about? When you go to, when you go on an airplane, listen to me,
this is so important. This is the most important thing I'm going to talk about all day. When you
go to an airport and you go in an airplane and there's bathrooms there, right? When you go in
and you close the door and you hit the little switch, a little fucking light is on. Just,
it just says that somebody's in it. No, no stalls in America have anything like that.
Only some of them do. For the most part, American toilets are like three pieces of sheet metal
that just sit hovering over the, off the ground and a lock that barely even goes forward enough
to lock the door. So if you want me to open a stall, if I don't know if somebody's in there,
the door's not actually locked. It will open. It's just, it's enough to just not have the door do
the stupid fucking thing that it does every time. When you go into a stall and you close the door
behind you, it just opens again. And you're like, get the fuck away from me. And then you,
that's enough to make it so the door doesn't hover back and hit you. Have stalls, let it go all the
way down. They don't have holes, huge gaps in the corners and make it so when you actually latch it,
there's a little light. It just has to be a fucking like 30 cent red and green LEDs.
Have it just be red or fucking green. Why is that so hard? It's easy. No joke, you're right about
this. Yeah, we've been doing toilet, we've been doing public bathrooms so incorrect in the United
States for like 60 years. We're just all peeing into walls and like standing behind fucking bricks
of sheet metal. If I designed a bathroom, I would, I would probably win an award. I would win awards
for this. It's not going to be expensive. It could be more, it could be cheaper than it is now.
No, I just talked about urinals. I never talked about stalls. Do what airplanes do. It makes
everyone so much more secure. You don't have to fucking worry about like the gaps in the fucking
stalls. Light, LED, red. I know that ones don't go in that one. That one is, is green. Now,
if you went into a stall and you didn't put on the fucking light that's red and it's green and
you got to fucking be aware of that. Okay. That's, that's a, that's a you problem.
You got to, if it's, if it's green, it means it's vacant. Otherwise you get into a problem there.
That's the one issue, but it'll be locked anyways. No, no, no. Cause you would do the thing to the
airplane. You do think the airplanes do when it's locked, it's red. Done. I'll take a hundred million
dollars in a grant please to redo every bathroom in fucking America. This already exists. Yes,
it does. It does already exist on porta-potties. So porta-potties in the United States are better
than bathrooms in fucking public places that may have cost a hundred to $200,000 to make.
A like $89 plastic box is better. I had to defend myself on this. $200,000 bathroom.
How much do you think toilets are? How much do you think those stalls cost? How much do you think
every sink is? It's like a hundred fucking grant, 200 grand to make like a full like 20 toilet
bathroom. Nice. Hey, somebody just gave, uh, that was modest narcissist five community subs. Thank
you. Modest narcissist. Appreciate it. Thank you. German has never been to a construction site
porta-potty. No guys. I don't like, I don't like go pull over on the side of the road to like,
go use the bathroom at like the construction yard. I don't do that. Oh, I let me go to the
bathroom. That, that seems like a good one. Uh, German sucks. Thanks for five community subs.
Tingy five community subs. Thank you. Like three or four back to back to back to back five subs.
Thanks guys. You're just too good for the common man's bathroom. I'm trying to improve the common
man's bathroom. I'm trying to improve it and make it better for everybody. What? Don't use my
lightning hands. German 2020. Uh, no. Hey, there's baby boy, baby boy, baby boy. Being back Sonic.
I do that face. I have a urinal installed in my house. Bathrooms are overrated. That actually
would be kind of cool. I mean, it sounds like you got a lot of money. This is great though. Thank
you, uh, eternal for this beautiful profile picture esque being back Sonic. It's fantastic.
How do I shit in public bathroom? We're not going to get started on this. People are going to think
I'm insane. This is German lemur. There's like two or three of these in a row. Hey, there's a
German Naruto. I like the style. I still don't understand what they were thinking with this hat
though, with the hair. How would, cause you don't pull it down all the way. That's supposed to be
a headband, right? This is really good, uh, pencil work, pen work, whatever it is. It's very thin.
It just goes under the hair. Yeah. But if I pull that down, that was sitting on the top of my head,
like all the way up to the top. If I had pulled that down, the top part would have gone over my
eyes. I was like balancing that like on the top of my forehead. Good. What do you mean good?
You have a small skull. I know that's okay though, but no, this is great. Thank you for this.
And we also have, uh, this is from the slime stream. That's me. I believe this is me.
That was not me driving by. So there we are. Distraught. That's a kind of a blurry photo though.
What? Worm? What? Wormy? What is wormy? What do you mean? What do you, wait, what do you mean?
What is that word? This is cool though. I'm a boomer. I don't, I don't know what that is.
It's a Splatoon thing. Oh, okay. Oh, all right. I get it. Have I ever played Splatoon? Maybe like
for an hour. Oh, okay. So this is like a Splatoon character or something. Oh, all right. Now it
makes sense. Now it makes sense. Splatoon. Very cool. Uh, Jeremy Elbertson breaks down his career
from the rat movie to Spider-Man, Vanity Fair. There's a little GIF involved us playing trivia.
German in 10 years. More like German in 40 years. I'll still have this face. This face
ain't going anywhere. No, I eat way, I take way too much olive oil and way too much garlic and
avocado oil for this face to turn anywhere. I'm sorry. Dr. Schmikeson on the right. Minus two
for me. I had more points than that. Sorry. I had way more points than that. BRB, stop streaming
for a second. I need to go shit in my urinal. Oh, Dunkin Donuts because you're cool. This is,
look at this. Now that's what I call a good photo. All right. Here's, here's what I would change.
Okay. Get rid of the, uh, the don't sue me branding. Maybe a couple of little ice cubes
and what's that like steam coming out like up here because it's cooling them off, but it's fire.
This is fucking amazing. Not out of his ass, like up like, like like little smoke.
This is fantastic work. I love this because this is what I do. This is just me every day.
I just not Dunkin Donuts anymore. He has to say Dunk. I'm not saying that it's Dunkin Donuts
is the name of the store that you get this coffee from. I'm not going to say it. He hates it. Why
would I hate this? What I just said, it was my like, I like this one. I can't play favorites
because they're all, all of these are my wonderful children. I can't play favorites on them. He's a
liar. I hesitated because I didn't want to say favorite. It's great. Thank you for this. And
you got the CB BB cold blue, cold brew blueberry. You want the best coffee from Dunkin Donuts?
Cold brew ice coffee with blueberry. That does not say what you're saying in chat. Hate to break
it to you. Ah, this is me as the giant rat. It seems equal parts is terrifying and interesting.
You just, did you say the blueberry flavor at Dunkin Donuts is the worst, most disgusting flavor?
Sometimes I think I'm an alien on earth. When I read stuff like this, I feel like I'm like
from another planet. I have to be. Blueberry is the worst flavor from Dunkin. What are you,
a hazelnut guy? Oh, blueberry tea is shit. I must be from fucking Jupiter. Very, very good.
Derma real life rat. Look at the claws. I even, I even have four fingers. You did your research.
This is a painting of the hyper cam. Very accurate. It looks great. That's from, yeah,
that's from condemned. Don't you wish you could go back and play a game again and wipe your brain
like we've talked about? I wish I could play condemned again. That game was so good, but this
is paint or is it, is it tape? Hold on a second. Is this paint or tape? I'm seeing like a little
bunch of bunching up here and like bunching up. Is this a plastic bag? Hold on. Look down here.
Is this like a plastic bag paint? No. Look at down here. Holy shit. Nice. It could be marker.
You're stupid. Sometimes I seriously think I'm fucking, like, I was dropped off here and like
somebody booted me up. No, you. No, this is awesome. I love it. Roach Ranch Zoo Resort off
of exit 78 said to close amidst money laundering allegations. Roach Ranch. Roach murder. Okay.
Roach Ranch was such a great place though. I love Roach Ranch and of course you got the
sign for Anthony for Anthony. You have to. I would love to go to like a bug zoo. People give bugs
such a bad rap. I mean, I hate them. They're disgusting. I really don't like bugs at all,
but like they get a bad rap because they're interesting. They're cool. They have like a
really, really, there's so many different species. There's so many different types of bugs and, and,
and what? Because like, yeah, I'm just saying the bugs have a bad rap. I'm included in this. I don't
like bugs. There are like three bugs that I like. Praying mantis, butterflies, and like stag beetles
and bees and ladybugs. Yeah, that's pretty much it. What about you? You killed a bee. No, I didn't.
Those were wasps. Wasps are fucking murderers. Did somebody just say same thing? Bee and wasp.
One of them is going to, is for the future of our planet and the other one kills for fun.
What are you talking about? Bad, that guy. Like hornets and wasps, they're like, they're murderers.
Hornets sometimes just, just destroy hives because they felt like it, bee hives,
and just take it over for fun. Wasp pollinate. Bees do justice. Bees do very, very good. Bumble bees,
honey bees, carpenter bees. There's wasps in chat. Hey, don't say that about us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I might punch you in the face when we come across each other on the street,
but I pay taxes. What's wrong with that? I might break in your house and like eat all your food
and like throw your fridge onto the ground, but I'm really good at fucking making pies.
Did you know that? Fucking wasps and hornets. They're mean. They're aggressive and they're angry
all the time. This is German Lego. This is great. And Nvidia Greg made this. The Lego hair is
perfect. The seagull, the skeleton. This really does look, okay. I look like a Lazy Town villain.
It's the hair. It's like that plastic-y kind of hair in the outfit. Yes, it's online thanks
to the five community subs. Yes. What would my gimmick be as a villain? I wouldn't have any
gimmicks. I don't have gimmicks. Boring. Yeah, I'm just, it's just me. I just have like funny hair.
I'm like every villain from all the Disney XD shows. Doesn't have any superpowers. Just dresses
up in costumes and like is kind of fucking annoying, right? Just gets in the way of
stuff that the main characters are doing. Happens to like pull the wrong lever,
like if I mess it up with my plan. Yeah, I wouldn't be a very good villain. Let's go.
Happy Thanksgiving. I hope you're hungry for some German turkey.
There's a lot of grapes and fruits. I don't eat very much fruit on Thanksgiving.
Look, there's apples in here. Tons of grapes. Apples. Oranges. Oranges. Oranges. Grapes.
I don't eat fruit on Thanksgiving. I mean squash. Yeah, I mean, but that's, I eat squash, corn,
green beans. I don't, apples on Thanksgiving. Like apple pie. Not like, who eats like grapes like
on fucking Thanksgiving. Do you guys do that? I've got to be. From Pluto. Nice work Dorkcube.
You got the facial hair really, really spot on because that's all that happens.
When I grow up my facial hair, it just looks like somebody took a stapler and just just went nuts
with it. It's not good. But this on the other hand, this is good. No emotion for two minutes.
Why would I do that? We're going over some great community art right now and then we're going to
go over community videos. Strap in for that one. We're almost done with this I think. Only a few
more. But good doodle. Good work. This is from the, I believe the Space Ace stream, which is really
cool. Or is this a JoJo reference? Space Ace. It is now. No, it's not. Cowboy Bebop. I just saw,
I saw the blue and I saw the like magenta. It's from neither. You guys got in my head here.
Everything, everything is JoJo if it's like brightly colored blue and magenta and like pink.
This is great though. There's the light gun. If you, by the way for some of the new viewers that
might be here that haven't been here for a while. In this shirt, mind you, in this shirt I did on
first try. I played light gun games which I'm very, very good at. First try I did the bonus round in
point blank, which is almost impossible to do. It is physically nearly impossible to complete it.
And I did it first try. That just, there's probably some new people here that don't know
my light gun skills. Humble brag. No, that was a regular brag. That was like bragging it to your
face. Awesome work though. And look at that. Good stuff. I like the glasses. I don't even have a
pair of glasses like this. I should probably get some then. I'm a new viewer and I don't believe
you. Somebody linked the clip. It's ridiculous. And then I fell out the window. That hurt. I like
the very, very nice glowing letters. It adds a lot. It does. No, not the haunted bugleberry 3000
people leave the stream noise. Now this is very interesting too. It's a nice suit. Is this, that's
the J. That's really cool. I didn't even know this was the J at first. And then that's me in a suit.
German 985. That's a Jojo stance, but whatever. That's how I stand. I actually do kind of stand
like that. I love it. You made the J this interesting, like Power Rangers villain.
That's awesome. He's my stand. You're such an old person. I haven't seen a television show.
This is not like required reading in high school. I haven't seen this TV show. Yes, it is. Yes,
it is. Well, all right. When your high school starts to have Jojo's Bizarre Adventure as required
reading, then we'll talk. TV wasn't even invented yet. Not yet. This is really well done though.
Is it like a heart monitor in the back? Like a, like a, what's that? One of those things.
It's really cool. This is me fat. Like really fat. This is kind of how I feel right now.
This is the clothes I wear every day. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. What do you mean? Uh-oh.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Stinky poopoo. What the fuck are you guys doing? Stinky poopoo? What are you guys
fucking doing? It's a, oh, it's called, it's, it's, oh, right. Okay. It's like a meme thing.
I look over it and I just see like a wave of people writing like, poopoo, stinky poopoo,
and shit. I'm just like, what the fuck is going on over here? Like, why did this happen?
No, I'm not watching meme video. All right. This is fucking fat Jeremy.
The Rumblers. The Compact War. Holy shit. Look at that. What is that? Is that beanbag? Is somebody
like in a beanbag Sonic? Is that like a cosplay? This is awesome. There's Dr. Jerma with the
Infinity Gauntlet. Anyway, there's Batboy, Pac-Man. They're all here. Everybody's here.
Infinity War. Marvel's Smash Brothers. Poster. Let's get it. Poster. Everybody knows what I'm
saying. Poster. There's a Glooman. Like a pixelated version of Glooman's face, like we do have on the
emote. Pretty, it's actually really good. I really like this. Watch it. Watch it. I'm not going to
watch the stinky poopoo video. I'm not going to watch it. Please. Please. I'm not going to watch
it. No. I'll watch it. I'll watch it later like in bed. You're going to unsubscribe because I won't
watch the uh-oh poopoo video. I don't know what to tell you on this one. I'll give you my review
next stream. It's cursed. I'll give you my review next stream. This is great though. Reminds me of
like a pixelated video game character. Unsubbing. I'm not going to... I don't want to watch this
video. We got so many other videos to watch. Do reactions. Reaction now. He's going to lose
3,000 viewers. No, I think I'll gain 3,000 viewers because I'm not going to watch that video.
Because as many people that are writing this right now that want me to click that video,
there's probably like two or three thousand people that are here still right now that don't want me
to watch it and will leave if I do. So what is it? What am I supposed to do here? Three thousand
people will leave if I don't click it and three thousand people will leave if I do.
What's the game plan here for me? Don't watch it. Damned if you do. Damned if you don't. Don't mind
if I don't. Oh all right. Everybody look what's on screen. The easiest way to make chat completely
just focus on... dog on screen. Dog on camera. Dog on camera. This is cute. He's so chunky.
He's like, you know, he's like a little black bear. That's what he looks like. He's so cute.
Yes, it's all love here with Otto. That's how I feel every morning. I just look at him and I'm
like, you're the best. He's my best friend. Show Otto the video. I'm going to print out a picture
of this video like a thumbnail of the video. I'm going to eat it on camera. This is very, very good.
I love this. You know who's going to love this? Kim would like this really, really. She like
loves drawings and pictures of Otto just like I do. This you probably go, what is this photo of?
Well, it's a photo of this. The coal miner. I still don't know why that even happened. That
was so strange. I feel like it was worse than this at some point too. It's football germa.
Look at that hair too. Look at that dusty hair. Somebody just wrote, do you guys have any idea
how annoying this must be for Jeremy to see this over and over again? They won't pestering him.
I will watch the first, I will listen to the first one second of this video. If it is not,
if it is not what I want, if I will click off of it, if I do not want to watch this.
Okay. Don't give in. You know what? Fuck it. I'm not giving in. It's true. All right. What's next?
Is there anything left? Hey, look at that. This is from the last stream. Bunch of psychos in this
mall. Erp. For the love of God, Frank, put on some shoes. This is great. This was like a few
days ago. Not all heroes wear capes. They just don't click poo poo videos. If that's the criteria
to be a hero, we've got a long way to go. Not all heroes wear shoes. Not all heroes wear shoes.
This is great. Thank you. Thank you, Multitrip. You did the watermark too. Good. And ladies and
gentlemen, there's one more. There's one more. This is just fucking crazy. Watch this. This is
what happens. You know what? It might seem like weird for you guys to see this, but this is the
type of technology that actually existed back in like NBA 2K 11. This is what it actually looked
like when you did this. Like NBA 2K, like 2009. It was this scary. But I don't even know how you
must've just mapped my... That horrible face is that same image. I'm not going to click on the ad
under any circumstance. Jesus. But that concludes the... I just clicked on the fucking ad accidentally,
didn't I? No, I didn't. Thank God. That concludes the images portion of the stream today. We're
going to move on to the videos. And we got a bunch of these. We have a lot to go through.
So I told you there was a lot this time. I wasn't lying. There was a shitload of images and there's
a shitload of videos too. I'm done. I'm not watching anymore. No, I'm done. I'm not watching
anymore of this. That was interesting. So first up, we've got... I need everyone to see this just
because this first one's called The Ring. It's called The Ring. I have to make myself a little
smaller because I don't want to get in the way of any of these videos because that's what we're here
for. We're here for the videos. And I also want to turn this way to be able to watch them with you.
Let's go this way. Sit here and make sure I'm in a good spot to view. I need a good viewing angle.
Okay, here we go. There's a videotape.
I went to a field trip today. The teacher called on me and said that I had the best answer.
That's the whole video. That's the whole video. It's not even... Again? You want to see it again?
Fine. We encores some of them.
I went to a field trip today. The teacher called on me and said that I had the best answer.
Why? But why The Ring? But why The Ring? That was The Ring.
Coming up next. You're gonna get flashed every time. I'm sorry. I'm gonna take a photo of you.
This is called Compact Python and the Holy Sippy.
And it's... You gotta do... You're gonna... You're gonna hoo on me here? Hold on.
Anger in the face. Look at that. I look fucking so mean and fucked up. That was a JoJo reference.
No, it's not. That's... This is not... That's... Is that Eric Andre?
How's that a JoJo reference? That's because of the arrow. Oh, well, that was... That was very...
That was very good. Classic scene from a classic movie, if you haven't seen it. This is... Jerma
slaps himself a lot. So you can... You can imagine what this one might look like. Oh, you want to
fight? You want to fucking fight? Don't fucking come at me. Don't... It actually sounds pretty
good. Oh, you want to fight? You want to fucking fight? Don't fucking come at me. Don't... That's
a pretty good ending. What was that last clip from? It's from the carnival. Jerma streams watching
videos just like I'm doing right now. That was pretty fucking crazy. That's... You know what?
That takes a lot of time because he's something... Maybe it's somebody you've hit at editing,
aficionados. Don't know. Every single one of these slaps had to be placed on a timeline
at the right second. You want to fight? You want to fucking fight? Don't fucking come at me. Don't...
That's like four hours of work right there. Right there. This is literally... It takes hours
to do this. There's a musical timeline. You've still got to place it though. What is FL Studio,
by the way? I don't know. Local streamer is a door-to-door salesman starring Homer Simpson on a big
beanbag chair. Hello? Yes? Hello? Yes? What the fuck? This is called Jerma Trek. Jerma Trek.
Frontier. These are the voyagers of the Starship Ent... Oh, look! It's the fucking Enterprise!
Welcome to Star Trek, the next generation! Captain Picard, Jean-Luc... Motherfucking...
Captain's Log, 5125, the board! Get out of the fucking way!
Shut up! Understood. Get in the car.
Why am I sneaking? Hey, man. Welcome to the stream. My name's Jerma. Nice to meet you. Right
there. Bingo! Right there. That's the follow button. If you click that, every so often you're
getting notified that I'm streaming. And I do lots of fun things on this stream, like...
We are the board. Lower your shields and surrender your ships. We will add to a biological and
technological distinctiveness to our own. Your culture will adapt to serve us. Resistance is...
Hey, boys and girls, looks like we got a pass. Hey, look at me! Look at me! That's what you do.
Ah! Yeah, that's right! This is fucking ridiculous. Uh-oh!
Oh, shit! Zombies! This is fucking ridiculous. He actually shoots them.
Fuck you! Why do I have to do that everywhere? What? Why is this so... Why is it so low?
Yeah! What happened to the audio?
Oh my god. Uh... The best part about this whole video was the... This part here is my favorite
part. The... The... What a... The look at... There's... Welcome to the stream.
You're getting notified that I'm streaming. And I do lots of fun things on this stream, like...
We are the board. Lower your shields and surrender your ships. We will add to a... Badass!
Hey, look at me! Look at me! That's what you do. Ah! Yeah!
Am I gonna scare him? Oh, I can't wait to get in front of the fucking camera and do this again.
You guys put these clips in such great places. You get in like six or seven more hours of stuff
to use. I can't wait. In another two or three weeks, I'm doing it again. That was so... That was
awesome. That was Germa Trek. Uh, this is Dick Richard versus Fat Germa, a test of strength.
Wait, this is like a real... You guys did this in real life?
I thought that was a TV show. That's the whole real costume.
It's a better costume than what was actually in the video.
No, you don't reveal! You don't reveal the face! You don't reveal the face!
Now everybody knows who's under there. Uh, I gotta tell you that this costume is better
than the costume that was in the actual wrestling event. Like, holy shit. That's
one-to-one. Correct. Excellent job. Is this canon? This is a dream of somebody. Somebody... This is
somebody had a dream of the wrestling event. And then it was down here. Is it canon? It's
canon in a dream. Like, it's a dream canon. That was called Dick Richard versus Fat Germa,
a test of strength. Uh, Germa plays as the best video game character in, uh, video game character
in gaming history. Oh, I'll show you where I'm gonna play. I'm gonna play Team Fortress 2 as the
pyromaniac. I'm gonna be playing Team Fortress 2 as Hackman.
Okay, that was fucking pretty good. That was really good. Oh, I'll show you where I'm gonna play. I'm
gonna play Team Fortress 2 as the pyromaniac. I'm gonna be playing Team Fortress 2 as Hackman.
That, like, I mean, I can go pretty high, but I don't think I can go that high.
That was pretty good. I'm gonna play. I'm gonna play.
That was close. I love the really, really quick ones that just get right to the point. It's just
right here. It's just like 10 seconds. It's just, I had, I made this and just show it. It's fucking,
I love it. Uh, Germa fights Crash PlayStation for the fate of nothing in particular in cinematic
widescreen. Well, actually, this is like, this is actually probably nine. This is probably like
14 by 7. I'm back. It's time for you to pay. Yeah, do I actually find him? He's not looking at me.
I've never seen a bandicoot before.
Not the boulder. Oh, I'm sorry. Sorry. I don't want to. Dude, dude, that's just a
taste of the balling that I'm about to do over here. All right.
Not bad dodging.
How's it going grandpa?
All right.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Rewind. Tevo. Tevo. I want to see this again.
You're going down. Boom. All right. Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Spoilers for Infinity War. If you haven't seen it yet, you have. You've fucking seen Infinity War.
It changed. Spoiler. What? Why are you making me go? How many times did I do this?
I don't. Diablo 4 cinematic trip. You're going down. That's my favorite part. How's it going grandpa?
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. You're going down. You're going down.
That was awesome. Clip that face. Dude, uh, this is, I got a warning for you on this one.
This one might be scary. I just, I've seen the thumbnails on all these pretty much.
I've seen the first images and this could, this couldn't bite scare small children. So
get them out of the room. Okay.
Hey.
There's more.
Um, I didn't even go on a diet. It's not a bad idea. Why is it more?
I actually like this a lot.
Just this part right here. The very first part.
That ABC EDFG. I don't even know how to fucking do the alphabet.
Put the links in the chat, put the links in the chat, put the link in the chat,
put the link in the chat, put the link in the chat. Hold on. I need to put the link in the chat,
put the link in the chat. Oh, we're not, we're not even 20% of the way through these videos.
Put the link in the chat. I don't want you to see them. That's why I'm hiding them right now.
There is the link for that video. I don't want there to be any spoilers.
Let's do the next one. This is called 1 a.m. news animatic. I think I, yeah, I know what this is.
This is, hello ladies and gentlemen, and welcome to the 1 a.m. news where we're reporting on a
local streamer who has gone insane and left his home. Hello ladies and gentlemen.
Fucking naked. Fucking naked. Am I actually naked? Oh fuck.
Remember who has gone insane and left his home. Hello ladies and gentlemen.
Naked. It's not, I'm not naked. That's an image of my chest. It's one frame of nudity.
No, I had like underwear on. I had shorts on. It says,
Jerma goes for an evening stroll in the woods.
You getting anything, Jeff? I'm not seeing anything on the thermal.
Hello? Is that me? Is that actually his iPhone?
Dad, you hear that? Gone. Something took off running.
Let's move that way. Stay tight, guys.
Look at this trapper. What the hell broke that off?
Something bit just hanging on a splinter back there, so be careful.
Yeah. Yeah.
Holy crap. What the fuck was that?
That's right there. Right there.
She's trying to go to the house. Let's get this son of a bitch right now.
Come on, close in on him. Really, dude? Really?
Find out how to go, Jeff. I'm looking right in there. I can't see shit.
Talk to me. It's right there. It went over the hill.
You see that buck? Listen.
Holy crap. How about you, son of a bitch, how?
Don't howl. He's pissed.
Yes, he's pissed. We just heard something howl
here in the woods, and it was huge. It was intimidating.
It was huge. It was super, super loud.
I'm just trying to go to the bathroom.
Holy crap. What the fuck was that?
Nothing to do with this. It's right there.
Right there. She's trying to go to the house.
Let's get this son of a bitch right now. Come on, close in on him.
Really, dude? Really? Find out how to go, Jeff.
I'm looking right in there. I can't see shit.
Talk to me. It's right there. It went over the hill.
You see that buck? Listen.
Holy crap. How about you, son of a bitch, how?
He's pissed.
Uh, this TV show, they just go in the woods and pretend to be chasing Bigfoot?
I'm more interested in this television show.
Yes, he's pissed.
We just heard something howl here in the woods.
Not just Bigfoot. How many other monsters are there out in the woods?
There's animals in the woods. There are bears. There are deer.
There's like wolves, bugs and shit, like frogs.
What monsters are in the woods?
The mothman. It's the devil.
It's a yeti. It's a vulnerable snowman.
They have like 11 seasons of getting just misinterpretations of bears making noise.
Really? All effectively that's happening right here is just a bunch of guys
are stumbling through the woods like irritating and scaring animals.
What do you got, Jeff?
You got anything?
Flashlight.
Walking right up here.
It's not real far away.
It's not.
And they got like guns?
I've never seen a movie. Don't you know that like you're going after like Bigfoot with
what is this a fucking like a shotgun? It's not going to work.
The guns aren't even real.
Bigfoot is you're not going to kill him with a shotgun.
You might be able to kill Bigfoot with like a large rock that you hold over.
Like it has to be as big as like it's like a boulder and you drop it on him.
You're going to shoot him with like a pellet gun.
These guys, they can't even see anything.
What are you going to shoot at? You're going to miss.
Real far away.
He's up there.
I don't see any.
They have these minor helmets on that can only see maybe like three or four feet in
front of them. If Bigfoot is running at you from 200 feet away, you need floodlights and traps and
they're not helmets. They're just bands.
This is an in- I want to watch this show. What is this show actually called?
Yeah.
Rustling leaves in the woods.
Not real far away.
It's called Mountain Monsters.
Mountain Monsters.
Have they ever found a guy camping?
Heard that noise over there.
There's somebody over there.
Yeah. And there's a guy just with like a fucking Campbell suit and he's just like,
hello, you guys all right?
That's called live footage from the Vegas region.
Pokemon Shpee.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't understand his preference.
No, no, you do it.
You do it.
I'm sleeping.
Yeah.
What am I here?
Okay, mom.
Five more minutes, mom.
Jesus.
So what- wait, Pokemon did a 24-hour stream where it showed Pokemon sleeping?
Why did they do that?
It was live from a region in the game.
It was worse than that.
So wait, it just showed like a picture on screen?
It showed nothing and rustling bushes and a horse.
So you tell me that Mountain Monsters has more content in it than the Pokemon live stream.
Interesting stuff.
This is called Lego Intruder Germa in the Bathroom Tiles.
We're gonna go to Lego. This is good.
Let's give it a go.
What the fuck are these?
Would you like some stationery?
We don't want to use- don't use those.
What are these? These are like notebooks.
Those explode.
Yeah, these explode.
Yeah, they detonate.
Yeah, if you throw one, you know, let's say at your feet and then you detonate it,
Are you sure these aren't bathroom tiles?
Holy shit.
This is like custom-made.
What the fuck is going on?
I don't even know.
Is there a game?
Is there a game here?
I don't know.
When do we start the game?
Pizza!
Oh!
Whoa.
Holy shit.
That guy got destroyed.
Pizza!
This is really well done.
This is really well fucking made.
Are you sure these aren't bathroom tiles?
2006 stop motion animation.
This is way better than that.
What the fuck is going on?
I don't even know.
Is there a game?
Is there a game here?
I don't know.
When do we start the game?
Pizza!
So loud, I'm sorry.
That's for the intruder stream.
Memories.
Not louder.
Softer.
This one's called Uh-oh, Germa.
Should I be a...
Oh no, I know what this is.
Do I?
I thought the uh-oh thing was somebody pooping or something.
Stop the video now.
What?
That was Uh-oh, Germa.
That was...
I kind of need to blink a few times after seeing that one.
This one's called Where's Germa?
Where is he?
Where's France?
I'm here.
That one was interesting.
That was an interesting one.
What was that?
There was people looking where countries were in Europe.
And then I showed up and screamed and then the video was ending.
I don't know what happened in this video.
There was an EU meme.
Oh, it's North America.
I don't know.
This is Michael's Rat's Redneck Birthday Party Remix.
World's first rodent superstar year.
Uh, Shazzo.
Shazzoip.
Shazzoip just gave 20 community subs.
This works pretty well.
Michael Jackson.
What's up with the music?
That was fucking funny.
That was good.
That was really good.
I liked...
I really like that one a lot.
I do.
That was great.
Oh, it was such a good boy this year.
This is called Tropical Trouble.
Tropical Trouble.
I wonder what that means.
Bumble Buck Productions.
Called Fast German Triple Alien.
It's this again.
In Tropical Trouble.
Why do we both have steering wheels?
Wouldn't that be counterproductive?
A co-pilot?
But not when you're both turning at the same time.
Yup.
Now they must work together to survive on the island.
It is Purple Alien's job to look for food.
While Fast German will build a shelter.
Fuck am I...
It's a coconut.
What the fuck is that?
How do I not know what a coconut is?
A full turkey dinner.
I don't want that.
Oh, it's an alien.
You're right.
I love the purpose.
Now it's getting dark and they have no food or shelter.
That's it.
So they decide to leave.
How did we get in the helicopter again?
The helicopter just sucked him up.
That was Fast German and Purple Alien in Tropical Trouble.
This is called Germacraft The Breakdown.
Already got a great caricature in this chair.
What's going on?
Why am I crying?
You can tell this is real because listen to my voice.
It's like stuffed up.
Was it just shit face?
You were Omega drunk.
That is actual Omega drunk.
Listen to this.
We actually get to see it on stream.
It's like you pitch shifted me 10 to 20% lower.
Fucking Minecraft is so...
It's a revolutionary game.
Is this when I stood up and did the speech
about how I was moving to Vegas and talking about the community and everything
and I was even blown out by the music?
That's the one.
Okay, I do remember this stream.
This is called Kooky Germa Joke.
Did it work?
That's wicked fucked up.
That's so fucked up.
What TV show is this from?
What TV show is this?
Is this Scooby Doo?
Oh my god.
How would you even find this to match this up?
Holy fuck.
Oh my god.
That's the worst.
That's the best noise I've ever made.
Did that win best noise last year?
It better have.
No, unbelievable.
This is called Germa Fortnight Black Hole Meme.
No!
Am I supposed to be...
Who jumped in?
Oh my god!
It's a mermaid!
Please!
It's supposed to be a YouTube reaction.
I can't see.
This is awesome.
No, no, no.
I'm fucking crying.
God damn it.
You're killing me.
...serial, non-branded, Captain Crunch character that is Fortnite.
Get the off-brand Fortnite.
This is not Fortnite.
Don't sue me.
Can they get it?
What is going on?
Fortnite is going on.
Love for Germa is not.
Wait, hold on a minute.
What you guys need to understand is
the face came here.
This is...
What is this from?
What stream is this from?
It's from The Thing.
That's from Darkwood.
This is reacting to scary fucking monsters trying to kill me on screen.
Why does this work as a YouTuber reacting to Fortnite?
No!
It's a mermaid!
Please!
I can't see.
Oh no.
Like, super overreaction to everything.
No!
He jumped in!
Oh my god!
It's a mermaid!
Please!
He jumped in.
That is phenomenal.
It's so funny.
I can't see!
This is from Darkwood.
Like, I'm playing a terrifying fucking game.
Why is everybody, like, dancing?
You're killing me!
You're killing me, Epic!
I need to know what it is!
What am I saying here?
You're killing me!
No...
Oh, non-Brit...
Right, from The Carnival.
You're killing me.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
We gotta keep going.
We can't get stuck on one video.
Oh my god.
There's so much going on in this.
That was great.
This one's called
Jerma vs Jevil Quest for the Gamer License.
I'm going off-cam for this one.
Because, like, boogers are coming out of my fucking nose,
so I have to, like, wipe my nose.
Asshole.
Oh no!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Nice!
Not bad for someone who died of Pinwheel.
I beat Pin...
Whatever.
People are starting to believe them.
You know?
I've gone to, like, Reddit threads before.
I've talked to...
Have I talked about this?
I probably have, but I need to make it...
I've reiterated again.
Like, someone...
There'll be, like, a Reddit poster.
I'm just like,
What the fuck?
I can't even, like, defend myself.
How am I supposed to, like, defend...
Who?
Up in the smoke.
Why is Stream laughs?
Well, if two in the hand is worth one in the bush,
looks like this guy went shush.
I thought the bits were a part of the video.
Ever heard of the stage tick tock?
No!
Uh, PhylacteryLich just gave 10,000 bits.
Thanks for the 100 fucking dollars.
Again.
And you say,
Jerma, you absolutely have to do another green screen stream.
This community makes amazing fan videos.
Well, that's the plan in, like, two weeks.
In a few days,
there's gonna be another Discord channel to talk about things for me to do,
and we're gonna do another 100, 200 actions in front of the green screen again.
Green screen DLC for free.
That's the title of the stream.
Pretty good title.
I do not want to know about TikTok clock,
but I do want to know about up in smoke,
but Jerma forgets how to use fire magic.
But thank you PhylacteryLich for the 100 bucks.
Seriously.
I'm back.
Up in smoke, but Jerma forgets how to use fire magic.
So I think the thing,
so I think the thing about,
um, I think eating, going on a diet,
it's not a bad idea.
It's, oh shit, hold on, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
There is, wait till he lands, wait till he lands.
Okay, he landed.
Ooh, up in smoke!
No, there, there, I heard it.
I just heard it, I did.
Colonel Mustang.
It didn't work.
Oh, fuck me.
Goodbye.
Oh, a fucking Colonel Mustang for a full metal alchemist.
You can, I love that I'm going to practice outside the room
because I don't want you to see it on camera
because it's embarrassing.
Keep going.
This is Jerma walks a thousand miles.
Everybody watching the VOD right now.
It's about to be quiet,
probably because this is looks like it's probably a full song.
Um, VOD, sorry guys.
You'll be back really soon.
You'll be back in exactly four minutes.
Making my way downtown, walking fast.
Face this path and I'm homebound.
Yeah, just making my way, making my way through the crowd.
And I need you, and I miss you, and now I want.
If I could fall into the sky, do you think time went past me by?
Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles if I see you tonight.
I'm gonna think of you and wonder if you ever think of me.
This is the whole song.
This is really well done.
Wrong way.
20 more community subs from Shazzo IP.
Thank you so much.
40 on the night.
Cause I need you, and I miss you, and now I want.
If I could fall into the sky, do you think time went past me by?
Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles if I see you tonight.
There's more song.
How long is this song?
Does this song end here?
Here come the emotes.
Rich.
Oh, right.
Making my way downtown.
I'm fast.
Face this path and I'm homebound.
I'm gonna get sued by...
What?
What's her name?
Melissa McCarthy?
Making my way, making my way through the crowd.
Who made this song?
Vanessa Carlin.
What?
Melissa McCarthy?
Cause I still miss you, and now I could fall into the sky.
Do you think time would pass us by?
Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles if I see you tonight.
So what if I like fuck up the VOD?
Can I like talk over this and make it so that it doesn't get claimed?
Do you think time would pass me by?
Like what if I just start going like...
Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles if I see you tonight.
Half Life 2 Zombie.
That was gonna work, trust me.
I can't even do that again.
Yes, I can.
I'm fucking so good at it.
It's the worst sound, best sound.
Make up your mind!
I have to sit here for a second cause if the VOD gets muted, it's gonna mute like another minute.
So we have to wait.
I'm looking after you, VOD.
This is for the VOD watchers.
Can I write this down so I can...
I need to communicate with them.
Here, I'll write unmuted soon.
I need to be able to commit...
Wait, don't...
Wait, don't go!
Don't move, don't go anywhere.
My hand is so sweaty.
I can't even write with permanent marker on it.
Here.
Unmuted soon.
Soon.
People thought I was making that shit up.
You wanna see something?
He's lying about how he's like fucking 200 degrees fucking Celsius.
Oh yeah?
This is permanent marker.
I just...
I melt shit when I touch it.
You saw...
It's a Sharpie.
This shit's...
This is forever.
That's such a shitty superpower.
Hey, do you guys remember the writing that was on my hand?
Who was here for that?
30 to 40 seconds ago.
Were you here for that?
Who was here for that?
Why am I on Reddit?
No, love that.
This is wrong thing.
Oh, that's the last thing we looked at on the image side.
Right.
Okay.
Let's go!
This one's called Sick Bass Drop.
I feel like if you did that, if somebody really did that, I think people would think it was
fucking awesome.
You don't think you would too?
It'd be so...
You'd be like, holy shit, this is...
What is this?
This is so different and new age.
They're drunk.
So that's even better.
They could like...
It'll be like, wow, this is the best song I've ever heard!
And then I'll get $500,000 in royalties.
This is German versus Obi-Wan and Anakin.
Hey, what's up, uh...
Is this Vinny?
Is this Vinesauce?
You're gonna pay for all the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
Wait, wait, what?
This is spoilers?
Okay, fine.
Spoilers for Star Wars the prequels that you're gonna skip anyways because you're not gonna
watch the prequels because people hate them for some reason.
I like the prequels.
What's wrong with them?
There's a lot wrong with the prequels, but come on, Yoda has the lightsaber?
Pog.
You're gonna pay for all the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
We'll take them together.
You're going slowly on the left.
I'm taking it now!
No, Anakin, no!
No!
Get the fuck out of here!
How dare you come into my dream and humiliate me in front of my 60,000 fucking viewers!
I'll bring you toilet water.
Problems with toilet?
Think so.
What's up, man?
One more time.
Hey, what's up?
What's up, uh...
Is this Vinny?
Is this Vinesauce?
You're gonna pay for all the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
That's Mace...
That's Mace Windu talking!
Is that Mace Windu?
Listen.
I'm taking it now!
No, Anakin!
We'll take them together.
We're going slowly on the left.
I'm taking it now!
You killed today, Jeremy.
Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
That's Vinny?
No, it's not!
That's the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
No, that's Mace Windu!
That's not...
Is it actually Vinny?
Listen closely.
For all the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
Is this Vinny?
Is this Vinesauce?
You're gonna pay for all the Jedi that you killed today, Jeremy.
We'll take them together.
You're going slowly on the left.
I'm taking it now!
No, Anakin!
No!
Get the fuck out of here!
How dare you come into my crew!
You humiliate me in front of my 60,000 fucking viewers!
I'll bring you toilet water.
The backhand is the best thing ever.
Problem with the toilet?
Think so.
That's what you sound like.
Imagine you had the time to backhand somebody in a lightsaber fight like that.
Ay, ay, ay.
That was fucking funny.
This is called Jerma Awu.
Why is this called Awu?
What brings you out this far?
What is going on?
Now, that's a name I've not heard in a long time.
I thought it was part of the script.
I think my uncle knows him.
I'm just playing Star Wars.
What?
Not yet.
You know it.
Of course I know it.
It's me.
I didn't know auto play was going.
I was trying to figure out what the fuck was going on in this video.
Turn off auto play?
I know!
Well, look, let me give some defense here.
We just watched like a Star Wars one.
I don't know if that was maybe the same person that made the video
or if it was like a group of friends.
They were like, hey, let's make like Star Wars shit in our videos.
I don't know.
That's a weak defense.
That's Jerma Awu.
This is also called Jerma Jump Scare.
What was that?
This is the same thing.
Oh my God.
This is called Jerma Bars.
Jerma Bars.
Previously on Jerma Community Night a month or so ago.
It's like when you get to a certain point when you sing
and you hit the absolute, I cannot do this, but I'm going to try anyways.
That's how you get like the like, now I know.
My A.
You can't like go any higher.
No.
Fucking Souls games.
When in doubt, radish it out.
Sounds like a snare.
One, two, three.
You know the drill.
Yep, we do.
We do.
Oh my fucking God.
Oh, that was a fucking awesome link, link, link, link, link.
Oh yeah.
I'll give you a link.
There you are.
Uh, moving on.
We've got, we've got, we still have a nice chunk of stuff to see.
This one is called Fireman First Day in the Park.
A Jerma985 animation.
First Day in the Park.
Animation by Kit Cekat.
Where are you going, Fireman?
I feel like this could be on like Sesame Street.
Never mind.
No, don't go in the water.
No.
He's all right.
That was cute.
Fireman's First Day in the Park.
You can come back out.
We'll just...
What is going on?
Is he all right?
What the fuck?
Crash it.
Why so many cars?
Holy shit.
Oh, snake.
The snake.
Otherwise.
There goes otherwise.
See, he's okay.
He's fine.
That was really just cute.
Except for the part where the whole thing burnt down.
And then there were 10 car crashes.
It's not the real Fireman.
You mean the whole video.
No, that was awesome.
This is called Source Filmmaker Bill Crazy, featuring Gary the Fuck Up.
Hey, what's going on, crazy fires?
It's me, Crazy Bill Crazy.
I'm here with another video, hit with always.
Gary the Fuck Up.
That's me, Gary the Fuck Up.
And today, as you see, I'm sitting in a pool of water.
Water?
And with water in it.
That's right, motherfucker.
And what's going to happen here today, Gary is going to drop a toaster in here.
That's right.
I'm going to see how long I can last.
It's going to hurt like a bitch.
You know what I mean?
Can't wait.
It's going to scare me.
Yeah.
Gary, I'm ready.
You ready?
Throw it in there.
Make sure you like this video.
Get ready.
Wow, that was...
That was crazy.
Hey, what's...
Gary, I'm ready.
You ready?
Throw it in there.
Make sure you like this video.
Gary the Fuck Up.
That was great.
And then the clown just kind of shows up here.
Wow, that was...
That was crazy.
What's this clown?
Good animation, good stuff.
There's a link.
You got it.
Let's keep going.
This next one is called SCP-985.
That's it.
The Elmo at the end.
Short, sweet, and it was really good.
Way to go.
Uh, I don't know.
This is called the third rat song.
Kinda.
There's the real image of my face.
That was really, really, really good.
Third rat song, kinda.
Yeah, that face will be an emote.
I will make it an emote.
I promise.
This is hard to see.
Why is this community so good at making music?
The better question is why is this community so good at making everything?
You want a link for this one too?
Sure thing.
Coming up next.
We have...
This is called German 985.
Fandango movie clips.
Green screen movie scene, one out of one.
Yes, I knew what it was gonna be.
I knew it.
It's so funny.
Cause like, seriously, sometimes you do like a Fandango movie clip.
It's like eight seconds long.
Why does it have to be this much time spent on all the stuff at the end?
You nailed it.
You fucking nailed it.
It's so good.
Steven Spielberg.
Okay, question.
What the hell is Fandango?
Why do they have all this stuff at the end?
I don't even know what this is selling me.
Is it a product?
Is it movie tickets?
It's a ticket seller.
So what's this like...
What's all this other stuff at the end here?
Do you go to Fandango and click on like I'm in an excited mood
and they recommend tickets for shows?
Yes.
Why would you ever do that?
There were like 10 to 15 movies in the theater at any given moment.
There's like two or three movies per genre for you to see.
It's not that hard.
Sometimes, yeah, less than that.
Like eight in the theater.
What's with the...
Ah, I don't know.
People screaming.
People were just screaming.
I don't know.
People just scream in this chat.
You guys know that.
You've been around a long time.
Why was I saying, ah, yeah, that is you.
That is actually you.
You're right.
Yeah, that's...
Yeah, that's you.
That is you.
All one, two, three, four, five...
All five of you here.
What were you doing?
I wonder.
That was fantastic though.
I want to link this one because like...
This is very, very, very, very creative.
Bingo.
All right.
We have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
There are ten more videos to watch.
This is called Las Vegas Noir.
Side comment?
Las Vegas Noir.
Captain, we were on our way to interview...
Yes, folks, I know.
This particular fiend is an old acquaintance.
I have tried to reaffirm his belief in a wrathful and terrible god.
Whichever way it goes, he did it in reverse.
You look like you've had it rough.
You're maybe five, five, five, six tops.
And you wear size 11s?
I don't think so.
You have no job and nowhere to live by the smell of things.
And you need money.
Answer the goddamn question, Rudy, before I brain you.
You disappoint me, Cole, folks.
Get back in there and make some lunch, boy.
I need a confession.
Hey, hey, whoa.
Why'd you do that?
Why did he just do that?
And you need money.
Answer the goddamn question, Rudy, before I brain you.
You disappoint me, Cole, folks.
Get back in there and make some lunch, boy.
I need a confession.
You can do this in L.A. Noir?
I didn't know you could, like, ragdoll off a building.
Holy shit.
This one's called German 95, 2019, HD trailer.
And it says, joker, parody.
Does it help to have someone to talk to?
You know, my mother always told me.
Deal is not on the table anymore.
I don't know what to do with this stuff.
Is this what you fucking wanted?
You wanted this shit?
Spider-Man.
Hold on.
I want to see this again.
Does it help to have someone to talk to?
You know, my mother always told me.
Be a good boy.
By the way, Spider-Man.
Deal is not on the table anymore.
I don't know what to do with this stuff.
Is this what you fucking wanted?
The age of just deep fakes.
You could deep fake anything on anyone.
Deep fake a costume on somebody.
You don't have to go for Halloween anymore.
You can just pretend you did a bunch of cool shit.
Just put on a cool, just have a computer costume on.
That's a Snapchat filter.
Still, you don't have to do anything anymore.
You just have to put a Snapchat filter on
and then put a fake beach behind you.
It's the same thing.
We only use Instagram stories here.
You want a link to this one?
I'll give you a link to this one.
Someone said, why did you turn the face cam off?
Because I got really sweaty.
I was laughing too hard.
Boogers were coming out of my nose
and I got really sweaty and smelly.
There you go.
All right.
Down to the last 10, I think.
This one's called Precious Germo.
Naked.
The eyes of a killer.
The eyes of Vaude ruined?
No, that's all right.
The Vaude's fine.
That was Precious Germo.
It was a lot of particle effects,
which are really, really cool.
This is called, can't think of a title for this.
It's a Germo meme.
Germo's Last Christmas.
Let it play.
I will light a motherfucker up right now.
I gotta go.
You know what I mean?
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta get out of here, man.
I gotta go.
What is going on?
Oh, okay.
That was strange.
Oh my God.
What the fuck?
What in the name of God happened at the end there?
That's terrifying.
Germo's Last Christmas.
Oh, all right.
I gotta get that off the screen into this.
This is, you know, I don't, well, you know what this is.
Do I need to even tell you what this is?
Let's just.
It only took three weeks to render.
That's so ridiculous.
Actually scary, yeah.
Okay, grass grows, birds fly, sun shines.
And brother, I hurt people.
I'm a force of nature.
But if you were from where I was from, you'd be dead.
I kind of turned into Voldemort for a second here though.
This is actually freaking me out.
I'll give you a link to it though.
That was a lot of render time.
A lot of computer time.
Germo's Scout.
This one's called the quintessential,
the most quintessential arcade sound effect.
Minor prize.
Go for the major.
Oh, fuck, it does that every time.
It does it on purpose.
It's true.
That's what happens when you walk by every single arcade.
You just hear that sound.
Oh, fuck, it does that every time.
It does it on purpose.
Germo, it's been eight hours, please.
What, like I'm stuck playing the game?
It didn't take me that long to beat this one.
They have an update coming up.
They're adding a whole new arcade.
Maybe it'll be worth taking a look.
This one's called F.
Um, hold on.
Nobody look.
Okay.
If you've, okay, I just, I want to check something.
If you've never seen, if you've never seen Attack on Titan,
this is an anime.
If you've never seen Attack on Titan
and you don't want to be spoiled on like episode three.
This is an Attack on Titan like episode three reference.
I mean, it's like, it just is.
It's like an early Attack on Titan spoiler.
Just to tell you, no, just mute me and mute your eyes.
Do you see my shoe?
What?
Why?
Yes.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
Fuck it, yes.
Wow.
This is what it looks like up close.
Turn it off.
Get to shut this off.
Shut them all off.
Turn your lights in your house off too.
This is great.
My stomach.
Things I didn't want to do on camera,
but did them on camera because I explained how badly
I didn't want to do it on camera.
I'll take it for 200 please.
God, that was fucking funny.
You guys didn't give this one a chance and should have.
Link?
Oh yeah.
We got three more videos until Community Content Night number two.
Is that an end?
Two more.
Well, three more actually.
Here comes.
I actually don't know what the last three are.
It could be anything.
This one's called Germa Psycho.
Okay, here we go.
I usually lock up one person per stream and I eat the key
and I've been doing it for about three years now, so.
What?
Wait, what did I just say?
What the fuck?
When did I say this?
Yeah, I usually lock up one.
Is this like out of context?
Yeah, I usually lock up one person per stream
and I eat the key and I've been doing it for about three years now, so.
Life is pain.
I hate life.
Just calm down.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm going to kill you.
You burn your body and eat it.
Every single bit of that will swallow you whole.
I'm going to swallow you whole.
Not so fast.
This wooden desk, you see, is 445 pounds.
And with ease, I can just get it.
I think I just ripped out the ethernet.
Did I?
No, I didn't.
Oh my god.
I'm scared of my own face.
What happened in this video?
When have I said these things?
I usually lock up one person per stream and I eat the key.
I know this one.
And I've been doing it for about three years now, so.
Life is pain.
Just calm down.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm going to kill you.
You burn your body and then eat it.
Every single bit of that will swallow you whole.
I'm going to swallow you whole.
Oh, that's from the Grandpa Does Drugs, right?
From an old, the old Call of Duty video, okay.
I was like, when on earth did I do that?
It's from Black Ops 2, right?
You see, it's 445 pounds.
And with ease, I can just get it.
Nobody used this.
Was this so bad that nobody used it ever?
I sat down and I did like a full like pretend to interview the person.
Does this just suck?
Is it no, is there no footage here that's usable?
What could we use it for?
I don't know.
Not so fast.
This wooden desk, you see, is 445 pounds.
And with ease, I can just get it.
I think it is from the Ethernet.
Wait, what do you do with this?
I guess you don't, I don't know what you use this for.
Don't worry.
You're going to get an extra fucking like eight hours of probably not that much.
You're going to get like an extra like six, five to four to six hours
of new actions in front of the screen.
You use it as a segue.
That's true.
I don't know about this one.
So I'm going to, I'm going to play this and then I might have to stop playing this one
because I see the title and it's, this is, this might be a very quick turn off.
Star, let's put cigarettes out on my dick.
Okay.
So already I know it's not going to work.
I told you I was fucking pumped up to like do this shit.
I'm pumped up right now.
We're both pumped.
Call us the pump brothers.
I'm going to teach you how to pull it off.
Star, are you ready for this?
I want to see how to pull it off.
Okay.
We're not going to play this one.
That was the last one.
That was so fucked up.
I'm not playing that.
No, I'm not playing that.
We'll play this one.
I said it.
Yeah.
Long time ago.
It's here.
What's here?
I know I said this like 10 years ago.
You just linked me the video.
Oh, okay.
Good.
I'm not clicking it.
But that, that actually is the end.
Except, except there's still one more thing.
That's the end of the videos.
That's the end of it.
Thank you everybody for your submissions.
There's, there's a, there should be.
Well, let me make sure there is.
Where is it?
There is.
There is, right?
Is there?
There is.
Okay.
So there are a few songs.
Do you guys remember?
Spoiled.
Do you remember when I did the,
I told you that the rat, the third rats song.
I talked about how that this is what it was going to be.
And I did it and I, and I tried to make it.
Somebody made it.
And this is exactly what it was going to be.
This is the actual, like what the third rats movie song was going to sound like.
Here you go.
Yeah.
And then the horn comes in and then the horn comes in.
You aren't listening.
I took off.
Yeah.
It's because it was really loud for me.
You aren't even.
I didn't mean to not listen.
I could hear it because it was so loud because I had my.
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
No, no.
It was very loud for me.
So even with it out, I could hear it very clearly.
No, the horn comes in.
He hates it.
What?
I don't hate it.
Stop making me shit any grin.
I don't.
It's very good.
The greedy grinner.
That's me.
There's also, there's, let's see what this one is.
I have my first kiss here.
That's before the play, kid.
Big face.
Yeah.
Oh, he's grinning.
He's grinning again.
This one's pretty good.
No emotion.
Why would I do no emotion for a hot single like this?
Our commercial with me or this?
React more.
All right, fine.
No, I'm not going to react more.
Why would you want me to turn it like a fucking cartoon?
Is this what you were looking for?
Wow.
What an interesting song this is.
I especially like this part.
Are we in sync?
That's what Mark Zuckerberg does.
You know what?
Is that what he does?
He just goes like,
I could just like bop my head to this.
This is a head bopper.
Dance to the music.
Thriller shoulder.
What the fuck is German dancing?
Why am I dancing?
Because I'm listening to a community made song.
I painted my living room wall green.
I hope it looks all right.
Did it?
I hope it did.
What's the name of the song?
It's called Jerma 51.
You want to link to this one?
And that...
Wait, we got one more.
This one is called...
This one's called Wait on Red.
It's inspired from the ending screen.
Don't forget this one.
So wait, wait.
What are you linking?
Let me...
Don't forget this one.
Jerma...
Jackson Jerma duet singing September on stream.
What are you talking about?
Did that come in today?
Because this is all as of like last night.
Was it...
Did it come in today?
Was that like this afternoon?
That's gonna have to be on the next one.
It was from 11 hours ago.
The cutoff was yesterday.
Who cares?
I'm trying to listen to a song.
Fine.
Link it to me again.
Follow the rules.
You are the streamer.
Make the rules.
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Save it for next time.
What?
Somebody call me a skull?
Wait, why are you calling me a skull?
Fuck your rules.
Do you want me to just fucking sneeze over there?
And just sneeze into you and have it just...
You just fall backwards.
With the might of the air that comes out of my body.
No, we need content.
This happens every like 30 or 40 days.
It's a perfect amount of time.
Four to five hours.
That's perfect for like a full community stream.
Yeah, we want to have to...
I want this to be like three plus, four plus hours every time.
I'll sneeze in your face.
Well, don't do that.
Give us the post or give us uh oh stinky.
You're not going to get any of those things.
Give me the rats link.
Well, let me link all of these.
This is the rats one.
And then this is the one we just listened to.
I'm not gonna play that video.
Why would I play that?
It's like me gnoming myself.
What's going on?
Why does my camera do this?
No, that's it for today.
See?
Why does it do that shit?
So what's going to happen here over the next couple days is tomorrow...
I have no idea what I'm going to stream tomorrow.
Because there's like two or three things that I really want to do.
But I'm not sure if...
I don't know which one I want to do.
Because like Outer Worlds is something that I thought I would want to do.
Dead Rising 2 is something I want to do.
It's Katamari is another one that would be fun to do like the second Katamari game.
I'm gonna have to like throw dice in the air.
I really don't know.
I'm gonna actually throw dice up in the air.
And whatever they land on, I'll have numbers for each one.
We'll see.
It'll be something fun.
And then as of this coming weekend here, there's going to be another...
I'm going to address you directly because I feel like it's more interpersonal that way.
In like three days, there's going to be another channel in that Discord.
It's going to be the Green Screen Movie Night DLC for free.
You're going to go.
There's going to be two channels.
One to discuss and one to make suggestions.
And then the Green Screen stream will happen probably two weeks from now.
Two to three weeks, depending on how many submissions we get.
Dead Rising 2 has gambling?
Well, you just convinced me.
Eyes up here.
Fuck do I read these things?
Anyways, the whole game takes place in Vegas, does it actually?
Is it for real?
That's pretty cool actually.
All right, thank you again.
I love doing this shit.
I think there's a ton of people that need to be showcased in this community.
I think you guys make some of the funniest shit that I've seen.
They were at least, again, like last time, at least five to 10 of these videos and images
that made me heart laughing.
So I cannot wait to give you guys all more material
because the more material that you have,
the more shit that you could just come up with.
And I love every second of it.
So thank you so much for all of your contributions.
There's a lot of them.
People continue to put stuff.
If you don't know, go to the Discord.
Community content nights.
Put something there.
Art, video, music related.
Something related to the community or the channel.
And I can't wait to see it.
Great fucking job.
I will see you guys tomorrow for either Dead Rising 2 or Outer Worlds or Katamari or I don't know.
No, I'm probably not going to play on stream Death Stranding.
Looks really interesting.
Dead Rising 2 off the record.
Well, you put an emote on it.
So it really is going to come down to what I want to do tomorrow.
I'm going to get up in the morning and I'm going to go, you know what?
That's what I want.
I'm going to do Dead Rising 2.
Or like, no, I want to play like an RPG.
It's how I get up in the morning tomorrow.
Death Stranding is an awful stream game.
I mean, it looks like people are having fun with it.
I know a ton of people are streaming it right now.
I don't think I want to play it on stream though.
More like walking.
It's all good.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We'll figure it out.
I'll be in the pre-stream.
You guys will see me in the pre-stream.
At least an hour or so before the stream starts in the first place and we'll figure it out.
We'll go over what we can do.
Thanks for watching, guys.
So before Community Content Night number three happens,
there will be a second green screen.
So keep that in mind.
The one that will happen in next month,
I might push it back a few extra weeks, like a week or two,
just to make sure if people want to get some of the second green screen stuff in, they can.
Is Community Night monthly?
Monthly with an asterisk because it's probably going to end up to be every month and a half.
Because the last one was in September.
September like 20th or like September like 18th or something.
And now we're at November 10th.
So it's probably going to be like bimonthly.
Because that does have to be enough to do a stream on it.
So that channel will load up every month or two.
When there's enough to do like a three, four hour stream, then hell yeah.
Thanks a lot, though.
It's still the same.
It'll always be.
It's bilateral.
It's always going to be you.
Did he watch?
Stinky.
Yeah, I did.
I watched it twice.
Once in slow motion to make sure I could get the whole thing.
But let's do the bits.
See you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
If you're sticking around, we've got a little bit of extra talking to do here.
So we had snowflakes.
Am I right for 250?
They said my PC blue screened earlier this week.
Got it working this week at about $600 worth of parts later.
That's not good.
I didn't get around to posting on the Discord.
Did a few more portraits.
Plus watermarked the older one.
Oh, stick those in there.
Stick those in there.
These are so good.
Now everybody just everybody just left their portraits.
We saw two of these already.
Uh, I watermarked the older ones.
There is a glue man and auto portrait.
Catching up on all VODs.
Did Kim enjoy the portrait?
I'll upload them to my Insta.
Same as the watermark.
Hope that's chill.
Yeah, they're fucking incredible.
This is fucking unbelievable.
Like, all right.
This was technically...
Technically it was supposed to be there yesterday.
This was supposed to be there yesterday.
Because their computer fucked up.
Okay?
Right?
This is not breaking any rules.
This was supposed to be submitted yesterday.
But look at this.
I promise you guys this is not just like a close-up of like inside of my nose.
Let me get this on the viewing angle here.
I thought this was a photo.
That's how ridiculous this is.
Are you kidding me?
Look at that.
That's unbelievable.
This is a camera.
This is a photo.
I had I gotta break the rule.
You know?
Okay.
My like mother would love this.
Look at this like detail.
I can't even describe how good this is.
Nice work.
Seriously.
That's like a 10 out of 10.
Yeah, they drew this.
They drew this.
And there's another one.
The other one is of Glooman.
And wait a minute.
Oh, please.
Wait, please.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna like actually...
I'm gonna print this.
It's my favorite character.
Yes!
It's Bugleberry.
There's a...
You did a Bugleberry.
Fantastic.
Hold on.
It's wild.
And there's that one and then there's a Glooman as well.
Best car...
Best worst character ever.
Speaking of best worst characters ever.
There's another one.
Good shit.
Let's get it in close.
This is the kind of shit that I would print out all three of these
and put them in small frames and have it decorate my entryway.
That's incredible.
Do it then.
Maybe I will.
Thank you so much.
Sorry you couldn't get it in by today.
But that sucks here about your computer.
That was Snowflakes.
Am I right?
Or Sneewluckeys.
With those insane incredible pieces of art.
Thank you for those.
We had 250 bits from Espada.
They say checks taste like shit.
I agree.
Checks do.
I don't like them.
I think they're very bad.
I agree with...
Don't break everything.
Every time you hear noise like that,
that's me raising my arms to talk with my hands
and smashing into something on my desk.
That's why that happens.
Like me putting my hands up.
Like moving my hands around.
Thank you Topac for the 250.
Shido was alive and well with the whole gang.
They've released a new music video and they're coming for you next.
It's a sweet victory.
Automaton.
Thank you, Topac.
Hey, thank you Stevie the XEV for the 400 bits.
They say I had a dream about you two nights ago
where you were hosting some strange who wants to be a millionaire event IRL with fans
and viewers you invited.
Viewers who lost you started openly taunting
and mocking each time.
My friend got up and nominated me after their turn
in which you gave me a hug
and the event turned into some jackbox game
where the answer is picked by majority vote by fans.
Of course, the first answer was feet.
Feetsies in which you overreacted.
At least I wasn't trying to like chase you and kill you.
Like some people have weird dreams like that.
But thank you, Stevie.
Sad Vega, thanks for the 250.
You talk about how you want new emotes.
Don't forget Jerma infected.
Jerma test.
Someone even shrunk it down and made it look really good.
We're gonna, you know what we're gonna have to do?
Pause the music for a second.
We're going to have to do a night
where the point of the stream is to add emotes.
You gotta catch me on camera, on stream.
And we do it on stream.
This is, I don't know, this will probably take a couple hours.
I will even title the stream like I'm just putting up new emotes.
Don't watch.
There'd be no reason to watch.
But you got me.
And you got me on camera.
And let's put in like 10 new emotes.
We'll probably do that at some point soon.
Not tomorrow.
No, tomorrow, I'm gonna play a game tomorrow.
Hey Stinky, thanks for the 250.
They say eat boogers.
Sometimes you do accidentally.
Everybody does.
It's okay.
Thank you, Alamanda for the 1500 bits.
They say, hey Jerma, I know I really love your streams
because none of my friends know who you are.
And yet I still, I love it still.
Here's a joke as payment.
My girlfriend has a, not allergy.
Something, something, something.
That is like another part of the joke.
I just didn't write it.
I didn't read it.
That's not bad.
But I don't even know why I stopped.
I don't know.
So you admit that you're, I'm not the joker.
I don't even, I can't, I'm trying to piece this like riddle joke together.
I can't, I, thank you for the incredible 1500 bits.
But it doesn't matter if your friends don't know who I am.
It's all good.
Maybe they'll find eventually.
Just link them to the screaming, crying, farting, face slap video.
I'm sure there'll be a fan immediately.
No, thanks for the $15 though.
Seriously.
Thank you, Doc3660 for the 300 bits.
Jerma, I could really use some advice.
I'm 22 right now and I'm really skinny.
I want to gain muscle and get bigger, but not sure where to start.
Do I eat like crazy for a month, get fat and then hit the gym?
Do I just hit the gym right away and eat more at the same time?
Where do I start?
Thanks a lot.
Um, depending on how, honestly, you just have to eat well.
You have to eat a lot of protein.
You have to take in a lot of protein and take in a lot of good fats.
Don't just eat McDonald's and Papa Gino's and Burger King and shit.
And you'll get, yeah, you'll gain weight, all of it in your ass and in your stomach
and maybe a little bit on your face.
The rest of you won't get anything.
You need to eat quality protein, quality food, high calorie foods
that aren't junk.
Eat good fats.
That's like peanut butter.
That's like different oils, like olive oil, cans of tuna straight out of the can.
That's what I did.
But I'm crazy.
Don't like do the shit that I did.
If you want, I like, I can't give you like advice that a doctor would give you.
That's like actually good advice because if I told my doctor that I was eating
like two or three cans of tuna a day, they'd probably be like,
why, what are you doing?
Don't do that.
That's terrible.
And I'd be like, well, I had to get big.
The reason why I ate a lot of tuna fish is because it's cheap.
Because if you need to eat a lot of food, you know, it can get expensive,
especially if you eat, you know, if you're trying to take in more than 2,
300, like 2,500 calories a day that you're trying to work off and like build muscle,
it can get expensive.
Don't get mercury poisoning from eating straight tuna for three weeks.
That's what I'm telling you.
Don't listen to me.
Just eat good food and eat.
Don't just eat one or two times a day like everybody does.
You should be eating.
You should be constantly giving your body energy.
So that's not two huge meals a day.
That's four, five, six small meals over the course of the day.
It's actually much better for you to eat smaller meals than huge ones.
Constant energy.
Drink lots of water.
Guys, you shouldn't be listening to me ever because I...
Okay, I'm going to say something here and then people are going to be like,
you're fucking insane.
All right, I know.
But listen to me.
Are you listening?
Listen to me.
You know what I mean?
Listen to me about this.
You know what I'm saying?
I used to just eat out of the jar tahini paste
because it's the most calorie dense food on earth.
One tablespoon of tahini paste is 89 calories.
Like Winnie the Pooh.
But tahini, it's so calorie dense.
It's sesame seeds.
Tahini is ground up sesame seeds.
Toasted ground hulled sesame.
It's the most calorie dense food in the world.
It's like peanut butter.
If peanut butter took out all like the...
It's good for you.
Tahini is good for you.
Just not a jar of it.
It's got polyunsaturated fats, monounsaturated fats.
It's got no cholesterol.
It's just don't eat a jar of it.
But don't listen to me.
I'm wrong.
And I know I am.
But I was putting tahini paste in place of stuff like mayonnaise.
Like if I made a sandwich like, you know,
sandwich with a lettuce, tomato, a little bit of onion,
some like deli turkey, a slice of cheese, tahini paste.
Because it was going to add like 200 calories to the meal.
What do you mean this keeps getting worse?
Are you eating a turkey sandwich is bad?
What are you talking about?
How have I not gotten diabetes from these foods?
There's like no sugar in tahini.
There's nothing...
Tahini is good.
Tahini is not bad for you.
Tahini, tahini three more times.
Tahini, tahini.
Hummus is another one, yeah.
Eggs, yep.
Guys, everything is bad.
Everything is bad for you.
If you eat a shitload of eggs,
your cholesterol is going to go skyrocketing.
You eat a shitload of fucking fish,
you're going to get mercury poisoning.
You eat a bunch of steak, you're going to get fat.
Everything sucks.
Just mix them all together and eat it like five times a day.
Slowly.
Just dump a beer in there too.
And blend.
No, honestly without fucking around and no jokes and everything,
the best advice I can give you is
eat high quality food more often.
Don't just get fat to burn it off
because burning fat is actually way harder than building muscle.
Sometimes you just won't get rid of it.
It'll just be there for life.
Just don't get fat.
I'm not a dietician.
I just told you I put tahini paste on everything.
She would probably monk a ass when you told her that.
And yes, I said her because my nutritionist was...
I'm like bringing up people in my life.
I'm like going through people in my life right now.
Nutritionists, the people that like helped me do things.
No, don't eat tahini.
I never said that.
It's don't do that.
Cut the music.
You should be doing a balanced diet.
Don't put tahini paste, like a bunch of it on your sandwich.
It's a bad idea.
All right, good.
Don't do that.
Eat some peanut butter on a sandwich toast.
That's what I used to do before bed.
I would spread peanut butter onto a piece of just regular toast,
like a good amount of it,
and I would eat that for a late night snack.
Peanut butter is very dense.
It's very heavy, very calorie dense, but very good for you.
Get the real stuff.
Does tahini paste taste good?
No.
In hummus, when it's mixed together with stuff, yeah.
It's just very, very, very thick and very, very, very distinctive.
It almost like coats your whole mouth and throat.
It's hard to eat.
Anyways, good luck to you.
Seriously, I had a lot of trouble when I was younger,
10, 15 plus years ago, trying to put on weight.
It's a never-ending battle.
Just don't do anything unhealthy,
because you'll cause more problems than you will fix.
I wish you luck.
Hey, Large27, thanks for the thousand bits.
No message, just 10 bucks.
Thank you.
Dino Pulse, thanks for the five hundred bits.
Can you explain the breaking spamming rules problem that chat has?
They are acting like a hive mind,
and that's why the art's been depicting them like robots.
Some of us are human here.
Not to be rude, just wishing us people in chat
would have a much more organic relationship with you, Jerma,
like other streamers.
What do you mean?
Organic relationship?
It's hard to have an organic relationship with anybody
when thousands of people are all saying different things at the same time.
Assimilate the thinker.
I think it's fun when chat kind of goes off the rails.
It's fun to see the collective unit doing things.
But in regards to chat to broadcaster to back to viewer,
there's a lot of people here.
So there's, I don't know what you mean by organic relationship.
Uh oh, stinky.
Why are you guys still writing this?
It's been like two hours.
No, I like to enjoy things as a group on Twitch.
And sure, when I do things like these community nights,
we're showcasing single people that make something or do something,
but we all collectively enjoy it as a group.
It's like impossible for me to ever give anybody like personal attention.
I'm not sure if this is where you're going with this at all,
but I prefer it that way.
This is a meme?
No, no, no, no, no.
I like it when we all enjoy things together as a group.
Because when you start trying to give personal attention
to people that are in chat or in the Discord,
it's hard to keep up.
And I've been guilty of doing stuff like this before,
trying to talk to people and see what's up with this
and what's up with that.
And you kind of get lost because there's a lot of voices.
So I like to keep my stream.
Like we're all just sitting in a giant auditorium,
laughing at stuff.
And then when the lights go off,
I put up a giant megaphone that says,
everybody go home.
Somebody might throw something at me.
And it's like, hey, fucking asshole.
And then they run out the back.
But I like enjoying things as a group.
Personal attention can get, it can get muddy,
especially because considering I don't really know
really, like really any of you.
Maybe some of you.
I like the Borg approach.
I've met some of you guys in person.
Personal attention in parasocial relationships is scary.
Yeah, I just want to keep expectations
completely where I want them.
And that's auditorium full of people
that are collectively all in the same place
enjoying the same things.
Robots.
So I was at Target today.
I love each and every one of you as the unit.
Look, you ever seen the movie?
Okay, we're going to go on a movie rant here.
Okay, God.
Now, I hope you guys understand what I mean.
I love the community, but I like to keep it
an open, fun community.
I would never, I'm probably never going to be
in one of those scenarios where I will,
because sometimes people say, hey, like,
you know, then this is nothing against anybody at all.
You know, people be like, hey, I'll be,
I'll be at X.
Are you going to be there too?
And it's like, I probably not.
Meetups.
Oh, no, that's completely different though,
because that's, you know, hey, this is something
that I want us to do at this event and go.
Find toothpick.
Yeah. And if you look, there's been plenty of people.
And I've recently too, this is not just
something that happened like years ago.
Within the last six months, people have just kind of
flagged me down in random places.
Has nothing to do with being on stream or anything.
And not like a gaming event.
It's just like, hi, I'm going to talk to you.
Or like, I'm going to hang out and I'll talk to you.
So this is not anything to do above that.
Vegas is huge.
Oh yeah. It's way bigger than like the Boston area
in regards to just pure volume and places to go
and where you can run into people.
But I like the madness in chat to answer that question.
To a degree, to a degree.
I'm happy that fame hasn't consumed you.
I think I'm incapable.
I think I might just be dumb enough to like
not be capable of that.
Like the sensor of my brain that could like turn that on.
I don't think it's worked since I was like fucking 19.
He's got a really low IQ.
He always was an egomaniac.
He's a karate kid.
That's right.
It all turned off.
I'd love to meet him.
I'd love to meet you too.
It'd be great.
I'm sure it would be really fun.
But I ain't going to give out my personal phone number.
Why? I don't know.
Anyways, let's keep going.
Not too much more.
We have demoniccucumber250.
You should take italics or Kim with you
for the next green screen stream
and get some double clips for these streams.
I was going to bring in a bunch of random stuff,
but I kind of, I kind of, it's just,
I think I want just to be me.
Plus Kim is not, she wouldn't want to do that.
Ego, ego, ego, ego, ego, ego.
There it is again.
There's the ego.
It's going to be me and my props like Carrot Top.
You know why I want to do it alone?
Here's the reason why.
Because there's something about being in a silent room
alone with a solo camera and a green screen.
It's, it's, it's weird.
I like it though.
It's oddly calming and interesting.
And then I have like the chat right there.
It's really, really interesting.
I got to get that germa psycho emote
because I don't even have a germa psycho emote
and it's used more than half the emotes on stream.
Thank you large for the 500 bits.
No message, just five bucks.
Thank you.
I want to get the, well, not quite yet.
Hey iPod, Matt, thanks for the 250.
Terma, every time someone says peepee poopoo in chat,
it reminds me of my dog Buster.
Instead of asking him if he wants to go for a walk,
I've always said, do you have to go peepee poopoo?
Everybody talks like that.
This is a really, really, really, really cute dog.
We always show dogs on the stream.
It's, it's, it's required reading.
Why is it upside down?
Uh, oh, there we go.
Look it, dogs are the best.
Beautiful dog.
We had those 40 community subs from Shazo.
Thank you Shazo, again, for your 40 subs.
That's a shitload.
We also had, uh, another 1500 bits from large
who has a message this time.
Thank you large for your multiple bit drops here.
Germa, long time fan, but pretty new to the stream.
Only been able to catch a couple here and there.
Usually watch Germa's second and the stream archives.
But I always wanted to send some support
and tell you how much you've made me laugh over the years.
Thank you for being my favorite content creator.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Thank you large.
Uh, glad to have you on stream this time.
Thanks for coming and checking it out.
Thank you.
Thank you Pigeon for the 250 bits.
Terma, I don't know if this is intentional,
but I posted my friend's video
between the SCP Scary Discord one
and the Rap You're So Precious one.
If you did this intentionally, I understand.
But if not, here it is.
Um, it's because this is on Twitter.
Uh, Twitter videos is kind of annoying to show on stream.
So make sure you follow the rules.
The rules say YouTube or Imgur.
YouTube, YouTube, Imgur, Imgur.
Twitter is really, really annoying
to actually like screen cap
because it starts off as this tiny little box
on the person's page.
And then if you try to make it bigger,
it takes up the whole screen.
The Twitter player is, uh, not so good.
Yeah, and Twitter autoplay.
It's just, yeah, yeah.
Imgur, YouTube, or in Discord
because 99% of the time,
I'd say just get it on YouTube.
It's much easier to cycle through YouTube
and have like a YouTube list
than it is to have YouTube, YouTube,
YouTube, Twitter, Twitter, Twitter,
YouTube, Twitter, Twitter.
It just, the format that I have
when I am tabbing through,
it's so much easier for me
just to have them on YouTube and Imgur.
So that's why.
And some videos that were uploaded to Twitter
actually had a second mirror that was YouTube
and that's the one that I used.
Thank you Piff Flavor for the 500 bits.
Germans want to give you money
and say that now 46.3% of my net income
is going to you.
Thanks, you thief.
Why are you giving me 46% of your income?
Shave the first number off of that.
And then I'd still be like,
well, you're giving me that much of your income.
He wants 6% of all your income.
No, I just said even that would be like,
what the hell's going on?
It's the 6% Jerma tax.
Jesus.
Hey, Jay Bong, thanks for the 250.
Appreciate it.
Jerma, you skipped over content I made.
Also, five or six things were skipped over.
Get it together.
Here's the thing.
When I'm compiling this stuff,
some things are going to get left through the cracks.
And whether it's something that I was like,
I want to show this or maybe I'll put it somewhere else.
Maybe I'll try this at the end.
Maybe I'll try this here.
Not everything that's uploaded to the Discord channel
is going to be shown on stream.
It's not as simple as,
oh, there were 425 images.
So 425 images are going to be shown on stream.
I'm kind of just trying to compile them
and put them in if I have this or too many of these.
Because remember, I do want these streams
to still stick in that, you know,
three to four, five, you know, plus four plus hours.
So just because it is put in that channel
does not mean it's going to be shown on stream.
I actually should probably put that in the rules too.
Yeah, that's probably a good idea.
Because the same thing for like the emote contest too.
It's just because somebody put an emote submission in
doesn't mean that I was going to show it.
And there's a potential for,
and this is something I thought
was probably going to happen with this too,
is people could get like annoyed
that their submission did not get put on stream.
But like I said, you have to realize,
I can't, it's not just going to be
every single submission is going to be put in.
A majority of them will.
Just not every single one.
Also time too.
Because when you see the stream go live
that has a community content title,
I'm taking all the submissions
from that period that I did last
to the day before the stream started.
So if you're like, oh, what happened?
What happened to my submission?
What the fuck is going on here?
I put this up today.
That's why.
It's because it's like the day before
so I can start to compile them.
More tidbits.
There should be a poll so we can select what he sees.
No, I'd rather just do it at my own discretion.
Because then you start, people,
there could be like community favorites
and people, stuff that I,
stuff that wouldn't be considered.
Wow, that's so good.
That's so incredible.
Or like, oh, that was really low effort.
A lot of the high effort ones would just be picked.
And then you would also end up
with a bunch of potential like meme videos
that would just get through
because somebody just wrote, oh, stinky.
Right.
But in the rules already,
it does say that it has to be at least,
it has to be related to the channel.
Like, oh, stinky makes no sense for me
to play on a community content night.
It just doesn't have anything to do with the channel.
It's just a video.
It even says, like, it's not like
I'm not gonna watch Gordon Ramsay
who says fuck off a hundred times.
That's community content.
No, telling me your favorite movie is Star Wars
is not community content.
Telling me your favorite video is the gnome video
It's like community-oriented content.
I have never mentioned one time on this stream
the uh-oh farting monkey.
The, there's just that it has no context.
Any game I've played, any stream, any, anything.
Well, I did, we did today.
So maybe it'll show up next time.
So it's only the community if it's about you.
No, it's just the farting monkey
has nothing to do with this, anybody in this community.
What does uh-oh stinky monkey
have to do with anybody here?
Other than somebody shared it to you on like Instagram.
What?
It's everything.
It's my life.
I gotta be careful
because now people are gonna start putting that
in their videos that they make.
It has to be about you and this channel.
And um, is this, is this like,
is this like German and the Blowfish
or is this German 985?
What's going on here?
He's a dictator.
No, long story short, this game content
that like we've played on this stream,
marine screen content, fan art.
Guys, originally, all right, hit the brakes for a second.
All of you guys that are talking smack to me.
This was originally gonna be a fan art section of my streams.
Any farting fucking poopoo smelly monkeys
in the fan art sections?
I expanded the fan art to do like green screen stuff
and like other community oriented videos.
All right, we're moving on, we're moving on.
Long story short, by my discretion
is what I'm gonna be picking to put on stream.
It has nothing to do with how bad or good content is.
Art is subjective anyways, that's right.
The fat germa was the uh-oh monkey, all right.
But it was a picture of me.
That's, it wasn't just the picture of the monkey.
They didn't, they didn't draw the monkey
and send it to me.
It'd be like, why is this monkey here?
All right, cease, cease.
Uh, thank you Flinzenberg for the thousand bits, appreciate it.
Germa really enjoyed this stream.
I just want to let you know that I've been watching your content
since your old TF2 days
and you're still the only person I'm subbed to.
Well, that's, how many of you guys only have like one sub on Twitch?
Is it me?
I saw somebody say me that's not subbed to me.
Who is it then?
Who are you subbed to that's not me?
Oh, I know who it is, Vinesauce.
All right, okay, I'll let that one slide.
Who else?
Star, I'll let that one slide too.
Grillmaster.
Now that's something I cannot, I cannot stand by.
You guys want to know like the 5,000 IQ play for me?
Make a Grillmaster account.
Have it be under my name and have subs on it.
So then people will sub to Grillmaster as like,
oh look, I'm subbing to Grillmaster instead of Germa.
Gotcha, I own that account.
Just play off of, hire like an actor to be Grillmaster
and stream and it's just like an actor that I've hired
and it just all funnels back to me.
That's a pretty good Disney strat, yeah.
So people would be like, oh yeah, fuck you Germa.
I subbed to Grillmaster and I'll be like, what, what, what?
Are you serious?
Get out, get out of here, you Grillmaster asshole.
And then other people will be like, yeah, let's go sub to Grillmaster.
Yeah, they'll get really pissed at about that.
They'll just be like, dude, are you seriously going to do that to me?
Get out of here.
Guys, this is bullshit.
Hey, speaking of people that give their hard earned money
that is never obligated to this stream all the time.
That allows me to live this fucking weird wild life.
Thank you, here they come.
And it's a shitload of people.
How many of you accidentally subbed to me
because you wanted to sub to Grillmaster, I wonder?
Thanks guys, seriously.
But thank you, that was Fleisenberg, or Flinzenberg for the thousand bits.
They said they've been watching for a long time since TF2.
Only person I'm subbed to.
And they also say, have you ever considered streaming the Wind Waker?
Maybe eventually we'll do a GameCube week or something.
Because there are a lot of good games for the GameCube that I passed up.
I have to play Mario Sunshine.
Holy shit, this is some actual legit classics I've never played.
Pikmin, I have to at least play.
Is me not playing Mario Sunshine on stream illegal?
Does hearing that out loud make you guys so angry
that it's against the law for me not to do it?
Put it on the list.
We'll probably do it eventually.
Hey, gnarly, thanks for the 250.
Another awesome community night.
There was so much cool shit the community made
and I can't wait for the next one.
I'll probably make more Soul Calibur VI characters for the next one.
Any requests?
Dr. Schmikeson, that's number one, for sure.
This emote, yeah, do the it's me emote.
That one would be good too.
We need him on the green screen.
That, now that's not possible.
I'm sorry to say.
Yeah, no, I love the stuff that people come up with.
You know what, maybe, oh, I will make people very bad.
What if Bugleberry is on that green screen for like a few minutes?
I gotta be careful though,
because I'm guaranteed to lose a thousand viewers or more.
It's all good, whatever.
With the reverb, I was, there's nothing I can even do about it now.
But thinking back on that, I was like, fuck, it's so loud.
But yeah, definitely Dr. Schmikeson.
Thank you doorkeeper the 250.
Did my video get lost or did the mods hate it?
It's not mods, it's me.
I didn't hate your video.
I didn't, but I'm just saying it's me that's making these decisions.
Based on a couple of internal factors.
No, that's, you're taking the words out of my mouth
and you're putting them in order the way that I said them
and adding hate on them.
No, like I said, I gotta put that in the rules.
That a submission does not mean it'll be on stream.
I think school's bill sucks.
It has nothing to do with videos being bad or video,
it's just trying to compile an equal amount of things.
And no, I'm not, I might hate your video.
That's not what it is.
Sometimes length or how long something is
or the content of the video, it could be anything.
Have you seen them all?
No, I don't watch the videos.
What I do is I open them.
I click, click, click.
Okay, hold on.
Let me see right there.
See the length, see the subject matter.
I go, what is this?
You judge the book by its cover.
Yeah, that's not how you guys read books.
I've read all the Lord of the Rings.
All I had to do is read the first fucking one page
on the back and the front.
Also something that I, okay, I'm gonna have to update the rules
because something that it's like, it's so subjective
that I have to update the rules
because a lot of submissions would come in
that would just like clips of the stream
or like clips of other people's streams.
Have mods filter?
I mean, they kind of already do in a way.
He's changing the rules for his benefit.
Well, also that's a lot of work too.
Hey, Marge compiled like fucking 400 videos for me
and like 200 pieces of artwork
and because they can't
because I have to show it on stream.
So they would have to make new playlists every month
and they'd have to give me like an Imgur file,
an Imgur album with hundreds of photos in it and stuff.
That's too much to ask somebody.
That's for me to do.
And they help a shitload for a lot of stuff
that you guys don't even know.
Dorky says, I understand and not everything be watched
but if I submit a video and you don't watch it
and I ask you why there's a variety of factors.
I'm just gonna update the rules
because right now it's,
I have it for under 10 minutes for videos
but it realistically should probably be under five.
And I think that was probably what the,
I think the video you uploaded was like five and a half minutes,
six minutes or something, right?
That's probably what it was.
Unless for like there,
because let me try to think of like some scenarios
where more than five minutes for like a community video would be.
Maybe in some cases, no music videos,
no full music videos.
Maybe to, this is so early, you have to remember.
Like this is the second one that I've done.
So I'm still trying to figure out exactly how these are gonna play out.
But like full songs, videos like over five minutes maybe,
I'm trying to think of what would work
because the bottles getting nuked on some of them.
Yeah, the music based ones are really good.
Yeah, that's right.
I mean, it's, I don't know, it's a learning process.
Just do an empty playlist.
Do all the music videos last so they get muted together.
That's a possibility too.
Are the ones being bypassed considered for next time?
For the most part, no.
But there are a few of them that I didn't show
that will probably just be on the next one.
I think door cubes yours in particular.
Because I'm still trying to figure out like length of videos.
And that was not on the rules at all over the last month or two.
So just write solid rules.
Well, there are rules there, but here's the thing.
No one will ever be happy.
That's just a fact.
Because if I make a rule that somebody doesn't like,
they'll be pissed off about it.
Don't have videos longer than five minutes.
Well, why not?
Don't have videos that are a majority of just clips from the stream
that we already have seen.
Why not?
Here come the protesters.
Ban Jojo videos.
Well, what if I didn't do that?
What if I do that?
What if I didn't do that?
Ban Jojo videos and dumb clips.
Do you see what I'm saying?
Somebody's already writing that.
Somebody is already writing that.
Ban my content.
What I'll end up doing is I'm going to go through
and put in some more like hard rules.
Because there are only a couple of real hard rules there right now.
Remember, this is the second time we've done this.
This is community content night two, not like 30.
Trying to figure it out as we go.
Flaccid rules.
If your submission got bypassed,
wait for the new rules to show up, which I will do them.
I'll do them later on tonight and probably tomorrow.
We'll see.
They'll be there in the next day or two.
Check through the solid hard rules that I'm going to write.
And then bingo.
Put it in.
Nice hard rules.
But to be fair though, there really were only, I think,
a handful of omissions.
Some of them may not have even been intentional.
You know, of the hundreds of submissions, almost all of them got in.
And unfortunately, when you're doing a new thing,
sometimes something falls through the cracks and
somebody's like, what the fuck happened?
And it's like, let's figure it out.
And that's what we're doing.
You need a German 985 quality assurance team.
Yeah, but then it's the mod's fault, right?
If I give a set of rules to the mods and then the mods go through
and they omit things that are not of the rules,
then everybody hates the mods.
And then it's just the cycle continues to repeat itself.
But to end this conversation,
if something you submitted was not shown,
check that Discord, the pinned message in the Discord channel.
I'm going to give like a bang, bang, bang, bang, bang rules.
Check your submission, do it again.
But also remember that omissions are probably still going to happen
just because of time and amount of submissions.
And it's not guaranteed.
Your video can't ever be guaranteed to be on stream
because what if it gets removed from YouTube?
That's not my fault.
I can't be like, it's guaranteed if you submit it with this.
It's going to be on the stream.
There are things out of my control that might happen
that I can't guarantee.
Like if your video gets like removed from YouTube or something,
or like your channel gets like striked,
I can't, there's nothing I can do about that.
Talk to YouTube and use some of your clout.
If you think under a hundred million years
that YouTube even has employees that work on a day-to-day basis
that listen to fucking content creators,
there are people with like 50 times more subscribers than I do
that get like the default support letter back.
That ain't going to happen.
But we got two, three more bits to do and we can go to bed
and I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Thank you.
Spooky Spitfire for the 250.
So Jerm, there are a couple things I have to say.
First, thanks for you for resisting the uh-oh vid.
Aside from meme value, it's the bottom of the barrel.
Second, I honestly haven't even touched Sekiro
since the last time I donated.
I don't know, something about Sekiro just turns me off.
Also, new ranting, new rating.
Dark Souls 1, Dark Souls 3, Bloodborne, Dark Souls 2, SD2, Sekiro.
Really?
Dark Souls 2 over Sekiro?
They're both pretty polarizing, I can see that.
Dark Souls 2 is better than Dark Souls 3.
I'm not sure, sir, I agree with that.
Third, what video is this?
It's an old video I did in like high school.
With friends of mine, we've gone over it before.
We have touched on this video like three or four times now.
Over the course of the last year or two.
Pretty weird video, yes.
Basically, there's new terms of service they can make a terminated channel
that isn't providing them income.
Their wording is vague enough that it can be interpreted as against
actually shitty videos or small creators.
Wait, what?
Is that for real?
What the hell is going on over there?
Jerma Ass Stinky Feet.
You changed your name, thanks.
You changed it to instead of has, okay.
Thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, a while ago you said if I didn't donate 46% of my net income to you,
you wouldn't be able to afford dog food.
Is this the same person?
I feel like these are the same people.
With two or three different Grillmaster accounts.
Is that what's going on?
What's with this 46.3% income thing?
You are a hive mind, that's right.
Chunky Baloney, thanks for the $5.75.
I know you love this monkey, stinky monkey thing,
but please stop talking about it.
The Jerma brand is better than this.
God damn it.
Thank you, Jay Bong for the 250.
Yeah, for the next green screen night,
please get some better lighting and camera quality.
Well, the lights are just the studio lights.
I can't really move those,
but the camera will be better this time.
That's for sure.
And then DoorCube, thanks for the 250.
This is touching upon the rules again.
I will make the rules very, very clear.
I have in my mind what I want them to be.
It might take me a day or two to get them up there in the pin message.
But just check it out again.
Your video was the carnival thing, right?
Carnival and like italics, like talking about me and stuff, right?
I'm remembering this correctly, right?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Yeah, that one probably should have been shown.
I must have omitted it.
I think it was the length,
but then it was like a 10 minutes was the length and
that'll be shown next time.
I actually remember that one specifically
and like clicking it and having it on a tab.
So it's my bad.
Shave my eyebrows.
Why would I shave my eyebrows?
No, no, the rules need to be hard.
They do.
I just like I, like I said, I had this thing in my brain where it's like
if you give hard rules for stuff about like what is like art and content,
it's like you start to run that line of
how can you even determine what's like should be allowed and what shouldn't be
when it's just like community meme nights.
It's a hard thing to do.
Like know this, know that, know this, do this.
Keep it under here.
Keep it over here.
It's hard to juggle it, but I'm going to put some legit rules again.
Third time's a charm.
We'll see if we get it right by number three.
And that's not to say anything was wrong.
This is fantastic.
These streams, the last two of these have been fucking amazing,
but including the people that should be included
is obviously a big part of it too.
So I'll get it right.
I'll get it right.
Anyways, we are at almost the end.
Lazy Luke.
Thanks for the 250.
Jerma, I made you this Jupiter page.
If someone does a jupin chat, you can click it to save the earth.
Wait, what?
You can click it to save the earth.
No one's done one.
Click on Jupiter to save earth.
Oh, I want to get this on stream.
This is really cool.
This is cool.
Is this going to work?
I think so.
Take a look at this.
There's some Jupiters.
Let's see them.
It actually works.
Can I click the mes?
Come on, flood it.
Let's see it.
I want to see more, more, more, more, more, more, more.
Only two?
Only four?
You can do better than this.
All right, I'm going to let them come up for a little bit.
Oh, shit.
Here we go.
That's because of slow mode.
Go for it.
There we go.
Here they come.
Save earth quick.
This is so stupid.
I love it.
Oh, shit.
You guys are kind of hammering down right now.
Nothing's touched earth though.
I protected earth flawlessly.
All right.
Let's kill this.
That's really, really cool though, Lazy Luke.
Another addition to the JermaBorg website.
That's good stuff.
That's really neat.
All right.
I got to put slow mode back to, I don't know, 10 seconds?
What was it?
What was it at?
Five seconds?
I have no idea.
But thank you to Cold Warhol.
Thanks for the thousand bits.
They say thank you so much for showing my art.
I'm glad you liked it.
Here's 10 bucks for not playing the stinky video.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
And yes, by all means, all the artwork was fucking awesome.
Grill Master is now hosting you.
Well, that's not even the right name.
So nice try though.
It's Grill Meister.
Frodiun Weapon, thanks for the thousand bits, Frodiun.
Love and appreciate the streams as always, man.
It was pretty low energy this month,
so I missed out on this month's community content night.
But I will try my best to submit some art for next time.
Can't compare to some of this amazing talent on here though,
but I won't let it deter me.
Don't be deterred.
Everything that was shown today had its own value.
That goes for videos and for art.
I just gotta work out the kinks and the rules.
But thank you.
Hope to see a submission from you soon.
Hey, Jerma has stinky feet, thanks for the 250.
I already got this one.
I don't know, because it's the 46% thing again, right?
Large, thanks for the 500 bits, large.
They say do it.
Scream, do it.
Why would I?
I'm not gonna scream.
Scream.
Verdebril Giant, thanks for the 250.
Just wanna show you Lazy Luke's game.
Thanks for the gut-busting stream.
It was a lot of fun.
I love this shit more than anything, so.
Getting to sit back and just watch the crazy shit that you guys do.
Get lurked on, what?
Well, I'm clicking the link.
I did actually see this already,
because this was submitted today.
I gotta put that in the rules, too.
Gotta put that in the rules, too.
The day before the stream, I got all the rules already upstairs.
In my mind.
I did say this is fucking awesome, and it's hilarious.
But I have to add to the rules that any submission that happens
at like 12 a.m., the day of that stream,
it's gonna be the next time.
But, I mean, you're a goddamn founder, so.
There's only fucking 20 of you.
Wait, did that work?
It did not work.
Why?
Oh, yes, it did.
I mean, you're a damn founder, so.
Do I have a big forehead?
Oops.
Wait, go back.
Go back there.
Go back, go back, go back.
Back, back, back.
Sorry for bumping you twice.
I do have a big forehead?
It's glue, man.
No, I guess I do have kind of a bumpy head.
It's awesome, though.
And we're gonna show it again next time.
Thank you.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow for, I don't know, Dead Rising.
I don't know, maybe Outer Worlds.
I don't know, maybe Katamari.
I don't know, maybe a PlayStation game.
I who fucking has any idea?
Could be anything.
Bath Bomb Boy, thanks for the 250.
You gotta make some of this art and merch.
They're such good designs.
They are.
But that's another thing that I want to get right.
It's really easy just to be like,
yeah, we'll do art on some of those.
And I'm gonna sell them.
But once money becomes involved,
it's, you gotta do that shit right.
You don't want anyone to be unhappy
or get taken advantage of,
or it's gotta be done correct.
Double music.
Zipper rule.
Oh, right, right.
Yeah, sorry about that.
And again, I do want to say,
if your submission didn't get through, I'm sorry.
It's hard for me to guarantee submissions.
But with solid rules,
I think that that won't have to be up to, like,
my discretion for the moment that I happen to look at it
and see what it is.
So hold me to that.
In a couple of days, look at that pin channel.
There'll be actual real, like, one through eight set of rules.
Sound good?
Sound good.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Hold on, but to be fair,
to be fair, for the most part,
I was referring to the uh-oh stinky monkey
being, like, not eligible for a submission.
That was where that conversation started.
All right.
Good night.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Take care, guys.
Wet Warrior, thanks for the 300 bits.
They say do me a favor to have a good one.
You too.
Right at the end.
See you soon.