Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Friday before Christmas. Christmas Eve is tomorrow. I can't wait. I love Christmas time, guys.
And you guys should all be excited as well because the giveaway is tomorrow at 9 p.m. Eastern Standard Time.
Good luck to everybody, and if you have no idea what I'm talking about,
there's gonna be a link in the description. Go enter that contest. You have until tomorrow morning to do it.
And because we are talking about Christmas and Christmas Eve, on Sunday, Christmas Day,
there will be a Grandpa episode. A very special Christmas Grandpa episode.
So stay tuned to Machinima Respawn for that. Sunday at 4 p.m. Pacific Time. Check your local listings.
So what are we doing right now? This is a direct hit soldier on Hoodoo, Payload Hoodoo.
I've gotten a couple of requests from the same person over and over again to do this.
So hey, I'm finally gonna do it for you. The guy that's been asking for like two months.
I'm gonna give you your direct hit gameplay. Here it is.
Sorry it took so long. So the loadout is gonna be the direct hit, the shotgun, the strain shotgun, and the equalizer.
I do a lot of work, and the title of this video is something that's gonna be like Century Madness
because they have like five or six engineers with a ton of century guns,
and I take out so many centuries with this thing, it's insane.
And that brings up a great point. This rocket launcher, thanks for the Uber by the way,
this rocket launcher can take out a level three century in two rockets. That's it.
You don't have to shoot it five times, you just have to land two rockets,
and it takes about one and a half seconds to drop a level three century.
This is obviously if the engineer is not right there repairing it like this one is right now,
but regardless, it can be a lot to have to handle if you are not standing right next to your century gun.
You will lose it in one second. You have to use the element of surprise, I guess,
when using the direct hit going after a century.
It is especially important in not a situation like this where there are a million people, a million century guns,
but in a typical situation, the other team will have maybe one or two engineers,
and they'll be going back and forth, grabbing stuff, turning around, whacking the century.
So if you time it right, if you can sit there and observe an engineer doing something,
you can take out the century within a split second of him turning around.
Get Ubercharged here, take out the century in two shots, and the engineer, go after the dispenser as well,
and if you were paying attention, I killed this is number five right here.
That's five centuries that have gone down in the last 30 seconds.
So if you can see what I'm talking about, it's pretty ridiculous.
Somebody else killed the fifth one. I think I had four right there,
because there was one over on the left side that somebody took out.
But regardless, I die right here, yoink, crit rocket in my face.
Let's skip the respawn time, because nobody wants to watch that.
So if you are looking for direct hit tips, I can't really give them to you.
I can maybe give you one, but the reason for that is because I don't really use it that often.
I use this and the cow mangler pretty much the same amount of time.
They're my bottom two rocket launchers.
So I can't really give you a whole lot of crazy things.
That being said, I can tell you one of the biggest tips I can give you,
make sure you always have at least two rockets in this clip before you go after somebody.
You will miss a lot with this thing.
And as you'll see here, I actually get ubercharged in a second,
and I miss this heavy like seven times in a row.
And the reason why it happens is because I keep reloading once, shooting it, reloading once, shooting it.
That doesn't work with the direct hit.
You have to really be precise. You have to know when to shoot.
You can't just blow around like a regular rocket launcher. It doesn't work that way.
Another tip I can give you is aim low.
I found this to be very, very true because if you aim too high with this rocket launcher,
you are going to go right by everybody's heads and you're not going to hit anybody behind anyone.
You want to try and go right for the gut, right for the breadbasket, right in the middle of the stomach.
Don't shoot too low. Don't go for their feet or their shins because it might just blow up in front of them.
But the reason why you do it is you're going to prevent yourself from shooting rockets into the skybox.
I can't tell you how many times I've shot this rocket launcher,
and it goes whizzing by everybody into a wall or into the sky.
Another tip, this is the last one I can give you right there.
If somebody gets too close, have your shotgun ready to go
because it's actually pretty difficult to land a direct hit shot somebody right in front of you.
I don't know, maybe that's just me, but it's actually difficult for me to do that.
So I just whip my shotgun out if they get too close, put a couple of shots in their face and they are dealt with.
Now this part right here is the most ridiculous part of the entire gameplay.
I get ubercharged right here. I promise you, none of these people are bots.
None of them are bots.
If there were any bots, there were probably only one or two.
Nothing like the whole team. I don't know. I have no idea.
You'll see what happens.
Come around this left side here.
Engineer tries to build another sentry.
I take it out and I take out the dispenser.
Oh my God, a sniper!
Don't worry, got my shotgun.
Take him out, take out the dispenser and then watch.
I feel like I was a disguised spy.
I really felt like I had a disguise on.
I was like, what the hell is going on?
I'm literally behind the whole team and no one is acknowledging me.
Even if these people were bots, they would have turned around and acknowledged me when I shot them.
This is like, what is going on?
Eventually, they start to acknowledge I'm here because I think they see the cart is moving.
But look, even still, I'm still just sitting on the cart just going, okay, I'll just pick off random people.
And I kill a bunch of people.
I get this guy, get that guy, take out one more person, then I get killed.
And if you take a look at the timer, there's only 30 seconds left.
Here's my feeble attempt to get on the cart within five seconds.
Does not work out and we lose the game, unfortunately.
But that's gonna be it, guys.
Have a very, very Merry Christmas if you happen to celebrate it.
Have a fantastic weekend, everybody.
I will see you all next time.
Take care, everybody.
And good luck on the contest!