Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Nightmare House 2, Chapter 5, and Chapter 6. That's right, I'm gonna do a double episode tonight, because I did not upload this yesterday, and you haven't seen Nightmare House in, well you saw it last week, but still. Gonna do a double episode to try and get through this series a little quicker. So let's go!
Chapter 5, what do I got? Looks like there's a little bit of a thingy thing here.
Flashlight used to be charged. This is the only way I can go, right? This is the only way I can go. What the hell is that? What is that? What is that thing? Pyro Technic Locker? Okay. Flare. Should I just run around with this? I have no idea what's going on. Hold on. Do I pick this? I gotta see what's even over here. Looks like a door that can be opened. Sure thing! Maybe not. How come I can't take these off? Is there another...
entrance or something? Well, there goes that one. Don't have very much. There it is! Get out of the way! Get out of my way! I got places to go!
I gotta bring this down here, don't I? Come on, light the way! A trail of flares. This is fantastic. Very good. There's one up there. Can I get out of here? No, I cannot! You're coming with me! Get out of here!
Hold on. Before this runs out, can I get in this little room? What's in this little room? Nothing? Looks like nothing. Come here! Come here! Come here! Come here! Come here!
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho! Pyro Technics! All kinds of Pyro Technics! Turn you on? Alright, let's turn it on!
Where's my guns? Where are my guns, man? Where's my guns? Did I lose my guns? Did they get taken from me? That's a lot of BS. Oh, now the flare is gone. Oh, great. And a room that's totally dark.
Should I go back and get... You know what? Screw it. Let's go. This guy's gonna get up. Yeah, he is. Stay down! It's like strobe light effect. I can't even see where I'm going.
Oh my god, there's another guy behind me! How am I supposed to... I need my guns! There's one down. Just gotta time it. Get him! Nice, nice, nice. Okay. So far.
Finally, my... Good god, what is that? Oh, it's the entrance to the green room I was just in. No flashlight, though. That's awesome. Forklift? Anything else over here? No, I'm gonna drop down.
Oh, I'm gonna throw up, man. Oh my god, this is like... I don't even know where he is. What the hell? Where is he? What's going on? Oh my god, he's like right in front of me! Oh my god! Oh my god! I don't even know where he was.
Please, please! Just get unloaded on! You creep! There's gonna be another one. Man, I can't see anything. This is so horrible. Get away! Where is he? Where is he?
I'm gonna break this. Oh, get me out of this room before I lose my lunch.
Okay. So that means like a saw is gonna come down and hit me in the face. Oh, you know what? Great. Great. Hey, hey, look at this! Closing me in the room! Hello? Hello? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What do you think? There's nothing I can do.
What am I gonna like launch? What am I in, like a spaceship? Nice. Nice. That lady is a troll if I've ever seen one. Nothing I can do over here except go in another vent. These things give me the most amount of trouble, guys.
Like, I really get so... What the... Get out of here! You go first, Flair. I don't want to go. There is nothing up there. Pyrotechnics. I thought that thing was just leaking gasoline for a second. We need all kinds of light. I'm lighting up the entire place. Get out of the way.
Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. That's the nicest thing anyone's ever done for me. Another Flair. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Oh, yeah! What the hell? Oh. Hello? Yeah. Yeah. How did I... I must have fell through. Okay. At least I got my flashlight back. Oh, this asshole. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I already saw those guys. They left me for dead. Yeah, don't worry. My entire squad died. All thanks to you. Shut off the equipment. Oh, he swore. I heard what he said. Coffee? I'll take a coffee and break it. Let's go. Charge that light. I don't want to use that yet. So, get through the door, man. What are you doing?
Hey. What are these? Crash test dummies? Which way am I going? Oh, we got the crash test dummies. Stop. Wait, what? Wasn't this thing just standing right here? Okay. Let's go. What the hell? What? Are these things alive? Why can't I go through them? What the hell is going on? These things are going to follow me, aren't they? Yeah. Get through that. Door closed. Oh, my God.
I feel like if you guys have ever seen Billy Madison, the part in Billy Madison when the principal comes out of the house and the kids are trying to tell the principal, open the door. Oh, my God. This is the freakiest. Oh, my God.
But when the principal comes outside and there's a bunch of kids out there and he's like, Oh, hello, kids. Hi. And then he like takes two steps and there's more kids. He's like, Oh, jeez. And then there's more kids. That's what's happening right now. These things just follow you around. Oh, hey. Oh, look, it's Jerry. Open up, Jerry. Yeah, let me in. Oh, let me in the door. Hey, open the door. You dip. You idiot. What is this guy doing? What does he want me? You want me to go around? You can't let me in?
Like, open the door for me. Thanks a lot. You dumbass. Yeah. Now, what are you doing? Are you? Can I get in here now? Hey, thanks. What's up, Jerry? You troll girl. You're not Jerry. So apparently these mannequins or these dummies, whatever they are, they eat people, too, apparently, because that was Jerry. Where's Dugan? What have you done with Dugan? What have you done with? I don't want to get close to this lady. Well, that's one of my other guys. Computer. Wait.
There's probably bullets or something over here. I don't want to miss something that I need. Potentially get some bullets or something. No, there's nothing. Isn't that just fantastic? Let's go. This thing's going to move. Watch. Nope. Yeah, that one is. Don't want to waste these. I got to shoot these guys. Got to make these count, though. Don't just shoot for no reason. Flare bullets. Good, good, good. I'll take that flare. Where am I going to bring it, though? That's the real question. Cold drinks.
Sure it is. Get out of here. Get out of my face. My god, this guy's relentless. Oh, my. Get out of here. There's another one. You know what? Get headshot. All right. I don't want to waste that on you. I'll just crouch down and hit you in the face. Play ball. Get out of here. Limey bastard. Hello. Telephone. Charge the light.
Wait. Get. What is going on? What? Oh, my God. Oh, my God. There's so many of them. How am I supposed to kill all three of these? Get off the other gun. Take that. Take that. Get out of here. One more. One more. Send them to hell. Good gravy. Now I have no weapons. Can't get in there. Can I go up there? No, I cannot. But I will take this flare for sure. Anybody in here? Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. No, you can't go in that door. So you might as well climb up all the steps. He ha. He ha. Who? Give me the flare. Dude. All right. Nothing. Nothing. Nothing. Radio room. I found it. Hooray. Now I can call my grandmother. Get away. Close this door, too. Incoming transmission from Dr. Butthead. Paging Dr. Butthead. Incoming outgoing.
A lot of incoming stuff going on here. OK. I've really had to unscrew the top. That's pretty ridiculous. Make sure you unscrew the top of the gas can. All right. Let's get it. Yeah, you're probably right. Actually, can I go in this door? I can. Let's go. Oh, dear goodness. Hey, everything's blowing up. That's probably not the way I should. Whoa. Hello. See you later. That's not the way I want to go. Yes, it is. Side step. Side step. Get away from me.
Get away from me. See you later. How's your Christmas? Have fun. Happy Thanksgiving. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Cannot go that way. Give me that health. Oh, I can't. I have to go that way. No, I can't. Back this way then. No. Where am I going? Why am I locked in here with the flames? Let's go back this way. Probably missing something. It's like the water. Bullets. Thank God. Oh, here we go. OK.
Maybe I could make the jump. Oh, OK. I got to make the jump. I'm stuck. I'm stuck. I am legit stuck. Not anymore.
Fire. Fire. Put out the fire. Hey, I wonder if there's going to be something behind me. Yeah, fire. Yeah, it'd be nice to open the door right now. OK. Thanks, lady. Appreciate it.
Get. I'm assuming I got to follow her. Into the morgue. I want to go in here first. Is there anything in there? There is. Oh, that was the door I could have gone in anyways. And all kinds of stuff is flying all over the place. Dead bodies. How sufficient. And that's OK. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I'm being like worked on right now. What? I'm like Skeletor now. I turn into like a supervillain.
That was interesting, to say the least. Hey. Oh, here's my crew. Yeah. Can you give me one of your guns? Do you copy? Oh, my God. Yeah. Give me health, guns, ammo and weapons. Heck yes. One civilian killed in action. All right, let's go. You leaner. Look at this guy. Just nonchalantly. Dude, there's a zombie apocalypse going on right now. And you're just leaning. You got to be ready. You got to be ready to rock and roll, man. Get out of my face. Chapter six. Evac.
Looks like we got some stuff. Hey, how are you? Keep moving. Charge the light. Yeah, I know. I know. I'm coming for you. This guy had a bad day. See, that really stinks. When you get a garage door closed on you, you know something's wrong. This way. Oh, I see a vent. Can't wait. Great. You want me to get into this vent? Easier said than done, dude. What do you think I am? Michael Jordan. I can't like jump that high. I can't like slam dunk into there.
I got to get. Yeah, I got to get in there. Head up. Head up. I'm stuck down here. So, oh, you can lift the forklift. Interesting. Interesting. Let's do it again. Charge the light for a second. Lift me up. Whoo. I'm at Disneyland. I love the rides. Oh, my goodness. Gracious. Pull out the gun. Hi, guys. What? What? What?
Just corpses now down there. Oh, that's just fantastic. That is amazing. I'm so glad that this is happening right now. Let's get out of here. So I lost all my guys. They all just like disintegrated into bones. God. Storage or that way? Storage. No storage. Okay. Be that way then. Be that way. What? What? You guys was just dead. Especially you, Dugan. Let's go. Yeah, blow it. Can you blow that up? Please tell me that you can do that. By the way, how come this guy didn't tell
me he could do this before? Yeah, you could open every door like that. Give me your shotgun. I'll take it from you. You're not really putting it to that much use anyways. Lair. Nobody can see. A bunch of boxes. Yeah, bunch of boxes. Hey, yo. Hey, how are you? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What is going on behind us? Oh, my God. I'm wedged in by the moron behind me. Hey, quit wedging me in, dude. Oh, they never stop coming.
Another flare. Pick it up. Bullets. Making sure I'm not missing anything. Let's go. Hey, get your magic shotgun over here and open this door. Oh, he did. Never mind. You're not needed. Bullets. Another flare. Let's go. Get me out of this maze of boxes. More bullets. They're preparing me for something, guys. You guys can handle that. I'm running ahead. Yeah, go ahead. Follow him. Follow them. Leave me be. Keep going. Keep going.
Keep moving. See you, guys. Thanks for the distraction. Oh, wait. Are they still alive? Hey, you made it. I'm so happy for you guys. Are all three of you here? You are. Very good. And I got plenty of bullets. Hey, shaky screen. Shoot it. Shoot it. Will you just use the magic shotgun? This guy's going to blow up and turn into a zombie right now. Oh, my God. I'm hiding behind this thing. Oh, it's not going to happen. OK. Get out of the way. Yeah, do it.
Magic shotgun. Shoot the door and it opens magically. I like your style, man. Hmm. We need to get that gate open. You two go see if you can find the controls. I'll stay here with him until he gets better. Yeah, that's a great idea. He's going to blow up and you're going to turn into a zombie, too. Go ahead. Are you kidding me? That guy just showed me up so bad in front of the guys, man. You're going to do that to me in front of the boys? Hey, get up here. I want to talk to you for a second. Hey, hey, do me a favor. Never embarrass me like that.
Again, in front of the guy. So you know what? I'm going to punch you in the face. You got that? Yeah, I'm sorry, man. Yeah, you better say sorry. Now follow me. Bullet. Let's switch. Oh, this one. The big one. So that means it's open. Get out of the way. Hey, look at look at the lower right. There's two dead. Guarantee there's going to be a giant monster out here. Should I shoot him in the head?
Oh, my God. Well, the game just got. I can't believe that just happened. Well, I just did that. I put an end to this. Just drop the gun, man. Come on. I just did. So I already did that. Well, all right. So I was supposed to do that to begin with. I just like jumped the gun.
Oh, my God. These guys are so like that. All right. Now, can you open the door? Yes, you can. You are getting too old. You can't hang anymore, Jerry. More ammunition. Yeah. Hurry up. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man. That was bad. Oh, what are we getting chased? Hopefully not. Where'd he go? I thought I was alone here for a second, but scared me.
Too many of them. There's too many of them. No, I don't want to use that. I'm going to use this first. Go through the weak gun first. Well, actually, this isn't really that weak, but it's not as powerful as the SMG by any means. Are you good? Yeah. Well, you're supposed to be. Yeah, breach it. Breach it, man. Hit it. Oh, he's already dead. I'm like unloading on a useless corpse. Stop. I can't see anything. Gonna have to switch to the axe because I know I'm going to need that crap later.
Go, go, go, go, go. Breach it. Breach it. Come on. I'll cover us. I'll pull the covers over our head to save ourselves from monsters. Secure the what? What am I securing? Oh, man. Come on. Get this.
Stop wall blocking me, dude. Gonna get me killed. Yeah. Eat lead. Health ammo too. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect. All right. We made it. Oh, yeah.
We did it. We did it. That's a huge moon. That moon is abnormally large. Oh, we made it. We're gonna get out. We're gone. I beat the game. I beat the game. I beat the game. That's right. I beat the game. You cannot beat the game with you. Oh, this guy's gonna. Oh, God. What? What? No. What the? Oh, my God. It's coming right for us. Oh, my God. Did I die? Let's watch this guy not make it.
No. Oh, that guy went flying. Where's my coffee? Did I beat the game? Did I do it? Loading. Loading. Flashlight. Flashlight doesn't work. Currently on fire. And I got all my stuff back. Chapter seven Requiem. You know what? Let's just blow right through this. Chapter seven. Let's go. Let's do it, baby. Oh, no. Jeffrey. Oh, no. Who is responsible for this?
Is it the doctor? It's definitely the doctor. Yeah, doctor dickhead. So the doctor was behind it all, huh? You know what, man? Okay, well, now you're dead. Thanks for the info, dude. Let's go kill this doctor. He's been playing me as a fool the whole time, guys. Oh, yeah. Sure. Okay. All right.
Yeah. So there's two options. Run away or fight the doctor. I think we're going to go fight the doctor. For all this trouble you put me through, there's no way I am not going to find you and make you answer for your crimes.
Yeah, I got my key card. Shut up, lady. What do you know? This doesn't open, apparently. Plenty of health. Keep out. Yeah, we'll see. We'll see, dude. So this is like the doctor's little dungeon. Yeah. Well, I want to go look at some of the stuff first. He might be what if he's just like sitting there eating potato chips? Can I just murder him? What does that do? What is this? I'm here and never lose hope.
Hospital. It's been a while. It feels like everyone's looking at me like they know what happened, what I did. I'm out of options. I have to hide here. Yeah. So this guy's a bad mother effer. He's been watching me. He made sure to cover his tracks. Well, I'll make sure to cover you. What's all this? This guy's a creep. What is that? Is that a picture of him and that girl? I'm coming for you. Plenty of ammunition. Plenty of health. Where you at? More ammunition. Wow. You're really
stalking me up here, game. You're really stalking me up here. Is it crane? What the hell is this thing? We're kind of like sick torture devices. This ball with spikes all over it. He's right there. He's right there. Oh, it's actually kind of creepy. Yeah, you nice job.
You picked him off. Game over. Wait, they're not real? So these things have not been real this whole time.
You're dead, man. When I'm done with this, I'm going to come smash your head into that computer. What's over here? More ammunition. Where'd they come? Turn this on. Whatever it is, I want to turn it on. Yeah. You have a lot of surprises for me, bro. This guy is messed up. You are messed up, dude. No, it's got to be. Maybe I just have to shoot this. No, I got to get up there. How do I get up there? Oh, okay.
I get it. I get it. I get it. I get you. I get you. You gotta break this stuff. You gotta break this stuff. Oh, my god, break it. Break the supports. Oh, he's blowing me around like crazy. It's all right. It's all right. Get these supports. Machine gun! Activate! Come on, break. I'm just going to shoot him. That'll break him, won't it? No, it won't. Take out one, take out one. Yes, take them all out. Come on! I need more health. There we are.
perfect double barrel shotgun that's not the shotgun is the SMG that guy even go
stop doing the pulse the pulse is what I need to I need to time it yeah oh come
on come on come on oh my god this is so ridiculous these things take so long to
break more more more more more more more more you bastard go go go need
health need health need health I sorry it was over here it was over here it was
over here where was it over here bang wait where's where am I going what's
going on no no no no no no no whoa whoa whoa whoa what the hell is going on hey
you yeah help me okay oh it can be how come there's still a shield on it I
can't get in there where's the other power supply okay I do have to turn it
off again no it's like already off get away from me double barrel shotgun in
your face here we go go go go go break break break that's it come on one more
one more little support one more side here it is yes I can I can destroy
whatever I feel like hey whoa that door doesn't work that door doesn't work
that it's only one left behind it where am I supposed to go um hello oh there's a door
haha blood covers the walls hey stop doing that oh it's those mannequins
again those little dummies my eyes I'm so scared I don't want to go you stupid
mannequins now no nothing behind me stop sweat a little bit here this is
getting intense even if you prepare for it it's still haunts your every move real
door no not enough with the fake doors whoa my whole world is crumbling hey I'm
back I'm back how are you sir hello don't say that don't you dare say that
she's my friend man and your little construction is gonna be gone for good
see you later goodbye it's now gone at the cost of my own life pretty much
it's over but I'm as always are knocked by my mic waving at this guy I'm gonna
die if I'm not careful here I thought I already knocked that over now what are
you doing oh more like nightmares look get out of the way even the cops are
coming hey hello what is going on get up pull yourself up man did I make it how
funny is that like you heard the sirens there now you hear the sirens here see
there they were coming they came from my house and they came right to here any
more help close to the core I'm not giving up I'm gonna break that last
little thing my jiggy and then we're gonna have tea and crumpets me and my
new friend wait what the final support see you later bye shoot the core for
good measure yes did I win did I win kind of what does he want you didn't
win oh it shut off right when you were saying that oh my god what oh my god
all right what a cold bitch hey hey listen lady oh I okay you're welcome
you're welcome for a second I thought she was gonna throw me around like what
was his name there the cyber ninja from Metal Gear Solid that's it
nightmare house 2 is officially completed I think unless something else
ridiculous happens don't think so yeah that's it I think that's it guys yeah
I'm hitting enter I'm hitting space escape click click just looks like the
credits so yeah I hope you enjoyed this triple episode this is probably gonna be
pretty long but yeah this is a pretty cool game pretty cool mod again you have
to have half-life 2 episode 2 for this to work and it is totally free and the
link to download this will be in the description so yeah guys thank you so
much for watching this playthrough of nightmare house 2 and I am going to do
the prologue I'm gonna be playing nightmare house 1 somewhere down the
line maybe the next week or so you'll see that pop up on the channel so yeah
thanks a lot guys I'll see you all next time and of course take care everybody