Okay, get Elden Ring opened. I'm very excited about this. I do have to change a few things.
The reason why I'm so excited about Elden Ring is we are, I believe, at one of the probably
final points in the game. I am halfway, I believe, down the Hallow Tree. It looks like there was a
lot more to go. I do have to change this title though because this doesn't work. Uh, how about...
What's a good... I've done Elden Ring so many times. I don't even know what a good Elden Ring
title is anymore. What do I title this? Elden Ring... Elden... All right, spoiler alert. End game
area. Spoiler alert. Alert. Nothing easy, whatever. Elden... Elden. Elden Time. Onion Ring. That's awful.
Elden Ring. Getting to the end? Question mark? We'll see. Stay tuned to find out. Is it a bad title?
Whatever, it doesn't matter. What is playing in my headphones? Oh, this music, right. I was like,
where's that coming from? Okay, very nice. Is the game gonna get seen here? That's a Tuber title,
if I've ever seen one. Yeah, it is. I agree. I'm not gonna disagree with you. Sometimes Tuber titles
work. The face... The face game is not going off. It's on. Face game, is it gonna go? Hey, loading it.
What was the last... Okay, the last thing that... Somebody gave me a list of things I could do.
By the way, this is very much spoiler territory. This is actually like the end of the game
or like the final arc. Just please be aware of that. Be aware. Looking for a game to capture.
Right here, dude. This needs to shrink. Okay, so we... Last thing that happened.
Let me take a look at the map. Yeah, so I... Spoilers for anybody that like seriously does it.
It's like, what's happening? This is a spoiler. This is an end game spoiler. Three, two, one.
I burnt the urn tree. The urn tree is burning. The round table hold is now burning.
The two fingers are still stuck with their game crashed. I don't know why they're not back.
You'd think that they'd be like... They'd come back. So there was the halog tree. It was up here.
Oh, that's right. I did that thing too. Okay, so there was the halog tree. I could keep going down
or I could do this crumbling thing. And I think that somebody said there was an actual,
probably a better way to do it. Should I start at the halog tree or should I start at the crumbling
place? Okay, so I'm trying to remember what the... Because I killed... There was a boss here. Let's go
find it. How did I miss this much? I've been streaming this a lot. This is like my favorite
game ever. Okay, so let's just get back into this here. I got my moon stuff. Very nice.
I think this is the wrong one. I think it's this one. It's this one, right? The last thing that I
did is I beat Loretta. Yes, right here. Okay, so then I could keep going that way. Now I have not
been spoiled on anything in the game. I've been trying to stay away from a lot of Elden Ring stuff,
but I know for a fact that the boss that everyone hates I think is down here. So I can't tell you
that I'm necessarily prepared. I'm going to turn around and go do something else if I can't do it.
I think I can level up. Maybe I can. So this stream is going to continue. It's still pretty
early. I imagine I'll be able to play... What time is it? Like three or four hours? See? I need some
souls. All right, well, let's just go. Whatever. Two headphones going in. It's just not going to do.
All right, halog tree time. Let's go. How's the volume? Is it good? It's going to play for six
hours. What's it going to go until I don't feel like it? Interesting. All right, so that's the
halog tree. So what the fuck is the halog tree? Is somebody going to tell me when I go down here?
I don't think I can jump to there. Jerma, are you EST or PST? I am PST.
I think we need a fucking style light. Yes, we do. G4! G4 RAID! G4 TV! What's going on?
So I probably scared the shit out of people. I'm sorry. I may have just scared the absolute shit
out of all of you and I'm really sorry. G4 just raided. G4 raided before too. Thanks, G4.
Thank you. That's cool. I'm sorry. I scared the shit out of you. I'm really sorry.
No, thanks for the raid. You just missed me. Excuse me. Round as the bro versus bro against
Ludwig Championship. I just won. Spoiler. Ooh, okay. Ancient Dragons. We're at the end of Elden Ring.
So those of you that came from G4, just be aware this is like the last, probably third of the game.
If you don't want to be spoiled or anything, just I would run away now, immediately. Because you're
going to see some shit that you might not want to see if you haven't gotten this far. And I know a
lot of people haven't gotten this far because the game is like 500 hours long. So I get it.
Should I go down? Yeah, and if those are the new viewers, we always have to have fucking
skylight on. Helps you see a lot. That's a good tip. Yeah, they had this misspelling here.
I don't know why it's spelled that way. It's S-T-A-H. I think that's somebody fucked up.
Elviel, Brace of the Hallow Tree. Both of my weapons are max level. So unless I change what
I'm doing here, I don't have any need to go back and upgrade because of those knights.
All right, Starlight's kind of getting in the way. Starlight actually is bad.
I gotta get back in the swing thing. I gotta get back in the swing. It's been a while. It's been
like four or five days. I gotta remember what the buttons do. We're good. We're good. We're good.
I got it. See? Oh shit. Please make your face cam bounce around with the window screen saver.
Why would I do that? I still don't have enough. Is there anything else out there?
Whoa! My god, you are alive again. Oh well. I need to do this so I don't get mad and lose my souls.
That was dumb. All right, I gotta get back in the swing thing. It's like warm up. You don't
just like go out and throw nine enemies. I gotta go to the bullpen and like warm up for like 10
minutes. You can't just go out and pitch nine enemies. You gotta warm up. You gotta go through
the fucking rotation. Why do we come in with a raid? A YouTube raid? What's up, guys? Bro versus
bro champion. Okay. Where are the souls? Okay. All right. Hey, I gotta pay attention. Don't get the
souls. Don't lose 100,000 souls like an idiot. All right. Warm up is happening. Walk onto them.
Do I have enough to level up so I can stop doing this? No. God damn it. Okay. Just kill
one thing out. It's got to be like a randomly person or something out here. There we go. Okay.
That's better. Level up. What should I put it into? Yeah. Welcome, guys. Thanks, Ludwig. Always a
pleasure and some time with Ludwig. Probably mine. I want my mana. All right. Let's go.
I think I exploded. Hey, blow up. This way. I gotta get my gaming juices. I feel like I
I feel like I used up a lot of my gaming like juices. Is that bird tree avatar here?
You're gonna need a lot of juice. That guy didn't even have an Estus. I don't even know why. He had
an empty flask. I think I'm just gonna go straight for now. I could drop down there, but I could do
that anyways. Let's see. Let's see what's going on here. Drink, bro. I'm all right. Let's go up.
You're an enemy? These guys drop a lot of souls. Holy shit.
By the way, if you don't know, I am a cold wizard. Utilize ice spells, cold spells.
Is it Flintstone Sorcerer? Well, not really. Wait, can I go up there? I can. I guess I could
have dropped anyways, though. Fuck it. Let's go. Let's do it.
Michelin knight sword? All right. What is that? Strength, dex, and faith. Sword forged by servants
of Mickela of the Hallow Tree. With a design modeled after those carried by carrion knights.
Instead of the glintstone, however, amber from the Hallow Tree is embedded in the blade.
A sumptuous piece, yet it has never been offered to any knight an ill-starred sword with no master.
Holy essence and fires off a golden blade projectile? That seems kind of cool.
Strength? Is it a great sword? Strength and dex. It's a cool faith sword. Do I want to go there yet?
Is the item down? All right. I'm gonna go to... Should I go down or keep going that way?
I could go down there or I could go over here. I want to see what that is. Is it gonna kill me?
Is a storm sword key thing over here? Is it not? No, that's where I came from.
I want... Oh no, I want to go down there, down there. All right. There is an avatar here though.
What have I done? Okay, I'm good. This is where the stone sword key is.
Watch out for the crazy enemies. I got a feeling these enemies are all gonna be crazy. What is this?
Triple rings of light? Fires three rings of light before the caster. This is int and faith.
Seen a lot of combo spells. Produces three rings of light and fires in four. The rings of light
return to a position close to the caster before disappearing. Gift from the young
Mickela to his father Radagon. Okay. Can't really use it, but yeah, I'm still using the baby rattle.
I like it. I don't know how much longer I'm gonna like it, but I know I like it right now
and that's all that matters. Good problem if that didn't find another fucking scream.
I really don't want to fight an avatar right now, but I guess I'm gonna have to.
He doesn't know. I actually don't, you're right. I would treat the reeds. What's in here? What do
I have in there? Is it the damage boost one? It is. Okay, I think I have enough flasks. Let's
top myself off. Let me try it. This is where I was before. Nice armor, dude. This is where I was
before, right? I don't need to climb up here. Let me just check. Let me make sure. Okay, we're good.
Go, go, go, go, go. So there's people shooting that stuff over there. I just stepped on his head.
Is there a faster way to get over there? Because this is kind of a terrible awful run.
I'm gonna assume no. So let's just. All right, so there's somebody doing that. Casting that spell
over right over there. Oh, is it just him? Is it just him doing it? It is just you doing it.
Why are you just spamming that? Come on, you don't have to. Oh, you do not like that cold shit.
Okay, do not get killed by this. We can grate some cheese here. We so desire. I almost died.
What's that? What do you got? Rotten staff. B and E causes scarlet rot buildup. Ceremonial staff
depicted the urd tree in its historic radiance. Festers with scarlet rot. Filled by the avatars
who protect the minor urd trees. It's rotten. Is there a race in here? No, there's a
room. But I should be fine because I have a flail. It's rotten. Newman's room. It's an item all the
way at the end. Sombra ancient dragon stone. Or. I have got a lot of those now. You guys weren't
kidding. Those pop up all the time. All right, what about even lower? I definitely can. Not yet.
Let me continue this way. I could jump off from here. That's really dangerous though.
All right, I need a shield. Parry shield please. I'm not putting up with this fucking asshole right
now. Parry, parry. I don't want heavy load but I just want a little buckler. There's a little
buckler. Don't I have one? Is this seriously going to put me over? Heavy load? It doesn't matter.
I'm going to parry it like twice. Is that a spear or is that the staff one? Oh, that's the staff one.
Never mind. Oh my god. I thought there was a railing. I thought there was like a waist high
railing or something. I did that. Don't, don't, don't, don't. No, I'm fine. Oh my god. I'm okay.
Oh, hold on here. You both suck. I don't want to drop down here again. It was terrible.
This way. Through there. Don't screw this up. You seem like the kind of guy that balls with
bumpers on. Yeah, I honestly think that the gutter in bowling, I don't know, it doesn't need to
exist. I don't understand why it exists. It's way more fun when it doesn't. You seem like you take
mini golf too seriously. Well, that's inaccurate because that means I would, you're assuming I
would play mini golf. I fucking hate that shit. I hate mini golf. Mini golf is the most infuriating,
unfun, terrible experience. It's never fun. Mini golf seems like a good idea for the first
20 minutes. Then you realize you have to sit there for three hours and do the whole thing.
Nothing here. Weird placement of that enemy. Once you get past the windmill, I'm done. I don't feel
like playing anymore. It should just stop at the windmill. There's two of them in here. All right.
I got to take this slow on this. Do it. Do it. Do it. You what? Oh, my heart hurts. Oh my god.
My body hurts. This is a fucking terrible place to fight you.
Get out here. We're both trying to do the same dumb shit to each other. Just get out here.
Good, good, good. Worst fight ever. Oh, a lot of smithing stones. Sevens. Sorry. Fight me.
This is back up, which I don't, there might be an item that I missed, but we'll see.
We'll continue this way. I'm going to say we're going to continue that way.
This way. He has such an ape face. An ape-like face. Do I? Kind of. I hear one of those cookie bugs.
Yeah, where's the cookie bug? Don't hit the guy in front of him. Nice. Don't waste man on this guy.
There's no reason to. Race. Oh, I can do that. Old Fang. Whoa. Looks like a building down there.
Have you even done the nebula move once? No, because the cold move,
there's not enough people to do it to. And the nebula is a great move and I use it.
Trust me, I do. Did I miss anything down here though? Let me just check.
I feel like there's like a grace or something here. What are you doing?
That guy aggro'd to me from downstairs. Really? I think it's safe to drop down there, but not
going to. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Okay. Hey. Well, I don't think we're going that way. Okay. Seriously,
what's the range on this? I have to go from above. What's that? You missed the grace.
Did I vote over here? I'll do the nebula in here. It seems like there's like five feet.
This is why you don't use the nebula. This is why I didn't want to do it
because you're on a goddamn. Oh no. It's one of those guys. Okay. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go. Oh my God. Who's behind me? Oh, ladder. Quick. Oh please. I don't care if
I get poisoned. Just go, just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. No poison. Drink, drink on the ladder.
These guys are the worst enemy in the game. Those things are so, I freaked out.
I actually think that's probably where, that's the way to go. Did I get there before?
I actually kind of don't remember. And then down here and then I don't know. I don't remember.
Down all the way. Can I make it from here? I think so. All right. What about this? What's this?
Christ. Seed. Ooh. Does that guy have a spear? No, it's a staff. No, it's not. Is that a spear?
Okay. It's a spear. I need a, I need a shield. Oh, good. Holy shit. I'm gonna fucking help you.
Oh my God. I lost my subway order. Meatball. Just Meatball Marinara every time. The only thing
that I ever get there. Everything else is fucking dog shit at that, at that place. Meatball Marinara
is the only good thing there. It's super basic. It's super simple. It's not like crazy. Nothing,
nothing weird. Now that I lost my souls, who cares, right? I can go wherever I want.
Staff though. Why is somebody, I hear somebody walking behind me. Where is this person? This is
freaking me out. The two moons. Get over here. There above. All right. Chest. Legendary. Clean
Rot Knight Finley. Clean Rot Knight? Legendary Ashen remains used to summon the spirit of Clean
Rot Knight Finley. Finley was one of the few survivors of the Battle of Aeonia.
When an unimaginable act of heroism carried the slumbering demigod,
Millenia, all the way back to the Hallow Tree. He managed the feat alone,
fending off all manner of foes along the way. It's not going to replace Mambo. That's for sure.
Really cool though. Sounds really powerful. Sorry, we already have a best friend.
I need to get Mambo to plus 10. I don't know what to get a great grave glove ward. Should I go?
I don't think the play is down there. It's over here. Yeah, Mambo. I already did that.
This is the, okay, this part here. So you drop down. I'm just going to run to the
fucking bonfire or whatever it is. Right, right, right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
All right. Right there. Right there. Right there. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Quick, quick, quick, quick.
Before he spawns, he's going to spawn. Go. Arrows? I think I'm safe. This should take me behind the,
yep, fucking avatar here. Oh, I'm running in the door. There's nothing here.
Oh, this is very bad. Very bad. Very bad. Very bad. Why have that there?
What's the point of this? It's just a thing. Why have that there?
Pulled for that reason. For that exact reason. For that, no, you fell for it. Yeah.
I'm right. Okay. That's the strategy. I know there's a grave somewhere. There has to be
somewhere right here. Right? All right. Same deal. Except I'm running right behind that avatar.
I'll come back out here and deal with this. Right there. Right past the avatar. Fucking,
why am I looking at you? Why am I looking over here? I know. I know. Stop looking over there.
Why am I looking? I know where it is. Just jump off. It's going to kill me. Three, two, one.
Fuck this game. Mad. Omega low. Oh, why did you jump? I, because I didn't mean to. My, it was a
reaction. I got to get there and then I'm going to go behind the urdry and attack from,
I'm going to go and backstab. Don't be stupid. Right here. Up down here. Don't stop moving.
There it is. Beautiful. Here. Excellent ball. That's fine. Go. Brink on the ladder. Don't stop.
Thank you. That went right between my legs. All right. Right there. Here we go. One, two, three.
Fuck just happened. You shoot. I touched it. I win. I touched it. I win. Ladder goes up, but
let's go. Let's do it. Check this out. Tree cannot come in here. Tree is in the building. Tree
can come in here. That's good to know. I thought you were going to get stuck. All right. You can't
come through here. No, I don't want to drink that potion. Where'd he go? What just happened?
Where'd he go? What do you got? Lord's Ruin and another rotten staff. Cross build is OP. Cross
build is very powered. I'm not just going to run through this thing because I want to see what
happens. There was an item or two that was over here. Works until it doesn't. I win. 11,000 souls.
Holy shit. Bud. Put your waste man on these chumps.
There's another one that's... Yeah, you. Does this reach? Really? Okay. Well, I think I can get these.
Let's see what's down here first. Can we get a birdwatch in the corner? Nah.
You can get like a sweaty guy corner. You can get a sweaty guy in a dark room. That's all I got for
you. Let's use the sowlord's room. 12,000 is what we need. 11,8. What about frogwatch?
Frogs are cool. Can we watch Jimmy Neutron? No, you cannot watch Jimmy Neutron. No frog stream. No,
stop. No frog. Stop it. That changed. Maybe I should turn the exposure up. What do you like
that I'm sitting in kind of a dark, sweaty room? It's reminding myself. That is... Am I urinal on?
No frog stream. No. Can we do an armpit check? No, no, you're like...
Hallow Tree Knight Helm. Elm worn by knights sworn to the Hallow Tree,
graced by a crown of unalloyed gold, increases faith by two. I think I look good.
This is pretty much what I'm going to be wearing. All right, so what's out here?
Elusiary wall? Elusiary wall this way? I mean, I could drop. No, that's where it just was. Nah,
okay. Good. Jerry wall? Elusiary. Elusory. How do you say it? Elus... Elusory? Here. Elusory?
What the fuck? Let's kill him. Right now. Watch this. I gotta kill that one first because that's
the one that casts spells. So we're going to go Dark Moon. I got it. Whatever. I got it. There's
nothing else over here that I need to do. What was that? A crystal, a rotten crystal sword? What
was it? You fucking suck balls. Thanks, man. I appreciate it. Okay, where is it? Rotten crystal.
This is int. Oh, it's strength. Scarlet Rot. Sword fashion from pure crystal,
a deed impossible for a human, and wreath with powerful magic, its attack scales with intelligence.
You can two-hand that? Yeah, but do I want to? I have no strength, though. I would have to respect
the character. We don't need to talk about respects until I really cannot beat certain things.
What does it look like? I mean, that's really cool. It's really cool, but it is kind of just
a weapon. It doesn't have anything like really fancy. Maybe rattle is slower,
but whatever. That's cool. Keep the rattle. Oh, Scarlet Rot. That's right. Huh. Let's look into
that in a minute. Not going over there yet. Hero's rune. What about the moon veil? I have a ton of
stones that I have not used in like 40 game hours. I can... goodness. Damn, that goes pretty
deep. If I want to upgrade another weapon, I can. So I'm very, very, very capable of just going and
just maxing out three other weapons if I really want to. What the fuck is that? It's one of those
things. What are you doing? That was... I didn't like that. That was unsettling. I didn't like it.
Is that rot? Of course it is. Holy fucking god, he came around. Holy shit, don't die, please.
Just gotta go in. Pest's glaive. Did I get one of these already? I feel like I've seen that.
Have I? No, where is it? Yeah, okay. I've seen it. Didn't impress me. Is there... Can I get... I
can't get on the horse either. This sucks. This really sucks. Oh my god, I cannot... All right,
that's bad. You gotta be shitting me. Okay, I need something. Please put a dagger on. A quick
step, right? Do not roll. Oh, that's right. Okay, I just need to dash. Did I roll to get it off me?
All right, I need some points of interest. I'm gonna get to that. Something's alive down there.
Soap time. Wow, it worked. All right, here we go. Oh my god, please. Please get the fuck away from
me. Please. Just keep going. Keep going. Keep going. I can get rid of it. What are these little
fucking weirdos? Don't use the fucking knife. Oh, bad. Put the fucking sword on. Put on a weapon.
You annoying little shits. I swear. I'm just leaving. Get me the fuck out of the way from this.
Go. Let's go. I don't care. Let's fuck these things. Oh, whoa. Am I safe? That sucked. What
the fuck is that? I thought I just went the wrong way. Please tell me there's a grace in here and
it's not like somebody's sitting behind the corner. Stoop his ladder. Yes. Thank god. All
right, now what? I might go back up. I'm out here. I don't want to go out here yet.
It looks like I could have kept going down. I'm here. I keep going. If you live in there,
you're fine. What about over here? Excuse me. Go that way. More rot. That's a legendary.
Ah, fuck you. Don't. What did you do? What did you just do? Oh my god. How did you miss that?
I fought a hundred of you. I'll fight you again. Holy shit. His health. Let's try it again.
I want to at least get the item. At the very least, I want the item. Those things are
everywhere. We get a post-death interview. Um, I don't, I don't, I don't give interviews.
You have to book me like at least three or four weeks in advance.
Sorry. I'm just gonna get the item and then run. Whoa. What the fuck? Why? That's so scary.
I thought he came from the other side. All right. Oh, great. Grave. Glob wards. That's what I want.
That's exactly what I was looking for. Holy shit. I can get a plus 10 mambo. I got this.
Fuck. He's gonna knock me off with a blast. I can kill him. I can kill this guy. Just burn.
It's a burn fight. You do dark moon. And then after dark moon, you sit up in your chair and
you just hope that your ass is not connected to your underwear. And that is now connected as well
to your pants because of just sitting here sweating. Okay. Same deal. We're going to go
up here. I'm going to the moon and then we're switching to the blade and I'm going to be
prepared. We're going to wait. Here we go. YouTuber voice, YouTuber gameplay commentary. Here we go.
Okay. So we're heading this way. Okay, guys. All right, fellas.
Hey, boys and girls. All right. Cool. Okay. Here we go. What was that? Too far away. Fuck you.
What?
It's going to explode. No. Blast you. Blast. It's not funny anymore. It's too far. Quiet.
This is a fucking hard game. This enemy is in a really shitty place. He's got a ton of health
and he can, he can bounce you off. He can knock you off. Quiet. I got it. It's like the third
attempt. I should try killing it this time. I don't even want those. Who cares? I'm level 180.
This shouldn't be this. I'm kidding. People are going to leave and be like, this guy sucks. I'm
135. I'm going to fight him from here. Really? That's really bad. God. Why? Why? Why? Dude,
why? This one doesn't count. What's going on? I got to get out of the rod before it builds up.
Kill him with it on. Who cares?
What was that shit? One of those like puppet hands that came up. Get off you golden seed.
That's it. Okay. Well, that's, I mean, how many do I have? I think I have like three,
but it's five, right? Totally worth it. Actually, probably worth it.
Considering that I think that's the only place you can get those now.
Right. I think this is the only place I've seen. I'm just going to go back. There's plenty of other
places you can get. Wait, there are a lot more. Oh, okay. Which bonfire is this?
There's at least 10 surplus seeds. That makes sense though. Considering a kind of,
I don't have enough to level up. I think so. We've won 20 something.
That's close, but it's not there. Well, I'm going to lose all these runes that I just
broke for no reason. Wait. Oh, wait. This is like a castle? Like a town? Like what is down here?
What is this? This is a castle. This is the halib tree, but it's like a castle.
There's a safe place to go from here. Okay. I could go up. What's up here? Might as well.
Okay. A lot of places to go here. That's high. Did I overshoot that or did I undershoot it?
I tried not to overshoot it. Souls are not gone. There's no enemies here.
There's going to be stupid fall deaths that are what caused me to lose anything.
Okay. Come on. Chonished. I'm going to fuck it up. What the? Did I go? I went, I went through it.
My character went through it. I literally went through it. He phased through it.
He just did the exact same thing. Bro. I'm trying to land on the little banister thing.
I did. I undershoot it. I like went. I got to go a little bit further. Hurry up. Let's go.
My God. I'm rushing now because I don't want to fucking run over the stupid twigs anymore.
I don't want to like walk across the tightrope anymore.
I can't like this in games. Not like this where it's just like, okay, you got to go like that way
and then down that way and then that way. And then you where you were. Oh, just get,
I want to just drive a car there. I just want to get in a fucking car and drive here.
Give me in a plane and just fly it there. Just fly. Just speed hack it. I don't need the ruins.
Whatever. I can go walk. How are you? I was in the middle of an animation. That's not fair. What?
I was in the middle of an opening animation. That's not, that's not how that works.
What's the item? What's the item? Did he take it?
What's the item? It didn't show up on my screen. What is it? What is it? What is it?
You got it. What was it? I didn't even, it didn't even show up on the screen.
Is it talisman? Yes. Dragon crest. Enormously boost physical damage negation.
Legendary talisman of wrought iron depicting a massive ancient dragon.
The ancient dragons who ruled in the prehistoric era before the urd tree
would protect their lord as a wall of living rock. And so it is that the shape of the dragon
has become symbolic of all manner of protection. He's pretty good. He's very good. Okay. Um,
this deck is still down there that I said you can't even see me. You threw the guy.
What? My God, you're so annoying. Get out of there. This guy's got to die right now.
They're flying. I just go down. You lost. Yeah. The guy shoved me. Who's next to me? The ledges.
I don't have anything left in there.
My fucking socks. That was so far too. Jesus. To go back to the stinky dragon spot. Um,
I'm, I have progress this way. I need to, I want to get out of this piece of shit before I go back
to the rot village. Okay. I'm getting out of this piece of crap. I know I just, I said a little bit
of swear word there, but that was crap. Okay. What is this? I don't know. We're taking it though.
This one's going so fast. Oh shit. Nice. Lost store. All right. Here's a boss. What do we got?
Here we go. Cut scene. Everybody quiet. Oh, running. Great. Go run and kick that away.
That's like a gun in a movie where it like gets kicked away and everyone tries to go get it.
As I awaited his return, heed my words. I am millennia blade of Mickeler feet.
I am Jerma. Sword of everyone. Hey, you get to do what I do. That's not fair.
Fuck you. How dare you. God, that hurts. She's healing.
Do something. Come on. Nice. Bombo. Good. Good job. Very good.
Fucking healing shit. I caught this. Dude, she's healing off of them. She's going back up full L.
Okay. Um, he's back up full HB. I'm fucking flabbergasted. Uh, so what we have to do here
is we have to, uh, go back to full fucking health. Um, excuse X. It's coming out of my mouth.
Excuse me. I'm dead. So I didn't even hurt the boss. Did the boss was not even injured at all.
Bombo seems like free health in a way. I'm very curious how I'm going to do this. He's
to dodge every attack. Okay. Let's go. Oh, that's a bad, not bad idea. No magic.
Too slow. It's too slow. How long does it do that for sword? Like clicks up. Oh, yikes.
Boys and girls, baby rattles going to turn out to be quite a good pick here.
Oh, boys and girls, baby rattle is the weapon of choice.
You can't stand in the air that long. Is this a fucking cartoon? Is this a cartoon?
She was in the air. She jumped in the air and stood there up in the air. I was expecting her
to hold a fucking sign that just said like, Oh, and then fall. What the hell was that?
Fucking goddamn cartoon shit. All right. Baby rattle is unbelievable here because it
is sloppy. Very sloppy. Oh my fucking God. We're back to full fucking health.
I'm going to do something fucking weird like this. That was weird. Oh my God. All right. Even
though she's going to heal, I think Bombo's got to come out. We also might have to upgrade
Bombo to level 10. Let's go Bombo. Very good start. Look at that. Look at that. Look at that
stagger. No, fuck. There it is. Nice. Good hit. Is this even doing anything?
She's healing off of them. Oh my God. She's going to heal. Okay. So summons are not probably not
good because she's just going to farm health on them. Oh, that's right. Okay. If I'm not going
to be doing that much spells and we need to wait like jump. Do I have like a, what should I do here?
Shield one. I think it's really heavy though. Enormously boosts physical damage negation.
What about, um, FP? I don't really necessarily care about potentially like sorceries. What about
does it matter? Does she do magic damage or something? What is she doing? Rod?
Raid? I don't see. Is there a raid? No, it's physical. Okay. So
arch attacks, stamina reducing attacks. Maybe it's HP. Just greatly raise max HP.
That seems kind of cool. All right. Let me try that. And I'm also going to move flasks around.
Let me just try it. Just purely trying to fight rune arc. I am not going to use a rune arc yet
because I'm not confident enough that I'm not going to die in 13 seconds. I also probably
should change my wondrous physique as well. All right, let's go. No summons. Fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck you. Thank God. Eat shit. Hey. Top myself off. Oh shit. No. No. My God. Fuck. Jesus Christ.
Oh, that was so good too. Oh, that sucks. Holy shit. This is unbearable. What?
One mistake and it's over. That was a really clean like first minute or two. Holy shit.
If you one wrong input, it's over. Holy fucking moly. All right. Come on. Holy moly.
It's got to be fucking aggressive by the aggressive. That's sloppy fucking beginning.
That's sloppy shit right there. I had no stamina to dodge. Quiet. Yikes, man. She's
already back to fucking full health. Is this even possible to beat? Is this even physically
completable? No one's beat this in the world. I saw the achievement pop up. It's at 0.0%.
I was wondering. I thought it was a bug or something. 0.0% of people have beat this.
Geez. We're that smart to get away from that. God. It's okay. When she goes shriek,
you got to just get away. Just dodge right immediately. Right when you hear the sound.
Fuck you. Oh fucking hell. You have to be perfect at this fight. Oh my God, dude.
This is going to take 10 hours of memorizing this whole fight without a doubt. What? Didn't swing.
It's so long. Like one, two, three, four seconds. Stop fucking swinging. Oh my God.
Holy shit, this is insane. Yeah, I'm trying, man. This is the boss that people said. Some people
took like 10 days on this person. Okay. I'm doing it. It's probably a phase two as well. This is
going to be so awful, isn't it? We're throwing caution to the goddamn wind.
We're doing a full on burger boy technique right now.
Consumables? Are you guys actually voting to see if I'm going to do this in 15 tries?
Add a zero. 15 tries? No. No, I'm telling you, this is going to be like a hundred.
I don't know how I would have voted for that one. All right, here we go.
You fucking idiot. Seriously? Really? Shit.
What? There's a lot of time to swing after that.
That was the one thing you could have done to avoid that. No fucking way. Not a chance now.
Oh my fucking Lord. I didn't get grabbed. I thought I did. What is this? Did she dodge this?
Oh, there's no fucking panel left. Hold on a minute. I've got an idea. I have an idea.
This is going to work. We're doing. Okay. Watch this shit. Randy's moon. And we're going.
I'm just going to bully. I think I can actually bring out serpent for this.
I'm going hard for this one. Here we go. This is going to be a nightmare, but let's do it.
Here we go. You guys ready for a nightmare? Moon. Three. Or two. I will take two. Two moons?
Oh my God. Just two moons. Just sit her into a moon.
Okay. All right. All right. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. We have to bully immediately.
Don't let her swing. Don't let her swing. Oh my God. What is that? What just happened?
I don't even know what happened. She got mad. Oh, that's the play though. That's going to work.
That is the play. It's just get in there and just absolutely stagger and bully.
Let's do it. She's in there somewhere. All right. Get her. Get her. Get her. Get her.
Don't let her do anything weird. Don't let her do anything weird. Get her.
Burger Boy technique. All right. Back up. Back up. No reason to get killed here.
We're going full Burger Boy. Who cares? Just kill her.
Back up. Back up. There's no way this works, right? There's no way. There's a phase two in there.
Ow. My face. Just phase two. This is going to be a phase two. This is going to be a phase two.
Oh, she's going to rip her arm off. She's going to turn into a zombie.
She's going to turn into a monster. It's a fucking phase two fight. I was so confident for no reason.
God damn it. Okay. So that works for phase one. Phase...
What do you mean no way? That was it? No. No, it's not. Why would there be a cut scene?
That works for phase one. Okay. That's very effective for phase one.
But oh God. I knew it. Right. There's no way.
Okay. Bombo, I think we're going to have to try a little harder. Bombo, you and me. Good luck.
Bombo, it's been a pleasure doing business with you. What the fuck? She exploded.
Bombo. Bombo, don't go in there. Bombo. Bombo, no. My game is frozen.
Okay. Well, we have a reliable way to get to... Let's let's do this smartly. I want more spell
damage. Less... I want sorceries. Boosting sorceries. Get Bombo to 10. Yes. That's exactly what we're
going to do right now. Do I have any runes? I don't. How much does it cost to get you to 10?
And use a rune arc? Still doing that. Okay. Wait, I can't see you. Wait, I gotta sell.
I gotta sell something. I'm thinking rune arc. Get Bombo to 10. I need to just sell like some
route. What do I have? No junk. How much does it cost? Fuck. Shit. I just gotta go kill a few
things. Sell your... Do not sell the grease. Do I have a lord's rune? I didn't see it. Yeah,
I don't have it. I'm just gonna go kill a couple things. Use rune arcs. Uh, let me just go here.
This'll be easy. That... That fight is crazy. It's really just... I honestly... No, no, no. We're not...
We're not just like dodging around and dashing around. Nope. That is a DPS race. That is a kill
her as fast as possible. Don't let her do any moves. Where's an easy place for me to get? Oh,
I know. That mog place. Where is it? It's like right here somewhere. All right.
Dermot, you're never going to beat this boss. I feel like I got... I feel like I got close enough.
I think it's... I think I can do it. All I need is like 10 bombs. But yeah, the sorcery boosting
talisman... If I just go for straight up just DPS, go for it. I think it's gonna be pretty
possible. I think it's gonna be okay. I also think that I need mana. Eels are very good, but
I don't want to run out, because that would be a disaster if I did. Okay, let's go get Mambo to 10.
There you are. Here we go. Mambo plus 10. I guess I had more
runes than I needed. We're also going to take a rune arc. Wait, what do I have on for a rune right
now? What's the best one I can put on for this? Odric is good. HP, FP, and stamina. I feel like
that's not bad. Greatly raises max HP. I'm gonna... I'll try Redan's. That's not very... That's not
that much. It doesn't seem like very much. Okay, well, let's go for it. I am as prepared as I'm
going to be at this point. Morgoth's is better. Well, I got this on right now. Redan's sucks.
All right, it's... Right here. Use Godric's. I mean, I already used it. Okay, here we go.
Let's try it. The same technique. Getting in there, and we are just bully, bully, bully, bully,
bully. Don't do anything else. Bully. Bully. That's it. We're not doing it. We're just bullying.
Get in there. Stagger. Come on. Keep it up. Get in. And go. Good. Good. Mambo, help.
Oh, she did it three times in a row. She did that same dumbass move two or three times in a row.
I lost the rune arc. I don't even need it. Fuck it. I don't want it. Not that one. Here we go.
Get it. Mambo, you got to get any closer, man. Come on. Fucking Jesus. Not a good... This is a bad
start. You did that move so early. Zone, zone. Good zone, Mambo. Good zoning. Oh, my God. She
just kicked the shit out of him. Oh, please. Nice. God damn it. He's dead. Okay. All right. We got
to phase two for the second time. I'm ready. Oh, my God. It explodes. What the fuck? What the fuck?
She doesn't come down. She stays up there. I'm just going to run. I saw her come down,
but that was just a stupid fucking phantom. All right. No more rune arcs until I can reliably
know what she's going to do in phase two. This is... Oh, my goodness. This is fucking awkward.
Get that backwards. I just couldn't fucking see. I'll be honest. There's so much red shit on the
screen. We got to keep Mambo alive. That's the stupidest fucking move we've ever made.
Do you just have to turn around and run? It does it three times. There's no way you can get her.
You cannot dodge that. You just turn around and run. There's so many attack animations in
one second. What's that fucking horse shit? Come on. I need you to get in there.
Good start. Run. It happened so quickly. That move happened so fast. How are you supposed to do that?
Holy... That's stupid. If she goes in the air, just run. Dumbass shit right there. That is dumbass
shit. Okay, if she goes in the air, run across the entire game. Okay, I got it.
If she went in the air for that, it's a different move. Mambo, I need you over here.
Now I'm paranoid that she's going to do it. Zoning. Back up. No, I didn't. She's actually
doing it to Mambo. It's all right. Poor Mambo. Oh, my God. I need Mambo for phase two so bad.
Come on, miss the fucking stun. She's right. It's so intense. It's hard to even fucking pay
attention. There's so much going on that she can do. Holy shit. It's so difficult to pay attention
to that. It's just like, oh, my God. She's in the air and then it's too late. It's like your brain
is like, oh, fuck. Okay, too late. Let's try it again. This is perfect. No, it's not. No, fucking
too late. Oh, my God. Damn it. Please. Thank God she didn't kill Mambo with that. That's actually
good. Keep her there. Get her, Mambo. Come on. Jesus. No. Mambo, stop her. Stop her, please.
This is un-fucking-believably difficult. They're going to nerf this one, too.
They're going to fight both these bosses, Verdan and this one, before they fucking nerf it twice.
Didn't get her. It's actually really hard to see. My God. That sucks. Mambo's going to die.
Really quick. Dude. Excuse me. I ran the whole fucking time. Hey. Whoa. Is she going to go in
the air? I'm so fucking afraid she's going to go in the air and ruin the whole thing. I need you
for phase two. She's still alive. What the hell? She's fucking healing. Damn it, man. That's such
a shit mechanic. Oh, my God. I can't fucking kill her. All right. Now what do I do?
Oh, my God. Okay. So she goes in the air. She comes down and then she explodes. How many seconds
later? Two? Will that still hit you if you roll? So you have to just do like two good perfect dodges.
I'm going to start to hear this fucking music in my head.
Don't go in the air. I have nowhere to run. Oh, my God. She's coming for me.
What the fuck? I don't know where she's going. No. He got it. All right. Come on. Dodge. It's
going to be a good dodge. Fuck. There's Scarlet Rye everywhere. There's Scarlet Rye all over me.
Is it the same move that she does? I don't know, dude. Oh, no. Oh, no. She does it. Oh, no.
Oh, she does two different things. She goes in the air now. She does two of those. She hung up
and didn't do it. Oh, my goodness. What level am I? 135. Should I just come back here at like
180 and just kill her? She does five different things. I have to float it. I'm just running
every time. This sucks. This sucks so bad. You can't. You can't. I need more bully from you.
Oh, she's doing it. That's so, dude. I got to fucking seriously. I honestly like it's like,
holy shit. I just like you get you get so into the fight and it's just so much going on.
So much fucking colors on the screen that like she goes in the air and it's like, oh, fuck.
I'm just going to shoot me in the face with the cannon. I can't fucking do anything.
Use the mimic tear. They nerfed that motherfucker. It's not worth it.
This is the strategy for phase two. God, I have no fucking goddamn idea how you're supposed to
reliably do that. This is just I don't think I don't know how to fucking do that. Dude,
some of these like speed run like no damage runs. Oh, my God. This is going to suck. Absolute
asshole. It's going to be fucking horrible. Dude, even when you fucking run, it don't matter.
I'm terrified. We're going in the air. If you're mid attack animation like this, it's fucking
horrible. Oh, come on. Get out of here. All right. Come on. Get it. Don't let her go in the air.
Consistent. God, you piece of shit. Just get hit. Um, thank you, mom. I can't fucking hit her.
Can I go near her? Where is she? I have no stamina to fucking move away from her.
I'm out of fucking stamina. Oh, no way, man. Oh, shit. I don't. I'm fucking dead. Oh, my God.
I ran out of stamina. Use a shield. Oh, my God. That sucked. How much stamina do I have?
20 endurance. Yeah, but I need to try the boys. I feel like the boys are going to be free food.
Use the boom blade. I'm not even I don't I don't know, man. I got to like get to phase two and not
ever spam that move the first five seconds. Like I need to be I got to see what she does in that
encounter. I'm just going to run away from her. If I get to phase two here, I'm literally I'm
not going to attack. I'm literally going to run around in a circle and see what she does.
And what was so un-fucking-variable that like even if you're remotely close, you're fucked.
Jesus, the timing is so fucked up. This is the hardest boss of any from fucking without a doubt
in my mind. Million percent. I thought the end of Sekiro was fucking horrible. At least like I had
a at least you can like fucking you have like a button to stop attacks. I think this takes the
cake. Like that L1. This is a Sekiro boss without the parry mechanic. I think she accidentally got
in this fucking game. I don't think she's supposed to be here. They like accidentally put the wrong
asset in here. I'm so paranoid of that move. I don't even want to like fight her. Dude, fuck you
with this fucking gap closing bullshit. Oh, come on now. God damn it. All these gap closes. Where's
my fucking Sekiro L1? Wrong game. Wrong game from software. Wrong game. He's going crazy. I'm
going to turn him out, man. Fuck me. Fuck. I'm going to hack my game and fucking get 10,000 damage.
I'm just going to kill her with one hit. Get her in the fire. Ugly. Ugly. She's going to go in the air.
I just know it. It's just like, fuck, you don't know when she's going to go in the goddamn air.
And it's like, man, you better not be within fucking 100 yards of her. Fucking leave me alone.
Jesus Christ. I was stupid, but I'm going to do it. No. Why did that not stagger? Oh, fuck. Come on.
No. Get back. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. All right. What are you? What are your moves?
What are your moves? Oh my God. She's doing that thing. It's different. What? That was different.
She didn't do the thing. That was different. No attack. Please. New moves so I can learn what
you do. Please get away from me. I'm such a coward. I don't care. Oh, it's over. Goodbye. Dude.
My genuine scared face. There's not even enough time for me to change to my other potions. You
know what I mean? Like, fuck this. It's more, it's like a lot, it's been really drifty and floating.
Please. Shit. Shit. Oh my God. There's no time. Oh my God. What are you supposed to do? There's
no time. There's no time. There's no time. There's no time. By the time she finishes that move,
she's doing it again. What the fuck, dude? You should use your melee art. Dude, I'm going to do
that and die instantly. I don't think I can do, I think that move is too slow. I think I just have
to fight her. Fucking drugs were they taking when they made this, by the way? Oh, here's a good idea.
A fight where the boss heals every time she hits you. Oh, and by the way, there's a move that
goes across the entire fucking boss area. She's got no stamina bar. She swings faster than all
the bosses in Sekiro. Were they, were they smoking crack when they made this? How much crack were
they on? This is crack. All right, settle down. I'm fine. She's going to do it. She's going to do it.
She's just, she wants to do it so badly. A little, the math problem going on in her little fucking
brain is being like, should I do the thing? Maybe. Nice job. Oh, killer quick. She annihilated him.
She fucking annihilated him, man. I'm so paranoid that she's going to go in the air and it's over.
Oh my God, it's over. Oh my God, that's so broken. Oh my God. I even tried to run, dude.
Mambo phase two, that's probably, but I gotta get through phase one.
Mambo is going to stay alive for phase two. He didn't run. Guys, she does a move that takes like
12 seconds to end. And she jumps in the air and does it within like half a second. If you're
already in the gap, it's fucking over. And when, if you're too far away, you can't fight her.
If you're too close, you're fucked. How do you win? What's the strat? I need to get a shield.
Guys, my dude, my dude can't fucking handle it. I think I need Mambo for phase one. Otherwise,
I don't know if I can reliably get through this. Bro, I can't see you when you're doing that in
front of me. Hit her please, Mambo. Please do your little stretchy thing and hit her. Don't let her
get any mana off you. No, she's building mana. Don't let her, I'll get her. No shit. Oh no.
Mambo get her. There are other people in this fight, you know. What the fuck?
No fucking shot. No fucking shot. No shot. No shot. That's not possible. She runs faster than
you. She does more moves per second than you can move. She's got the biggest gap closers of anybody
I've ever seen. What a piece of shit. Look shit faced. I look fucking drunk right now.
Dude, I know. Okay, I understand. Like just dodge, just dodge. Being perfect in a soul is like,
this is a fucking from software game. Why am I saying that? You can't be perfect, man. Like,
it's just too hard. It's too much. But even if you were perfect, I want to like watch that clip
of what just happened. Because goddamn, it's like attack, attack, attack, attack, attack, attack,
attack, attack. It's not time to do anything. You can't, you physically cannot do anything
because I just get hit. Watch somebody do a no hit of this. They're, they're fucking, they're,
they're working in slow motion. I already went over that. Oh fuck me. Thank god. I love when he
hits her. It sounds like a trash can lid. He's using a trash can. No, don't go for me, please.
I'll never turn you back on mombo. Big fucking mistake. I don't have the stamina. I might have.
Oh shit. Fine. Oh boy. Bro. This is shit. Oh damn it. Fuck you, dude. Jesus Christ.
What the fuck? What? Panic roll. Those are the amount of rolls you have to do to not get hit by
that dumb fucking. That's so fucking annoying. This piece of shit is dead eventually. And we're
going to eat one of these. Oh, I'm so mad. This sucks. This sucks. This sucks. This sucks.
I had no stamina to run. I hate when you do this shit. I can do something. Do something. What are
you a player in PVP? Fuck off. I thought he just cut her head off. Please help me and kill her.
Please help me. Get out of the rock. Get out of the rock. Fuck you. Oh fuck. It's so much slower.
Oh my god. I thought it was the yellow one. Is it? What one is it? Dude, the fact that she goes in
the air and she does two different fucking moves. She does the like, here I am floating.
Or, or it's like, whoosh. How are you supposed to tell? How are you supposed to tell?
How are you supposed to fucking tell? Different poses. Oh yeah. She goes, instead of going like
this, she goes like this. This is stupid. I think it's a hundred degrees in this room.
I'm like being cooked in here. I'm being cooked alive in here. If there was a piece of meat on my
shoulder, it would be turning brown. It would be, it would be like browning. It would be like, oh,
I could probably eat it. This fight sucks. Oh fuck. God damn it. I don't know how many fucking
people do that. And she's doing the fucking thing again. Oh my god. I couldn't even see.
Goodness. Too many moves. They're going to take away one of those swings. It's so fucked up.
Mambo for phase two only. I'll try that. Can I even do that though? I feel like I'm gonna get my ass
kicked right now. No, I don't want to listen. I'm not using the stupid mimic tier. Quiet.
I demand silence. Oh fuck. No, I forgot what that move was for a second. Yeah. I forgot. I like
forgot that because I didn't have Mambo. Like this is the first time I have seen and heard
without Mambo. And like, I just forgot. So when From Software makes another game,
right? What are they? What do they do? Did they just? Okay. Does the next game? It's like,
oh, we have to do something harder than millennia. The two hands come out of the
fucking screen and just choke you and just push on your trachea. What's next? What do they do?
You know what I mean? Like, oh yeah, I'm at the final boss. Oh, wow. One of the final bosses of,
of, uh, just slash arc. Wow. I'm here. Let's see about these hands. Whoa, guys, do you see these
hands? Oh, I dodged. Fight the fucking hands. What's next? Like, what the fuck is next?
Oh, yeah. From Software's new game is called Nut Kick. Oh, oh, like something just kicks me
in the balls from under the desk. What else are they going to do? How are they going to do
anything else? It spells in here. It fucking spells in here. I can tell on you right now. It
stinks in here. Not kidding. No, I didn't shit my pants. Imagine setting up. Oh, yeah. This game,
Nut Kick. Yeah. It's like a thing down here. I just like sit there and here comes the boss.
Why would you set that up? Why would you wouldn't even buy it? Oh, fuck. I'm going to die.
I'm fucking dead. This one's a real try right here. Everyone warned me. Oh, hey, dude. I know
you're like, yeah. Hey, by the way, like going there at 150, by the way, don't, hey, listen,
fucking do. Don't listen to these fucking idiots in the chat, man. I'm telling you,
be a fucking level 150. Get your fucking vigor up to fucking like 60. That's how I did it,
dude. Don't fucking listen to these dudes. They're trying to get you killed and they think it's funny
when you die. Look, trust me, I'm a fucking nut kick pro. I just sit there and let it kick me.
Listen to me. I got all the fucking tips. I did world first get a nut kick fucking a hundred times.
Yeah, that's me. I got that. I got that. I got that. Why am I just doing
this? I think I might be out of it. I think I might have to take a break.
This might be break time. Oh, here it comes. Oh, I'm going to go for the record.
I'm going to turn the fan up. Okay. So what went wrong there? There's too many, so many memes
tonight. Oh, sorry. G four rated. Are you still here? I hope not. I hope that. I hope not. Thanks
for the brain. That's like an hour and a half ago. That was two hours ago. My thing. Am I saying
thanks for the raid to G four, two and a half fucking hours later. Are you drunk? We'll bring
it out. Mambo prefers wrong is whatever. I'm pissed. It was four hours ago. How long have I been here?
Come on, Mambo, get in there. That actually is. Oh, no, she's got it. That sucks when she does it
to Mambo because then Mambo is not going to be around for the second phase. She's almost back
to full health again. Again. Oh, come on. Oh my God. I couldn't. I'm trying to change my fucking
sword. Oh my God, dude. Like holding. Like I got a fucking complaint. Like holding Y and hit R one
to go to the two hand man. Sometimes like it just like fucking is weird. It doesn't like happen in
the lower left. It doesn't like say, oh, you're holding Y. It just thinks you're tapping Y.
I mean, like you have to switch your weapon. You have to like one. It's like a full second
that you have to hold it. It's like, hold. There it is. Hold. There it is. You're already running.
What's this bullshit? You never run. You knew I used a rune arc. You piece of shit. Shit. Shit.
Shit. Shit. What was that? You piece of shit. You missed. I'm going to shit my pants.
I give this one more try and I'm going to do it. What time is it? Don't shit your pants. I'm done
if I want to. And I might, I just might. I might just fucking, you know what I mean? Like just
you can't see what's happening in that fight. I'm just freaking out, man. What are you doing?
Don't do it. One of us has to fucking do something. So no, I forgot. I'm so I can't,
I can't even fucking man. That's like my brain is just like, for some reason I thought like she was
in phase two was going to do the swoop. Last one. This is the last one. This is ridiculous.
This is like truly a fucked up encounter. This is fucked up. Holy. Holy. She's not actually right.
Nice camera. Oh, there she is. I found her. Okay. One, two, three, go. You're scary. I'm not scary.
I'm having fun. Not having any. I'm not. What are you, why do you call me a horror fight?
It's a, what? You didn't see anybody go. Oh, what the heck? Oh shit. I'm lost in dark souls.
What the fuck, dude? It's scary. I'm not the only person that's done this. There are tons of us get
very heated and very upset at these games. I don't know what you're on about because I know for a
fact that at least there's no way I would be able to do this when I'm 40. No. Okay. Okay. Here's the
thing, guys. Listen to me. If FromSoftware comes out with another game in like four years and I'm
still screaming, we're just going to skip that one. We're just going to skip that. I'm not going to
be able to do it when I'm 40. I don't know. This is the last time that I think I'll be able to beat
like a fucking FromSoftware boss. When I'm 40 years old, I'm going to be like, I'm going to have to
count when I dodge. You know what I mean? Like one, two. All right, let's go. Good luck to all of you.
Good luck to all of you sorry motherfuckers that are going to have to play the next FromSoftware
game and go up against Melina the maggot and deal with the harder boss they make.
It's going to be harder than this. Go luck. I'm going to be on the sidelines. I'm going to be like,
oh shit, man, I'm glad I'm 40 and I don't have to do this. What happened? I wasn't even looking.
Wait, did I win? They need more. No, not again. Not again. Get in there, Mambo. Come on. Come on,
son. Come on, son. God, it's like you can't. It's so hard to see them. One does like a thrust.
There's like three that are like one, two, three thrust. The thrust one is like it comes like from
here. Oh, this sucks such ass. It's past your bedtime. No, it's not. This is the actual last
try. You take too much damage, then you die. Um, no, not really. Yeah, I didn't even see it.
Too much stuff on the screen. He's going to die for that. That sucks, man. I like need him for phase
two. I'd rather she do that to me. Keep at it. Oh, this is bad news. Really bad. I was such a bad
spot. Oh my God. Like how, man, I was just underneath her. More roll, dude. It's just that
move is fucking impossible to get away from. I was like right there as you just too close.
I could dodge through it, but then you go dodge through it like three or four times and not get
hit at all. I want to beat this, but it's so un-fucking-bearable. That's un-fucking-bearable.
No, you need the cheering and inspiration. I need the boss not to 10,000 animations
before I get to drink out of my flask. That wasn't to you. That was a great, that was towards
Melina. It was towards Melina. It was not towards you. I'm going to make that very clear.
That was a growl towards Melina. Very upset with her. I'm just going with my eyes closed.
Fuck it. Who cares? This boss sucks. I'll as well try to do it without fucking looking.
What's happening? I thought that was me that died. What happened? What? What the fuck happened?
He was stuck in the corner. Oh, I was like, why am I alive for this long?
Jump over that move. Write that down and put it on the wiki. I look fucking horrible.
I need more stamina. I need, I'm going to respect him. I'm going to respect him.
I'm just fucking around now. Get a bleed weapon. I don't want to go get the mimic tier.
Go get a plus 10 bleed weapon. Sit in the corner. Fire arrows at her in phase one.
Go get the summon that is like the cheese for this and just stand there and win for free.
What the fuck happened here? Travelers close? What do I do now? You're already doing a cheese
strat. What difference does it make if you do another cheese strat? Okay. You came in here with
10 dex, 10 strength. Do 10 vitality, 40 endurance, and you dodged every single attack and you did
14 damage a swing. Good. I don't want to do that. I want to kill this person.
Melania, Melania, Melania, Melania, Melania, Melania. Excuse me. Melania is who I am referring to.
Don't fucking twist my shit around. I want to kill this person. I want to kill Melania.
I want to kill this person as quickly and as efficiently as possible.
That's sorceries. That's, that's lightning moves. I don't want to dodge every attack.
I want to kill this person as fast as possible. I want Melania. I don't want to dodge every attack.
I want to sit there and fucking annihilate. He hates Melania's. Oh, it's, you're making me very
upset. Okay. So we're going to go. I just so badly want to just Melania needs to die
as fast as fucking possible. I want to kill them so bad. I want to go back in there and fucking get
what I can't. It's, it's like a Ouija board right now. Like I want to go in that room and do it,
but I'm going to go over here instead. You keep making it. No, you know, I don't twist my words.
To playing against millennium, these guys actually kind of feel like I, I just, let's go
beast man's curb sword. I would, I'm gone. Like there's no way you get that close.
But what, what is even over here? No attention. I didn't do it. Did you beat millennium? Yep.
It actually wasn't even that bad. I it's weird. I just pressed R1 like over and I didn't even
I just pressed R1 like this. Like I didn't even, I just staggered her a bunch of times. It's crazy.
I think I spoke something up because it was like, eventually like,
I think I crashed the game a little bit, but whatever. I'll take the win. I don't care.
She was frozen, like going like that. It was pretty cool. I got like the men.
It was so weird to watch. It was fucked up. I just walked off the edge.
Sounds like the game's fault. I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'm fine. I knew going into that, that was going to be fucking hell. Have I been up here already?
I am going backwards. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. I remember this. And it's down here and straight ahead.
Find grace is that one. So wait, I killed the dragon that was out here. All right. Yeah. So I
got to go this way here. This one tempest facing balcony. Dragon over there. What the fuck is that?
I'm going to get some water. I'll be right back. Fuck. I'm going to fucking freak out.
I so badly want to go to that bonfire and just go in the door and kill millennia. You know what I
mean? That's all I can think of. Except my head rent free. Just there. I see her face.
This one. Right back. See, it's wet. Wet seat. I wish that was his joke.
Okay. Well, that millennia was fun. This dumb ass game. I'm kidding. I like it. So I don't want this
to be loud. I'm going to mute actually. I hate when this hurts. You know, like that, like boom,
when you break a seal. Really loud. Just a little one. Just one of these little protocols.
It's been fun. Are you afraid of turning a gas stove on? No, I just don't like it.
This is where I ended up. I guess I can go down. Came from in there. I'm going to go down. I go
over this way, I guess. Whatever this place is. I'm really, really curious if the two fingers
have something to do with this. Just thinking about millennia. I just want to go in there and
you know what I mean? Who's shooting at me? What is the hard cap for damage stats, by the way?
Are you going to fight the secret boss here or are you going to let me strong do it? Let's see what
it is. I'll try whatever it is if I can do it. Cool. So what's here? Golden rune nine. That's it.
Ninety is the only true cap. Hailing falls off at eighty.
Somber stone. That's weird. My whole computer just hung up. How you doing? How you guys doing?
You guys all right? You guys doing all right? How are you doing? How are things? All right?
My tooth hurts. Oh, I'm sorry. Are all of these things tied up to the... Are they tied here?
Yeah, they look chained to these posts. Do you press joker impression? Dude, no. No,
thanks. Not... All right. Give me another day. Damn. You go sweeping with it, all right?
Can you just be funny again? What do you mean again? When was I funny? Was I funny before? What
did I do? What was the funny thing that I did today? Holy shit, this goes all the way down there.
Oh yeah, I did say I was going to ship my pants on command. I don't know. What do you want me to say?
She said I was upset about stuff. Remember, like, getting the nut kick bit? I don't remember that.
I remember talking about, like, FromSoftware's... I don't remember. It was like I got kicked in the
nuts from FromSoftware's new game. All right, this way, that way, or that way. This way.
Cool. Raid the blind rage. No, I remember talking about it. I'm kidding.
Oh, you are. I just have such a treat in front of you. You really are. Bloodborne?
Never played it before? What the fuck are these eye frames? Dude, what the heck? These fucking
halberds. The hitbox is a gigantic ice cream cone. I can't wait to investigate this. Yeah,
it really is too bad Bloodborne's not on PC. Come on, get out here. Leave me alone. Oh, another tree.
Oh, I'll go right. You have spells, you use them. I know. You think I don't think I know
that I have a spell? Come on. I know. I know. I actually have too many mana blasts if I'm not
against millennia. Oh, don't get up, right?
Okay, I could go that way eventually. Maybe I get there from here. Oh shit.
What are these guys? These? What are they? And not banished nights? Okay, well, it's that.
That. What? I have to fight two of them? Gold skin duo. Oh my god, this is going to be awful.
Doesn't that suck shit up? I don't know who I'd rather fight.
What's the game lagging? Well, okay, they're in that room. What is the fastest way to get there?
You got to fight. I can't move. I'm going to sneeze. That's why I want to be aware.
I don't think there's anything I can probably do about it. I could probably do this.
Oh, it's right here. Excuse me? Why can I go in there? What? Um, I can't go in that door.
That's the only door that looks like that. Like, listen. Horseship. Really? Does this one work?
Where are they? Dude, that move is so dumb. This lag is killing me here.
All right, let me guess. You go like, get like huge.
Huh? Really? Okay. It's kind of annoying, isn't it? This honestly doesn't feel that bad.
I feel like I'm going to be okay. So they've resummoned each other.
Is there someone outside the door? I wonder who it could be. I'm going to fly into outer space.
Oh, you know, it might be Roger. Wait. No, it's not. Where am I fucking going?
Okay, it's not there. You got to go around here. Where the fuck? Okay, honestly.
Where? Stop swinging at me. I need to. Which way is it? Is it down this way?
Isn't this where it just went? It's like all the way down and around, right? Yeah, down here.
That's supposed to suck up sorceries and it doesn't. You're already doing the.
I guess there's 50% health. Oh fuck, they're both in their second phases.
Do it! Shit, and you're going to summon your fucking friend again.
I have no healing potions left. What are you stupid? Why would you come in here without them?
I'm like, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. What? What's going on? Okay, are we good? Are we good? What the
fuck happened? Backflame tornado. Cool. This boss is the worst boss in the game with the melee build.
I think millennia probably is the worst boss in the game with any character. Very cool. All right.
I got a bell too. What was that bell? It was not that bad. I feel like that could be awful.
Kind of was. Especially, I don't know if it's with other people too, but this room,
I feel like every 10 to 20 seconds lags. That makes it even worse. That's eight and nine
smithing stones. Holy shit. Really? You can get every single weapon in the whole game up to plus
nine. All right, that's cool. I guess I should just keep going the way that I was going before.
Straight through here. I can go that way or this way. I think it's cool.
Mimic is pretty stupid. Yeah, I like it. Okay. A lot of people have been telling me to use the
mimic on millennia. No, I'm close enough. I think I could do it. I need to hunker down
and really go for it. I probably am not going to do it tonight. I'm going to be really, really
honest with you. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Actually, you know what? Let me do this while I'm here.
Mimic makes the game really easy. Look, if I need to do the mimic, I'll do it, but I don't think I
have to. I don't think so. Well, it is still difficult with the mimic. I would. Yeah, I make
the game easy. That's not the point. Oh, I mean, the point with any video game is to have fun.
All right. That's the whole point. However, you get enjoyment out of a game you're playing. That's
how you should do it. You have certainly learned that from Molina. That's not what I wanted to do.
Oh my goodness. This is very sloppy. Okay. That was, I just got like trapped.
I mean, I got literally trapped. It's one hundred and thirty FP for the black knife.
I didn't have, do I actually have that? Barely. All right. Let's try this again. That was annoying.
Okay. Blink. Good. You're in the lake. Are you going to the area after Loretto?
I would rewind about an hour or two. I would rewind an hour. You're probably okay. If you
rewind exactly one hour, I'm probably purple and screaming and talking about getting kicked in the
balls. You have to rewind a little. Oh, that's annoying. Stop it. This glare in my eyes. I
can't even see where you are. That's a boss door. I'm imagining I have to go around.
Walk into range. I don't. You're not going to do this.
You're pissing off my cat. I'm sorry. I didn't. That's not my intention.
This place is probably, I would say the coolest part of the whole game. I think
scenery wise and scale and how cool it looks. All the tornadoes. This place is awesome.
Dragon's dragon. It's like a dragon place. Jack over here. All right. I can climb this. Can I?
Oh, it's not. Wait. Oh, I did that.
Fall off the edge. Yeah.
I don't know how to get there. It's down here and then around. I don't know. Whatever. I gotta run.
I don't want to lose those souls, please.
I make too much noise. Oh, another one. Jesus.
That's a good movie death.
Is that all that was over here? Did I really come all the way over here for a lightning grease?
No, right? That's a pain. Hey, I could jump to there and go that way. Let's check and see
what's up here though and just walk. Dumbass. Nothing gonna explode. Okay, so I can jump from
up where? Where's this? There's just another. Okay, just go this way. What's in the colosseum?
Gonna be a dragon. It's gonna be a huge dragon. And then we're gonna get lore dumped. I kind of
hope we get lore dumped. I want to get lore dumped. You see, tarnished in the age of dragons
and the two fingers. I want. Give it to me. I want to get lore dumped so bad. I am hoping for like
a five minute cutscene. Souls game? I know. It's not gonna happen. Any superheroes in chat?
Um, I don't know. Do we have any superheroes here? Where? That's over here. Oh yeah, okay.
Um, I'm gonna keep going down. It's gonna kill me. Wait, actually you mad scientist.
I'm imagining I gotta go like across there? There? To the right? Is there where to go up from here?
Oh my god, that hurts. I forgot you have to jump. Oh boy, it hurts every moment. Yeah.
Where is he? Those guys are tricky. Is that like an axe? Is it like a dragon? Oh boy. Nice.
All right, don't fuck this up. You need to go to bed? I will. Whatever. I want to see what this
boss is. 122. Shit. Well, okay. You little shit. I hear another one. Missed.
What? I feel like I can make this jump, but it's definitely a shortcut. So, um, I,
I guess we're gonna run. Run? I'm gonna die. Is there safety over here? No.
It shows up on the ground for like a second and then it goes away.
Oh shit, this bird's all over me. Can I get on my horse? Oh Jesus.
You're not gonna kill him? Dude, I need to be safe for a second here.
I'm not gonna fight the guy with five eagles surrounding me. Where is he? Where does he go?
He leaves. He left. You're gonna be a pain in the ass. I know you are. Okay, so he's gone.
I'm back. I don't, I don't know. He's not here. Okay, I'm just gonna keep going. He's gonna jump
on your head. All right, let's walk through this. We're getting really close to the tornado.
I'm almost at it, man. I missed the item behind the dragon. I did? Oh shit, there is an item.
Have you seen a tornado in real life? I have not. I'm equally terrified and fascinated.
Thank you. Yeah, I'm equally horrified and fascinated by tornado. So what's up here?
I'm gonna two-hand this now. I feel like I have 30 smithing stone sevens. Is there a guy going?
What are you doing? What are you, why are you getting into position?
Oh, why is he standing there like that? Get up, stand up. Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Fool me. Why am I going back to this thing? That's it, right? Just you two. There's another one in
here. Yes, there is. You sneaky little shit. Another bell bearing. I don't get the grace.
What? What's going on? What? Grace up at the lift. Yeah, I mean, I'm just, I'm just going, man.
I'm going. I'm right here. I don't want to die. I'll go back after the grace. Let me level up.
All right, it's time to start putting points in endurance, I think. Or should I get to 60
bigger? I think it's endurance. That's so low. Okay, so I'm here. Are you saying that there is a,
oh, back here, there's a secret area. Somebody said, shut up, chat, get a hobby.
Get a hobby. Um, this dragon has no health. Can I get there quickly from somewhere? I've even been
down there. Yeah, right. Isn't that the guy that was throwing lightning at me? Yeah, it is. It's
on here. Use your hat as a glider. Just go down the stairs. Yeah, I guess I could just run. It
could have been a lot more nerve wracking. I feel like it may have been. Stop already. Stop. Okay,
so this dragon has no health. I was, yeah, I've got a feeling you're gonna be a brilliant
ass, aren't you? Um, let's go. Why does he, his health is so low. Okay, that was cool.
Why was his health so low? That's not what we were talking about. By the trees where the guy got into
position. What, over here? You mean down here? By the trees where the guy got in position over here.
Am I gonna die if I do that? I feel like I'm gonna die. Am I dead by these? Dead? Okay, well,
I, I thought it was there. Press the button, at least it's gonna be there when I get back.
Okay, so we're at, oh, around still? I'm there. Right up through a path to see guys and look down
to the right. Fucking leave me alone. Is it, it's right here, isn't it? What's that? That's not it.
Why did he jump? I was already gone. I mean, if I, I went into the tornado, you don't have to come
follow me. Straight out and then look down. It's so funny whenever they see that. They're, the AI
in From Software games is so funny. And the reason why they're so interesting and the reason why
these games are so fun, it's because the AI in these games has one thing that it does. It is one
task. There's no dialogue. There's no, oh, stranger! Get him! No, no, no. Their AI is just
fucking kill that as fast as possible, no matter what, under any circumstance. They don't do
anything else. They just kill as much and as fast as possible. They'll even hit each other. They'll
kill each other. They don't even care. I think that makes them even more terrifying. So many games
do the AI where it's like, they'll talk to you. They'll stop. They'll pause for a second.
They'll have something to say. They'll have something that they do. They'll fall down. They'll
drop something. It's just one thing is programmed into these enemies. Kill! It's so funny when they
both have the kill program. And when you have like two or three enemies that have the kill program,
and they just start beating the absolute shit out of each other. And they just start beating
the absolute shit out of each other. It's so funny. That makes them so much more terrifying.
Especially the knights. Especially the characters that you would expect to be able to talk to you
or say something or act any differently. No. Nothing. No talking. No expressions. They're
just trying to kill you as hard as possible. Now, Bloodborne enemies did talk, but I don't think it
took away from the experience. You know, like, away! Away! Oh, you foul beast! You're on the
right way. You are no one in here! And they did like the huge scream. What do I do? You have to
jump off it. Just lie down. Look. Look. I don't get it. Dirt patch? What? Backwards? Hey.
Finger. No horse allowed. Interesting. This is a huge area. No horse. I mean, you're coming with
me. Melania was fucking messed up, man. It was so hard. I think we got this one together. You and
me? Yeah, you and me. That's a bad voice for that character. Dragon Lord Placidusax. That
lightning. Placidusax. I'm just trying to keep my eye on the ground. Nice. Right down? Does it come
up? What happens? That is quite the move. Gotta be aware of that. It's got like two heads. Whoa!
Don't get greedy. Don't get greedy. There's no reason. That fills his whole body. Oh my god!
What the fuck? Oh, it's like that bug boss. It disappears and it's scary.
I wonder if there's a place where you don't get hurt in that. Oh my god! No! I'm terrified.
What is he? Oh my god, that was fucking majestic. Out of time? Kind of. Oh my god.
Almost out of mana. Let's go get ugly. Do it again.
That was crazy. I thought he was done with the attack. One, two, three, four, five, six. One,
two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six, eight. Searching around in your fucking
huge ass backpack. Why did I do that? Because I had no health. Oh my. Ouch. Because I had like
this much health and I didn't want to die in one hit. These. I get it. That was fun. That was a
cool fight. What else do I want to put on here? I'll take, let's take, I'll take a rune arc.
Let's take it down there. Go the fuck back up. Does he hate the game? What? No. I think it's
amazing. Where's the nurse here? That fight's really cool. I'm looking forward to doing it again.
I wish there was a statue down here. I don't have to do this every single time.
Let's take a rune arc. Why not? Yeah, why not? Let's go. And let's go.
Elden Ring is objectively a mediocre game. I'm gonna have to disagree with you a little.
I'm not going for, I'm not doing any moon shit. No moons. That's way too fancy right now. Just
kill it. Oh fuck. My fingers are getting like really sore and slippery. That's a sign. That's
a bad sign. How do you do that? The edge. You know what? Oh my god. What am I thinking?
That's a perfect time to do this a couple times. There he goes. He's gonna do this bullshit. Yep.
Oh, he does a little, a little hop. He does this little like, oh shit, this is bad. He does like a
little shit. Fuck out of this. This is a really awful sloppy fucking run. This is the worst run
I've done all night on any bus. It happens when you play for eight and a half hours.
That's the watch. I'm gonna have to leave it. Unless I can fucking take this. Oh, come on. Oh
my god. Miss stamina. Where is he? Oh my god, he's behind me. Moon. I did like five moons to him.
You gotta rush him. That was the last bit's rough. I was really, really sloppy on the first phase
there. I was just like jump, jump, jump, jump, jump. That was awful. Nebula will be really good.
Actually, that's a really good idea. I'll try Nebula. Moon isn't good to spam. Use it once
with the debuff. Does the moon make anybody take more magic damage or is it only cold
sorcery damage? The only frost. I'm gonna do, let's just go in there and just, just Nebula.
Let's do Nebula. Let's just get in there. Just get, let's get in there. Watch this.
I'm just gonna get in there and Nebula. Let's get in there. Yeah, it's Nebula time. Fucking,
let's go. You wanna cast this for free? Probably could have got a little closer,
but whatever. Nebula, let's go. Nebula. I'm not, I don't even care about these souls.
Check this out. All right, the first part of this fight, he just puts that shit everywhere.
And this is what happened to me last time. I can't tell if it's better. It's hard to tell.
Am I doing more damage? I think it takes a little longer. I don't think so. Cold is better. He's
gonna do that move where he spams the ground with that bullshit. Where is it? Come on, just do it.
I know you can do it. All right, the one fucking second that I... Stop it! Oh my god, he scared
the fuck out of me, dude. Can you fucking stop doing that? Dude, stop. Stay. Why is he not staying?
Am I still in it? God damn it. Oh my god. I'm dead. Why is it always fucking right on me?
You have to be, it's right on me every goddamn time. I don't know what these assholes are like.
If you get closer, you just have to fucking, you just have to run. Just run away from the fight.
Don't get close to him. Don't stay far away. Don't get close to him. Don't get far away. Don't get
close to him. Are you stupid? God damn it. Where is he? You? What the fuck do I do about that move?
Fucking Jesus. What are you doing, man? You done? I can't get him down at this part.
They had to put another one of these assholes in the game that just like
fucking appears behind you somewhere. So when he starts doing that move, he's gonna run out.
Okay, the actual first thing is first. Do not, under any fucking circumstance,
do not go near the boss in the first minute. He just puts the red stuff on the ground and
you're gonna get hit by it and you're gonna drink four flasks because you get stuck in there. Do
you understand? So you're literally just bad. You're literally getting banned for five days.
Got him. I'm probably streaming five days. By the way, five days is about five minutes.
They brought this gimmick back. It's just like the boss disappears and you fucking
found him. I'm not gonna take a rune arc. I don't think it's a waste. See? He does this stupid shit
and I keep getting hit by it. I'm not getting hit by it anymore. Check it out. It's the same two
stupid ass fucking moves in the beginning. Just wait till this asshole is done with his stupid
spam the whole fucking room and now let's play the game. He's ass kicked.
Ambo's getting destroyed. He's trying to run away. He's like, oh shit, am I too far away? What?
No, I'm not. Okay, here we go. Fuck you. Done? No! Jesus! Oh, that little fucking crowhop is so
stupid. Fuck you. Where is he? Oh shit. Dude, come on. What the fuck? Oh, you pain in the ass.
I already knew. Dude, where? Where? No, that was quick. That was quick, bro. That was quick.
Bro, that was quick. You built a pain in the ass. I don't know. I think that was fun. Remembrance of
the Dragon Lord. That's a lot. Mogs was the most in the whole game so far.
Mogs was 420,000. I mean, that was a really cool fight. It was. You know, the teleport shit.
That was probably one of the cooler fights in the game. Just in regards to bosses.
Interesting that was. So this is... I have so many fucking items in my inventory.
Where is it? Is that just a spell? Isn't it a remembrance? Where is it?
Oh, it's a weird looking. Remembrance of Dragon Lord Placidusax. He went into the urd tree.
Hour of its namesake can be unlocked by the finger reader. Yeah. Dragon Lord whose seat lies at the
heart of the storm beyond time. Said to have been Elden Lord in the age before the urd tree.
Once his god was fled, the lord continued to await its return. This dragon was the Elden Lord?
The original Elden Lord. That's pretty cool. 25 endurance is probably what I'm going for here.
Anybody have anything to say about that? Anybody have anything to say?
You're still gone. But what's up? What is it? What's the item?
Dragon King's Crag Blade and 36 faith. Golden Breath of the Dragon Lord.
It storms the caster into the dragon lord to spew golden breath.
These are the dying whales of the dragon lord who once dwelled eternally beyond time.
Seems pretty good. These are both awesome. This is just a pure dex weapon. That's pretty cool.
How much longer? I'm gonna see what the boss is up there and then I'll probably end it there.
I don't think we're gonna beat it. Well, I'm gonna break it. I'm gonna smash it.
Because I thought that's not for this character. Oh yeah, Holly is doing dragon stuff. So
when you get that, it's gonna be cool. Next boss is one of the best in the game.
I think that one was pretty cool. I would put that up there. 30,000 souls is really nothing.
I want to keep going over there. This area I think is my favorite area of the game.
I think it's just really really cool looking. This place is beyond time. What this place is?
I don't get it. Yes it is. The right place. Everything went backwards. Not right either.
Which is the? This is where I fought him. Dragon Temple. What's the right one?
By the bridge bud. There we go. Okay. So this thing like is rewinding time.
Or it did when I lay down. Why did it do that when I lay down?
Go down there. Storm at the center is beyond time. Well, no time like the present.
Free sentinel? It is. You're like a waffle tree sentinel. You're different than the others.
One of these guys. Eat that and I will die if I didn't. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Whoa. Malformed dragon helm. Malformed dragon armor. Let me take a look at that.
Holy shit. It's not even that heavy. Malformed golden armor adorned with various dragon imagery
formed by the misshapen tree sentinels. After the great ancient dragon Bransax attacked,
the sentinels had an epiphany. The only way to truly protect the urtri was to become dragons
themselves. Is that better than what I have on? Kind of is. Still medium. Still medium. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh wow. Cool. I look pretty cool. I don't want to lose a hundred thousand souls so
we're gonna I'm just gonna go this way for a minute. There's another way to go over here.
I need like another twenty thousand. Is there anything else that I missed?
Probably. But that dragon wasn't even the boss. Like the actual boss of this area.
Is there anybody can just fight right here? Oh my god. Thank god I jumped. I just I just need to
kill a few. Seven. I got a better idea. Stop looking. Stop looking at it. Like it's a broken
toy. Watch out. It's so funny. They go like. I don't understand. Like why is it so confusing?
What's there? 130? 120? We'll do endurance again. 128. Almost there. 25. 27.
We're good. Bye. The base of the tree before millennia is a better spot. Get auto to fight
millennia. Game crash. Please don't tell me you crashed. I think it did. Did I go too fast?
Was I going too fast? Hope it's still there. You went too furious. I think I'm fine.
I just want to see what's in there and then that'll be it. Bricked. I didn't. I don't think I bricked
the save. Get some rest. Yeah I'll be fine. I'll be all right. It's definitely fine. When will you
play something else? When I'm done with this. Which I'm getting painfully close to the end of
the game. Painfully. See? All right. Just time. Let's do it slowly. I'm not going to do it. Okay.
Ready? Endurance up. Now let's see what is behind this door. Very curious at what's up here because
this area is already sort of interesting. I want to know what is in here. Who's behind this whole
thing? Why? And what are the fingers? Why are they here? Why won't it talk to me anymore?
Don't answer that. All right. So what is here? Oh that's a loading screen. Wait.
It's him? What is he doing here? That's um Garanc right? I don't know what Garanc is doing here.
He's a different guy. Didn't finish the quest line. No I didn't. A different beast clergyman.
All right. Well okay don't roll to the left. Noted. I can't believe it. I didn't. I don't know.
I said it and immediately forgot it. You will not take destined death from me. All right dick.
Okay get away from the left. He's throwing rocks fast. Gotta wait a little longer for that one.
Geez man. Jump. What did you do? Like fuck you. I'm just gonna do this.
Don't see the fucking stupid.
Guess who? Who's around this hand?
We're gonna see what they look like. Oh he's one of those like wolf lion people.
That weapon is insane. Maleketh the black blade.
You have a debuff? I'll just set up the bonfire. Next. The ability is bleeding you.
That's a cool fight. Low health but high damage. You just kind of gotta get in there huh?
I wonder if I should just go to town. Reduces your max HP. All right well let's go. Just
don't get hit. This is terrible. I can't dodge. I'm fucked. Yeah I'm dead. Just go. Like dude
what was I thinking? He comes in so fast. Thank you game. Good luck. All right let's go.
That's not gonna work here. Up. Down. Jesus. Okay goes up and then down and then up and then down
and just like that. All right put the put the fucking stupid moon blade away. This is just
gonna get me killed. This is the reason I don't even want it on the bar. Let's get rid of it.
These are gonna get me killed. I need to think what else what do I have that's quick?
Comet? No. I don't know. Magic glint blade. I don't think any of these are gonna do anything for me.
I think I have to try this. This might be interesting. All right just in case. I'll
I'll keep the moon. Yeah let me try this. I wonder how this works. Five more minutes and then I'm
gonna go. I did not anticipate this being a nine hours rune. Bounding rain of stars is not quick.
I'm curious if I can get it off before he comes over. Baby rattle is an accessory at this point.
I mean at this point I have the plus 10 wooden sorcery thing. I feel like if you got hit by that
it'd be way better. Did you do it to the pillar or bro? I'm curious if it'll not. It's okay.
I wouldn't say it's great. Jesus christ. Oh my god. What the fuck was that shit?
We have two minutes left. Now also like the only thing from software at this point you just have
like a line in the middle of the health bar. Like the like phase two. Here comes phase two.
Just put a line in the middle. We know it's there. We know it's there. Like I don't know how many
more like hey look Jebaites. That counts. Ah fine. If that motherfucker goes down and starts talking
and being like death is mine. I am going to keep spamming spells at him. I'm not going to let him
keep talking. I'm going to go up there and whack him in the fucking head over and over again.
Why would I let him talk? Shit. What's going on? Why is he stuck?
God damn it. What the fuck? What? I couldn't do anything. I couldn't attack him.
He was just never ending. Never fucking ending. Oh my god that's so frustrating.
I was cringe ass guy behind the pillar.
Oh that's so fucking frustrating. I know attack him but like dude when the guy is like just spinning
and fucking flipping and like like fucking fanning these blood. I've only seen it two times.
Fucker. He was dead. This is literally the fucking second time I've seen that move.
Why is that not hitting me? Gotta be ready for phase two. Oh my god you motherfucker. Is it going
through his fucking stupid ass fucking cloak? God. I gotta stay right as they're on his legs or
something. Uh he almost fucking had it too. What a piece of shit. What a piece of shit. I just like
that time when he had like one hit left he was just like dude I didn't know if he was in what he was
gonna fucking do. This guy flips around like a fucking maniac. Okay he blocks it right. What does
he do here? Stop dodging! The input happened and I didn't do it. This game sucks. There's a cut scene?
What is it? I'm kidding this is one of the best games to come out in the last decade. I'm kidding.
Is this the third phase? No I got the resemblance. What words am I saying?
The rune of death is unbound and the lands between us shrouded by death's dark fate.
Flames will also burn the impenetrable thorns. Farewell it is then. You'll be elden lord yet.
What did you do? Um I burnt the whole world to the ground. He looks depressed. I'm just tired.
I'm just tired man. I'm cranky and I'm hungry and I'm tired and I'm stupid. What happened here?
Lindel Ashen capital. Whoa oh can I still go to the round table? New items can be purchased
from the twin maidens. This place is in the urn tree. Will you wake up already? This is a
fate sword. Alaketh's black blade which once harbored the power of the rune of death with a
sad shadow of its former glory. After a fragment of death was stolen on that fateful night,
Alaketh found the blade within his own flesh such that none might ever rob death again.
Set free the remnants of death and death plunging the greatsword into the ground to summon a
myriad of blades. In addition to dealing immediate damage, this attack reduces the enemy's maximum
HP. What about this? Man faith gets all the cool shit at the end of the game. Black blade spinning
slash that emits a wave of light. 46. It creates an illusory black blade then leaps forward to
deliver a spinning slash that emits a new wave of light, followed with one additional attack.
This blade was once imbued with destined death. In addition to dealing damage,
it reduces its foes max HP. Remembrance of the black blade. You didn't get the coolest int spell?
So wait, why are the two fingers still doing this? Where's the guidance? Where's the help?
Alaketh's helm. Queen Merica's loyal half-brother wore a blade imbued with destined death,
and there was not one demigod who did not fear him. Champions knew what was at stake. Indeed,
that is what made them champions. So let me get this straight. Is this guy who's got destined
death that people are afraid of? You can't come back or something? Like if Malaketh killed you,
were you like dead permanently or something? I don't get it. Destined death. You die for real.
Everyone's immortal. But if this guy killed you, you're dead. You don't come back. How much better
is this? It's all right. Very cool. I'm going to crush it because I am a sorcery person.
Who's left here? I see. You're here for some spirit too. Really? You're still here?
Who are you? I must be a blacksmith. Now, let's get smithing. Who are you? Tell me about yourself.
Could you tell me what happened? Why is the round table burning?
Why does that girl wait for me? What happened? Have I forgotten something of dire and bones?
Who are you? What does Gideon say now? Is he still just here? Or did he leave?
Remember that. I got a lot of these bell bearings. That's crazy. Cracked crystal.
What else is new here? Ease. Protection. Divine fortification. Amp. Talk to the girl again.
I don't know why he's making me laugh, but when I said this game sucks, somebody just went,
no it doesn't. It just hit me right now. That's funny. I see. Okay. Yeah. What happened to Hugh?
It wasn't just me this happened to. I think he'd forget who you were as well.
I knew he'd burn himself out. Old Hugh. I think we could talk him into leaving the round table
a hold now. Maybe it's better that we don't. It's only proper that we respect his choice to stay.
Why is- what's wrong? With Hugh. He made me who I am today. I'd like to return the kindness.
Whatever small way I can. Please become the elder lord. He was always saying that you were a lord
to him. So slay her with the weapons he smithed. Slay the god who cursed us all.
Well I thought that America was- Queen America was the- I mean curse. Is America evil? Okay.
I- I'm curious. I'm not going to bed yet. I'm curious. I just- I'm just- I want to know. I want
to know. I'm not going to bed. Not yet. I'm not going to fight any bosses. I just want to see
what's going on. I want to see something. See. I'm not doing anything. I'm not going to end the game.
I just want to see. Because I'm not sitting at a cliffhanger until I stream next.
Go talk to Hugh. You know, where- this is- look if I walk in the door and I get killed by the
boss- I'm not going to fight the boss, right? I just need to see. All right, let's go. It is
capital bash. Well I'm- now we're going to the urn tree. That's the destination, right?
Behold the urn tree yet stands. All in unwavering mindless of the scourge of the flame of ruin.
Ha ha ha. And we are yet golden ones. I'm gonna laugh my ass off if Margit shows up
like a fourth time. So this is the capital. It's- this is all ash. Huh. This is depressing.
I wonder if there's even any enemies here. This feels like it's just kind of a
solemn walk up to the urn tree. Okay. Well that's probably- is that an elevator?
Okay. Anything else I can do over here? What does your belly button look like?
Um, it's like the size of, uh, like a half dollar. It's like this big around. I can actually put like
stuff in it. If I have like change and stuff that can go in there. Okay, let's just like,
go I guess. You know the grace that I can go to? Our capital is burning. Okay, here we go.
We're in the- I knew you'd come. To stand before the Elden Ring. To become held. What a sad state of
affairs. I commend your spirit, but alas, none shall take the throne. I told you he was a fucking
asshole. Queen Micah's high hopes for us. But we continue to struggle. Unto eternity. To get Ian
off near the all-knowing. He does- okay, so why did he tell me to do this then? What's your fucking
problem? Oh, you're a real fucking chump, that's for sure. Unless let me go, let me guess. He's
got a face to it. Not actually. Shit. Okay, I'm gonna kill this guy right now. I just- I didn't
know what he did. He's- does he have a rune? You actually died? He actually died, to get Ian.
Dude, we're going on 10 hours, man. What do you want me to say? It's right here. Okay, let's
fucking destroy this guy right now. I didn't- so he's a mage. Fuck you, Gideon.
Oh, that hurt me too. Fuck you. Okay, magical. Magical protection. I'm wearing-
excuse me. Magic protection. I need to put it on. I don't know what I'm doing. I- I'm just
giving- I don't know what I'm doing right now. I'm doing fucking Donald Trump. It's like fucking
nine and a half hours, 1230. I'm gonna play this game, Gideon. I don't- I don't get this.
Wasn't the whole time, Gideon, like, oh yeah, we have this place for you,
tarnished and tarnished, come and go, and we're gonna do the Elden Lord stuff. Yeah,
go get the runes and become El- why is he- no, no, don't be Elden Lord. How dare you.
What is he talking about? Didn't- wasn't he the one that wanted us to do this?
Or does he just want to do it himself? I got news for you, Gideon.
There ain't a chance in hell that you're- actually probably better than I am, yeah.
I need magic. Magic defense. That doesn't do anything else besides magic. Magic? Oh god.
So many pieces of armor. I don't- I have no idea which is better.
Oil Knight? Uh, some of these are probably better up here. All right, you piece of shit.
And I'm not gonna cast spells at him. I'm just gonna go bash his head in with this will.
What's up, dude? Runes, who cares? I don't need them. I'm gonna fucking beat him, all right?
No, I want to see what's- I want to see what's in that door.
I want to see what's in that door. It's right there. I'm not gonna- I know it's the final boss.
I'm not- I just want to see what's in the door. Holy shit, that hurt a lot. You idiot.
And who could forget Sir Gideon Ofnir? We all know him. There he is.
You drink?
What's happening to my brain? This dude's wicked high.
All right, I'm just gonna go in there and I'm gonna go with my fists and I'm gonna fucking
crush his head. He's actually throwing. I just- I'm fine. You gotta do a comedy one sometimes,
okay? You gotta do a comedy one sometimes. That was a good strategy and I'm gonna do it again.
Sorry, everybody. I apologize. I do. I'm gonna stay across the fucking whole room. What is he
doing? Now, all rise. You're tarnished. You're dead. Die, you old fuck. Ain't nothing in there,
is there, Gideon? You're out of spell power, aren't you?
Hey, butters. Hey, beavers. Scepter of the- Oh, you get- He's got awesome armor.
I love his armor. It's so cool looking. Can I put that on? So what's- I don't understand
what his problem is. All-knowing helm. Helm set with countless eyes and ears,
won by Gideon Ofner, the all-knowing. Knowledge begins with the recognition of one's ignorance.
The realization that the search for knowledge is unending. But when Gideon glimpsed into the
will of Queen Merika, he shuddered in fear. At the end, that should not be. I love that helmet.
I have to keep the head on. All-knowing armor. Light. Really light. Wait, in case you didn't
notice, he had all the boss powers? He did? Okay, I- that- I'm now- I- it's- it's time to go- I'm
gonna- I'm going in the Erd Tree. I'm probably- I'm gonna lose, right? I don't think I'm gonna
beat this boss. I'm not prepared for it. Oh, the staff! He did have a staff. I've got an entire
museum in my backpack. Honest to God, where is it? It is int scaling. Scepter in the form of a hand
grasping a pearl. Signature weapon of Sir Gideon Ofnir, the all-knowing. Pearl stands for the world,
the heavens, and an eye. Representing the many forms of knowledge, never fully attainable.
Even knowing that, the all-knowing's hand grasps for it. Knowledge above all. Raise the scepter to
manifest the realm of the all-knowing. Enemy magic and holy damage negation will be reduced for all
within the area, including the caster. How long does it- this is- this is a weapon.
This is not a staff. This is an actual swinging weapon. It's a mace. Oh, shit, it is.
That's really cool. I'm gonna have to check that out. I mean, literally with the end of the game,
whatever. All right, I- it's- we're going on 10 hours- 10 hours. I know. I gotta speed things up
here. I want to go in this door. I just need to know. I want to see what- I want to see Queen
Merica. Definitely fucking in there. Definitely in there. Guarantee it. I want to see Queen Merica.
I need to go up to the urn-free entrance place, which is up here, right? He has returned. The
Lord has returned at long last. Our very first Lord to brandish the Elden Ring once more.
Are you talking about me? I didn't think I had to jump. I thought I was just gonna fall on it.
And Sir Gideon Arthas arrives. He tarnished. He dead. He lives. That intro is so good. It's a
great intro. It almost feels like it's like a- like a- promoting like a wrestling event.
Like hype up- hype up all these superstars. How many times have you watched it? Well,
at least a couple of times. That's it, probably 20 times. Bird Tree Heal. I have any idea what the fuck
is going on in this game. Vastly heals HP for self and nearby allies. One of the ancient urn-
bird tree incantations. Heals a vast amount of HP for the caster and nearby allies. Hold to continue
praying and delay activation. The urn tree once flourished with abundance, yet it was only for a
fleeting moment. Such is the course of all life. A moment. A fleeting moment. The urn tree like
actually had power. Deer. All right, I want to know. What the fuck is it? What's in here?
What is it? Here we go. I'm turning it up. This thing that's getting the shit out of me.
It's been a long disdow fight. Farnished warrior. Spurned by the grace of gold. Be assured the
Elden Ring resteth close at hand. Who the fuck is this? I am returned. Wait, is that-
To be granted audience once more. Godfrey?
But what is he? How did he- How did he- As Godfrey, the first Elden Lord.
Godfrey, the first Elden Lord. Where have you been this whole time?
I was hiding behind that pillar over there for the last 600 game hours. You just didn't see me,
but I was snooping. I gotta jump. I gotta jump with that shit. I gotta jump. I didn't want to
take a rune arc. I wanted to- That's not good. Bomb up. Dude, fucking stop kicking the ground,
you dick. Oh shit. Dude, yikes. Ambo, you gotta help me here, man. Ambo, please. Ambo, please help
me. Dude, base two. You gotta fight the goddamn- You gotta fight the lion.
Speak of service, Sirosh.
I've given thee courtesy enough. They're into a street fighter character.
I fight just horror alone. Wait, the- Wait, the chief of the Badlands? Wait,
the chief of the Badlands from the intro? Oh my god, he's actually fucking zangy.
That ain't gonna work against this. I don't think so. Oh, I don't know about that. I don't know
about that. Where was this guy the whole game? Wait, Godfrey? I'm Godfrey. I'm God- No, I'm kidding.
It's me. Horlou. It's me. It's me. I'm Horlou now. Horlou is Godfrey. There's so many names in this
game. I know it's time to go to bed, but let's round it out at 10 hours. Come on. Oh, it's a
little early, but I'm fine. Oh, fuck. Too greedy. Let me do it again. I thought he was gonna hit
phase two. I was really thinking if that was phase two. That wasn't bad. Mambo's getting his ass
feed. Mambo is making me happy. He's the chieftain of the Badlands when he's just hanging out.
That doesn't make any sense. Close enough? Don't jump into it. What, are you stupid?
Oh, shit. That's bad. I'm dead. Kick. What the fuck? The suplexes. Jesus Christ.
I'm getting so fucked up here, dude. I'm getting so fucked up. I'm getting so fucked up.
Dude, I'm getting so fucked up here. I don't fucking have any idea what happened here.
I don't fucking have any idea what's going on. Jesus. No. There's so much going on. Just get away from me.
Grow. Oh, I'm dead.
Casting is too slow. Oh, I got the magic resist gear on. Shit. Did somebody say? You're gonna say
so bad. Oh, come on, man. This fight is fucking cool. You gotta get.
I don't know. Should I just go full oven mitts? Okay. I'm ready. I am going to wait to summon
my buddy. Phase two. Oh, shit. He doesn't. As sloppy as fuck, I'm gonna tell you.
Get the fuck out of here. Let's go. Come on, Gwen. Come on, Gwen. This guy's just fucking being
the shit out of me. Oh, my God. Oh, fuck you, bro. Bro. I had to do that. Isn't it? Oh, shit.
Oh, I'm dead. Stop healing in front of him. Dude, he's just fucking so fast.
Actually, there's probably not a window to summon in phase two. You're right.
Going like ding, ding, ding, ding. No, you're fucking dead. I got him. I got him. I got him.
Out of something right before phase two. That's the play is you got to get somebody. You got you.
He's just so relentless. All right, let's go. This fight's fucking awesome, by the way. This is the
best fight in the whole game. This is the best fight in the game. I will stand by that. I gotta
wait a second for this. I should. Yeah, that was dumb. Let's just be balls. No, man. All right.
Come on. Oh, my God. All right. I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. Here we go.
Oh, get in there, Mambo. Come on. Shit. I thought he was going for Mambo.
Mambo, please get aggro, please. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Sit down. I almost fucked it up like three
times. Remembrance of Hora Lou. But, dude, who's Godfrey? The same person. It's the same guy.
That was the best fight in the game by far. That was by far the coolest fight in the whole game.
Is it health or is it endurance? But fair. Yeah, that was so fun. God, that was the best fight in
the game. I wish I could do that again. And the remembrance. I think I'm gonna do endurance,
right? Like, it's the safe thing to do. I want to read this because... So what, people,
you change your name? Oh, I'm Godfrey, but I'm also Hora Lou. I don't get it. Where is it?
This is a paragraph. When Godfrey, first Elden Lord, was robbed of his grace,
becoming tarnished, he took with him his kinfolk and left the lands between.
After the long march of the tarnish came to an end, Godfrey divested himself of kingship,
becoming a simple warrior once more. Godfrey got exiled and then changed his name. Hurry up
and end the stream. The Europeans are gonna wake up any second now, Monka S. I look so awful today.
I'm the sweatiest I've been probably in the last month, at least. This is the sweatiest stream by
far. All right, lore masters, I need to ask a question. If I go in, if I go in there and see
what's in there, is the game end? Only if I... Okay, I kind of want to... Let me see what's up with
Godfrey. I know we're going really late, but let me just see what's in here. Where is that going? Oh,
yeah. Okay, so are the fingers gonna talk to me now? Dude, what are you doing? What the fuck?
They just fucked off. They don't care anymore. Okay, I want to see what this remembrance is.
But if you're dead, how are you doing this? Axe of Godfrey, dex strength, 42 strength. Damn.
Weapon of Godfrey Elden Lord, it was broken in a battle fought as leader of the tarnished
during the long march. This weapon is symbolic of Godfrey's vow to conduct himself as a lord,
later becoming an emblem of the golden lineage. In the days of the past,
the crown was warranted with strength. Or Oralu's earthshaker. Oralu's earthshaker slammed
both hands into the ground. Okay, that's awesome. Heavy. This is strength stuff.
They said they wouldn't talk for thousands of years. Read Godfrey's icon talisman. Do I have
that? I don't have it. All right, it's time to go in there. I'm not going to use either one of these,
but I'm not going to break it because in case I don't want to lose the souls. It's time to see
what the fuck is inside the tree. Finally. Let's do it. What's in here? Title theme.
Radagon of the Golden Order. Damn. That's a little display on that. Thought I could jump it.
Oh shit. Okay, I gotta stay behind him. Don't blast it. Shit. Not bad. It's not bad. Oh fuck.
Oh my goodness. Okay, you gotta run. I just want to see phase two. I want to see phase two and I'm
done. Radagon. I just want to see phase two because this is not the fight. Mom said it's my turn to
be Elden Lord. So what? I don't get it. How do you get away? I think you have to dodge through it.
Dude. What the fuck? I just want to see fucking phase two. Oh my God. I just want to see you
turn into another fucking monster or something. I got to get that down if I'm going to see phase
two. Dude, I don't know where the fuck to go. Why is it on phase? Oh, oh, I get it.
Show me phase two. I got it. I don't know. Phase two. I got it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get
it. I'll get it. This is fun. You've got to earn phase two. It's so late. I know. I'm so sorry.
This is so bad. But I gotta go for it. Oh, you do it twice? What's this whole shit?
That was a bad fucking combo. That was dog shit and you all know it.
This is dog shit and you all know it. I've never seen him do that fucking move. What is he doing
that? Oh, come the fuck on. Dude, stop doing that. He's done that move like 50 times this time.
Do something else. My God, you're going to drive me fucking crazy. Jesus, I dropped my head back.
He just kept throwing those stupid fucking spears. He did it like 10 fucking times.
Stop doing that move. Do something else. You have like 40 moves.
I just want to see phase two. You keep getting hit. Yeah, because it's like he goes, huh? Boom,
then they explode. And sometimes he does two. Sometimes he does two. This game is a three out
of 10. It's a three. Wait, I can summon in here? Oh shit, I can summon. I didn't think it would be
allowed in here. Fighting the fucking Elden Lord. I don't remember your name in the intro,
dickhead. Dude, show me phase fucking two already so I can go to bed. I just want to see what it is.
Mambo, help me. Oh no, you got flabbered. That was so sad.
You didn't, Mambo. What the fuck is that? Get it, Mambo. Oh, Mambo's way outmatched here,
I think. I just got glassed. Doing it again. What? Show me phase two. Let's see it. Phase two
incoming. Mambo, just touch him, please. Get it. Mambo, settle down. Save your strength. You're
going to need it. Dude, what are the fingers? I don't get it. What is that? Elden beast. Mambo,
hold on. Yeah, we can't even get over there, Mambo. That was a good run. Oh, she just
liquid-fired him. Mambo just got liquid-fired. Oh my god. Okay, you guys are screwed up.
What are these? What is this? I don't get it. They're just fingers? Talk to people?
All right, do I have to do phase two again? Do I have to do phase one again?
They really want to fuck you up here, huh?
Yeah, they're really looking to fuck you the whole shit up, huh?
All right, well, that's cool. I am definitely not doing this tonight.
We'll come back to this. I'm just doing... I just spit everywhere. I'm not even playing. Look,
I'm not even playing. I'm just sitting around. It's not even going to be playing today. See,
he just hit me so bad. I'm dead. I'm going to die right here. He hit me so hard.
I'm not even playing. See, look, I fucking got hit by a regular attack. Are you kidding me?
What a shitty player, right? I don't even have any mana. I'm not even trying. I'm not even playing.
Oh my god. How do you get away from that? You got to be shitting me. Am I seriously too far away?
I'm not even playing. Just checking it out. You're making pick his own bedtime.
Okay, Elden Beast. I'm going to get in close. Stay right behind you. I don't know. Stay in
underneath. You don't want me to sit. Oh my god. You're so fucking far away. Can I get on the horse?
What do I fucking do here? This is not where you're supposed to be. All right, good night.
I'll see you later. I don't have any heals left. Whose hand is that? I don't get it. It's aliens.
All right, I'm done. That's enough. That's enough. Okay, that's enough.
Well, there's the Elden Beast. Okay, this guy told me. Where was he? Is he still around?
Three fingers. What the fuck are the fingers? The two fingers. The three fingers. The Elden Beast.
I don't understand. I can't believe that dude. That two fingers abandoned us and we're in the
tree and this motherfucker doesn't care. I'll be back in 10,000 years. Horse shit. Where you at?
Honestly, still just hanging out there. Well, okay. Pretty cool. I'm going to bed. Have a
wonderful evening and wonderful sleep everybody. Sorry we went so long. That was a lot going on
today. We did bro versus bro with Ludwig. We're out of the end of Elden Ring. I didn't beat it,
but here we are. Damn. Very cool. I have a lot more questions though. The next stream,
I will see you guys on Sunday. We'll go Sunday. So nothing today technically and then nothing on
Saturday. I'm going to try to beat Elden Ring on Sunday. Hopefully. Check the Godfrey armor.
Uh, didn't I get so many armors? Where is it? Oh, it's at the finger lady. Right. Okay.
Elden Lord Crown. The age of the urtree began amongst conflict when Godfrey was Lord of the
battlefield. He led the war against the giants, faced the Storm Lord alone. And then there came
a moment when his last worthy enemy fell. And it was then as the story was told that the hue of
Lord Godfrey's eyes faded. I didn't register any of that. No, I didn't. Godfrey fought
Acid Disax, the dragon, and four or five extra sweet sours in his bag. I was like really happy
about it because you get to save them. You're only going to use one. I don't. Okay. There's a lot.
I'm going to watch the baddie video. Wasn't that dragon was an Elden Lord? What the fuck is an
Elden Lord? I keep hearing these terms and I don't know really what any of them actually mean.
Oh, tarnished. Two fingers. Elden Lord. Elden Lord. So, a dragon was Elden Lord, which means that
the greater will, right? Like, yeah, that's fine. The dragon's an Elden Lord. This guy killed the
dragon and like became Elden Lord and they were like, oh shit. Um, okay.
Tarnished are people who lost grace. But what is grace? What does that mean? Elden Lord is like a
God's chosen person. Grace is the guidance of God. It's the guidance of the greater will. Okay. So,
why did I burn the urn tree? What are we doing in here? Just because you wanted to get inside.
Get the Elden Ring, you idiot. Because the world sucks. Okay. I guess that makes sense.
I'm very interested in the lore. I really am. So, is the greater will and the urn tree the same
entity? What the fuck is the urn tree? Why is the urn tree even here? Who planted that shit?
Who planted the urn tree? What is the howling tree? Why is there a howling tree?
Why is there so many- why do those people have trumpets? Why is there so many trumpets?
All right. All right. I'll see you guys. I'll see you later. I'll see you on Sunday.
Why do they have trumpets, baddie? Please tell us. Very interesting. That's cool though. So,
Horoloo is Godfrey. Godfrey. We fought Godfrey's yellow shade in the- why was he not here? Remember
it was like he was bright and gold and we fought him in that- before the throne room and then he
shows up again later. Oh, hey, it's me, Godfrey. Was that him fighting us? Was it somebody pretending
to be him? It was a force ghost. It's cool. Yeah. All right. All right. All right. All right. Just
go with it. I am. I'm just very curious. And what's- what is- with Gideon so badly was like,
oh, you are gonna stand- wasn't he like, oh, we both- well, you're gonna stand before the Elden
Lord. Oh, that's what we tarnish do. That's what we do. Don't go stand in front of the Elden Lord,
you dick. All right. Watch the lore video. I think there's still more to know because this is-
obviously this is an end of the game, which is going to be something, right? All right. I'll see
you guys later. Thanks for watching. I'll see you next time. Staying up late. That was a meaty one.
This is the longest stream I've done in a long time. I think the first, second or third Elden
Ring stream was pretty long. I'm gonna give this game a three. We'll bump it up a little bit. It's
like a 9.7 maybe. That's cool. What a cool game. I'm- is it weird that I'm sad? I'm kind of sad.
It's not over yet, but it is- it will be really soon. It's sad. We'll get another stream out of
it. I still have to rage quit Milani again. I've got to kill the glass boss. Pretty much it.
Ending of playing your first playthrough of a masterpiece is always sad.
Yeah, I kind of look at the map. I'll go to bed in a second. It's just like- this was a journey.
This was absolutely a journey. I have no idea what the hell's really going on, but
it sure was fun walking around through the sewers as well. Three fingers. I did fight Mog.
Yep. I killed- yep. I killed Rikard. I killed Mog. Very cool. No, this is- it's fantastic. It is.
Well, think about this, right? I will leave you with this. I have been playing this game a lot.
We have officially passed more than a month of playing this game every single time I turn the
stream on. A month. I can't remember the last- even other From Software games. I can't remember the
last time that a game has kept my attention for more than 100 hours. I don't think so. Nothing
has kept my attention for this long. But Elden Ring streams are not going to stop because I'm
going to try to beat the game. Let's hope I do it. I will eventually, right? I want to do an invasion
like PvP summon night. I think that'd be fun. Do some like- have like a community password
and just fuck around. Also might need to do the Me Strong stream. Yeah, I'm not done with it. I-
the game is too good to leave it completely. Oh, it's April Fools. I got nothing for you. I'm
too tired to have anything for you. Gotta do something weird. Here's the joke. Happy April
Fools, everybody. Beating the game tonight. I'm- I'm kidding. I'm kidding. It's a joke.
Look at my eyes. God, I look like- my face looks- I look weird. You beady eyes.
Stop. Do a tier list. Legit do it. I'm not- I can't. That was a joke. I'll see you later.
99 hours? I'm gonna go over 100. Come on. All right, good night. Thanks for watching, as always.
I'll see you guys later. See you on Sunday. Somewhere around four o'clock Pacific. We will
try to beat this game. Here's some of the other stuff that is in the game. And depending on how
long that takes, we will potentially go into some PvP stuff. Maybe I'll do some summoning stuff. If
you guys want to summon me to your game. You want to summon me, German985, to come and visit
your game. That's right. One of you lucky few will get German985 to come and enter your game.
Help me fight Milani- okay. Maybe we should just Mario Party Milania. It doesn't matter.
We Mario Partied the Dragon in Dark Souls 3, and I don't think we even beat it. I think I had three
or four of you guys come in, and we still couldn't do it. Do a hamburger helper tier list. I will be
very upset if you do that. That fight sucks. It's so bad. It's just too much. I definitely- okay,
before trying to do Milania, like really grind out the hours to eat Milania, I'm gonna have a
full breakfast. I'm gonna have to take some vitamins. I'm gonna need a full like eight hours
of sleep. I need to be ready. Do a From Software boss tier list. That actually sounds like fun,
although I don't really remember all that much of some of the other games. I would need some
refreshing, but that'd be fun. Well, thanks for taking the journey, as always. Have a good night,
and call your mother. See you guys soon. Not right now. Good night.