Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
Otto in the background again, making all kinds of weird noises. But anyways, gonna be playing
as the spy tonight, using the strange dead ringer, the Letronger and the Big Earner.
And in the title somewhere, it probably says, the live forever setup or something like that.
Let me just briefly explain what I mean by that. So the Big Earner, if you don't know,
when you backstab somebody, you get cloak. Same thing with the Letronger, if you shoot
somebody you get cloak, and the dead ringer lets you fake your death. So what happens,
what ends up happening in most of the gameplays you use this with, you will get a backstab,
fill up your cloak, be able to pull the dead ringer out, you're alive. You get out of
the dead ringer, somebody sees you, you can't backstab them, shoot them two or three times,
let the dead ringer rinse and repeat. Now this may or may not be total overkill, but
I like to use weird setups sometimes, like to mess around with the loadouts. And this
actually does work pretty well, because as a spy, I used to be a really good spy back
in the old days, back in like 2007. And then once all the loadout options came out, all
the variables came out, I started to lose my spy deal, I started to not really do as
well as I used to. So stuff like this, any way that I can help myself play spy better,
I'm going to try it out. I guess the real downside to using this setup is of course
if you have full cloak and you backstab somebody, you're not going to get any cloak added to
your bar there because there's no over cloak. Oh my god, I just thought of like a new item.
What if there was an item that gave you over cloak, like an over heel, like if you got
over heeled, you got over cloaked. Oh, maybe I'm just going off on a weird tangent there.
But anyways, playing on King of the Hill Harvest right now, and I got to tell you, playing
on King of the Hill maps, they're like really the only places I can play spy anymore. I
can't play on payload anymore, I can't play on control point, I seem to die instantly.
Right when I kill somebody, I always just die. I'll get one backstab die, get one backstab
die. But back in the day, back when this game was in its real infancy stages, I was really,
really good at the spy. And I think I know what's happening. What's happened is a lot
of the players that have played this game for a long time, and even some of the free
new players, everybody's just getting better at this game. So it is definitely, definitely
getting harder to fool people. Because it's the whole adage, fool me once, shame on me.
Fool me twice, shame on you. I said that wrong. Fool me once, shame on you. Fool me twice,
shame on me. There we go. I got it. But it's that old adage. It's, you know, you fool somebody
enough times, they're not going to get fooled anymore. And I think that's what's happening
in Team Fortress is, at least when I play spy, I feel like everybody knows exactly where
I am, where I'm going, and that sort of thing. And like I said, this can be totally attributed
to people just getting better at the game. And I love to see that, guys. I love to see
people getting really good at Team Fortress, because that means people are playing it.
You got to remember, to be able to be good at something, you have to really put time
into it. So to see these people all doing very, very well in a lot of the servers I
play on, it's great because it means Team Fortress is still alive and still running
And then they're going to tell their friends, once they're good enough, and once they know
how awesome the game is, they're going to tell their friends, their friends are going
to tell their friends, and Team Fortress hopefully will stay strong forever. And it's actually
getting a lot more attention than you'd think. A lot of the big YouTubers now, a lot of the
big commentators are starting to play Team Fortress. They're starting to get into it,
and they're starting to say, holy crap, this game is really fun. And they're going to start
making content on that. So stay tuned, but you're probably going to see a lot more Team
Fortress pop up in the YouTube scene in the very near future. That's my German prediction.
So I got to tell you one more thing before this video. There's only like another minute
or two in this video. Can I tell you my addiction lately? I mean, really, I've been so addicted
to a television show, the last week or so, I've watched every single episode and I can't
wait to see the movie now. In my Q&A a long time ago, I talked about Fullmetal Alchemist
and how I watched it. Not really a big anime person, but I did get into it and I did love
it. So I found out recently that they made a new one. They made a new Fullmetal Alchemist
Brotherhood. And I couldn't believe it. I was like, oh my God. And I actually remember
reading some comments on that Q&A video of people saying, you should watch the new FMA.
You should watch the new FMA. And I was like, what are you talking about? I remember looking
up stuff on it. And it looked like it was the same thing. I was like, did they just
remake this? But no, no, my God, it's a totally different story. It totally follows the comments
or the manga, I think is what it's called. And it is amazing. I got to tell you, if you
are an anime fan or you like anime at all, go watch Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood.
It is really, really good. And when I say I, I mean we, me and Burger Boy have watched
every single episode. And we've also trying to get tickets to go to the movie in Boston.
I think it opens April 12th or something like that. So that should be fun. And that's just
I've been totally addicted to lately. The characters, the story, everything is so good.
I think it's better than the first one. If you were a fan of the first one, watch the
second one and then tell me you don't like the second one more. And I guess a follow
up to this would be in the comment section, if you know any other animes that are really
good that I would enjoy, if I like Fullmetal Alchemist, leave me a comment of a different
anime I would like. And I'll tell you to preface that, to preface that, I'm not big into anime
and I don't really like the goofy type anime where everyone's always like screaming and
yelling and like laughing and stuff like that. I like the serious type of anime where, you know,
there's like blood and fight scenes and characters and stuff. I'm not a big fan of the, let's just
say like the Sailor Moon type anime. But yeah, that's going to wrap up this video guys. Thank
you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I will check you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.