Hello. How are you? I'll wait until you say good. Good. Good. Bad. Why? What's the best chat color?
Um, I'm more of a prehensical myself. That light kind of pale orange color.
Somebody said, uh, awful. That color sucks. That color's fine. Oh wait, wait, wait. Can you change
your color? Can you guys all make your colors orange? Wait, have I had the same color
for like five years on Twitch? I have, haven't I? I've only been this lime green forever.
I've never changed color. I thought that just meant I was the streamer. I think that I could,
how do I change it? I don't think I want to. It's been that lime green since I made this
account. What a revelation I'm getting right now. Now it's too recognizable. Yeah, I'm just the
green guy. How am I doing? I'm doing pretty good. I'm just hanging up. I forgot you could
change color. I didn't think you could. I don't know why, because people, I don't know,
I thought it was just, I thought it was every new account you could change color.
I don't know. How do I do it? I'm scared though, because I'm, okay, I'm clicking on
the chat. I'm scrolling around. I see emotes. Where's the change color button?
Chat settings. Edit appearance? I feel like it's going to crash my account.
I've been green for too long. Nah, okay, I know where it is. All right, that's fine.
Anyways, today we're going to do Dark Souls remastered, except not the regular Dark Souls
remastered. We're doing Dark Souls remastered randomizer. Got a lot of requests to do this
over the last few months or so, the last six months or so, people have really
been talking about this. This is going to randomize, and I can set the parameters. I have
it, I have it pretty basic right now. This is randomizing every item in the game. This
randomize every enemy in the game. I think I'm going to have random armor on and a random
enemy. I can also change it to be every single enemy can be one enemy, so I can actually just
fight. Well, I don't want to spoil it, because it's something I want to do. Dermot lied about
the clown car. He's going to be changing his name at some point over the summer,
but thank you for the five community subs. Appreciate it. All pinwheels. Well, don't ruin
the joke already. There's a couple of different playthroughs I want to do here.
I'm going to try... how hard do you think that would be to play through the whole game against
pinwheel? Every enemy, every boss is pinwheel. Do you think I could do that in two hours?
I kind of just have to run to the end, right? Anyways, it's ready. Hopefully the game
doesn't break, because I have random enemies and random items. They're going to keep
cloning themselves, so it's going to be kind of hard. Make every enemy a wheel skeleton.
Look, my goal here is to see if I can get to the first boss. How random? Everything is random.
Just to test it, I made it so bosses can't randomly just spawn in. Everything else is
completely random. I can change that, but I just wanted to see if this works, because I
didn't really want to test it because I didn't want to see it. We can go back and fix that.
There's a lot to do. But anyways, welcome everybody. Let's get started. I'm going to do new game.
Already have stuff. What do I have? What is that? Oh, it's best shield in the game?
All right. I don't even know what this stuff is. You're in the chef costume. Brand... oh yeah,
random name. Right, yeah, random name. That's true. What am I thinking? I can't do this shit.
Random name. Is there a name generator online? Random name generator. There has to be one of
these. Random name generator. This website can suggest names for babies. Why would you
fucking have a random website generate your baby's name? Okay, I'm just going to do
generate name. First, first name only. A masculine first name. Random. Generate a life story.
What the fuck is this website? I can generate a life story? Okay, I'm going for it. Okay,
so I've got, uh, Waldemar Manfredi, masculine, elderly, adult, nationality, German, from Bavaria,
aged 84, physical, 5'9", right-handed, blood O-type, and is gonna die by heart disease
in less than like six years. This character's like dead. All right, Waldemar Manfredi.
Okay, uh, class, uh, randomized. Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
what's going on here? What? Oh, it's, oh yeah, it's random. The bandit? What is that? I don't
think I've ever even seen that item in the game. Two swords? There's another giant hammer?
I mean, look at that bandit hammer though. I'm going for bandit. Gift.
Binoculars. No, no, no, this is important. Uh, fire bomb. Physique. I feel like, is that
random? Tiny head. Just make him a pear. I kind of like the pear. Face. All right, here we go.
We have to do random, right? Is there a way I can just do random? All right, I just took a
picture of my face every day for 10 years. That's just one of these YouTube videos. I
didn't have it on different. Oh, wait, wait. Oops. I don't know when to stop. All right,
I'm going to do 30 more times. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30. No, I already had a blue person. I
had a blue character before. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11,
12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30.
This is a sunburned dad. No, that's fine. That's good to me. Yeah, that looks good to
me. I'm ready. I'm ready to test it. You ready for the test? Start the game with this
character. Here we go. It's going to be loud. You can't turn down cutscenes. Turn your volume
down. You guys have seen this cutscene a fucking hundred times. What is that?
It's a bush. Who's in there?
And in this land, the undead are caught.
Are those crystal lizards? Here I am. So what is this weapon?
This is your fate.
Okay, I would have laughed so hard if that randomized that rat or something.
I can't remember how to play this game. It's been a long time.
Thank you. Look at that beef jerky. Slim Jim. All right, here we go.
Dungeon cell key. I thought it was supposed to be random items.
It's okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. What is that? What is that? Sif?
This is too much. I thought I made it so it couldn't do this.
Just give me my weapon. Wait, that's a boss. Oh, oh, right. That's the asylum demon.
I'm so confused. Oh, it's just. Look at how laggy this is.
How am I going to be able to beat Sif at level zero? Does he still come to the same place?
Where is he? Oh, what? Can he not come down? Do I have a bow and arrow?
Hold on. I think I can get him. Can I get him from the other side?
Because the asylum demon jumps down, I guess. Go for the egg thing.
Oh my god. Hold on. Those things are late game, aren't they?
I can't even equip my thing yet. Okay, hold on.
These things are easy. I don't remember. Blacksmith giant hammer.
I gotta put that on right now. Hold on. Insufficient strength to wield this.
This thing sucks. Why did you guys tell me to get this?
Give me the Estus. Is it actually good? Okay, thanks.
Take this off. I'm not even going to use it. All right, so hold on.
Let me see the stats here. I have to go actually into my equipment.
Do I? No. 237. That's actually pretty good. Minus 83.
I need 16 strength to hold it in one hand.
That's like mankind off the fucking top of the cage.
Somebody's dead. How the hell are you a normal enemy?
Actually, is this an electric divide? The shield is actually good.
Keep the shield on. Is it? Oh, it's the grass crest shield.
Yeah, right. Why is it? Okay, cool. This is the stamina one.
I forgot about this thing. Oh, Jesus Christ.
I gotta fight the Capra demon up here? That's not gonna happen.
I have to reload this and redo the randomization.
I fucking hate fat rolling. Drink something quick.
I can't even fucking move. I'm taking off all my armor.
I can kill this guy. Let's go. I got this.
Now that I can actually maneuver around. Let's go.
What? All right, let's go Capra. Firebomb.
I feel like these should all be randomized too.
I think the whole thing should be. All right, let's go Capra demon.
Where'd he go? Where the hell is he?
Where did the Capra... Am I losing my mind?
Where the fuck did he go?
You pre-recorded stream not wearing hat.
All right, settle down. 389 damage.
There's another rat in here. This is doing so much damage.
I think the asylum is toned down so you can actually get out.
But can I get out? What?
Oh, what? I thought it was Sif.
What is happening? I'm so confused right now.
Stop doing the same move. He's dead.
All right, wait. Sif was the other one.
All right, for the one that you can fall down.
Right, right, right. Okay. Nice.
This thing is pretty good. This is so stupid.
And you've doubted us. I don't know why. Why would I ever doubt you guys?
I really hope it's like Gwyn flying over here to pick me up.
No, that's too bad.
How long am I gonna do this for?
Until I get to a point where it is no longer feasible.
And then I'm gonna go absolute psycho mode.
This is essentially just the test to make sure it's possible.
And then we do it again.
You're gonna get over-encumbered in 10 minutes.
No, I'll be all right.
Tiny being's ring. What's the tiny being's ring?
I'll take it. Let's go. I'm ready.
Let's go fight the gold guy.
This is like a storyline DLC guy, isn't it?
1500. Guys, if we get some...
Oh, Jesus Christ.
It's the phone column.
Oh, wait. Will he fall off the edge?
He's stupid, right? He's too big to be over here.
He'll fall off if he swings this way.
Oh, great. They're all just single file coming down this way.
Oh, Jesus.
Watch out for the mushroom. Watch out for the mushroom. Watch out.
Slowly the phone column is making its way over here.
God. And you wonder why I didn't turn bosses on initially.
This is hell.
Holy shit. I thought I just got one punched.
That was really close.
It's like that was a...
I wouldn't have paid for that pay-per-view.
I would have wanted my money back.
Okay, we're fine.
Got it.
I'm just gonna go level up again.
Why wouldn't I? Just wait.
Oh, gold pine risen.
Nice. All right, hold on.
Just a shit... an absolute shit lot of vitality.
All right, I'm taking on the fucking golden guy up here.
They will respawn.
That's right.
I forgot.
I forgot what game I was playing.
Oh, god damn it, man.
Like that... this is gonna be impossible.
I'm gonna have to just run.
A hundred and eleven.
Bye.
What the fuck?
What is that?
Hold on. Every item is randomized, so I have to try to get them.
Hello?
You can't... you cannot come over here, can you?
There's no way he can come over here.
Do I not get...
Okay, I was gonna say, do I not get the souls?
Miracle great heal and twin humanities.
What's the other ring that I just picked up?
Boost curse resistance.
Just put it on.
Might as well just have it on.
All right.
This is the safe zone here.
Okay.
I... I forgot that it's not left button.
It's not... hold on.
Just listen to me.
You have to... you have to tap dodge again.
I was clicking in left stick.
It doesn't matter.
I'll be fine.
He dropped an item down there, though.
I don't care.
Fuck it.
What am I gonna go?
Collect all that shit?
No.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Dragon scale and a sorcerer's catalyst.
Okay, hold on.
The items... I have to pick them up.
Chester's long coat.
Hold on.
Damn.
I'll put this on.
It's mid roll, sorry.
That's not gonna do anything.
I can't even cross the bridge.
I just gotta run.
There's no way you're gonna be able to do that.
You have to run.
You gotta get to...
Killing one of these things is 5,000 souls.
Out of my way.
Just run to the bonfire.
I should be fine.
I gotta maneuver my way.
Maybe go up top?
You motherfucker.
Oh, you dick.
How did you...
Why would you even be coming down here?
I have to kill him.
Just let him despawn.
Let him go all the way back.
Just go back.
This is the remastered version.
Lose you that of curious.
Got it.
Alright, I'm fine.
Alright, good.
What?
Who?
I don't know what that was.
I don't know what's in the wall.
It's a giant rat.
I got...
No, dude.
You can't.
This is just...
This is comedy only.
Because how am I gonna be able to fight Yhorm?
Whatever his name is.
This is...
That...
It's in the way.
Oh, god.
Okay, I'm good.
I gotta go...
Just get to the bonfire.
I'm gonna go get him.
It's my turn now.
I just wish he's blobbing in the way.
I can't get by this.
Is there a sec...
Is there another way I can go?
Can I jump off the fucking side?
Oh, how did you get by?
What?
How did the fat guy get by?
Relentless.
They're fucking relentless.
Alright.
I'm gonna...
I think I can run around.
I'm gonna try to run around them.
I'm pretty sure I can get around that phalanx thing.
Whatever it is.
Just go up to the catacombs.
You know, that's not a bad idea.
I could also hold on.
I could also go down too.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Let me go through the graveyard.
Is he gonna die?
Alright.
Can I go up here?
I'm trying to remember Dark Souls.
I remember this guy.
And then I remember...
There's an elevator up here.
So I can't do this yet.
I don't think, right?
No, I need to activate the elevator.
Check for the items.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
There's items and shit.
Well, that's Astora's straight sword.
Isn't that thing one of the best...
That's one of the best short swords in the game, isn't it?
Well, I'm gonna work towards that.
I'll keep on the hammer for now.
Alright.
Now I can go down.
What's the thing?
Where is he?
You can go down.
There's like a...
There's a couple of chests, right?
Over here.
It's not good in Dark Souls 1.
Guardian soul.
And the hammer of Vamos.
Really?
Should I just get fucking like 20,000 souls?
Let me see that hammer.
C scaling and strength.
And it's a one-handed hammer.
So this is better.
Is it worse?
With better strength though, wouldn't it be?
Oh, what?
You're right.
It is worse.
Dark hand and crystal greatsword.
This is so overwhelming.
Should I just use the crystal greatsword?
That doesn't break, don't they?
Dark hand?
What?
This is 200 damage?
I'm gonna try it.
I didn't want this in my chest, right?
No.
There's one over here.
Well, there it is, guys.
There it is.
You got what you wanted.
Come on, get it.
Oh, I don't know if I want to use this thing.
I need to parry you.
That's it?
25?
No, no, no, no.
He's dead.
The dark hand.
This thing's actually pretty good for a parry.
I'm gonna drop.
Why does he not do anything?
I'm still confused at what that does.
Why is there a house cat over here?
Is that just a scaled up house cat?
Oh my god.
That was fucking scary.
It's just dogs and cats.
They don't even attack.
He's not even gonna attack.
Don't even tell me he's gonna throw that ball.
What is he doing?
He's just placing balls.
Is there a hole?
I don't see a hole there.
He's just dropping them.
Don't hurt the cat.
You said free souls.
What?
I need the soul.
All right, fine.
Look, I'll cast an energy spell to heal.
I'll get this role playing heal spell.
What?
Hey, easy.
Easy.
Slow down.
Go this way.
Move this way.
No, move.
Is that an NPC?
Oh, it's a painted guardian, right?
What is sprinting over here?
It's one of...
I'm back.
It's me, the kitty.
Oh shit.
He's getting closer.
I gotta move.
Can this not...
I can't hurt this, right?
Listen.
Oh, that's what that sound is.
All right.
I need to get in there though.
This is so dumb.
Okay.
So I got dingy gloves.
Purple moss clump.
Really?
I can't really help you.
You're locked in here.
There's nowhere for you to really go.
Don't push me off the fucking edge, you punk.
If one of us is going, it's going to be you.
Oh.
Move.
Just fall off.
It's not going to move.
There it goes.
I actually can't get out of here.
No, there we go.
Okay.
Now let's...
Don't...
Did you even think about it?
Okay.
I want to go investigate the guy dropping the rocks.
This is really important.
Wait, I can't pick up the...
Does he fight?
I thought he just drops rocks.
I don't think he fights.
I think his AI is only to pick up and drop rocks.
Free souls.
He's friendly.
Sorry.
He was doing the equivalent of gardening.
But that's like 10,000 souls.
Yeah, that's a lot.
Red titanite chunk too.
Shit.
Is it two black knights?
I got to go level up.
Just take the items and run.
Oh, just get one.
Just get one.
I'm not going to...
I won't live.
This is the Uchi Katana.
No, not worth it.
Go.
Get out.
All right.
Time to level up.
I could go down.
No, it's too risky.
I have 10,000 souls.
I'll kill the...
I could...
Hold on.
Let me take care of this.
It's that one person said no balls and I had to prove them wrong.
What did he just throw out of me?
No item?
This guy's gonna take a lot more.
He's got a big mind up.
This is gonna take a while.
Leave him alone.
Well, he's attacking me.
He's trying to kill me.
I'm gonna get killed.
Dammit.
I thought I could get the third one.
Oh god.
Fuck him.
I don't even care.
No, he's almost halfway.
He's gonna hit him once.
Got it.
All right.
That guy sucked.
No items.
Why?
I need items.
Now leave.
Not yet.
I want to get to a boss.
The closest boss is the...
The Taurus Demon.
Now there's a bonfire down there but I ain't gonna do it.
Just pinwheel.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna level up and I'm gonna go get Taurus Demon.
That's safe.
That's a safe play.
You're right.
Guys, it's not even gonna be pinwheel.
Don't you understand?
It's gonna be a different person.
Yeah, I am afraid of pinwheel
because he's gonna get randomly rolled into like three Gwyns.
Painted cardian robes.
Let's go.
It's so funny how it just starts hanging.
Use the docket.
Well, now you have to die.
They take up so much space.
What should I even be stacking here?
Just health?
All right.
Let's get some more endurance.
Just a shitload of strength.
More.
Okay.
I'm going.
Here we go.
More.
I'm gonna get to Taurus Demon.
I need...
You know what?
Actually, 20-20 hindsight here.
I should stack in here.
I think I got punched in the back of the head
and it severed my spinal cord.
It's all right.
I'm fine with dying here.
Use the soul?
Yeah, I can.
I could.
Just use the...
You're right.
Yeah.
Use the guardian soul and get 12,000.
Sounds pretty good.
He leveled 23 already.
Didn't mean to do that.
I have another one.
It's all right.
Now I shouldn't just take a punch in the back of the head and die.
I need to get to the first fucking boss first
before we do anything else.
Well, I'm dead here.
I just jumped into that.
Oh, god damn it.
I'll be happy if I get past the first boss.
I wonder if I can randomize...
Is anybody familiar with this mod?
Know that if I can just turn the game off
and randomize it and play this game again,
do I have to skip?
Oh, and do I have to reload a new game?
Or does it just do it no matter what?
Okay, that's cool.
I just have to get to the bonfire.
Unless you change the seed, it's fine.
All right, that's cool.
Just a humanity in a randomized land.
You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, the rat, right?
All right, let's try this again.
I'm gonna get topped off
and I'm gonna go on the right side.
Holy shit.
I didn't even pick anything up.
I got hit so hard, I got an item out of me.
I dropped a loot for that guy.
You guys, come on.
Wait, he moved.
I don't know what triggered the move, but he moved.
I don't even know why I opened that door.
No, no, get out of the way.
Get out of the way.
No, please.
Oh, I can't touch it because they're in here.
I gotta get all these people.
No, fuck.
I got tripped up on the pot on the ground.
I'll get up there.
It was the stupid armor dog that blew that whole thing.
Thank you.
That was a pretty good jump you just did.
You just saved me.
Move arrow.
Is it time for me to puke?
No, not yet.
I'm doing all right.
The same shit's gonna happen again.
He's gonna be in the way.
I'm gonna have to try to shove the hammer.
Why?
I just alley-ooped myself onto his lance.
I might have to go down to the crypts.
I'll get stuck down there.
Yeah, but at least I might make a little bit of progress.
What if I just go down?
No, I have to eventually get up here.
All right, here we go.
I need to go right this way.
What?
Wow, what does it make any sense?
He hit me with the backswing.
I was the catcher behind him and he swung too hard and hit me.
Oh, come on.
I'll get it.
Look, this is the hard part.
The easy part is when the boss gets re-rolled as this pinwheel five times.
I'll laugh my ass off.
I'm not gonna get hit by it.
Not gonna get hit by it.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Told you.
All right.
I have the right idea.
Comes.
Get through.
Watch out.
I'm not gonna get hit by this.
Told you.
To the right.
I get stuck on the thing somehow.
In a second, I'm gonna have to wait for him to come over here.
Yeah, all right.
When he gets down here, I'm going, I gotta wrap around.
One, two, three.
Okay.
This is actually not terrible.
I'm invincible.
This is perfect.
Perfect.
Not perfect.
Very bad.
One v one.
All right.
This is the best attempt I'm gonna have here so far.
What does this thing do?
Does it just moan?
Or does it do anything?
I don't remember this enemy.
He tried.
Do you see that?
He tried to just lance me from all the way up.
All right.
He has a tongue that comes out.
He's not gonna be able to hit me with it.
I'm too tall.
I'm too short.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna be...
I'm just gonna stand here.
I'm way too small.
That guy's so desperate.
I have to get rid of him too.
No, I don't.
I just have to make it up there.
I think I should probably kill this thing though.
He's gonna be able to come down.
All right.
Drink.
Oh, the Estus ship.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna run.
All right.
Out of the way.
Out of the way please.
Oh my god.
Please get out of the way.
Where is he?
Just kill it.
I thought he was gonna keep moving backwards.
How hard is it to kill this?
Find out.
I don't know.
I'm not gonna fight it.
I'm gonna run and hit the boar
and then keep running around in a circle.
Do it.
Sit down.
I'm good.
So, uh, next step is to keep going
and to go kill the Taurus demon.
I'm gonna wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Use this.
Congratulations.
You made it through the first bonfire.
Yeah, I know, right?
I want more health and endurance.
Is my plan to keep not killing things?
I just killed a bunch of things.
I mean, it's kind of hard with what they're these.
All right.
Yeah, you're gonna put another one
of those right in front of there.
But this is hell.
This is actually hell.
I'm not gonna be able to do this.
This is fucking over.
Are you serious?
Hi, guys.
I could jump off, right?
It's these boars.
The boars are just blocking the path
and making it impossible.
I think I could get in there.
Let me try to jump down.
Wait, hold on.
Let me see if I can just.
As long as I get in.
All right, I'm in.
I don't even know where the dog came from.
It's like Minecraft.
Yeah, it is kind of like Minecraft.
When you.
Oh, my God.
Just climb up.
They can't get up.
Damn it.
I have to.
I have to kill them one by one.
That's the only way this is gonna happen.
Let's go.
Like that one.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Did you walk up here?
I hear something moving.
It's that.
I don't.
I have to take care of this thing.
Oh, you dick.
No, I'm gonna jump off.
Where's the jump?
Is it at the end of the bridge?
All right, I know where it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
Go's armor and bellowing dragon crest ring.
Are they going all the way around?
All of them.
That's how Dark Souls works, right?
Sorry, it's gonna take them a long time to get here.
Is there any items over here?
Do I hear a cookie bug?
All right.
It's just one of these little idiots.
Oh, you fell down.
Stupid.
Not as tough as your mother.
Are you?
Cyanide just gave 20 community subs.
Thank you, Cyanide, for your 20 community subs.
That's a shitload of money.
Thank you.
At some point, I gotta make a move here.
And I'm not gonna go for that chest right now.
I'll get it later.
This...
Oh, god, there's nobody.
There was nobody up there.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I'm kind of panicking.
I just gotta get up there to get to the...
Get to the Taurus Demon.
Taurus Demon, go.
That is not the Taurus Demon.
That...
I think...
I think he's just gonna fall off the edge.
Hello?
Wait a minute.
This is important.
The gaping dragon cannot fit up here.
These guys don't do anything, right?
They can't.
They're just spectators.
All right.
Good luck.
Is he gonna aggro?
He takes up the whole bridge.
If he goes down, he's gonna be on the whole bridge.
I can't do this.
Oh, he's on the...
His tin box is so big right here.
Is he aggro?
No!
No, he's gonna run, isn't he?
He runs, right?
I don't fucking remember.
Oh, shit.
Did he...
Did he go down?
Is he gonna run?
Oh, god.
Oh, no.
I'm dead.
Oh!
Do I have anything...
I'm gonna take a humanity.
Should I take a humanity?
Oh, god.
He's gonna run.
I am fucked.
I'm fucked.
Wait.
What?
Climb the ladder!
How did you get down here?
Yeah!
Oh, fucking god damn it.
Oh, and there goes the humanity.
Shit!
And now I'm all the way back here.
That sucks.
I think I missed.
I did.
I'll get it this time.
I thought he was gonna fall off the edge.
Don't worry.
I got this.
Let me be fair.
That's only like the third time I've ever actually done this jump in the five times
I've played through this game.
All right.
I'm not doing this right.
That's the sixth time I've attempted to do that jump in the five times I've played this game.
I didn't even know that existed until somebody told me to do it.
Just roll?
I thought I was supposed to jump.
I'm trying just to roll.
I'm trying to do it.
I can't do it.
How did I do this right the first two times?
I don't understand.
What am I doing different this time?
I don't understand what I'm doing different.
Fucking dicks.
Oh my god.
I have no idea why I can't do this.
Please stop.
I'm not doing this on purpose.
I'm trying to make the jump.
What is happening?
Why can't I do this?
My fucking god.
What am I doing wrong?
I'm about to turn the stream off.
I'm doing it.
I'm turning the stream off.
Gotta put my password in.
There it is.
Okay.
Countdown in about four or five hours.
The stream's gonna turn off.
I did it.
The countdown started in like six hours.
The stream's gonna turn off.
I, honest to god, have no fucking idea why I can't do this.
I did it like the first three times I tried it.
What am I doing wrong?
I'm just gonna run.
First of all, let me change the worst setting of any video game in history.
Hold on.
No, no.
No, what the fuck are you doing?
Oh, I am.
What is happening?
Just what the hell is going on?
It's because I'm using Switch.
Fuck you, game.
Unbelievable.
Back.
Save.
Changes.
Go.
Why is this?
Why can I not dab?
What?
Okay.
It's fixed.
I'm gonna try this last time.
I tried just to roll off.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm doing wrong.
I don't understand.
I really don't get it.
I'm just gonna go the normal way before I fucking freak out.
I tried just to roll off.
No, I'm going the fucking way.
I'm not taking the shortcut.
Let's go.
I made it.
These enemies.
Those things are so horrible here.
I swear to God.
I seriously sucks.
This jump is easy.
I don't know what I'm doing incorrect.
And plus I have like this asshole up my ass the whole time.
I can't line it up.
Just walk?
Just walk off.
Why can't I do this?
Oh my God.
I'm seriously.
I'm fucking getting so pissed off from this.
This is making me madder than the whole eight and a half fucking hours
of Mario Maker last night.
I tried to press B.
No, I'm getting caught.
I'm just gonna run.
Oh my God.
I'm gonna fucking lose my mind.
I'm just gonna run.
I'm gonna fucking lose it.
I'm not doing it anymore.
Why is that the thing that's got me so caught in fucking A?
This is such a shit roll too.
I have like all these fucking DLC enemies.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You did it.
Hey, you did it everybody.
Yeah, he's won.
I see you finally.
Why are you standing in the worst possible spot?
I couldn't fucking do it.
I promise.
I don't know what the hell is wrong.
I couldn't get it.
I tried.
All right, let's get the gaping dragon.
Thank you Pixel Mike for the five community subs.
I have to kill these guys up here
because last time the guy came down and caused a problem.
This guy made his way down somehow.
I don't know how the fuck he did it.
All right, if like shitty Ornstein and Smog kill me up here,
I'm gonna be so mad.
I'm gonna be so upset by this and I can already tell.
Why do you have so much health?
Is lightning resistant another problem?
All right, this is the attempt here.
I'm gonna try to just be careful.
I almost puked.
It was almost time to turn the stream off.
I seriously almost threw up.
All right, so let me put on something.
I'm not gonna put on like this dumb shit.
Am I still?
All right, what about?
I mean, it's a mid roll, but I don't want the mid roll.
Here we go.
Oh no, he really immediately.
Also, why do I keep jumping?
I thought I unbound that from B.
That's a hitbox still.
Cut the tail.
He's in such an awkward position.
Oh my God.
Don't do it.
He's too big.
Oh my God.
He's gonna go forward.
Stop running.
Stop running, please.
Oh shit.
Anyways, that...
Okay, hold on.
I know, gaping dragon, I'm not gonna make fun of you
because I know how hard it is to make it
from there to the platform down there.
I'm not gonna make fun of you.
And I know you were very close
to just turning off your stream.
And I think you actually did turn it off
because you're not still live anymore.
Missed the item, did I?
All right, what do you guys think?
It's time for a roll.
You want to roll it?
Let's try to get to one more boss
and I'm gonna roll it.
I'm not gonna kill him.
Why do you think I'm gonna kill...
All right, is it gonna be the...
Will it be the dragon?
Or is it gonna be somebody else?
No, why do you have to be here?
Oh, come on.
This is like the fourth one of these guys.
I'm coming here too.
Me too.
Let's go get him.
Does he breathe the fire?
Where is he?
Is he just not here?
Oh, he's up there.
It's...
Is it a gargoyle?
He's just stuck up there.
No, he's still in here.
I gotta go back.
I gotta go to the shortcut.
I had to just escape through one zone somewhere.
Is he...
I see the shadow.
He's still following me.
Is that a shadow?
Oh, he's still following me.
He's gonna fall off the edge though, I think.
He can't fit up here.
There's just a bigger rat in here.
No.
I have to knock that shortcut down.
Okay, I'm fine.
We're good.
Slide down.
All right.
Good.
Are these random?
I didn't choose anything.
You can't choose.
Hold B?
That's...
I thought that that's what I was trying to do.
All right, let's go back.
Okay, let's see what happens when we get up there.
I'm not going that way.
I'm going up.
Is he actually gonna breathe fire?
I don't think he's gonna breathe fire.
He just stuck in the wall.
He's just a decoration.
Cleric armor?
Can I...
Let it...
I let the fire.
This is fucking crazy.
You probably had to pick all these enemies.
No, it's all random.
You can go in and make every enemy the same enemy,
but you can't do random.
You can't place them anywhere.
You cannot place them.
Yeah, we are...
Once I want to see the next area.
Can you imagine if From Software games were actually like this?
Well, they are.
Scholar of the First Sins did this.
That's what that expansion was.
So they did...
They already did that.
And I thought I got through.
Okay.
This guy's like just trying to pretend he's not here.
He's trying to camouflage into the wall.
Hey, I'm not here.
I'm part of the decoration.
Jeremiah lied about the clown car.
Thanks for five community subs.
Thank you.
At least I'm safe here.
I love it.
It's so dumb.
You talk about immersion breaking.
It's that...
That's like...
This is comedy.
That's just a joke.
All right.
I need to...
I'll be safe as long as I get to the button.
I can't.
I'm gonna dash through here to the T.
Oh, I'm dead.
Well, the door's open.
So at least I can probably handle that now.
I want to throw...
I want to shoot the dragon up there.
3,000.
Who died?
Can he spawn at the bonfire?
I need the Lord Vessel, don't I?
Which I'm kind of just coming to a realization here.
I think the Lord Vessel is a random item now.
Hey!
What happened to his head?
Oh.
I can't go...
Those of you that wanted me to go the rat way.
I don't think it's gonna happen.
Maybe it is.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Okay.
Ring of the Sun Princess.
I gotta look at some of these rings.
Boost defense.
Well, boost sorcery.
Boost miracle synergy.
Well, none of these are really any good.
Here we go.
Undead Parish.
Slinky.
Demon...
Two Demon Titanite.
What?
Wait a minute.
This is the...
That's the dragon.
You all right?
He's all right.
He'll be fine.
I want to see if I can spawn that dragon.
I want to see if I can kill the dragon.
I'm gonna throw like a fire bomb at the dragon.
Let me see if I can get him to be back here.
Can I just farm Demon Titanite?
I probably can.
Yeah, I can just...
I can farm this bro.
Now, who's up here?
There's usually a Black Knight up here.
What is it now?
Ring.
And there it is.
The best ring in the game.
I will definitely take that, sure.
Thank you.
What rings you got?
I favor protection.
The unstoppable.
All right.
Let's go.
Deal with this idiot.
He threw his weapon.
Doesn't have one anymore.
That didn't hit.
Oh.
I got such a shit seed here.
I think the reroll happens at Capra Demon.
Because if Capra Demon...
Hold on.
No.
Bye.
I'm just gonna run through the...
I'm just running straight through.
If I even get there, yeah.
That's another thing.
If I can even go there.
Let's see.
I also...
I need Estes Chunks.
Well, thankfully the boar is not here.
There's just a couple of little enemies.
Okay, what have we got?
Gauntlets of the Vanquisher.
I gotta clear this.
I can't bring these guys all up here.
I mean, will it...
Hold on.
Thank god.
I think that's just a regular skeleton that just came on.
That's the first regular skeleton I think we've seen.
You're too big to fit in there.
Yeah.
So I'm safe here.
What is this?
That's another pig.
How did...
How did you get up here?
What is that?
I think he's stuck.
He can't move.
This, like, elephant thing can't move.
I can kill it.
Eldritch Horror.
His audio isn't even working.
That's the kind of enemy I feel like will crash the game.
All right, let's keep going.
There's more of these.
Say horror, horror.
Horror.
I am in so much trouble.
I'm in so much trouble.
Don't come all the way down.
Back up.
Please back up.
You can actually fit down here.
Look at the top of the church to see the boss.
Hold on.
Nice fucking superhero anime move.
I think I can go by.
I was raided by Robaz.
Welcome everybody from Robaz's channel.
Hope Robaz...
Hope you had a good stream.
Welcome.
We're doing Dark Souls Meltdown stream.
Where...
I almost just rolled off the edge.
But this is randomizer.
Everything's randomized.
As per the name.
That means all enemies, all items.
Everything has been randomized.
And there is an Estus thing right here.
Unless it's random, which...
Yeah, I...
That...
It's all random.
I'm not gonna be able to get the Lord Vessel.
I'm gonna have five Estus Flasks the whole game.
The Lord Vessel isn't random or isn't the Estus Flasks shards not random either?
I'm gonna be screwed.
But welcome everybody from Robaz's channel.
Thanks for joining us.
If you want to stick around, there's plenty to see.
If not, then have a nice rest of your night.
And happy 4th of July soon.
Oh yeah, this doesn't have shards.
It has the Firekeeper Souls though.
The shops are also random?
That's so stupid.
All right, let's take inventory here.
I'll keep the grass shield on.
I don't...
This is good, but I don't want to use it until I need to.
I forgot, yeah, you kindle the fire.
I remember that, yeah.
All right, let's see what he got.
Let's see what he got.
What do we have for miracles?
Not very holy of you.
You got Havel's Helm and Crimson Robe.
How much is that?
Five thousand?
Free Souls?
Wait, hold on.
Oh, I thought I could buy them as many times as I wanted to.
All right, bye.
I'll come back with money.
Let's go see...
So here's my question.
The gargoyles...
Is both gargoyles considered one entity?
Or are two gargoyles going to have two different bosses here?
This is going to be horrible.
This might be the end where we have to re-roll.
Because I don't foresee this being...
What's that word again?
Oh yeah, possible.
But I've done the impossible before.
I almost...
I took like 20 to 30 attempts to jump over that bridge thing.
So, you know, anything's possible.
All right, let's go.
Thankfully, it's just a dog.
Usually it's a guy with a sword and shield.
Let's play this safe.
Wait, aren't there like 300 people in this room?
Am I even going to be able to get up the stairs?
And it's all huge, huge enemies that are so hard to beat.
I don't know how to do this.
I'm going to have to just get the throw.
He got in, he got in.
They got in, they got in, they got in, they got in.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, they're going to flood in here.
Oh god, no.
Okay.
My only option, I think, is to pull them all down here.
So then it's a bigger space and then I can run by them.
You are stuck.
All right, how much health do you have?
Way too much.
There's no chance I'll be able to fight this thing.
I got to get you over here and then I got to run around.
Goodbye.
See you later.
I also have to go get the bonfire down by the blacksmith too.
Oh fuck.
Oh no, this is not good.
Very bad.
Is it not?
I can't believe I just got fucking hit right when I was about to swing at them.
I can't believe it.
They're too big.
What?
Where are they coming from?
Why did every single one of these rolled enemies
have to be five times larger than the space?
Oh my god, and there's another one of these crabs.
No, I thought he was stuck.
I thought he was stuck.
What was that teleport dash?
And Andrew, what's his name?
Andrew, I need your help, please.
He cannot get down here.
There's no way it's possible.
He's not going to make it down here.
Get the bonfire right here.
Let's go see what he has for us.
By the way, let's just check what this usually is the thunder god.
It's just kind of a regular enemy here.
No, it's not.
It's one of these guys.
These guys are awful.
There we go.
Scratch that.
Easy.
A falchion.
All right.
Hello, Andrew.
Andre.
Humanity.
Large soul.
Homeward bone.
Velka's rapier.
Barb straight sword.
Spiked shield.
Leather boots.
Maiden gloves.
Hat.
Well, I can't none of these.
You can buy infinite souls this time.
Can I?
Well, I guess God lied to.
All right.
Let's try to make it back up there to the gargoyles.
And I'm gonna I'm gonna tune this one too.
This is a pretty central bonfire in my opinion.
Because the uh later on you have sends right there.
I don't have any humanity.
All right.
You have to actually use it.
Invades incoming.
I'm offline.
I'm gonna get this to 15.
Oh, you can't get this one to 15.
Right.
It's all right.
All right.
Cool.
Here we go.
I don't have the right of kindling.
Right.
I'm gonna make it up there and it's time to go.
You can see my bum.
You really can.
This is very revealing.
I'm gonna go quick.
You take up that much space.
I'm shocked.
It's not no way.
I have to re-roll this.
Just let it on my neck.
I have to pull them down.
They have to fall off.
And then I gotta climb the ladder.
I'm not gonna be able to get the ladder in that time.
No way.
The gargoyles are right up there though.
I need to get up there.
I'll get up there.
Everybody's so huge.
Just make a giant blockade.
Okay.
I'm not even hurting this dude.
Diagro.
Come on.
I just brought the other guy over.
Just reset them.
Reset them.
Just kill me.
Damn it.
Can I re-roll while the game is open?
No.
That would probably be a very bad idea, right?
I'll try this one more time.
Because he's in the spot right now where he's very easily just block the door.
Hey, he's gonna block it every time.
There we go.
I made it.
All right, come on.
I'm...
Forget about the dog.
I'm going right up.
No!
All right.
I have to do this tactically.
How do I tactically take care of this?
All right.
Now they have to all fall down.
So here we go.
Ready?
Now they're all looking at me.
Now get them to all fall down.
Come on, all of you.
The whole entire trip of you come down.
Come on, please.
All right, go.
I don't think there's anything...
You motherfucker.
You're the only one.
You gotta be kidding me.
That was the one, too.
I have to pull them all down that little hallway.
They'll...
Sorry.
I'm good.
I'll get it.
I'm just gonna walk straight through his legs.
He'll do that every time.
All right.
Here we go.
Agro.
Everybody.
Here they all come.
Hey, look at me.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're all very, very cool.
Here we go.
There's you.
I have to wait till that weird blob,
amorphous, weird thing falls down, too.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
There it is.
They're all down.
Nothing is gonna block the way now.
There's gonna be a slug right here.
No.
Good.
Go.
Oh, Jesus.
All right.
I made it.
Here we go.
Did the gargoyle...
Is that a gargoyle up in the top left?
Is this a skeleton?
What?
No.
What is that?
I don't know what I'm looking at here.
He's being pulled through a fucking black hole.
Wait.
What do you mean bell gargoyle?
Is there gonna be a...
Shit.
Ow.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
No.
Oh, I didn't dodge it.
I'm bad.
I'm in trouble.
He's fucked up.
His AI is fucked up.
No, it's not.
Off the edge.
Back up.
Quick.
Wait, he can fly.
I don't think...
I don't think that's possible.
Use the dark hand?
Reroll.
All right.
Let's reroll.
We're gonna reroll it.
Here we go.
Wait, hold on.
Should I put the crystal sword on?
It's gonna spawn another boss.
Go down to...
All right.
I could go down.
Yeah.
Let's do...
I'll do dark root.
I'll try dark root.
I'm allowed to reroll once an hour.
Yeah.
Can I upgrade the hammer?
What does it take?
I can.
What is it?
Twinkling titanite, unfortunately.
I'll try...
Here's the thing about the butterfly.
This could be a very, very good thing.
Because the butterfly might just spawn in the air
when I go through the bonfire
and just fall and die.
If it's not the butterfly.
So it might actually be a pretty good idea.
Thanks for the easy enemy.
I really appreciate that.
What the hell was that?
It's dead, whatever it was.
Yeah, this is our remastered.
That is the best T-pose I've ever seen.
Ow.
It's marvelous.
What am I stuck on?
How?
No!
Don't die here.
I don't know what it is.
I've always had trouble with these snakes.
For some weird reason.
I don't know what it is.
Like, I don't know what it is,
but I don't know what it is,
but I don't know what it is.
All right, let's go butterfly.
I just have to get through here.
Don't forget about the secret.
Don't forget about the bonfire that's right here.
You never played Dark Souls before.
It's right there.
Am I gonna be able to...
I can't get that open ever.
Moonlight Robe and Red Sign Soapstone.
Well, at least I can invade somebody now.
Let's go.
Now, if I remember that there's
like six or seven enemies over here,
and they're all crabs and shit.
Why does it have to be crabs?
Thankfully, they're not getting up.
Homeward Bone.
Key to the Seal.
Do I get to skip Light Town?
Wait a minute.
Key to the floodgates of New Londo,
which seal away the Four Kings.
Oh, it's the Four Kings.
That's so stupid.
Will they aggro?
I don't want to fight these guys.
I'm just gonna go around the edge.
I'm putting up with this.
Giant Rat?
Just a regular rat, actually.
Is there something back here?
You need to get every single item.
One of them is going to be the Lord Vessel.
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
I think I have it set that key items
are not...
T-Pussing Dragon is so stupid.
He's just doing a plane impression.
Oh my god!
Why did they all come to life instantly?
Well, at least I got the item.
Oh, a golden legend.
Get out of here.
No, no, no.
Hold on.
Isn't this shit down here?
There's like three to four items.
Yeah.
I hope one of them is the Lord Vessel.
I would laugh my ass off.
Oh, no.
Don't do it, Jeremy.
No, that's not what's gonna get you killed.
It's not that.
It's the enemies.
Oh, I'm in trouble now.
Oh, I've really done it now.
Crystal Shield, Shortbow.
Fuck, these guys are horrible.
I remember they're in the depths, right?
The catacombs with that pitch black place.
Nothing else.
Get up back up.
I don't even care.
Tomb of the Giant, not the catacombs, though.
I knew it was one of them.
Whatever the one is that is all dark.
Missed item.
It's too dangerous down there right now.
It could be the Lord Vessel.
This is gonna be the Lord Vessel.
What the fuck?
All right, got that item.
All right, now I just gotta go this way
and then we gotta fight the butterfly.
Let's see what it's gonna be.
I'm thinking the butterfly is gonna be...
What do you get?
Place your bets.
Who do you think?
It's gonna be Gwyn.
Whoever it is, they're gonna fall right to their death.
Here we go.
It's Ornstein.
Ornstein.
And he is so huge.
I don't...
He needs to fall off.
He's not dead?
What do you mean he's not dead?
How is he still alive?
He fell off the edge, but he was so big
that the fall damage didn't kill him.
Just menu him.
Hold on.
Not yet.
I may be able to get him to walk off.
I don't even see him.
No, I'm just gonna reload
and he'll probably die, right?
All right, here we go.
No, it just resets the area.
Where am I?
I...
He died to moonlit butterfly.
I gotta get him to fall off
to where there's no ground
and it's that side that he's on.
I'll get there, hold on.
All right, let's try this again.
I have to get him to fall off up here.
Over this way, come here.
You're gonna fall off here.
Can I just kill him?
He doesn't have that much health, does he?
Fall.
Fall that way.
He's got a dickload of health.
What am I talking about?
There he goes.
All right, dead.
No, it has to be over here.
This room is not programmed to kill bosses who fall.
Yeah, that's right
because there is no way to fall.
Falling is not possible.
Optional, so it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna try to fight him.
Here's the problem about fighting him.
I might actually get him down to halfway
and he'll fall off.
It's gonna take forever.
Shit!
Just wait.
I don't think it's gonna happen.
Wait, wait, wait.
Just wait.
You sounded like a crosswalk.
Wait.
I'm getting baited.
Reroll.
Time to reroll.
It's reroll time.
I think we're locked.
Here we go.
It's time to reroll.
Wait.
All right, I'm gonna do it.
This time I'm gonna make it.
We're gonna up the ante a little bit here.
So this time, let's see.
Let's do...
I can have it be replace bosses with only bosses
with normal enemies or with bosses or normal enemies.
Replace normal enemies with bosses or normal enemies.
Or, okay.
How about replace normal enemies with bosses?
Might have to reroll this one instantly.
Replace all normal enemies with bosses.
That's clown show though.
No, we're not there yet.
We aren't there yet.
Replace NPCs with bosses.
I think that's kind of fun.
All right.
Enemy placement anywhere.
Percentage for a boss to spawn.
Chance that a boss will be replaced with a boss
instead of a normal enemy.
I'm gonna put this at...
Let's put this at 50%.
100%.
No, that's too wild.
Let's do like 30%.
That's better.
All right, here we go.
I'm rolling it.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
Here it comes.
This is gonna...
Hold on.
Wait, I gotta do it again.
This is gonna be fucking nuts.
33% chance for a normal enemy to be boss.
We may or may not have to redo this again.
Because this...
And I'm not rerolling the items.
The items are still the same.
That's way too high.
We'll see.
It might not be.
Well, maybe we'll...
Maybe we'll get a good roll here.
All right, let's get back in.
Let's see who we rolled Orenstein into.
Now it's possible that Orenstein could be rolled into a skeleton.
And I'll kill him in one hit.
Every three monsters is a boss.
Kind of.
That's too high.
Well, it's all right.
Here we go.
I think it's a normal enemy.
Moonlit Butterfly is...
I think it's just like a chef.
That's the easiest boss in the game.
Pyromance.
The Acid Surge.
Purple Moss Clump.
And what?
I don't even know what I just picked up.
There was like five items here.
What did I just get?
Acid Surge.
Humanity.
Okay.
Nice.
All right.
Did you reroll items?
No, I did not.
I will not reroll items until it's very, very necessary.
And maybe when I reroll the items,
maybe we'll do it a few times and get something weird.
I don't know.
Hello Carving is what was up here.
And Helm of Thorns.
And Wolf Ring.
Hello.
What's that helmet?
Helm of Thorns.
Yeah, let's get it on.
All right.
Let's head back down and let's have the fun begin again.
Now I'm going to go try to do the gargoyles again
because it's going to be something different.
Use it.
No, I don't think so.
I don't want to.
No, no, no.
I don't think so.
Do it.
All right.
Fine.
Hello.
God.
That wasn't it?
That was an exact audio replication of that item.
Why is the rat so big now?
I didn't do anything to increase the rat's size.
Why is he huge?
This is kind of freaking me out.
He's enormous.
Okay.
Let's go back.
I want to do the gargoyles again.
I need to level up too.
I hope the gargoyle is a rat.
I hope the gargoyle is two hollows.
Are two hollows.
No, I'm not doing that.
All right.
Let's do strength.
Where are all the bosses?
See, I told you it was a decent number.
That means there's a 70% chance and it rolls every time.
70%, 70%, 70% that it's not going to be a boss.
This thing is freaky.
Got it.
Another one of those blobs.
Just avoid it.
I don't want anything to do with you.
Ow.
My back is so itchy.
Could you put Bart Simpson in with this mod?
I don't think so.
It has to.
No.
A secure randomizer.
I think that game may be not completable, but you can.
Let's upgrade the hammer.
Wait, I need twinkling titanite.
Never mind.
There's a mod for custom skins.
I feel like that would be so hard to implement.
Andre, you look a little...
Hi, Andre.
Speaking...
No, never mind.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't say it.
I know what everyone's going to say.
That's pretty good, though.
These didn't change.
There's a reference I can make here, but I'm not going to.
Uh-oh.
I have to re-roll.
I got to go through the Valley of the Drakes.
Yep.
I got to go around the whole thing.
Just kick him?
Does he stay like this forever?
He doesn't, right?
I just fucked up the whole game.
Wait, no, no, no.
I can remove sins.
That's right.
Okay.
Everything's going to be fine.
I just can't level up any items.
You have to beat the gargoyles to get them de-aggroed.
That's it.
I can do that.
What?
I don't understand.
Um, it's that...
How do they get them both as the demon?
10,000 souls for free.
Oh, look, a skeleton.
So scary.
I'm going to...
I got to go to this bonfire.
What?
Get it?
No, no, no.
I need...
I want this bonfire.
That was the centipede demon.
You're not changed.
That's kind of freaking me out.
Why are you still the same?
Did he roll into himself?
All right.
Now we're going to go back and it's this Capra demon.
That's fine.
Yeah, I'll get the secret items on the elevator.
Not a bad idea.
How high up is it?
Is this the first cliff or the second cliff?
I think it's the second cliff, right?
There's two ways to go, right?
Or this is just the first cliff.
Yeah, it's that first one.
When you walk up the tree, you go to the bird.
There is only one, right?
I'm like combining every game I've played from From Software.
Okay, so I got those.
Isn't there...
Yeah, there's those up there.
How do I get up there?
Can I even get up there?
Wait, I already got those.
How do I get across there?
Oh yeah, you jump, right?
Now you jump to one of these.
Now you jump from here.
Whoops.
I was trying to...
I got fucking locked.
Yeah, you jump from the grass part.
It's been a while.
I got stuck down there.
Now you get AI?
All of a sudden, the first time in two and a half hours,
the armored pigs have artificial intelligence now.
It took you 10 of those for you to do anything.
Well, let's do this again.
This is my first Dark Souls experience.
This game looks fun, but hard.
Yeah, it is.
It is pretty hard, especially considering
when they do this, all the random bosses that spawn.
It's like weird that they put that in the game.
Oh yeah, so jump from here to there, right?
Yeah, right here.
I'm so awful at this kind of shit.
I got it.
All right, there's items.
Is there one over here?
Up there.
Actually, I have to fall from there, don't I?
Anything in the nest?
Mimics?
I'm not even sure Mimics spawn.
I don't think it can.
Isn't it impossible?
Master key.
What does the...
Open any basic lock.
Oh, right.
Cool.
Is there anything else up here?
Whoa, don't fall off.
It's slipping me off into the nest.
Is there an item in the nest?
Wasn't I just up there?
I'm going to fucking fall off here.
Yep, bye.
Whatever.
All right, I'm going forward.
Hello?
That fucking hurt my face.
My chest hurts.
I just did not expect that at all.
Okay, he's dead.
I'm sorry about that loud noise.
That was fucking terrifying.
All right, I'm going back to the tower to go to the gargoyles.
He was silent.
It was completely...
There was no sound at all.
It was silent.
That was so quiet.
Use the nest, go back to the undead asylum.
Yeah, we can do that.
I want to do this first, though.
Because then...
Well, it was sift before.
Now who knows what hell it is now.
It's my birthday.
Can you say what's up, sinners?
What's going on, sinners?
Happy birthday.
I don't know why I just even did that.
This is going to be horrible getting up here.
Oh no, a slug.
Thank God it's not a boss.
Okay.
We got to do the same thing again.
We got to pull everybody down.
Oh, hey, guess what?
The demon just jumped off a cliff somewhere.
Come on, everybody.
Holy shit, that reach went through the whole cathedral.
Oh, come on.
Let's try this again.
Unbelievable.
Well, now I know he can reach me from wherever he's standing.
Click on the link.
Link, link, link.
What is this just going up?
I will get to these gargoyles.
It's going to happen.
Reroll, but make everything a skeleton.
I mean, once I get sick of doing this,
we're going to throw all the dice in the air.
I'm talking every enemy pinwheel.
I'm talking only giant rats.
Like, only rats run through.
See if I can beat the game against all rats.
All right, I got to make...
I need to pull.
There we go.
Come on down.
I think I got the guy that was the...
Okay, Ornstein's down.
They're both down.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, man.
Not good.
You got to be kidding me.
This is bad.
No, I'm fucked.
I have to kill stuff.
I can't just run through this.
When people come down, they have to die.
I got to go up the stairs first,
kill the two things that are there,
and then aggro everybody down.
Every single enemy is Artorias.
Can do that.
Oh, that's a sign.
It's time for rat-only mode.
Not yet.
Okay.
Quickly go up here.
Take out these two enemies.
And when I say quickly, I mean do it quickly.
This guy...
Stupid long arms.
All right.
Now I have a straight shot.
Pull everybody down.
Watch out for this demon.
Everybody come down.
Come on.
I need Ornstein.
And there we go.
All right.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You too.
I need you too.
You too, you too.
The big guy had to go down too.
I don't think he did.
No, I'm in trouble.
Oh, no.
This guy is attached to me.
They all have to come down.
All of them.
Otherwise, I can't even physically walk through the door.
It's just that stupid demon outside
that can just sweep and hit me from anywhere in the cathedral.
Do I have skulls?
I do not have any skulls, I don't think.
All items are randomized as well.
So I don't think I even have one.
Check new Londo?
Yeah, that's true.
I'm going to give this one more attempt
and then I'm going to go the other way.
I'm going to go somewhere else.
Although, is there even another way I can go right now?
I'm going to pull the ones that I know I can kill
because I keep getting screwed by the rat.
The two long-armed people.
Yeah, see, this is what's causing a problem.
I would love to see.
All right, that clears out all the shitties.
I think I'm going to pull the other shitties through the wall here
because I think there's a couple that can still make it through.
There's a rat there.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
That just killed me instantly.
I thought I had the right idea.
Fuck.
Oh, it's so aggravating.
Damn it.
Why did they have to kill me in one hit?
Like, does it really have to kill you instantly?
Like, you just die?
That's the most amount of damage I possibly could have taken.
Yeah, I know.
It sucks.
I'm getting up there.
Stuff everybody into a door.
I just delete the dragon.
It's the dragon that's causing the problem.
There's the rat.
The dragon is making this so hellish.
If only he just wasn't in the way.
All right.
Well, I'm going to go for it.
It's important that they all come down.
One, two.
Where's Ornstein?
Come on.
Three.
I need the big guy, too.
Big guy.
Come on.
Go.
This is the one.
This is it.
I'm going to get up there.
Just watch out here.
This is probably going to be like a rat or two.
35,000 soul.
Oh, I don't know what's following me.
They're scaring the shit out of me.
All right, I'm fine.
Taurus demon time.
Not Taurus demon time.
Gargoyles.
All right, here we go.
Please be a default enemy.
I can handle this.
There's the guy in the back.
There's a guy standing in the back.
I could have done it, too.
Wow.
God.
It was the Taurus.
I was paying attention to the magician in the background.
I can do this.
It's going to be two Taurus demons.
Whatever.
Oh, I'm going to pee my pants, too.
Shit.
Whatever.
I have to get through this.
It's such a pain in the ass to get them all to follow.
Now, I need a weapon I can actually upgrade, too.
All in due time.
So many things are going to go wrong here.
You know what?
I don't care.
Just fucking come down now.
Let's go.
All of you.
Now, you're on the perfect spot.
One, two, three.
Come on.
Down, down, down, down, down.
All of you.
Everybody.
Down, down, down, down, down, down.
Good.
He just dragged across the whole game.
Oh, shit.
Don't be the wall here.
All right.
That was pretty clean.
Everything could always be better, but that was fine.
It's just a Taurus demon.
Oh, fuck.
The boogie man's coming to get me.
What?
Hold on.
Is that Gwyn?
It's actually Gwyn.
He's serious.
Just let me get it.
All right.
This is possible, but it's own.
I have to.
I have to kill the Taurus demon immediately.
I have to kill.
It's going to be like four or five swings.
He has to die immediately.
And then I have to just start parrying Gwyn.
Oh, go fuck up Gwyn first because he's T-posing.
That's very.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea either.
I hope I can kill him while he's standing there.
Come on.
Two, three, four, five.
Bring him down.
Good.
You have to be sitting in the door right here.
Could you be anywhere else?
I mean, and I'm talking anywhere.
I'm talking about fucking anywhere.
This is bad.
Oh, here the dragon is.
How did you fit in here?
There's no way you can even fit up here.
And yet you walked up the stairs normally, very casually.
I'm going to try this one more time.
That's it.
And then I'm going down to like the skeleton zone.
Here comes a meltdown.
No, you can't.
There's no such thing as a meltdown on a randomizer stream.
You can't melt down here.
None of this is in my control.
Two, three, there they go.
All right, let's go.
You had to leave that one.
How dare you?
The dragon's out coming up here.
I see him.
He's making a...
What?
How the fuck did you already get up here?
Get out of my fucking way.
No.
Why do they have to take up every space?
I have to go up there.
Just skip to Blighttown with the master key.
If you kill Gwyn, you beat the game.
I'm going to try to hammer him as much as I can.
Like just...
I'm going to go kill everything first.
And then I'm going to pull it.
I'm going to do it the way that I did it before.
Come on in.
Let's go.
Like turn the corner.
You can do the same dumb thing over and over again.
Okay.
Who's next?
There's a rat too.
Anybody else fit through there?
No.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
I need you to fall.
This is why I didn't...
This is why it doesn't work that well.
Slug?
I can skip the slug.
You punk.
You've got to be kidding me.
Why would you turn at that exact moment?
The exact moment that I needed to go through that door.
No.
No meltdowns.
I'm good.
I'm going to go straight through.
I'm going to try to kill Gwyn as fast as I can.
Wait.
Will he kill him?
I don't think he will.
Oh shit.
Don't activate him.
What?
What was that?
Okay.
Let's go back.
I'm trying to pull him as far away as I can.
Don't jump off the edge.
I don't want to fight him.
Cut off Gwyn's tail.
Gwyn is...
Hold on.
Is this actually hurting him though?
Kill the demon now.
He just killed him.
He killed him.
I didn't kill him.
Why can he not hurt me?
What?
Oh.
I...
I'm like flipping.
I can't.
Fuck.
I thought he couldn't hurt me.
He was like swinging.
Why am I parrying?
Because my brain wanted to...
I don't know.
I'm going down.
When he killed...
When he killed the Taurus demon,
it like freaked me out.
And then all of a sudden,
I get to fight the last boss in the game
on the fucking tower.
Let's go.
I'm going to go down here.
Idea.
Have the master key.
So why the hell wouldn't I just go here?
Okay.
Well, nobody seems to be doing anything.
So this is a perfect opportunity to like pick up stuff.
Go to the smith.
I can't.
I have to kill Gwyn to unlock the smith.
That's...
Isn't that...
That's a boss.
I don't want that to happen.
Wait, the smith...
The giant?
Wait.
Am I mixing three games together?
Oh, the Giants and Dark Souls 3.
What the hell is pendant?
Oh, it doesn't do anything.
Who's down there?
I don't know.
Who is any fucking idea?
Actually, no.
I know who you guys are talking about.
Yeah.
Nah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This guy down here.
I still can't even upgrade this.
What do you got for items?
Murakumo.
Gauntlet of thorns.
I'm putting all my points into
strength.
The Sorcerer's Catalyst.
Why is this 500,000 sold?
Very, very rare.
I need Twinkling Titanite if I have any chance.
I already defined like a...
Buy the sword?
How much was it?
Should I get that sword?
But I...
My strength...
I have no...
I can't even...
Yeah, it does cost nothing.
You're right.
Well, here's the thing though.
I don't think I can even put it on.
I need 13 decks.
I can't even like use the damn thing.
A lot of people want me to use the Dark Hand.
But nah, this is just doing way more damage.
Use it as a shield?
All right.
Where the hell do I want to go?
Try just fight Artorias.
No, that would be a mistake.
No balls.
What?
Where is he?
Get him to fall?
That's the plan.
Crash.
It's dead.
Oh well.
Let's reroll it again.
Except this time.
I'm going...
I'm gonna go nuts here.
Let's see if I can do it.
I'm gonna do all Pinwheel.
Replace normal enemies with Pinwheel.
Replace NPCs with Pinwheel.
Let's open the config here.
Disable all and only Pinwheel.
The thing is I have to find Pinwheel.
This is gonna be the ultimate run.
Pinwheel.
Where...
There we go.
Done?
Okay.
I wonder if I can even walk like 20 feet.
This is gonna be fucking so stupid.
But that's what we're doing here, right?
That's why we're doing this.
Where am I gonna end up?
That's alright.
How scared am I?
Eh.
I think maybe like a four.
Well, one of them already died.
I didn't have to do anything.
Pinwheel, easiest boss in the game.
That's not Pinwheel, okay?
Why is that here?
That's not Pinwheel.
I selected Pinwheel.
This is not Pinwheel.
Weirdly enough.
It's all bosses, but none of them are Pinwheel.
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh god.
Why would I come to Blighttown of all places?
Look at this shit.
Jump off?
I'm not gonna jump off.
This is fucking terrible.
I don't...
Did it not save properly?
Pinwheel...
Clones...
I don't even remember how to get down.
Oh, Jesus.
Um, I haven't even collected any items.
I have so many souls.
Oh, fuck.
That was right next to my head.
Kick him off!
Kick him!
Um, um, um...
Down...
Wait.
Is this a mimic?
I can upgrade the sword.
Finally.
Thank god.
Alright.
Now, what's the safest...
There's so much going on the screen right now.
This is a bone home.
Not yet.
I am sweating right now.
Bad.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
You know you're right.
You guys are right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's get out of here.
I'm gonna level off like fucking 30 times.
Okay.
No!
I fell off the shite.
That's the voice we had.
Didn't you all know it?
Okay.
What is that?
Who is that?
Found him!
Let's go, you motherfucker.
You and me!
No, no, no.
Not good.
Shit.
God!
Is she dead?
Did she fall off?
She fell off.
Okay, she fell...
It's just me and him now.
Got him.
I win.
You didn't see?
What do you mean you didn't see?
Scripted, scripted, scripted.
What do you mean?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
He's dead.
Oh, what is that?
Just do it like...
Wait, somebody's behind me.
Somebody's behind me.
I don't know who it is.
Can I get out?
He...
Did he follow me?
Oh, no.
It's because I hit the reset button.
Oh my god.
What?
I was behind him.
Yeah, I can almost afford that sorcerer's staff.
I'll kill him again right now.
For the doubters.
Where is he?
I'm terrified.
I can't really move.
Where's Pinwheel?
This time.
It was for real.
Where's Pinwheel?
I need to...
I'm gonna be unstoppable.
I'm gonna level up everything into strength.
Into...
I'm gonna get to 50 strength
and then all hit in hell.
God.
Just let...
I can't touch the bonfire
because he's just hanging out here.
Where is it?
What are we doing?
What?
Why would it...
Why would it highlight no?
Can anyone explain to me
when I press use item
why does it highlight no?
First.
It should highlight yes.
Why does it highlight anything?
I have to go to another bonfire.
I have to go to another...
Pinwheel.
Wait.
Got it.
I just keep spawning.
I'm just gonna keep getting free souls forever.
I'm gonna get 99 in every step.
I just keep doing it.
This is just cheating.
It's just cheating.
All right.
Up to Pinwheel.
Let's go.
This time Cox ain't gonna fuck it up.
Dad.
You saw it on camera.
What'd he drop?
He dropped something.
Pinwheel did not kill me.
This is this guy killing me.
All right.
I have to get the fuck out of this.
What is coming out of the house?
This is like being inside of a hurricane.
I'm inside the eye of a storm right now.
This is a tornado
and a hurricane going on.
This is lightning striking.
No.
This is like riding a Harry Potter ride.
I feel like I'm riding a ride
at fucking Universal Studios.
Are they killing each other?
All right.
Let's go.
RT Ice.
Are the gargoyles dead?
They just...
What is the ice?
What is causing the ice wave?
This is too much stimulation.
It really is.
Okay.
So I am now going to...
I'm laddered.
Try to get Pinwheel to work.
So what am I doing wrong?
I thought everybody was supposed to be Pinwheel.
Get me the fuck out of here.
Get me out of here.
Let's try this again.
Okay.
So.
Disable all and then Pinwheel.
And then I guess I have to save it and then load it.
So there.
Save as Pin...
Okay.
Pinwheel.
This should do it.
Okay.
So I need to select Pinwheel.
Pinwheel is selected.
Pinwheel.
All right.
I think we got it now.
Let's try it.
Watching the Crystal Dragon just fall into the abyss and putting his hands up.
That was...
That was a highlight of the night for me.
All right.
Let's try it.
It keeps going down a roller coaster.
Like the first drop.
All right.
Please.
No.
What the fuck?
It's like they never stopped.
They never stopped.
Hold on.
Let's try it.
I gotta do one...
Let me try one more thing.
All right.
Let's select that.
Get that gone.
Okay.
See if this works.
Now I got it.
This will be it I think.
There we go.
Pretty sure I just did it.
If not, there's one more thing I can try.
And if not, it might...
But I don't know why it won't work.
It's just a war.
I think we got it.
All right.
So if I die one time, then that's bad for my image.
Then I have to turn the stream off.
No.
I need to...
All right.
Let's go.
Let's go down to...
Where the fuck do I even need to go?
I gotta kill the stupid Taurus...
I gotta...
No.
I gotta kill the pinwheel guardians.
The pinwheel gargoyles.
I'm just gonna...
I have to run all the way back.
Get the most important speedrun of all.
All right.
Almost there.
I'm not going to die.
It is almost impossible for me to lose this.
It's two pinwheels.
And I have 50 strength.
But I don't...
This is not even an upgraded weapon.
That's the one problem.
This is not an upgraded weapon.
Can I even climb this without getting hit?
I don't...
Guys, I may as well have one Estus.
Because I have to drink the whole thing to fill a health bar.
He's making excuses...
I am making excuses already.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm kind of freaking out because this is so...
This is so easy.
I did...
But I got a mushroom.
I just skipped it accidentally.
Ring the bell.
I'm gonna beat this whole game tonight.
What do you think about that?
By the way, here is the stipulation for the rest of this particular thing that I'm doing here.
If I die, the run's over.
Or I have to get to the end.
I have to beat the game.
You want me to start from scratch with this?
No, because everybody wants me to lose all my stats.
No.
That's not part of the deal.
All right.
Let's go down.
Get some of that new gear.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Oh, he doesn't need to just do that.
I thought he was T-posing.
All right.
Pardon me.
Request.
Absolution.
I don't have enough money.
Look at this thing.
Grant?
All this stuff is bare...
This stuff is all pretty much free.
Learn gesture.
I will.
All right.
Learn T-pose.
Now I can do it with my friends.
And I still can't do this.
Well, oh well.
You can make a new character without deleting this one.
Yeah, I can.
Pull?
What do you mean pull?
Pull, pull.
We gotta...
You wanna...
Wait, what do you mean pull?
Now let...
I'm gonna do the pull.
Let me do the pull.
It's my...
I'm gonna do the pull.
No, that pull doesn't count.
That pull...
I'll do one.
I'm gonna go...
Look, we haven't gone pee.
It's been three and a half hours.
Let's go to the bathroom.
I can keep this character.
All right, here you go.
We need some official rules.
I think you should start with normal enemies
and bosses only as pinwheel
until you ring the first bell.
Then pinwheel all.
We're gonna get like super deep with this.
All right.
Well, I'm gonna pee.
I'll be right back.
We'll see what happens.
All right.
So I'm gonna save this character.
It looks like majority has ruled here.
I'm gonna implement some rules, though.
This is gonna be some important rules.
Yes, that's exactly what it's gonna do.
Rats for enemies, pinwheel for all bosses.
I'm gonna try to beat this game as fast as I can.
By the way, I get to die three times.
I get three lives.
If I die three times before...
Okay, let's put it this way.
Hold on a second.
I'm not gonna beat the entire game
with pinwheels and rats.
That's gonna just get boring.
I have to beat three pinwheels.
I have to...
No, you only get to die once.
All right, fine.
If I die once, then it's over.
I have to beat at least three pinwheels.
All right, here we go.
Let me just save this.
Make a new character.
Put a timer on.
What do you mean?
Why do I need a timer for this?
How long do I get?
Like, guys, I don't even remember
half the ways to go in this game.
You think I'm gonna beat this whole game
in an hour or two?
All right, let's go do it.
All right.
Replace normal enemies only with normal enemies.
And then the normal enemies are gonna be rats.
Replace NPCs.
Do not replace NPCs.
Or should I replace NPCs with pinwheels?
No, do not replace NPCs.
All right, fully randomized.
They can be anywhere.
All right, this looks good.
Now I'm gonna open up the config.
Let's put on pinwheel.
And small rat, rat...
Large rat and snow rat are active.
That looks good.
All bosses are gonna be replaced with boss,
and pinwheel is the only one that's selectable,
so this should work.
Let's go.
By the way, dying to a rat does not count.
Dying to a pinwheel ends the whole run.
And I may, I may need to...
It depends.
Let's see.
It depends on if a new character is a random roll
or if it's all the same random.
Let's find out.
I might start with the same equipment.
Yeah, let's see.
I'm gonna have to change equipment.
Pinhead.
Pinhead is pretty good.
I'm gonna be knight.
You have to pick the class?
Deprived.
Why do you guys get to pick?
A hair.
I don't know, let me go to customize.
All right, that's fine.
Here it goes.
Rat!
That's not a rat.
What the fuck is that?
It's not a rat?
Why are they all these...
Why is this happening?
Let me see.
Did I have something wrong here?
Shouldn't be.
It's on...
The profile is set to...
It's on pinwheel.
Pinwheel.
It's selected, okay.
That's rat, small rat, snow rat, and then pinwheel and that's it.
It's selected.
So that should be fine.
Hmm.
Replace normal enemies only with normal enemies.
Replace bosses with bosses and I have them selected.
Is the beginning just an exception?
It might be.
Hold on.
All right, here we go.
This is probably what's going on.
Enemy boss can be placed anywhere in the world.
Yes, you can find things like madness in the asylum.
Okay.
I think I had like a little lock on it.
Let's try it.
Okay.
And I'm on pinwheel config.
Should do it.
Let's go.
If this doesn't work, then I'm not sure what else to do.
We might have to just go back to the other file and say sorry.
You got a 300 word essay due tomorrow.
Dude, get on that.
What are you doing here?
It worked.
All right, we're good.
So begins the run.
300 word...
That's not...
Yeah, that's like...
You've probably written more words in chat today than you will for your essay.
Will I do you math homework?
Yeah, what is it?
Give me a problem.
There he is.
He's already up there.
I see him.
See ya.
It's a 2016 meme.
Am I really getting grabbed by old 2016 meme?
Is that happening to me?
Got the hammer.
All right, let's go.
Blood shield.
What does a blood shield do?
All right, let's go.
Kill the first pinwheel.
Gives resistance.
Oh, I see.
Thanks.
This is going to be actually pretty easy.
The only thing I have to worry about is the first two pinwheels are going to be hard
because...
Why is he up here now?
He shouldn't be up here now.
Yeah, the first two pinwheels are going to be hard because I have no stats.
Where's his health bar?
Oh, he doesn't even exist yet.
I have to...
Hold on.
Where'd he go?
This is just going to hurt me.
All right, here we go.
I thought that was going to hit me.
He's stuck.
He's stuck in a time loop.
I can kill him.
He's so fucked up.
First pinwheel down.
The first of at least two.
Take the humanity.
Thank you.
Level one, one.
Hold on.
Give me a second.
I have to be right back real quick.
I got to talk to Kim about something very quickly.
I'll be right back.
All right, we're good.
Sorry about that.
We're good.
Weirdly enough, for some reason,
uh, the ceiling light in our bedroom like crashed just fell down.
I don't know how.
So everything's fine.
It just don't ask me how that happened.
A fucking ghost.
Uh, yeah, I'll put those on.
Is the eagle shield better?
What was that?
Somebody's shooting at me?
Whatever, let's go.
All right, speed run time.
Let's hurry.
Oh, it's the pinwheel that's downstairs.
This should...
Actually, you know what?
I will beat this tonight.
I'm going to beat the whole game tonight.
You know why that is?
Because I'm simply just going to run to every pinwheel.
This is not going to take more than like 30 minutes.
All these items are in the same spot, though.
That's the only problem here.
All right, what?
Doesn't matter.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Go, hurry up.
30 minutes on no balls.
Time it.
Fine.
How do I do that?
I don't think I can add one.
Here we go.
I got one.
So I got, uh, let's say one hour.
This should do it.
I said 30 minutes.
That's too bad.
One hour.
If I don't beat this in an hour, then I have lost a pinwheel.
I will accept it.
But I'm just going to literally jump down the hole and kill like the speedrun strategy.
All right, here we go.
Let me add this source.
Where is it?
I need this to be in Chrome because Firefox can't be pulled.
I forgot.
Cane and lynch rules.
No, I'm not doing a cane and lynch rule set here.
I'm doing one hour.
How about this?
Okay, if I kill at least five pinwheels in an hour, I win.
I might not even be able to get all the way through.
It's pretty possible that I might not do this at all.
Pinwheel percent.
All right, let's get this a little smaller.
All right, you ready?
In three, two, one, go.
All right, can I make the, can I make the rats smaller?
This is not fair.
They take up so much space.
That doesn't count.
It really doesn't.
I can die to it as many times as I want to a rat.
They're really just going to blow this whole thing.
Oh, god damn it.
Bye, all of you.
Okay, what's this item?
Five pinwheels, right?
That's all I need.
What do you mean no?
Why does this one have like rot all over it?
Is this a pig?
This is not even a rat.
This is a pig.
Nice random items.
More shit.
These are just a nuisance.
I've come to, that did so much fucking damage.
It's unbelievable.
I, can I get rid of the rats?
Can I please get rid of the snow rat
that does all your health in one hit?
No, I can do five.
Take off the leg armor, recall.
Leave these things alone.
They do so much damage.
The rats are harder than pinwheel.
I'm going to lose again.
I'm going to get hit again.
This is such a mess.
Because then he's going to stuff his face over here and die.
Oh, he fell off the edge.
Guys, it's fucking stupid.
I can't even move.
I would have had this better off all of them being pinwheel.
Give me the item.
Just dropped an item.
You rolled all the way.
You can't be serious.
Make them all small rats.
Yeah, can I make them all?
If I can't get up there again, I don't care.
I'm doing it.
I'm making them all small rats.
Pickaxe, nice.
What's the timer for?
Uh, for me to beat the game.
Me beating the game is killing pinwheel five times.
I've already done it once, so four more times.
This time I'm going to be ready.
Because these people, the guy, they aggro from over here.
Just wait it out.
Fuck it, just go.
Seriously.
All right, I got the first bonfire.
Touch it.
Just let him in.
I can't, that's not going to happen.
What do I want to do?
Uh, it doesn't count if I die to rats.
You can't help it.
Get out of the way.
Please leave me the fuck alone.
No.
They're just obstacles.
They don't even attack.
The giant rats are just fucking annoying obstacles.
I'm dead.
Get over here, you motherfucker.
The snow rats are actually later game enemies.
What was I thinking?
Okay, give me.
You actually attacked this time.
I can skip a bunch of that shit.
I just skipped like, I skipped like fucking 20% of the game.
Okay, just, just go.
How much time?
50 minutes?
I want to get up there.
No, don't even, just go.
Pinwheel is the easiest thing in the game.
It's almost impossible to lose.
I just have to get through the rats.
Somebody do it.
My fucking god.
There he is, pinwheel number two.
Come here.
I teleported all the way back here?
Oh shit, I forgot about the rats.
That's like the fucking real bots.
Watch out for the fireball.
I need, I need to, I'm just doing all endurance.
On to the gargoyles.
Sometimes they drop an item.
Okay, let's go.
I have to beat the whole game.
I'm working on it.
It's, it's going to be pinwheel, right?
Pinwheel is just going to be hanging out up top?
Yep, he's just hanging out up there.
Sorcerer's Cloak.
Die.
Another pickaxe.
You're doing speedrun prevention tactics.
Oh, I'm aware.
Uh, strength and dex.
Which one?
Strength.
I need to be doing, I need to do a little bit more damage.
I need, um, what's with all the dumb shit stuff?
This is boring.
I want items.
Whatever, run.
40, 46 minutes?
Why would I ever select to have big rats?
Looking for items.
No, fuck the rats.
Just get the items and run.
Chain leggings.
That may have been a mistake.
Willard just showed up.
Oh, god damn it.
Please, no.
No, he's going to fill the door, isn't he?
I thought he was going to run right into the door.
Just try to block my screen.
Oh, no, it's king rat.
They're fucking everywhere, man.
I, I, I'm going to give it the shortcut.
I'm going to need it.
I know this is a waste of time, but I want to, I can just skip it.
Let's go.
Left close.
You have to beat actual pinwheel last.
That's not part of the deal.
Your goal is five pinwheels.
So if you fight the rat goils and go below the blacks, but that's all five.
I need that master key.
Oh, shit.
I'll get it later.
I don't have time for that.
Oh, oh, no, they fill in the doors.
The rats were the worst decision.
I think the rats may be the worst decision.
Impossible.
This is impossible.
Whatever this item is, just what is it?
Sorcery.
I have to clear this whole room of rats because the giant rats
are going to make it impossible for me to run fast.
I need more strength.
That was just a drop in the bucket right there.
What do I need?
24 and 13.
24, 24 strength.
I can, I can do that.
What a great speed run.
Yeah.
Oh, good speed run.
Saving frames here.
Master key.
What the fuck just happened?
I hate this.
Why did that happen?
I just bumped my head and fell backwards.
I don't know why that happened.
It bounced me backwards.
Why did that happen?
It doesn't even make any sense.
You couldn't do that if you all,
if you all loaded up Dark Souls right now
and tried to just do what I did.
It wouldn't be possible.
My hand fucking slipped.
This is what I wanted to do.
I forgot about these items.
There's my strength.
Okay, go.
Okay, let me go back around.
Break the soul.
Get the strength.
Optimal route.
It's all right.
I'm good.
I'm gonna need two.
I need more than that.
What happened? 38 minutes?
Uh, I'd lose.
I have to clear the rats though.
Use my souls.
What do you, what do you mean?
I don't have to, I gotta go.
I don't have time for this.
I gotta go.
I, there's just no time for this shit.
Use the greatsword.
I'm using the axe.
Because this has a, uh, how about this?
Will this be good?
It's one hit.
Okay.
That's pretty great actually.
Let's go.
Dark Hand doesn't have enough,
they're all stuffing through here.
This is fucking hell.
They're just gonna chase me up the stairs, guys.
I don't, I hate the rats.
They're ruining this whole thing.
It's just, it's these snow rats.
They're like fucking DLC rats.
And they're killing this run.
I knew they were behind me.
I knew it.
Look at how many snow rats.
It's not even fair.
There's too many snow rats.
And pinwheel is like, I could,
I could close my eyes and take a bath.
It's these dumb snow rats that I put in.
Do something.
I'm gonna have a lot of shit.
All right, time?
34 minutes.
I'm almost halfway done with the game.
I get to add like 30 seconds to the time because of the cutscene.
I know I can skip, but I want to see this.
Is that his teeth?
That's his insides.
Yeah, I think that's his intestines or something.
Not today.
Uh-oh.
I gotta stop panicking right now.
I'm like freaking out because
everyone's laughing in the chat.
I can feel you laughing at me.
He's really close to the edge though,
and I don't want to go over there.
I'm gonna wait till he disappears.
I'm gonna kick him off the edge.
Will he fall off the edge?
Please.
Just kill the motherfucker.
How did that miss?
I'm good.
Everything.
Don't worry about me.
Ring the bell.
It's Twin Humanities.
That's it.
Go 10 flasks is what it took.
Blame the rats for that shit.
That's not my fault.
So what's the fastest way to me to get to the end of the game?
Like to win.
Oh wait, what am I doing?
What am I doing?
Why am I doing this?
Nah, I didn't want to use that.
Do the Sen's Fortress skip?
How do I do that?
Is it enough to do two-handed?
What do I need for two-handed?
I need those two decks.
Shit.
I'm using the crystal.
All right.
How do I do Sen's skip?
No, I seriously can't.
I don't know.
I can't do it.
Let's go.
All right, now I have to go back here and then down.
I gotta go.
No, I gotta go through with that.
I need that basement key.
Yeah, I gotta go to Blight Town.
I need to get that master key right now.
Go get it.
Do the Underground Asylum pinwheel?
No, no, no, no.
That's optional.
I gotta get the master key
and then I gotta go open the door and then go to Blight Town.
All right, let's go.
Whatever the fuck this is, let's get it too.
Can you give us a Monka S?
Not unless it's warranted.
All right, now we gotta go down from the...
Everything's fucking up in my brain
because of the dumb timer.
I have to go up to the blacksmith.
No, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
What are you...
What is he doing here?
Where was the favor of protection?
It's in the same spot where it was last time.
I have to kill that fucking asshole.
Sorry.
Yeah, I don't have time for it, you're right.
All right, let's go here through Blight Town.
Well, isn't there a way that you can jump
across the whole thing in Blight Town?
I don't know where the hell it is.
I don't remember.
You fall and then exit game.
Is that what you really do?
Like, jump all the way down there.
Is that actually how I do this?
Let me go.
So fall off here and then exit the game.
Is that true?
When do I have to exit the game?
I forgot.
Everything requires a confirmation in Dark Souls.
Quit the game.
Are you sure?
Windows user authorization services.
Are you sure you want to open that program?
So you do quit game and right before you die.
So you like land quit, but you can't be dead.
I don't have time for this.
You'll fuck it up again.
All right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
I'm just gonna go down.
I'm gonna try to go down swiftly.
It's at any point during the fall.
You have to quit as soon as you hear the scream.
They're lying.
He's lying.
I'm just gonna quickly get down.
You dumbass snow rat shitheads.
Leave me alone.
All right, quickly.
Let's go.
How do you speed through Blight Town?
You just like walk across.
And there's giant rats here too.
This is such a mistake.
Can I go across that?
No, I have to go down again and then across.
Hold circle.
Yeah, I'm holding circle.
I don't know why it's not doing it.
I'm like holding down circle.
Or B, whatever.
I'm down.
I'm doing it.
I'm trying.
It won't do it.
Dick.
What did I, what the hell did I just do?
I gotta go down there.
It's the quickest way to, can I fall over there?
And then, and then from here I gotta go down.
Right here, come on.
And then there's a bonfire down here.
Somewhere.
Where the fuck is the bonfire?
It's like over here.
Yeah, it's like down here.
Screw the bonfire.
I need the bonfire.
Where is it?
If you seriously kill me,
the rats have the shittiest timing too.
They do like the little bit, bit.
It's the worst enemy in the game.
Why did I pick all rats?
I should have done all,
like what other joke could I fucking come up with?
How about all skeletons?
Funny, right?
And these idiots poison too.
I couldn't think of a stupid or fucking thing to try.
Leave me alone.
Are these all gonna be rats down here?
Because they're technically enemies.
Oh, please.
Here we go.
Why is this one on fire?
Demon pinwheel.
I thought that hit me in the head.
No, I'm not going to lose.
It's just ring the second bell
and then I have to go through sense fortress
and then I can get to the end of the game, right?
Okay, now let me get out.
Now, it's the four kings.
Sense fortress is like the end of the prologue chapter.
I have to do the four pinwheels.
Okay, give me out.
I need to.
I did kill five pinwheels, that's true.
All right, now where do I go from here?
We go from...
I'm back in Blighttown though.
Do the ceaseless discharge.
There's no time.
There's a chest back here.
Hold on.
This could be a game changer.
No, not really.
Go back and fight.
I have to go back and fight ceaseless discharge.
Well, hold on.
I have to go all the way back here.
Why did I bone then?
What was the point of me boning?
Somebody said bone now and I listened to them.
Why would you listen to us?
Because you guys are helpful sometimes.
You give me correct guidance.
Waste of like six minutes.
If we told you to jump off a cliff, would you do it?
No, because I know that would harm me.
Ceaseless is optional.
Yeah, but at some point I have to kill as many pinwheels in another 12 minutes.
And why do you think ceaseless is really optional?
This is the clue.
Hey, well, I might not do it in an hour,
but I could probably get this done in like another 30-40 minutes.
All right, let's go.
I gotta go down.
And then doesn't there look a lady down here?
No!
We had some time for the cutscenes.
It's not intentional.
I swear to God.
I thought I had enough health.
I didn't realize that because I was poisoned.
So I was just taking damage.
I wasn't paying attention to it.
Oh well.
No, I'm gonna die again because of this.
How did you swim through all this?
I fucking hate the rats.
I hate the dogs.
Dogs and rats are two of the worst.
This time I'm not gonna let my poison tick down
and not pay attention to it to a point where I die from that fucking drop.
I mean, there are a lot of mistakes made here.
One of which is having giant rats and snow rats and any rats.
I should have had no enemies.
How did the time go back up?
I don't know.
Did you come?
Did you go to the bathroom and come back?
Because maybe you thought you were gone for longer than you were.
I'm just a bonfire.
I don't care.
I know it's the spider lady.
It doesn't matter.
Okay, now if I remember it's...
Wait a minute.
How is this ceaseless discharge gonna exist?
It's just pinwheel.
You see him down there?
I don't see anything down there.
Watch him be like 500 feet tall.
I don't think this is gonna work.
How do I get him to spawn?
Didn't even get a chance to spawn.
He's dead.
All right, now I need to...
What's the fastest way to get the hell out of here?
And the fastest way...
What's the fastest way to get out of this?
Go to the altar and get the armor set.
It's not gonna be an armor set.
It's gonna be dumb.
There's nothing here.
It's gonna be...
It's random.
It's a humanity.
So ceaseless discharge.
Dead.
Bone and walk to the elevator and go back up.
Why did I do that?
What the fuck did I listen to people for?
It was right behind me.
I just had to...
I thought I...
I can't believe I did it again.
I really thought that I was, for some reason,
didn't rest at that bonfire.
Let's at least go through here.
Where's the...
Where's Quelaag's door?
It's like a hidden door or something.
Where is it?
All right.
So now...
Killer.
You know you're right.
That's true.
There's not even...
There's not even a fucking fire soul here.
It's a random goddamn item.
Okay.
Let's go.
That doesn't count either because those aren't rats.
I mean, those aren't pinwheels.
Sen's fortress.
Let's go.
Why...
Why do I still give a shit about this?
It's been like an hour and 10 minutes.
Why do...
Why am I...
Why do I care about this so much?
Ring the bell?
I did, didn't I?
I didn't.
Ring the bell?
I...
I rang the bell.
What do you mean it didn't ring the bell?
That's the first thing I did when I got up here.
Let me go back up.
Do you actually didn't?
No.
You're not gonna fool me on this one.
I'm sorry, guys.
The first thing I did was pull the lever.
I remember...
I have a distinct memory.
I want that item.
Swan, let's go.
I'm gonna turn timer off because I don't even need it.
What's the point?
If you turn off the timer, you're admitting defeat.
And then we go back around.
What am I looking for here?
What am I trying to get to?
If I fell off right there, I would have been...
It would have probably been the other whole thing.
I would have turned it off.
Up all the way and then back to Sen's, right?
Sen's fortress should be pretty easy,
considering there's literally nothing besides rats.
But who knows?
That might be horrible.
There's something over there too, but I don't care.
I'm on a timer over here.
Yeah, there are traps, but I know where they are.
Jerma ain't shit.
Get rid of them.
Get rid of that person.
Don't die to poison.
Poison is your enemy.
Okay, now I need...
That's the way out.
See you later.
Just a couple of snow rats.
Don't even pay attention to them.
Just go.
I go right into you.
Bone now.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, no, no.
Seriously, like, I can't fuck this up.
Dying here would be an actual stream disaster.
All right.
Sen's.
Back through.
Gotta wrap around.
I'm gonna go the...
I'm just gonna go the way that I know how to go.
Some people are probably saying,
Dude, dude, boy, you're going the wrong way, man.
You wrapped...
No, you went the right way.
You could have gone the other way.
You could have gone that way.
And I'm like, it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna be fine.
Should I bone now?
This is a good time to bone.
Uh-oh.
This is bad.
So I have to go this way.
Blacksmith and then across to Sen's.
And to stream.
No, I'm going to do this.
I just have to kill Penguin.
Was there a spell in front of the...
I really cannot die before getting to the blacksmith.
You're still following me.
This is really, really stupid.
Like, hold on.
I can't skip Sen's because I can't parry rats.
Right.
You're right.
Yeah, unfortunately.
It's all right.
I got this.
I didn't make him like a Taurus Demon or something, right?
No, thank God.
What do I need?
Demon Titanite?
Where was the Demon Titanite?
Didn't the slug have it?
No, it's because the rats are all...
I'm not going to get any items to upgrade weapons.
I'll be seeing you, Speaker.
That's not good.
I'm not going to be able to get them.
It's all rats.
I'm just going to pick up dung.
That's the only thing they're going to drop.
Whatever.
Let's go.
You have a Gravelord sword.
You don't need upgrades.
Yes, I do.
You know who you're talking about here?
It's in the chest.
A regular mace.
That's great.
Did the balls that still drop?
No, the boulders can't drop
because there's no giants to drop them.
You gotta be kidding me.
This is what you do, right?
Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I forgot there's some traps.
And then...
Wait, hold on.
I have to wait for this to come down.
I did know where the traps are.
I know where they are.
This is the right thing, right?
Okay.
Now, it's...
I have to move...
I have to turn this.
And then we go...
Where the fuck do we go now?
Up or around or...
I don't remember.
I forget.
I need to go on top.
Oh!
I told you I knew where the traps were.
All right.
Then it's up.
Watch out for the rat.
There's two.
I don't know where they are.
Now we're on...
This is the iron...
The iron giant's up here, right?
I gotta move my body for this.
I'm going too fast.
I can stand right there, I think, right?
Can I stand in the middle?
All right.
We're good.
There it is.
Now is...
There's no explosive throws.
That can't be possible.
No.
No way.
No rat is going to throw an explosive bomb over here.
Okay.
Just got to go up.
I'm almost there.
And then I can go to Gwyn.
Wait.
What about that ring?
Let me see it.
Reduces lava damage.
Crown of the Dark Sun.
Nice.
I'm the Angry Mario Sun.
Cool.
All right.
Let's go.
Now that was an epic gamer reference.
Thanks.
You can go up in those, can't you?
I remember this place was so ridiculous.
Thank god I can just walk around through it.
Leggings of Thorns, purging stone.
Humanity.
Hooray!
I did it.
Give it to me.
All right.
And a Londo.
How much more do I have?
To actually just jump right down to Gwyn.
I'm almost there, right?
Yeah, this is 50% of the way through the game.
You're right.
That's true.
You know, you're right.
You still are about 30 minutes to an hour to get to Gwyn.
Hey, well, at least, hey, I beat the good half of the game, right?
Yeah, that was fun.
I'm not, no, I'm not.
That's the only fire keeper I have left.
Didn't beat Bed of Chaos.
I know I'm missing stuff.
I'm just trying to...
Oh yeah, still have to beat like Ornstein and Smog and...
Why is there a pinwheel here?
All right, can I turn it back to like random nonsense again?
I think this has lost its luster.
Do a pole?
Hold on.
After the next pinwheel, I'll do a pole.
I'll give it the eight minutes.
Because I truly failed at that point, right?
Perfect.
Why do they always perfectly do this?
Even a rat will do it.
So that's surprising to me somehow.
Watch the Lord Vessel be in the rafter.
Holy shit, that almost didn't make it.
Then I got to turn this.
We spin all the way around, which leads me over here.
To which is the...
There's a front door, right?
Over here.
This makes 10 pinwheels, doesn't it?
I think this is 10 pinwheels.
Almost, that was close.
You almost had it.
What'd he drop?
I don't know.
Did you set these enemies yourself or did you get fucked by the seed?
That would be really funny if I didn't set this.
And it was actually just pinwheels and rats.
All right, executive decision.
At six minutes, I'm turning it back on to complete random.
And I'm going to try to get through at least this part again.
I mean, there's only so long that you can take an hour and a half of pinwheel and rats.
You know, there gets to be a point where...
You see what I'm saying?
How much more of that can you take?
Not very much, right?
This is actually a really hard part of the game.
It is made completely negligible from rats running off the cliff.
This is where the big bow and arrow guys are.
This is awful.
This spot in particular sucks.
Where's the bonfire?
Isn't it in here somewhere?
I don't even need a bonfire where I'm going.
Where's Ornstein?
I'm close to Ornstein.
I don't need a bonfire where I'm going.
That's gonna be fine.
It's just rats.
I thought that was an enemy and I was like, why is that here?
Shouldn't be.
Four minutes.
This will be the final thing that I do until we do absolute hell mode again
and I'll try to get through something.
I have to be pinwheel and pinwheel.
How do you pronounce Einstein?
Einstein.
I don't need bonfires where I'm going.
Don't worry guys.
Oh yeah, I can jump off this.
Here we go.
This doesn't do anything, right?
Wait, will it be...
Is it gonna be NPCs?
I don't got time for this shit.
It's just gonna be normal.
No, you've already seen that before.
Who cares?
You want me to use the orb or do you want to see two pinwheels?
Both.
I'm gonna die to this person.
I can't even use this.
It's gonna be three pinwheels.
Oh no, it's not.
I got no stamina for this shit.
Bastard.
No!
That does so much fucking damage.
Whoa!
Hey!
What's going on?
What happened?
Hey!
What's happening?
It's so loud.
It's fucking up my concentration.
It's burning into my brain.
It hurts.
Take the popcorn out of the microwave.
Oh, it's the timer.
It's the timer.
The hard part's over.
Just get it done.
It's getting louder.
I think it's actually getting louder.
I miss it.
I like Monopack.
I kind of like want it back.
Where is it?
Oh, it's freaking me.
It's fucking messing with me even more.
Did I win?
I didn't even get his item.
That, I swear to God.
I thought, I, you know what?
Here's what I thought actually happened.
I thought there was an emergency on the computer.
Like somehow in Windows 10, there's an emergency signal
with something really bad.
Like you got a virus or your memory is bad
or your computer's gonna start to burn or something.
Like Intel has a thing.
Like your computer's burning.
I had no idea what that was.
Here they go.
I love the little teeth intestines thing.
Pinwheel and pinstein.
Wait, what happens when you kill one of them?
Do they turn into a super pinwheel?
Oh, look at this.
I think he just got bigger.
That was a lot easier.
Which way did he go?
I swear he was just standing right in front of me.
Weird.
Here comes the Lord Vessel.
Now I go talk to the weird snake thing in the ground
and I say yes.
And we're going back to fully random.
I did my pinwheel.
Penance, give me the Lord Vessel.
Thank you.
Go get the Lord Vessel and then come back to see me.
Bring the Lord Vessel back and claim Gwyn as the rightful.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, by the way, eat shit.
I will transform into pinwheel.
Whatever.
Let's go to...
Where do I want to go now?
Quickly, quickly, tell me.
Where do I go?
I go to Firelink, talk to the snake.
And then we're going to do all random.
Oh, yes, you found the Lord Vessel.
Give it here, you fucking wanker.
All right, fastest way for me to do this.
What's the fastest way to get to Gwyn?
Say yes or say no.
Did you kill a bunch of people going down here?
Who are you killing?
People are just dying.
Sif, Four Kings, Pinwheel, Nito, Gwyn.
That's too long.
Killing the actual pinwheel is your real final fight.
But the thing is, pinwheel is not going to be pinwheel.
Pinwheel is going to get replaced by a different boss.
See, that's the big kicker here.
All right, here we go.
The timer's still on the screen?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Let's warp to...
Where the hell do I need to go?
First of all, let me do random.
This is all saved, we're good.
All right, here comes the shit show.
And we're probably going to end on this note here.
I'm actually surprised we've been doing this for five and a half hours almost.
So let's do one more rowdy randomize.
Replace bosses with bosses.
Replace normal enemies with bosses or normal enemies.
Replace NPCs.
Replacement chance for a boss to be a random enemy will be 20%.
All bosses.
So replace bosses with bosses and replace normal enemies with bosses.
Am I doing...
We already did that and it was too much.
No, replace bosses with bosses.
Replace normal enemies with normal enemies or bosses.
And there is a 10% chance that a normal enemy will be a boss.
Don't replace NPCs.
It's fully random, you can put them anywhere, 10%.
Let's open up the config and enable everybody.
Okay, that sounds good to me.
Am I feeling lucky?
We'll find out.
This is the best night to be high.
Oh, by the way, I'm not going to be live tomorrow because of 4th of July.
Kim and I are going to go see some fireworks.
So you'll probably see me again on either Friday or Saturday.
I might have some stuff that I want to do for the carnival.
So depending on...
Just keep an eye on the sus.
Friday or Saturday you'll see me again.
Should be fun.
And I'm ready to start.
Let's go.
Speaking of getting high, I won't be broadcasting tomorrow.
Oh, really makes you think.
No.
All right, let's go.
I need to go to...
Uh, what?
Firelink?
Or what's closest to...
I have to go down in like the depths or something.
Catacombs or something, right?
If I remember correctly, I just have to walk down from Firelink.
Go revive the Firekeeper.
What's dying?
I don't know.
Something above us?
Oh, the timer overlay, right.
10%?
10% chance.
Oh, are you sure it's on 10%?
Because I swear it is.
It's not on 100.
I saved it.
I made sure it wasn't.
You're back.
Everything's fine.
You're alive.
Is it still not lit?
I have to light this thing.
I'm not going to go like this.
But now you stand up.
Well, maybe I...
You ran out of time.
You lose.
All right, let me get this off the screen.
That would be nice.
Let's go to Firelink.
Now I need to go from Firelink.
No, don't...
I don't...
Everything's already lit.
It's fine.
Okay, we're good.
So now I need to level up.
I don't have enough.
Here come all the enemies up there.
So you're just hanging out here sleeping.
Now I need to go down from here to the graveyard, right?
This is the fastest way to the graveyard.
I always have trouble getting to the graveyard
by simply walking to it.
It's like down that way, right?
Isn't it like down here?
Where is that dumb walkway to the graveyard?
It's not this way.
Help me, help me, help me, help me.
Somebody help me.
Help me.
I need help.
Wait, it's an emote-only mode.
Fuck.
What are you guys doing?
Why is it an emote-only mode?
What's going on over here?
Left of the snake man.
All right, I'm going to go left of the snake man.
Thank you.
10 percent.
How is this 10 percent?
It's like 60.
I don't- I've never-
I don't think I've seen-
Did I actually get cursed?
Oh yeah, because these stupid things curse you.
I've never even seen that boss before.
Oh, and I'm-
My HP is cut in half.
Great.
Good thing I have that-
Good thing I have the purging stone.
I'm not using it yet till I get through this.
I wanted the item.
Shit.
I gotta just run.
That wake up was-
May as well have been street fighter.
What?
Why does he have a big purple rock?
He has a crunch berry.
That was boo berry.
That wasn't even an enemy.
What a shithole.
Oh my god.
This is just a shit show.
Thankfully Sip is not running over here too.
Is it 10 percent for normal enemies?
I really would not be surprised
if that were the case.
I deserve to die for that one.
Dude, it really might be 10 percent for normal-
There's another big fucking enemy over here.
There's another centipede down here.
Let me look at it.
What does it say?
Percent boss chance.
Chance that a normal enemy or NPC
will be replaced with a boss
instead of a normal enemy.
10 percent.
It's 10-
It's on 10 percent.
Percentages don't work like a one in 10.
That's 10 percent.
That means 10 percent per enemy.
So one in 10 chance for every enemy to be a boss.
Yeah, but that's still a nine out of 10 chance.
It has to roll that.
You still have to roll a one.
You know, in that scenario
you still got to roll a one.
I don't know why I keep going down
the stairs over there.
If you open random number generator right now
you probably get six, two, two, eight, nine,
two, six, six, six, four, three, three, three, six, eight, two, two, one.
I don't think I'm even gonna be able to walk through this door.
What an ass.
Oh no, an ass?
All right.
Perching stone time.
Do you see anything down there?
I do not see a boss.
I love how the dog T-pose is just a fancy weird rug.
It's one of those like stupid like rugs on the ground.
Just rolled into that.
Okay, is it bonfire?
I'm rolling it again.
I'm putting it down to five percent.
I just rolled it.
I ain't having the centipede down there.
OBS crash?
No, OBS is fine.
Reach it up.
Well, you want to reroll the items too.
I mean, we're at the end.
Why don't we just reroll items?
Just who cares?
Yeah, fuck it.
Let's do it.
All right, here it comes.
Let's reroll the items again.
So let's do just scrambled.
Scrambling the items.
Success.
Items have been scrambled.
So have the enemies.
Do I like my eggs scrambled?
Yes, I do.
I like them over easy, over medium.
Semi-side up to me is disgusting.
No, would not like to eat that.
Is there a bear in here?
Oh, it's a cat.
Did my items?
The items on me didn't scramble.
Where the hell does it think I am?
Oh, okay.
No, this is where I was.
What's the tree?
Is that a piece of broccoli?
Wait.
Oh, all the items have been respawned and replaced.
Interesting.
Okay.
I want to see what it is.
I just want to see what the tree is, man.
I just want to see what the broccoli thing is.
Okay, somebody explain this to me.
Do you know that inside of a clamshell package,
a plastic packaging smell, like brand new plastic packaging.
Why am I smelling that right now?
What does that mean?
My room right now smells like synthetic plastic.
Synthetic plastic for no reason.
As opposed to...
No, no, no.
It's a very distinct plastic smell.
Just give it to the broccoli, please.
No, not like plastic burning.
Just plastic like inside of a plastic bag.
I need to kill the broccoli before I die.
Thank God.
Bag on head.
What's happening?
There's a bag on me.
What the fuck is that smell?
It's freaking me out.
All right, hold on.
I'm gonna need to go see why the house smells like
the inside of a clamshell synthetic packaging.
All right, hold on.
Give me a second.
What the fuck is going on?
I'm not crazy.
So Kim is cleaning the oven all the way up here.
I knew it was happening.
Yeah, I'm telling you.
Am I putting you guys to sleep?
Sorry about that.
All right, let's wrap this up.
I need to kill the real pinwheel
and then stream some propaganda.
I'm determined to go get whatever is in pinwheel's place.
It has to die.
Not terrible spawn here.
Remember, all the items have been replaced again.
They've all been rolled again.
Not worth it.
You don't want to eat something coming up.
No, so what happens is when you clean an oven,
you have to make it really, really hot.
And from there, it's just kind of hot.
What is that?
Use the parry dagger.
No, it's a DLC boss.
I did all the Dark Souls DLC, didn't I?
I don't remember seeing that.
I didn't skip anything.
I know, I remember the Kameera thing.
I never remember it looking like that.
I thought it was orange and like tan, not white.
No, that's just him.
Remember I did both of them?
I did, yeah.
Remember I did the thing where you don't have to do it
and I killed them both?
Hey, you know I did the thing where I started talking
and walking in a circle?
You know how I do that, right?
LOL.
Yeah, when I get to this, this has got to end.
This is like, I think this is what it feels like
when somebody screams in your face
for more than like five to 10 straight minutes.
This is definitely what it feels like.
You'd feel all fucked up,
but it would be things would seem off.
Your room would start to smell like plastic.
Okay, I'm so close.
This time, just fall and run.
No, you're too big.
He's too big.
And then there's the little dinosaur things down here.
There's a guy down here.
What did I get caught on?
I have to kill this fucking thing, don't I?
You can do the same fucking move like five times.
I hate this game.
He's not even supposed to be down here.
I have to kill this.
Let me fight a blue dragon in as much room
as it takes to fit a blue dragon.
It's fucking great.
There's all kinds of zany characters here.
Everything is so zany.
Is he still trying to beat the game?
No, I'm just trying to get to Pinwheel
who is not even real Pinwheel.
But there's a different problem here.
There is a blue dragon who is now blocking my path.
I'm probably gonna have to aggro up here.
I didn't even know you could do that.
Actually, stay there
because you'll block anything that comes in.
He can't fit through there now either.
Oh my God.
Don't block me.
Come on.
I have to bait the electricity and then...
What just came down here?
What just sprinted down here?
The cat.
I'm gonna reroll it.
You can't fight that thing down there.
You can't fight that fucking thing in that room.
I gotta reroll that thing.
Pull the switch.
I want the bonfire so I don't have to keep...
But even if I get the bonfire,
I'm going to be at that bonfire
and a blue dragon will be behind me every single time.
I'm just rushing.
Fucking randomizing, man.
We're getting close to throwing up.
I would just walk straight, but watch.
I have to deal with all this bullshit.
It's safer to almost die.
All right, I'm gonna go pull the switch
and I'm gonna run the hell out of there.
This double blue dragon shit is like seriously...
How many enemies are in this game?
Like 600.
And I get just blue dragons.
I'm going for the pole and then I'm out.
Okay, give me stamina.
Here we go.
Please move.
There's another blue dragon, I swear.
All right, what do we got?
What do we got, what do we got, what do we got?
We have nothing that...
Is this thing gonna activate?
Is it gonna activate, isn't it?
It's not gonna activate, right?
Can I just...
No, it's a...
Shit.
Where are you shooting me from?
What's this line of sight you got here?
Oh, God.
Just go, just run around them.
Don't activate.
As long as these pigs don't activate, I'll be fine.
Why am I not hurting this?
Fully armored pig.
All right, so far so good.
Oh, God.
Come on.
Basement key.
That's not gonna do shit.
I don't want to get punched in the back of the head.
What the hell?
Is this a trap or is this a...
Why is this over here?
You can't be serious.
Did I just actually get hit right in the fucking head?
But a toxic...
Oh, my God.
Why do you have to be here?
I don't have any clumps, I don't think.
No, why would I have any clumps?
All right, I need...
What do I need to do?
I need to deactivate.
I need to...
I'm dead.
I don't even have the fucking bonfire either.
I don't even...
I don't remember this area at all either.
Of course you have to place those toxic enemies everywhere.
Like, why wouldn't you?
Just put...
Put blue dragons and toxic fucking...
Blow dart people.
I ain't ever gonna get that bonfire as long as he's in there.
No, I'm dead.
There's nothing I can do.
Just die.
Mushroom?
Use a...
What mushroom?
Removes plastic from the body.
This fucking thing has to die.
Where is it even aiming?
What's with the stamina?
I just cheesed this asshole.
All right.
I got...
I'm good.
Ay, yi, yi.
Not everything's respawned, though.
Not like it matters.
If Pinwheel is not Pinwheel and he's somebody...
I hope he's somebody really, really easy.
Please, Pinwheel.
Do not be...
Can't I just jump over this or something?
There's a way to do this, isn't there?
I can just launch over here and grab or something, right?
It's like right there, isn't it?
Am I...
I'm correct, aren't I?
No.
Is it up higher?
Over there?
I've never tried...
I've never done it before.
Right there?
On the other side of the bridge?
I've never tried it before.
I don't know.
I'm just trying to get to Pinwheel.
Right off the front of the bridge, okay?
This guy wasn't here before.
Is there a reason why there's a giant in the way?
In fact, I'm gonna like right there,
but there's spikes there, aren't there?
Won't that kill me?
Bottom of the bridge.
Like right here?
Is that it?
And is that the right way?
I was gonna jump over there the first time.
Just drop, don't jump.
You just...
Really?
Don't jump.
You just fall.
Just drop.
Really?
So you're talking about...
Let me just get this right.
So you're talking about just drop...
Oh, that little...
That little thing right there.
I see what you mean.
Like right...
That's what you're talking about, right?
Okay.
All right.
So now I know what that is.
Then you do a second drop.
Learning things every day here.
I haven't played Dark Souls Remastered in a long time,
but last time I played...
I only really completed Dark Souls
and played it when I streamed it.
Please get out of my way.
You're making this hard for me because I can't see.
You big giant.
Okay.
Why did you come down here?
Did you see me do that or something?
I don't understand.
Okay.
Well, that's good.
I wonder if...
Can I just go in here?
Aren't I getting close to Pinwheel?
This is Manus, right?
Oh, Nito.
There's an item down there.
Doesn't Nito like come pick you up?
You lie in the coffin, he drags you in.
All right.
So let's drop again.
But where...
I'm just going to be careful.
So drop again.
Where though?
Over there?
Okay.
And it's a cool item,
but it's definitely not the item you think it is.
All right.
Holy shit.
The giant came down.
Everybody came down.
And now...
I bad-grewed everything somehow.
Just run.
I'm not dealing with this bullshit.
Everybody just got hit by the grenade.
Don't do this to me.
Unfucking believable.
Just...
Just big obnoxious fucks always in the way.
I'm just trying to run those boars,
the boars and the rats on this randomizer night.
They haven't done anything but just be gigantic assets
that just get in the way.
They don't do anything else.
They don't even fight you.
They don't even attack.
They just get in the fucking way.
They're just kaizo blocks.
They don't even do anything.
Don't come down here.
Is he dead?
What?
Oh.
And it's always a chef.
I'm gonna fucking kill this chef.
All right.
Are you guys ready?
I think it's time.
Here we go.
It's time for me to beat the real Pinwheel.
Who is it?
Somebody easy.
What is it?
Wait.
Doesn't this guy spawn like a hundred skeletons?
Oh no.
He...
Pinwheel, Nito.
Doesn't he do like a big explosion?
I'm not gonna be able to get away from that.
It's gonna hit me every time, I think.
There's the real enemy.
There he is.
I killed Pinwheel.
That was Pinwheel.
Pinwheel was spawned and I killed Pinwheel.
I win.
Sorry, guys.
That's how it works.
I died to Nito.
I killed Pinwheel.
That's a victory.
I missed.
If it wasn't, fuck.
I already won.
Now that stream's over.
I killed Pinwheel.
The giant was in the way.
I couldn't see.
It's over.
I beat him.
You all saw it.
I don't need any more proof.
The name tag said Pinwheel.
I killed Pinwheel.
He nudged me a little bit.
Why does he have to be standing in the exact place that I won?
Have I eaten a McChicken yet?
Yeah.
Yeah, I have.
Yes.
I can't kill Nito with like in 30 seconds.
All right, here we go.
I have to kill Nito in like 12 seconds with like 30% health.
Got him.
No, you don't get to say shit.
You thought it was going to happen, but it didn't.
I just want to close the book on this.
All right, the book is closing on this.
If I wasn't toxic, and you know what?
I'm going to dump a humanity into this.
Who really cares?
I'm just going to take three humanities.
I have to at least try.
I cannot do this twice, right?
Summon help?
I don't think I want to go online with this because it might be bad.
All right, please just get out of the way.
No toxic bullshit.
There it is.
He's going to try to smash me.
Don't let him.
Yep, I knew it was coming.
Why am I online?
That's an NPC.
Here we go.
All right, let's try.
Is there enough room?
I just barely have to go all the way to the end.
God damn it.
It's close.
I got to keep him at this side.
I think this is too close.
I'm dead.
Oh, that sucks.
See, I already killed the pinwheel so he's not spawning.
This is too many.
There's like 15 pinwheels in that room.
So yes, guys.
Yes, I died to a room that had Nito and 15 pinwheels in it.
All right?
Yeah, sure.
I will take that loss.
That's okay, but it's not even real.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
Hope you have a happy Fourth of July.
They die in one hit, but that doesn't matter.
Yeah, ants die in one hit too.
But if there's a thousand of them, you're gonna die.
If you get swarmed by like two or three thousand ants,
you're dead.
You're gonna die.
You're gonna get like stung in the face and shit.
Oh my god.
All right, the stream's actually over.
I can't attempt this again.
He was deposing.
All right, that's it.
That's it.
I am not doing it anymore.
Didn't puke.
I just did.
Fuck you, man.
Why did I just do that?
All right, quiet time.
Here we go.
Real attempt.
How the fuck am I not hitting this guy?
Okay, here come the pinwheels.
Oh shit, I'm gonna get hit by this.
I gotta tank one.
Look, look, what do you mean look?
What am I looking at?
Why am I looking at chat?
Pinwheel is officially dead.
I did not lose to pinwheel.
Three tries to beat the real pinwheel.
Hey, now I'm like satisfied and I can turn this stream off.
That's it.
That was Dark Souls randomizer items and enemies and bosses and shit.
It was really fun.
It was a little ridiculous,
but you can probably hear some of the fireworks right now.
People uh, July 3rd and July 4th.
Uh, that's gonna be it.
I'll see you guys in a couple days.
I'll let you know.
Check the sus.
It'll probably be either Friday or Saturday.
And we got 20 community subs from cyanide and five from play for doctor.
Thank you both of you.
Thank you cyanide.
That's hundreds of dollars at this point, right?
That's like 50 community subs tonight.
Jesus.
Thank you.
Happy 4th of July.
I'll see you real soon.
Will I do a Dark Souls 3 randomizer?
I did a lot of weird Dark Souls 3 stuff before.
I was played as bosses and times 20 speed and slow motion.
I had a lot of mods before.
First person mod, which was really fun until you get to a boss.
But yeah, you can find these on uh, the Nexus mods guy has a page.
But yeah, thanks everybody.
See you soon.
We're going to do the bits.
Hope you enjoyed it.
That was exactly what I thought it was going to be.
It was a lot of fun.
Do Dark Souls 2.
What am I doing tomorrow?
Me and Kim are going to go.
We're probably going to be just somewhere in Vegas to see the fireworks.
Because I'm pretty sure they do like a pretty big display at every major casino
and resort and stuff.
So I think we're gonna go see it.
But let's go back to earlier this afternoon.
We had snoozing copter with 250.
Thank you snoozing copter.
Can't watch for long because I work tomorrow.
I know we are obligated to watch, but I can't.
I'm sorry.
Please don't ban me like all the others.
Anyway, years back, you told us about a smoothie drink you made every morning.
The only thing I remember was frozen strawberries, I think.
What are the other ingredients?
Also, when was the last time you actually went to the gym?
I'm curious because you still look like you're in shape.
Well, the you're talking about banana.
So Greek yogurt, a banana, strawberries,
and coconut water or milk or almond milk.
I would not do regular milk.
I would do a lighter milk because the banana and the yogurt is already really heavy.
You don't want to really weigh it down.
I used to drink that all the time.
Doctors hate them.
Or if you want to do peanut butter, peanut butter and banana
with the same base of that Greek yogurt and almond milk.
Not as heavy.
It tastes awesome.
You can throw in some whey protein, too, if you really wanted to.
Almond milk is bad.
I can't drink it straight.
Yeah, but almond milk is really, really good to mix with a bunch of other stuff.
Almond milk tastes the most like milk to me
when it's mixed with other things that you usually would mix milk with stuff.
It's a good milk substitute for a lot of things that require milk.
I just said the same thing,
but the second time I actually made it a coherent state.
I translated it for you.
But now I haven't been to the gym in a while.
I walk around a lot, though.
It's so nice out over here.
It's so hot out every day.
I kind of make it a mission to at least get outside and move around and walk around.
So I do stay active, but I'm not lifting weights anymore.
My back is all fucked up.
I can't really can't do it anymore.
I don't know.
Something happened like a couple years ago
and I just started to get really tight back there.
So it's hard to really do much lifting-wise.
I mean, if I can move around, fine.
I can run.
I can jump.
I can dash.
I can slide.
But lifting weights is kind of like off the table, I would say.
Triple jump?
Nah, I can double jump, though.
But C4G, thanks for the 250.
Ignore that last guy and ban them.
We don't ban anybody here unless they do something wrong.
Or they break a rule.
Or I just look at you and go, you're out.
Or if you make fun of me.
Or if you backseat too much.
Or if you disrespect somebody in the chat.
We don't ban anybody here unless you do any of those things.
How much did you bench?
I used to back in the day.
Somewhere around like 2011, 2012.
I could do like 215.
Like three or four times.
And then I had to put it up.
I also weighed.
I was a lot heavier than I am now.
I topped, I think I was like 165 or like 170 or something.
168 when I was at my most stacked up human.
I think like two, it was over 200.
I know it was at least like 200, 215.
That I did at least two or three, like four times.
They say as long as you can do your body weight,
then that's pretty good.
That's actually really good.
I've since come way down.
I mean I'm probably like 155 pounds now.
154 maybe.
Yeah, I was 168.
I'm now like 150.
Maybe a little bit more.
That's great for your weight.
Oh yeah, man.
I used to do 35 pound dumbbells to curl with.
I don't think I could do with two hands.
Pick up a 35 pound dumbbell and put it over my head right now.
I think back at the shit that I was doing and I'm going,
how the how did I do that?
I can't even pick up one.
I was really into it though.
I was super passionate about it.
I was really into it.
I was super into being healthy and eating really, really good
and going to the gym and doing it right.
Trying to do as good form as I can.
Going four or five days a week.
Not working the same muscle groups.
I'm talking Monday is chest.
You know, Tuesday is what you usually do.
Like chest and tris back and bis is what you do.
And then you give your day of rest and you come back and do legs.
You do back core.
I was out of the gym four or five days a week.
I was so into it, but you kind of have to be
to be able to have like real results.
If you want to be, oh, you know, I want to get jacked.
It becomes a part-time job that you have to fulfill.
And it got to the point where I started caring more about
hanging out and making a YouTube video
than going to the gym for three hours.
So really it was making YouTube videos
is what kept me back in the house.
And I was like, no, I don't feel like doing that.
I want to play like GTA four.
I became a gamer.
Yeah, but it's all good.
I started, I still try to save as healthy as I can.
You can be healthy without lifting weights.
As long as you keep yourself fairly active
and you eat right, you'll be all right.
But thank you to C4G again, C4G again for the 250.
Also bots back.
Thanks for clearing it up.
Here's the stats of some previous streams.
If you are curious, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
What happened?
Oh, I know this is this.
I love data.
This is awesome.
I want to go over these because this is great.
Let's go over these charts.
I'm going to put them on the screen.
So we've got these are the amount of plus twos and minus twos
and it's in a chart sense.
Let's get them on the screen so you can see.
This is very interesting.
Here we go.
There's another one.
There's three in total here.
This one is great.
This is my favorite one.
All right.
So this is the deep rock galactic stream.
So as you notice, there's a huge decline in the very beginning here.
And the reason for that is because the stream started
and once we got going, Star and I pretended
that we were just going to sit there silent playing the game.
We were doing the...
Yeah, what do you got?
Yeah, send it over here.
Okay, yeah, we did that for about a half an hour.
Everybody hated it.
Let's see.
I mean, people thought it was absolutely terrible.
And we came right back.
We bounced right back.
I think I fell off the cliff and that's where it just jumped.
It was like five minutes.
Yeah, well, I'm embellishing.
And then near the end here when we started to do the soundboard stuff
really picked up.
That's really funny.
But this one, this is...
What's this one?
This is the Mario Maker.
So this is Mario Maker.
So what happened in the middle that was so funny?
And then what happened at the...
Somewhere an hour before the end of the stream
where it was like, holy shit, I hate this.
And then we bounced way back near the end.
This is all over the place.
It was the car.
That's so funny.
Oh, the McChicken was right at the end.
Right there at the very end.
And this last one was Space Engine and Cook Serve Delicious.
I don't know what happened here.
Still at minus 50.
Well, these are only three that were taken.
There's a lot.
This was a really funny stream.
I think the Flush joke happened, right?
See that first peak?
Yo, then I said...
Yeah, you're right.
I said, Shpee.
Somewhere in there I said Shpee and we rocketed.
We went parabolic after I said Shpee.
There was no stopping it.
That's interesting though.
So what was today?
7.42.
So what was yesterday?
And do we have any idea?
That's not bad.
Yesterday was like 500.
Oh yeah, it was off yesterday, right?
That's so funny.
That's great though.
Thanks for the charts.
It's funny to look at.
It's interesting just to see what works
and what doesn't in real time almost.
It's interesting.
But thanks for the 250.
Thank you, S10W Update for the $5.
Hey, Jerma985 of the hit YouTube channel,
Jerma985.
Back to donate here again after...
Even after the horrifying McChicken eating.
Hope to donate lots more now
and good luck with life.
Enjoy.
Those McChickens were pretty good.
What am I gonna eat tonight?
Something healthy.
I'm talking about lifting weights
and being at the gym.
I need to eat something good.
I'll think about that.
But thank you for the $5, S10W Update.
Appreciate it.
I will do my best.
Good luck with your life too.
Jerma lied about Taco Bell.
Thanks for the $3.
Hey, Jerma.
Can't stick around for the whole stream
but I just saw Spider-Man.
No spoilers.
But it was a super good movie.
I heard it was fantastic.
Yeah, I'm not gonna read anymore.
I don't...
I know there's no spoilers in this message
but I don't want to even say the words...
That word.
The guy that is the bug with eight legs.
But I heard it is fantastic.
Thank you, Jerma lied about Taco Bell.
I'm actually looking forward to seeing it.
I heard it was really good.
Sol Harv.
Thanks for the $2.50.
Hey, Jerma.
For your next burger eating stream,
may I suggest reviewing the new Cheetos and chicken burger from KFC?
It goes great with a cup of coffee to wash it down.
I feel like that's the only opportunity I'm ever gonna have
to solidify that joke in history forever.
Do I eat the KFC Cheetos chicken sandwich
and drink a black coffee?
Just to even take a bite?
Just so I can have it on camera
and know that I did it.
That'll be the next eating food embarrassing stream.
We'll see when that happens.
Jerma lied about Taco Bell.
Thanks for the $2.50.
They say Jerma Defoe.
Jerma Defoe.
Thank you.
Do it quick.
It might be a limited time thing.
You're right.
I'll do it soon.
Oh, Rijian.
Thanks for the $3.50.
Jerma, why are you such a psycho
hurting these innocent kittens and workers?
How would you like it if I walked into your office
and stabbed you midstream?
Here's the thing.
I don't work in a dungeon.
With bones everywhere and bodies and urns.
I haven't eaten three people today.
Some of the fucking monsters out here
have eaten people in the last four hours.
I haven't done that.
You hear that?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, what the hell?
It was just getting started.
It's fireworks.
It's the 4th of July.
Well, it's the 4th of July eve.
Don't you guys know that 4th of July
means a week before and four months after
people still do fireworks?
That's how it works.
But thank you, Rijian, for the $3.50.
Cyanide Zero gave a ton of subs.
I think at least 40 or 50 of them
over the course of the stream.
Hundreds of dollars.
Thank you, Cyanide.
Is Otto okay with fireworks?
Yeah, he's okay.
He's not bad with loud noises
or consistent popping, cracking sounds.
During thunderstorms, he's fine.
Hold on.
Do it again.
I actually got fireworks are legal in Nevada.
So Kim and I have some sparklers
and some little spinny things.
And probably going to just play with them.
That's one thing.
Fireworks were always illegal in Massachusetts.
And it was always like,
oh, look at all these fireworks.
Oh, we can't really do anything.
I'm not even sure sparklers are legal
to buy or own in Massachusetts.
I don't know why.
Because I know that there's like three
different types of fireworks, right?
There is no fireworks.
Fireworks are legal.
There's fireworks that cannot go into the air or explode.
They call them safe and sane.
Those are legal in Nevada.
So you can't know aerials and no explosions.
Everything else is able to be purchased here.
That's the same thing in New York.
Yeah, it's like that everywhere.
There's only a few states, I think,
in the United States that even allow
the purchase and sale of aerial fireworks
and firecrackers and Roman candles.
I don't know.
There's not very many.
Way more states in the United States
have sort of put a leash on fireworks.
But yeah, you'll probably hear it
a few times in the background.
Sir Black Mage, thanks for the 250.
There's a clip here.
I wonder what it is.
German admits he is afraid of pinwheel.
Yeah, I am afraid of pinwheel.
I did say that.
But you have to give me the context of
I'm afraid of 100 pinwheels.
Are you afraid of one Nito-sized pinwheel
or 100 duck-sized pinwheels?
Whatever the thing is that people say.
It doesn't matter.
Thank you to Sir Canine for the five dollars.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dark Souls Randomizer,
the series where I play Dark Souls.
This is going to be a single-player let's play.
And when I say let's play,
I use that term pretty loosely
because I am an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of cheating,
at least I'm hoping.
So grab yourself a nice cup of coffee,
a nice hot cup of cocoa.
I got apple cider here, freshly brewed.
Let me just take a sip.
Oh, that's some...
And then they ran out of space.
Thank you Kermit the Frugue for the three dollars.
Love you and your streams, Jerma.
If you're ever in the mood for more JermaCraft,
call me.
Carson said he would love for you to join
SMP Live, his big Minecraft server for streamers.
People do there.
Please Tim, but they have Shpleef.
Do they have Shpleef?
That's all I care about.
Yes, they do.
Thank you for the three bucks.
And maybe if I ever get the urge to play Minecraft,
I'll hit some people up.
We'll see.
Thank you for the three dollars.
Smelly boy, thanks for the 250.
I honestly cannot believe you allowed yourself
to be killed by Pinwheel again.
This time it was on camera.
Actually recorded broadcast live on this website.
Tar Alecran, thanks for the five dollars.
I think it's pretty obvious after watching you tonight
that you've never actually played this game.
And at the time you beat this game on stream
was actually just pre-recorded footage
with gameplay by a different streamer.
I mean it was a different,
I mean it was a different streamer.
It was me and a different day.
So it was a different me.
Every day when you wake up, it's a new you.
When you go to sleep,
you wake up as a new person, like in your brain.
Every day you get up, you're a new person.
I think you can get banned, of course.
I'm not going to say that.
But thank you Tar Alecran.
I beat Dark Souls Remastered on stream
and most recently beat Sekiro on stream
and also finished The Last Boss, The True Last Boss.
I know a lot of other YouTubers and streamers
that you may have come across gave up or said,
nah, this is too much.
Or they did it like two, three hundred tries.
I did it in 52.
I think that gives me a little bit of a right
to say these things and play Randomizer
and follow a couple of clips.
I think I get the pass there.
I missed Jerma from last Tuesday.
Where's that?
Where's that guy?
But thank you Tar Alecran for the five dollars.
Appreciate it.
Man up.
Thank you, man up for the 250.
Have a McDouble on me.
Not tonight, but I will.
Eventually.
Thank you.
That was man up with Icy Hot.
Bake me home thanks for the 250.
Sir, no, it's the same one.
The fax machine thanks for the 10 bucks.
Scrambled eggs are the best with the shell.
I mean, you have there's a kappa here before this.
Scrambled eggs are best with the shell.
That means it's a joke and it's not real.
Can you eat?
You can eat eggshells, can't you?
You're not like supposed to, but I think you can.
Hard boiled.
You can eat gravel too.
Yeah, but I mean, you can act.
Yeah, yep.
But thank you for the 10 dollars.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you.
The fax machine.
Let's get the credits rolling here.
There was shitload of community subs.
Throw them up.
Thank you everybody.
If you're a sub to this channel, or if you're not, either one.
Here are tonight's subs and resubs.
Much love to you.
Thank you for your continued support of this live stream.
If you play SMP live, you will be famous.
But then I'll be Minecraft famous.
Is that something I necessarily want?
That's the best kind of famous.
Is Minecraft famous?
You already are Minecraft famous.
I am not Minecraft famous.
Speaking of Minecraft, thanks for the sub, Minecraft.
Appreciate it.
How would I beat that?
I made 11 videos on Minecraft and they got like fucking 8,000 views each.
JermaCraft is how I found you.
Anyways, thank you to BakeMeHomeForThe250.
I think we got it already, but it popped up here again.
Trampston, thanks for five dollars.
McChicken part two, McChicken part two.
I'm not going to eat McChickens on stream every night.
That's not going to be a thing I'm going to do.
I mean, that's a pretty hilariously stupid thing to do at the end of your streams.
You're just the McChicken guy?
That's your live stream schtick?
I would start to feel bad every day.
People get hyped in the chat over it,
and people get really excited for the McChicken portion.
All right guys, here it comes.
I got two McChickens tonight.
Here's the McChicken portion of the stream.
Two?
Yeah, you don't just eat one McChicken.
You can't go to McDonald's and just get a double cheeseburger meal.
No, you get a double cheeseburger meal, two McChickens, a large fry, and an apple pie.
You don't just, oh yeah, I'll take a Big Mac meal and that's it.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll take a Big Mac meal and a 10-piece nugget.
You don't just order one thing off that menu, ever, because you know it's not enough.
You know it's too much, but you also know it's not enough.
But we have a couple more here.
We have SirK9 for $2.50, all these bits, and still in Anor Londo.
Omega Low.
Omega Low, the big one.
Man up with Icy Hot, thanks for the $2.50.
I had no idea that eating burgers was a German meme now,
but you should buy a second McDouble on me, for plus two's sake.
I'm not, I gave McDonald's a two out of five last night.
You think I'm gonna be the McDonald's guy?
I told you it was gross.
At least three or four times.
2.8, 2.8 is not free, and 2.8 is not a good score.
That's still under 500.
Well, it's just not, it's just over 500.
That's not very good.
That's like getting a 58 on your math test.
That's not good.
That's still an F.
That's good for me.
Clueless Sniper, thanks for the $2.50.
Right at the end.
And thanks everybody for watching.
These last couple of streams have been kind of insanity.
So we're probably gonna dial it back a little
and relax on the stream on Friday or Saturday.
I have a couple things that I could do.
Hopefully you have enjoyed them.
I've had a lot of fun in these last couple of streams,
even though they were a lightning rod,
like times 10 energy streams.
They've still a lot of fun.
But happy 4th of July to everybody that celebrates it.
I'll be back in a couple of days.
Keep an eye on the sus as of tomorrow night
and you'll have a really good indication
of what the next stream will be.
Take care.
Much love to you.
See you really soon.
Take care, guys.