Good afternoon, good afternoon, good afternoon. Sorry I'm late, sorry.
Something came up last second that I just had to take care of.
Care of it? Everything's good? We're ready to go. Sorry I was, uh, late.
Sorry. Don't apologize, welcome. Hey, thank you. Hey, look at that.
When are we gonna do porn week? Uh, that's every week, man.
Keep apologizing. Where is New Vegas? What do you mean New Vegas?
Like Fallout New Vegas? Are you trying to tell me to continue a playthrough of a
game that I stopped four years ago during my do I like live streaming trial
period? Yes. You know, it's kind of funny.
If I did that same save file is still here. I could probably open it and I'd be
sitting at the door that we were at four years ago.
Should I just open it and pretend like it's been not even a day?
Okay, so last, uh, last week we were here. Pretty cool adventure so far.
I would have no idea where I was even going. I can't do that.
But hello, welcome. We're gonna be doing, uh, I did a poll
before the stream started. We're gonna be doing Psychic Detective.
It is a meaty 3DO game. It is an FMV adventure, from what I understand.
I heard it's crazy and you know how much we love our FMV games on this channel.
You know it as much as I do. This game is three discs long, which back
in the mid-90s, a three to four disc game
was like every Lord of the Rings movie back to back.
That was a huge amount of stuff. It was insane to know that that was the case.
If a game had more than one disc, you knew you were in for it. This is a new mic?
No. I'm just sitting a little closer. Look out, Jerma. This could be a porn game.
It's not a porn game. It's a detective game. It's not a
porn game. Turn your face cam on. Don't have any clothes on?
Don't have a face cam. Sorry, guys. Just imagine what I look like right now.
There's a couple other games that are FMVs that I cannot wait to play on this
ancient dinosaur device of a console. I'm not going to tell you what they are.
You'll experience them with me as we do. Psychic porn.
All right, let's go. Psychic Detective, welcome everybody.
This will be, I do want to say this though, as of today
we're going to put a little cool down period on the 3DO in the last three
streams in a row. So we're going to put the 3DO away for a
week or so. We'll come back to it. It's always here.
It's available. We'll do something else this coming week.
All right, let's go. Psychic Detective. Oh, by the way, I want to make sure I
start saying this more frequently. FTK is not canceled. FTK is going to
happen on October 3rd. That is the date for it.
October 3rd. I think I mentioned the 26th before, but no, no, no, no, no.
October 3rd, 3 p.m. Pacific. It is not canceled.
I saw you on my recommended, on my first, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Saw you on my recommended. This is my first stream. Pog.
Can we get a warm welcome for Poinster? This is their first stream ever.
Phantom. Hey, welcome to your first stream ever.
That's the Pog. We, and by the way, we do this for all new viewers.
He doesn't know that we do this for everybody. Are you ready for the
sing the welcome song? Okay, here we go guys. You know it. You
guys know the lyrics. You guys start. You start. You guys do it first.
Here we go at the same time. Ready? Hey, I know you're new.
Welcome to the stream. Pull up a chair. It's quite the dream.
It's your first time here. Oh, what a joy.
But don't act like the stream is a toy. You.
All right, fuck that. Let's go. No signal.
Okay, you know what's really funny? Can I go off? I'm going to go off right now.
Do you know how exhausting it would probably be for every new follower or
every new subscriber if I had to sing that fucking song?
I would look over and they would be a new sub or something. I'd be like,
oh wait, there's this 10 new subs. Hey, welcome to the stream.
It's just you and I. So he's gone. No, he didn't leave.
He actually left. No, he didn't. He's here. You're going to get a personal
song sung about you and leave? No, I didn't. He didn't leave.
That was a personal directed like welcome song.
Actually, that's kind of weird. I probably would fucking leave too.
I'd probably leave if I came into a stream and I was like, hey,
my first time here and it was like, hey, Germa, welcome to my new stream.
You're a new guy. Everybody sing on the side.
It'd be like, I'm fucking out of here, man.
I just want to relax and just watch TV and eat like french fries.
Like, fuck you. Like, stop talking to me.
I just want to watch the stream, man. I've so overdone it to this person
at this point that now I like they probably I would get back.
This is the most overdone new viewer experience.
Okay, let's go. It's time for psychic detectives.
I have two different drinks here. Does that make me a psycho?
Does that make me a weird person? Yes. Movie. Wait, what do you mean movie?
Why does it say movie? Is this a movie? No, this is a video game, man.
Electronic arts and colossal pictures. It's a fucking nightmare.
Psychic powers. The world is yours to control.
That's a load of crap. What the hell is going on?
I need to turn the...
If I could predict the future, there'd be a few less dead bodies.
We just got a shot. I need to turn the volume up.
There I was, doing what I do best.
Look at that hair. That's my hair.
The old freak of nature routine. Called myself the psychic flash.
Hey, the old folks loved it. Me, I got that.
He's so close. Why are you this close to the audience?
Your grandfather gave this to you on his deathbed.
It's the Joker. It's just the Joker.
He's acting like the Joker, too. He's just sitting there staring at me.
With one shove, she sent my whole spinning out of control.
She showed me how to transmit my psychic self into the consciousness of others.
To see through their eyes, hear through their ears.
The real mind pirate stuff.
What?
Naturally, there was a price.
What's with the cat?
My father just killed himself.
Is he psych... What?
Is he psychically detecting the cat?
He showed me to a family gathering maze and ear.
This guy looks like every family feud host.
Lady, this is only $400. What the fuck is this?
Another special lesson.
All right, deal.
Ugh. Ugh.
What's Black Diamond? Some missing necklace?
Just a game. A silly old Russian game.
His outfit. He's like a fucking circus ringleader.
That's where my father jumped from.
What? Why are we here?
I tell you, Eric. My father was beaten, disgraced.
Too stubborn to give up like that.
Wait, we're going in?
Where are we?
I'm Eric.
That's my sister Monica.
Where are we?
Very cute. Very weak and gullible.
Who's the plastic dress?
Wait, what do I have to touch?
I have to like touch...
Maybe you can find out for me.
Okay, so...
And him?
I don't know. My father had a many...
Why do I feel like we're at like dinner for schmucks right now?
Am I one of the schmucks?
If there's money to be made, he smells it.
Keep an eye on him and Monica.
Where will you be?
What?
Me? You don't have to worry about me.
Okay, we've got people to talk to?
All right, come on.
Are you a friend of Garelia?
No, I want to talk to...
We're going to Moki.
I just... I totally just told her I gotta fuck off.
Uh-oh.
This is the scariest lady ever.
What was that?
Why are we in this scary house?
Okay, we'll...
Oh, we're inside of his head.
We're inside of Moki's head.
Brass ring.
Okay, we're looking for a brass ring.
Should I just stay in...
Okay, what if I stay in this guy forever?
Isn't that sweet?
You put it in the shredder, man.
You don't have to just rip it up in three pieces.
Who... What are we looking for?
Why are we in this guy's head?
We're just sitting there watching a movie.
Yeah, that's us down there, right?
You think you'd puke if you saw yourself walking down the stairs
and looked over at yourself, looking at yourself?
I would fucking puke right now.
Monica.
You should talk to Max.
Max sent me a check and the authority to give you
whatever kind of advance you'd like.
Oh, okay.
The donation of the Vladimir Pozzak collection to Mirage Quest.
Oh, back to Moki.
No, I don't have an option.
I have to be like within laser eye distance of them.
Oh, in my head.
Wait, this is what I see.
Cigar.
What am I...
I'm smoking somebody's cigar?
I must ask you to go.
Your uncle was a big noise.
A real player in the old country.
Paranormal espionage.
Did I just get kicked out?
That's all I'm allowed to say.
But perhaps you would be interested in a little collectible.
Oh, that's what I need.
I want that watch.
He's shameless.
His hands.
He's got like three hands.
Chad.
Oh, what's Chad up to?
Oh, wait.
This is the money.
Chad's got the money.
Are we Chad?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
What is all this shit?
This is like an incantation?
Hi there.
What is going on in this house?
What'd you find?
This is the most fucked up house ever.
Just a little notebook.
This is just improv class the house.
Okay, you got to walk into a room.
And now give me an object.
The book.
Okay.
And then she we're back in Eric's head.
Big knife.
We don't know that.
No, you have your chance.
I don't have any idea what the fuck is going on.
How do we make you sing?
Jesus.
Wait, wait.
A knife.
Knife.
Pick up the knife.
I had one second to look at that.
Take a genius to play it out.
I was coming down.
She was going up.
The door prize was a hunk of blood pudding.
I didn't I'll go away.
I didn't touch anything.
What happened?
Chad sort of made a mess.
Chad made a mess.
Are we leaving?
Please insert disc two.
Okay, let's go ahead.
I'm going to put in disc.
That was a quick.
That was very fast.
So what have we gathered so far?
Hold on.
40 minutes or so.
Where the fuck are they?
Where are these discs?
All right.
What have we gathered?
So far we've gathered that
there's a guy.
Somebody jumped out of a window.
And then we all went to a dinner party at their house
to find out who did it or something.
And then somebody gets stabbed.
There's a ring.
There's a watch.
You know what?
I have no idea.
So just I'm going to put disc two in.
We're going to see what happens.
I don't think can I even get into disc two?
There we go.
I don't have to press a button.
The game has.
Yeah.
I don't understand what you went through.
All the FMVs that are available in one disc.
That seems a little ridiculous.
12 video files on each disc.
All right.
Let's continue the story.
A meaty 3DO game.
Yeah.
Or like this is AI dungeon.
Shot for shot.
What happens next?
Crops got involved.
From the puka lounge to multiple stab wound city.
Courtesy of my libido.
I made a mental note.
From now on only do you brunch with these people.
You sure it was her?
Yeah.
Like I had a front row seat.
But why Chad?
Your father keep a green notebook?
Yeah.
Any idea what was in it?
Not really.
Don't play with me, Lena.
I don't know.
His big secret.
I feel like I skipped to the middle of the movie.
I think Chad was going to sell it to the weasel.
The Sylvia chick had other ideas.
Did we accidentally do the right outcome?
Eric, you're better than I could have hoped for.
Okay, here we go.
So are we good night?
Give me those keys.
I just wanted to take the keys, man.
I just wanted to take the keys.
Hiding somebody.
Shut up.
Who is he?
Sergey.
And Sergey is.
Not my lover.
Not my plaything.
Just a poor defenseless man.
Did I lose?
Did I touch the keys?
Poor defenseless man.
So how-
All right, we're gonna follow her.
I have trouble doing exactly what I'm told.
And I hate being lied to.
Okay, she was going to bite my head off.
Now what?
But that's better than getting it blown.
I'm really close.
Did you notice I'm just following her?
Did she not look?
She doesn't know I'm behind her.
She has no idea that I followed her.
Okay, that was way easier than it even seems to be in like GTA.
Knock on the door.
Don't look so surprised.
I mean, I followed you all the fucking way here.
Are you satisfied?
Did you find all the dirty truth you have?
That puppet.
Let's touch the puppet and see what happened.
Kiki dance.
Who did this to him?
What?
Well, who do you think?
The great Vladimir.
How could he?
Oh, he was so pleased with himself.
Such an elegant solution to such a messy situation.
The two of you-
What did she say?
Vladimir?
Oh, please.
Wait, I can go with somebody.
Let's go in her head.
Why is that so funny?
I guess you have gerbils that are running on a wheel.
I guess it's hilarious.
What the hell is going on?
Can't we help him?
Is he dead?
Did I just like psychic him to death?
Isn't that the thing that they keep the bingo balls in?
We need all four.
And you think I can find the other three?
I just hope you're ready.
I need to find four of these magic cylinders.
At least we have the actual thing we need to do for the game.
Don't do it.
Wait, it's-
Okay, that's-
That's-
It's improv.
It wasn't anything.
Oh, shit.
Where do I go?
Oh, in Max's head.
There's a little hot shot inside my head.
Eric Fox.
That name means nothing to me.
He's leaving fingerprints all over my mind.
I just changed the channel.
How can you tell?
You'd never understand.
Hey!
I'm not all tricked out and psychic,
but I'm damn good at what I do.
Smoked you out.
Maximum sub bonabim.
What about Eric?
I'm going to squash you like a sow bug.
What happened?
Aggression.
You just spat me out.
You can use it.
You can read me.
You can read all of us.
You can go anywhere.
Oh, you little innocent boy.
It was mine.
He gave it to me.
Are those stink lines?
Is she like smelling my body?
You did that.
Wait.
A dad just made her be aggressive.
But I think maybe you deserve it.
What?
There is a chance to spy, to go anywhere.
Read Psych-lana.
Wait.
Did I just?
Did I?
This guy.
Who the fuck is this?
He's not even here anymore.
Did that even happen?
You're under arrest for the murder of Sergian Olsenko and Chad Zatowski.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
Anything you say can.
How many times are they going to put cuffs on me?
That was like five different cuffs.
So you like to read me?
What were you doing in the house?
Did you get the knife?
Like to cough turkey?
Sure.
Every Christmas.
You did a real number on Chad.
Not much darker meat was it?
I know who did it.
It was that chick who runs the tea room, Sylvia.
She killed him over a notebook.
Can you believe that?
You saw her?
These guys are touching.
How small is this room?
Is this an airplane bathroom?
He was nailed.
He was a fall guy.
He was going to jail.
Oh my god.
I guess we're going on to...
There is no losing.
We're moving on to the final chapter of the game.
This is like a roguelike.
I could just do it again.
Let me get this right.
So we didn't catch the killer.
That's what you have to do.
We caught it the first time.
But when that guy walked in with like two bleeding breasts,
we have no idea what happened to him.
And the guy had a gun.
We didn't catch it.
Well, let's see what happens.
You know, I'm going to keep these discs at the ready.
They need to be available.
Main character looks unreasonably sweaty.
I mean, yeah.
All right, we're in jail.
It's like I'm standing still.
Shit, I missed enough.
I could have gone in that guy's head.
Too weird to lie.
Detective, could you take that outside?
Detective, can you please not like light your nose on fire?
Why are you holding a lighter up to your eyebrows?
That's kind of strange.
We're going to go courier.
Holy shit, dude.
He drove like a type A wired on coffee and stressed to the max.
Come on.
Huh?
Jesus.
Yak, yak, yak.
He cursed the world, cut off everybody,
and had this false chipper voice for customers.
All righty.
Just sign right there on the Dipsy Doodle.
All of us are working.
Can we do the speed limit, please?
Excuse me.
Hello.
You're bigger than me.
Not much.
A deeply disturbed head.
We all do this.
The psychic detectives can't be choosers.
I do this.
Dream, dream, dream, dream, dream, dream, dream, please.
Not that, but I do the sounds.
Those noises, I do.
All right, what's in the package?
So nice.
He's got all the...
All right, we're going to Bagman.
Courier's walking by.
I'm Bagman now.
I just...
Get a life, dirtbag.
Wait, I can just jump into his head to laugh at him?
The rest became a blur.
What was the point of being able to jump into him?
Green light, green light.
He whistled at women and ate bags of pork rinds.
I couldn't stand it much longer.
Even jail was sounding better than...
Hey, somebody likes your hot shots.
He just pulled me out of that.
Sorry we kept you, kid.
Why is he in jail with me?
Oh, why is everybody in...
Why is she in prison?
Even the receptionist was in prison.
I think we should see how the old woman is doing.
What do you think?
I think we forget about her.
Who the kid?
Papa Vladimir?
He hid the fourth collector.
Am I going to have to put up on disc three?
How could you?
Eric, you are a genius.
I know.
Okay, here's where the...
Oh, there's Bagman.
Is it active?
Can you tell?
Barely.
But no tricks.
Just get it for me.
Can't go into Bagman again.
That's unfair.
Holy shit.
Okay.
But you're a fine looking couple.
You know, I tell you,
I get some butt ugly people in here sometimes.
It's a pleasure just to look at you.
Let me just look at you.
Can I see that metal crystal beer mug?
Oh, we get...
You can have it.
Some old bitch brought it in, I tell you.
You guys are a lot more fun than she was.
Two out of four.
Have a nice day.
Who's that easy?
Why would you say that?
Hey, do you want to get to hold it?
Can I hold it?
We don't need...
It's not like a dog
that you just got out of the pet store.
We can do this.
No, come on.
Let me hold him.
Okay, good.
Now we got...
Find them.
Tell me what they're doing.
Madame T.
Idiot.
You take too long.
Have your only hope.
She's talking to herself
but she know we're in her head.
What did you learn?
With your lady's steam.
What old lady?
Old lady's a pain in the key store.
Fine.
We'll give her the precious student.
Okay, so we're gonna go see the old lady.
Wait.
There's something I want to try.
We only need two more of these.
What are you trying?
Papa.
Triangles.
What is going...
What's he doing?
It was Max.
He was here.
Walk pattern.
It was Bugleberry.
It was Bugleberry
laughing at somebody
how bad they hated the new carpet
that just got delivered.
What the fuck am I doing?
It was already open.
It was clearly already open.
Case.
Okay.
Shards.
Workbench.
Let's get the pin.
Okay.
What's with the flashing lights by the way?
Where are we?
Shards.
Wait, he just broke one.
One of the spirits?
Or was it open...
Workbench.
Okay.
No.
Go to Madame T.
We go to Madame T?
Lexi killed your dad.
Lexi?
Lexi, Max.
Same asshole.
How do you know?
Why do you think I touched him?
To sniff my fingers?
What a weird thing to go to first.
I'm sorry.
He was here.
He wanted the fourth collector.
And he torched the hell out of Vladimir.
Uh-oh.
Madame T.
We're too late.
Just for me, Eric.
Make her...
...wist.
No.
Hello on the old lady's face.
Oh.
Find what you can.
Find what I can.
Rip her to pieces.
Feed her or fry her.
You think you can use me?
Bend me?
For practice?
Get out!
Oh shit.
We blew it.
Get out before I take a turn.
You tell your next mirage.
We are ready.
Didn't she kill the person?
Anybody tried to talk to Moki lately?
What is Moki?
Uh-oh.
What is this game board?
Did we just get three?
We got a third one?
What in the name?
This is no game of checkers and pieces.
You must pick thoughts, Eric.
Go on.
This kind of...
The guy kind of looks like my dad.
So I'm just gonna pick him.
How about the skull?
Cigarette.
A shoe.
Yes, always pick the shoe.
Vladimir, he loved the shoe.
Always the shoe.
How about...
And you?
As long as I am alive.
Cool.
She's playing her pieces now.
Is this like auto chess?
Are they gonna fight?
I don't understand this.
You move first.
That is what this is.
I attack the shoe.
I'm gonna use the shoe to attack this person.
Got it.
They are the same.
Nobody wins till the next move.
Too bad for you.
It's my turn.
Okay.
So you're gonna go with lady versus dad.
You kill dad.
We take turns.
One of us will lose everything.
You understand?
Kill him.
Brat bastard, to be my laptop.
So what?
Own the fear.
Find the scar.
Free the girl.
Steal the kiss.
You're a little cocky.
I think.
Hi, noon babe.
Big showdown.
Eric, I don't think you realize.
What?
That I could walk away a fritter?
That I'm insane to do this?
What don't I realize?
Andy Samberg and original Luke Skywalker Mark Hamill got fused together.
Light a fire.
That really got me rocking.
I still have no idea what's going on.
So we now have to do her bidding.
Join the war on depression.
That's okay.
I mean, yeah, but that was back to disc one.
Holy shit.
We go backwards?
Let's make sure this is disc one.
I got it.
We're in a loop.
I don't think it's a loop.
I think they just compiled all the video files alphabetically on each disc.
Here we go.
Movie.
Is this the guy from Command and Conquer?
Wait, why'd she just fall down?
Wouldn't she just standing right next to him?
Would she do that?
She went and found a painting of him.
Why'd she just punch him in the face?
I don't even know.
I left her alone.
I have no fucking idea.
I left her for him.
I saw like a Mazel Tov thing and then...
What's he doing?
Let's take him out.
I want to go.
What do you mean take him out?
Then go.
But I'm holding this.
Maximum me.
Maximum you.
Is that like a self-help guru?
We're just walking into this guy's...
He's crossed-armed waiting for us.
This is the kind of reaction you have and the noises you make when you first pull up
photo booth for the iPad.
It's true.
Everybody played their part perfectly.
This is how you do it.
No wasted motion.
No parlor tricks.
Say goodbye to the girl.
Go to the car.
Harder.
Don't you want to see her cry?
No.
You think I need your help?
Oh wait.
You think I want you watching me?
He's psychic detecting me.
You're a cheerleader, a throw-ruck.
Now move!
Go!
Damn it.
Good boy.
Daddy's good boy.
Nobody wants to burn you.
Just bring me the toy.
These are the good times.
Bad ending.
The old man knew I was the best.
There was never any question about that.
The question was how to keep me happy.
You can't turn referee into a trendy style.
I'm sorry.
That fucking best don't work.
I made him look brilliant.
Surrendered Jim Chujinka.
Miss Layla.
But she is so stubborn.
And I get so pissed off.
Oh not this again.
Okay.
Cigarette versus, I don't know, a metronome and Bill Murray.
Versus, and the toy.
There's no shoe.
Oh wait, he had a shoe already.
Your move.
Try to be interesting.
Okay, we're gonna go cigarette.
No, we're gonna go toy onto shoe.
It's my game now.
The old man can rot.
I make the rules.
It means whatever I want it to mean.
Okay, we're gonna go, uh.
You're a butcher.
I'm a surgeon.
Lancing and popping all the little pimples that stain my natural glory.
So this has been just a psychic fight between the two of us the whole time.
A lot of real estate for a lucky man.
Sorry, I still have the, I still have the metronome.
It blocked.
Why'd she do it, Max?
I don't know.
She gave up.
She couldn't stand to see you become such a monster.
Okay, this is important.
Metronome versus shoe?
Or metronome versus lady?
I don't know.
Shoe.
Fuck, they canceled each other out.
Canceling each other out like smothering a silent stream.
War, you are so handsome.
So full of blood.
Of the balls.
I'm not even playing cards.
Double war.
If only I could die.
I win.
Kiki, I win.
Kiki!
Okay, so that's a bad ending.
Moki's playmate.
The village idiot.
This little piggy.
Maximum eric.
Double war.
Pooka lounge blues.
Lexi's last laugh.
Change heads.
No third chances.
Pretty bracelet.
The healing hothead.
The big kiss.
And the grand slam.
If you turn the menu over,
you'll see our list of our beverages.
And some alcohol.
You can order as well.
Start it a little bit.
Buck that one up a little.
It's okay.
Come on!
Give me that one.
Did you play black diamond with madam?
Tikonov?
Did I?
Belvages.
Yeah, yeah, belvages.
And now what?
Is that it?
Do we do it again?
All right.
Now that I know what's going on,
I want to try to do it again.
Now that I know what's happening,
I want to try.
I want to do it one more time.
Do you?
No, but yes.
We have to try a separate outcome.
Here we go.
We get invited to the dinner party.
That's my sister, Monica.
Okay, Monica.
He was hoping to come in first.
I can't believe it.
Your sister doesn't waste much time.
We have to get into Sylvia's head
because we're going to watch her kill the guy.
Meet him at the tea room at 10 o'clock.
I can change channels.
This is just in real time.
I miss the good times.
Monica, focus.
Max wants to make you an offer.
To me?
Mirage Quest would like to handle
your father's collection.
Which one?
Tea room, 10 o'clock, yep.
Max, Mirage will personally help you.
I could accept no less than 200.
Have you no shame, idiot?
It's just a giant twister spinner.
It's not ready for twister, you bastard.
We do that after our dessert drinks.
Okay, here we go.
Play Black Diamond with her.
All right, Black Diamond.
Felt like a good time to get acquainted with dad.
What worked in the Pooka Room
was bound to work around here.
The house had seen better days.
Better days, worse days.
It was just starting to give a big wet kiss
to the rotten days.
And there was stuff all around keeping secrets.
I wanted to find more.
Window.
He threw him out the window.
Yep.
I must ask you to go.
Your uncle was a big noise.
A real player in the old country.
Paranormal espionage.
We have to go to Chad.
But perhaps you would be interested
in a little collectible.
Chadster, shame on you.
This is Chad.
All right, stay with Chad.
She comes in and she stabs him.
Save him.
Can I?
But not to touch.
Oh, shit.
I just jumped onto the game board.
We're not going to see Chad die.
You are bold, disobedient.
That is good.
You will need to be reckless.
This is a Christopher Walken character.
He was lexing me up in hell for all I care.
What'd he do?
He was Vladimir's most brilliant pupil.
It's like SNL skit.
We first to learn how to destroy the black diamond.
Oh, she's going to teach me how to play.
Bash the hell out of a kitty cat?
Real brilliant.
Child is a symbol of the real power.
Time is right.
Oh, she could sense the murder.
Who is in the study?
Sleazy Chad.
Quickly, go to him.
What are you doing?
Get, should I get out?
Give me the inkblot.
Why do we call him Sleazy Chad?
Can't we just call him Chad?
She was hitting decibels dangerous to psychics and dogs.
Seemed like a good time to find my lovely escort.
What the hell is going on?
Dead body, lots of blood.
Your sister thinks I did it.
Decibels does not equal frequency.
Give me a break.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah, so?
All right, here we go.
We're on the right track.
This time, I'm going to stay as Bagman.
I'm not going to change from Bagman this time.
I want to be Bagman for the rest of the playthrough.
No, shit, I think I misplaced the second disc.
No, shit, that's Jurassic Park.
It looks the exact same.
Where'd it go?
Oh, no.
Disc three, that's disc one.
Where's disc two?
This is why I fucking hated having multiple discs.
You could always just get to the same part of Final Fantasy VII
before you had to stop.
Right before you met Kat-Sith.
We got spoilers.
It's a character in the game.
What are you talking about?
All right, these are both right here.
I got them right in front of me.
It's not, it's Kate, not Kat.
Kat, write nothing back.
Lousy party.
I sat there knowing two things dead certain.
Laynen was going to drag me in deeper
and I was going to follow like some over-sex schnauzer.
All right, should I not touch the bracelet this time?
Obtahoka, what's that mean?
It means stop it.
All right, kiss me sound whacked.
Your dad really did jump out the window.
You sound whacked.
Not exactly suicide.
What was it?
I don't know.
As someone was messing with his head.
That's not possible.
What's not?
Well, you know.
This is some ugly ass seat covers.
I'm still trying to get used to it.
Yeah, right.
You sure look busted up about it.
So are we good night?
All right.
What's Monica?
Just a little more.
I'm gonna let her go.
I do not trust this mirage quest.
You're going?
I have to.
Don't ask why.
Just hate.
I don't like the rules.
What?
Eric.
Maybe I want to know why.
People are in danger.
Let's be specific.
Lexi, Anna, all my cousins, little children.
Just trust me.
I have to follow Monica.
I might come by later.
Bring the boyfriend.
Bring the whole box of dirty secrets.
If there's a knife in my back, throw it in the sink.
I'll do it in the morning.
What?
What do you mean if there's a knife in my back?
I got something in my eye.
Should I follow her?
I'm gonna try to get a different outcome this time.
All right.
We're gonna just go inside of her head.
Something's in my eye.
It's horrible.
It's like a knife in my eye.
What?
How are you?
Mokie found dead.
You're that psychic kid.
Flasho.
Flash in the pan.
I've seen the act.
I'm gonna get arrested.
To my pal, Mokie.
Listen, you little putz.
You're flying blind.
You need Mokie.
Mokie knows the dirt.
I think we need Mokie.
I got it stored in my cheeks.
That would explain the breath.
Listen, you do me a little job.
I clue you in.
Oh, shit.
You say, Foxy, time's a-
No, no, no.
We're gonna go with Mokie.
It's maybe a mistake.
Who is this guy?
Where do you fit in?
I ran a little office.
Code name, Svengali.
You're a spook?
I'm a broker.
Lexi wants it effect.
I bring the dough.
He brings me one of these.
Then what happened?
He grabbed two and flew.
Too bad his chopper didn't.
These photos are huge.
I'm standing in Finland, my juts in my hands.
And a Svengali.
So that leaves two collectors.
He's not only psychic, he can count.
All right, let's get to work.
Here's the gig.
You piggyback inside and get to Max Mirage's table.
Main room, far left corner.
Yep.
It's not like I use a map.
Hey, I wouldn't know.
I'm not psychic.
I don't have the sexy gift.
I just come from a clean straight shot home
where nobody mess me up.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what it means.
I know things.
As usual.
Sexy.
Okay.
Is there opportunity?
There's a phone call coming in.
Fake it.
Two minutes.
Be there for it.
And don't screw me.
It's a phone call.
Did I, I didn't fake it?
He's still sitting here?
Psychic bastard, where are you?
Inside?
Have we crossed the room?
Oh, I'm faking being inside.
Kill him.
Yeah, I'm with you.
How to play.
Let's hear it.
You put the fear of God in him.
Why does it go smoke?
Anyone hear him talking roosties?
Just the whole damn room.
You're a lying little punk.
Maybe I couldn't get there in time.
Maybe you're full of crap.
Why don't you go peep the psychic slot?
That's about your speed.
What?
And if you're thinking of taking a ride in my head.
It wouldn't hurt that much.
That would not even really hurt.
That'd be slightly irritating.
Wait, we just got telltale.
No.
Psychic pizza.
We know when you're hungry.
Okay, let's get this part right.
This guy ends up with like three stab wounds in his chest.
We have to stop it.
Kiki's the, Kiki's the toy.
Well, who do you think?
This guy gets murdered.
We have to follow him around.
He's so pleased with himself.
What's his name?
Such an elegant solution to such a messy situation.
The two of you he didn't approve?
Oh, please.
I just don't want to explain.
All right.
Yeah, that's the four device.
He laughs at the rodents.
He died.
Kiki is the doll.
Can't we help him?
Okay, here we go.
This is where it all goes to hell.
Is how I fucked it up last time.
We're going to jump to somebody else here.
We need all four.
And you think I can find the other three?
I just hope you're ready.
Help him.
I'm going to try.
Because last time I didn't go to the old lady.
We came back here and there's a bunch of dead people.
Okay.
All right.
Max.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
No, shit.
We left for two seconds, man.
I just like in the time it took me to wash my hands in the bathroom.
You're under arrest for murder of Sergei Nosenko and Chatskovsky.
He died.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to literature.
Can I go back?
Anything you say can and you'll be used against you in a court of law.
I went to the same guy.
Redo.
I think I'm okay.
I think I'm ready.
How long have you known Chatskovsky?
Why didn't Lena want you at the house?
You boffing her, kid?
You want to be boffing her?
What kind of game is she running?
She's looking for a psycho collector.
A whole bunch of people are looking for her.
Her dad made him four of them.
They're unbelievable.
It's kind of like some crystal hugging hop head.
Guys, I know this is hard to believe.
There was only one way to slip.
Somebody said cigarettes are cool.
Yeah, I have a cigarette.
Everybody smokes inside.
Everybody has yellow curtains and yellow stained ceilings.
No wonder.
A realtor is going to come in and say the property value dropped by like
40 grand because the whole house is yellow.
I smoke in the house.
I think I can still salvage it, though.
I really think I can.
I can't believe the exact thing.
Dude fucking died again.
And that guy came in with a gun.
He didn't even shoot anybody, though.
All right, I'm going to get this right.
Here we go.
Ready and go.
Shit.
No.
Back.
I don't suck.
Why did I click that?
I tried to piece the night back together.
That psychic slushy cup collector had torqued me sideways.
And something was trying to bubble up.
I had done this.
No.
All right.
Let's go somewhere else.
Can I psychic somewhere else?
I never trespassed again until last night.
And like a sick joke, he threw me in the closet.
I think we still get out.
There was squat to do.
Hard to keep the mind sharp.
I thought about all the women I'd ever slept with.
What?
All the women I wish I'd slept with.
All the women who called me shallow.
Is this what you care about?
And then I thought about like, you know, what the plan was going to be.
Oh, we had a new follower just came in.
A new viewer.
Welcome him.
Welcome.
Okay, this is it.
Opportunity here.
Wait, it's different.
Bokey.
Sort of psychic seal of approval.
Make sure my collector ain't a fake.
Come on, kid.
Clock's a ticking.
What do you think?
Yeah, we're going to go.
This is white hot.
We snag a collector.
We're big league.
Psychic mercenaries.
Eyes on the road, please.
That collector belongs to Lena.
The hell it does.
I shelled out cash four years ago.
So you say.
Don't you get it?
Lexi never died.
A face job and a lounge act worse than yours.
Max Mirage.
No, Wayne Newton.
Come on, kid.
Get with the beat.
That ponytail.
Okay, here we are.
And Sylvia.
He's very small.
What are you doing?
Harry.
I didn't know he's that small.
Ask you the same question.
Strictly insurance.
Make sure you got the genuine goods.
You ready?
No, I got to tape my ankles.
Let her rip.
I'm way taller than that.
Okay.
You can go weirder.
What?
Much weirder.
Take the lint out of your back pocket and stuff it into a chicken breast and eat it.
Give me the collector.
Well, let's get weird.
Somebody call the fire department.
Let's bail.
Oh, hey.
Sorry.
It's yours.
What?
Fuck.
Get a grip.
Try short.
Whose limo is this?
This wasn't the deal.
You're right.
Run.
Yeah, I was a coward and he was toast, lightly buttered and burnt to a crisp.
Max Mirage knew all the black diamond tricks, but he was never going to share them.
What is this?
It just went up on the curb.
I've been looking for you for hours.
Sorry, I was trying to help Moki.
What happened?
Fried rice.
Max has three collectors.
He's a lexian disguise.
What's new with you?
Monica.
How do we get out of this mess?
By making Q stronger.
I got to get stronger.
Okay.
Yeah, here we go.
Back to the mansion.
She has to see it alone and I'll wait in here.
Wait.
Look.
Come here.
It's here.
The fourth collector.
Please, Eric.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
I've missed them all.
I missed them all.
I didn't know what to do.
I was going to go to Madame T.
Jeremy, you stink.
Hey, I'm not going to get the same ending.
He had the case hidden away.
It's going to be the same ending.
It's not going to be the same ending.
He's strong because he has more of those collectors.
I need all four to beat him in the mind game.
All right, let's go to Madame T.
While we're still time.
Lexi killed your father.
How do you think?
I don't touch stuff so I can sniff my fingers.
Lexi is Max.
He came here with a collector,
started frying Vladimir inside out.
Did they say Lexi is Max with like plastic surgery?
He said he got his face changed and stuff.
And then did he say that?
I'm confused by that.
Anna.
Oh, right.
Smothering the old lady.
I'm going to work me over, Clash.
What do I do?
Is that considered a promotion?
Zip it, Fox.
I don't blame him.
Monica's a cute little thing.
Unforced beauty.
Only 21.
I'm not biting.
She and Max, we're talking a serious item here.
We're talking ransom.
That's about all.
You want her back, you bring the fourth collector.
And of course, I decided to break her neck just to piss you all.
I saved her.
How could you, Eric?
No, you do good.
See?
You see the itch.
You love the itch.
She will betray him.
I think we just...
Get the collector.
Go to Max.
Challenge him the game.
Why not get the collector?
Hide for Max.
Play with the collector.
He is too powerful.
If you do not stop him, he will hunt you like a dog.
I never got to practice.
Find the scar.
Choose me if you can.
I'll choose her.
It doesn't make sense.
Not all the games make sense.
It's a Christopher Walken character.
Let me try it.
You must not deplete yourself.
She's in the car?
I'm the hope, okay?
The old lady said, Eric, you're the boss.
You play Lexie.
You put your ass on the hibachi, not your bossy burnout sidekick.
No, I don't want to confront him, though.
I'm sorry we have to fight.
Choose her and the shoe.
Should I?
Should we go in there, though?
Or should we do something else?
Because look, it's like, oh, go get him.
We don't have to, though, do we?
Fuck you, game.
Okay, so what's the play here?
It's Madame T, shoe, cigarette, cigarette.
It's a walkthrough.
I guess I could, couldn't I?
Does it really matter?
Let's see.
Does anybody even have a walkthrough for this game?
Okay, if I remember this part.
Don't squeeze me out.
But she's a Karelian and so photogenic.
Okay, let me see.
Oh, tricks to play Black Diamond.
Anna, the kite, Monica, or Lena are powerful.
Monica's weakness is with the doll and Moki.
And Lena is a draw with the doll and Sergi.
I think I would ever figure this out on my own.
Hey, I left her alone.
I'm scared.
I left her for him.
Queen B is all hot and bothered.
I gotta rub that itch.
If you must.
Just let me hang on to this.
We're trying a different tactic.
Wait in there.
I got no time for catfights.
Now move.
Am I telling her to wait while I go spend time with this girl?
Wait, what?
You know, I'm rooting for you way deep down.
Can you help me beat Max?
Oh, right.
Creamsicle Moki?
Okay.
Which one of these is your favorite?
Soldier.
Good.
I'll tell you what.
You can have it, but I need to know what happened to you.
Scary.
What happened to him?
Why is he like three?
Do you remember where you were?
Do you know where Eric Fox is?
I'm here for me to adore there.
There's nobody in this audience.
Play your little hide and seek.
It's megalomaniac.
Only one game matters.
I don't think so.
What just happened?
When he's properly cooked.
Wait, we were just dead.
You took your time, Jim Chushika.
But you gave me all four.
Who's that dude?
Edik Tartu, Lexi.
Go on, get her out of here.
I want my sister.
But I'm so very fond of the Bozark family.
We were too busy watching the little kid play with toys.
Can we sort of skip the male bonding?
As you wish.
The old man only cared about results.
Total neuralytic paralysis.
But how do you destroy someone mentally?
You take their fear.
Okay, what is he afraid of?
Traumas and nightmares and turn them up.
Full volume, a hideous marching band at the back of the brain.
All very amusing with rabbits and mice and half dead soldiers.
When two people know what's happening.
Okay.
Two talented people.
It's really a most fascinating game.
Two.
You have your thoughts.
I have mine.
Three.
And winner takes...
Four.
He activated the four pillars.
Here we go.
Okay.
So who is it?
Who's Anna?
The cat.
He's afraid of the cat.
He's gonna fear cats.
Go on.
Pick a pretty picture.
Madame.
Definitely Madame.
We need Madame in there.
She said use her.
I think he's afraid of cats.
Cigarette?
I think I'm gonna use the cat.
Okay.
Now what else?
Which one of these is Monica?
Which one of these is Lena?
The shoe?
There is no shoe.
Cigarette?
Or skull?
All right.
We got one more choice here.
Left or right?
I don't know which one of these is who.
Skull?
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Your move.
My move.
Try to be interesting.
Okay.
So cigarette versus...
Cat versus cigarette.
No.
Cat smoke cigarette versus doll.
Cigarette versus...
Uh...
Shoe.
There's no shoe.
You want me to hum the Jeopardy theme?
Don't let the cat smoke.
I'm not.
Old woman to red square.
Okay.
Old woman to red square?
Yes.
Got it.
Good.
All right.
Good move.
No!
It means whatever I want it to mean.
Cat dead.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Now we need...
Uh...
Cigarette ver...
I don't know.
Old lady versus doll?
Or late girl versus doll?
Cigarette versus skull?
Cigarette versus skull.
Yes.
I would be paralyzed as well.
I'm just wondering who cares in all caps.
Cigarette on lady?
On cigarette on lady?
Oh, they canceled each other out.
Shit.
A lot of real estate for a landmine.
Okay.
Come on.
Oh!
All right.
We got old lady versus doll.
This is all we can do.
This is it.
Come on.
Yes!
I win.
Why is he three feet tall?
Oh.
Never mind.
Okay.
Conclusions.
Uh...
Oh.
I got...
I know what...
I know what this is.
I get it now.
I get it.
These are all the endings.
That makes sense.
Sure.
Okay.
So we had double war last time.
Oh no.
What did we have last time?
The big kiss.
The grand slam.
No third chances.
Double war.
Maximum Eric.
What's the big kiss?
I have no idea.
No shit, dude.
Is it that obvious?
We want Maximum Eric.
I want...
I don't know how to do that.
So this is the only walkthrough that I could really...
One of the walkthroughs that I found
gave like a bunch of just like random info
and then at the end says
for different endings,
you can try to play this game again.
Sorry if you find difficulty with this walkthrough.
And then that's it.
Who the fuck was gonna make a walkthrough for this game?
I can't...
I don't know.
I'm not gonna be able to get Maximum Eric.
Hold on.
All right.
Maximum Eric ending.
Psychic Detective.
Psychic Detective strategy guy.
I don't know.
Maximum Eric time.
YouTube it.
Nobody has this on YouTube.
Cheat code central.
Due to the interactive nature of this title,
there are many ways to complete the game.
The game can finish in one of several endings.
Although the following walkthrough
may not be the most optimal,
it does expose most of the major plot themes.
Note the solution branches at several points
in order to reach different endings.
Okay.
Hold on a minute.
So the Grand Slam solution is the best ending.
They go...
I think these are ranked
in how good of an ending they are.
If you want to know,
Moki's Playmate is you play the entire game
without making a single choice.
You just let it do whatever it's going to do.
That's how you get that ending.
So, I mean, I don't...
We wait at the...
We want to go back and just watch the whole thing
to see what happens.
Watch it again.
Okay.
All right.
Let's see.
Let's at least get the worst ending in the whole game.
Okay.
I'm seeing a lot more yeses than I see nos.
Look, you can't just write...
You can't just write...
Fuck off.
Do them all.
I'm not going to do them all.
All right.
What's the Village Idiot?
Hold on.
Maximum Eric solution.
Yeah, that's real specific shit
in a lot of these later endings.
No.
All right.
We're going to do the dogshit ending.
Who owns the secret room?
I don't know.
I'm just going to sit here back here
and drink some coffee and hang out.
Make us click the ending we want.
Guys, I can't even get the solutions
to these endings.
There's so many of them
and none of them have any guides.
And the game is such a mess
that I can't do them all.
Okay, here we go.
I am going to put the controller down.
I'm not going to touch anything.
See what happens.
Here we go.
That's my sister, Monica.
Cute.
Very cute.
Very weak and gullible.
Who's the plastic dress?
Maybe you can find out for me.
Thank you for streaming.
You make a lot of...
And Tim.
Oh, thanks.
I don't know.
That's Moki, right?
There's money to be made.
He smells it.
Keep an eye on him.
So I just don't...
And Monica.
...pour it over.
I don't warg into anybody.
So what happens?
I just stand around?
Normal man ending.
Yeah, I'm just a guy.
We missed this part.
What a shitty game.
Holy...
Oh my God.
You made a board and don't have any rules?
And then you're selling it as a board game.
This lady had found her niche.
House party from hell.
Not even a decent bean dip.
I was getting itchy fingers.
I went fishing for knickknacks.
About nine steps up.
What'd you think?
I couldn't tell.
You keep moving.
Even when you trespass.
Yeah, I like...
I love a good bean dip, too.
Driving into our part of you is asleep.
Hey, no one does autopot like Eric Bach.
I do.
There he is again.
Still don't know him, huh?
Oh, just some greasy little man.
Not like you, my sweet boy.
That's who he's talking...
That's who she's talking about.
Felt like a good time to get acquainted with dad.
What worked in the pookaloo was bound to work around here.
The house had seen better days.
Better days, worse days.
It was just starting to give a big wet kiss.
Dude, when we get to the point where the guy dies in that room,
we're gonna get to see it this time.
There's a lot of shit here that we did not look at.
We just looked out the window and then ran down the stairs.
Ten to one.
Secbethpah meant confidential.
That sounded like a good time.
Didn't anybody crack a smile in this country?
Doesn't Moki show all these photos here?
Maybe this was Papa Scrapbook of golden memories.
So how come I had a full-on case of the ripple in the ions?
These people were running a game.
A game I couldn't quite see.
Yeah, remember Moki shows all these pictures?
He stole them from here.
Okay.
I got more than I bargained for.
Like sneaking into someone else's nightmare.
Feeling right at home.
What the fuck are these drawings?
Who drew these?
I must ask you to go.
Your uncle was a big noise.
A real player in the old country.
Paranormal espionage.
That's all I'm allowed to say.
But perhaps you would be interested in a little collectible.
Chester, he's shameless.
Maybe I was trying too hard.
Maybe I stubbed my brain on something.
Because I was hearing voices.
Big time.
That's right.
Come this way.
All the way.
Time to pay me a visit.
Weren't we in somebody else's head at this point?
Let's walk around in a circle.
I am Ikunos.
Madame Ikunos.
This was the tutorial that we missed.
Quite the spread.
We don't clean up after this lady.
She's got like five empty coffee containers.
Oh.
Well.
That's interesting.
Never mind.
I didn't say that.
The one with the gift, smell it.
Yeah.
You smell anything in here, you've got your own gift.
I made a mental note.
Be less amusing.
Did I say she smells?
Come and sit.
But not to touch the game.
It is bad.
The devil itself.
What happened?
I didn't touch anything.
Bravo.
A marvelous raw talent.
Thanks.
You cannot do this with everybody.
Only with another psychic mind can you explore and talk.
Or do the nasty things.
I think I'll take a rain check.
And only another psychic mind can show you.
She's trying to hit on me here?
And only some of us can, you know, do the sex in our heads.
I'm one of them.
I'm available.
There's only three people on earth that can do this.
How can you?
You think it is a big joke?
Playing with the power.
Oh, come on.
It's a living.
Mental sleight of hand.
It is more.
You are the only one who can stop him.
Stop who?
Where is Chad?
In the study.
Quickly.
Go to him.
Oh, no.
Chad's dead.
What happens if you don't touch anything, though?
You don't say anything or do anything deep sleep?
I'm assuming if you pick up the knife, everyone goes, he did it.
And you get arrested and you go to disc three automatically, right?
It didn't take a genius to play it out.
I was coming down.
She was going up.
The door prize was a hunk of blood pudding.
Time to go.
Chad sort of made a mess.
Let's go.
Okay.
Incoming disc two.
This is great.
I'm going to hold on to this one.
I'm going to keep this in a glass case.
I'm going to hand down psychic detective to my grandchildren.
Oh, shit.
Was that just two or just three?
No, we're good.
Green vented.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
I see what you're doing.
I kind of get it.
Although I don't.
You know, I watch people stream among us and I have absolutely no idea what's going on.
I just kind of pretend like I do.
And then they just all start yelling at each other.
I sat there knowing two things dead certain.
Layne was going to drag me in deeper and I was going to follow like some over sex schnauzer.
What's that mean?
It means stop it.
All right.
This may sound like your dad really did jump out the window, but not exactly suicide.
He's still playing this.
Well, actually, I don't know.
You're wrong.
Someone was messing with his head.
I'm not playing this at all.
Actually, I'm sitting here without the controller in my hand.
What's that?
Um, well, you know that he's dead.
I'm still trying to get used to it.
Yeah, right.
You sure look busted up about it.
This ending is going to suck, too.
It's not going to be worth doing this a third time.
Watch, Monica.
Just a little more.
I do not trust this mirage quest.
You're going?
I have to.
Don't ask why.
Just hate me if you must.
What's that face I can do?
I can do like a sad face.
I can do a sad reaction.
I missed that.
Oh, I would have done the sad reaction.
Oh, you idiot.
How come I never thought about going home?
Wait, do I go home?
Hey, bright boy.
Want to get arrested?
Go sit in the cop car.
How are you?
Moki found dead.
You're that psychic kid.
Flasho.
Flash in the pan.
I've seen the act.
Moki's plaything.
To my pal, Moki.
Listen, you little putz.
You're flying blind.
You need Moki.
Moki knows the dirt.
I collected.
Stored in my cheeks.
That would explain the breath.
Listen, you do me a little job.
I clue you in.
We also could have followed Monica, too.
That could have been interesting.
Time's a-wasting.
It's a midnight sale.
Come on, now's the time, Foxy.
Take it or leave it.
Two exotic bombshells.
I end up with you.
Hey, kid.
You haven't seen me dance.
You know how they pronounce it?
Frick.
What assholes.
So?
So, history lesson.
The Black Diamond Campfire Girls.
Circa 1987.
It's the Resident Evil 7 family.
Vladimir Potsok.
The KGB kissed his ass.
Like it was sable.
Know why?
He made a little toy.
The Psychic Collector.
Lil' Lena.
Damn good psychic.
But a skitzy broad with a psychopathic papa.
Boo hoo.
And a Slasnewitz.
Eight years old.
She boils a cup of tea by looking at him.
Batting clean up.
Lexi Golitsyn.
Power hungry.
Perk hungry.
Borscht.
Turn myself into Moki.
Morty, I'm Moki.
I'm Moki, Morty.
Sergei Zansko.
Your rival.
It's not even funny.
I'm laughing at it, though.
I don't know why.
Because this makes no fucking sense,
what you just said.
Double the pain.
Who's all for?
We're talking frontal lobe trauma.
I turned myself into Moki, Morty.
Here's the key.
Do piggyback inside and get to Max Mirage's table.
Main room, far left corner.
Maybe we go in.
It's not like I use a map.
Hey, I wouldn't know.
I'm not psychic.
I don't have the sexy gift.
I just come from a clean straight shot home
where nobody mess me up.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I know things.
As usual.
Moki, Andy.
That's fine.
Yeah, sure.
There's a phone call coming in two minutes.
Be there for it.
And don't screw me.
No, I don't even go in.
Psychic bastard.
Where are you?
Inside?
Have we crossed the room?
Here we go, kid.
It's the same path.
Yeah, it is the same path.
It's the same run.
Are you telling me that me actively playing the game
versus the game playing itself is just as bad?
That seems fucking impossible.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Let's hear it.
You put the fear of God in him.
Oh, for real?
White as a ghost, Moke.
Anyone hear him talking roosties?
Just the whole damn room.
You're a lying little punk.
Maybe I couldn't get there in time.
Maybe you're full of crap.
Why don't you go peep the psychic slot?
Why would this be Moki's playthrough?
Or Moki's plaything?
If we don't do what he wants and he gets angry and runs away.
If you're thinking of taking a ride in my head.
Eight, four, eight.
There it is.
Okay, this part, I'm really...
I need to see what really happens here.
Pizza!
We know when you're hungry.
This dude is the guy that walks over with his hands on his chest,
blood everywhere and the guy with the gun.
We keep missing this part.
Not this time.
Watch, Monica.
Learn everything, Eric.
Everything!
Say something!
Was that...
Was there a hand over there?
I quit.
I could put a puncher?
What the fuck was that?
On principle, of course.
Not because you're running away.
Oh, you think I'm scared?
You feel it.
Even when you touch.
Just before the flash, it's there.
What happens if I don't come back?
Or what happens if I come back like this?
Don't touch anything, don't touch anything.
My father made this.
Not to teach or to feel better.
But to destroy my Sergey.
From inside out.
And you want me to use it?
You will come back.
You are the best I've seen.
Okay, so now...
No!
No, no, no.
I didn't do anything.
Why is it...
It's not going to come back with him walking in with blood all over him, is it?
It's going to open.
No, it's not.
It's not.
Okay, don't do anything.
I want to see what's happening to him.
You must have...
Get out!
You don't know what you say.
You cannot hear him.
You cannot protect.
Dracula.
You won't accept.
I miss him.
Stop it.
You will be adult.
You will be...
She's going to get...
She's going to get the last...
Okay, we're good.
Now let's see what happens here.
It can't be changed.
You can't change it.
Maybe you could have...
Maybe you could have gone back and seen what they were doing, but...
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
Anything you say can and will be used against you in the court of law.
Fine.
Lock me in my cell.
I sure as hell couldn't keep me in my body.
You could have switched to that guy's POV.
It's not going to be the same ending.
It's going to be impossible to be the same ending.
How long have you known Chad Kwiatkowski?
Why delaying a one-year at the house?
You boffing a kid?
You want to be boffing us?
What kind of game is she running?
She's looking for a psychic collector.
A whole bunch of people are looking for her.
Her dad made him.
Four of them.
They're unbelievable.
Sounded like some crystal-hugging hophead.
You wouldn't believe what can happen.
Guys, I know this is hard to believe, but...
There was only one way to slip this.
Find this damn collector myself.
I didn't even notice that face that got in leftist making.
All right, here we go.
It's time for the conclusion.
They're not pressing a single button.
If we get the same ending, I'm going to be very, very mad.
That would be upsetting to me.
All right, I got the worst ending on my own.
I don't think that was the worst ending.
I think it was a bad one, but not the worst one.
Hey, Fox.
Be a good boy.
No eight-dimension crap.
Go to Bagman.
I'll be honest.
I don't even know how I got to Bagman in the first place.
What is this dork cube, Link?
What the hell is dork cube?
I was sick to death of trespassing, head-hopping, trance, being.
I needed time to think, to figure out what I do next.
I'm not doing the feet thing right there.
No.
Mayor Patterson answered allegations
that the murders may have been motivated by anti-Corellian sentiment.
You won the black diamonds game last time.
That's the only thing that made it a good ending.
You got the worst good ending.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Great.
Very cool, Link.
Crashing the website.
Well, when like 6,000 people click on something at the same time,
I'm going to assume it's not going to go very well.
It's so weird because when you...
Here's something weird.
Your teeth make up a huge amount of the way that you look.
That doesn't even look like me.
It's because the teeth are different.
It looks like a different fucking person.
Like that fake mouth.
It's just...
I am a different person.
New viewer.
I remember going to places like...
Because you guys know what Cold Stone is, right?
Cold Stone Creamery did this thing where anytime you got a tip,
and if you tipped anybody from Cold Stone,
they would have to sing this tip song.
And I remember always just thinking like,
they don't want...
Hey guys, we got a tip.
A tip just came in and we're really hip.
And then you could just tell it was like,
I don't want to fucking sing that.
So I would just...
I would put money in and be like,
you don't have to.
Just give it...
You don't have to do it.
I'm just going to say you did.
Yeah, I know you don't want to.
You don't have to.
You look disappointed.
Something for a pony or maybe a blonde.
I got a real job for you.
A real gimme.
A thousand bucks and 30 minutes.
Doing what?
Sort of psychic seal of approval.
If they wanted to, sure.
I would sit there and fold my arms and be like,
let me hear it.
Come on, kid.
Clock's a ticking.
My pal!
I thought he just ran away.
You just want to use the damn thing.
Kid, this is white odd.
We snag a collector.
We're big league.
Psychic mercenaries.
You with the brain, me with the Rolodex.
In the bit song.
The hell it does.
I shelled out cash four years ago.
So you say.
Don't you get it?
Lexi never died.
A face job and a lounge act worse than yours.
Max Mirage?
No, Wayne Newton.
Come on, kid.
Get with the beat.
Yes, he does have a rat's head.
Yes, he does.
Okay, here we go.
This is it.
This is where it's going to...
The path is going to branch here at this point
because I'm not going to run.
Don't say it.
What are you doing hanging around?
I could ask you the same question.
Strictly insurance.
Make sure you got the genuine goods.
No, I got to tame my ankles.
Let her rip.
Don't move.
The real thing?
Yeah.
Did the earth move?
Oh, man.
This is Bush League.
This is Bush League?
This wasn't the deal.
You're right.
I feel just...
Um.
Did she take his hairpiece off?
I'm your mommy now.
Okay.
Oh, hey, shit.
Monica, your car has got a lot of trash in it.
She does that thing when she freaks out.
She's like moving all the McDonald's and Wendy's bags
like deep into the bottom of the seat.
Like, fuck, fuck.
Ah, yeah, that's how I've been, you know, living out of my car.
You know, like we all do.
You just take your hand
and you drag it across the back seat
desperately trying to make room
and hope there's no stains.
What's wrong with me?
Think how you can train him.
Too much DMT?
You find the village idiot,
make a special delivery, and then maybe...
No, that's not the ending that I want.
Wait, did he just shoot the kid?
Take this.
Get the collector.
Challenge Lexi the game.
What do you mean, three?
Challenge the game?
He already blitzed me.
No, we cannot face him.
I've made you weak, but not so stupid.
Choose me.
I'm this guy.
Quickly.
Or he's destroyed.
No.
I leaned in so close for that.
I'm not a warrior.
Choose me.
I'm a freak of nature.
She pulls up from down below the frame,
an envelope with the fucking Smash logo on it.
This isn't Karelia.
You should run with the wolf.
Come with me.
We can take this thing to Mexico right now.
Start a new life, a new show.
I'll touch objects, you look real moody.
Why couldn't that work?
He's been listening.
She's in.
If I'm so weak, why would they make me come in here again?
Like, he already won.
I think it's time for the powerful, psychic old lady to have a try.
But her excuse was,
No, no, you're weak and terrible, and you suck.
But you do it again.
That's all I got from that.
Same ending and coming.
It can't be.
It actually cannot be the same ending.
Seven hundred dollar console, by the way.
Omega Lola wasn't that much money.
Although, like, I'll sell one to you if that's what you want to pay for it.
Karelia, so photogenic.
Why can't they all be full screen?
Why does it have to be in the tiny little window?
This doesn't even look bad.
Why does it have to put it so small?
Trouble in the rat hole.
Monica's up there.
Top floor.
What about Max?
He's waiting for us to make a move.
I guess you couldn't see the icons, huh?
Let's take him out.
I want to go.
Then go.
But I'm holding this.
I'm not going to get the same ending.
Is this a great country or?
Mirage quest.
What a scam.
You know, only in America could someone declare war on depression.
Depression is very important to Karelians.
It makes all that boredom seem somehow.
But did you say Karelians?
What was Superman?
A room full of sponge cake.
Every crumb in love with Lexi.
A humble beginning.
To what end?
Good seats at the ballpark.
Plank steak whenever I want.
Krypton.
Unlimited will wash your head.
What was he?
You're a mage.
Karelia on its knees.
Klingon.
No, no, no, no.
No, just a little.
So you've brought a toy.
You are prepared.
Superman was a Klingon.
Cold feet?
I'm not surprised.
A Kryptonian?
Hehehehehe.
Oh shit, this is getting weird.
This is how you do it.
No wasted motion.
No parlor tricks.
Say goodbye to the girl.
Go to the car.
No.
Harder.
Don't you want to see her cry?
Hey.
You think I need your help?
You think I want you watching me?
You're a cheerleader, a throw rug. Now move! Go!
Good boy. That is good boy. Nobody wants to burn you.
Just bring me the toy. These are the good times.
Okay, hand it over.
It's a simple game, Rio.
I don't want to play the game though, but I don't touch anything.
I don't get it, how do I lose?
He is scared of the cat. That was a right call.
Which ones are stronger?
Alright, so now we lose. We have to lose this.
I don't want to accidentally win.
Alright, how about this one?
Take the bracelet, the doll, and red square.
And then, I don't know, this guy.
Okay, let's lose.
Okay, let's take the doll and put it over to cigarette.
I can tell which hidden the little bogeyman that scares you in the dark.
He works with me now. He tells me all your secrets.
Okay.
You're a little burnt up, aren't you?
As if I needed a handicap.
Cigarette on two. Alright, that's two in a row.
Terror feeds the gift. Terror makes you stronger.
And lets me pull you apart.
Not the same ending.
Okay, now we're going to do red square to lady, right?
Doesn't she destroy red square?
That one was particularly tasty.
The damn thing is rigged.
Well, take notes.
For some other lifetime.
Okay, time to lose.
Game over.
Yep, that's me.
The babbling idiot and his new best friend.
I want deep down.
You're still a little part of me that's really smart.
That knows what's going on.
Deep down.
Just doesn't get out much.
Did have that hair.
Yeah, that was really not worth watching the whole like 26 minute movie again.
To just say I want ice cream in jail.
It was not worth it at all, actually.
Wasn't even the right one.
Yeah, it was. It's Moki's Playmate.
You get that by not doing anything.
Alright, let's move on.
That was a meaty one though. I knew that was going to take at least a couple hours.
We're going to move on to...
We're in the 3D, I might as well stay on it.
We're going to play a game called I'm Mercenary.
Fucking Christ, finally.
Hey. Hey, come on, man.
Enemy Spider-Man? No, I'm Mercenary.
It looks pretty bizarre, but let's...
You know, we'll take a break too.
Just a quick one.
Let's go pee.
Grab a water.
And I'll be back in two minutes.
We're going to play I'm Mercenary.
In a sec.
Why are you all sleeping?
Okay, I'm Mercenary.
Probably should change the title to just retro.
Alright, let's go.
I have no idea how good this...
This game might be a fucking dud.
It looks wild.
So we'll find out.
A 3DO experience.
From Electro...
How much did EA have to do with this?
The games are exclusive EA games.
Did they make it?
Were they part of the process?
There's a lot of EA games.
Wake up.
Satellite Intercept.
Pick HQ.
Transmission.
This is in the sake of every generation to come.
Listen to me and behold your future.
After 10,000 years, I'm free.
It's time to conquer Earth.
Your children's children will become enslaved.
Forced to fight each other to the death.
Unless you listen to what I say.
I know what must be done.
But I am powerless to act on my own.
We must have a warrior from your time.
Someone outside this world we call perfect.
That person was just sleeping in a chair on the top left.
And must send us a warrior to destroy perfect.
Can you scroll it a little slower?
That's not me. That's not me.
Copyright 1995. You just took me out, man.
Leave the flatline thing there.
You just pulled me out.
New Jump.
Okay. All I can do is New Jump.
A211.
Near Little Rock.
Okay.
One of the Ghostbusters?
Why do they all have syringes?
We've got to pull him out.
No! I thought it was going to shatter.
That's actually what would happen if you got pulled out of the Matrix, by the way.
Help destruct?
It's the guy.
All these tales. Could it be?
It's going to be that guy from the Unsolved Mysteries thing.
Some of these are fiction. Some of these are fact.
Can you find out which one?
In crazy stories.
This one. This one was real.
I know. Real fucked up, I know.
This is all we got from Thor.
Jonathan Breaks. Yes.
The day to analyze it quick.
I don't think I want to go into that.
It's clearly just a dentist's chair.
No, it's a barber's chair.
With a headband on it.
A gamer coffin.
We haven't determined what happened yet.
But be careful in this area.
This is where we lost contact with number four.
Sorry, I think somebody may have hit the side of the TV with a hammer.
I think they're ready whenever you are.
So you can't really tell what the hell is going on here.
Neither can I.
Approaching synchronization now.
Waveform sync.
Check. Interference pattern.
0.5 milliseconds.
Forward.
Going in. Ready to link.
Jump in. Three. Two.
One. Let's go.
Are we in?
This is what it feels like to be in an MRI.
What the hell is going on? Gamer?
This is not what I thought
this was going to be.
Enter the playground.
Falcon.
It really is just a game. It's just a video warning.
Low defense. Red spire required.
Are these teammates?
Am I out of ammo?
Dude, it's a battle royale.
Wait a minute. What am I going to go?
I spent all the money on the
elaborate intro.
Touch this? I just picked that person up.
I think we're capping the point.
What's this? D.
O. A. What is that up there?
I killed that person.
I'm rank 255.
I need to go find a red spire.
Okay. Let's go.
This is a blue spire. It's not what I want.
Red spire. Is it on the map?
No. It's blue. Blue?
Also blue?
I think I passed out.
Rank...
I don't know what he said.
This is the type of game that you would see in a
Mountain Dew commercial.
It's like a game that you would see
on the background of a
TV show tries to show you what a
video game is.
I'm going back in.
Total jumps. Rank 255.
Defense, offense, and agility.
Ammo algorithms.
Agility is green.
Offense is red.
Defense is yellow.
Effectiveness is 34%.
Let's jump.
Mountain Dew commercial.
Would you be the test subject
back in the mid-90s
to play a game like that if you got to be
in VR for like 10 minutes?
Let's see if I can figure this out.
That Mountain Dew commercial the whole time would be like
with two
top boxes you can level up.
If you send in five labels
you'll get 200 XP
points.
Take your game to the next level.
And the person has a huge fucking headset on.
They always just have a gigantic headset on.
And they like put their hands in the air and they scream
yeah. Alright I'm in yellow right now.
Should I just hold it? Just hold this?
Red. The music's not bad.
No it's not. It's alright.
Alright red. The bars are going up.
Okay I'm standing in the red. Is that
the red bar is going up?
That's offense right?
That guy's 256? Did they explain any of this?
No no no. Somebody died in the chair.
Now I have to come in here and
dude this guy is
kicking the shit out of me.
That guy just destroyed me. I didn't even get a chance.
So you guys just
got to see in real time the reason why I don't
play online multiplayer games anymore.
That's my experience.
I just got in. Okay I'm running around
this corner. Oh I got hit hit hit hit
every single thing. I got
like triple tapped. I'm dead.
Oh. Okay well
I guess I'm going to start again. Oh I got
hit in the air and then hit in the air and then
juggled and hit in the air again.
Alright I think it's going to open up Minecraft.
Let's jump again. Ammo algorithm.
Yeah I don't even know what that's supposed to mean.
That song sucks? Okay.
Keep moving. What happened?
I just killed the yellow.
Okay just keep walking. It's blue.
What does blue do? Blue is making my
defense go up. And offense. Alright
keep moving. Go go go go go go. Don't stop.
Good. Good. Alright keep going.
Warning. Low agility. Rest for a while.
I have to stop. Low agility. Stop stop
stop stop. I'm stopped. I can only walk a
certain distance. I get it. Okay.
Get to a bonfire. Hold on.
What's this thing? Like an eye? I have to kill it?
Touch it? High explosive area
effect ammo uses 10
units per blast.
Did I get it? I think I got it.
Hold on. This is red. Rest for
a second. Run run run run run.
This is like blue's base. Pick that up. What is it?
I don't know. I didn't touch it. I just missed everything.
I missed every single shot on that guy
and he was like a level one scrub.
Warning. Low agility. I know I know I know.
Stop stop stop stop.
Shit. I'm gonna.
Come on dude. What the fuck.
When does my brain shut off?
That's what caused his algorithm to crash.
I don't know. No.
I'm feeling there's more to it than that. Jim, I think
there's a little more to it. I think he's just not very good.
Here's your stats. Let us know
when. This guy lied on his resume.
It says he was
he said he prestige three times
in Call of Duty Black Ops.
That's true. That doesn't mean
anything though. It just means he sat there
and just got experience over and over again.
This guy's not even good at anything.
You hired this guy on prestige alone?
You really fucked the whole thing up.
Didn't you Mike? Only on prestige
three. Prestige three. God damn it.
You can sit in the corner of a lobby
and get to prestige 99 in
three months.
The Devil XP Mountain Dew.
Look at how big this is.
Yeah, we probably shouldn't have given him all those cans
of Mountain Dew. What is this?
What did we just
stumble upon?
Do I get to select a unit?
Wait a minute. This is cool.
I can talk? What who is
where is? What who
is? What is P-Fect?
What is Pusher?
It knocks people out of
your way. Where is
P-Fect? It's everywhere.
You can't get away from it.
Where is
Stunner? Wherever you find it
I guess. This is the shittiest eight ball
I've ever shook in my whole life.
There's all the same answer. Where reality
ends and the dream begins.
That was the slogan
they hit us with when they launched this thing.
A new frontier in
virtual reality they said.
What they didn't say was that this
is the final frontier.
Oh, well that's kind of cool. It's like Star Trek.
Okay, goodbye.
What do you have to say? Did I somehow
accidentally beat the game?
How do I get higher rank? What is the
Garden? What is Perfect One? What is
Ashflay? What is
Chafe? What is Boomerang?
What is a
Pems?
You just don't get it, do you?
You're not going to get out of here alive
and ne- Was that actually Penis?
Was that like a how dare you don't ask me
that question? Nothing, really.
What is the Garden?
The Garden is perfect.
And perfect is the Garden.
Where is the Garden?
Wherever we are.
That is the Garden. Where is Perfect
One? Perfect One
is dead. Oh.
Oh, no.
Who is Perfect One? A liar
and a lie. There is
no Perfect One. So Perfect One is
dead, though. Where is Roberto?
Roberto is sixth in the hierarchy.
He's the crazy one.
Or maybe we're all
crazy and he's sane.
Goodbye. So, can I
pick one of these? What
the fuck is that?
What is this thing?
Like a fly?
I've been watching you.
I see
everything.
You know? Okay.
What is the
Garden? The Garden
is good.
Oh, I said what is the Garden?
Not how is
the Garden. What is
Perfect? It's everything
and nothing.
No, no. I didn't say why.
A computer program. A universe.
A dream.
It's all we have.
Okay.
Let's say where is the Garden?
There is nothing
but the Garden.
Are these people in the computer? Are these people
with me in the game? Are these other gamers?
Is that like a cool
transmog this person has?
I don't understand. Are these other gamers?
Wait, hold on. This became
a completely different game.
Okay, who is
the Garden?
It's the same thing as Perfect.
Okay, enough of this bullshit. What is it?
I don't know. A lot of people
have been killed around the East Residential
District lately though. Thank you for the info.
And no one's seen anything. What? Oh.
Makes you wonder.
Okay.
What is a cannibal?
It increases your offensive capabilities.
Okay, goodbye. Alright, which one should I touch?
Should I touch the Five Head?
Oh, that person's naked.
I can't activate any of these
things? Okay, I'm just going to leave.
The Prophecy of Porn Week
is true.
The door seize is neutral.
Enter to heal. Oh, shit.
Oh, they're trying to go into heal.
Should I just camp and wait
for them all to come out?
Yeah.
Jim, he's using his tried and true
tactic of Call of Duty XP
boosting. This is how he got his prestige.
I told you this guy was the real deal.
He's spawn camping.
He got me right in the fucking head. And when he finds a good
player, he runs the fuck away. Let's heal.
Find a red spire.
Wait, there are new players here. There are people here again.
This really is just
like, okay. Wait.
I want to talk to this guy. This is other
players.
Where is Ice?
If you think you can handle Tesla,
try looking around the power plant.
What is perfect one?
The ultimate virtual warrior.
He's never been defeated in combat
and he's been here since the beginning.
The perfect one is the rank
one. Where are they?
The spire.
The spire. Okay.
This person hit a hundred times on character
generator. Okay. Well,
what the hell is this? What is
he? A grenade
more or less.
This is like Dr. Manhattan's friend.
Dr. Charcoal.
A stun gun. It's a stunner.
I don't know where in the real world.
I entered in Palo Alto.
You can make the jump
anywhere in the country. At least
you used to be able to. I have no
idea what's happening on the outside.
This is a side hang. That was a lie.
I don't know where in the real world.
I entered in Palo Alto.
You can make the jump anywhere
in the country. At least
you used to be able to. I have no
idea what's happening on the outside
anymore. This, somebody just said this
would have been really cool to play back then. Yeah.
It would have. I mean, nowadays
not so much, but still
is pretty interesting.
Character generator. Okay.
Somebody said to go to the east side.
Why do we all have to fight each other out here?
Oh shit.
Okay. I'm gonna go
I'm gonna run away. Let's go over here.
There's a building I can go over here.
Can I go in here? I think I might be able to go in this.
Alright, slow down.
Can I go in this?
Enter the pyramid. To face
Medusa. I wasn't ready
to face Medusa?
Uh oh.
This is gonna be this.
Shit. Watch out. I'm gonna go this way.
Where is she? Agility
is bad. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Is she gonna wrap around me right?
My offense is not terrible.
My defense is so bad though.
I'm gonna spam as fast as I can when I see her.
It's gonna be like
Oh shit.
What happens if I win?
She's rank 11. I'm about to be a 255
versus an 11. If I win I get to 10.
I just got one shot.
Run through the fields?
Wait, I'm supposed to be
dying?
I'm supposed to die
and run through the field
and stuff. Okay.
Get more power.
I lost agility and lost
D.
I'm supposed to die
and run through the field and stuff.
Okay.
Get more power.
I lost agility and lost defense.
Alright, we gotta run through a static
field. What the hell does a static
field look like?
Kill enemies, collect their static.
Now start and select to return to the lab.
Okay.
Okay, I got static. I get it.
Alright, cool. Did I touch that?
Weird pool ball. High power, long range
blaster uses three zero units.
Alright, so I think I collected that.
Low agility, rest for a while. So what if
I press start? Select ammo.
Oh shit, look at this.
Default, default. What's this one?
Select ammo.
Give all messages. Information
only. Warnings only.
Okay, let's go back. Select.
No, I can't do it yet, I don't think.
I get it. Okay.
Alright, so
there, I'm level 255. I have to
only kill 255s.
Do they just keep me in here overnight?
You're a prisoner.
I don't think I'm a prisoner.
Alright, let me try this a couple more times.
So I have to run around and kill a bunch of things that are my level.
So we're only looking for
shitty players. Avoid everybody
else. Burn messages back on.
Okay. Pointing, low defense.
Give me that static. I need, I'm already
dead. Static.
Okay. Static.
Static. Okay, now what?
Select ammo. How do I get out? How do I do?
Should we be strafing? There's no strafing.
There's so many
people over here.
Can you give me a flamethrower
or something?
What's this game called? It's called
iMercenary.
Alright, I keep losing shit
permanently. Okay, if I run around
fast, I run out of agility
and the game says stop moving. And when I stop moving
a guy 50 levels higher
than me shoots me in the head and kills me.
It's like a new map. Alright, static.
Damn it. I don't have any
ammo. Alright, I'm done.
I'm done moving on.
New game.
This is ridiculous.
No, it wasn't. I didn't kill anybody.
Stop gaslighting me because I'm the only fucking
person that signed up for this experiment for $40.
Alright, last one, last one, last one.
One more. Stop gaslighting the word
gaslighting.
I feel like the word has feeling.
Alright, I gotta at least do something interesting.
Alright.
Shit is so low. Look at how big that bar can be.
The fuck, dude?
Where am I supposed to go?
What do you have to say now?
Nothing. It doesn't have anything to say.
In fact, I think, I think they may have, I don't think very many
people still work here. That guy might be
the janitor for all I know.
Run from spire to spire. Alright, that's what I'm gonna do.
Just stay near
the pyre. You need to kill
higher rank than two of these. Alright, I'm just gonna go
fire.
Okay, cool. I just, if I stay still I'm gonna die.
Why is my chili so bad?
I can only walk for two seconds.
What's the point of having traffic
lights? Stop, stop, stop, stop.
It's so slow.
I'm softlocked. No, don't put me back
in. Can I please eat
something?
I think we ran out of FMV sequences.
So, we're just gonna get the basic
ones. Alright, when I kill
the green guys, do I get green
stuff? Alright, I can almost make it to the blue.
I'm almost there. Low agility.
I think I just died
from being too tired. Alright, that's it. I'm out. Pull me
out. Pull me out. I'm done.
That's it. I've done it.
This is German Pluto.
...capture those static algorithms.
Permanently add their power to your projection
into perfect. Get to the point.
The rhythms you can crash into in Huffman,
the more powerful you'll become.
The better your chances
of attaining our mission objective.
Gain all the power you can this
way. Why didn't you tell me
this? Like
18 days ago
when I got into the machine.
Wasn't somebody in this before? Somebody
died in this thing. You don't think they had the data
before? Alright, one more.
One more. This is it. And then I'm done.
This is it. Last one. This is the actual
final one. This is the last one.
This is it. I promise.
Agility done. No more ammo.
Okay, fuck it, I'm out. Take me out.
I love this game. Don't stop.
Run into the static fields.
I died. Nobody even shot me.
Nobody shot me. I've run out of lives.
I've gotta go. Okay.
It's time to move on.
I don't even care anymore.
I'm just being tortured in here.
Can you at least just wake me up
and just give me a Red Bull? I feel like I
would have a little bit more opportunity to succeed.
Stop just waking me up and putting
me back to sleep, dude.
Restart the game.
We're gonna play another one. What do I wanna do now?
Here comes a mystery. You have no idea what it's gonna
be, but it's gonna be a mystery. Well, you know.
Give me one sec. Okay.
So this one coming up here
is completely in Japanese.
I have no idea what's gonna happen here,
but this is called Montana Jones.
You're gonna have to help me out here.
Out of this, probably about 6,000 people
or one of you know how to speak Japanese.
Somebody will.
It's a cat, Indiana Jones.
Wait a minute.
This is Wacky Racers.
Same company.
Now I'm excited.
Because Wacky Racers was awesome.
Nice.
Montana Jones.
Fully animated?
He was like facetiming like a grand
kid. Making funny faces.
But Zelda CD-i
is not. It's better than that.
Okay, Montana?
Alfred or Melissa?
Give me the gist of it. Give me the gist of it.
Give me the gist. What did you say?
I can't select anybody.
What the fuck was that?
Did I take too long?
Alright, where are we gonna go? San Francisco?
The Caribbean Sea?
Through England, Egypt,
Tibet, or Sofet?
Sofet.
San Francisco or
Sofafet? Let's go San Francisco.
Oh, you know what it probably was like? This message will
self-destruct in 10 seconds, right?
I got that part.
Now what? It keeps floating.
Okay.
We're landing.
Landing in San
Francisco. We're gonna try to get a diamond.
San Francisco.
What are we looking for?
What are we looking for? What are we looking for?
This way. We're trying to do
this way.
We'll take a firework, please.
I guess.
Okay.
Now what?
I guess we'll take one. Is it puzzle time?
Oh shit, I don't even know what the puzzle is.
What is the puzzle?
I took the first one.
You never take the first one.
It's okay. If I can't read it, then it won't come true.
I don't know. If I can't read it,
if I can't comprehend it, can't understand it, it's not gonna come true. It won't be real.
Friends like that. What does it say?
Is that cursed?
Okay. What about in the
in here? Down the street?
Let's go in here.
Expensive vases?
Are we stealing something from here?
I don't understand. Steel?
Are we taking something?
Vases? Lamps?
Jewelry or something?
Should we go in here?
Yes.
This is Zero-kyo.
We are friends.
Don't desecrate one of the areas. I didn't do anything.
What are you talking about?
Shut up and pretend to be Zero-kyo.
This is Zero-kyo.
Is he angry?
He's like, come on over here.
Come here.
He says here.
Please translate for me.
Is it here?
I'm trying, but you aren't reading my messages.
Alright, I'm gonna read your messages from now on.
Sir, Sir Linkerton.
Sir Linkerton, please.
Help me.
Why, where they come from?
That many people could fit on that?
Where are they coming from?
Am I about to make a deal?
Linkerton, what's going on here?
He said welcome.
He said a little more than welcome.
Did I pick that up?
Okay, what did he say?
We just took him.
Were we supposed to?
Two minutes of dialogue.
I'm getting destroyed.
Did you bring the money?
I don't think we have any money.
I found this guy snooping around upstairs.
Bring him.
Oh no.
Stay calm everybody.
We don't know what he's planning.
This became a different video game.
Five nights at Freddy's.
Should we leave?
Alright, I need a translation.
What is she saying?
What's this room?
I need to break my neck, she says.
That's not what she said.
Alright, what did he say?
What did Linkerton say?
That's the only person I'm listening to.
What should we do? What's this room?
Need a key.
He said next game.
I'm sure she did.
Every room is the same.
He said this video fucking sucks laughing my ass off.
He says you moron, you are going the wrong way.
Does anybody have any idea what's going on?
He might be saying you need a paper.
You need a paper.
Shit.
I need a paper.
He said play wacky braces.
Come on.
Toilet paper.
Stop.
We can't help you go through the maze.
It's all the same room.
I have to memorize what I clicked on.
Shit.
Get me out of here.
I'm finally out of here.
I took back the
Bannereck's Tojiki from the gang.
And it's a big success.
Get in there.
We made it out.
Nice work.
It's too early to be at ease.
Come on, come on, let's go.
Wait up, you little brats.
Manic Dragon, height 5'2, weight 3'2.
What is the trouble?
Why am I looking at this?
Am I going to ride it?
How many games are there?
I didn't mean to do that.
This whole thing was made in dreams, by the way.
Life?
Why is my life a fuel gauge?
How about his head?
That didn't work?
Why is there a timer?
Get up.
Don't get hit again.
I just have to avoid it.
Easy.
Wait, secret.
Oh, I did it.
Let's go.
Go where?
You can run into the walls?
Why can you do that?
I'm not...
It's getting...
It's going so fast.
You have no idea.
Okay, well, San Francisco apparently has been destroyed.
I don't know.
How about England?
I am way more interested in this game now.
Because of the...
Eight different game modes that exist.
Translator, ready?
Lost in England.
This boomer unironically enjoys shit.
Is this an anime made into a game?
I don't know.
Maybe...
Okay, so we've got cars.
It is.
Oh, no. Translator.
What was just said?
I feel like this is important.
Where's my translator?
My chat's going too fast.
Should you change your name to Fart?
I can't even...
That's so dumb.
Why did I read what you said?
It asks you to go back to Boston.
No, it didn't.
It asks if you want to use the car or the taxi.
But that's not a yes or a no.
Do you want to use the car or the taxi?
Yes.
Oh, dear God.
Do I have access to brakes?
Or speed?
We're going very slow.
By the way, you're driving on this side of the road, right?
You have to drive on the left side.
I can't do anything.
Let's get to full letter grade.
Technically, that's true.
We're going five miles per hour.
It's okay.
I tried to side swipe him, but it went fine.
We made it.
Looks like we're taking the taxi.
Where are you off to?
I don't know.
That's Glastonbury Hill.
It's a beautiful place.
That makes sense because we definitely didn't drive more than 300 feet away from that way the taxi was.
There's an Excalibur somewhere in this church.
We barely pulled out of the driveway.
Let's go in.
There's an Excalibur somewhere in this maze.
Okay, time for another guess which way to go.
I can't get any help from anybody.
I need help.
They won't help me.
Touch it.
What did you say?
Did she say don't touch that or touch it?
Friends later.
Holy shit man, Montana's dumpy.
Now that opened this.
That's the way that your dog looks at you.
When you're talking to them.
I'm a dog and I heard my name.
Can we do it?
Another one of these.
Right next to the...
There's another one back here, right?
Down here.
Pull this one.
That should open up the one behind us.
Theoretically, right?
Then we turn left.
Should I...
That's probably that one.
This game predates the Bible.
I don't know.
Probably not.
Straight ahead.
This one might do this door.
I hope.
Next? No, no, no.
I don't want to say that right now.
You really don't want to say that.
That's not what you want.
I'll take the sword.
These Excalibur?
That means I'm the chosen one.
I'm the chosen one.
Boss fight with the sword?
That would be awesome.
Mechanic mole.
You can't wield Excalibur if you're not chosen.
Doesn't it burn your hands?
Pennsylvania?
Can I use the sword for anything?
This is Super Mario shit here.
Look at these blocks.
Okay, I'm fine.
Shit, I gotta go down.
Don't blow this.
It gets progressively faster.
We're good, we're good.
Oh no, that's more of this shit.
I just took a brick to the head.
All right, easy, easy, easy.
I have to beat one of these levels at least.
Shit, come on.
That's bullshit.
If you get touched by a brick, you go all the way back to the beginning?
That's stupid brick checkpoints.
Who the fuck are you?
Wait, who's that?
Don't get hit by a brick.
All right, easy.
Don't move.
You tell me I was that far away.
Think of this game like an ass.
And pretend to eat it.
All right, ban that person for at least 30 minutes.
There's more of this. There's probably three.
Good to know that that guy is now a part of the encounter.
Just stay up top.
Why give me such an opportunity to not get hit?
Oh, give me a fucking break.
That was stupid.
I won.
I don't have the sword.
I think it's just cutscene only.
I said, what did we do to deserve this punishment?
You guys didn't do anything.
I'm gonna need some time to fix this.
Welcome back.
You got the legendary sword, Excalibur.
I immediately killed Mogura with Excalibur.
Please stop playing the 3DO.
No, dude.
What do you mean?
Stop.
I'm gonna beat you up.
It's not just a background.
It's also a foreground. I get it.
No!
Hooray!
I don't think I did that.
I need to get back up on there.
Where the fuck am I?
I can go through to the
background, background.
But not the background, background, background.
What's up there? Okay.
Shit! Did he touch me?
Fuel gauge? I don't know. I'm probably made out of
metal or something.
I just want to play Sonic.
Should I grab the chain?
I'm gonna hand him this.
Is there a...
I need my translator.
What does that say? Lusiary wall?
Are we jumping out the window?
Well, he's here.
He said jump.
Jump. Okay.
I'm gonna jump.
That was risky.
That was pretty good clear.
I like that one.
Did he fall?
He said bite the disc and play Doki Doki Literature Club.
Okay, sure.
I bet you that's what was said.
We're home free, right?
We got the good thing we needed.
Horse?
Or horse.
It's a bear.
What are the wheels for?
Do you really put aesthetic wheels
on the back of the...
and turn into a car?
You're killing us.
Why am I killing you?
Hey, hey, hey.
You're choking me.
Get your hands off your own neck
and pretending it's me.
Go, go, go.
It's gonna fall.
Oldest trick in the book.
You are personally squeezing my brain juice out.
If that's the case,
the whole world will know I'm Zayac.
You guys!
Don't think this is over!
This is better than the first game?
No, it's not.
They're both equally good.
Welcome back.
I was a little worried.
Have you forgotten
that I'm the luckiest man in the world?
I would love to be killed by you.
Not by the weird
I-kill-you fantasy.
I already made that video. You can go watch it right now.
You can go pull up the green screen right now
and just sit there and be like...
You can sit there and watch the ASMR
murder you video.
Alright, this was funny.
It was fun. What's next?
You said...
Yeah, that's what I just said.
This one's over.
It's been three and a half hours.
I don't want to really
pivot to anything else right now.
I think we're going to clean this up
with a really good one.
The one that's coming up next is called
Way of the Warrior.
It is a full on green screen
real people in like costumes
fighting game.
This is where we're going to end it tonight.
We're going to pick that up. We're going to try it out.
It is an actual costume fighting game.
Give me one second.
I didn't even know what that image was.
I just saw that there was an image loaded into OBS.
I didn't want to blind you with those bars.
Let's put it up whatever it was.
Head to head fighting action.
Huge digitized characters.
60 to 80 moves per character.
And secrets to die for.
You've got my attention.
This is one of Naughty Dog's earliest games.
Is that really what this is?
Holy fuck, you're right. I didn't know that.
This is Naughty Dog's first game.
That's pretty cool.
Here's some gamer history for you here.
You're right.
How does it feel like I look like this guy?
Sometimes.
Music by White Zombie.
Real band, huh?
Way of the Warrior.
Thanks for using my subpar translating skills.
Hey, you were the one guy today.
I already love it.
This is like comedy mortal combat.
Or is this supposed to be taken seriously?
I don't know yet.
Mortal combat is already kind of like comedy mortal combat, isn't it?
Find the way.
CDI Genon?
Okay, here we go.
The fighting has but one empty page.
And it is written that the way of this tournament's winner
will fill this page,
finish the book, and tip the scales
in favor of good or evil for eternity.
The balance of the world will lay
in the hands of everyone.
Find the way, noble challenger.
Find the way of the warrior.
CDI Genon?
Okay, here we go.
Game? Arena? I can't...
No, game.
Arena? Names?
No name.
No name. Skill.
Whatever, let's just go.
Let's go to just game.
Jakey, Jake,
Dragon, Australia,
Hong,
Jitsu,
Bar, brawling?
That's high.
Style.
Military UK.
I kind of want...wait, what about you?
Style? Original.
What is original style?
Jakey, Jake?
Alright, let's do it.
Alright, I'm going to say Muay Thai France.
I want to do Muay Thai.
Oh, I need a second controller.
Uh oh, wait.
I don't want to hear any more exposition from this skull.
You already did this.
The graveyard.
The throne room.
The temple.
The pit. Alright, the pit.
Alright, the game is
demo mode? Tournament mode.
Okay, we're going to do
tournament mode
at the pit. Right?
Are we ready?
There we go. Alright.
Look at those skulls.
Those are secret characters.
Are they really?
Blue man, Jax, and scorpion.
Here we go.
Wait, he grows?
Alright, that's a dog. Does it block?
Is there a move list?
Wait, no.
Stop.
Can I do moves?
How did he do that?
Sonic the Hedgehog.
Come on.
Dude, this is hard as shit.
Rematch. Come on.
Alright, that's upper punch.
Lower punch.
I'm trying to do like forward, down, forward,
C. Down, forward, C. Down, back,
C. I
used the combo.
I didn't even do a move.
Hold on a minute.
I need the instructions.
Okay, it says
special moves, nine, page nine.
Special moves.
In order to perform a special move,
you need to develop some special button technique.
First, it is important to remember that forward and back
refer to the direction of the character. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sweep attack. First down, then
down, forward, then down, forward.
What? Press D-pad
down, then press D-pad down, forward,
then press D-pad forward.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Down, down, forward,
down.
Skill points and magic.
Push the D-pad to the back and hold for two seconds.
Okay, cool.
Hold B button and press D-pad.
Alright, here we go.
Special moves. Perform a sweep move, then press
the left shift.
Press D-pad down, diagonally, then press down, diagonally,
D-pad down.
I have
whatever.
D-pad down, then D-pad down,
forward, then D-pad down.
I'm gonna win. D-pad down, then D-pad down, forward,
then D-pad down.
Means down, down, forward, then forward.
Okay, down,
forward, down, forward, down.
This is why fighting games aren't mainstream, folks.
Well,
I don't know about that.
If I hold left, it should charge.
I don't even get to do one move.
He did one...got it!
Why did I get hurt by that?
This is why
Smash is the most popular fighting game,
Omega Low.
Fox is at the bottom of the tier list.
I have to win one.
Come on!
It's anybody's game.
Don't lose.
Do a leg sweep.
I'm trying, man.
Please block.
Block. That's block.
Get the fuck out of here!
What was that?
That's frame precedence?
What's with the frame precedence? Bullshit.
Trying to figure out moves.
He's doing a...
I just got fatality'd.
Have you found the block button?
Yeah, it's B, but I can't even block.
He gets to throw shit
in the air.
I just threw something at him.
He gets such fucking
frame precedence, it's not even fair.
We both move at the same time,
and then his one hurts me instead of him.
Instead of me hurting him.
Block.
Block's not gonna do shit.
Sword versus fist.
I'm gonna check a new character out.
Do low heavies.
I don't think there is low heavy.
I think there's just punch and kick.
No, don't rematch.
Alright, one more try.
It's gonna be quiet.
It's hard.
New character.
You gotta use your burst.
Yeah, I know.
Alright, we're gonna do it with Shake.
We're gonna go with Shakey Jake.
How am I supposed to know what the tier list looks like?
Turn the skill level down.
Alright, here we go.
I get a weapon this time.
Do you have any fucking moves?
Oh, I thought she disappeared.
Shitty Jake. No, it's just...
I get to turn the skill level down.
Get the fuck over here.
Don't be dazed.
I got a fucking force field now.
This play is just so much better.
This is just somebody that knows exactly how to play this fucking game.
Dude, you're getting recycled.
How do you grab?
I keep getting grabbed.
I think I got it.
I'm gonna do the good A bait.
Is it gonna work every time?
Come here. Let me win one, please.
You're getting farmed.
How does every character have 60 moves?
Yeah, that's what I want to know too.
I think they're physically talking about even just low punch and low kick and shit.
I don't think it's possible to win.
I know it's physically impossible to win.
I can't do it.
Spamming's not gonna help me.
It's not gonna do anything.
What do I think of the music?
I can't even pay attention to it.
You know when you play a fighting game versus somebody
and you know that you're a thousand times better than they are?
And you let up a little
so they get to win at least one of the matches
so they don't never fucking play video games with you ever again for the rest of your life?
Why can't they do that to me here?
Nobody wants to play with the person that's gonna win every time.
You gotta give a little bit of give
so I think that I'm doing okay.
Even if you're gonna win every single match.
It's like, man, I got you in that one.
Yeah, you totally did.
Nice job, man. I didn't see that coming.
I didn't see that throw coming.
Hey, you want to play tomorrow, right?
Yeah, yeah, I love this game.
I got him now.
I got him locked in forever.
Look at the instructions, lol.
Yeah, I just read the manual.
You don't need to send me a PDF.
I have it right here.
I have the physical. Hold on.
I want to see these characters. I'm not still gonna lose.
If I lose
this next match
I'll get 50 subs.
Well, the best character in the game
he has the Honda Punch.
Don't get cocky. I can't lose this.
Yeah, I'm not gonna have to give 50 subs.
It's not gonna happen.
It's cheesy. It's not cheesy.
The developers have it in the game
so I'm gonna use it.
Oh.
Hey, dude, you're kind of being an asshole
with that kind of exploity kind of move.
Well, if the devs didn't want it in the game
they wouldn't have programmed it in.
I win. No subs.
Scamming.
Oh, this is a really important question for you guys.
So I have
I didn't even know they were making this.
I bought it because I wanted to play it on stream
eventually.
But, uh, Kingdoms of Alamore
the re-reckoning
they re-kind of did the game
I bought it for Xbox 360.
Is the Xbox 360 version
better than the remake?
Should I play it on the original version?
Or should I play the new one?
Shit. But it's fun shit.
Kingdoms of Alamore. What?
I'll play either. It's a shitty remaster.
It's not a remake.
The game's boring. Don't even play it.
Bad game. What do you mean bad game?
New one looks nicer.
We'll see. Got some quality of life fixes.
Alright.
If I end up with less than 50% health
at the end of this round here
then I will give 100 subs.
Good.
Uh, crisis averted.
We're good. He's too OP.
I'm fine.
Ah!
I didn't make any bets this time.
Every anime fight ever.
Get off!
Ten seconds.
It just goes to...
Nevermind.
I was looking at chat. I wasn't paying attention to the game.
I was looking at the chat room.
I think my 3DO is
overheating.
Where's my character?
Why am I green?
What is happening?
I think the 3DO is going to break.
This thing was 600 bucks.
It better not be breaking.
It's going to be fine.
By the way, it's not even 600.
We're good.
It was way less than 600 bucks.
I just want you to think that I spent way too much money on this.
Dunk it in water.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Put it in rice.
Put the 3DO in a bag of rice.
And then put it in the fridge.
I learned a new move.
This is horrible fucking gameplay.
I'm embarrassed for you.
Because you're watching me do this.
You know what I mean?
I'm embarrassed for you guys.
Because you have to experience this.
I'm embarrassed because you guys are
embarrassed for me.
So I'm embarrassed for you.
This gameplay is so bad.
That if somebody came in right now
that has never seen me stream
and watched this, they would have to assume
that every single one of you was a fucking bot.
That I was viewbotting.
This guy's playing a fighting game
and he's just crouch kicking
and not talking.
He's just losing and shit.
They have to be viewbotting.
They have to be.
Why don't you guys just start saying
you know when somebody's
just egregiously viewbotting
and all the comments are just like
wow, can't believe you just did that.
Nice one.
Loving the stream.
Blowing my mind.
And then they'll say in the chat
they'll talk about something that doesn't even exist.
Hey man, what setup are you using?
I'm really starting to get into the idea
of playing games on my PC
and I'm just curious what I should be using.
Well I have a GTX 1080
and that's what I use.
That's what I would say you should use too.
What happened to me?
No, don't use emotes.
No emotes. Don't do that.
Only say wow.
Cool gameplay or something.
Emotes have given it away.
I should accidentally alt tab
and show like five
viewbotting programs and go oh shit.
And it's this 56
this 5,673 people there.
I alt tab and it's just
5,672
viewbots.
Because I'm watching my own stream.
I have my own stream open.
I got power up.
I'm done.
I'm done. I'm done.
I do want to see the secret characters though.
There's so many people left to fight. I don't want
no. This one's supposed to be good.
There's still so many more.
There's still a stack of like
fucking so many 3DO games. But we need
a 3DO break I think after
this. This is just
Mortal Kombat.
And how the fuck is that move fair?
Explain to me how an entire
screen filling move. You can't
dodge this fair. Gonna be blocked?
Oh it can be. Okay.
I want to do the uppercut into the acid
like in Mortal Kombat.
It's kind of just making me want to play Mortal Kombat.
Is that me saying hey?
Stop. Only I can do that.
So what should we do next?
What should we do after 3DO? After 3DO
cooldown. I could do saw.
I could go back to saw.
Do saw 2.
I could do super monkey ball.
I could do
face painting. I don't think I'm going to do that.
Doom Eternal?
I don't know.
Monkey ball? Monkey ball next?
Well not today. But I mean like next stream.
Monkey ball next stream? Super monkey ball
next stream?
Super monkey ball next stream.
Lock it in.
There's one. That's a no more baby
games. Yeah and then I'll go
you know what? We'll do VR. I'm going to give you a date for VR.
Because there's so many VR games I need to compile.
Let's do VR.
How about
The week of the 28th.
And then we'll lead into
FTK.
So we'll do some VR stuff.
For like that 28th.
The week of the 29th. 30th.
Lock it in. I want to get back into it.
It's been a long time.
Half Life Alyx? Yeah.
We'll start with Half Life Alyx.
That's something I've wanted to do for a long time.
What about Drew Crew?
Drew Crew is I think not going to happen
for a while. You got that
one chance randomly a few
weeks ago. Remember where I panicked because
I didn't have anything to do and had nothing to play and I freaked
out. Something happened.
What happened? And I opened up
one of the Nancy Drew games and then I immediately closed
and freaked out. When was that?
Okay. It was weird.
It was Fall Guys? Oh
that's right because the Fall Guys servers were off.
I haven't done that move.
I don't even like this game but I'm still here.
I don't know. It's alright.
These songs are all the same song.
Uh oh.
I need to play Lisa the Painful.
I'm not going to play Lisa the Painful.
Not on stream.
Can you play
SSX Tricky?
I don't know.
It's going to be a painful
chat experience. What about Ratatouille?
Funny that you say that.
I told you that over the next couple of weeks.
I wasn't going to tell you when it was going to happen.
But Ratatouille is
going to happen. I'm not going to tell you when.
It's going to happen when you least
expect it. That wouldn't have been great if I had that
ready to go right now and I switched right now.
It's not going to replace FTK.
Can you go off the edge?
You wouldn't expect it during FTK.
Yeah, neither would I because that would be
a
waste of resources
and time.
When is FTK? October 3rd.
3 p.m. Pacific. October 3rd is the new
date for FTK.
The Gran Turismo 4.
Is there any actual driving game
that would be fun to scream? Would that be fun?
Is that one of those scenarios
where I would just be terrible at it and it would crash
and I'd give up after five minutes?
How?
Showrunner?
I actually looked into that. I just want to be able to drive
cargo over snow and mud
and stuff, right? It might be fun.
Maybe I'll play that soon.
We should do an FTK
command.
We'll play the Ratatouille game
on September 28th.
What? Oh, shit.
I actually did promise it already
when you least expect it, right?
Oh.
Did he just say find something new?
He's mad that I'm doing the same move.
He's getting bored of the scream too, just like
you guys are.
On VR!
I don't expect you to keep your promise. Yeah, I did
every promise on July 30th.
Alright, there are only two
I'm going to try as hard as I can to get through this. I want to beat the game.
I'm ready.
I'm going to just absolutely steamroll
the other two competitors. Let's go.
Do VR and Ratatouille?
This whole
room has to be set up for VR and has to
stay that way for a little while.
I like to stand up and do VR. I don't really like
the seated VR. That makes me want to puke.
So,
standing VR, I have to kind of
move stuff in the room and get it ready, so it has to stay
like that for a little while. Beat Saber?
I played Beat Saber already. It was good.
I had a lot of fun.
I don't know if I would play it again, but I played
a lot of it during the last VR stream.
I'm not going to find something new. This works.
I'm not ready to order
anything else off the menu yet. I know what I like.
Hag me when Jerma
lies. Uh, one time
I shoved a brick of cheese up my nose.
True, true. Okay, how about this?
I'm going to stream for another 12 hours
today. Is this the last boss?
Is this the boss?
I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna.
That's not true. Hag him.
Platforms? Yeah, this is kind of cool.
Cheesed your way to victory.
Yes.
It's still a victory. He's
so pissed. He doesn't want to give me
the medal at the end of the game.
Oh, damn it. Do something different.
You know, I've never had to get at a good asshole
like you with a trophy.
Now what? I won. You don't deserve it.
Let's get to the end.
Oh, I got
Contra'd.
Yeah, I got to the level 3 in Contra on
easy and the game said, uh, please
please play again.
This time on the normal difficulty.
Well, yeah, that's okay.
All right. All right.
I'm gonna call it here.
We're gonna come back with Super Monkey Ball.
Monkey Ball now? I can't do Monkey Ball
now. I have
discs surrounding me. I have to
clean this shit up.
Today was Psychic Detective
Day and I loved every second of it.
There's a bunch more 3DO stuff, but
I think we need, we need to, we need to cool down.
It's too much.
Too much weird shit in a row.
So I will see you guys
on
uh, on Monday.
I'll see you Monday.
For Super Monkey Ball.
Gritty goes on fire. Yeah, it's like
freaking me out. Things like heating up and glitching
and shit.
See you guys for
Super Monkey Ball.
Thanks for watching as always.
Just watch the Psychic Detective endings
on YouTube.
Maybe I will in the bath later.
I have to turn this guy off.
This guy's gotta go.
The bath stream?
Okay, if I had
clothes on, could I do a bath stream?
Would that be okay?
Yes. Would it?
Alright, well let me think about that.
I'll think about that. Uh, let's go say hello
to Vinny. Like seven
days to die.
Not yet. Not yet.
Because we have credits to do.
Who's that guy? I want to be that character. That was like
Skeletor from, uh,
Prang. What?
What's the game called?
What the fuck is the name of the game? The game with the
skeleton with the sword and the shield. What is it?
Uh, what is it called?
Kill, uh,
Killer Instinct. Not the
brain that sits inside of the guy in Ninja Turtles.
No. Alright, here come the
credits. Thanks for watching everybody.
Ooh, this is different.
Ooh, this is
cool. Uh, that's pretty
sick actually. Nice job.
Thank god the music ended.
Now it's readable. That's actually
readable. Thanks for the subs
everybody. I appreciate it.
It's like your names are being etched
into the book. How long does it take? I mean,
we're at age. I can't be that much longer.
I mean, there's a lot of subs.
There's always a lot of subs. It always takes a long time.
There's always tons of fucking subs.
Happy birthday.
Am I gonna stream on my birthday?
Oh shit, I might have a
birthday stream on Monday.
It might be a happy birthday stream
on Monday. That's very possible.
I'll bake myself a birthday cake.
There needs to be music, doesn't there?
Oh, the music's not even hooked up here.
How old are you? 74th birthday?
No. You guys can take a guess of how
old I am. Wish my dad a happy birthday.
Hey, Tasty Turd! You might not
know that that's your son's screen name.
And you might have just heard that. Wait, it's my
birthday, and my son's screen name is
Tasty Turd, but I'm sorry to be the one to
bring that up first. But
your son says happy birthday, dad.
Thank you, Tasty Turd.
I will see you guys on Monday.
Have a great rest of your night. We're gonna raid Vinny.
Go say hello. Take care
of yourselves. And good night.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait a second, wait a second,
wait a second. I'm gonna give $100
earlier. I wanna make sure I catch
this. I just caught it right here.
10,000 bits
from
Makao
Nuko. Thank you for the
$100.
Irma, your content always seems to make me laugh and I'm feeling
down. I started watching a YouTube video seven
years ago. Keep doing
what you enjoy. Lots of love.
Thanks a lot. Seven years is a long time.
I'm surprised that
some of you guys have been around for that long and you still
think this is interesting. I think we've
said this before, but even after like watching seven or
eight seasons straight years
of a TV show,
you kind of start to go,
eh, I'm kind of over it. So
I'm just happy that a lot of you guys
are still around. I'm glad that you are.
You didn't say it was interesting.
Alright
guys, I'll see you later. See you
Monday. Let's go raid
Vinesauce. See you
later.