Hello. How are you? How you doing? It's good to be back. You haven't, hey, you haven't even heard
my voice in like two months. Well, except that maybe three or four times I popped in and said,
look at me. During the rerun streams, which, oh yeah, I did plenty of those. I did two of them
and then they never happened again. These community subs.
I'm hitting the community sub lottery right now. There's so many. I can't eat this. Thank you for
the like 200 community subs right off the bat. Like 30 of you. Oh my God. Yeah. I'm here. I'm back.
We are not going to start streaming yet. I have, we got a lot to talk about first.
We are not ready to just go into the stream. There's, we, there are some things. Oh, I'm
already seeing the monkess. Well, you should be monkessing because we got some changes
that are going to be made as of today. I'm here. I will be here. Oh, it feels so good to do that.
I haven't done that in a long time. So many of these. Yeah. No, we got a lot to talk about.
I'm not just going to get right into it. I'm going to get right into talking about,
talking about things though, but very importantly though, we'll really get started.
I've got to talk about steak. They sure are the most delicious thing I've ever had in my life.
There, you can make a sandwich out of a hundred percent pure whole wheat beef.
This is how I like to do it. I like to fold it over, but it's all right. It looks like dog food.
All right. It looks like dog food, but it doesn't taste like it. I promise you,
it doesn't taste like dog food. It's like a hundred percent whole grain beef.
July 30. You promised number one kept. I just spit all over you. I hope not.
And he got a haircut. A little. Yeah, I did. Can you see? Hey, I'm fine. Everybody thought
I may have been like being like decrepifying. No, I'm fine. Well, well, not really.
That's what we're going to talk about today. Well, you know, so the first thing I'm going to,
look at my teeth. I would eat this whole thing right now, but it's been sitting here for about
like 20 minutes, 30 minutes. It's kind of cold. That doesn't mean that it's not delicious.
What the fuck? Where's my camera? Is this, there can't be, there's 10,000 people here right now.
What the fuck is happening? Why are there over 10,000 people here? There's 12,000 people here.
I, Hey, remember me, your favorite streamer. Now I'm like on the spot. Shit. I thought there was
going to be like, I thought there was going to be like 1600 people left. Uh, Hey, welcome to the
channel, everybody. No, no, I'll get real. It's time to get real. Stacom's brand Stacom's.
This is not an ad. Oh, doesn't this look like an ad? Don't think about the Stacom's packaging.
It just looks like an advertisement. Like if this was just sitting back here, that's an ad,
right? In the freezer, this is an ad. Oh, by the way, can we, can we just quickly look at the back
of this? What's that say? Let's see. Hey, can somebody read me one of the ingredients please?
What's the ingredient? What is that? What's it say? Wait, it doesn't say a hundred. It just says
beef in all capitals. Why is this like somebody in chat? It's why is it in all capitals? Does that
stand for something else? No, right? That's not like Beatles eggs and emulsified frogs, right?
Oh, he's stalling. He's stalling. All right. I'll get to the real bullshit. I'll get to the real
shit. I got, I'm going to get to the hill. Let's get to the real shit. Okay. I haven't streamed for
two months. All right. So anyways, if you don't know, there are 13,000 people here now. This is
the most people I've had on my stream for like fucking a year. Okay. So I took a leave of absence.
I was gone for about two and a half months for the sole reason to try to help let me focus and
diagnose an issue I was having. I have back pain and chest pain that it seems to become from a
mystery source. And I can announce to you right here today that I still don't know what's wrong
with me. I am currently on painkillers, not, no, no, I'm not on narcotics. I'm on non-narcotic
painkillers. And I had two injections in my ass at the same time. One on either side and
okay. Yeah. On my hips. I'll say hip. I had two injections in my ass and they're supposed to keep
me going. Painkillers. I don't want to get to a point where I'm taking these every day for the
rest of my life. But while I'm on these, I'm going to just continue to stream. I'm not going to
disappear for another three or four months. I really didn't want to have it go more than two
or three months that I just, I want to stream. I want to be here. I got God hand to play,
God damn it. One of my promises that I have to keep today. Oh, by the way, there is a promise on
here. We'll get to it. I'm just not doing it. But a lot of people are saying, take care of yourself.
We waited. We'll wait more. I appreciate that. But I don't want to wait anymore. There's so many
things that I want to do. There's so many things that I have planned. I don't want to just not be
away anymore. So what's going to happen here is because I'm still in the process of figuring this
out, it, that doesn't stop. So we're going back to the pre Vegas stream schedule. I'm going to be
streaming three days a week. That will let me have time to be able to continue to focus on this, but
still stream and still be here. Right? Secondly, and this is the biggest change of all, and this
is something that a lot of people are probably going to be sad to hear this, but it's necessary
and it's something that I have to do. And I'm going to say it just right now. We're going to
rip the bandaid off. The end of the stream wind down is going away. I am no longer reading bits
on the channel. It's gone as of today. And the reason why I have to do this is because if I can
only stream a few times a week and I know that my streams are only going to be about four to six
hours, I want to be able to have as much time as possible doing whatever it is I'm doing.
And those of you that have been here for a long time, you know that if a stream was four, five,
six, seven hours, that actually mean this, it actually meant the stream was about eight or
nine hours because of the time after the stream, right? The post stream wind down. So it's going
away and it allows me to sit here if I'm still comfortable and not have to focus on, Hey, it's
been like four or five hours. I'm okay. But I know I got about an hour or two after the stream maybe
to do the bit readings. So it was a hard, that was a hard decision to come to because I don't,
I know about a lot of people like that and I like that too, but what will replace it.
And when I say replace, I mean like not, it's not going to happen all the time. It'll happen very,
very sparingly is I'll start doing them in the middle of streams. If there's a game or if there's
a comb stream or we're just hanging out or something and I'm able to be able to kind of
split my attention, I'll just do it in the middle of streams. No TTS. I'm not doing that. I will,
I will never turn that on for any reason. So that will happen. It's not going to happen all the time
though. That's going to happen once in a blue moon. So TLDR before we really get started,
my problem still persists. I'm on pain medication. So I'll be, I'm all right,
but I got to still figure out what the hell is wrong with me. We've ruled out a shit load of
really scary things. So now we move forward into trying to figure out what the hell this actually
really is. Thanks for the gold kind streamer. You're welcome. Although I didn't give you anything,
at least the bad shit is ruled out. Yes. And we are continuing to do that because now at this point,
when you get to a scenario where this is just such a strange problem that I'm having, all you,
all I'm doing at this point is ruling out bad things until somebody goes, Oh, I think we got it.
There are 15,000 people here. All right. Are you guys ready? Are you guys ready? What's the first
thing I'm going to say on stream? What should the first thing be? Hold on. I got to reheat these
steaks. Okay. Let's do 25 minutes. What happens if, okay, nobody, no, I don't even want to say that.
Did the myth busters ever do this? Like, did you ever microwave like a ham sandwich for 30 minutes?
What happens? I'm not going to do it. Don't do that. If that's like, like, did the myth busters
do this? Did the myth busters ever turn the microwave on for a long time? What happens? Oh shit.
Okay. I've done, I've got so many stories locked up here. Stake them subscribed.
You are going to hear so many just random out of the blue. I'm going to just be like, Oh,
and by the way, like six weeks ago, I was on the drive through. All right. Well, come on,
let's go. I've been telling people I was going to play this game for a long time.
This is the main July 30th promise. Yeah. Resident Evil four is on there too, but I want to do this.
I want to, this is what I want to do first. I want to give this some time. I'm only going to
play Resident Evil four as like, Oh, look how high July 30th. He played it. I'm going to,
I'm going to get to the first time that somebody says, and then I'm going to turn it off.
That's my cue to turn it off. Are you guys ready for God hand? Look, I could play it again. Like
I can't do all these things on July 30th fog hand. All right. Hold on a sec. Okay. You ready?
It's installing. Oh, is this game good? I need to be real with me. Did he already do normal heroes
too? All right. Hold on. This is installing. Give me one sec. You just sit there and look
at that for a minute. What was it? Yeah, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm prepared.
Oh, the fuckers didn't think I was ready to do this. Did you come on? We mode.
Okay. Here we go. Pre-recorded. Oh, I know it is not mission seven, right? Revenge mission seven.
You would, would you like me to prove that it's not pre-recorded? I can. Here we go. Ready?
I will prove to you. This is not a YouTube video. Circle, circle, circle, circle, circle,
left, right, left, right, circle, circle, down, down, down, down, down, up, up, up, circle. See?
Like there's no way I could have fucking matched that up perfectly. You think I could have matched
that up perfectly? No. It's so loud. Yeah, whatever. The hours spent practicing that.
No, that's impossible. All right. Let's make this impossible.
Ryan's gym, Naomi's lab, Ryan's gym, side job three, side job two, side job one, two,
three, two, two, three, three, three, two, three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three,
three, three, four, four. I can't even do it right. Whatever. Revenge mission seven.
Add this to the list of promises that I've made. With the rose nasty, correct? It's fake. It's not
fake. Look, I'll prove it again. Ready? If this was fake, this would be really hard to time.
It would be hard to do that. Three, two, one. Wait, wait, wait. All right. Let's go. Let's get him.
These are the rose nasty, right? It's your nose. Okay. I went the wrong way. My nose is
fucked up that way. It was the wrong way. My face is getting skewed. Joe Otto. All right. If I fail
this, I have to eat a steak and shoot. I can't even hear anything. I haven't played No More Heroes
in a really long time. Do you remember my last stream? My last stream was like three months ago.
Before that, when was No More Heroes 2? Like fucking four months ago? You suck. LOL. Yeah.
I don't remember the fucking move. I got a minute and 30. I'll be fine. I think I care so much about
proving to you guys this is real when it very obviously is. Why is it still in my head? Like
somebody's going to think I'm fucking mindless. Do I really care that much about that? The game is
still live. Well, it's all right. It's only going to be on the screen for like a minute and four
seconds. Why is he playing this? There it is. Promise done. That was revenge mission seven with
the rose nasty on hard. Maybe. All right. How are we doing on? How are we doing on? You know what
I'm saying? God hand. Wait, I'm going to delete this. I'm switching between my sources guys.
All right. I'm ready. All right. I just freaked out for a second because
you got to see this. So he got this high capacity PlayStation three, right?
And yeah, I may have like torn it open. Fuck. No, I needed that. All right. I have to hold this
together. Make sure you guys recycle. OK, as effect. OK, so this is it. You want to know
just how much of a fucking idiot I really am. So I bought a PlayStation three because I needed
one for God hand, obviously. And I used to have one, but I got rid of it. Right. So I get this.
And I don't know why I thought this, but I did. This says, as you see, OK, like includes, right?
Like includes all this stuff. Like, oh, look, it includes. What does it include? That is,
I thought there was twenty five hundred games and one hundred and ninety fucking movies on this
thing. I was like, what? Hold on. Like, why is it preloaded with seventy three thousand songs?
What is one of these like fucking hack boxes? I was like this twenty five hundred. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. Right. I forgot about that. I forgot that PlayStation three was back in the age
when space was a really big deal. And talking about that, you could have like sixty seven
million MP3 files on your hard drive was a huge deal. Not in twenty twenty. You could have over
sixty six trillion JPEGs. It's like, wow, that's a lot. Oh, that's why you're saying Mass Effect.
Why is it telling me to download God Hand again? I don't want you to see that. That's a spoiler.
Get out of here. Why is it down? Why am I done? I don't have to download God Hand again. I just
did. It just installed. Hey, it's a good thing I could put twenty five hundred God Hands on here.
All right. Now I have to actually make the audio different. Is it the updater? No,
no, no. I'll be ready in a second here. You hear that? OK, God. Yeah. All right. Here we go.
It's time. I've been promising one. Here's the thing. There are fifteen thousand of you here
right now. OK, I have been promising one person for the last probably year and a half
that I was going to play this game. Oh, please. There is a signal there. And it was me. Warning,
you have it. OK, let me do this, too. Oh, it feels good to be it. God, it feels good to be playing
games in front of an audience. Well, now that's loud. This game contains scenes of violence.
Oh, my God. There's so many community subs. So much money's come in. And I'm ready. Dread just
gave a fucking hundred community subs like Jesus, man. Oh, wait, hold on. I got to turn off the
we thing. No, no, no. I think I just closed all windows on my computer. Did I do that?
Why is that even an option? No, close all. No, no, no. OK, we're good. We're good. Are we good?
I don't fuck it. Am I still live? I don't know. I think so. Just don't touch me there.
So I'm like, I like this music, though. Oh, shit. Did I already make a joke about this music?
Like two years ago, I said it was beach music. Another hundred fucking subs ready.
Why can't I press start? Oh, wait, wait. What's going on? All right. Help me here. Ready?
That's another hundred fucking subs ready. Ready? You got you guys are going to go.
It's a ton of money, dude. Thank you. And the next time you're in Vegas,
hit me up. OK, so you guys got to help me here. He's insane. No, I'm a little rusty. OK, ready?
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three. Are we matched up?
Load game. New game. Load game. New game. We good? The delay? Not at all.
It's not a 10 second delay. Get out of here. Mod. I need a mod to do this. Mod. Is it all right?
Is it too? Is it too early or too late? I don't have any mods. That's kind of a bad test.
All right. Ready? When I make noise, use it. All right. How about this? Ready? You got it.
Turn that off. Vibration. One, two, one, two, one, two, three, one, two, three, four.
Good. So I'm late. Am I late? It's a slight delay. Me? Am I late? Or is the game? Am I early?
I'm late. My voice is a little late. OK, got it. Check it out. Ready? Here we go. Ready?
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, one, one, one. Up, up, up, up, up. OK. I thought that just said
enemy lifeguard. What the hell does that mean? Here we go. New game. I'm ready. No more stalling.
Well, I'm not that good at video games. Oh, this is ugly. Like really ugly. I thought
this was supposed to be PlayStation 2 on the PlayStation 3. Upgraded graphics.
Easy means normal. Well, why didn't you tell me that?
Or how do you play? Didn't I hate this game when I played it for 10 seconds?
I swear to God, I hated this game. I was like, oh, this game's stupid. Is there a reason why I
stopped playing this? Probably. Why am I playing this again? OK. All right. You got square, square,
square. Let's block. Is there no tutorial? OK, is there a is there a lock on? The game is actually
terrible. Stop. OK, there's a dodge. Let me just check out the moves. OK, how do I turn?
R2. Does R2 do anything? L2. L2 does the Dark Souls. Oh, should the guy? Oh, no.
God, I hope the guy is here. That has requested this game a million times.
Snoozen, are you here? That's the only reason why I'm doing that. I was going to play a fighting
game in the arcade. Stinger. What is it? What is that? What button is that supposed to be?
Pretty good DDT. He's not here. He's not even here. He's going to shit his pants when he
realizes he missed this stream. It's actually kind of fun. All right. R1 does like a super move.
Shockwave. Ball Buster. Can you string stuff together? Can I move? I can't move the camera
back. This game was made in like 1998. Kind of like Dark Souls. Cool. I made that joke already.
Fuck. I'm pretty rusty. Sorry. Guys, I haven't made any jokes in two and a half months. You
understand that, right? I've been lying down watching The Chase on my iPad for two months.
I know a lot more trivia than I did before, but my comedy might be a little bit diminished.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Bod Stomp. Holy shit. Do it again? Okay. That's an EU game show?
No, no, no, no, no, no. You don't understand. I watched the American version, so it's the beast.
All right. Let's get on with this. That's really all the content we have.
It's just The Chase. I don't have any other content. It's all my content.
Shit. Wait, this is a, this is a, oh. Wait, go back, back, back, back, back, back, back,
run, run, run, run, run, run back. I don't even know what way is back.
Tutorial. Right. Use the right analog stick to evade. What was that? Food? Nice.
There's coins and shit. All right. Nice. Okay. So I got 400 gold. This is a way.
I think I'm getting the hang of this. I, is it 30 FPS? I mean, it is a PlayStation 2 game.
What about circle? Wait, whoa, hold on a minute. Triangle is a move too. Hold on.
Okay. Triangle X and square are punches, kicks, and got it. All right.
What's this? Do you buy stuff? I'm starting to like this game. He's got a weapon. Can you use
weapons? Oh, all right. I picked that up. Yeah, I can. Oh yeah. This game's got way cooler.
You can make your own game. What? You can make your own game. I think I may have read that wrong.
Harry. Oh, cool. All right. Level one. I can't wait for him to never play this again.
Well, this, this is what, this is the goal for me is to play this. Press start. Roulette. Wild
pitch. Select a technique to exchange. I want wild pitch. What? Oh, uses one orb, uses two orbs
or three orbs. There's a dev here. I'd be interesting because doesn't the studio not exist
anymore? Techniques. Okay. So I could wait. So that's left jab, straight left hook, uppercut.
Oh yeah. Okay. Dude. Okay. You know what this, you guys are playing WWF, no mercy.
Do I unlock moves? You guys have never played no mercy? Oh yeah. That's right. I'm an old guy.
I don't think I have anything I can do about this, right? Guard breaker, charged weight,
charged punch. I think so. Wait, I already have that. That's down and triangle. All right.
I like that one. I'm an old guy. Yeah, I am. German is the only person streaming this game on
Twitch. I feel like you could say that about almost every stream that's done on this channel,
with the exception of like Mario Sunshine. All right. Let me see this thing. This is important.
So you can cycle choices. Oh, all right. Well, how do I throw this at this guy?
No. All right. Nice. I'm into it. I'm into it. Why is this controller so sticky? It's kind of grossing
me out. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Level down? What do you mean
level down? You can level down? Wait, level down? What happens if you die? PS3 controllers are just
sticky by default. You know what? I actually, I'm dead. I believe that. I actually believe what you
just said. Continue. Yes, of course. They're just sticky. It's just the way it is. Somebody
paints it. All right. So I have, I can't, no more fucking around. Let's go. I'm going to beat this
right now. I used to do that. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Now, now you got me in my game mode. Use
guard breaker. Okay. You will. It's just a, all right. I got, I'm not going to, what's wrong with
him? Yeah. Oh yeah. I remember laughing at that. I thought it was so funny. Stomp him.
Cool. Oh, I, that was, that's a lot of money. I think I did better. So I got more money.
No time limit or anything, right? That was, there was a hundred subs. When? All right. Now
let me try this. Ready? Check this out. Ready? Okay. Divine smash. That was pretty good. That
was pretty cool. I can't wait to just make upper cuts only. Give me that. If you're looking for
insane combos, you're not going to get them from me. I'm pretty much, I, guys, you remember when
you watched play Lord of the Rings? Remember how everyone was so mad that I was just doing the
X, X, X combo the whole game, even though I had other stuff. Oh, wait, snoozing copters here.
Snoozing. What's up? I have, I have to read this. They snooze and gave a hundred dollars
and thank you for that, but I need to read this because this is like, this is, this person is
waiting for the stream for like two years. I'm so happy you're finally playing it. It's the best
one week early birthday gift I could have gotten. This is the only time I'll ever give a hundred
bucks. There's so many moves to unlock once you get the hub world. There's a baseball home run
swing as a special move. Chat was lying. I'd never missed this stream. I was here for the no more
hero section. You liars. Well, you're going to be really disappointed when I give up on 15 at the
exact same place that I stopped last year. Shit, I wasn't fast enough. You got to be fast. What the
hell? Why did I watch so many episodes of this chase and not like play games? What the fuck? Oh
my God. What the fuck? Okay. Do a move. Wild pitch. Wait, wait, wait. Do it again. Do it again.
Step on it. Step on it. Stop his head. Run, run, run. Is there any, where's the, where's the
cherries? I want to do wild pitch ball buster. All right. What is that? Okay. Somebody tell me
what the bar on the bottom means. What's the bar mean? Oh my God. He's going to follow me. He's
going to follow me. He's going to follow me up here. He's going to follow me up here. He's
going to follow me. R2. Please do R2. What? What is this? What? Is this the god hand?
Oh shit. This is the god hand. Get the fuck over here. I didn't know what that was.
All right. You can stop playing now. Yeah, maybe I will. Oh, it feels good to be back. Don't kick
that, right? This is a red barrel. All right. What the, that would have been really bad.
Okay. Where am I taking this? Holy shit. The whole room. Oh, burgers. All right. Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey. I should have given this game a more of a chance. I feel bad that I didn't. That was pretty
good juggle right there. You know, for the nine year old that's playing the Mortal Kombat cabinet.
That's the kind of combo where like six people around this little kid are like, yeah, yeah,
and he's like, yeah. Don't fuck this up here. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. What am I doing?
Upstairs, go upstairs. I'm not fucking around with this. Okay. Yeah, there's probably food in here.
Where is it? Oh shit. Oh my God. That just made him mad. That just made him mad. Is this cardboard?
Did this even hurt? I got to be honest. I don't think that would hurt. Is that weird for me to
say that? Like an empty wood box like that. I feel like that wouldn't hurt that much.
If it was an empty box and it wasn't that heavy. Don't you think it would just kind of like
bounce off your chest and like hurt a little? You get like a bruise. L1 is quick turn. Holy shit.
Give that person mod. Don't, I don't want that person to have power. It's a wooden crate,
not cardboard. I still, I mean, I don't, I still don't think it would hurt that much.
What the fuck? I didn't know he was right next to me. All right. Am I going to have to start
the very beginning if I lose? Wait, yes. Oh shit. Okay. I unlocked something. Uppercut.
Oh, right hook. Wait. Okay. Left jab. Oh, fuck that. Left hook. Right hook. Left hook. Right hook.
Um, hello? Left hook. Right hook. Left hook. Right hook. Why not? I can't do the same move
more than once. Oh, that's fine. Yeah. Left. Okay. Yeah. That's all right. That's all right.
That's fine. That's fine. Oh my God. I'm going to lose. Where's the food? Where's the best place
to get food? You too. That guy was not a bad guy. Oh, whoops. Well, I didn't, these just stay,
I don't know. He even went down too. Shit. That made me look real bad. You're a psycho. I'm not
a psycho. It's just, he happened to be, wait, I can, all right, let me, I'm going to save this.
There's not another little boss or anything. Is there, where are those guys? Where are those guys?
Where are you going? I, I, I don't know. I mean, people are still fighting me,
so I feel like I'm going the right way. Do they just spawn? Yes. Oh, how do I get to the end?
I don't know where I'm going. No idea what's happening. Oh God. I know. Okay. So there's a
mini map. The mini map just shows coins. I don't even have anything charged up. Oh shit. Wait,
wait, wait, that's cool. Don't practice it yet. Wait till the next level.
I love that move. That's the best move for sure. What?
Stop using, I'm abusing that move. Turn the face cam on. Ah, ah, wait, I can do that and then stop.
Oh, all right. So I have a God Hand move. I'm going to read this. Smash through a blocking
enemy by using a guard break. Yeah. Okay. Well, is he going to do that right now?
Hey, yeah, that's the technique right there. Uppercut stomp, uppercut stomp, uppercut stomp.
He's going to do it to every enemy. All right. I got a pipe. There's no food in there. Just one
coin. Oh, sorry. One assassin coin. All right. There's a guy down there. Hold on. How do I throw
it? I'll be taking that one. This game is pretty fun. I do like it. Can I go in the chimney? No.
Is this guy bigger? Okay. Here we go. You wild. Yes. One more of this guy right here. Okay. Here
we go. I'm ready. Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here. Whoa, he's angry.
He's the thing, the centipede from Mario. Oh, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay. Because now I'm going
to grovel. Why level down? Come on. That was stupid. Oh, no. I'm going to lose. I'm going to
lose. I'm going to lose. I'm going to lose. I'm going to lose. I'm going to lose. Is there a potion
in there? There's a potion. There's a potion. There's a potion in there. There's a potion in
here. I'm going the other way. I never was going to left-hand turn. Where's the potion? Where is it?
Okay. Oh, fuck. Wait, wait. Oh my god. I'm going to lose. What do I do? What do I do, guys? What do
I do? What do I do? What do I do if I lose? What do I do? What do I do about this? Shit, he's so fast.
He's so fast. It's not fair. Extract him? I don't know what that even means, dude. Shit. Come here,
come here. Get him. Get him. Get him. No. Fuck. Wait, so I have to do the whole level over again?
No, I don't. This is like part two. Yeah, we're good. We're good. We're good. Stomp his head.
Hit me with the fucked up hitboxes? Yeah, it kind of was. You're losing in the tutorial.
Well, you must be new here. That's just kind of what happened.
I'm bringing a weapon. I'm going to make sure I have everything fully loaded.
Just be happy I'm not walking off of an edge. Don't worry, Jerma, this is hard. Yeah, it looks hard,
but I'm into it. I'll get it. Okay, I want to make sure I got a weapon. When I put the weapon down,
I need to go in with a weapon. Go get him, champ. I'm going to try. This is not a bad checkpoint.
This is fine. I got plenty of time. Okay, now I'm going to throw this at him and then come back and
get that hammer. Don't use any move here. Give me the weapon. No, don't. I'm using it for when
he turns into the fucking Warcraft character. Oh shit, he has it. I'm ready. Not yet. Okay,
it's a big fat guy and then I have a big punch. Let's make this quick with the fat guy. There's
still plenty of food. Okay, good. Okay, don't even look. I missed. Head stomp, head stomp.
You dick. Fuck. You got meter. I don't want to use it. Okay, I have a full meter. I don't even
need to use it. What is this? Back fist strike one. We got to take a look and see what that is.
Is that too long? No, stop. Okay, I'm hitting circles. Wait, wait, wait. We go bang, bang,
bang, bang. That's wrong. That should go at the end. Yeah, that's angry. So it should be like,
all right, I'm good. Did it get any new roulettes or anything? Okay, let's go.
I took two bites of that Steak'em sandwich and all I smell is what the pan smells like
after you make it. Not even the Steak'ems. I'm talking about the pan. Oh shit. I'm sorry.
I should have prefaced. That was what my burp smelled like. Sorry. My burp just smelled like
the pan. Oh, there's a next area. Okay. Finally. Save the game. Thank God. Okay, enter. There's a
casino in this game. All right. Oh, wow. No way. I can't believe this is in here. Video poker. Oh,
yeah. This is great. Okay. We're going to hold on to those two kings and we're going to see if we
can get a three. All right. That's 200 bucks. Play high or low. Sure. Oh, it's going to be lower
than that card. Thank you. I'll take the 400. Let's do it again. Oh, that's going to be much
higher than a three. Why would it be lower than a three? That's the odds of that happening are
impossible. That's a perfect number. No, it's not. What are you fucking 12 on Jeremy grow up? What's
this one? Wait, I can get thrown out of the casino. I are low is the game to play if you're
into double or nothing. That's only if you guess right. You can. Oh, should I have to fight him?
He just almost insta-killed me. Kick him with the ball. Oh, shit. I didn't even hurt him.
I couldn't even hurt him. What's his name? Mr. Satan from Dragon Ball Z, right? Didn't he suck?
I remember playing Dragon Ball Z, Budokai, whatever the fuck it was called. And when you
picked Mr. Satan, you didn't do any damage to anybody, which is kind of funny that they put
him in the game in the first place. That's what I just felt like right there. What is this? Well,
you don't lose any money. I'm going back in there. I'm going back in to the dog race. I don't know
what that is. Is it blackjack? This pool is a huge pool table with bowling balls. That looks gigantic.
Am I nuts? I want to play slot machine. Whenever you clear a stage, you can try new missions at
the fighting ring. Gordon Street said this is a nice bonus for clearing all 40 missions.
What's this? Blackjack! Yes. Okay, here we go. Bet max. Heal. That's a 15 versus 3. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. I'm going to stand. Whatever. That's shitty. That's shitty. Do it again.
Axe it out again. That's a 20. You know what? I'm just going to stand. You probably got a 22.
Oh, where was the insurance? Although, who does that? Why even say insurance ever at any casino?
No one ever does it. 13 versus 5. You're going to have to stay on that one. Yep. Did I just get
omega lulled by staying with anything? If you have anything over a 12 and they show 5 or 6,
and I'm getting omega lulled on that one? Shoot. Bet max. I am betting max. It's a $500 table.
Oh, yep. This is 11. You double down immediately versus 6.
That was the worst thing that could have happened. 11 with a showing of 6.
You double that every day. That's not good. We're doing all right. Doubling down on 11.
Yeah, you do that every time. I'm not going to lose all my money, but I'm not getting up off
the table until I get to 10 grand. Safe. Draw. It's called a push. Why is this in here? This is why
you wanted me to play this game so bad, huh? You better not have blackjack or I'm going to
fucking scream. Look. Wait, look at it. We're at what? 59? Just got to win one more hand.
Why can't I put all of it on the table? You know what? Fuck it. I'm going for it. Let's go.
The person ace. You know what's funny? Sometimes the drunk guy at the table
that has no idea what's going on. How many does that have? I'm showing an ace. What do I have?
17. I'm going to double that down. Sir, you're doubling on 17. Yeah. Okay. What the? And it's
like a fucking four. Oh, cool. Like, holy shit. Sometimes you have to do the guy that's had like
fucking eight cocktails. 13 versus 12. Chad, help me out here. Now help me out here. This is a tricky
situation. Help me out here. Fucking one person. Why did I listen? I have one person said it.
16 versus 10. Shit. Oh no. What does double down mean? Double down means you have to take
another card and you put up double your bet. It's only for advanced players. No,
I, what happened to my money? I had 30, I had 6,900. There we go. Finally. Look,
I'll wait. Why is it? That's an insane payout. Why is it? Am I getting 2000?
What does this table pay out for Blackjack? Oh shit. Oh my God. That's a double. That's two
in a row. Look at that. More than what I sat down with. 18. He's going to flip over a 10,
but I got it. You got to do it. Yep. Okay. Three. That was too greedy, greedy, greedy. No,
it's not. Watch this. Anybody else? So I'm 34. I turned 35 this year. Does anybody else have
trouble counting eight and seven together every time? No matter what. Every time. I don't know
why. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Something about seven and eight together. It's just, I can't even do it.
I have to use my fingers. I'm not even kidding. I swear to God. 16 versus seven. This sucks,
but you got to do it. Hey, fuck. What does that make this? That's 17. Oh, thank you. I thought I
won. Shit. I have to leave. I have to play God Hand. You know what I'm doing right now. This
is a perfect scenario. Come on. Versus four. Give me a 10. Oh, that's good. I, I hate this. I hate
this. And I'm never doing this again. Ever. 19. Sand. I have to get to 10,000 or I can't play.
I can't believe this is here. Why is this in here? 14 versus 14. You have, I got to stay. You have
to. There. That's what I'm talking to my mother on the phone. And I'm saying again, mom, I'm fucking
gone. I'm not coming back to the casino. I had to call you and tell you I'm not doing it. He's so
bad. You're not very good at this. True. All right. Fine. I'll double down the next one. No matter
what. Fuck. I can't. That's horrible. How did I fucking lose? No, no, it's no. Okay. I'm done.
I just need to get to that's 20. Cool. Stop. I know I will. I just have to get over 6,900.
Double it. 14. But stop telling me to do that. You're the shitty friend that's sitting behind
me with no chips on the table. I blew all my money two hours ago. Hey, double it. Double it.
Double it. And he's like spilling his drink a little bit on your back. And it's like fucking
get. Come on, dude. Go back. Go back to the room. It's the worst thing ever. You can't win.
All right. $4,000 is where I'm pulling up no matter what. Give me a 10. Fuck yeah. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Either 7,500 or 4,000. No, because I'll be here all day. That's like.
No, you can't double this down. Because if it's not a 10, I lose. Fine. I lose. I win. Okay.
I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I win. I'm out. That's it. I'm out. What did I say? 75?
Oh, 74. 7,400. Come on. We can't. 74. Thank you. There we go. That looks better. Free us.
Okay. Now what's this thing? What's this thing? I'm not. I'm trying to just open the case. How
do I do that? Is this like a see what ball is in what cup thing? Oh, no. Wait, where's the slot
machine? Where are the slots? Are they? Are they not turned on? Do slots. Do slots, dude. I don't
think I can. They're upstairs. Are they? Oh, they are. Where? No, no, no. Please, please, please,
please. What? Guys, there's not even slots up here. It's a lie. It's not even. There's no slots up
here. It was a lie. It was a lie. Video poker of the slots. Oh, did they have regular slots?
That's the high rollers room. Those with less than 100,000 gold bankroll need not apply.
Go back to Blackjack. I'm not going to go back to Blackjack right now. I already won. What the
hell? Oh, wait. This is a huge. Okay. Hold on. Blackjack. All right. I'm going to leave.
You missed it. Second floor. I just was on the second floor. You mean like through here? Second
floor. I mean, I was just on the second floor. Door. No. Right. Keep going. Keep going.
I am. This is like the third floor. No. Blind. Where is it? Second floor. No. Yes. Go down.
Look, if your casino is hard to find the slot machines. Whoa. You got a problem.
Where are they? I don't know that through the Castlevania door. How am I supposed to know that?
Oh, look at me. How much is it? How much is it? How do I do it? Okay. That's it.
This is bad content. This sucks. Like this is not fun to watch. This is bad. This is not fun to
watch. I'm just going to place. No, but there's roulette over here. I just know I can't play
roulette. There's only one big one. Oh, this fucking steak. I'm saying, which is stinks. I
have to get rid of it in a minute. I ate like half of it and it was cold and I took too long to get
her. I never puke from smelly things, but like this is like getting to the point where like it
might be a puke scenario. All right. I got to get out of here. And it's 110 degrees in Vegas right
now. And even with the AC going, it's like hot in this room. This is just a hot like sandwich.
There's a hot steak sandwich over here. It's like an 111 degrees. Double tap forward to run. Holy
shit. That person deserves and just give up to everybody. All right. So I beat level one. Cool.
So what's in the shop? Okay. Purchase new techniques and long straight pay up top elbow spin
sold out. How can a move be sold out? Can't you just tell the person to come over behind the
counter and like show them how to do it? I can't. I can't teach that move. I don't remember what it
is. Once I tell somebody else, it's deleted from my brain. I don't know what I have no idea.
Oh, I already have it. This is charge punch two. Oh, this one's good. And it's exactly $8,000.
Wait, roulette power up. Oh, look at that. Oh, wait. What's it called? Oh, I want to get the
$8,000 power uppercut. Yeah, that's eight attack strength. I'm getting it. You can sell moves too.
Charge punch one. Charge punch two. Let's go. Wait a minute. Can I do?
All right, let's go. Stake them sell out. I feel like that would be a really bad thing. Right. I
think like that was a terrible ad. And if you paid for that ad, you would want your money back. Do
the fighting ring. I'm not ready for that. Do the do racing. Do the racing. I don't have any money.
I have zero dollars. I can't bet with my mind. Let's stay in that hotel. I'll search for their
base from here. Pretty good cat puke if I do say so myself. Much better. Gene, are you listening?
Have fun. Got nothing to do with me. Impossible. That was so bad. It was so late. I've been,
it's been two months. I was quick with it. It would have been, I've been too much. I've got to
give you some slack the first time. I don't know why I thought she's gonna say bed. It's time to
get to bed. What the hell? Huh? Check your back, smart ass. Me. God hand. Son of a bitch.
Damn it, Olivia. Why does it say God hand on it? Is that like official stationary of the game?
Why does it have a brand on it? Why does it have the game on it? Weird. Oh, from when the
bouncer beat the shit out of me. Okay. I don't understand the whole level up thing. Whoa,
that was a cool reversal. Can I eventually get new moves to the ground? Hey, holy shit. I got
this backflip ender. That was cool. Oh yeah. I forgot. Derma plays is there too now, isn't it?
Yeah. Step on his head. That's the best move in the game. You still do it even when they move.
You know what? I just want to, that was kind of a waste, but you know, whatever. Use guard when
they're blocking. Does it knock them around or knock them down? Is it what's case sensitive?
Oh wait, what's going on? All right. I'm going to take, Oh, coin. All right. Let me take the
explosive. Hi. All right. What's this tutorial? Pressing the left analog stick forward twice.
Well, I don't think I can be holding anything. Oh, that's me. Level two. All right. What does
that mean though? What does that mean? Can you fall off? Game is harder when you level up.
You get more money. Nice. What are you doing? Why is he? Okay. That was weird. He just actually
was walking towards that guy, like locked onto him still. Stop doing that. Sure. No, I swear to God.
Look, if I was making a laugh out loud, I fell off the edge joke. Don't you think I would have
walked off the edge? Why stop at the edge there? If you're not going to make the leg. What happened?
Somebody right now is screaming right now that I didn't fucking far break them.
I'm not making very much money to go gamble. Charge that punch for more damage. I'll try.
As the newest member of the four Davos, you had better have a good reason for calling us here.
That is Cosmo from the Fairly Oddparents. Thank you. I'll take a hundred points.
Feel it. Mine is a hundred. It is. Look it up. It is. He is a God hand. God hand is so blase.
Call me the devil hand. I don't care what you call yourself. I don't trust dirty
evil hand. Your kind is so incredibly stubborn. Humans will be nothing but worker bees creating
honey in our paradise. You can think of other things to do with mortal men.
So uses they can be such wonderful toys.
You look old chica. No way. Let me deal with this human cabron.
Stop. You're going to get hurt.
And that hurt your hands. You need to use those.
Find out if this human truly is the God hand. You're the boss.
That was it. Oh, shit. It's not even worth it. Six hundred bucks. Not even worth it.
What am I going to go play one hand of blackjack? No, I want to play at least five hands of blackjack.
This stream cannot be 50% gambling. 50. This thing stinks. I've gone. All right. I'll be right back.
I'll be back. Where's my be right back screen? I don't know. I'll just write it. Hold on.
I have to get this out of this room. All right. We're back. All right. This is actually this is
important. I don't know what came over me, but I was about to take a bite.
And that's not even that big of a deal. This really has been what sitting here, maybe an hour,
two hours. I like was like, oh, yeah, maybe I'll bite that. Maybe I'll do it. And then that's
probably not a no. He went on a second vacation. I didn't go on vacation. Who goes on vacation for
two months? Wow. You got to you got to have a pretty pretty great life. Yeah, I'm going to take
a big just a vacation. Yeah, I'm going to go on vacation for two and a half months. You do.
What's this tweet? Everyone's freaking out about. Look at this. Look at this. Look at this. Look at
this. What is this? Hold on. What the fuck? This is a cameo. I can't wait. Hold on. This is really
important. Who is this? We put this on the screen because this is important to me. Cameo. I don't
know who this is. Wait, do I? Taylor here on behalf of the German, my. OK, this is fucking OK.
It's OK. I'll show. Hold on. I got to put it on. It's been a while. Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. It's a Twitter video. You guys going to be able to see this
at Fenway. You, Jerma, a healthy return to.
What is happening? I hate computers. What the fuck? What's going on?
Picture of Josh Taylor here on behalf of the German mights. We'd like to wish you,
Jerma, a healthy return to streaming. I also saw some of your work in TF2,
and I think you'd be a great addition to the team. On second thought, I don't think you
meet the height requirements. Remember that story in German craft episode one where you
talked about giving the double middle finger to the kid out of the back of the school bus?
Look at him now, man. I don't think you make in the team anytime soon. Welcome back, brother.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Boston Red Sox picture of Josh Taylor here on behalf of
the German mights. We'd like to wish you, Jerma, a healthy return to streaming.
I also saw some of your work in TF2, and I think you'd be a great addition to the team.
That's the best part. On second thought, I don't think you meet the height requirements.
To the Red Sox? Remember that story in German craft episode one where you talked about.
Do you think he's played TF2 before? Or do you think that was him being like,
I don't know what the fuck this is? He has to have, right? Who hasn't played Team Fortress?
Oh, well, that was that was pretty cool. I guess if we tell you the idea that I wanted to do
where I just did cameos for the whole stream, but they didn't cost anything.
I literally just did them for six straight hours. It was like we would put it at, it would just,
well, it would have to cost something. It would have to cost something. It would have to cost
something because otherwise, how the hell would that happen? It would be your bit message comment,
and it would be me doing the cameo for you. Do it with channel points. Maybe. That's so funny,
though. That's, I love it. The gerbamites. Hearing other people say that, it's just,
it's so odd to hear that. The gerbamites. He's going to be a money milker. Let's get back to this.
Unfortunately, you don't meet the height requirements.
Okay, but you don't even know how tall I am. All right, let's go.
This is a little loud for me. I'm going to turn it down.
Maderma, you're so slow. I know, and I'm working on it. Holy shit, he just beat the shit out of me.
Somebody said you can charge it. Wait, I can pick him up off the ground? Oh, that's too bad.
Jesus. What the fuck was that? Give me this. You can charge it. I thought you guys were lying.
There we are. Okay. Beating a dead. Whoa, that was cool. Bot machine. Can I play it?
Oh, he was. Oh, shit. Wait. Oh, shit. I came up at the wrong time. He started stomping. I know
that's his secret move. Holy. Let's go. Nice. Let's end this box. Chop acquired. Yep.
Listen, wait, that's 10? Why the hell would I have to do this? It's three. Okay, we're going
to chop. Chop. Get rid of that jab too. Chop, uppercut, right hook, back fist. That's better.
It's slow. That's all right, though. Dude, what a cool combo. That's a nice combo.
Is that sarcastic or you actually mean that? Let's try it. What's that? I can't fucking believe
there are like still 14,000 people here. Hi. Welcome back, everybody. That's crazy.
I still, I can't believe there are this many people still. Do it. I just did it.
That move is pretty good. I'm telling you, that move is really good. It's been so long.
Entertain us with a tuber voice. I don't know. It's too early for that. Wait. Watch this. Watch
this. Holy shit. Watch this. Shit. Fucking hit him. Break. Do the guard break. Dude, I just
forget how to fucking play video games. I could have done a suplex. Holy shit. I can't even like
do anything to this guy. All right. Will you get up and throw me an orange? Give me an orange.
Why can't you just give me a Gatorade? I'm like in a marathon running by you. Please.
Okay. Hi. I saved you. Now give me one tiny like Nyquil cup size of Gatorade.
What the hell does that do, by the way? Nothing. Oh, what's the strawberry worth?
That's full health. Of course, the strawberry Gatorade is the best flavor.
Why did I take that? That was a mistake. That was a huge mistake. I was one paying attention.
Purple Powerade and strawberry Gatorade. Holy shit. Wait, is that actually the Gatorade?
Is that purple Powerade? Oh shit. I'm not done.
I was just opening the door and you see that. That's the strongest guy. Check. What do you mean
check? You can juggle them. Okay. Is he all right? Check. The poison is killing him. The blood serum
is the only antidote. I gotta get it. I don't even think about it. Yep. No. Well, that guy's dead.
I was trying to pick up the gold. Too greedy. No, I was trying to pick the gold up.
Show Otto to prove you didn't make him into the Steakums sandwich.
All right. So wait, where's the... Did I unlock something? No, he's down. He's in the house.
All right. We just have to get to... No. Okay. Just a little bit.
Damn it. It's because I didn't save the guy. 14. What a shitty hand. My God. All right. I was
going to say no way. He's in your house as a sandwich. That was such a bad idea.
Okay. I can't even max Ben anymore. Oh, what am I doing back in here? Why am I in here?
I had like 1500. Shit. Give me a 10. No. He's going to flip over my ace. Watch. Ace.
I love Blackjack. I love gambling. I don't actually. 16 versus a 2. Fuck. Yeah. He loves it.
All right. 1600. We're back up to exactly where I want it. Here we go. And that's how you do it
right there. You just stay on 17 and you just put both hands really hard down. So all the chips and
all the cards all go up a quarter of an inch off the table at the same time. No. Oh my goodness.
How many threes and fives have I got on this deck? At least I can take my last hundred dollars.
And come back. It comes to come back. This is the comeback right here. You can't softlock
yourself in this game. You can just go and beat up people for money. Oh, those are eights.
Always stand on eights. You all think I'm going to punch him. I'm not.
You're never going to get to high roller. No, I probably won't. Why? That's okay. I don't want
to be a high roller. Guys, high roller means you do $10,000 per hand Blackjack hands. I don't want
to get there ever. If you can in like 10 minutes, I've paid for college already. No, I don't ever
want to get there. What is this? $10,000? Well, no, you can do like two. You could probably do
like three or four Blackjack hands. And no, you can probably do five, 10 Blackjack hands in 10
minutes. They go quick. That's not a high roller. Hey, sweetie, you're not going anywhere until you
still gambling when I come back. Such a sexy man. Just my time. I'm not that kind of guy.
When's resonable four? Oh, right. That's all right.
Like I give a shit. Unfortunately, time's up, baby. Oh, wait, what? I'm not doing it. I'll do it. I
promise the next time he walks. Told you. What's the plot of this game? Doesn't matter. Guy is angry
and has superpowers. Other guy is angry with superpowers, just like this guy. They may or
may not be related. There you go. That's all you need to know. He almost walked into it for me.
Oh, that was so off. I feel bad. Maybe I should walk into it so he feels better about himself.
I got it. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Come on. Jeremy, do it. That's so good. Why the hell would
I? Am I not doing that? What is that? Oh, my God. Holy shit. I'm into both at the same time.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, that was insane. All right. I need, I need, I need to heal, heal, heal.
Is that Homer Simpson? That was Homer. That was Homer Simpson. No, I tried to pick up the
fruit, not the crate. All right. I got this. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got
it. I got it. I got it. Is it the sand? Hey, get that shit out. Stop doing that. It's not even fair.
Go back to what you're good at. That's stepping on people. What the fuck was that?
Okay. Here we go. I just picked up two. All right. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead.
Where is it? Where's the other guy? I did it. What's this? That was awesome. Okay. Here we go.
I'm going to immediately, I'm going to do the, here we go. Ready? And I'm both together.
Come on. And God, stop. And then regular stuff. That takes so much help. Watch it. Watch it. Watch
it. Watch it. Wait, they've started to do a move. Oh, I got it. Come on. Stop. Come on. I need healing
right now. Did I make, did I dodge? What the fuck is happening? I'm going to save the God mode
until a little bit later. Just one default that'd be really good. Get the fuck out of here.
Nobody asked if this was a rerun. No, it's not. I'm here. Not you. Oh, I like streams when Jeremy
makes noises that consist of, oh, whoa. Oh Jesus. Right behind you. This guy was flying down.
Oh no. How do I stop it? Can I say no? I didn't want to do that. Okay. Let's go. All right.
And let's go. Oh yeah. Damn it. Stop him. Oh, come on. What the hell was that?
I need to, no, that's not food. Oh no. What's that? They're going to, I've never seen him do it
because I always stop it with a thing. He's never getting up. Oh my goodness. Oh my God. What's his move
doing? I don't know what they're doing. Oh, you what do you know? Lost now. Doesn't look like he's
packing. He's lost his balls. What? Why do you buy costumes like this? Now I've got 5,400 bucks.
I'm good. IGN couldn't beat this part. Is that real? I'm not like making a, oh, like the game
journalists can't jump over Cuphead's first wall. No, I'm saying like in the IGN review of this
game that they say I couldn't beat the first boss. Yes. What the fuck? There's somebody in here.
Get out of here. Wait, can I? Great. I just wanted full health. Wait, if they're inside, does that
mean, okay, if he's in here, can I just throw him around? Oh, okay. Good. IGN gave it a three out of
10. Grandma, I'm feeling sleepy. Can you tuck me in? Yeah, sure. No, we're not doing this. No,
no, no, no. We're not doing that. I was about to just like, that would have gotten weird.
Fuck him in now. All right. No, how do you talk? No, no, no, no, no, no. Okay, fine. Here's some,
some water. Here you go. And here's some, here's this little snack too. Don't get too many crumbs
in the bed. No. All right. Goodbye. We're done. I'm not doing this anymore. I'm done.
You got like five seconds. That's all you're getting.
Our slot prices are fit for a king. Right now hitting the jackpot will earn you a new technique.
You're a bad father. I'm not your father. Don't you think that I, I'm not your dad. I'm not your
guardian. Don't you think that's a little strange? Sad, sad, sad. Like I, I'm not your guardian.
Right. I'm not your, you know, fatherly figure in your life or mother. It doesn't matter. The
motherly fatherly. I'm a guy. Would you want just a guy to come in and tuck you in?
Double that down, please. Yes, to be honest. Do it again. Perfect. Yeah. That's how you do it.
That's how you do, do two double downs in a row. We go for one more. What do you think? That was
such a bad time to do that too. It is blackjack. Turn it over. Oh, that's fine. This is some pretty
sick, like Ghostbusters for the regular Nintendo music. Love it. Getting close to 10 K. We're
almost there. I'm going to go buy some moves. Five, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, five.
You have to stand here. You have to stand. You can't, I don't, you don't win that no matter what.
You don't hit that. You don't hit that. You don't hit that. Guys, guys, I have won
$75,000 playing blackjack. I've also lost about $88,000 playing blackjack. I think I know
playing blackjack. Here's your 10 K. 10,600. That means we got a clean, we got a clean hand here.
Okay. I don't, I don't know. I don't know what this is. That's like five or 15. But then when
another ace comes up, I don't know what that does. I don't know what this is. I have no idea.
I don't, I don't know what that is. What is this? This is now 16.
Five. I just got $3,000 to have five cards. Holy shit. No blackjack.
You just leave. Well, when I get to 15, now I can leave. Every hand is the last hand unless I win.
Don't you know? That's how it works when you go to the casino.
Please stop gambling. I got 13 grand. These, these, I don't like the low maximums. Where's
like the $5,000 maximum? Stop wasting our money. Do the slots for good moves. Let me,
let me go see what's available at the shop before I do that. What's this? I've seen people say this.
Warm up room, stream fighting ring. Take the techniques on sale in the shop for a test spin.
You can set up your techniques as normally is in the menu. Just like a training dummy.
I didn't even hit this thing. All right. I did it. That was fun. Oh, so this got to be allowed out
here. All right. So let's, uh, let's do it. Let's go into the extreme fighting ring. Sub subs. Yeah,
there's been so many. This poor Gore gave 50 community subs. Arub just gave 10. There's been
hundreds and hundreds of fucking subs today. It's just, it's, it's overwhelming how much money
you guys are giving me today. Thank you. I do want to make sure I make this clear again,
because it's been obviously a couple of hours since the beginning of the stream.
I'm making some changes to the stream. I'll go over it very quickly just to make sure I can
keep people aware. I'm going back to the pre Vegas schedule where I'm only going to stream about three
days a week. And after that, I'm also getting, it's hard for me to even say it because I feel
bad and I liked it and it's just, it just has to go away though. The end of the stream bit reading
is going away. I know a lot of people probably maybe don't know that as of today. It's, I'm only
going to stream and then we're going to do a little like maybe 10 minute wind down every stream.
The reasons for this are because I still haven't figured out all the medical stuff. I'm still doing
it. It's still ongoing. I didn't want to just not stream for like six months. I just didn't want to.
I wanted to be here. I want to stream. I like doing this. It's fun. I enjoy it. 10 minute in quotes.
Right. And it allows me to stream. Like let's say the streams are going to be four to six hours
because they will be just because of trying to keep myself comfortable. Those streams won't
actually be like three to five hours and then like an hour of bits. They'll be four to six hours.
How do I go in here? Four to six. Is it am I doing something wrong? Welcome to extreme fighting.
You may enter the ring after you have completed stage one. Oh wait I haven't beaten the first
stage of the game. That seems impossible. Somebody asked is it temporary? I don't think so because
I'm going to be very honest with you. If this turns out to be a long-term management scenario
because I'll it's very clear that this is not just something just oh yeah I have X and I'm
going to take a medicine for a week and it's going to go away. I don't know what that scenario is.
This could end up being a more longer term management thing.
So if that's the case then you know obviously that's I think it's probably going to be permanent.
Stages are like world so okay. I want some I want a new move. Why can't I get new moves? Oh wait
smoothie. Wait this increases your HP and that's not just like a thing that you store that you can
drink for 20 health that means you go up permanently by 20. Oh shit okay I get I see what this does now.
Increase number of attacks by one. Increase TP by 30. What's TP? TP? Yeah okay my TP went up by 30.
I hope that's a good thing. Oh long straight. All right let me try these. Let's sell. Let me see.
So what can I find rare techniques and sell them? Yes that's actually really cool. Now it's 10.
Six. Changing that one to long straight. Oh but is right hook five? No no.
But I can put these just on the regular move. I'll keep the right hook it's fine.
See what it looks like. Also you have a lot of community content to catch up. Yes I do.
That's going to be that is going to be very very difficult. That's what we're talking now like hold
on sorry. Hold on. Wait a minute. Okay well I can't even mute my microphone from my stream deck
anymore. What happened in the last two months? Hold on. Morty. Anyways I have no idea what I was
just saying. I forgot everything. Right community content night. Uh there's like four months of
backlog. There's a four month backlog. This guy I don't even know what the hell is gonna happen.
I'm gonna have to figure that out. And the DLC movie night also has like three months of content
now. We're gonna be we're gonna be busy on some of those days.
Watch out. Oh what the hell. Counter. Do R2. No I don't want to waste it. I can't beat this guy on
my own and I can't what yeah I can't just always rely on my god hand. This person's just been
sitting here watching. Yes you can. That's what it's there for. Uh huh. I know I know. No. Give me
that. All right two cherries. No don't look at that yet. He didn't even stand a chance.
That's what happens when you actually focus and turn it on. All right let's go. Did I actually get hit
by that? That angers me. He's got his gamer mode engaged. It's been a long time since I've engaged
the gamer mode. It's been a while. You are right. It's been a while. This is a perfect opportunity
for the god hand. I don't even need to pummel him. Just kill him. Oh what did I just get? Okay
I'm like burning right now. I'm on fire. Shit. One of these guys. No pummel him. Pummel him. Pummel
him. Pummel him. I gotta get off these stairs. Imagine not screaming for two months and you come
back with this trash game. I'm sorry that you feel that way. I'm sorry that you're not happy about it.
I'm gonna lose. Shit. Oh these guys suck.
All right what's the technique here? I shouldn't. Why did I even. I told you I shouldn't have used
it. That was my mistake. I won't make it again. Wait I can break this. Yeah. Oh shit he's mad.
Three out of ten IG. At least I got further than that. Where's the guy? Stop. Stop him.
Okay didn't even need to use. This is a lot. Are you fucking kidding me?
It's like UIRL. You look at porn books all the time.
Porn books. All right give me. Let me see it. I want to see it. A book of porn. A thousand bucks.
Okay now I need to use the god hand when this guy comes up.
I don't want to use it until the guy comes out of the ground. Is the guy even fit at health?
Are you ready to see that? What the hell was that? Do you stick up to dodge?
Oh this is bad. I'm gonna die.
Why are you still alive? He stomped that guy's head into the ground a thousand times in the
stairs and it gave him extra health. That wasn't fair. Press R2. No I can't.
Hi. There we go. Yes. Okay here we go. I'm ready. Stinger. Did he learn to. Oh wait. I don't have
time to think about that for it but I'll ask you a question. Okay so you're talking about this.
This dodges every move. Can I actually dodge with this? This dodges every move.
So it's not. I don't. Stop playing bloodborne and play god hand is what you're saying.
Most moves. Okay. Okay I see. How come there's a guy didn't pop out? Okay well I'll take it.
What's going on?
Shit. Guard broke me. Double stomp. Shit.
Sorry. Shit I missed. Who's to help you?
Oh my god. There's a guy in there. Come on do it. Thank god.
Oh what? Holy shit. That was terrifying. Why was he alive? Was somebody in to help?
I don't have any help. Just throw all the boxes at him. I can't pick up the table.
No. What's this? How do I leave? I'm just gonna leave the area. I'm just leaving. I'm gonna leave.
I can't even fucking believe it. Just kill me. Kill me. Just kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me.
Do it. Hit me. Do it. Please. You can't vertical attack though. It's not worth it.
Just. Ow. I said just run to the end. Yeah just run to the end. I'm not fucking it up.
No more laughing. No more funny jokes. Not me. You. You're telling funny jokes. Not me.
Apparently this guy didn't really deserve that and of course.
Oh these guys. I hate these guys. Oh fuck you guys. I'm so mad. What's wrong with me?
No I didn't want to turn it on. All right I'm running to the end. What about the book?
So what's the thing at the bottom right? What's that do? Well you are now. Okay. I'm ready for
what? I'm not gonna go in that room. I want to get them all for god's sake.
I want to get some new kicks man. I got the two. I need some new kicks. Don't we all? I can actually
use some new shoes. Full health. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. You wasted it.
Wasted. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. Germa. What? What? What? What? What?
What's the matter? What's everyone freaking out? What's what? What happened?
Wish me a happy birthday. Happy birthday. Hey Kiki. I think that was your.
La Bamba. I'm not very good. I'm not very good. It's okay. I think I can still manage.
What? Okay. Is there? Is this something that makes them angry? Am I doing too many moves of the same
type in a row or something? Is that? I don't want to fight in here. Shit. All right. Let's go. I
can't go. I have to kill this guy. Are you recording? Of course it is. Of course it is.
I'm not even here. What was that tweet? That fake tweet one? Whatever. I'm like somewhere. I'm in a
different country. R2. Not yet. Not until it comes out. It's coming up. Now we do it. Yep. All right.
I feel safe now. I feel good. I did it. Yeah. The Rosary is reacting. I need another one. Don't I?
I need three. Where's the third one? We get a raid? Oh, we got a raid. What's up R2? Thanks for the
raid. Welcome everybody. R2 game crowd. Welcome. My first stream back. Oh banana. Great. Double
banana. Cool. All right. I do. How do I get ready? Yeah. Thanks R2. Hope you're doing well.
Thank you so much for the raid again and like hit me up. We haven't talked in a while. Hit
me up. I haven't like talked to anybody in like four months or like three months. I just disappeared
from the internet for like at least two or three straight months. All right. What now? Where do I
go? Oh, there's money. You guys have money. Oh, okay. Psycho. He hates talking to people. No.
Did I not kill somebody back here? Help me out here guys. Wait. Oh, next area prompt.
That's kind of like the door that's going backwards. Where are they? We'll get knocked
the fuck up. Can I pick those up? I really do want to find a new low kick, high kick. Oh shit.
That's actually worth money. Can I take all of them? All right. Do you think I'm ever going to
get to level three? Will I get to level three? Do you think? No. No. Not at all. At all. Oh,
feels good. Can I pick up all the jewelry? Wait. I'm confused. Bombs everywhere.
Should I just run around? One left. Okay. What's next? Stop picking up the fruit when you don't
need it. You're pissing me off. Shit. I tried to do the swing through his hands. He's angry with
me. Yes. This is the game music. Yes. It's the game music. Turn the music off. The loop is driving
me nuts. Did I really just level down? I'm sick of you. How do I rewind? Where's my safe state?
That was horrible. This is really good YouTube copyright replacement music. Yeah, it is. It is.
You're fucking me up now. I can't focus. All right. Look, why? Why does all copyright free
replacement music like that have to be so shitty? You want to make a hundred million dollars?
Make like really good royalty free music that you can just license out to people. Wait. No, that
means that doesn't make any sense. You don't license it, right? It's royalty free. So that
means you don't have to pay for it. Just make music and sell it. Yeah. Right. Okay. Nice 76
performance IQ frame. All right. Can I do anything else fun in here? How do you remember that?
I barely remember. I don't even remember that. Okay. I got 16, 17 grand. What's the max bet on
this? A hundred. I'm worth it. I'm worth my time. 500 to a thousand. Max of a bust. Dog, dog, dog,
dog. Is it ready? I'm not a high roller. Is there something I can do? It's easy money. It's outside.
Fighting ring. General store. Beer. Exit. It's in store. Legend. Okay. Am I really just getting
baited here? I don't know why. It's after this level. Okay. It's 10. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want this. And I'm going to get this too. That's worth it. Increase the number of attacks.
Let me see here. So wait, I can. Oh, really cool. All right. Wait, didn't I get in on that? Wait.
Oh, low kick. Finally. Nice. We end it with the yeah. All right. Let's go.
I want to find some new moves. Not the standard ones. The power ones. Nice. All right. Let's go.
And I have more house. Hyper dimension. Neptunia sucks though. No, I'm not playing that again.
You can promise not kept. No, I don't want to play that. I have absolutely no. I have absolutely no
interest in playing that game. I looked it up on steam and I'm just like, I don't, I don't want to
play this. I don't. I just don't. I don't want to play that. I just, I'm just like, I don't want to.
I'm not going to play this. That's it. I just, that's it. I just don't want to. He's a liar.
Remember you're too young for that series. 35 this year. What are you talking about?
How old do I have to be? Finally a boss fight.
This little wave on is the God hand. Oh, that's rich.
That's a nice carpet. What's the matter? You want a tight budget, big guy? You know what? I'm
getting a bit hungry and a little wave on sounds like it would hit the spot. You need to feed your
brain, not your ass. At least the, I hope you fight. Wait, was that just telling me how to press
R2? I don't think you realize what you're getting yourself into.
Newsflash, big guy. You can wax on wax off all you like. I'm still kicking your ass.
Oh, no, I can't dodge that one. Oh my goodness. He's driving me. I keep fucking up the dates.
Just, I get, or who else plays games like this? The way that I do where I know that it's square,
square, square, square, right? It's four times, but instead of four times, I hit it 200 times.
I can't, I just, and then when it's time for me to do the guard break, I just don't do it.
Because I'm too busy smashing square to make sure I have the combo going a row.
Oh, this is going to take me a minute. This is going to take me a minute.
Maybe not. This health over here, I can do it. Get in there. Oh, greedy. There's a golden chest
over there. What's in the super chest? Is it Guest Man Kablam acquired? Shit, shit. Relax,
dude. What am I? I'm freaking out tonight. Do it, dude. Where the hell does that mean?
Where is he? Finish him with a fucking stomping head and shit. What's with this camera? Yes.
I'll help you out. All right.
Wait, why did he turn to stone? He's alive? Why is that so normal for him? It's just,
yeah, that happened. That's what happens to me when I die. Fat boy. This dude wrote all these
over in the car over here. They're terrible. I just lost 3000 fucking dollars. Slain Villagers
1 minus 3000 gold. That's a huge penalty. Ben Elnor gave a hundred fucking dollars. Thank you,
Ben. I'm missing huge money too. Let's go gamble it. Yeah.
Is that the equivalent to some of those old lady, old person chairs that go up the
side of the staircase?
Elvis, I'd love for you to take one puff of your cigar.
It's been four years.
This guy sounds like
you can go. Oh, but don't you kill him. I want to have some fun with first
mast. Our time has come. We shall dispose of this so-called savior and rain despair upon humankind.
All right.
Hmm. So do I get the new thing now? That's stage one. Yeah, I can buy more health now.
That's important. All right. So where did you just, you said it was outside.
This is just a complete lie. This game is going to get very hard. Yeah, I'll probably give up by then.
Maybe I won't. Entry into the ring is free. All right. Fighting ring. Number one, level two,
three, 50. All right. Let's just do level one. Oh, is there a timeline? This is not hard.
This is not even hard. This is not even hard. This is literally level one. Yeah, I know, but still
level one, a level two. All right. If I just do level six, can I get all the prizes from two through
five? That makes sense, right? Oh, shit. Hey. Hey. Oh, so I'm level three. Oh, this is just hard.
Let me find where some of you that play this game and do that and beat this level because
you're having fun playing level three. That'd be fun when you do it. If you like it.
I didn't. Running.
The only thing I know how to do. They figured me out. I don't want to do that. Here's a tip.
Can we all make them see this? Jeremy, it might help you if you incorporate a guard
breaker into your square combo. Bad idea. Wait. Oh, that's cool. I think I want to change this.
That's quicker. It sucks. Oh, this sucks. But I'm going to use it for a little bit.
All right. Now I'm going to just quickly, very quickly save the game, go to the shop.
OK, tropical smoothie, HP by 40, first roulette wheel orbs by one. That's pretty big.
Oh, for a number of attacks over the health, right? It's always health. I'll get health
straight to a chin music. Oh, this is too. I like that big high kick.
Drunken fist. That's awesome. Oh, I'm going to. Yeah, let's go to music,
get music and report anything else. Not really. Let's put that in. I think chops got to go.
Let's start with chin music into a chin music. Apparently what? Start with chin music
into a roundhouse kick into. No, that's too slow into a pimp hand into a pop.
Probably this. All right. How's it look? I want to change this to spin long. That's not what I want.
OK, maybe I sidekick. Yeah, let's go.
Our break. I'll do it. I will do it. Use guard breaker. You have you need a guard breaker.
Hey, Olivia, it's not on there. Yeah. Oh, jean. You're the music off. Don't you're back.
Me. I just about died because of you. But the God saved you, didn't it? It's strong, but it's a
pain in the ass. You should try it for a while. Let's accent. Nice one. You want to keep it,
huh? Worst character. The main character. That's a problem when you say that you want me to check
it out. That would hurt. Well, then time to get going, champ. Why are all the cutscenes in this
game in the same room? I feel like we've been in that bedroom every cutscene. Can we be anywhere
else? Can we go somewhere else? That's right. Cool. Yep. You're right. It's got to be on there.
Can you stop from that part? I just did it. Oh, Keith. I think I can still try that. Yep.
That is what I'm going to be doing. Boys and girls. Can I do like a was giving me a prompt
when he was going down there? This is not an old screen. This is a new one. Sure. Sure it is.
Elbow spin one. When am I going to get elbow spin two or anything too? I can only have two moves
that are two. He's going to shoot me in the face, right? I know what to do. I thought you throw it
at the grabby shave. That was wrong. Dead. Show us today's newspaper to prove this is a stream
today. Because I haven't picked up a newspaper with my hands since I was probably 11 and I
hate touching them. That weird sandpapery, inky, horrible feeling when you touch a newspaper. I
hate it. If I touch them, it makes me just revile. He's right. Yeah, I know. There we go.
Give us the news. Guys, I don't know the news. Thank God it didn't hurt me.
I love when that happens. I love when that happens.
Jeremy, do you not go into public? Not really right now. I didn't say that. What? You didn't?
All right. Hold on. I'm getting my ass kicked right now. I'm getting my ass kicked.
Hold that thought. I'm going to lose again. I don't like these guys. They're the worst.
Those guys are the worst guys to fight anyway. You sound tired, Jeremy. I probably am. I am on
painkillers. Maybe that makes me a little tired. I don't know. He's on coke. How would coke make me
tired? I'm really thinking about just relaxing and getting some tea, getting into bed,
and doing a line of coke off my bed stand. Just to really unwind and go to bed.
So I just lie there in my bed, facing up to the ceiling, just scream. I haven't gone up here.
What's up here? That move never gets old for me. It really doesn't. I love it. It never gets old.
He didn't deny it. Guys, yes, I am on drugs right now. I'm on drugs right now. I had two shots
into my ass, and I'm on drugs right now. Described by a doctor that are non-narcotics.
Oh, come on. Give me a break. Shockwave. One on each cheek. Yes, that is it. What happened?
Is that guy using the power of his mohawk to do that? That's really... I love it.
Okay, let's just do it. I'm not messing around anymore here. This is something. I'm going to
do the suplex. Oh, ass implants. Guys, my ass is huge. I don't want those. Trust me.
I have a huge ass. It's fucking gigantic, and I've come to terms with it. I have to come to terms
with it at some point in my life. I mean, he jumped over it. Wow. Why would you say that?
I don't know. Why? That's a good question. Because I just did, all right? It's canon now.
It always was canon. Please come in. I need help from you. Are you going to give me help?
Oh, I also have to talk about this because I didn't really mention this at all.
This is really, really sad, actually. Those of you that during the course of the last two months
that have been popping into the Discord and the chat sometimes, I've been talking about a stream
that was going to happen where it was going to be a baseball stream. It was going to be two full
teams. It was going to be a full baseball game with a bunch of crazy shit. It was going to be
as big as the carnival. The deposits were already paid. I lost a deposit on this. It was ready to
happen at the end of August. But it's been postponed indefinitely because of the coronavirus.
So I did want to talk about that, too, because that sucked. We thought that maybe we could have
had it happen if we had everybody tested. Logistically, it just wasn't going to happen.
This guy is smashing me in the head over and over again with a club. And now I'm going to just
stomach. Into the fire. Well, at least he died. He did get the last laugh, but it doesn't matter
at that point, right? But it sucks because that was going to be so much fun to give you a little
gist. By the way, it's still going to happen. Everything is done. Tons of stuff has already
been paid for. Everything is ready to go. It just can't happen until it's safe to have 30 or 40
people in the same spot, reliably, because I really didn't want to have it be the case where
I was putting people in danger or we were doing something that we really shouldn't be fucking
doing. The idea was that two or three months ago was like, OK, well, hold on a minute. Let me see
if this is over the next few months. Do we get like a treatment? Does something happen? Or
is it the case to start going down? And we had that big spike in a couple of the states
a few weeks ago. It was just really clear. It was like, no, we can't fuck around here. We just can't
do it. But it will happen. It's going to happen eventually. And I cannot wait for that. I can't.
It's going to be my favorite stream ever. Probably I go, why? It just you'll see. I can't wait. It's
going to be the best stream I've ever done. Will it be better than the carnival? That's tough,
because it's two completely different genres. It's going to be a ton of fun. All right, fine.
I didn't even lose any health. I didn't get hit once. What you're saying is I should just skip
all the screams until that one. If you only want to see stuff like that, then sure. It's up to you.
You're going to be waiting a long time, though. That's not going to happen for at least the next
four or five months. At least. OK, bye. No, don't. Yeah, you don't have to.
Where am I going? Is this all that was up here? Just a cool weapon?
Damn, all right. It was just for the weapon. More promises. What about the other promises?
Oh, yeah. Resident Evil 4. I already ate the steak of the sandwich. Oh, FTK. I know Jokey.
Jokey FTK, which is a new creature. Oh, yeah. July 30th. FTK is done. It's ready.
That will also be soon. That will probably just replace where the baseball stream is going to be.
It's been 100 percent redesigned. It's not even close to the same thing that you saw before.
It's actually like a full on experience. It's not just dump 300 people in a Minecraft server
and break the server, have everybody lag and then have me die four times while a thousand people
run in a circle. That was it has been it's been being worked on since that stream happened.
It kind of just haven't stopped. I didn't kill anybody. I just I just accidentally
punched. Had a relief. What does FTK stand for? It stands for fuck the king. Oh, I told you shit
was just going to start coming to be all stream. I have 15 webcams. The webcam stream is going to
happen probably within the next couple of weeks. I forgot about that. I have like 16 webcams.
I don't know how you forget that, but I did. Yeah, I have them. I'm ready. Not the top rope.
That's going to be such a hard. I'm going to need some time to really set that up.
You know how hard that's going to be to do if I delay 15 different webcams to be happening
at different times. I will lose total control. That stream is going to be terrible. I'm going
to lose total fucking control and I won't even be able to know which webcam is which.
It's going to be a mess. It's going to be the worst stream. Well, we'll see if it gets nominated.
Wait, it could be best stream though, right? It's possible. One of the things I want to do.
I'm going to look. It's not just going to be a mess. I'm going to have various activities.
I told you one of the things I want to do is I want to take a piece of my body or my face
and have it be 15 different pieces that I have to put together.
You know how hard that's going to be to not move and do that.
You did that already. I did it already with like two or three webcams copied a few times. I never
did that with 15 webcams copied like 20 times. I'm probably going to break my USB bus driver or
something. My bus driver is just going to absolutely just it's going to shit the bed.
Does what I say make any sense to anybody at all? I feel like I just kind of made that up,
hoping people wouldn't think that I like I was like pretending to know what that was.
Weirdly enough, that was weird, right? Oh, like my USB bus driver, right? Like maybe like a
hundred of you were like, oh, he knows what that is. Does that mean anything that I fool a hundred
of you? Is this such thing as a USB bus driver? No, yes, it's redundant. How is it redundant? What
does it mean? Universal, universal serial bus driver. Why do I think this is so funny? It's
not even that funny. Serial bus driver. Okay. Do you get, do you know what I'm trying to say though?
Can I actually even plug in 15 webcams into my computer or am I going to overload the system
and it's not even going to work because wouldn't it need to take up a certain amount of slots like
not like actual physical slots, but the USB bus driver can only handle like eight or something,
right? Will it work? It depends. You have a splitter, it will work. There's like 24 seats on the bus.
Okay. So that means I can have like, I can technically have 24 things plugged into a
USB in quotes, even if it's an adapter or an extender. Does it matter? Does it matter like
what operating system you might need a USB PCIe card. That's the person answering the real
questions that I'm asking. Why are you asking, why are you asking this after buying 16 webcams?
I didn't even, not even one single Google search about this. Are they all 1080p?
I don't even know. I don't guys. Okay. So you know how there's those companies like Logitech,
the Logitech C920, right? The C250. These are not Logitech's. These are the ones
that get sponsored on Amazon. Whoa, Amazon's choice. I don't look at that. They could,
I'm not even sure they're HD, which is probably a good thing. What am I doing? I'm going against
my, stop losing. Stop. I'm getting such shitty hands. This is not even fair. Okay. Somebody got
it. Thank you. Thank you. I want this person to be known. Somebody said it. I have to scroll up.
Hold on. Here we go. This is from treefiddy. Thank you. You have a minimum of 16 lanes,
which means 16 devices for the PCI slots. So that guy isn't far off. Thank you. So there you go.
Imagine if I have to buy a PCI USB slot thing. All right. Come on. Give me the five card free
grin. We go. Come on. There was worth a shot. I almost had it, but not quite. Oh, I forgot.
Everybody hates that voice. Right. In a couple of months. I forget. Bad. What is that? What does
that mean? That's two. It's three or 13 plus K is. Okay. Now that's 20. Is this 20?
It is. Yeah. All right. Coming back. Why would I hit that? That's 20. What the heck?
Four, five, six, seven, eight, 18. How many 21s is he going to get? Okay. Finally. 21. Yeah.
Can we get a shuffle, please? Can you shuffle that deck? How many times I've gone to this buffet
here? I think I can request a shuffle. Thank you. How much money did I have when I sat down?
Feeling the street coming with like a sad guy. What is that? A thousand people left. No, no.
I'm doing that a lot today. Oh my fucking God. I'm out. I'm leaving.
That's the funny Reddit guy. You think I'm the funny Reddit guy?
That's me. The funny Reddit guy. I just keep losing. Man. I'm not going to. I can't lose it.
No. Oh my. The number of webcams that can be connected to your computer is limited by the
USB bus and the video resolution. In general, it should be fine to connect three to four webcams.
If you want to connect more, you have to increase the USB bandwidth by adding PCI to USB cards.
Told you. I told you. All right. I'm going to get a. How many PCI slots do I have to take the
video card out? OK, so how many PCI cards do I need? Wait, the easy solution. The problem is
to buy an inexpensive USB hub. USB standard supports up to one hundred and twenty seven devices
and USB hubs are part of the standard. I mean, that's I bought a USB hub.
One hundred and twenty seven. Then you're fine. OK, so that's that's zero dollars.
If you unless you've reduced every webcam FPS output to 15, your PC will be
1680 frames per second, which would melt your computer.
OK, that's all right. You absolutely need either one time 16 card or two times eight. Set up a fan.
Did I just take the side of my computer off and just put one of those little fans just blowing
right on the graphics card? That would be even worse.
That's not how computers work. You have fans in your computer.
This intake exhaust. What if I just made an extra shit? I have to stop these out,
get the right guy for the job, close back out, hot back in.
Just put a bunch of hot air on the computer. Bad hair. Don't do that.
I don't do that. There's a jump over that.
They're screaming. All those cameras in the TV would be kind of hilarious. Oh, my God.
What are the specs of the birdhouse? I need to know so I can recommend a suitable formula
for seasoning your motherboard. Please just stop listening to these people.
You just need a powered USB hub and you'll be fine.
Finally, you need a new house. Liar. No, I really do remember, you know, you know how I know this
because I remember a long time ago I had a ton of things plugged into USB and I couldn't get a
controller to work because I ran out of USB like bus drivers once and I remember it stuck with me
forever. This was like probably 10 to 15 years ago. I remember this happening.
USB hub is not going to give you bandwidth. Yeah, that's what I was concerned about.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. There we are. Give me that melee. Throw it. Throw it. Holy shit,
that does a lot of damage. Give me yours. Let me tell you guys the story about how me and Burger
Boy went to go get iced coffees before and he got two huge iced coffees and he drank them both in
five minutes and he looked at me and he said, I'm done with mine. Give me yours. He wasn't even
kidding. He was like, he actually wanted me to give it to him. That's fucking based.
He went right into the fire. Daisy cutter acquired. What's that? We got more. We got more
computer scientists. The USB 3.0 controller has a theoretical maximum transmission speed of 625
megabytes a second, which is capable of handling 34 cameras. Thank you. Automatically assuming that
I bought the nice one that has USB 3 and not like 10 USB 2.0. So what does USB 2.0 have?
Can somebody do that math for me, please? Don't use USB 2.0 controller has an effective
35 megabytes a second being able to handle two cameras.
I'm going to need a 3.0. All right. But I always thought that you needed a 3.0 USB device to use
a 3.0 capability. I can put a two. Didn't I have this problem like three months ago on the green
screen? Ooh, I want that. What is this thing I got called Daisy cutter? What is it? Wait a minute.
Is it one of these? Oh shit. It is. Okay, cool. I'll try it. 16 camera outputs would cause a
high-end CPU to reach a temperature. I can't even read it. 400 degrees Celsius. That's got to be a
troll, right? That's got to be fucking made up. 400 degrees Celsius is hotter than your engine of
your car. That's not even real. That's like a jet engine. 400 degrees Celsius is like the surface
of Mercury. I don't think that you're accurate. Let's try it. What's it called? Daisy cutter.
Let's go. Ooh, okay. That was awesome. Turn them into fireworks.
It was right about Mercury. Yeah, sorry. Somebody paid attention in fucking geology.
Whatever class taught you. Yeah, study of rocks. Geology. Yeah, you understand that your planet is
just a huge rock. We have gravity that spins it around the sun. They're just huge rocks with
moss and water on them. Atari. A planetologist. Space. What are they called? Seriously, I'm being
stupid right now. What is something that studies space? Astrologist? Is it astrology? It's an
astronaut. No, not astrology. Yeah. Astronomy? What is astrology? It's not astrology?
Astrology is a suede science that claims divine information about human affairs
and terrestrial events by studying the movements and relative possessions of celestial objects.
What's my horoscope? Let's find out. I'll read it for you. Let's see what the horoscope is.
I feel like if I go to one of these astrology websites, like, hey, what's my horoscope today?
Like, I'm literally about to download a bunch of fucking viruses. MSN.com? MSN still exists?
I thought that got liquidated like 20 years ago. MSN? The Microsoft network? Okay. Okay, here we go.
For July 30th. Today. This is today. Everyone knows it. Nothing can stop you when you are
determined to get something done. As long as other people are on your side today, you'll be amazed at
all the things you are able to accomplish. But don't get too excited, because it's also time to
take care of all those thankless tasks that no one seems to want to deal with. You may need other
people's help to get them done. I didn't even... I don't think I'd read anything. I think that was
just a full paragraph run-on sentence that said, do your best today. All right, what about my love
horoscope? You should be feeling good about yourself today, even though your tendency is towards too
much self-criticism. You drive yourself very hard, and your ambitious nature can sometimes make life
too stressful. Try to relax and enjoy the company of loved ones today. You'll be in the mood to see
a movie, get together with friends, or even go out for a long hike today, aka every single fucking
activity that exists lumped into three different statements. Your head should soon clear and your
emotions begin to stabilize. What about your career? You can find that a lot of issues are left up in
the air today. You might finish a meeting with co-workers and think that everything has been
settled, only to find out later that there are still many unanswered questions. Make lists of
important issues that need resolution today, and double check the information that bosses or clients
have conveyed to you. You may find that small errors are easy to overlook today, so pay attention.
I don't have any co-workers. All right, here we go. Finance. This is important.
Today you might experience insights as to how to advance yourself in business.
These could come your way through dreams, sudden revelations, or perhaps even through visions.
Why am I having like finance fever drug dreams? Don't hesitate to put them into action simply
because of the unorthodox way they came to you. Some of the most progressive and successful ideas
have come to us because the inventor had a vivid dream. Write down your insights and go for it.
Time to act on weird fucked up shit that happens in my dream tonight. Okay, hold on. This is for
tomorrow. They already know. They already know tomorrow. This is tomorrow. A group with which
you are affiliated might be all inflamed by supposed events and issues that could prove
well to be nothing more than a rumor or gossip. The discussion about it seems to be turning
into an old-fashioned brouhaha. Don't be afraid to stand up and suggest that someone be assigned
to check the facts. All is done as it seems, and it's useless getting all excited over nothing
that you're affiliated with might be inflamed. Is this because I didn't play the anime game?
Like, I'm not going to play that anime game, and tomorrow someone's going to be really mad about it,
and it's going to be a whole thing, isn't it? Okay. And finally, my well-being. Let's see.
I'm getting a little inflamed. That's a weird way to say that. Inflamed? What is it, like a
paper cut that you didn't put any fucking massive tracing on and it got infected? What are you
talking about? Your well-being. Today you might want to go for a hike or a bike ride. You'll have
a lot of energy, so you probably won't want to stay in the house all day. Try to get outside and
do something athletic. You'll always enjoy being out in nature, so why not visit a park? If you
have children, take them with you. Your mind and your spirit will thank you later. This is wrong.
Being outside for more than 30 seconds at a time just inflames me. Well, there you go. That is my
horoscope. This horoscope wants me dead. Why? Show Otto's horoscope. I don't know what Otto's
birthday is. He was a rescue. I don't know his exact birthday. I'm not sure what his exact birthday
is, but all I know is that he should probably wear a mask. Don't be fucking stupid going outside
without a mask on. Don't be dumb. You guys know who that is? Oh, we got two guys. That wasn't Bernie.
That was Dr. Fauci. Everybody's Bernie. Can I get up there? What does that mean? What does
it want me to do? Oh, how do you like this game? I think it's fun. I think it's a fun game. I wish
this game was like redone and made in the current time and that there was more stuff to do. Oh shit.
That was, you're right. No, that actually was something that was on the list of promises.
Another one. Done. Is it open? Okay. I've done some research. This is all capital.
Hold on. This is busted. I've done research. A YouTube channel did a test with 15 webcams running
on a single computer. One of the CPU cores combusted causing the computer to go up in flames
reaching 368 degrees. If you do this, you'll cause a house fire. That's not even real. Why was that
so specific? 15 webcams? It can't be real. Is it real? Oh, but you guys are getting inflamed.
Whoa. It's a huge giant. Everything. I need help. All right. I'm going to go into Homer Simpson.
Okay. Here we go. In three, two, one. Or should I say Dill? Wait, I haven't even done like one of
these yet. Hey everybody. Morse. All right. I'll do Morse code. You ready? I'm going to turn this
down because it's probably going to piss off a bunch of them. Maybe that was something. Maybe I
said, I don't know. But where is this guy? Do I have to wait for him to put his hands down?
He's being held hostage. What did he just say about my wife? Oh, come on. Come on. 50 USB
webcam. We're still on the webcam. I've just been laughing all through. It's been a long time.
I've been away for so long that I forgot how funny this was. Somebody said, I think you
just activated as a sleeper agent. Kill it. Kick the bomb over there. Oh, this game is a sleeper
agent. All right. Easy. Slow down. Slow it down. I'd like to see that person timed out for five
minutes. That was wicked funny. Really relevant. No one's allowed to be funnier than the screamer.
Otherwise they get the boot. I think it was dead. I wish it was a more efficient thing than the
stomp, but it's just so good. It's so efficient. Can't ban us all. Yes, I can. I can though. I
really can take a long time, but I could. I don't want to do that. And I like you. I'll get these
webcams to work. Don't you worry. Wait, he's so angry. What's going on? I kind of feel bad for
that door. Oh, there. I used to be scared of Baraka when I was younger. By the way, I thought his
name was Butterupka. That's the way the guy said it. Butterupka. No. I thought it was Butterupka.
Butterupka. Butterupka. Butterupka. Butterupka. I can't do it. Nobody can do that guy's voice.
There's only three people in the world that can do it. Him, two others. They all do movie shit.
Why did I slow down? I think I'm building up a little too much lactic acid in my right foot.
Too many reps. I can't do it anymore. What am I talking about? You know what lactic acid is,
right? No, I'm not lactating. Lactic acid. Lactic acid. Where's his door? Where's his door?
Lactic ass eat. Yes. You did a view stat. That took you a little while. You were sitting there
thinking, okay, lactic acid. Okay, galactic, lactic, lactic, ass eat, ass eat, ass eat, ass eat.
Come on. You spent a long time on that one. Over here? Am I nuts? Where's this door?
There's supposed to be a lock on it. Am I nuts? Yes. Where is it? Under the bridge? No, this is
where I came in. This guy's nuts. Check the minimap. There's nothing on the minimap.
What is this shit? Come on. Look, if it's something that I can punch through, I don't think it needs a
key. Just being honest. All right, scene up. Into the casino. I'm back with some more bankroll.
All right. Honestly, I'm not going to fuck around here. Nobody can be this unlucky.
Nobody can be that unlucky. It's not possible. Oh, of course, showing an ace. Get out of here.
All right. I'm going up to the slot machine. Level two makes Blackjack harder. I mean, isn't
Blackjack just chance? There is no difficulty. You don't have to balance a fucking spoon on your
chin. It's just Blackjack. Let's go. Do I get moves from this? Is it possible to get a move?
Present. Aw. Present. Present. Come on. That's it. Present. Fucking goddamn it. I didn't win once.
This is one of the new moves. Give me my money back. Look, if I go sell some moves,
I'll have money for the dog race thing that you're talking about. What even is that?
Load the save? No. I can't come back day one and save scum. Not on day one. I'm sorry.
All right. Into the shop. I don't see a dog thing in here. Use the Konami code in the shop to unlock
every move for free. What? What's the Konami code? Let me see if I can get this right.
Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, left, right, B, A, start. There's no B. It's up,
up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start. There's no B. No, you can't. That's not even
real. By the way, OK, I don't know why I thought this was a Konami game for a minute here. I thought
that was an Easter egg because it's Konami. No, this is like Clover Studio. Capcom. Did Capcom
have a code? Why are people calling you Jarma? I don't know. Jarma, shut up. Wait, is this one
of those things where why people call you Jeremy that's not your real name? Because Frank doesn't
sound as cool as Jeremy. You know, sorry, guys, Frank Ugly doesn't sound as good as Jeremy
Elbertson. What does Grovel do? It makes you go level down. Am I ever going to get to level three
on stream? No, just do it. You know, I'm not going to. I know his name was
Frank Ugly. I just didn't want to tell anybody because it was embarrassing for him.
Let's make this happen for real. No more dicking around. No more damage. Only me dishing damage.
That's it. Jarma, Jarma, Jarma. All right, look, I'll look at that and like,
I'm just running through this really bad trap layout. Where are the other two?
There we are. Give me that thing.
I want that golden bat. Oh, shit. Attack the guy with the red face, the red head, the red fire.
Oh, I'm in trouble. I need a weapon. I need that weapon. Dead.
Oh, see the TF2 cosmetic. Yeah, I liked it. I liked it on Twitter. Check my Twitter likes.
It's pretty cool. Why did I do that? Can I please get through this? Let me at least get past this
part. Foreign links. I do not be on day one. On day one, guys, I do not be in there. I'll be really
upset. I want that. He picked it up. Of course he picked it up. I didn't want to break you.
There's a lock on. Lock on is like not exist in fucking video game world at this point. Oh,
God. I'm doing it this time. Let's go. No more fucking around. Hey, Jarma, nice to see you.
Nice to see you well. Did you enjoy the Fred movie? He was more popular than Justin Bieber.
Come on. Now break it. Are you kidding me? Come on.
You keep getting me with this fucking mallet. Fred was the funniest shit in 2007.
That missed me by a few years. I would never classify for me that Fred was the funniest shit
in 2007. I'm very old, though. Oh, my God. I'm so mad. I'm so mad right now. I can't even play.
I'm fucking furious. Give me the fucking thing. OK, didn't Fred go on to make a bunch of other
stuff when he got older? Didn't the actor that played Fred turn into not like an 11-year-old
and he was like a 25-year-old still like pretending to be like six? He was like six,
too. Didn't they do that? I don't know why I have this memory of that happening.
He was one of the first. Where am I going? He has three movies in a TV show. Well, fucking good for
him. That's fucking awesome. That's awesome. I'm doing YouTube videos like in your house.
All right. I don't want to die. I can't even see where the whip is. Are you jealous of Fred?
No. Why does that make me? It's not OK. It's not like I was also doing like Fred videos.
It was like I was like Timmy or something like Tommy. And I was trying to do the same thing.
And he got famous and I didn't have to look at that says the guy with 10,000 Twitch viewers.
This is out of the ordinary. I'm surprised there's still this many people here.
We usually hover around five, four to six, which is still a shitload of people,
but 10 to 15,000 is not normal for this. You're looking for love. You're looking in the wrong
place. Scram, sweetheart. What do the five fingers say to the face?
You're never going to get new shit if you don't stop spending money. I know. I know you're right.
I know. And I'm done after this. We go. Check it out. OK, that way. Now we're on a roll.
Now we're on a roll. Now we're on a roll. That's it. Give me a 10. I have a Resident Evil 4.
It might be. I mean, I'm only going to play that for like 10 minutes.
That's why I make sure I have the promise there. I win. It's a good game. It's better than this.
Yeah, but this was a long time coming. Look, I'm going to play through
most or all of Resident Evil 4. I'm just going to have like a laugh out loud moment where I played
10 minutes today, only to have the promise be kept. What else is left on the promises?
Can I do them all? Spoiling the joke. I did them all. I win. I ate the steak of the sandwich.
All right, let's load up Resident Evil 4. Resident Evil 4 doesn't have gambling in it.
I can't and it's not integral to the video game money. You didn't even do the dog race.
I feel like that dog race isn't real. I feel like a lot of people are just telling me it's real and
it's not even real. How do I do it? You have to unlock stage two to finish chapter two.
OK, am I at a boss right now? Yes. All right, let's kick this. Let's kick this guy's ass.
Why doesn't he want to beat God Hand, Pepe Hands? Well, it sounds like I don't.
Oh yeah, you guys cut my arm off. Divine Smash.
Oh, OK, here you go. How much health did I have coming in here?
Damn it, I keep missing it. Show it to him. And then, jump. I'm so sorry I just died.
When's the next remap for this one? Tomorrow. I'll be live tomorrow.
And what are we doing tomorrow? Holy shit, I have no idea.
Walk it. You got nothing. Can't even hit me. Again. Oh, get it. Oh yeah. He's pissed.
Wait, what does that move do? You stinger. I don't use Ball Buster. I'll never use it
ever again. I promise. Oh, fuck. Of course. Right when I die, Vinny does that bullshit.
Back every fucking time. More food. More than that. More than that.
Oh, this sucks. I gotta fight all three of these fucking people. Need health.
That's a fucking boomerang. Of course, that's what they do.
This is hard. This is hard. I might rage quit this. Every time. You see how every fucking time
I do that? I'm trying to do the down punch. I gotta change technique. This technique sucks.
It's taking too much time. Easy, easy, easy. Why does it have to be every time I go in like
that? It happens. My fucking god. I'm so done. I'm so done. Oh my god. I'm done. I'm done.
I wish I could not just hit the fucking square thousand times. This game is about just don't hit
square five thousand times in a row. But like, come on. How the hell are you supposed to not do that?
I'm done. I don't fucking know. I'm in so much trouble. He dodged it. You. Come on.
Well, boomerang doesn't go backwards and forwards. It goes back. Get him. Why is he
able to back away from me? Are you kidding me? No, I want to do the cobra twist to him. Stop it.
Stop. Stop it. Okay, I need to heal. I'm dead. No. What the fuck? The dodge. Where is it?
No, no. The guard break. Damn it. I thought it was a pizza. No. I need to see phase three.
Give me phase three. Okay, phase three coming up. Give me the god hand. I almost got it. Let's go.
What? Is there health? Is there cheese in here? Is there cheese in here? Fuck. There's no cheese.
Is there any food? I'll get it this time. Are you kidding me? I'm trying. Do it. Do it.
Do the charge. I tried to do it. I'm so bad. I hate it. He hates the ninth planet. Pluto?
Pluto's not a planet, right? That's the joke. I made a whole episode of TV about that, right? The
funny show. Will. Oh, I could have. I could have tried to do it. I'm a little busy.
Are we going to play Silent Hill 2? Maybe. Give me one day. I just got fucking so much health
taken away for nothing. All right. He's dead. Don't pick that up. I don't know. Oh, you motherfucker.
Okay. Don't get angry. I want to do the Cobra Crystal. Use the hand. No, no. I'm saving the
hand for the girl. No. Fuck it. Let's just do it now. No. All right. I need health.
Okay. Here we go. This is it. This is it. Here we go. Easy.
Easy. Where is she? Oh, what's up? Do I have any moves? Get it. It's in the fucking corner.
Please have fruit in here. Please have fruit in here. Please. Oh, man. God damn it. Why can I?
What is this? Holy shit. All right. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Please. Oh, my God. Don't fuck this
up. Yes. Get out of here. Oh, I'm energetic today. I've been screaming. I'm making noise.
I bet you're not really popular in hell. That's a little odd. That's not it. There's no other
enemy, right? I hope not. Thank God. Gamble all your money. All right. So the dogs here.
Where are the dogs? No, that's not it. Shit. I thought that was going to be the end of the
chapter for sure. Mash up the right stick. You can be invincible. All right. Let me see.
This is something I'm going to be able to do. See if I can beat this guy on the doggy door.
Okay. Punch these. Okay. Hard. This is hard. Well, I can tell you I'm going to have to stop
getting. It's going to be almost that point soon. I can feel it. You'd have so much money
if you just didn't gamble. Well, only like another 20,000, which yeah, that's a lot.
That's a lot. That's a lot of money. That's true. I got to get better at doing that.
It would have been way stronger. I'm playing with a handicapped one because I'm gambling
a lot of money. It's a gamble handy. Game's cool. It is pretty cool.
You're done. Will you keep ignoring our advice? No, I'm seeing it. I'm just not processing it.
This is a little bit different. I see it, but I don't process it.
That is probably what I would be saying.
Wait, did he just say he was Alexander? I'm Alexander. Is this the guy we've been looking
for the whole time? How many people are in this house? We'll find out. Five? Six? That's it.
Wait, was I supposed to jump up the ladder? I don't think I was supposed to wait.
Oh my god. I'm dead. Oh, that's that's it. I'm moving on. Damn. That was fun. I didn't
expect the game to be that hard. I haven't saved if I ever want to go back to it.
Now it's time to play Resident Evil 4. How am I going to do this?
I'm going to do it like this. Soundtrack could use a little work. It's really the only complaint
I have, and I wish there was a walk-in. It was really fun. No More Heroes 2 has been open the
whole time. Yes, it's been open. Let's pause at that screen. All right. Promise. Final promise
of the evening. No, I'm not playing that Neptunia game. You just turn this back. I can't turn off
the PlayStation 4. All right, let's do it. Let's play Resident Evil 4. You're a liar.
That's okay. I can lie about that one. Resident Evil 4. 1990. Everybody's seen this cut scene.
Who cares? I just need to shoot a guy. All right, remember the first one. That's it. I don't even
have to kill the guy. This controls like ass on PC. Why would I use the controller?
I'm just ruining this. All right, that's it. There it is. Thanks everybody for watching.
Appreciate it. There it goes. Okay. I hope you enjoyed yourself. All right, how about three?
I'll do at least three. What does that mean? What is that? Am I saying it right?
What a sterile means outsider. Okay, there you go. This is hard. They're controlled in God hand.
Why is the mouse not turning the character? Anybody remember what to do?
Don't you? I skipped all the cut scenes. Don't you like bar up the walls?
You like board up the windows and shit, right? Okay. We're looking for three. I don't know.
What's the quick turn in this one? This game is so much fun. All right. Where's the dog?
Where's the dog and the dog out here somewhere? Where's the dog?
I'm coming. Okay. You're saved. All right. Cool. Nice. Now, you know,
if those of you that never played this game before that dog, if you save that dog, he comes
and he helps you during a boss battle. This is making me sick. This is actually making me sick.
Shit. There's two. Okay. And there's a guy in here.
That was close. No, that one doesn't count. That one doesn't count. That was not
that was that wasn't the same. I'm going to die anyways. You think I'm going to die
on easy in Resident Evil 4. If I die before the third,
I will, I will give 5,000 subs to the channel. Leon, how you holding up? Bad question.
Somebody say it. Somebody say it. Holy shit. They all said the same line. That's impossible. What?
Why are you doing this? Come on.
Say it. Say it. Yes. Am I triggering right now? Let's see how I'm using the weapon.
All right. If I don't kill this person, if I don't hit this person with a direct headshot
and not kill, if I do not hit this person directly in the head with a shotgun headshot,
I will give 10,000 subs to the channel. So easy, but holy fuck. Oh my God. I fucking
messed it up. Holy shit. This is too hard. This is actually hard to do. Thank God. Holy shit.
Like my credit card can't even charge that much money a day. It would be impossible. Okay. Do
you see right there? If that was still going on, I wouldn't, I wouldn't have to give 10,000 subs.
Do you see how that was kind of in the ear? Holy shit. I got her, I got her right in the nose,
like right in the forehead. Holy shit. That little leg shivvy. Stop gambling. I'm not gambling.
What do I get from that? That's just losing. All right. I'm going to get going. I'll see you
guys tomorrow. I probably am going to play Resident 4 for real. So the end of the
stream is still going to exist, but it's only going to be about five minutes while we just say goodbye.
Are you going to play the Wii version? Isn't the Wii version the best version? Yes, it is. It
definitely is the most fun. The one problem that I think I might have to be careful of with the Wii
version is how you have to hold your arm up. I think I might have to come up with some kind
of solution for that because like holding my hand up and forward and tilting would, I don't know,
that might mess me up. Like my back, like shoulder chest bullshit. We'll see. What? It is good to be
back. Thank you. There was a ton of people here and there was a shit load of fucking money.
A ton of people gave money, a ton of people subbed. It feels good to be back.
I will see you guys tomorrow. It's going to be a mystery stream tomorrow. There's a ton of
games that have come out and there's a ton of things that I still have. Let's say our goodbye.
I'm gonna figure this out too. Why is it doing this? Stop it. Oh, it's a fake windowed mode. I
forgot. Hey, there we are. So we are going to... What is this? Why is this just playing?
This was just... That was a square space add. Okay, let's put the... Where's the...
Where's my... There they are. Okay, make sure they're still here. I'm gonna run the credits.
This could be very, very, very insane. This is gonna be... What the fuck? Okay, so hold on.
This is... There were about 2,600, 2,700 subscriptions today. Yesterday in the last
five hours. This is going to be out of control. Thank you guys for just dumping that much money
here. I really appreciate it. I'm sorry that I was gone for so long and I know that I was doing it
for health reasons and all that shit, but still I really didn't want to be gone for that long.
And it is... I'll be a little bit real with you. It is a little frustrating knowing that the entire
reason why I left was to get this kind of figured out and it's still happening. So just kind of
bear with me while I continue to try to figure out what's going on. I hope we're just gonna keep
doing it. We're just gonna keep trying to figure out. I have doctor's appointments every week.
I just need to... I need to know what's going on and I need to start getting treated for it.
So here we go. Here come the subscriptions today. What? What do you mean?
Right. This is... This is not right. Let me see why this is doing this. I don't know why this is
doing this. This is gonna be eight hours of credits. Okay, let me try this again. Why is this taking
so long? What the hell? Okay, let's... I'm gonna try it again and go. Wait, why are they different?
Why is it Star Wars? Wait, what? That's... That's not the...
There was more people than that. What happened? Okay, well thanks everybody for coming to the
stream. That's sad. Am I gonna get DMCA'd for that? No, I was doing it with my mouth.
Um, can I pull it from this other spot? Let's see. All right, I can pull it from... Yeah, okay,
I can pull it from here. I can pull it. Yeah, I can. Give me one second to go to it. But yeah,
I'll see you guys tomorrow. If you're not sticking around for the credits. It's... There's an insane
amount of people here. I can't imagine this many people would be here every day. But if you stop
by just to say hello, I appreciate it. Thanks for giving me the time of day. Okay, let's get this here.
This'll work. Why can I not capture my Chrome window? Dude. Well, I have to use Chrome because
Firefox is like annoying. Why? This is... I can't just capture my window. Why? Why is my Chrome?
Who was that fucking risen? Okay, finally. That was annoying. All right, here we go. I got it.
Get it out. Did I? Okay, here we go. All right, here it comes. Thank you everybody. Run them. This is
long too. Yeah, be careful. Your computer is gonna hit 400 degrees. But it's alphabetical. I was
gonna say there's a lot of C names. Holy shit. This is unbelievable. This kind of hurts my head to
look at. I think it actually is slowing down my computer. But only in the J's. I cannot believe
that there is an amount of people who scroll this fast that have decided to pay this channel $5 a
month. You know how fucking ridiculous this is to look at? I can't fucking believe this.
It's unbelievable to see this happen. You saw your name. That's pretty good considering it's
all mushed together. Yeah, we'll do something interesting tomorrow. But that is, I'm not sure
yet. But I'll figure it out. You know what I really do? Who's a Z name? Do we have Z? How many? Okay,
how many Z names are there? Holy shit, there's a lot. Easy top crackhead. All right.
I'll see you tomorrow, guys. I want to raid somebody with like a fucking 8,000 people.
It's been a very long time since I've done this to anybody. So what are we doing? Let's see. Who's
streaming right now? Good night, guys. I'll see you tomorrow. You want to join in the raid? Please do
if you feel like it. What do we got? Let me make an executive decision here.
He's playing Diablo 2. He's playing Diablo 2. Is Ludwig streaming? You know, I'll tell you. He
said some incredibly nice fucking things about me. Somebody showed me a clip of him talking.
He put me in like S tier for streamers and it's like, oh, thank you. I can't even believe I'm
that high up. I think I'm a fucking B minus. I was shocked to see that. I was like, holy shit,
because I'm an egomaniac. No, an egomaniac says they're B minus when they think they're an S.
All right, that's how it works. So sure. Yeah, well, you know what? Let's go say hi to Ludwig.
I think I've raided him once before. What's he doing? What is he up to now? Let's go check it out.
Seriously. Why is my twitch stuck? He's doing the god gamer gauntlet. All donations go to
Make-A-Wish. Well, that's fucking awesome. Yeah, absolutely. Let's go. Go say hi. I'll see you
guys tomorrow. Take care.