Okay, that's done on Twitter. Oh god, people are dying. They need my help. I got you. Don't worry. I got you
There's a spy up there, but I can't do anything about it, but I can kill this sniper
Never mind. I got to write this on Steam. I need to go on Steam
Community. I need to sign in first
Groups. Oh, I have over 5,000 members. Wow. Awesome guys. Thanks
5,000 Steam group members. That's unbelievable. Party
And it's happening, let's say in 15 minutes. Sounds good. I think it did it pop up. Oh
There we go. Hit it. All right. Now we can stop playing. I'm in my server right now guys. If you're wondering
It's 8 o'clock at night. Yeah, are you in um, Australia or something? Must be pretty
Across the world. Uh-uh
Let's play Soldier. Do do do. Oh, I think uh, I think we're gonna have a special guest
Yeah, we're gonna have I think we might have a special guest in a second here dudes
No, I gotta do something real quick real quickity quick. Get back to this page
So one more test for the new guys that just showed up. Was this in your sub box?
Cuz I feel like it's not. If it is I'm totally wrong if it isn't then I screwed something up
But I think we might have a special guest referee
Hold on just a minute guys. Hold on just a minute. Thanks for the aid doc
Let's over here all and
Special guest are we gonna have a special guest? Oh ladies and gentlemen
Special guest is I'll let him introduce himself when he gets in here. What's up, man?
Hold on. Hold on. Oh, you can't you can't no one can hear anything you saying cuz I have to change this
I
Like I built you up to I was like, oh and here he is the special guest and I ain't nobody can hear you
Now they can
Hello, it's star ladies and gentlemen. Oh my god. Is it the real one or that fake imposter guy?
I think it might be the fake one
usually is I
Literally just woke up got out of bed. Hello. He's streaming. Okay
Yeah, yeah, I just decided to do it
You know, I didn't do it last night. So I tell myself I have to do it every week
There's a good goal and why it's on
It's on your YouTube channel
Yeah, I don't see it. Maybe I'm just dumb. It should be in feeds. Oh, yeah, that's they like tuck it away there
Yeah, it's not like in like subscription boxes in the feed. I think
I'm like shooting people on my own team. I'm like doing
Can you get in here? I will do that. I just is it possible?
One sec. I was just like removing HUD elements and I'll fix that up
Somebody said star. I just want to let you know you are the shit broseph. Oh
Shit I did not know that about myself. Well, you are nice nice
Pyro, good job. Good job pyro high drizzle
No, oh my god run
Nothing I could do there and now the plan is to jump
Oh the rocket you're gonna use the rocket and immediately get back stabbed again
Server is full who'd have thunk who'd have thunk man my reserve slot. I'm gonna have somebody in the sir
Oh god, this might be bad. I
Might have to kick a couple people only because my reserve slot doesn't work right now
Kick well, let me see. Let me see. I'm just gonna ask if anyone's cuz I'm not gonna kick anyone unless they're willing
See if I can get maybe one or two people
because I need two slots I
Am that fat
Boom
All right. Let's see. Are you are you like auto joining?
Spamming join game. All right. I gotta get that set up my uh
There's a lot of things you need to get so I know there is there is a lot of stuff. I need to get set up
like removing gold rush
But what?
Really, you don't like gold rush
It's all right sometimes I don't know it seems like it's come up a lot every time I look at you on the server
It's up. Hey, let's play gold rush. Oh, I love going to rush
Gold rush is like my favorite map
No, I I I gotta there's a lot of things that have to happen with this server
All right, you still is it still full? Yeah
Ready ready. Oh, I'm about to do something right now. It's a drastic time scalper drastic measures
Are you leaving your server? No, I'm gonna restart it
Yes, that's the fairest way to do it. This is I guess this is the this is the really only way the fair way
No one's leaving
You're all getting out. It's closed
This is my server, but we're trying to get star in the game and my reserve slot isn't really set up correctly
So it doesn't work
So I need to restart the server
Just to make it so everyone can you know get in if they need to server is going to restart right now after I do this
Let me do this
Log in to here
But somebody's how's your morning doing? You said you just woke up. Yep
That's the best kind of that's the best kind of out of bed. Yeah, just
Well, at least I went to the bathroom first it wasn't like hey computer
Yeah, at least you did you uh, did you do number one number two number three or all of them number one?
It's not like pork. What?
extra info
You could have said all the above. Oh, no
I had to give the extra info to like brag that I ate a whole bunch of pulled pork yesterday
And it's probably the greatest food ever made. I love pulled pork pulled pork is incredible
All right. So here we go. Server is going to restart so
Start spamming
It's like I'm playing Diablo 3
Look at this the stream is like look at look at how stupid this is right now. It's like, oh, can we get into my own server?
Oh
My god, I think I got into my own server. Yes
Or a harvest event. Did you get in? Yes. It is a good day to be harvest event
It is a good day. Well, that's that's one way to do it. So now we can start the stream
So thank you for your patience dudes. I appreciate it. It only took like 75 hours to start the stream
only all the hours
all the things
Joking. All right, I have to restart TF2. Oh, do you really? Oh
We cursed it yeah, I do
Did you do board do something break my graphics card immediately crashed
All right. Well, I I were you will get in here if you restart as quick as you can do it quick
Speed run join to the still it's still it's like seven on seven right now. And if not, then I'm gonna have to kick somebody
someone
Who's playing spy? That's that's how you'll choose
It's full. Oh, no. No, I got it. Oh, yes. Yes
I I I need to get like a custom hard like a real customer because right now this thing is like blocking my view
This capture and hold the control points to win the game. It's like day. I didn't know that
Tell me again. Oh
I just I thought that was a trade. Sorry you were trying to do me do it again. I'm sorry. I
Thought I was a trade. Oh
run
The control point is being captured. I was just assuming the item server was perpetually down
Yeah, it should be up. I got I got my items. Yeah, I do. So hello everybody
Welcome to this early Sunday stream
We've got special guest star here. I am going to bottom frag every time. I
Probably will do all I want to do is jump
Like jump it or all I gonna do
We jump this way that way oh
God why is it doing this? Okay, it didn't crash. It didn't crash. It's all good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
All right. I'm getting shot at from somewhere. Oh
I'm too crazy
He punched me. He actually punched me
See I changed my setup a little bit
See I'm playing obviously in a window and I move the window to like the right part of my screen
So I'm just like look it's it's really I gotta get used to this
Because I have the chat on the left and I have the window I know I need two monitors so bad it
I can't believe I waited as long as I did the end
Just for streaming
You know, I just need I need a I need about a computer, you know
The problem it's the problem is my computer is just it's good
I have a really good computer, but it's just not good enough to do two things at the same time
I'm gonna go scout. We'll go and scout. What's what somebody's asking the IP. It's just in my server
Oh, and I got smashed right there. That's not good
many centuries I
Shouldn't even mention it with nothing. What what am I complaining about? Nothing? Nobody heard it
No one heard. Oh
Get him. I can't believe I got up and get away. Also another problem harvest event is really dark
So it's like hard to see anyways
This map is I should play it more often because I play way too much harvest, but this is like it's totally different
Yeah, it's like it's like a whole new world
Playing crit scout. Yeah
Can't even go over there
with rocket jumps
Rocket job. Oh
No, I render the damn ghost. I hate this ghost. Why is this map in my rotation? I don't know why I
Missed actually, it's good every now and then yeah
Kind of like uh, I really hate I a ducked for the fact that has pumpkins laying everywhere
Mm-hmm killed by a pumpkin you feel like an idiot, but I had a look amazing
compared to the other viaducts
Yeah, I I ducked is fun. Yeah, I just got killed by a pumpkin
Crit scout crit scout. Oh, come on. He wasn't even there before
That's malarkey
Malarkey malarkey
Somebody's behind me, but I want to kill the soldier. He's dead. Anyways, no, this guy's got me. This guy's got me
Oh, this guy's got me. Oh, no, I got him. I'm not going in there pumpkin
Pumpkin, I shouldn't have shot him from that far away
too bad
Actually not doing too bad right now
Well, I'm doing terrible because I have a market garden anyone yet
Hey, it's all for that montage remember
Totally. I got the most amazing one yesterday
Quite literally the most amazing market gardeners probably ever happened ever
What'd you do?
It's I don't know. I don't know how to describe it, but it was for rocket jumps
I was surfing up a ramp so I was technically on the ground except it doesn't count. He was on the ground. Mm-hmm
That you know, I know man, is it the same type of thing when you when you
You know when you air blast somebody that's on an incline and they don't go anywhere but it technically they're still in the air
Yeah, it's like if anything is slanted and you rocket jump fast enough
You'll slide up it and sort of launches you off. It was the middle of sliding up something. I hit somebody
Yeah, when I use the uh
The reserve shooter I'll air blast somebody that's on an incline. They don't go anywhere, but I still get the mini crits on him
It's weird
Is the server full I believe it is I believe it is have to imagine so
This is your first stream ever
Welcome. Thanks for coming
whole chaos
Absolute chaos. I need health. I'm not going after that demo man with that health
What a bad I did. Why am I drinking this right here? That was a terrible idea
Pumpkin, yeah crap. Oh
That is star that is star your ears are not deceiving you
I think I just rocket jumped off a pumpkin and it was it was glorious
Is that like possible can you actually do that either that or a rocket hit me as I jumped I don't know Wow oh
I was pulling on
That was just one of those moments my whole body just shake shook shaked because I like was pulling up my melee and he
Shot me
Nearly 11 p.m.
What do you only Q bandit where you from in that's that's a long?
That's a huge difference. Yeah pumpkin
Yes, this is being recorded and will be uploaded in a few hours whenever I finish
14 days you got to wait for it
It's two weeks for processing
Actually, you know the the 720 streams on YouTube they do take quite a long time to process really
Melbourne, Australia
That is across the whole world. Well. Thanks for coming dude. It's a long ways away go in
immaculate crits
No, I can't go over there that certain death get out of here go go go. Oh, it's the ghost
Now I am so dead. Nice shot, dude. Nice shot. Do I have any scout tips? Um
Star do you have any scout tips?
Shoot things I guess
Shoot things and run
Yeah, I will tell you those scouts for me at least used to be one of my worst classes I was awful
And I just played it's just the more you play with it. The better you're gonna get I know I had like a
Die a lot. I had pretty much
It was my least play class behind pyro. Now. It's one of my most played classes. Oh
God you need to die a lot to start realizing you're gonna dial on this
Stop dying. No, I think we've got a robot star here. I'm sorry
No, no, not anymore. Not anymore. Okay, I am getting random blanks like so maybe every once in a while. I'll be a robot
That's okay. We we forgive you. We all still love you. I think that's spy. No. Yeah, it is
Oh, yeah, it is. I could smell you getting off the elevator
There's no elevator on this map. You wish here last night to wasn't you come on. What's that? What's that from stuff?
I don't know. Oh, come on. I'm sorry. I'm not cool. Oh
home alone, too
I'm the one that's not cool and you're here quoting
Nevermind
Did you I spoke to it? I've got I love that movie
beep-boop shot beep-boop. Oh
So I went to Dunkin Donuts. Don't do it. Oh, you know, it's so good
You got Dunkin Donuts in New Jersey. That's a case. I love the place. Isn't it? Yeah
Actually a one train ride home from Boston. There's Dunkin Donuts. There's like three Dunkin Donuts in South Station. Yeah
So I bought a dozen chocolate frosted doughnuts for myself
The person getting them for me just the entire time. They're picking out doughnuts giving me this awkward. Look
What could you possibly be using these for?
That's a lot for one person I
Need two slots
You need two reserve slots
Please reply what server is it? It's my server
my server
German's East Coast sir. No put it down. I
Hate when that happens when I you go too far. He's like just miss with the mini century
That's too far man
You miss with the mini century. I don't know some some reason it happens though. Oh
God, this is the ghost again. You know what? I'm just gonna taunt because oh when you taunt
I'm just like dancing. Oh wait, that's because I have that I thought I had the
thought I had the
Gunslinger out, but I didn't where is he? I heard a spy
Now that was a dumb thing
Someone said doughnuts are amazing, especially crispy crispy creams. You've had a crispy cream doughnut. Um, I think so
No, maybe oh, they're so good
Crispy cream doughnuts are incredible. I don't know don't have names
Well, it's it's like it's like a company it's like kind of like a Dunkin Donuts
crispy creams
Pretty much a crispy cream doughnut is just a glazed doughnut and it literally melts inside of your mouth. It is just on it's unreal
You can't there's only like a few of them around around the Northeast though
unfortunate thing you've ever had
ice cream
Um ice cream. What it what's ice cream? Is that like something to do with like milk?
What am I doing? Why am I doing this?
Am I ever gonna put a ping limit on my server to be honest?
Probably 20
Probably not
The only reason why I say that is because I haven't had one in the last like
Two or three weeks since the service been online and hasn't really been any problems
So probably not and if there ever was one it would probably be something very very high something like ridiculously high like
480 or something
That's pretty low
I wish I had 480 thing. Oh
This heavy. Oh my god. I ran out of bullets. Oh, no. Oh
You're dead. Oh, why'd I do that?
Mr. Foreman Gary the Foreman Gary
Okay, I think this is guy's name
Okay, he told me uh, I
To say his name
And I just did it cuz I felt like
Don't worry. We'll get this thing built up baby. Let's do it baby. There was a ghost
I'll name him Gary. Oh what I didn't get it off in time. Oh, I'm so mad at myself
Let's go for a punch ready. Oh
Get over here you son of a
We're going punch only engineer right now, it's gonna work cuz every time I scream
I'm telling you dude every time I stream and I just go for melee only it for some reason it works
I don't know why I don't know. I
Wish I knew the answer
But for instance like oh my god, this guy just crits cringed me. No, I have no oh
It was a nice attempt with the
ng fist only crits cringed
It's super effective
That's her Pokemon. I
Hate this door glitch on harvest. I just want to leave. Are you stuck somewhere? Oh
Punch in the center. I'm gonna punch the crap out of it
All right, so I'm gonna ask you this first before I
Before I answer it, but do you like the Vikings?
Vikings huh?
like
Like real Vikings or are we talking about fictional Vikings right now? I don't know. That was the question
No, I actually I meant to hit J. I hate how J and K are right next to each other. I mean
Thor was okay
so
Yeah, Thor was okay, I I enjoy bike
But if you're having stream issues try to refresh the stream refresh the page
Oh, you're gonna say grabbing stream issues then Vikings aren't that good
Yeah, if you're especially if you're on 720 then a good refresh the stream will probably help you out probably
And Vikings are even worse
How does it look by the way for anyone watching how because this is only the second time I've ever streamed in 720
Is it we good?
We sound good. We look good. We smell good
And your internets fine with that?
Apparently it wasn't last night. That's for sure. I
Not tried to stream 720 a long time
My internet just seems that it doesn't enjoy
Yeah, I'd rather lay back
Hey, if if all goes well, then that's I mean last time I did 720 it seemed to work. Okay?
But last night I was trying to set it up because I usually stream on Saturday nights
And it was just like no I could I could barely stream in 360 last night
I was like testing it by myself on listed
Or private whatever and it was not happening
If you haven't stream problems, I feel bad for you, son. I got nine and a half problems motor stream ain't one. No
Joby
Joby, I love your quote
Hey, look at what I tell you just punching. Oh, you're not getting away
That was the shotgun
No, it wasn't knock. Okay. Yeah, that was a I punched my fist and it looked like a shotgun. Oh
my god
chaos
There's like a line of soldiers waiting to market garden me
I'll go. Don't wait you go. What class is star star?
Spies bond
What class is a
What
What class is star? He's a soldier. Sorry when that's by backstab me
I had like like an aneurysm or something. That was weird
Don't do that. It's not good for you
Many century fight. Well, we got two many centuries and we got a spa. I am almost there
No, I don't want kills on my market gardener
81 81 nice nice nice nice nice nice
Somebody asked am I gonna do another scary game facecam?
Yeah, dude that game was horrible
Horrible in the terms of I completely I'm with you. I'm good with scary like just watch me. Oh god, please
Why are you still going down?
We've agreed. This is a bad idea
It's you know what? It's because I started I'll give you guys I'll give you the backstory about that video
so I started recording and
I figured because I got a bunch of people asked me to do that
Somebody was like, oh do amnesia do SCP do this or that so I just was like, you know
I'm gonna do it
I feel like doing it and I got to a point where I was gonna turn it off
I was like, you know what?
I'm not gonna make this video like I'll just do something else like I'm not gonna make this video
Because I sat down with it and notice how the video started when I was like kind of down with two
Yeah, like I I just I pretty much get oh god, I'm lagging why oh
No, that's the order. That's the door glitch. I think you were talking about before
What's I the video starts and I'm like already down two floors
That's because I stopped recording and I just sit in there going. I don't I can't do this
I really I really didn't think I could do it and then halfway through when I was actually recording
You can you can see like in my face during the video. Oh my god over time over time. This is a pretty ridiculous fight
I'll get back to that story in a second. We lost no
Oh
Round ends as I'm midair. That's market going someone. That's all that matters
It's all matters
nothing else matters
But yes, I mean I I started to get to that point where I got the first spooked the first like big jumping scare
For a second. I was like, you know what? I'm about to hit I'm not I'm gonna hit escape f9 and I'm not doing it
But that's what I said, like, you know what? I can't give up like I have
I'm already like halfway done with like this thing. I might as well finish it
When that guy comes out that stuff, I'm not gonna ruin it really if you ever do
It's it is it is terrifying
Rage quits the game for you, too
That's why like at the end of the video I look like somebody hit me in the face with a wrench after that
I watched more videos of the game because like I wanted to figure out like how it ended or there was more
yeah, I freaked out because
seriously like
What you saw at the end of that video was like a 100% genuine like my face
I thought I didn't even know what was going on. I freaked out and then I was just like wait what happened?
Why am I did me? I was genuinely befuddled. Oh, that's not live stream it. Oh
Yeah, keep playing
Become known as the stair simulator guy the stairs the new stair simulator you're on it
Somebody was telling me to do a containment breach, and I looked up a couple things on it and my god that kid oh
my god
That it just looks it looks it looks ten times worse than scp. Oh eight seven the regular one
Wow nice shot
No, I'm gonna go
Bye like that one is like actually 3d make creatures and weird like stuff. We're not really 3d, but it's I
Was scared playing Quake 4 so
There's a game. You should not be scared playing
Quake 4
Yeah, there's this one room where there's like a giant beating heart in it
It's really dark and it took me like 20 minutes to get there
But all you have to do is walk up some stairs and like the missions over I
Was like just crouched walking the whole time like nope nope
doing this oh
We're gonna get up. I knew that was gonna happen. I knew that was gonna happen
What class do I play the most probably engineer you get actually we'll take a look you know
I do from here
Stats there you go. I've actually don't think I've ever shown this excited in a Q&A one time
But these are my team fortress 2 stats
And the reason why spy is so high this goes back in like 2007
Like that's all I played
Got a spy. I was looking at my set the other day, and I was disappointed with how much spy I played
Mm-hmm like 35 hours. When did I do that? When did I waste that much time?
Yeah, I have 138 hours to do that. That's nothing though
And also this is um I think my stats got reset at some point like very early on in the game
Oh, yeah, I reset mine a while. Yeah, oh
God there was one day where I was playing with bots and no one was playing with bots
I was like oh, I have to do this. I have to reset this
Bye
Spy on spy on spy
Whoa whoa no I didn't want to hit end
All right team, what do you say we do this come on? Let's go, baby
Did the dirt did it did the dirt? We're all hitting this together Jake
I'll play spy
spy
Spy I want to be the cool kind of person who plays spy. I want to be the coolest on this play
Oh come on. I was trying to did I actually get away with that like I did no I didn't oh
God, I just keep getting people like right when they have no health
That's how you do it. Oh, I knew I was gonna screw that up
Knew I was gonna screw that up. It's a bad attitude
No, I did a dead space to video well technically by I technically did grandpa has one on respawn
It's a hole in this straw, and I can't drink the rest of my iced tea
You're supposed to be a hole in it. That's how straws work. No
Aren't you so glad I'm here?
I am I it's
Hold on let me fix this
There we go. I did that. I did the best thing I flipped the straw upside down and put it back in genius
I know I am a genius already. I have no idea where we're going
I should have just changed the map to begin with but I was too busy like not paying attention
Hopefully, it's gold rush stars favorite map
like nowhere to jump I
Love gold rush so much
Actually, I did see one person who can do a jump on
Second point second map of gold rush from like start to finish all the way through with one jump
I'd probably just spend the entire round trying to do that
And if I did it our team would win just instantly. It's like getting a nuke
Getting a nuke
Somebody asked do I like yeah?
I'm using the diamond back because I like it and plus it's it's strange to so got to use it if it's strange I
Think that the diamond back has a bad rap
It's
Okay, I mean it's not it's
When you're fighting like 40 gunslinger and cheese. It's yeah
Well, let's put it this way right so the the ambassador and the diamond back had to do the same damage, right?
The ambassador shoots slower
The ambassador shoots 20% slower than the diamond back
But you get crits on the headshots
I mean you get crits on this if Doug you said if there are many centuries around I would say they're both good a
Lot of people really bash on the the diamond back well the best part about the diamond back is the sound oh yeah
So I mean technically it's it's like a better. It's a
Default if you're not going for headshots. It's better than the ambassador if you can't get headshots. It's better than the ambassador for sure
The ambassador is still though. It's it's so good. It's so good. Oh
Yeah playing that guitar. Oh
Are you why am I wearing that like Christmas item? I gotta put my ring on and somebody gave me
I have like the Christmas heart thing on you're just I don't know you're
hearty
I'm a cold so I could think of I totally forgot the frying pan
frying pan is
There's a mini century
I'm gonna take that out
Do rank oh
Screenshot post to reddit
Screenshot screenshot screenshot, but I need help what am I doing hide behind the cot?
I blew up in a bush get over here get over here
God all right here. We go
to kill you oh
No, oh my god. That was so I'm sorry dude. That was like a face stab and a half
Don't ask me how that happened. I want that medic. I want to kill that medic. I
Want that medic to heal me?
Yeah, I'm disguised as you. I know that I know the deal. Oh, I tried a side stab and it never works cuz I'm too terrible
It's fine
But you spent all the hours. No, I got body block
It's gonna be awesome get fear three fear three
You're three being scary. I don't think so hmm. I heard it's pretty I heard it's got its moments
My roommate in college played he was like a big fan of fear one and two he like praised the game all the time
I just never had time to play it be honest a
Lion cast I got a I got to talk about that. I will talk about that
I think I want to do it in a proper video though. Not like really in a live stream and wait. That's you
Yeah, I just I shoot you. I'm sorry
But it's okay pretty much for the just about 400 people watching right now. I will I will give you a sneak peek of what's going on
I'm playing in a tournament if those of you that know incredible orb
He put together a team. It's an invite only
Tournament for this new game. That's not out yet. I don't even know if I can even say the name of the game
It's like in not even in pre-alpha
But this this next weekend
We're gonna be playing a tournament
Me incredible orb and I will see stealth and whoever wins that tournament
It's gonna be all streamed total biscuits gonna be casting it. It's gonna be pretty ridiculous
and
If you win you go to e3 and then if you win that you go to Paris
So when we uh, I want to win
So I don't even know but I want to win. Oh, give me that crit. Give me that crit. Oh, no, no, please
Please I want to get this crit, please. Yes. Yes
But yeah, it's it's not it's not
It's kind of like a quake type game. It's kind of like a quake mod type game
But yeah, it is uh, it is a oh you're gonna get crit right here, baby
Do it
But I'm gonna make I'll make a proper video explaining
Explaining what it actually is in like a vlog or something in the next couple days, but it's exciting. It's really exciting
I haven't been able to talk about it. So my lips had had to be sealed the last couple weeks
But yeah, maybe we'll get to go to e3. I need to do more secret things
It's like really. Hey, I'm doing something I can't talk about. I
Need to do more secret stuff
Please don't shoot me. Wow, that was an amazing shot
Too bad. He didn't kill me. Yeah total biscuit
Yeah, I forget their names. There's three like super super famous guys that are gonna be casting it on twitch
I don't know their names though. I know total biscuit. That's it. Well, it doesn't matter. I just did a good rocket show
That's all that matters
here
What what why am I on fire?
What look at this what's going on? I can't look at this. Why am I on fire right now?
What is that? I'm in a booth. I
Pulled up the dead ringer and I oh
that was I think I just had like a brain fought right there cuz I pulled the dead ring around when he lit me and
It worked and then it instantly why did I come out of it? Do you hear the noise?
It was like oh I came out of the dead ringer
But I didn't I was still in it
It is not Renaissance heroes
Is orb even online? I'm just gonna like ask him if I can like talk about it
Can I be like, hey, can I tell people what I'm doing?
Where's it illegal?
Yeah, we're very cool for us to
Hey, I'm gonna go off spy. I'm too stupid right now to go to play anything else
Say hello to your Spaniard viewers. Hello everybody in Spain. Hope you guys are spending good in that Spaniard land
The cool part is I want to go to you three. That's like the main thing
Is it me? I could really care less about like winning the whole thing. How is you I?
Could care less about winning like the whole thing
but I do it would be awesome to go to e3 because then I could make videos and stuff about going to e3 and
It'd be so much fun. Well, that was a Wow
I am sorry to every single person here that just got covered in that Girardi. That was my fault. Well, I'm got quick fixed
What am I doing? I gotta get up here. What are you doing? Oh
Dang and
Oh, I hear the Christmas bells
Need ammo, I probably will do more morning streams
We're not really morning streams, but early afternoon streams on Sunday
Just because I know that Saturday night can a lot of people can't watch it
And I am sorry about that
Oh
Every time I see somebody in the air. I always think it's you and I get scared
Every time every time somebody's
Oh, it's any time you're in a anyone's in the air I keep thinking it's you and it freaks me out
It's perfect
Spawn to spawn belly to belly the bum for jumbo
Spawn to spawn belly to belly. You know what that's from back to back belly to belly. I think it's from where
Where in the world is Carmen San Diego? I really think it is the game show the old game show
Somebody please look that up. Somebody find that out for me right now. I
Bet show is unwatchable. I wouldn't know
There he is there he is he's going for those garden kills no cool free
Hi stuff
Hey
Wait that wasn't you it wasn't no, there's actually I know looter you like where's the same hat as me?
It goes from our garden. Oh my god. I thought it was I thought it was you I was like, oh my god
Oh, no, if it was me, I would have got you
Her her and star star sounds a bit robotic. He said he's his internet's going up and down. So sorry
Not anymore though. You sound fine now. Okay, good
Now have I killed one person this like entire time, how do I have 18 points?
What what did I do? Did I kill anybody? I guess so. I don't even like remember killing anyone. I
Did a jump I did Joe my mommy was proud
Well, I got up my cat is like scratching the door. I probably have
One of if not the most annoying cats in the world
See he knows my window when it's open, he knows he can come over and annoy me by just going like
Until I come let him in and if I don't let him in he will sit there
He probably wouldn't even eat or sleep until I let him in like through like the window
Yeah, you kidding and it's like, you know, there's another way you can go right that you can't get in my window
He just knows I'll let him in
Always leave it open
Hmm. So what time is right now?
That's the real question. I don't know probably another round or two on
TF and I think I'm gonna transition to some Diablo free
Diablo some Diablo cuz I gotta get my witch doctor up in
You know, I think we're still the same
45 I did level up a bit. Hold on a second. Are there there's not random crits on right now, is there? No
Was that it cuz that guy that guy was uber charged. He wasn't crits create. That was weird. I got killed by a crit
Yeah, you know, no, no, no, no, you know, it probably was like a fuck banner. That peepee probably was the peepee banner
Keep banner that I'm gonna get headshot. Oh
My god, you both just like came in at the same time and I missed
Let's go. Yeah
Let's go
No, no, no, no with that thing what Tommy's left? Yeah. How do you aim?
I love the Thomas love. It's my favorite. It's too hard
Aiming is hard. Yeah star does make rocket jumping look so much fun
He also makes it look really easy too, and it is absolutely not
One of the best videos I've ever seen of Team Fortress 2 is that video where you jumped to do
Where you jumped across like the whole thing a high tower and man-treaded some pyro it was unbelievable
I wasn't even that good. Oh, it was the don't even know
When I finally put all these park gardener kills together
Well, when you finally put this bark garden thing together, I I it's probably gonna get like 700 million views. It's gonna be that good
The bomb is mirroring a checkpoint. All right. Oh
Man, hey you did
Somebody wrote I can't believe I'm watching a YouTube stream. That's working
Yeah
There yeah, YouTube streams are well, they're in beta. So there is always gonna be a lot of problems
But you know, whatever it's all good. And who's the other guy that is star? I'm a guy
That is STA our star. Thank you for spelling it
I
Somebody write stars channel in the in the in the comment section just so the people that don't know will know
It's youtube.com slash niched
ni
I see HTS, right? Yes
Usually I'm pretty bad
So I know you're gonna win this tournament because I'm guaranteeing it's a spelling bee. That's why I don't want to talk about it. Oh
My god get out of it
Just on your head. Oh, it's so scary. I
Like don't know like what to do it. There's like spies this rocket garden ring stars and
This other guy that's like another star. It's doing it. I'm like a heavy. I don't have any points
Just saw that guy get smoked. Oh
Here's a pro like a pro tip pro tip as heavy on car
If you're being a cart heavy do it do the crouch dance. You got to go like do do do do do
Do you do you do you gotta like crouch grouch grout grout?
You gotta be gonna win because I I think I've convinced my team not to try it all off
You see like the pyro walking out there
We're taking it easy
Cart heavy is fun. Yeah, okay. It is cart heavy spot how to jump is cart heavy
You got to get the new rocket launcher for the heavy. Yeah
the best you could do is like
Yeah gloves of running urgently jumps
Here we go ready. That's I'll show you how to rocket jump as a heavy
See look at how far I just went. Oh
No, I'm almost out of my lodge
Dunkin Donuts fresh-brewed iced tea. That's not a good thing
Get another I have to drive to Dunkin Donuts. I wish I'd said the Dunkin Donuts in my house. Yes
Get a Dunkin Donuts just buy a franchise just own it just so you can live in it. I
Would I would if that there if I had a house
Think I'm not even really a big coffee drinker as I'd love iced tea and their iced tea is really really really good. Oh
Dear God chaos
Maybe I should shoot some things. I think I'm gonna shoot some things. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I got I got a ghost recon
They gave me hats
Ghost recon. Yes. So now the classes I'm allowed to play insist of rocket jumping soldier or one of the classes that got a hat
Is that game any good he played it's not out yet. It's out in like a week. Oh, it's looking really good
Yeah, I heard it's supposed to be pretty
Your hints they're going a different like direction, aren't they? Whoa
It's kind of funny that a ghost recon is I love the first one
Mm-hmm, and they have dumbed down the series a lot since then and usually that would like piss me off to no end
But for some reason this time I'm glad ghost recon is dumber
Because what was the one game? I'm happy about that. It's dumber. It wasn't wasn't the ghost recon series very very strategic
Like I had a very stuff or planning groups and this one
I mean it has all of that but for the most part, you know, it's not gonna happen, right, right
It's kind of like TF2
Hmm. So when I watch like trailers over those things reminds me of Gears of War a little bit like that kind of it's like third person
Yeah, it's not that third person vibe to it
It's definitely it has like all the wall hugging mechanics that gears would have
But I don't know. I actually wanted this game since they first started showing single-player trailers of it
But multiplayer looks pretty fun. I love fun things
Yeah, definitely
Fun stuff. I throw to peepee
Alright, we'll do I cannot get on that car. What am I doing? Why did I just pull that out? I'm gonna die
Why what about what do I have this awful not fists of steel? I need to put
Dermot you keep running in a circle. I know
That's what happens when I live stream
My two centers of my brain fight for dominance and like I then I just like walk about in circle what happened
Now we get a wrangled
Century that is yikes
Like that's a spy. Oh
I
Missed my melee swing because I was in his body
Where's this other guy? Wait sandwich take it eat it. Yeah
Come this way. Come this way. I'm gonna go up. We're gonna go up top and
Oh
Get on the car
And come on somebody touch it. Oh, I should have stayed behind it
Yeah, but you didn't you know, I'm stupid
It's a one more round after this and then we'll move on to some do I have below three? Okay
Take that
I should have ready. That's it. No, it's not. Oh my I should have given a sandwich my poor medic friend
No
That was essentially a warning new rank
I'm sufficient kind of lethal. It's good. Oh
God spy a
spa
yes, this will be on YouTube in
When I finish the stream, it'll probably be up there after maybe an hour to a processing. So
We assume what time is it right now?
It is nine thirty a.m. For me probably stream for another couple hours or so at least another hour
and
It should be up by maybe noon ish. Maybe
That's what it says about I talked to some people and they said that apparently that's not true. That's not the case
Yeah, I guess there's a lie to you
It's like oh you can't you can't upload a automatic stream longer than two hours and then people do it
So I don't know. I guess they would want to discourage everyone. I don't know. Yeah, it's weird
It's very weird
Someone said since when is her blur go a warning her blur
It is yeah, I could be seen as a warning. Well, what else do you think I'm gonna do if I'm screaming that?
I'm either on the toilet or about to kill you. Oh man. They have too many things going on in there. Watch out buddy
Yeah, you take the sandwich. You need it you eat sandwich. I'm we gotta go. I gotta go around
It's all about is it they only have a mini century man
We're getting pushed back by a mini century and like a bunch of devil man. Oh god. I'm so dead. Oh god
Why do I not have these out somebody asked? All right, here we go. Here we go
There we go. Come on. Come on. Somebody help me. I shot you with my gun
It was a bomb gun a bomb gun. Is that new? Yeah, I hope I get it
I am really believe all don't know
I'm probably not gonna switch servers for some of you guys asking only because stars in here and
I wouldn't want it to be like oh, we both can't get into the same server and plus I'm on my server
So I like playing on my server because I like playing with the dudes on my server because they're cool
So one more we say let's go to
No, no, no, no, no, let's go to good old gold rush. Oh, please. No
All right, fine. We find out
Well, I'm trying to like figure out how to like do something fun. Ah
No, I slapped you I got you. You need to rapid-fire that. Oh you can do that
Yeah, if you just keep mashing the button you can get slapped so much it like pops you up in the air
You there. All right, let's go. Oh, you're gonna be mad, but I kind of want to play on Turbine
No, it's not as long as I don't know. I just want to jump in turbine. I
guess
Turbine has stairs. I
Just love Turbine. I love a lot of things. Don't I should have played two for two for it?
But turbines like the good two for it, isn't it? No two for it is the best two for it
No, a two for it is the best two for it. I'll stick with demo night. Oh, it's my spray. Ah
German oh
Everyone now hates you Gary monster. Look what you did what I do what I do what happened what I do
You picked this map. So
There's a ceiling on this map
There's nowhere that does not have a ceiling. Yeah, but you could do like an off-the-wall kind of like move. Okay?
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know I'll ask him star you're gonna play Diablo 3 as well. Yeah sure. Yeah, sure
Yeah, sure
T Milan
Okay. Oh, I hear a dog. I think that might be my dog
My dog. Oh my god a sentry
Strategy to turbine hold mid win game. Oh
How are you still here to overheal makes sense? Oh, okay. Damn it. I I
Was trying I was gonna go for a top kill and I'm gonna walk into corner
Why is this response so long I changed that
It's respawner way. It's respawn time right change the respawn on turbine. You can't
It's to turbine. Come on
You could change the respawn easy cat. I don't know. I have my respawn wave time at 2
And that's supposed to be god crits
I thought I was gonna bite my ankles in a second. He's probably gonna run here
Oh, come on, I want my crits. Oh my crits let grandpa play Diablo. I don't think he would get it
I think he'd be too confused
Because there's too many numbers to deal with in Diablo. You don't just like shoot people
Well, that's why they made numbers off by default and no advanced tooltips
People like him what just happened?
All right, so I charged with the charge and charge and right when I clicked right click
I got backstabbed and my body just like baseball slid across like the whole map. I
Love getting backstabbed or right as you rocket jump and your body just poof
Okay, what do you say let me find some dude to run into here there's a mini sentry
Mmm help me. I'm real I swear
That's a sticky
Mm-hmm. That's me getting shot hide right here. Shh. I know a secret
And then you just what what I I was gonna work on my secret technique and 20 seconds. Hold on a minute. Oh
Actually, I was about to type in the server password
Like hold on. Let me just like type my Archon password right now in front of like 400 people
Okay, that would be a bad idea
20 that's too long 20 seconds. It's supposed to be like 9
Come here. There's turbine. Oh
Why how did knock back?
Get over here. It is morning. It is 9 just about 10 a.m. Here in the East Coast
United States. Oh, I've got I thought it. Oh, yeah, we had like 2% health left 10% 20, whatever
I killed a guy. This is why we can't have nice things
Please German just please one two for it. I
Think two Ford is is maybe I took it out of the rotation
Alright, how about this before I leave? I will switch the map to two for it. How does that sound?
That does not sound good. Yeah, but this guy does. Oh
Okay, I did not know that was coming
Yeah, he was too busy hitting me
Remember if you crouch and just stand still when you're in a melee fight one-on-one
Probably gonna win because people freak out too much they run around they go. What is this and hey open that door? Whoa?
I'm going to get the intelligence. You know what screw this. Oh
Never mind. He already got it. Good job scout
Good job, dude
You type 25 comments and haven't gotten a cheeseburger yet
So I think there's a YouTube bug you should have already gotten at least three cheeseburgers dispensed from your laptop reading or just
Chat the stream. How do you do that?
It's an uh
It's just you make it. Oh, I'm sorry. I can't speak too much stuff going on
You uh, you just do
Update comments automatically and they'll come in as they come in. I
Think there's still like a minute or so behind though. That's the thing with YouTube
This isn't even pro turbine
There's no banana
pro turbine
Yeah, I'm pro turbine. There's a banana
Is it really?
Well, they call it banana, but it's like a different path on the side. It's shaped like a banana
Yeah, you should you should get a double cheeseburger should come out of your
out of your CD tray
Every 25 comments that you make on the stream a double cheeseburger from your favorite
Restaurant comes out of your CD tray. I don't have a CD tray. That's probably why it's not working
Yeah, if you don't have a CD tray or a zip drive to you have to have like a zip drive. Oh
God
Why am I still equipped? Why is it still out? Why do I still have this out? What am I doing?
Can't believe I got away with that. Oh my god. I can't believe we got away with that either. Oh
That was a brigade oh
I'm at the end of my drink. You know what that means
It's time to this thing is like floating. What the hell your cheeseburger had blue cheese
Sounds pretty dang good
All right star you ready I got a question for you. Oh god, what is
One more round we'll do one more
Please please
All right, fine. We'll switch. All right. We'll go to start a star. What map do you want to play them jump tricks?
You want to play the jump map? I don't even think I have it installed
All right, it needs to be like in like the team fortress database thinking like frontier
Frontier and
Here we go
Your cheeseburger had a green bun. Well, that's definitely if you're gonna ask me a thing
Oh, yeah, I forgot the thing. I was gonna ask you
Probably was really really important. Yeah one round of frontier and that'll end the team fortress for the day
Then it will bond Diablo 3 for a little while
I was trying to think of good stock payload maps that aren't upward and my mind just blanked and I said frontier
All right, what do you mean red or red or blue better? Let's go. Let's go blue go blue
I'm gonna play medic
Because I kind of feel like it. I like this setup. I'm gonna stick with it
Except I don't want the crits create a gadget. I want the default Medigun. There we go
You gotta keep control of your TVs. You have snipers hump in the door
Spray
mission begins in
500 seconds that would be nice
There's a sign out here that says speed limit 15
speed limit 15
Five
Thirty so have you guys been able to hear the in-game audio like the explosions and stuff
Or is that been too low? I'm always so afraid to turn that up because I feel like it's gonna overpower everything I said
I think I'm gonna get crits, which is perfect because then how could I possibly miss a market card?
All right, who am I gonna give this to? I don't even know we'll go with the
You know, he's already doing one. Let's go this way. Oh my god. Oh god. Oh god
Wow
Come here. Come here. Oh
God work
We're good. We're good
You're good. I'm not. Oh, no, I was bro. I was my hand my right click
Did you drop uber my right click was clicking on the uber?
It was like and I got backstab
I've got oh, no, that's you. I can't believe that no work
I don't even know if it was you because there was like three medics
Maybe two I can't count. Give me that uber. Give me that over
All right, I'm not gonna look now I better watch out I'm doing it right
come on heavy and
Team uber I'm hiding everyone is safe now
Yeah
Come on. Give me another uber. Oh god two spies. That's not gonna work
I'm in of my head right now
spies a spy a spy
Help me
No, stay alive this guy. Oh my god. You were about to die. Oh
I'd use it. I didn't want that was really early
I'm ashamed to say I know you this guy. Oh, yeah. Well, look what we just did
We just came like that
We did a good job
Well, I saw this guy only had like 1% health and if I didn't use it
He would have died and it was only me and a sniper behind him. So
When will the next grandpa video be uploaded? It was uploaded last night
Machinima respawn. It's on the featured video list. Go check it out
Actually to be honest, I'm sorry. I didn't even I didn't even let anybody know that was there
I'll do that today after this is over. Oh
This is bad the tension
I guess I do have two kills. No, come here mark. Let me hear you. Oh
backed up into a knife
somebody wants me to say a
Dirty word hidden do it. It's hidden in like a regular sentence. I know that I know that trick
That's a dirty trick
If your chat is frozen try and re refresh the page
reexec
Really? What do you say? Really? What?
reexec the config
I need help. I need you to heal me, please. Oh
This thing is so good. I love this thing
Doesn't seem like much what the overdose doesn't seem like much but it is
It really helps in situations a lot of situations at all. It's not that much it is though, but you need
boot solider
Yeah, but then you start to take damage like you you don't get the full plus three. Yeah
Well, you just have to make sure you hit every needle
But that's too hard and you are gonna land right on my face
Now if you're gonna back up like a punk not gonna
Like what you don't want to die
See look, I'm running fast. I'm gonna back up like a punk. All right. I'm going for a team over right there
We're looking at we gotta push up. It's not it's not gonna be a single man effort right now. Oh
No, oh did I just totally block you from that? I
Actually apologize if I did I probably missed anyway, I'm missing like every swing
giving you per sauce
No, I don't want him to die that's a spy that's a spy that's a spy it definitely is no it's not
You know this thing be careful. I thought that was I know not that anything but the little full caver
Anything with the evil caper miss out. Come here. Don't run away. Oh
Everybody needs help and there's nothing like oh
Don't die. There's a guy behind you. I'll push that up
Oh, yeah
Get on this. How is this mini century? Oh, I'm dead. Goodbye. Goodbye cruel world
You got chicken out of the tray. That's that's not supposed to happen
There's only supposed to be cheeseburgers meat and cheese the ketchup onion mustard
Relish why am I going this way? I always do that on upward. I always go the wrong way upward support the little guy
hashtag that's my
philosophy and
Apparently grandpa you sentry set up and you guys have a lot of stuff over there
You don't even know yet because it's set up like four miles away
You need a time to prepare and put it in a really really lame century spot. So name for that lame
name
Everything's name. I
Backed up into another knife backed up back it up. That's the way
You are up top there and I'm gonna die
Man, these spies are really making me paranoid
There's like forty hundred of them. I mean to
This one back here somewhere. Oh, there is
Well, I was gonna heal that guy too. My god. I
Am NOT turning my back. I'm gonna face this way the whole time. See I knew it get out of that
Oh overdose you are my friend
It's all in your mind
Yeah, but even if it is on my mind, it's still still makes me get that extra mile
In your mind. Oh
My god, I can't heal y'all Ryan. All right, let's push this thing
Somebody get up there. Somebody get up there. There we go. There we go. There we go
push little wagon
Prepared for lame century. Are you mentally ready for this?
Is there like a bunch of there?
That's all right. It's all right spy. I got you. I got you
I'll make sure you have a nice thick overheal
By the time you get out of here and by the time I'm not afraid to leave which is right now
There's a lot of people there. Oh
No, no, no, heal me. Heal me, please. Oh damn it bomb gun. Ah
That was pretty nice run though. I I'm proud of that little run proud people say you should try to pan me
I am missing every single market garden. Oh, that was a glitch
That's why that's not why it looks like he's running slower. That was weird. We got you
I gotta get up move up move up. No, come here
That gear up. Oh, is our century gun?
Damn leave it is we got three medics to we should be pushing this car like crazy. You need 14 heavies
We only have one and there was there's a spy right there that pyro. I'm waiting for him to come over here
My yeah, here's no head either. Where's this head?
Where's this guy's head? Yeah, I've been noticing that a lot lately. Is that just on spies?
Yeah, if a spy disguises as a pyro when they're wearing a certain hat, it can't display the hat. Oh
Or something like that. Oh god. I that guy just ubered at the same time as me
We just both over the same guy at the same time
Yeah, I'm going I'm going for it. I'm going for some not so stuff right here
What I'm sniper because we had none. No, we have three
Now this is a higher number that guy only needed one hit and I didn't get it
What movies were films my planet on scene?
Probably I still haven't seen the Avengers. I have to see the Avengers
Have you seen that star? Yep. Is it was it good?
Yes, I know it's good because there's explosions
But I had like a two hour long conversation with someone about why it's terrible really
Just nothing makes sense if you watch it you need to question everything that happens and say why is this happening?
And you will realize you don't know
Nobody knows the Avengers. I don't really watch a whole lot of movies to be honest
Dark night. Yeah, that's definitely one. I mean yeah hat you have to see that though
That's pretty much. They beat you. It's pretty much a moral obligation for every human being to watch the Christopher Nolan Batman movies
like please
You know, you're bring a spy yeah, hey I know I
Am aware of that. I realized that like about
Two or three seconds into that over. I just thought I'd let you know
Yeah
I realized because I realized especially when he ran the other direction when I ubered him and he turned left
And they went backwards. I was like wait a dip fights that way. What are you doing?
You could just have uber phobia
Good. Do I read any books? I do not don't really actually I take that back. I
Read some time. I read like graphic novels does that count? Oh?
That does not count, but there's words in there. Let's just look ones
Duck to Naples that makes good ones. Oh
Dog to Naples makes great great graphic novels the earthworm Jim guy. Oh, I didn't know he did that
Yeah, they're pretty good. At least like the art is very very interesting really awesome. I got you. I got you ballin Colin
You need help more than anybody. I'll make sure to get you. Oh my god
All right, you know what no more medic. It is pyro time want to see my backpack
Here you go. It's kind of all over the place right now ever since I gave everything away
I don't have any more like cool hats okay. I should stop stop doing this and actually shoot bullets
Why I gotta take that teleporter am I doing spies
Spies have no match for the pyro and except sometimes
No, don't don't don't don't don't don't oh
Come on. What did he even come from I have zero unusuals?
bad player
Yeah, I don't know how you guys
Aren't winning more well. We only have one minute. That's pretty much the end right there. Do I still like the gorillas?
Oh my god. Yes
Gorillas are the best band like ever. We're not gonna win this
Too much too much good stuff happening on it as a center. We lost it's over
It is over so in that in that case. You know you always got to do this. You're always gonna go spy
the skies as
An enemy heavy or something. Well, you know I'm gonna play I'm gonna go scout just so I can run away
I'm gonna take the coward way out. Why am I taking the teleporters? Let's go. So this is where we transition
What oh wait, can we maybe you
Yeah, it's over it's over
I'm gonna move on to some Diablo 3. Oh my god. Are we gonna find items or gold?
Hopefully gold cuz I need more. No, we've lost. Please. I hope I don't find any items
Oh
Well, thanks guys for playing if you got in thank you
And time to transition to Diablo 3 if you just came if you're wondering all but it's over though
It's this is all gonna be on YouTube later on today. So yeah
Thanks for playing dudes. Let's go on to Diablo 3. This is where we go
disconnect
quit
Yes, we're all do you sure? I don't know. I have replays. I don't want to lose. It's now
Diablo flee
Super Monday night combat. I've it's I
Can't I can't get into it. It's I don't know what it is. I'm not sure
I have a couple of friends now that are really starting to enjoy it, but I just can't I don't know why
They did just add a new game mode, which is weird. It's kind of like realism
I guess where everybody dies quicker
Really? Yeah, I just I need to get into it at some point. Maybe I'm not sure yet
But is this even in the right spot? I think it is not quite. Hold on
I'm gonna screens gotta go black for him second dudes
You can even rocket jump in that game and I still don't like it that much
So, I don't know what else there could be to encourage me to play
Maybe hats. Oh
There are hats then. Yeah, that's a good way to play screen region. Yeah, three
That
You know, you can stream with DX story and it's better in screen region. Really? Yeah. Whoa stream section. Oh my god
Do you use the x-tory? Oh, yeah. Yeah you do. Yeah, I do. I don't stream with it though
You should oh my good God every time I try to bring a stupid window right now. It'll be magic
All right. I'm gonna try this in one more time because this is being ridiculous
Okay
Streamception mania that was just like I felt like I was looking through a tunnel right there that might like I'm gonna like puke
Okay, love of everything that is sacred. Can we get this in the right spot? Yes, DX story telling you but DX story is
Expensive. No, okay. That's good enough. Good enough. Good enough. All right. Nobody likes steal my password
Stolen hacked nobody steal my stuff because I have like I have like really good stuff. No, I don't. All right
I'm on nightmare. Oh, you like my my like witch doctor name
Burglar he's the burglar and you and I in a game. I'm not in a game. I'm on axe 3 nightmare
No, that's I'm further than that. Well, you have to come help me. Okay, you have to
Okay
Are you sure you don't want to just kill asthma and 4,000 times? That's what I think
We're gonna make this game where you don't have to run the same bosses over and over again
Then we're gonna make asthma and give you all the experience every single cent of experience
I want in my bank account. So for hold on I gotta get over like the Diablo 3 lag for the first two minutes
I'm just like doing random moves. I wonder I you know, there's got to be a reason why that happens
It has to be because it's syncing you up with like the DRM or something like that has to be I don't know
But you need to invite me. That's right
Invite to the party. Yeah, and now I'm gonna reject it
But please be my friend
The turd burglar I made his name burglar because of like burger boy
Yeah
Yeah, you gotta get rid of it. You gotta get rid of the initial lag of Diablo 3
Whoo-hoo. Hooray
All right. I think we can do it
Well, it's the the reason why it lags even when I'm not streaming when I'm just playing just by myself
The first like two or three minutes every time you play Diablo 3 for some reason it just does
It's do a new move and it's like wait. What is this? Yeah, you have to like what it load Diablo 3 or anything
It's so it's sort of like Minecraft
That's like the only way I can really make an assumption to what it's kind of like, you know
Minecraft is like when you first start playing it's like loading every single thing in the world. See like
No, I have to load all this stuff
It'll even out in a minute. I promise
You know, what's a good game
Medium pizza medium a large cheese pizza. Yes
Let's go let's go with the lag
Alright, I want to get some Reyes and some uniques
Well, people still people people are still seeing streamception. No, they're not in this
Or is that just an old comment from somebody from a while back? I don't shoot arrows anymore. I'm taking what's going on people's thing
They're seeing
Shouldn't be
Let me watch my own stream make sure like nothing's happening. You should stream with your story
I gave the recommendation and I should stream the cops added
Teach you in two seconds every time I stream when I did the x-split game stream thing
For some reason I don't know why it like it lags. It lags really really terribly. Oh, no, we're not getting streamception
Looks okay. What about 720? That looks okay, too. Okay, just making sure nothing was happening
It's probably the YouTube comment system like all slow and dumb
That's where it is probs
So I I'm playing which doctor which doctor is very fun
Very good. Very cool. I
Am shooting bombs
bombs
There's actually pretty cool build with demon hunter. I found out that we just regenerate hatred like ridiculous amounts of it
You could use cluster our non-stop
Really our is amazing
That's pretty cool. Pretty damn cool
pretty snazzy
This guy's an elite in these
Did he killed my little buddy? Oh, he's back. Don't worry. I have a feeling maybe I shouldn't even be helping you. Why I
Don't know. I've got
5300 damage it feels
wrong
But I need the help get out of here
Already a rare really didn't think this one happened. I thought it was just gonna be the sea of blue, but I want one
What do I think of the spider-man reboot? I?
think it's um
It's not out. Well, I mean, I don't know I thought it was gonna be like a Christopher Nolan type reboot
But it's kind of everything's like all CGI and stuff
I want to see it
I'll probably watch it to be honest. I was a big spider-man fan. I loved the first movie second one was good, too
I
Don't get away
Hopefully this time they do anything with venom even later on hopefully he's not like a total d-bag
anything like that
Venom I have a cool face and giant teeth, but I pull my mask back to talk
Thanks. Yeah, I didn't really like the way they handled venom either. It was kind of lackluster
I'm mad at you because you took my girlfriend or something. I don't remember what his deal was wasn't he also in
The only in the movie for like 25 minutes the actual that I'm like symbiotic monster thing
And the way he beats him he's like oh you got a humiliating guy like that
Why are you gonna be like don't you are a good guy spider-man?
You guys want to see my ruins. I'll give you a little look see
looksy-doo
So this is poise. I'm using poison dart and fire bats and I have it so it's just pretty much pure damage
So take a look poison dart. I have it so it's and the the fire one
So just doesn't more just straight-up damage every time you hit somebody that is leveled up apparently oh
I'm sorry
Then fire bats. I have the poison ones actually I got a new one. I have ferrets hmm
I'll stick with the poison ones for now. I think
Ferrets yeah, I got the gargantuan the one that goes crazy when there's more than a few people around
Yeah, I
Got oh yeah
Soul harvest because it is just too good to not have intelligence. Is it giving you now?
102 for every enemy affected so I get I can get a fire like 550 in intelligence if I get five people oh
It's a that's a lot mass confusion and then spirit walk mass confusion makes every than everyone hit themselves pretty much and
Spirit walk is just amazing because it makes you pretty much unkillable. You just go like this you go whew and you run around
Very very awesome
So do you have ferrets? I don't know I don't have ferrets on let me turn on my
There it's like this a little my GPU
fan a little higher
Yeah, okay
Just to make sure
All right, we're gonna go we're gonna find this. This is the spider lady isn't it oh?
Yeah
She's down away still we missed her we missed her all right if you were just here for the TF2 then take it easy man
Thanks for coming
me this gold my ferrets they pick up gold for me do they really the most yeah the most important skill in the
Game is pick up gold
That is a really important skill because you have to like go move over and run over and they increase gold fine
Just for being ferrets
Like I didn't know ferrets did that
But they're rolling in it
Rolling in those ferrets, so we went the wrong way
Diablo 3 that's the name of the game in d3 going the wrong way
It almost feels sometimes like
It generates the map as you go somewhere they go people he went this way. Let's generate it
So many little spider freaks oh god
Come on go ahead go get him gargantuan
So though we were talking about the gargantuan that this little buddy that I have for a pet
And we can't at the conclusion that this is what he's doing so I'll try and do the voice
I'll definitely get it through this fight
They're ready, so this is look at how like cutie is
So where are you just like right where's that?
That's the noise he's making when he runs
To be actually right I hit this guy. I help you
Out it hurts
I just feel like he's just a big dumb cute, but I'm gonna die there's an elite right here. It's okay
I'll hold you
Confusion
Let's get a rare
So yeah
I thought I had a really cool skill that what could rival your mass confusion because it knocks everything back for like 10 seconds
Really it doesn't work on rares
Really like all rares are immune to knock back. That's kind of BS
Yeah, I was kind of gonna. Go like all knock back demon hunter. There's Diablo 2 mm-hmm
I probably still am but it's just kind of sucks that rares are gonna be like there
Okay, you might you might get one
Back up a little bit
German can you make a shout out to edgyl like in the stream just say your name? What's up edgyl?
Eggle
And go waffles
Yes, oh
God, yes, please actually don't like waffles. I go. I know that's blasphemous. I know
Like Elgin waffles are better naturally I mean
I
You know waffles are just too um it's almost like too much. It's too doughy ready for me same thing with pancakes
I'm not a big pancake person either
Wow, I did not need to know that about you
I don't think anyone you just know that about you like everyone is leaving the stream right now
Because I said that
Well, what's the point of watching this if this guy doesn't even like pancakes I?
Thought we could like bond on some sort of human level, but apparently not
Thought we were gonna be friends
Why would I want to be friends with you now? I need help do I have any potions that I'm not using I?
Gotta run back to town real quick
You don't like pancakes unsubbed
No, I love pancakes come back. I resolved me joking
You know I the only pancakes I like are
Chocolate chip pancakes, that's it
Everything else I'm not a big fan of are you just like trying to run your name into the ground what chocolate chip pancakes are really good
What's wrong with that?
Chocolate chip pancakes this is a breakfast food. We were talking you want to put chocolate chips
Would you put like chocolate chips and scrambled eggs and be like ah good idea?
Yeah, but scrimp eggs are like eggs. They're not like
Pancakes are sweet
You know let me give you a rebuttal would you put cheese on your pancakes? I'm sure that wouldn't be that bad
I don't think so. I don't know about that
What does cheese go badly with?
Besides chocolate chips like a glass of chocolate milk if you like put easy cheese in it
Well besides anything chocolate
Well when does chocolate go bad you just made my point for me
I'm trying to say chocolate doesn't go with anything. What is he just eat chocolate chocolate?
Chocolate ice cream chocolate milkshake chocolate strawberries. Yeah, those are all but
the point is
I'm right. I just said I just had to go back to town again because I forgot I went here to buy potions and I didn't
chocolate chip pancakes
That's the best part about Diablo 3
Is what you time to consider the important parts of life
There we weren't talking about this from playing tf2, but now we're down to the root
Now we have a little it's a little more laid-back. We get some time to discuss things laid back
It's a little more laid-back. I would consider this more serious
This is so serious. It's Diablo here. I am clicking on things and you're in town clicking on things
This is the most serious thing I've ever done in my life. Well snake. Oh, well, whatever. I'm just gonna come meet you
Yeah, this is act 3 nightmare if you guys are wondering this is the car I don't have this character in hell
He's only 46. He's little
And you are I had I need to come up and find you. Yeah, I figured you'd spawn on me
Well, I don't assume that I'm that intelligent
Okay, sorry
I've never been to comic-con. I can't I want to go. It'd be really fun. Oh, there's an elite right there not cool
Yeah, that guy
Comic-con is really interesting because it's isn't comic-con not just like comics. It's like pretty much about everything isn't it?
Kind of a little bit everything they have a lot of movie stuff there too, and I don't know I could have gone once but I
Might go to
This one on in New York, right? New York and in Chicago. I probably go to the New York one
I can have the chance if I had like the money
That's the most important thing go into all these events. It costs money and that's just money that I don't have
My gargantuan I need more health. I only have like 11,000 or so
Somebody wants to know
If you're gonna, oh god treasure goblin really get him get him buy some blues
No, no, no, this is not good at all
Mass confusion get him there. Oh god. This is just chaos
He's dead. Oh, and he dropped a rare
gay nightmare rare
Oh run away run away run away
Totally there. I'm gonna jail you and then order you so what I was gonna say is
Somebody wants to know if you're gonna continue your let's play they want to know there because they want to see the whole story
They said oh of Diablo 3. Yeah, I was gonna upload one last night
Actually, I did upload one but apparently never finished rendering. So it was like a fourth of a video
That's the worst thing see this video the one that right when this is the stream is done
Once it gets uploaded to YouTube it is gonna take like two hours to process. It's just like yeah
Yeah, I wish there was a way. I did a full circle
We did but that's we need XP and we need items. Well, I want I didn't even identify that but well, this is a one-hander
ooh
There's no dexterity on it though, but this is actually pretty good
You know, hey, I have this thing that I found. It's a blue. So, you know, it's good
Go over here. Do you want to look at this? Is this thing better than what you have?
I know. I mean you could maybe use that. Let me see. Oh
Geez, it's not better. That thing is not better. I will sell it. Um
I'm gonna be losing
2,000 life if I put this on but I'm gonna gain a ton of damage damage always need damage
That's 2,000 health I'm gonna lose but you know what it's worth it to do almost a thousand more damage. Yeah, it's all blue
We'll do it. Yeah, we'll do it and temporarily. I'm just gonna put a
This gem into it. All right
Lost a bunch of health. So I'm gonna be an absolute wuss. I have pants too. Maybe you want pants pants
I don't need pants. What do I? Oh god way better than what I have again. I'm gonna be losing health. Oh
Well, I'm losing health who cares put this in there for now just to have it in there for now
Alright
What's that?
What's all this? What's what are you dropping? I want to look
Imagine if this is what Diablo 3 was where you just stand in place and items fall. What's this? We're not what's that?
What's this? What's this this magic in the air? What's this? What's this?
All right, 20 German points to whoever figures out what that song is from
You remember what you can buy
German points. I don't think anything to be honest, but you can still buy a salad
You can buy a German salad for 15 German don't sell a German. Give it to me. There's probably chocolate chips in the German salad
I don't know if people want it, you know, I can't believe that you uh, but you don't like chocolate chip pancakes
That's that's some that's unbelievable. I've never actually had them just because the thought of that is absolutely rare
this
disgusting
Chocolate, oh, it's an offhand. Hold on. I'm oh
man, oh man
Gosh gee golly, I can't I don't have time to look at that, but I think it's better
I'm a witch doctor. I am a witch doctor
Star is a demon hunter. We're two best friends in Diablo 3. I hunt demons except sometimes they help me
Make sense make sense
the bones I carry a bow and
Confusion mass confusion. Everyone start fighting each other. Oh
My god too much
Good thing you don't have that health. Good thing. I need it. I could need it. I could use it
I'll get the lead watch out. We got an elite and he's got that pole move and he slows you down. That's just fantastic
He did
He has all the things you drop any
Yeah, those of you that said nightmare before Christmas you are you are a winner you get my right?
I'm gonna I'm gonna put my hand up to the screen right now and it's a high five. Hey, come here
Hey punk
Where you go?
What's that?
Wait, where do you keep finding these things? I don't floor. How come I'm not finding these in
It's way better than what I have. Thank you
That didn't I just find so many items. I don't know what to do
No, where the there it is
1947 intellect it's way better. It is way a critical hit chance though
It's got two point five percent crit on it. This does not have it. But oh, hey, what's your amulet?
I'll inspect you. I'll inspect you this time. I'm gonna put this on
I'm gonna put a
Vitality gem in that cuz I can't I'm under 10k health right now. This is awful
Check out this amulet and tell me if you're like interested
And you could just have it anyway
All right, like say seriously you have just replaced like six pieces of my gear
Okay
The critical hit damage this this I have a rare on 30
What do you think 30% more crit damage or extra health and a little bit more damage?
How much are you creating with mass confusion?
Ten million. I think I'm gonna leave it on because I do pretty big crits with a poison dart
It's a treasure Google
What I recommend getting d3 compared to d2
I probably not there is this really good game
Called you know, I think this is a treasure goblin. Where is he? Why is all his money over here?
Why was that money right there? Where's this goblin? That was the goblin like
you go
Diablo 2 is
One of my favorite games ever made so I'm very very biased when it comes to comparing Diablo 2 and Diablo 3
But Diablo 2 I mean this game is awesome. Yeah, I'm playing it right now
I've dumped a ton of time into it. But if you were a huge fan of Diablo 2
Then it's if you saw I did a review on this game already it's on the channel, but
It's it's kind of a letdown in the item department at least as of right now
They're gonna apparently they're gonna maybe potentially look at legendaries because where it stands right now a legendary item can be potentially worse than a blue
Which is that's that just shouldn't be happening
But for the most part, I mean if you've never played a Diablo game
This is a perfect time to get into it because this game is just it's very streamlined. It's very fun
Addicting I say yes, go buy it go buy it if you've never if you've never played Diablo before and you want to then
Check it out for sure. It's awesome
Star oh god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god too many balloons
Oh my god, my friend my my gargantuan
He died
No, he almost did he grew
stabilizers
You need to have like when you go home with your witch doctor on the wall
You need to put notches on the wall for how higher gargantuan grows. Oh, I want to look at something real quick
Give me one second. Okay, I'll hide in corner with you. How far behind is the stream?
Like the street like I think this I think my 720 stream is like seven years behind
that happens
Let me take a look at this
Because that's like so people are still like just answering that nightmare before Christmas and that was like five minutes ago
So I want to see I want to see just how far back it is
Somebody said 15 seconds
Actually, you know the YouTube comment system is probably just bugged like it always is. I probably said that before
Yeah
Why am I why I'm watching an ad?
Adception right there ads on top of ads on top of ads
They're advertising an ad go watch this ad
Please go watch this ad on top of this ad on top of this ad go watch this ad
Let me see. Let me see. Go watch this ad on top of there's a goblin and you're
Go watch this ad my entrance too low for this
Yeah, I guess if you're behind on 720 then oh my darling. What am I dead from?
If you're behind on 720 then
I died. Oh
Is that my fault?
No, it's my fault
If you're behind on 720 refresh the page because that'll put that I'll kick that'll get you back in check
Because some people are like five to ten minutes behind
Why don't I have ad block on? Um, because I mean at least for YouTube. I like to support youtubers
Like at least people that run ads on their videos. So if like if I have a friend or something that has ads
I usually keep it on
Just because I like to be nice to them. I don't
Very good guy plus can't add block block other stuff. It's that kind of not supposed to I don't think so
What's the not supposed to block?
I don't know like I remember like hearing that some it's some places like it might think something is an ad when it's not
I don't think I've seen anything like that. Do you have that block? I do I turn it off sometimes though
Usually when I watch streams or whatever. Yeah, I
Assume that's what a lot of people do cuz man
I guess it can get really annoying like if you're just browsing websites and it's like oh take over your entire screen with an ad
I hate those
Like four pages to tell you that this is an ad yeah, the worst thing is open and tell you to watch the other page
Oh
that
Did I have for a second? I thought we just beat her but I was looking at the chat
Kill the daughters of pain
destroyed
Wait, did she really did die? Didn't she? No, no, that's that's like her like introduced myself thing, isn't it?
Oh, yeah, this is the one where she doesn't even fight you
She just like shows up and like hey and then you shoot her once and she says no she just introduces herself
Hi, I'm a spider
Yeah, somebody said ad blockers can mess up some for honestly for this part
I was playing through when I was doing with this character and I was thinking to myself that
you probably were supposed to beat her there and
There was probably supposed to be a different boss later and they just are like
No, yeah, baby. No, I will just let it blittered run away
Really feels like that
Feels like that with a lot of stuff in this game
But there are they're patching it. There's apparently a big patch
they're working on for this game and I don't they haven't said anything about it, but
Let's let's wait and see what it is. I hope it's $15
Dollars it was $15
I would literally a dump a brick like a brick would I would I would have to run to the bathroom because a brick would
Be coming out. I just imagined you taking a very long drive to a nearby dump taking a brick out of your car
Just flopping it somewhere
That is how mad you are going that far out of your way
So close now
children of the corn
No, you destroyed the heart. I'm so mad, but I'll keep haunting you
like my body their implications
Anyone would want to bang his spider
Spider so seductive good job confusing those two bugs
oh
Hey, I did my part
It's not like these things are giving me they like died before it even came out. I
Did my part say I should have used it right now, but it's not cool down because I'm stupid
No, yeah, and this would be a great time to use it because there's like a bunch of blue people. Oh, I see a yellow
I see yellow. I'm not gonna pick it up now cuz I want to kill stuff first
Then the server shut down. Oh, that would be terrible if it did. I'm already overburdened
Really you were just in town legs. Okay legs
these are
Very good for someone else. That is not me. Oh, I will hold on to them. Oh
Gotta make a town run. It's all about that money all about the paper. It's all about that
Diablo 3 money once I get a million gold. I'll be happy slowly getting open floors
I have five hundred seventy one thousand going to get in there look at some of this stuff
I got a lot of just crappy rares that I just need to sell it's gonna take too long in the auction house
Mmm, I'll save these for later. Maybe I will try and sell them
Yeah, I think my auction house actually like cleared and all of the items that were in the completed section are gone
No, the items that I was something are gone
Weird that shouldn't do that
Yeah, I shouldn't but
Mmm, I mean just I got a stash a lot of this stuff. I I need after we kill
Asmodan I need like a million minutes to like sip sort through all this stuff that I have
Okay, I hope people are ready for like the most exciting part of this stream
Jerma going through his items and figuring out what he's gonna sell. I
Would decide him. Okay now I got room in my backpack. I'm just gonna sell these I don't need them
Whatever I'll hold on for now just because you destroyed the sin heart
Potions are expensive in this game
Yes, I concur
Potions are very expensive. That's why I got ferrets
ferrets
My buddy's here
You know, I'm gonna check out that other ruin for fire bats
Check it out money money money. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get the money. All right
Get a good a good a good a good rapidly summoned bats that seek out nearby enemies for 280% weapon damage as fire
Oh my god, I'll try that right now
Don't even know there's a lot of damage. I would recommend that to anyone
Who likes damage? I'll stick with blow dart just cuz I love blow dart. Let me check this out. Let's see. Oh
It's okay. Cool
It's a lot less group. Not really a crowd move anymore
It's kind of a single-target move. No, I should go to whimsy shire. I
I'm not at that stage. I'm a noob. I'm not ready for the ponies. I'm not ready for it yet
What is Hodor?
Holdor? What's that?
I guess I can just kind of stand back and do this. It does a lot of damage
Blows through mana like crazy though. I don't know if I like it. I'll try it for a little while
I'm not picking up pages of jewel crafting only because I'm it's not something I plan on doing at least right now
Once I have a ton of money. Well, then even then you would use tomes. Yeah, I mean it's I'm in nightmare right now
So the pages of jewel crafting
Aren't gonna get me really anything. Why is my dude dead?
run away
Go get him back
The reason why I didn't stream yesterday is because I was having internet problems for some reason. I couldn't I couldn't get 720 to
To go go through and even 360 was being really really slow and choppy. So
Something was going on with the internet. I don't know why but
Doing an extra long one tonight today this morning
extra extra extra
Re-extree read all about it. You can help me if you like it. I
Felt like it then if you're just joining us if you just you just kind of jumped in this is stars here
The star
47 there we go. Level it up. Ooh new runes. What are they?
Spirit walk rune. I'm gonna check that out
Yep, this would be on the channel later
for show for sure
for sure
Find the time is it?
20 of 11 a.m. Oh
Yeah, it tells you the time in Diablo. Yeah, remember we were talking about that. It's like, oh how much time have we lost?
Oh, there it is. And my DX story always covered it, but actually it's on the left now
The sin hot get that waypoint bats bats everywhere
That money give me that money yo money you should
See I used it a good time that time didn't are you proud of it? I am there was
There was a lot of reasons to do that. I
Might have to take off that passive skill what makes all my mana stuff cost more money
I mean more mana. I'll make sure my mana cost more money
I don't know why that cost more mana for what it's
It's
All of your damage is increased by 20% but every spell cost 30% more mana
But that's so good. That's it's so much more damage than I wouldn't be doing
Squeaky chair wait wait, I'll probably be playing Diablo 3. I mean today you mean today
Probably after we kill
Aspidan once we get to the last part of this act
I might take a break, but if you meant long term I'll be playing this game for probably a very long time
I would say if it turns out after all the patches and all the bug fixes and
After the initial launch period then if it all stays well, and it's all good
I'll be playing this game for a very very very long time
Yeah, okay, you're here this game. I'm excel
That we still need to play
Most mxd most extreme elimination channel. Yes. Did you actually install a t2? I?
actually did not
But I could that'll take two seconds. It's only like a one gig file to be honest. Oh, did you download it? I?
Think I have it downloaded so it shouldn't take that long to do when you download it and install it. Don't open it
Oh do that okay? I think actually I think I still have I think I downloaded it on this computer a long time ago
I think it's just still sitting like the installation file is just still sitting on the computer somewhere
I'd like to ask you a very serious question right now, okay? What is with the dudes in the background?
What is your theory on why you can never see their feet?
They're having a party and
They're the pinatas these poor guys
I mean as man would certainly have a much higher chance of winning this whole war if you just like
If it is unchanged yeah, you know watch out for the disco ball one of them
You unchain one of those guys. He will take out an entire city. Yeah, I don't know maybe they they're not that good at fighting
So they're big good at what are they doing? Why are they here? Well? I mean look think of it this way
These guys are probably not that strong at this point. They've been kind of chained up with like stuff in their heads
Why I don't think they'd be that tough anymore if you released them. They probably just fall over and go all right
We even if they just fell over that'd be a pretty big fall
Take a fall in the right spot
Maybe all around and be like change my diaper
You don't want that in her I get there wherever you're so close now so close oh
Yeah
You destroyed the sin heart. I can't believe you how dare you?
Second important question. Yeah, why is there no elevator here?
Yeah, and you know what follow-up important question. How did asthma Dan get down here?
Like did he didn't come down these stairs?
He's too big
Was he just like born in the bottom, and it just never goes anywhere. He doesn't ever go out I
Guess like oh, let me like here's my house my big asthma Dan house. I'm like a
75 foot tall like 9 million pound monster
Let me walk down my spiral staircase when you can like astral project images of your heads
You can talk shit to people
Like when that's your thing. I don't imagine you're going out. Yeah, I probably just sit there and like call ex-girlfriend
You have no hope put the foot dive
Eat it bats eat bats
More bats stand in the middle. Oh
God oh god. Oh god. Yeah, I need I need a more crowd move. This is this big very single target
It's not sure I'm gonna stick with it, or I'm gonna change boys in dark something else
Maybe he uses teleportation. That is a good theory. That is a good theory
Maybe I mean
He is the lord of
Sin here. I was saying be here. Did you say beer? I said beer
Yeah, as my dad like he owns a micro brewery a
lord of beer
How dare you do oh god? I'm dead. I'm gonna die right now
How dare you insult the lord of beer?
well, oh and the fear of my delicious hops and
Yeast no, I thought he was fearing. That's why he was always
The world here be lord of sin getting off on that
He is a weird one
He does live with a spider lady. That's hell-bent on making us like love her but hate her at the same time
Why won't you bang me? This is his roommate by the way, you know that that's as you that's what you got to live with
I would go for like his wife or something
Maybe he just got drunk one night and woke up down there is what someone said she just won't leave like oh, yeah
Where am I? I'm so shit face right now. What is this place? I own it now. Oh
This is mine. Oh
This is mine
Why these giant tall guys are here, all right, this definitely gets comment of the stream
Damn it. I want to take a dump. Well, you guys talk louder so I can hear you from the crap. Oh
my god, oh
My goodness get her yeah, I can't even stun that that move only works on like actual enemies
unfortunate
All right, kill it before the teleport kill it before the teleport
Oh
No, I don't I don't I unless you're like a normal and one-shot or maybe we're getting it
Now blow up at one of asthma dance like four hearts, is he a cow or something?
He must be a cow don't know cows. Oh my god, I'm an idiot
Cows have multiple stomachs not multiple hearts. Oh, is he like a cow? He has like four hearts
Derp, oh look. Oh, come on. It's starting to make sense. What's what is it? This is one of those big guys chests
It's ripped open and the heart is placed over here
What what you see? That's why would they do such a thing and then the heart powers?
Duracell I
Don't get how the hearts power is well, how come then look at this guy?
How come this guy isn't like has a sin heart? Maybe he's not cool enough
I guess they're I guess they're like harvesting them. Okay, seriously seriously. Look at this
There is no way asthma Dan can fit down this staircase. Look at this. There's no way
Look at this. Look at look at up. Look at the height. I'm pointing at the screen right now, by the way
I don't know why the height of this ceiling look at this
Oh, I'm gonna go in my door like he wouldn't even be able to get in here
He just jumps down like he doesn't use the stairs. He just wrong bat and he rolls off the edge
Somebody asked how is this early morning?
I started this anymore. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I started the straight. I've been going for a couple hours at least a few hours
It was it was early morning
When I started I am here. So after this I'm probably gonna
Close the stream out for a little while. I might come back. I'm not sure though
Probably not because I want to get some food and my way I might go to the gym but get the way point
We're about to kill asthma then
This is on nightmare. So he might be a little tough
Yeah, okay, he might be super tough
Everyone's gonna be very disappointed when he dies
That's that's that's that's that's
I started to oh, let me use mass confusion ready. I'll do it. I'll use it. I started at
7 38 a.m. My time so it's been about three hours
Going on like three and a half. Maybe I never I never know until I'm done and I look at the file that goes up
to YouTube
But it'd probably be about three and a half four hours the whole thing I would assume. Oh
God, oh you live in Hong Kong. So what is like nighttime or something for you?
Well, you wait now you're behind. I don't even know time zones how you work
If you didn't get to see the TF 2 or you do well
You didn't get to see the beginning of the Diablo 3 stuff
It's all gonna be up in probably a couple hours. The whole thing will be on YouTube
mass confusion
Didn't even oh there we go. All right, I got that thing with charms kill him. You're on my team now
Oh, okay. Oh, I wasn't talking to you. Hey kill him. No, I'm not that much of a jerk. I just got a rare
Come on. Give me a good roll. Give me a good roll
No, I'll actually put the gem in there. No, I don't think so
Do I look good in this?
Does this make me look fat?
Oh
Where's my buddy? There he is. He always dies and I never like realize it. Yeah
if you just made like a compilation of
The noises I've made in this stream and just made a video of it
Like it would be like you probably pretty funny like yeah, what?
I make a whole lot of noises
Someone said go star. I love you. I'm going here. We are. All right, so this is it. So after this I'm gonna
Close out the stream and we will go from there and this will all be uploaded to YouTube
If we if we don't wipe like five times, which we will not star is a pro
Well, there is there's a guy that like lives in his like down here and that's it he can't move wiggles around jiggles
There he comes go get him gargantuan, you know what I want to do this and that bats
He's going down
very very easily
What does that bomb move you're doing? Oh my god
I almost got one shot what bomb moves the way it kind of looks like that looks like the assassin skill
Remember the first assassin skill you really got is do oh, yeah fire bombs. Yeah, kind of like that
I can't even like I really only use it to build hatred. I'm gonna die. Oh, you're dead. I'm dead
Stay alive star. Um, I'm okay. I got ferrets
Use those ferrets to kill this
Bat sloppy bastard. They're trying to keep up with me and they're like spazzing out so hard
There is no way you're gonna be able to come get me by the way
I'm like in this pool of not like this darkness pool. You're gonna die of even trying to revive me. I
Got you. Trust me. I could do it. I gotta do it just because you said I couldn't oh
Oh you did it I love you
Oh
These he spawns ads
It's a it's a MMO term give me a legendary give me a legendary no just give me a blue
Gotta be sweet. Oh, no, we gotta see the uh, the cutscene. Oh skip
No, I want us to know what happened. All right, here's what happened
So we just killed a big fat guy and he died. Yeah, and then she slams a rock into his soul
And then they all rock out. Oh
I've never been to Hong Kong. It's very far away. I've never even I don't think I've never been besides Canada
I've never been out of the country
You know, I was in Pennsylvania ones one time person furthest. I've been is probably Wisconsin from Minnesota
Whichever is further furthest I've been is Seattle Seattle, Washington
Just said you were in Canada. Well, I I've been to Canada. I don't live there
Whatever whatever well, I meant like out of the country. That's like the only that's like the furthest place out of the country
I've never never gone anywhere else
That's a lot of damage. It's too handed though. Hmm. I don't want to do this vent
I don't want to go on spoiler. Alright spoiler alert spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler
Except here we go. Spoiler experience. I don't know how many times I have to say that spoiler
Okay. All right
That's gonna be the end here guys. Oh
My god, what goodbye
Everyone I every time I try to end a YouTube stream like I like always forget how to do it
So let me like figure this out
Yeah, thank you all so much for watching sticking around
And goodbye to star say your buys
Thank you star for coming along and playing. I hope you all hate
Derma, I mean
Pancakes with chips. Hey chocolate chip pancakes are good. They're good. I'm hoping every comment is about that
Just telling you you're wrong. You're wrong. It would make my day
Event manager life control. There it is. Alright dudes take it easy everybody and take care of buddy pea soup
No, yeah, I'm still figuring out
I'm trying to edit