Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with one of the weirdest games I've ever played in my entire life.
This is Pac-Man 2 The New Adventures, and if you don't know what this game is, then you are in for a treat.
You're in for quite a surprise, mainly because of the game's gameplay. It doesn't make any sense at all.
I'm not gonna spoil it. You'll see it in just a second. Gonna go into the live commentary here,
and I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.
So, as you can probably imagine, this game is not Pac-Man. This has nothing to do with the old Pac-Mans.
This is, like, I have a baby, I have a wife, that's Ms. Pac-Man, I'm assuming.
We're out of milk and Pac-Baby's still hungry. Can you go get some more milk, please?
Sure, I guess why not? No problem. Welcome to Pac-Man 2 The New Adventures.
So, let me break down the controls real quickly here.
I move this cursor around, and I can either shoot a slingshot to, like, get his attention,
and make him stop moving. Like, for instance, that didn't work. He just got really happy.
Stop. No, no, no. Stop with me. Stop with me. Stop moving. I have to, like, do this.
Okay, you're safe now. So, you have to interact with the world around Pac-Man to...
What the fuck are you doing? You're supposed to go that way.
Pac-Man has the attention span of a goldfish in, like, the first grade.
Alright, so you're getting happy.
What was that face? No, go back. You're going the wrong way, stupid.
He just did this, like, I don't know, like, he did this crazy, like, old man, curled up litho.
I wouldn't even do that again. Go over and get the milk, you friggin' baby.
Oh, look, it's a chicken. Get the chicken. Shoot the chicken. Alright, get it.
I'm not exactly sure what the whole point of this game is, because it...
I'm sure it's becoming very evident right now, guys.
They thought Namco thought it was... Are you serious?
Did he just seriously walk into that? What an idiot.
Alright, just walk into something and let me have one of these.
No, go over here. Go to the hot dog man.
You pissy bitch, just go this way and look up. Talk to him.
Do you not see the hot dog man? Oh, oh, did you finally see him?
How do you not see this hot dog guy? Are you kidding me right now?
I just pissed him off.
What just made him so happy?
Why can I not just control him? Why didn't they make a platformer?
Why did they not make this game a platformer?
Why is it, like, a point and click, like, follow the moron around
and make him, like, look at stuff and get scared by, like, animals?
Nobody has any mail for Pac-Man?
I love that face so much. I love everything about that face.
Eat the apple. Eat it. You know, it's good. It's delicious.
All right, now sneak by this dog. Be careful. Look at the dog.
You just had an apple. You fucking idiot.
I just, I didn't tell you to do that.
Read the sign. He is so happy.
He doesn't even care that this could be, like, dangerous.
Grab that apple. Pick it up. What the fuck was that?
What the fuck are you doing?
Why did he just scream? What was the point?
What, what, who, who screams? Who screams for no reason?
Who, who, who screams?
Now he's depressed. Where are you going? Where is he going?
Oh, yeah, you should have looked out for that.
Yeah, you should have paid attention to your surroundings, you idiot.
Look, look, look, look, look. Don't trip. Don't trip.
You see it? Okay, step over it.
Yeah, it's a skateboard. Get on the skateboard.
Go have some fun for once in your life.
It's still telling me to get the milk.
All right, go get the milk. Go get the milk.
I need to do something. Go get the milk.
Go that, yes, yes, yes, yes, this way.
Sure, I know you're, I know you're upset.
I would be upset too if I tripped on a rock and screamed at a bird for, for seemingly absolutely no, my fucking God.
Pac-Man's very chaotic life is kind of like managing a sim.
When you have a sim that is unhappy, they don't go to work right, they don't perform well, they have bad...
Oh shit, hold on. Okay, I don't want to get in trouble by that.
But when you have a sim and they're not like at their peak happiness, you can't do anything with them.
They don't want to do anything. They're too tired. They're too hungry.
I at least have all my bars filled up on the happiness and energy meter.
So I should be able to do this now. Pick up the milk, please.
Stop whistling to yourself and pick the milk up.
Please, please pick up the, please just stand, stand, get underneath it.
There you go. Do you see it? Okay, you see it.
Here we go. Bang. It worked. I'm going to, I'm going to get the milk.
I know I pissed him off in the process, but it's okay. Just, just get your composure together.
Get yourself together Pac-Man and pick up the milk and go get the milk.
Watch out. Don't trip on the rock. Get off the skateboard.
Actually ride the skateboard. There we go.
I even told him to look too and he just didn't. I think he just has tunnel vision.
Are you going to actually listen to me this time? Look, look to the ground.
Stop. Why are you riding a skateboard with your eyes closed? What are you doing?
Who closes their eyes and rides a skateboard?
That's the dumbest thing I've ever fucking seen somebody do.
Hey, yeah, I'm going to get on a skateboard. Might as well close my eyes as tight as I can.
This is ridiculous. How am I supposed to make him not close his eyes?
Here he goes again, closing his eyes.
What if I shoot him? Will he like open his eyes?
Hey, there we go. All right. So to get him, yeah, yeah, thanks.
Does this honestly surprise you every time?
This can't surprise you every time it happens.
I wonder if he's going to stop and like look at the cow for the fourth, fifth fucking time in a row.
Hey, look, I love cows. Hey, let me stop and like look at the bird too.
He's like, I've never seen a bird before. Is there another bird in here?
Yes, birds. Oh, look, another bird. Isn't that wonderful?
Goal. Goal.
That's a nice walk you got there, Pac-Man. Nice high legged walk.
Oh, yes, you want a hot dog. Oh, yes, I love hot dogs.
You cat son of a bitch.
What are you doing? What does he do? What does he do?
Get the cat. No, no, no, no, no, don't get another one.
Don't get another one. He's going to spray you.
He's going to spray you with ketchup. Eat the pill and it'll make you feel better.
Oh, my God.