Does anyone dare to challenge me? Figures. What is that? Rips the hilt of my...
Hey, how you doing everybody? Welcome. Welcome to the stream. Oh, gamer has logged in. On time.
Wait, what? Why do people get... why do people... residents sleep during when I'm on time?
Is it because you like hanging out in the chat so much and you like chatting without me here?
I can... I understand that. You're 15 minutes early. No, no, no, no. I am 15 minutes now.
It is now. There is no late. Between 3 and 4 p.m. There is only now. If it was 4 p.m. 401,
that's late. If it was 259, that's early. 3 to 4. Now. There is only late. All right,
give me one second. I'm gonna make a tweet and we're gonna talk about some stuff. We're
gonna go and let a little stuff talk. Not very long. Maybe like five minutes. Not even. Not
even. All right. Okay, so I was talking with your mother last night and we have decided
that we're gonna bring this up in a respectful, nice way. We didn't want to, you know,
alarm you or anything, but your mother and I were cleaning up the house and we found
a bag of marijuana and I know it's not mine. It's not hers and we've already talked to
Jacob about this. So we're just coming to you in hopes that you can maybe
shed some light on what this is. I learned it from watching you. Well, the character...
Listen, and this is tough. I know that, you know, you're 14 and it's tough to understand,
but that's a character that I play on television. The character, it's not real. I'm an actor
and I play a character that's... Think of it like recess. When I go out and I do recess
with other people doing recess and it's filmed and then it's put out as if it was real.
You know, my stoner personality that I put on that show is not something you should be doing.
He's RPing with chat. Yeah, what the fuck am I doing? I am like, we're just like role playing.
But how are you? Hope you're doing well. What we were really going to talk about
is today. What's happening today? Look, this is what's happening today.
Gonna do Might and Magic again. We're dialing it up to a million. We are going to do an
8v8v, no holds barred, large map. I ain't fucking around today. I've already picked
who and the music's not even on. What kind of streamer am I? Drop the house lights, please.
Thank you. And bring it up a little bit. There it is. So today we're going to... I've
decided I'm going to be green again. You guys aren't even dancing to this music. All you
can do is put your hands in the air and like move them like this. I can't fucking turn
the webcam on. My hands are in the air with my... Okay, I'm going to describe it. My thumb and my
middle finger are together on both hands. They're both in the air and I'm... Okay,
almost like I'm making like a kick the field goal here with my arms. And my hands are
swaying back and forth. Wrist turn in towards head. Wrist turns out towards the outside.
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two. Make the music louder. Why would I do that?
I should be dropping it. But I don't care. So we're going to do this today.
I'm... This is the last stream for a little while. For at least a couple days. Probably
three days. Because I have colonoscopy coming up here in a couple days. I'm kind of
foodless at the moment. Like I can't really eat that much. I can't eat anything tomorrow.
I have to not eat for 24 hours before the procedure. And I can't really eat that much
today. So I might lose a little bit of energy here. And when that happens, I'm
going to have to leave. So I'm going to go as long as I can with like no real energy.
What procedure? Colonoscopy. Colonoscopy. Yes, I can drink coffee. That is a thing.
I can have chicken broth, coffee, jello. And I think I can have like just nothing really
heavy. No high fats. I can't have anything with seeds in it. With skin. No berries. No
strawberries. No beans. Nothing like that. But we're gonna, we're just gonna go. So please
excuse my low energy here. No, I'll be fine. I'm like, please excuse my low energy.
It's like going into like work and talk to your boss. Excuse my low energy today. I've
got a colonoscopy in a couple days. It'll be good. But yeah, that's happening. This is
the last stream for a few days. And then let's go. Let's just go. I decided to pick. I know
you guys are looking at this going, Hey, what the hell? How come you, what I wanted to pick.
You should have let me pick. But I felt like going with a fortress. They looked pretty good.
No lizard man, serpent fly, Gorgons, Wyverns, Hydras. I like this. And of course I had to pick
Voi. Because Voi looks the most like Otto. This kind of looks like Otto in the morning when
he puts his head under the blanket. Districts like Otto too when he has his head under the
blanket in a different angle. All right, so we're gonna do, we're gonna start with
Wyston. No, not this guy. You want to be this guy? That's just like Vincent Van Gogh.
What is he doing here? You have all these monsters and actually, well, there's, there's another
person here. But I mean, like, why is Vincent Van Gogh in the middle of like two Ottos,
like dragons? It's the Burger King. It's not, uh, now you've said the fucking Burger King.
It's like young Prince Burger King. It's Burger, it's a young, it's Prince Burger King. All
right. It's a Beastmaster. I don't know what that even means. Everybody else who cares?
This is on the map Warlords. I have no idea how this is gonna play out. We're gonna
stay on the same difficulty. We're not gonna, we'll do 130%. Just a little bit on the higher
scale, but that's okay. That's what we do. The only way to lose is to lose everything.
The only way to win is to kill everybody. Can you turn off taxes? Uh, I don't think
this scenario does that. Battle Royale. Yeah, I think I'm ready to go. Are you ready? Wait!
Lower the difficulty? No, it's, it's okay. It's okay where it is. I just made some
mistakes. One. Three. Oh my god, this is gonna take forever. This is a huge fucking map.
And there are eight, there are seven people here. I do have the corner though. I'm in the
best spot I think. I really believe that. This is an 11 hour Simpson stream incoming.
No. Oh fuck. All right, what do I got? I got five, I got 15,000. Let's do this right.
Look at this place. I've never seen this before. Like a little swamp. All right,
Citadel. Town Hall. We want to get this immediately. So, Town Hall will give us a
thousand gold day. We want to get it immediately. Prepare to backseat. Backseat gamers.
Let's get these gnolls and let's go out. Let's get it. Just look at it. I'm going
to play this as to the book as possible. If there was an encyclopedia on how to play this
game, I'm going to play it that way. I can't beat that guy. I'm just looking for a resource.
Lots of sprites. No. No resources right off the bat. There's a gate? Hold on, am I locked in my
own kingdom? Garrison. It's a garrison. Are you serious? I can leave people here?
This is unbelievably awesome. Wait, did I get a raid came in? Oh fuck, Jesus. I didn't even
see it. RT Gamecrowd came in with like a trillion people. Uh, thank you RT Gamecrowd
for the huge raid here. Welcome everybody. Hope you're having a good day. Hope your stream was
good. What were you playing? What was RT playing? And did they complete the game?
They're playing Nintendogs. How many dogs did he have? 50 dogs. All of them. Well, I hope
it was fun. Thank you so much for the raid. Welcome. A lot of you just came in. So,
we're playing. This is Heroes of Might and Magic and I'm going to win. I just started.
Get joined at a perfect fucking time. Let me tell you something. We've got the Burger King
Prince here. We've got our Gnolls here. I just started. I got a garrison here. What other things
can I point out that are just obvious if you're looking at the screen? I got a moat here.
Or a river. I've got a colon here. Got a colonoscopy here in a couple days.
That's what it's gonna look like. Let's go. But thanks again. Now he's doing- every time
a raid comes in, I gotta turn on like the YouTuber voice. Hey guys, welcome. Witch's Hut.
An ancient witch living in a strange hut welcomes you, teaching you pathfinding for her own
inscrutable purposes. That's actually really great. 25% less rough terrain penalty. I'll take
it. Of course I get a link to that. Do you guys just have that in a tab? How many of you
guys have that shit just in a tab waiting for like a reason to use it? Why have that just
ready to go in a tab? Lots of gargoyles. I can't beat them with these. All right,
swan pond. I need to see what's on the swan pond. But let's go back. We get gold a week here,
or every day. All right, we got the town hall. Citadel marketplace. I want a city hall.
So we need mage guild, marketplace, and a blacksmith. Of course we need the blacksmith.
So let's get that built. We're gonna go as fast as we can to get that 4,000 gold a day.
It's really important if you don't know what I'm talking about. When you get- when you
upgrade your city more than two or three times, you get to the maximum amount of
money. This is going to be the capital down here. You understand. All right, swan pond.
I got luck up. All right, don't be an idiot here. I don't want to be like a fucking idiot
here because the last time I spread the fuck out, mercenary camp. What's wrong with me?
That's all. I can only go that far. That's it. All right, well we need a marketplace
to get to the marketplace. While we have the wood, we're going to use it.
Okay, so should I go down or should I go up? Remember, there are seven other people here.
There are seven more fucking players. What do they- down? Up? I'm going to- the next
thing that somebody writes, I'm going to go down. Down, okay. Another colonoscopy here.
Log. Can I touch it? Pack of Cerberi. I don't think I want to fuck with that.
Finally, we get some treasure. I forget, at the beginning of the game, you can't move. You
move so slowly. All right, we can probably- now we can do- we need mage guild, and then we're
going to do upgrade that hall. I wasn't doing this. Remember last time, I was like, let's
make like a hundred gnolls. I'm gonna have four heroes. Always go with experience first.
Let's get that level up here. That treasure chest had advanced pathfinding and basic
ballistics. So this is a brewmaster? What do they do? A beast? What do they do?
What do they do? Specialty is Ballista. It increases the attack and defense skill of any
ballista for each level attained after fourth level, so I think we have to do ballistics.
Basic armor reduces all damage inflicted against the hero's troops by five percent.
Basic artillery gives control of the ballista to the hero. That's pretty awesome.
Uh, wait, don't I already have this though? You know what I mean? I like already have
this. Basic artillery, but- okay, but that's- okay. Yeah, let's do it. Oh, it's a catapult
versus ballista. I get it. All right. Nice. I have one for ballista, now I have one for
catapult. I have one for- yeah, they're different. Wait a minute, what are you doing F for?
What are you talking about? This is good shit. This is good shit! What are you talking
about? Let's look up here. All right, we got a crossroads. We got lots of dwarves,
and then a war machine factory. I'm gonna- well, this is just wrapping back the other way. Okay,
let's go back to town. There's not a whole lot of resources back here. There's this. I gotta
stock up enough. Let's get that, uh, let's get the city hall built. Now we got 2,000 gold a day,
and I think we're gonna do another hero now. I need a tavern for that though. We'll do
tavern next. I'm the king of the mud. War machine factory. Uh, there's no- none available.
I can't just- I could get this right now. This is the first day, 10th. I mean, I should just get
them. But I already have it. Well, I'll get these then. Might as well just fill the party up.
Yeah, okay. That's awesome. Nice. Sick. Fucking unbelievable. I'm doing so good.
Tavern. Is there a tavern here? Oh, there is a tavern. All right. Well, now I'm- oh,
that's another beastmaster. I don't want to do necromancer again. I did it last time,
and it didn't- I'm gonna do auto. Waking up in the morning under the blankets.
I don't want phant again. Phant sucked. No, I'm doing auto. What, if I don't hire him,
he's gonna end up on the other team somewhere? What are the chances to get phant again?
Yeah, he sucks. And plus, he's gonna ruin my whole thing here.
No, can I pay him a hundred bucks to, like, never come back? I'm going with, uh,
I'm going with auto. Resurrect is good. No, I don't want him. He was bad luck charm last
time. My level four hero sucks at fighting level 17. My name- no, he was, like, level 19.
No, he's gone. You know, he's not leaving. He's like, can I please come? I'll sit here and as
long as it takes. All right, let's get you on a different path here. Two beastmas- specialty
wyverns. Nice. Basic scouting. Easy to see. One extra square. Cool. Okay. I wonder if we
could take on the sprites. Who's my other guy down here? Let's look here. Is it an observatory?
Oh, now we can see. Hey, you're already coming down here? How does this guy have this much?
It's the first- it's the first week. That's not possible. Lizard den. I gotta build some of
these. He- I- he went all in on troops. What is this glyph of fear? Resource silo. All
right, I'm gonna get the lizard den out. Let's get some lizards. And you come on out.
Actually, no, you know, you can stay there. I don't- I- he's not gonna come over here.
That's, like, rough terrain. This is, uh, lots of dwarves. I don't- what is this? It's
like a lumber mill. Water wheel. 500 gold. That's not that good. All right, let's, uh,
let's go the next week. See what happens. He's fucking coming down here. Why is everybody
coming down here? Pack, pack, pack, few, several. He's already here. They're already encroaching
on my swamp. Serpent fly. Basilisk pit. So I need- I need- what do I need? A couple of wood.
This is a marketplace. I need- I need- I need some wood. Let's go. I have lots of ore.
What do I need? Three? No, no, ten to one. Come on. Oh, this is bad. Well, I got 16, 14.
I could- I could go up here and maybe make a trade here. I gotta go up into the garrison
because I don't have any more troops. I don't- I can't even buy them. Lots of sprites. I wonder
if I can just kill this and take this all. There's so much wood over here. I'm gonna try
it. I can do this. Oh, this is- I see. Sprite- I did- sprites are, like, the easiest
things. I didn't- I didn't know they were that weak. Well, I say that. All right,
we'll get this wood and I'll be able to get some more troops. All right, good. I lost
some gnolls, but it's okay. Oh my god, there's so much over here. Claim this. Ah, I'm so far
away. I can't- Look at all this stuff. He- He's gonna come down here and he's gonna kill me,
isn't he? I- I've got to go down. I'm gonna wrap around this way. Damn. I only have 24 gnolls.
I'm gonna hit the mercenary camp and I'm probably gonna die. The- The- Sneak King is
gonna die, like, today. Hope you guys are aware of this. It's a new week coming up.
Citadel Captain's Quarters. That's good. How many Captain's Quarters? It's just money.
We can do Citadel. Citadel is growth for everybody. Okay, let's just hope he doesn't
do anything. He's gonna- We're gonna fight and I'm gonna die. Say goodbye to the Sneak King.
No, he's just- Already has all this shit. I think I just lost. So it turns out being
down in the swamp was not good. Um, I- Not yet. What is the biggest threat here? 13 to 10. He
just has- No, it's- I- I lose. He actually bought units. Well, because last time when I did that,
it- It snowballed me into not being able to do anything. I tried to, like, upgrade the
capital first because I figured with a huge map, I wasn't gonna get attacked in the first
month. It's not over yet. 10, 20. Oh, it's definitely over. Ah, I wish I had anything.
End of the- End of the mudshire. I mean, hold on. Hold on, though. It's not over yet.
Come on! It's not over yet. It's not over yet. No. Holy shit, I might actually win. No,
I won't. No, there's too many. I forgot about this guy. Well, I tried just making
a bunch of monsters last time, and I- And nobody attacked me for six months. And then I went- Let
me try to get, like, money first. Let me, like, tech first. No, I'm attacked in the first, like,
two weeks. He's gonna take all this stuff. Oh my fucking god. He didn't get it all.
Come on, a second. I might really get revenge here. Where the hell am I going?
I can't afford it. Buy a hero- Yeah, buy a hero, stack with units, then send out.
That's what I did last time. It's not over yet. I'm- No, it's not over yet. Not yet.
Witch or cleric? Probably witch. I can get my revenge here.
Okay, it's not over. 35, 13, 4. I got him up here. He's got 24. There's nobody in this garrison.
He's gonna get this materials up down here. Yeah, I made it, okay. Now the question is,
can I get far enough where I can meet you up here? Oh, am I one fucking pixel away?
Come on. I can do it. Oh, no! Attack him? No, I can't. Not yet. I want those gnolls.
He took everything. Oh, it was a bad fucking start. Because he still has the-
All right, fucking get rid of him. Because he still has this shit. Like,
the- these guys- he has, like, more than I do. All right, it's time to win.
Magic arrow. We're gonna deal with you. Fly over here. He took all that stuff. Like,
what are you even doing down here? This is like- this map is huge. Last night,
we didn't see a monster. We didn't see another person for two to three straight months.
Bullshit. What's going on? Why am I- Oh, what? Okay, I can control them because of the-
I get it, right. I kind of have to go back. It's because it was water. All right,
that makes sense. I can't shoot anybody. You really don't like that tent, do you?
Bug on bug action. Is that an oof? All right, gnolls are gonna be so heavy this game. It's
not over yet. I just got kind of, like, fucked over in the beginning. It's okay. Don't
worry. We're gonna be fine. I'll get really good experience by doing this.
All the experience he just stole from me? I'm about to get it right back. Don't let
him run. I'm trying to get the gnoll up there. There he goes, dead. No running for you,
900 experience. All right, now I get the wood and I get the learning stone. Okay.
I- God damn it. I can't believe he came in immediately and just took all my shit.
I'm so irritated about that. Allows your hero to learn fourth level spells or eagle eye.
I'm so fucking, like, irritated. I wonder if it should be- probably wisdom. Give me this
back. One of you take it. All right, now everything's okay again. There is another
person that's over here. There is- okay, what do you got? We got lots of skeleton warriors.
There's a lot of stuff up there. Lou, what do you got? Oh, you got nothing. See,
like, why could I be over here where he is? He's got a pack of, like, rats and that's
it. Of course, the one dickhead that stacked minions, like, ran straight down.
All right, uh, let's go back to the castle. I got zero idea. Okay.
Uh, glyphs of fear, captain's quarters. Might as well just make it just because
get those extra gnolls and then next week I'm gonna get the fly den. What does it cost?
Serpent fly. I need five wood. I have the rest. I gotta work on wood. All right,
you don't have anybody. You gotta go back here and we're gonna claim this, too.
Lots of halberds. They're hard, though. Where are you right now? See, like, he has, like, a pack
several. Where's he going? Down the sanctuary? Okay, well, that's all done. I got that
claimed. You go in here. Okay, I can't do any of this. I need that wood. I'm gonna get,
what, one a day? Two a day? Don't have enough to do anything. I need 50 and 12. I
think I can go out with her. 50 gnolls is a lot of gnolls. I should be okay. In fact,
I wonder if the gnolls can take on the halberds. Holy shit, this nine, those nine wood. He missed
it. I thought he got everything. Oh, wow. Thank heavens. Serpent fly hive. And I should
do the gnoll hut. Upgrade the gnoll hut and get super gnolls. No, what do I do? Super,
no. I think I'm just going straight up with extra super gnolls and then I'm gonna transfer
them into super gnolls and then go up. All right, come back here. Oh my goodness. Everybody's
like all over the place now. I want these 50 gnolls to be super gnolls. Out of the way.
Bingo. Gnoll Marauders. What's the difference to you? Three, five, two to three, six.
Two to three, six, five. Two to three, six, four. A higher defense, higher attack skill. Yeah,
they're just better. Now, better lizards? What do you think? Should I just go straight up
better lizards? I wonder if I should do that right now. Yep. This is, this is good now. This
is really good. Lizard warriors, lizard men. Two to three. Okay, hold on. Five, six. They do
12 shots. Six, eight, 24, two to five, 15, 14. Better speed. All right. Looking good so far.
I think it's time to just, I'm gonna, I think I can take these, uh, Halliburters.
Maybe I should wait till next week and get a fully upgraded because you're,
he's just not doing shit in here, is he? I'm thinking of just waiting to next week,
get a good pack and then bring it up. The plan doesn't change here. You know what I mean?
I don't think I should change the plan. So capital needs castle. So I need 10 wood.
I need serpents. So I need five wood before the end of this week.
All right. Do you think, should I go after the Halliburters with my 50 gnolls and 12,
lizard warriors? Wait, just in case something fucking really bad happens.
I just, that just gets this shit out of me. Conquerors. I got this. It's gonna take me
forever to get here. Let's do haste. Bloodlust. Bloodlust on, uh, I think I'm gonna think
bloodlust on you. Bang. Nice. I don't want, nobody die. Nobody die. Three dead. You gotta
go twice. All right. Yes. And I get this right here too. Oh, I'm so fucking happy.
Knowledge plus one level three. Advanced first aid gives control of the first eight,
10 to the hero, healing 75 points of damage to the first unit of the selected stack
or basic water magic. 75 points of damage. I feel like I would want the water, but
that's it. 75 health is a lot. Look at all this. Nine ore, five ore, five ore.
There's so much over here. Beautiful. All right, I got another couple days before.
I need, uh, let's go in here. I need, what the fuck do I need? Five wood. What do I have now?
Two. Got a couple days left. All right, let's grab that. Six. Claim this. I couldn't touch it.
All that wood gone, but it did help a lot. Okay, so now I've got two a day over here
and it's all the way down in my swamp. Seems pretty good. All right, we're almost there. I
need one more wood, which will, I can get it tomorrow. That will bring me to serpents. Oh,
I should get this. One wooden one ore a day. That's amazing. Cage of warlords.
Shipyard. I can buy boats from here. All right, let's get that serpent flyhive next
and then I'll show, I have a good army and I'm going to go take them out.
One of my thoughts in the game so far is game is phenomenal. It's absolutely fantastic.
Okay, so let's bring you back. It's almost time for a new week.
Flyhive. Get it. I am now, I'm now available. Hold on. What about tomorrow? Growth is in coming
tomorrow. Flyhive. I can't do it. I can do it tomorrow. I can do superflies tomorrow. Next,
it's first week. Second week. Here we go. Superflies. Get it all. I'm going for it. Watch
this. And then this, this hero is going out. You leave for a moment. Do I have to back up?
Can we not both fit on the road? Oh, this is going to be awesome. All right, here we go.
Ready? I am ready to take a large army up. Upgrade the, or should I get basilisks right
now? Which one? Basilisks or better flies? Basilisks may be this strong. Am I not going
to have enough money to do this all? I don't know what to do. I'm going to go with the flies
because now they're superflies and I can get 20 of these. I don't have enough money. I can wait.
We'll do it tomorrow. I need to get money. Go get money. You just go buy stuff.
Who cares if this guy dies? Who cares? Scout, get out here. Go adventure. Go claim
something. You're giving me fucking diarrhea. Like go claim this. Oh, I could kill this guy.
I could kill this guy right now. Get this tomorrow. How are we doing? More. This is damn
good army. All right. I'm going to, I think I'm going to go with this. What do you think?
This is, this is a damn good army. 43, 12. This is damn good. I could kill this guy.
One more day and that's it. Last day. That's it. That's it. No more. No more.
I don't care what happens. Oh fuck. He's going to kill me. No, he's not. I'm going
to kill him right now. Right into my trap. Okay. Come on. Come on. What do I need? I could
do. Oh, God damn it. All right. I'm going up. I'm going up. I'm going up. I'm going up. I have a lot.
I can get rid of orange right now. I'm going in here. He's blocking the gate. He's going to
die, but it's okay. Look at this crew. This is a really good first month, second month crew.
He's scared. He ain't fucking going to handle this. I'm going to kill him. He's dead.
Let's start clearing shit. You can take the next stack of people. Where am I? Oh,
right here. All right. We're going this way. I've got a lot of good troops.
I'm going to head out towards the witch's hut here. I got basic pathfinding. Good
mercenary camp plus one attack. You're in big trouble and then I'm going to claim
this. We'll get the we'll get through this and I'm going to go down. I'm going to
grab this. There's a harpy loft over there. I've got a plan. I think it's a decent plan.
Let me get the basilisk thing opened and upgraded. Basilisk pit. Make it. There it is.
Four basilisks are available. We let them hang out. We don't have to do anything about this.
This is your team. Now you die. What about the dwarves? What is it? Lots of dwarves.
I can handle it. I want this sulfur pit. Oh yes. I did. Sometimes you just have to go
for it because they don't want to fight you. 35 dwarves. Now you actually are dead. You
can't be scared. Sometimes you just got to go for it. You ain't going to get out of here.
Head in here. Let's get you in the building. Get you some troops just in case something bad
happens. We've got four baskets on you now. What else can I buy here? Nothing. I've got no
money. Here we go. Really? Really? Time to die. In fact, I can just bring the serpent
straight in and just murder you. Let's go bloodlust on the serpents. The serpents are going right
for the jesters. Infecting everybody. I love it. Okay, let's move. You got to start moving
down here. I wonder who's my more priority. Probably the gargoyles because they can move
really fast. Get those dwarves up there. All right. Gargoyles. Dead. Let's go for the
golems. They're the most dangerous. Fine. Bring it up to the nose. That was a mistake. You
shouldn't have done that. He's gone. I didn't lose very much and I got a bunch of experience
and he's out of here. Let's claim this all. Back to the building. How are we doing? Okay.
Got more. What do we want to build? Glyphs of fear plus two to a garrison's hero defense
when defending. I can upgrade the pit next. I just need money. We're going to get the glyph
just to get it. All right. Here comes somebody else. Who is that? That is blue.
Several pack, few. You're dead. Oh, this feels good to be powerful. It feels good to have like
power. Lots of stone golems. I mean, we're going to meet you halfway here. You're in
trouble. Get out of my territory. I told you it wasn't over. No, it's not over. Restart,
restart. No, no. You got to push through sometimes. Blood obelisk. Cage of warlords.
Upgrade basilisk pit. Now we have greater basilisks. Six to ten and five. Six to ten
forty. And they're faster. Now the pit has eyes. Yeah, that's fucking weird.
Okay. Continue. Where are you going? You're going all the way down here. What are you
doing, man? Are you just like, are you just asking to die? All dwellings increase population.
I don't think I even need, I don't think I even have to go down there.
I'm coming out because guess what? I got nine basilisks and he's not going to take this.
Maybe I should just follow him down here. Yeah, let's, I'm, no, you're not taking
this all from me. Well, now you trapped yourself, but I'll take it back and I'm
going to block the road. Good luck. Pink is dead. Pink has been vanquished. There are seven who
remain. Same deal. Bloodlust on, bloodlust on the archers. And then we got here. Anybody,
I don't think Hayden has any ranged. I think I should probably go for the wolf riders.
Now bloodlust is melee. Fuck. It's only melee. Damn it. I'm going in for wolf riders. I'm
going to feel like killing in one hit. Yeah. I mean, you just, you don't stand any chance.
Why would you throw it at him? Yeah. You're more of an immediate threat.
Enemy ran away out of my territory and look where we are down here and I can go down here
and I can stock up again. I'm going to be fucking pretty damn unstoppable. Look at this.
Mm hmm. Pull him out. Actually, I can just trade them. So, hey, come here. You're going to have
13 more of these, 12 more of these, 33 more of these. And actually I'll give you one dwarf.
How does that sound? All right. Back in here. You and the one dwarf. Now that's an army.
Oh yeah. Give me the other stuff too. Give me like, give me like literally just,
I'm just going to strip you. Give me, uh, give me this shit. Give me this,
give me this. I already have one of those. You have any artifacts? Get back in here.
Good. Now it's time to go up and I now have basilisks. Good to go. This is a huge army.
Now I get to go wherever I please. I've already got this claimed. I'm going to go right.
Nobody is over here. Now I'm going to go down. I'm going to go down and go up. Let's
get rid of these gargoyles. Move on from here. Don't pursue. Let him run.
Sulfur. Plus two luck. And pond. A pack of Cerberi. Now that might not be something I want to do.
I wonder if it's something I should try. Don't engage. Now this is a harpy loft.
Yep. I just have more units. It's time to begin conquering. Wait, let's get back to the
castle. Let's get some more of these units just in case something fucking bad happens.
Lud obelisk, cage of warlords, wyvern nest, gorgon lair. Let's do gorgon lair. We'll get the growth,
double growth from gorgons. And remember, we're just, we're stashing here with this guy.
Until I get another castle, I am stashing. New week. All populations have doubled. Now
you're over here. What are you looking at? There's a blue over here somewhere.
Where's that blue guy? Right here? Okay, you really, what do you got?
Pack. You. Lots. Bored. Lots. Pretty dangerous. But I'll be okay.
Let's head up this way. Make sure to go down. Let's go through the stone golems.
Don't pursue. Let him run. Cliff nest. The cliff nest is guarded by several rocks. Do you
wish to fight the guards? Rocks. Is it, am I gonna get griffins? All right, this is,
all right, hold on here. Um, magic arrow. Haste. Bloodlust on, bloodlust on the dragonflies.
Just get him in. Or haste on the dragonflies. Wait for him to come to you. Um, I think he
can make it across the whole thing, can he? Or haste on the archers. That's not a bad idea.
Haste on archers. So maybe I should just wait, because I think he can fly all the way
across. Yeah, I'll wait. I'm gonna put the basilisks. They have 60 health each.
I'm putting basilisk in front of archers. Block archers. Get the dwarves in front of
the archers. Just make it try to get, no, no, don't, don't do that much. Should I just
put every hex? Here we go, look at this. Here he comes! All right, he still has to come to us.
Uh, haste the archers again, but bloodlust, I'm bloodlust on the, uh, on the gargoyles.
And then I'm going in. Wait, don't haste the archers. Increase the speed of the selected
unit. Everybody, people were telling me that was a good idea. Was that not a good idea?
Haste is just movement. Oh, was I getting baited? Everyone was like, haste the archers,
haste the archers. Speed is just movement time. Then I thought maybe it was turns as
well. All right, I'm going to bloodlust on the basilisk. And where, we're going in. Get in there.
Over the gnolls. Basilisk, bloodlust. Bang. He's only got one more. One more hit. Nice. I lost
it a little bit, but not, that was, that was. Okay, here we go. Expert first aid. A hundred
points of damage to the first unit of the selected stack. Or should I get earth magic?
Yeah, first aid, unless you have, here's how first aid is good. Because remember, it's to the first
unit of the stack. So if you have, let's say, for instance, like a dragon or something,
something that has more than a hundred health, you know, if a dragon has 150 health, then
right, you just do that. But I don't have anything like that yet. Let's do earth magic.
This is a pretty stacked party right now. It just is. So, I mean, I could meet you here.
This would be a fight, but he wouldn't take the castle. I'd probably win. Where do I go down?
I don't have, I used all that money. I don't have any more money to do this.
I can't really do it yet. I wonder, I don't know if he's gonna come down. Okay, if he
comes down here, then I start to change my strategy. Because I don't think he even knows
this exists down here. Should I pull back and go on defense? Well, we'll have to find out.
We'll see what he does this week. There he goes. Okay. He's not coming down here.
Up or down? I'm gonna say down. Nothing in here. Okay. Let's take it slow here.
How do I get in there? I think I can get in there from here. Look at this down here.
There's like a little slot down there. Go back. Let's check on, I'm just gonna,
I'm building, you know, I'm just gonna build, upgrade the Gorgon lair.
And then now look at this. I can get upgraded Gorgons. What do they turn into?
Are they throwing up? Why is he puking? Why is he just throwing up? 10, 14, 12 to 16,
12 to 16. Same damage, same health, but higher defense and a little bit faster.
Can move further. When I get the money, I felt like somebody was just going to just drive into
the house. Like I really felt like somebody was going into the window. Like I thought
that was somebody in a little drone flying and crashing into my window. That just scared
the shit out of me. That was in the house. Yeah. That sounded fake. Somebody's in a pod racer out
here. That was a Star Wars fucking pod racer. That wasn't even a car. Yeah, it really was.
Just waiting for the guy to yell out outside his fucking car.
Oh no. All right. Stick to the plan. I'm going back this way. I need to get this
so much treasure under there. I'm taking a risk and see if it pays off. Any more of these? Let's
check. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me just get this. Are there any more in here?
No, I didn't know if it maybe this. I don't know. Go down. Come on. Come on. Make this
worth it. Make it worth it. The hat. It's got to be like a little path down here. Make
it worth it. Please. There is, but there's like fucking magma elementals. I don't think
I can go through here. Should I do this? There's a lot of treasure over here.
Somebody's coming. Pack lots, few, several, several. This'll be a fight. But what if they,
but what if they're, they want to join us? Um, okay. But, but what do I do? I have too
many people. Harpies? Harpies are out of here. Trade Harpies for magma elementals.
I spent like a thousand bucks on these though. Six to ten. Holy fuck. Oh yeah.
What about the Dwarves? The Dwarves are kind of terrible though. They haven't done anything.
They just stood around. They just watched the fight. Six. So seven and eight. Six and five.
Now they're better. Yeah, there's a lot of them. Yeah. Okay. That's it. That's,
holy shit, man. Sometimes you got to go for it. And now I got a ton of stuff down here. 500
gold. I'm thinking I buy, I'm, I'm thinking to take the money because then I can buy every
unit. Someone's coming down here. It's always experience. Yeah. Level five. Expert. Wisdom.
Basic navigation. Chris, you're here as movement points at C by 50% or fifth level spells. But I
don't have a mage tower. And then we get to go this way. Look at this little fucking secret.
I'm gonna head back here. Upgrade these guys. How much can I pull out? A pretty substantial
amount of people. There's still one dwarf here. I mean, this is a decent army. What the hell is
that? I tried to click it. He's taking my shit. Dragon wing tavern. This item increases
your knowledge and power skills by plus two. This guy scares me. He's coming. He's wrapping
around. It might be time to, but I want to go over here and see what I want to get all
this stuff. Look at all this stuff. I can go back and just stack and have so many.
Should I, but, but he's gonna come down here and take all this stuff.
The stuff's not gonna go anywhere. But I have to go all the way around. He's gonna get there
before I do. Lots of griffins blocking the way here. I'm going for greed. I'm going for
greed. I am. I'm sorry, guys. I got plenty of growth. Holy shit. Pack of dragonflies.
You want to join me? I'll let you. You can join me if you want.
Odd by the power of your forces begin to scatter.
Water elemental conflux? Uh, oh, these things are so good, but I don't have enough room.
Look at all this. It's so wonderful. This is so much. Lots of, okay, this royal griffins
guarding. This like mini boss and then actual boss. So I gotta be careful down here.
Delete the dwarves. Delete the dwarves. Just get another hero. All right, I'm gonna get another
hero and I'm gonna walk up over here. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm getting a
little overwhelmed. I'm not gonna lie. I'm getting kind of overwhelmed. Um, what, hold on. I need
a capital. I need a castle. I need 5,000 gold. Let me just get to, hold on. I'm overwhelming
myself. I need the money. I need the, I'm so, look at how much I have. 100 fucking ore,
30. I'm so stacked on resources this game, but I don't have any money.
Let me just fill it up. All right, he's not coming this way. He's not coming this way.
Oh, look at all this stuff. Always experience or should I take the money?
Free. XP is priceless. I know it is. Money. Money for the army. I'm getting greedy.
Basic sorcery. Expert first aid. Level six. And there's all this up here. I wonder if I can
take some of this. Five percent more damage. I'll take it. Nothing else this way. I got
mercenary camp plus one attack. Head back here. What do we got? Castle. I need 5,000 gold.
Get plenty of units stacked up. I'm gonna save. I'm not gonna spend any money.
We're good. Now here's the thing. A pack of pit lords. I can definitely take them.
There's only a pack and it's a fucking gold mine behind them. They're dangerous. They have a lot
of health. They have a lot of damage. They do not have any ranged. I'm thinking just magic
arrow. Protection from fire. That makes no... I think I'm just gonna have to zap.
Okay. Don't go anywhere. They're probably slow. What's their speed? Seven. They can go far.
I think they can fly. Just hold back. Hold back. I just want to say I need to see.
I've got my own like shitty version of them. I have my like bargain bin knockoff version
of these guys. Nobody move. Nobody do anything stupid. Send the dwarves in. Fuck them. They
got whips. All right. Now I've got an opportunity to dwarf. Bloodlust the dwarves or just zap them.
Just get rid of the stack up here. I think I'm gonna zap and just continue to fight.
Give the dwarves haste. Now zap. Let's take it down four. That's perfect. All right. I think
it's time to go in. No. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Don't go in. Not you. No. He can
make it. I didn't think he could make it all the way. All right. We gotta... It's time to go.
Kill him. Dead. Stay here. What the fuck did he just do? Why is he... What did he turn into?
He turned into like a... He re-transformed or something? All right. Dwarves. I can't get up
there. They're gonna have... They'll kill it eventually. What does it do? Can I see the
stats? It's just a kind of a shittier version. That's okay. Summon demons from dead ally.
But... Oh, he's doing it. So he's casting it on that dead body. Okay. So he needs to die.
Like now. Send in the fucking dwarves. Fast lift to get in. If I kill this, will he revive it?
Or can he only... How many times can he do that? Good. Okay. I'm gonna give bloodlust
to the dwarves. They're gonna show their worth. Keep the... Actually, he's blocked it right
now. I'm not gonna stay where I am. Everybody else is gonna have to move. It's gonna... You
have to do the bath list. You just have to kill. Go on, dwarves. Nice. Surround him. Nice.
One more. You got to go twice. Kill him. Thousand experience. I had some blouses,
but it's okay. We have a gold mine now. This is a thousand gold a day. And I get
plus one attack. It was a little sloppy, but it's all right. Now I wonder. A lot of centaur
captains. I probably can get in. I can probably do this too. We can replace the gnolls with the
elementals. Either that or we stack. Okay. Let's do what I was gonna do. Castle
and then capital. Capital's next. Maybe I should... I think it's time to maybe head back
because I don't know if it's gonna be possible for me to do this.
Lots of captains and lots of griffins, but I mean... Can I get that wood here? I don't
think I can get through this. I'm not sure. The royal griffin. Lots of royal griffins.
I mean, this could just be like... I got plenty of stuff. Hold on. We're gonna just do this.
I'm gonna trade the gnolls for the elementals because, I mean,
they're not doing anything for me right now. What's worse? 27 dwarves or 15 gnolls?
6-7 defense. 8-8. 2-4. 2-3. 20 health. No, these things suck.
Yeah. We're gonna replace. We're gonna get six water elementals. 3-7. These things aren't that
much better though. They actually aren't very good. It's not worth 1,800 bucks.
No, it's not worth it. It's not worth it. I can stack the gnolls. Yeah, that's true.
I saved it right before that, right? Like, I saved it literally right before making that
turn, right? Because that's a waste of a turn. I did, right? Yeah. I mean, that was just a waste.
Okay. Here we go. I already got the plus attack. Let's see if I can get through here.
Do not engage. Yes! I get the two wood a day. Should I go for the... Look at this. Should I
go for it? Should I go for it? I'm going for it. Oh, man. 14. They're not scary at all.
I thought they... Royal Griffins. All right. I thought they were going to be insane.
Please. This is gonna be easy. I was scared for nothing. All right. I'm gonna give...
I'm gonna give bloodlust to the basilisks or the... Maybe the magma elementals.
No, the basilisks. Or the brux. Check out their abilities. Unlimited retaliations.
So that means that they will attack back every single time. Haste the archer. Yeah. All right.
I'm gonna defend. I'm gonna bloodlust. I'm gonna haste the dwarves, right? And just send them
out there. Fuck them. Haste the dwarves? Just get them out there? Yeah. You defend.
Basilisks, I'm gonna stick them right here. They're not gonna move because I think they
have to go. And the magma... Get the magma out there too. Yeah. Step it out a little bit.
You stay. Gnolls don't move. Let's shoot down. Let's shoot at you. See, they can't make it.
Now I'll have... Wait, why could you do that? These things suck. Just kill them. Why won't
they do anything? Why are the dwarves freezing in panic? I just hasted them. They have low
morale. Well, I did pretty good. And then we get all this stuff. And I might have to wait
till another turn. Yes. Look at all this. Artifact. Boots of speed. Gold. Oak trees.
What are... Oh, no. That's just oak trees. Okay. Never mind. I thought it was wood. Okay.
Things looking up. 15. Look at all this money. I think I'm gonna be really greedy.
I don't think I'm just gonna take like 20 grand. No, play long, long game. Long game.
Long game. Basic scouting or advanced earth magic. Yeah. I said that in like a YouTube
voice, but I know I did, but I don't care. I'm excited about that. One on the finger.
This item increases your luck and morale by plus one. Maybe the dwarves will actually
fucking move now. Six mercury. Six gems. 700 gold. And boots of speed. One on feet.
These boots increase a hero's movement rate over land. That's amazing. Finally. Did I
miss anything? I got everything, right? I think that's good. I think I've cleaned it up.
All right. Nobody in the area. I can come back and claim some stuff. And then...
Yeah, this is looking good. This is looking good. How much money do I got? Stack it up.
I need 10,000 for the capital. What are we? Day five? Let me get the wyvern nest.
Take over the other cities. Yeah. I mean, I'll be able to. What do you got? Few, few,
few. Dude, I think I'm gonna... Here's my plan. I've already... I did like the magical,
like hidden secret area. I'm gonna get out of here. I'm gonna go back to the house.
I'm gonna stack and have like a hundred of all these. And then this person's gonna be the
conqueror. And I did just get those boots, so let's see how well they work. That's pretty
good. I mean, that's pretty good. I'm going a lot further, I think. Is that just placebo
effect or what? I forgot the oak. Oh, whatever. Okay, whatever. I need to turn
this into a capital. Let's do... I could do... No, I could upgrade the wyvern nest for the
next week. Yes. Wyvern monarchs. 70, 18, 22. That is much better. I'll have plenty of time to do
other stuff because it's gonna take another couple days for me to get back here so I can
do like the mage guild. Lots of griffins. Get the fuck out of my way. All right, let's go
back. I can do mage guild level two. It's a bunch of resources. I can learn new spells.
And let's recruit. All right, now I'm going to save money. By the time I get back there,
I want to have to be a capital. Purple's dead. Purple's heroes have abandoned him.
He is banished from the land. There are now six that remain. Bye purple. It was really nice
knowing you. Oh boy, that's a lot. 50. That's 50 griffins. Oh fuck. All right,
send in the dwarves. Send in the dwarves. Hide everybody except the dwarves. All right,
where do you want me? Walk straight ahead into the 50 griffins. Do you think that's wise? No,
not at all. Oh, what's this? Nice! And bloodlust and haste. Everybody else chill.
We're all just watching. Is he going to do it? Move it. I'm coming through. Death comes for you.
Everybody stay. Just support the dwarves. Bloodlust. He's got extra luck. They're dead.
It's okay. It's all right. They got rid of seven. Not very lucky. Six dwarves die. Oh,
hmm. I gotta send the magma guys in. A new hero approaches. What? Why do I have to do this?
Because you don't come from our castle. What? What does that mean? It means I can't make any
of you, so I have to fill my stacks with people that I have in my castle. But do you
see how strong I've been for you? Have you even seen what I've done for you?
Well, prove it. Show me. You're an idiot. You let him go by. You let him go by. You shouldn't
have let him do that. You've killed everybody. Come on. Show why. Now everyone's going to fight
now. Nope. Run away. Send the dolls in. Block the path. Lucky shot. Good.
What do I do? I'm not doing that. Purple's dead. I'm going a long way. I'm not losing
all my... I'm not losing all my basilisks to 50 griffins. Wait, purple died this time. No,
you're not purple. Yeah, purple died. Plus I can reclaim this stuff. Yeah, no, I'm going a long
way. Wait! Harpies. So much for not save scumming. Yeah, but sometimes you have to.
I'm playing a win. I'm playing a win. See, we still have one dwarf. Six thousand. I can
do the citadel capital coming up real soon. Don't buy anything. I've got a mercury
factory that I'm going to reclaim. Cliff nest. Get the rocks. No, what? What are you talking
about? I already cleared it out. Did they already like me? 10,000 not yet. Tan came in here.
Well, whatever. I don't really want... I don't really want the rocks. I'll give you a very
specific reason why. They're good, but they're kind of just gonna take up space
and the dwarves and the rocks, they're good, but they're gonna just take up space and I need
more of my own units. Did I already go here? Holy shit. Yep. Okay. Everything's good. Now
we're just gonna make our way back down home. 10,000. I can now do the citadel and things
are looking good. Capital building 4,000 fucking gold every single day until our last day.
I can put them in the garrison. That's not a bad idea. We're gonna, this is what we're gonna do.
Yeah, we're gonna dump. Let's touch the rally flag first. What's over here? That's a lot
of griffins to be guarding something over here for no reason. What is this? Odd. All right,
let's get the rocks, the dwarves, and the magma men in the garrison or keep the magma men.
That's good. Let us recruit. I got 6,000 gold. More hiring. What you gonna do?
Wait two. That's because I'm trying to get these like out of the monarchs, right?
Okay, we'll do it next week. Get you guys upgraded to the better ones. I want to see
where is that nest. 70 health. 70 health. This is 14, 14, 14 to 18, 14, 14, 18 to 22,
and faster. Nice. Okay. You head out of here with one dwarf, please. You're gonna transfer
this dwarf. You're gonna go sit in the garrison. I'm gonna get another hero.
You thought this place is called mud shit? No. It's not called mud shit. All right.
We're back. Now we're gonna restock. Pretty damn good. All right. I need more gnolls. I got
lots of money. I'm gonna send you up to the garrison. Are these bulls? These bulls are
upgraded. Mighty Gorgons, yeah. They're not upgraded? I thought they were. No, I didn't.
Hydropond is the next thing coming up. Or mage guild level up. I think mage guild.
Yeah, they're leveled up already. You hang out in here for a minute. You get in the
garrison. Can I not put you up here? I guess he can't go in the garrison. Okay. Well,
I kind of need to send him out to do stuff. He's gonna go explore up here while I get this
hero ready to go. We went down last time. I'm gonna go up. I'm gonna go this way.
He's just a scout at this point. One dwarf scout army. That's probably a really stupid
idea, but you know, I'm going for it. What's the worst that's gonna happen? He's
gonna die. He's a level two. Okay, we need some more. Got more bulls. I just need more cash. I
need more money. I gotta get in that guy. I gotta conquer. You're coming down here. What's
this look like here? Several pack and then lots. Several. What is that? This is Jabarcas.
Yeah, go explore. Go explore. Get us some resources. Get us some money. I can get 27 of
these. More of these. Good. 73 lizard warriors. I might even split these up.
I think here's what's... hear me out on this. Get to a hundred lizard warriors
and get a new hero that is just a, you know, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15. Just have all
archers. Like 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15. And then send them out. Why? To lay the
smack down. I don't know. You suck at this. I'm doing pretty well right now. I couldn't...
people came to... okay, he made it over there. He had to have lost shit for that, right? He
took out three staxi griffins. He's probably weak. Nah, stick with the scout. What is this?
Warren? Something down here maybe? I got 5,000. That's a new weak. I just... I can get more
fucking gorgons. God damn it. I have so many of these. All right. I think it's time to,
I think it's time to take, take her out again. Although the next thing I'm going to do a bunch
of gnolls. Or should I just stack her to be unbeatable? She will be un... okay, let me
see what you lost by doing that. Guys, guys, those griffins joined him. If I had just
walked over there, I would have probably had like a hundred griffins. Damn it. That sucks.
That really sucks. Would you like to... sure. 14. All right. Ogre fort. What was anything down
here? I wonder if it... is it worth checking to see if there's something like on the edge here?
Just gonna check. Nothing. I could still kill him. Should I just go after him right now with
this army? One more day. One more day. Recruit everybody. I don't have enough money. Let him
at least go through the garrison first. Yeah, that's true. There he goes. 31. They're not that good.
Okay, 31. Holy, he's got... what the fuck? He's got six cyclops. This is actually a good indicator
to see what he's got. He's got six cyclops. Oh man. He's got five behemoths. This is what
throws us over the edge. Bad. Very badly. If only I had like tried to pursue that,
I would have had these griffins. And that changes everything.
Uh, I mean, I'm just gonna fly around and just have him come to us. Maybe I could take out
somebody? No. It's impossible. I'm not gonna be able to kill one person.
Yeah, this game will... I can't even attack. I killed six of their riders.
And now he didn't even want to come down. He's coming down. Well, it's gonna be a fight.
It's gonna be a fight. Give me some more archers. 87 archers. He might not come all the way down.
This ogre hut right here. Let me just go up this way. Claim that. I have that claimed,
that claimed. Blue is up here. I don't think I can do anything with this.
All right, let's see what happens here. No. He just took... all right, he turned.
Open field? I don't know if that's a good idea. More archers. A hundred. They have a hundred
fucking archers. Let's see. Let me take a look at the garrison. He left his riders in the
garrison. But he's got such power units. He's got such heavy units. He's gonna have to come
to me. I'm not gonna risk it. Can I claim this and take ogres? I can. I'll do that next
turn. It's like this guy can have at least something. This is like the battle. Here it
comes. Here we go. Here we go. Minimal casualties. But did she not learn the spells?
Didn't upgrade it to level two or three? I'm just going with... who's the most dangerous
here? Somebody can fly over. I'm thinking of... this is range. The cyclops has to go.
These two... that'll be a fight. Five cyclops. Gotta go for it. Four. All right, grab the bat.
Don't move. There's no reason to go out there. Just have to defend. Are you ranged? I mean,
do I just dive out? Okay. These are pretty beefy. 70 health, 1822. I mean, I could
probably kill a... stay just to defend. All right. The ball... what are the... what's the
ball stats? Pretty beefy. I could... to stay... hold the line. Oh! You can do that?
Since when can you do that? That was... fuck yeah. I got to do it twice. I got the once
again. All right. Now who do I buff with this? I'm buff... should I buff the archers? I think you
have to. They're the only ones that can do anything. It's defense. I don't want anyone
to die. They're the only ones that can do anything. All right. Now we've got the healing
tent. Who got the axe thrown in their face? You did. They're getting in line here. They're
not... I might not lose like very many at all. Magic arrow and we'll go for... they're just in a
line. This is like a diner dash. We're going for the front of the line. Catapult. Oh my god.
Buff, buff, buff. They're trying to get in. Oh, crash. Nobody move. Don't ever... nobody
fucking move. Oh, he's in. It's okay. He's in. He's poisoned. Get in there. Get up there. Smash
him. Right in front of you. And extra lucky. Oh my god, dude. I can't... I didn't lose anybody.
I'm gonna get so much experience. I lost like five people. Don't anybody move. It's too
dangerous. Get the fuck out of here. He lost everything. He lost all his shit. Everybody.
Blue is now in a lot of trouble. That was like their biggest units. Advanced sorcerer.
Basic intelligence. Maximum spell points or expert earth magic. Gone. Now we do this thing called
I want my mage tower to be higher. Mage build level two. Weakness. Disrupting ray. Ice bolt.
Quicksand. All right, good. We're gonna do it again tomorrow. Let's go get our shit. What did he
take? He only took the ore, huh? Nothing else claimed by him except up here. The 100 archers
is very strong. Yeah, it's very good. Uh, I mean, this garrison is just dumb. I don't really
care. I'll just get it back later. Continue the exploration. Actually, no, I'm one of the
ogres, right? Well, let's just, is there something I can claim like up here? We can go up this way.
Mage tower. Magic plains. Yeah, I'm just gonna wait. Here comes Tan. Oh, fine. You don't. Wait.
Burger Prince is dead. Is Burger Prince out? Burger Prince doesn't have anything.
I think we just retreat here. There's no reason to have anybody do this. One dwarf and 14
trolls. That's it. See you later. The cowardly jerel flees from battle.
It doesn't matter. Mage tower. Level three. Let's take a look. Earthquake randomly damages
two sections of castle wall in combat. Half the selected enemy unit forgets to use its
ranged attack and fireball burst into flames fire damage to the target and adjacent units.
All right. It is time to take you out. I now have a very, very good formidable offense.
Well, maybe I should do one more day. Yeah, well, next week. One week. Two more days.
Two more days. That's it. Just two more days. All right. Did that. Two more days.
God damn it, man. And that will get me another tower in the, in the, no, I got
a level three cage of warlords defense and strength plus two to a garrison. No, just save
hydra pond. I could get hydras. Oh, that can be on another hero though. I got to get out.
I got to get moving. I've got to get out here. What did tan hold on to tan just like,
I can kill them right now. It's time to go. I can do it right now. Give me more height.
Give me more of these. I got to get somebody out there. Look at this. This army is fucking
insane. 35, like 20, 30 bulls, 116 archers. Like, I just, I got to get, I got to start
conquering. This is good because then another hero can start stacking. I got all the spells
learned, right? Do I have the spells learned? No, I do. Okay. Come on. Sell, sell the ore.
But I, it's, I need it. It's only 25. How much are dragonflies for one? Oh god, he like two
grand. Oh, that's so many. Come on. What else can I do? A little bit. No, no, that's it. That's
it. That's it. That's it. That's it. 125 nulls, 126 nulls. Let's go. A new hero can come in
tomorrow. I am stacked. No one will fucking defeat me at this stage. Not even close.
There's just hobgoblins hanging out over here now. Oh, it's because it's the month of the hobgoblin.
Oh, well that makes sense. Nobody in this garrison go. Why would you go? Well, lots of hobgoblins.
Get out of the fucking way. Why do I have to go all the way around? I can't just,
hey, thanks for killing it. He's dead. Goodbye. Oh, you are pathetic. Look at your
pathetic army next to my large army with all the dragons and the magma and the
earthquake. Oh, do you have fucking fireball? Oh, what's that? Oh, sorry. Am I gonna fireball
the fuck out of you? I'm thinking fireball the centaurs. Whoa, what's this? What's like the
cousin it? Psychic elemental attacks all adjacent enemies without retaliation. Mind spell immunity.
Okay, kill this immediately. Fireball down here. That's not a mind spell. Fireball.
Hit the griffon and hit everything down here. Bingo. You got nothing. You have nothing.
And in fact, I could probably fly over with my bugs and just start killing. But maybe I won't.
Get out of here. You realize what's happening. He must have had something really, really good.
Because why would you? I mean, he retreated. He deleted all those minions.
All right, we're gonna go up, up here. Let's hit the rally point.
He is. Oh, it's no, it's Gibrakas. Wait, new hero time.
Merlinda the witch or Luna the old enemy. I think it's gonna be
elementalist or witch. The witch. Let's get you some minions. Pretty cool.
Pretty good. Witch. What's your specialty? Is weakness. Better effect. In just a moment,
after another week, you're going to be heading out yourself with a stacked group of
minions. It's a stacked group of minions. Just nothing over here. Somebody already took it.
All right. Super north or right? I think I want to do. What's the sanctuary?
I want to go that way. Super north? No, look at this. A thousand experience. Sanctuary. Great
weight has been lifted. You feel safe. I don't think I can be attacked here. I don't think
I can be attacked. I'm going up this way. What do you got over here? This is a little
standoff. Hole. Should I check the hole? No, I'm in the hole. Why do the fucking hole
just make me do that? I didn't even want to do that. Hole. Hydro punt. How much are the
upgraded hydras? I can do it tomorrow. I don't like that route you're taking. It's really
pissing me off. I'm going to go beige tower. No, up here. I want this experience. A thousand
experience. Thousand exp. There is a sawmill right here. Grab this. Almost there. Fifteen
thousand. Taking all my shit. Something that way. Yep, sulfur. Fourteen thousand. I'm almost
there. I now have ultra hydras. He's coming after you? I don't think he is. I mean,
I'm about to meet him. I'm about to go down that way. Yeah, this is his like shitty guy.
He's got like a few, few, few and a bunch of dumb skeletons. This is his main. Might be
time for an open field battle. And then head up this way. Or head down here and check out
the other quadrant. Yeah. Where are you off to? Did you just recruit those or did you kill them?
I swear to god if you recruited them. Nope. You had to fight them. Hello. Upgraded hydra
pond. Chaos hydras. Regular hydras. 135 health. 250 health. Attacks all adjacent enemies
and cannot. Enemies cannot retaliate. 21 defense. In a few days you'll be able to take
your venture of your own. Your move. Oh, don't get away from him. He's so strong.
Fuck out of here. Let me back my stuff. Well, he's dead now. I got you locked in here.
You got a boat? I don't see a boat. Did you get them? Did you take those worthless things?
Oh, you did, didn't you? Here comes Tan. Uh oh, there's a battle going on over here.
Okay. Uh, no. That's mine. Here we go. Here comes the big one. Fireball weakness maybe. Or just
fireball. Right in the middle here. Fireball right here. This will get all three of them.
More fireball down here. Do I want to hit more units or do I want to get rid of
the water minions? I think I'm thinking right in the middle here. This is perfect.
I get the tent too. Let's go for it. Yeah. I hope that was worth you like $3,000.
Okay. The big bad guy here is the behemoth. Oh, 300 fucking health. Focus. Oh, this is not good.
I gotta focus behemoth. Actually, like fucking, it's 1200 HP. Uh, I don't know if I want to,
do I just, I think it's time to, we just gotta go in. How many are here? 250 hobgoblins.
Who's ranged here? I don't think they have ranged. Unless these guys throw axes or
something, right? Don't these guys throw? No. No, they don't have any range. Well, they,
no, they don't. No fucking ranged at all. I just got fucking, all right. I gotta,
you have, I gotta fight back here. Oh, you can move across the whole fucking map.
I'm gonna have to petrifying attack. You gotta go to, I just have to try to help
and get rid of you. Nice. Come on. Let me go with the Gorgon. All right. Should we send
him to slime? Okay. I'm going to buff Gorgon. Buff Gorgon. Gorgon. Go after the behemoth.
Sacrifice the magmas. No, no, no, no, no. We're going to slime. Slime the Gorgons.
Here we go. Death stare. Protection. Go for it. Here we go. Fuck just happened.
I just killed two. I just killed two behemoths in one hit. Are you kidding me?
I get to go again. Oh, nice. God damn it. I could have been able to attack you.
Oh, you're still alive. He's still alive. No. All right. Snake is going to go take out the
minions in the back here. Right here. Wait. Fireball. These guys. I might be able to get
rid of most of them. Or Fireball right here. I think I'm going to Fireball right in the
middle and then do bloodlust. I could, that was pretty, that was good. That's pretty good.
All right. Now clean them up. Snake. Into the back. Snipe. There's like three there.
Snipe in the back. Ow. Okay. Dragon. Go for behemoth. I think we still have to
surround the behemoth. What does he have? Two? He might have like, okay. All right.
Only one more. Where are you going? You're going to the archers. No, you're not.
Why would you go for the gnolls? Behemoth is dead. 252 of these guys coming in.
Oh wow. Magma. Get in there. 214. I just killed like 60. Bulls. Up here. Up here. Up here. Up
here. Kill the Hydra. The dragon. Yes. I still can't, I can't cast any spells. All right.
Bring them up. Bring up the gnolls. I win. There are some casualties, but I mean like,
I did it. Basic logistics. Movement over land. Yes. Advanced logistics. 20% more movement over
land. Uh, that's awesome. Let me get this back. It's already there. Okay. Looking good.
Now what about you? You have several big scary birds. I'm going to keep moving with this
group. I want to come back up here. Claim. I'll claim my stuff back. Nothing else.
Is this just disappear? Back to the citadel. Let's get another team going. Now you're coming
down here. Why? Okay. Why? Why do I always have to deal with the fucking asshole that
has like the shitload of enemies? I keep like preventing you from coming down. All right.
I need to head back out again. You guys just taking up space. Okay. There we go. 48 of these
in a room because of, let's take it. I have to go restock. I got these chaos hydras though.
So these things are fucking insane. Oh, there's two gnolls. All right. Restock. I'll be able to
have probably five. I'll have at least five chaos hydras, which now I become the behemoth.
Right? No. Do I want to get up here and claim? Did you take anything else over here?
He took this. I want this back. What is it? Sulfur. Is it worth me taking a detour? No.
Just get back. Just get back into town. Not worth taking a detour for. All right. Now.
Here we go. Bang. Bang. Bang. Bang. Magma. Magma has to be traded. For chaos? I mean,
five chaos hydras. Magma or? I mean, this is a destructive team. You can keep the gnolls.
Gnolls for magma. Yeah. The magma can't be replenished. That's true. I could wait another
day. Yeah. I'm going to leave magma, but I'm going to wait one more day because I want,
uh, I want, I want to take more. I want more. One more week. Give me more.
Okay. Hey Red. You're fucking dead. Okay. Okay. I want some archer. No, just go. I'm ready.
Save it. Red has, uh, what? Okay. What denomination turns into a throng? Is it a
hundred or is it more than a hundred? It's a hundred plus. Okay. So I have a throng of,
and then what? Lots is between what? 50 and a hundred. I mean, this would be,
this is very equal. It's very even. And a horde is what? More than 500? A horde is 50 to me.
All right. I'm going up. It's time. I'm not coming back again. I've got my army. This is
the army that I'm going to use. I'm going straight up. No, no, no. I can't go straight
up. I can say, yeah, I can. So whatever's left, I need to start taking cities and
buildings and stuff. Red's going to make their way to the right. I'm going to go north. I'm
going right up that road and I'm going to have a second army. Yeah, I'll have a second army.
Let's go investigate what's up here. Is it a road? It does lead to here. I'll take this
and there's a little lake here. I'm not going to forget about my second hero.
Keep going. Nobody in your garrison. It's mine now. All right. We're crossing into
uncharted territory. Another, you have two garrisons. Ooh, this is like undead world.
I can't even go up there. All right. Starting to build a little bit of a force here. I get
the magma guy here. What about building? Blood obelisk. I'm going to do some of these.
Plus two to a garrison hero's attack when defending against a siege. I'm going to get it.
I'm going for Red's castle. I think Red is up here, right? Red or Tan?
Blue's dead. Blue is no more. There are five remaining. Tons of resources up here that I
can just take. Should I go up here? I feel like this is... I need to see what it is.
Anything else? Cage of warlords increases the defense of the hero. Should just get
to plus one defense and I think I am maxed the fuck out besides the shipyard. This is my
ultra capital. Here he comes. Teal is dead. Uh-oh! No! Is there a castle up here? I hope
you got it. It's not a castle! I thought that was a castle. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He might not come all the way down here. He might not come down here. Nope. He didn't come
down. We're good. Something's right fucking here. All right. We just made... Okay. Give
me those chaos hydras. Give me some of these wyverns. Bulls. Okay. We're... Everything's
going to be all right. He's got fucking phoenixes. Well, I kind of just lose. There's
not much I can do. I might have to reload. There's not much that could be done. I think
if I lose this castle, I lose because I was wasting time. Well, I thought there could
have been a town up there. It don't matter. I'm just going to go straight this time
and I'll be able to take the castle straight from the road. Yeah, but I mean,
this is like tons of little paths you can go around. All right. I think I lose. No, not
quite. Green's dead. You only have seven days to capture a town or you'll be banished
from the land. I mean, I would have done things differently. I would have done it a little
differently. Let's just see what's up here. This is orange. Do you have a castle right here?
How far up is your castle? It's like all the way up there, huh?
Take it? I mean, I don't know if I'm going to be able to take it. I might
have to reload. New home. I don't know if it's going to be new home. It might be. Let's
find a new home. Let's see if it's a new home. Hey, can I have your house? Oh, I have earthquake.
Oh my God. I'm just so distracted by how annoyed I am at losing my fucking capital.
Well, we can just get in. How should I go after here? I'm using a fireball and a siege.
I know I'll probably win this, but at what cost? 250 health. Two to five damage. It's
not going to be enough. I don't think I'm going to be able to kill it. I'm going to
try and kill the bulls or the basilisks. I don't feel the kill though. I'm just going to go for
like the fucking basilisks that have the least amount of health. We'll just go right here and
see what happens. Kill in one hit? Yes. I get to go again. Perfect. Let me get minimal losses
here and it won't be a complete waste. Why in with the dragon? Yeah, just kill that.
Why would you attack this? Basilisks can't get in. You can move over. Can you knock it in either?
Hydra can't get in. Nobody else can get in actually. It's the same faction. Yeah,
we might just be trading castles. Not dead. You're still alive. That seems fucking ridiculous.
There's only one of you. Kill it. Holy shit. How do you still have one? I've done like
four or five hundred damage. What the fuck? I can do this.
Didn't do anything. I still can't get in there. I didn't do anything. It just like
shook the ground for a second. Who's in? There's still you, the bulls. What do you
got? Eleven. Let's go for the bulls. I'm not even fucking hurting these things.
Ninety-five archers can't even kill one bull. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
That's 39 of these things. Hooray. Hello. Kill. Kill. I'll go in next. I'll just hang out here.
I'm gonna be healing somebody. Can you move, please? What should I do? Fucking magic arrow.
Ice bolt. Let's just ice bolt this motherfucker. Let's kill him. There's just the
nulls and I have a new town. I kind of died but I lost a lot but I'll get a ton of experience.
Forty-four hundred. It's the same town. It's the same one. Let's just hope that they build
up their town as much as I built up mine. Expert sorcery. Fifty percent more damage.
What does it look like? All right, well you don't have a capital but I can get that
very soon. What about the dickhead that's right here? He's gonna kill him right now.
Wipe out. I'm gonna kill green. I'm literally gonna wipe out orange. I have enough to get rid of him,
I think. He only he has like a pack of lots. Pack pack. He doesn't have like he's several.
Not green. I'm talking about orange. Yeah, I think I can take him. Let him attack but I
don't think he won't. He'll run away. He's gonna run away. I want to eliminate orange.
Here we go because I've got five. He has five. I have 12. He has 10. Yeah, I'm gonna win
this. I got 39 fucking bulls. He's dead. 160. Yeah, these guys are terrible. This is like
having gnolls. They're not that good. All right, priority target is the titans.
Could just throw a fireball over here and we'll throw a fireball here or I could do
bloodlust on the hydras or I could yeah I could do an ice bolt on the titans.
Actually, I like that idea. I like the ice bolt on the titans or weakness or
yeah let me do that. Randomly places eight small patches of quicksand on the battlefield
which are only visible to the caster and creatures native to the terrain.
Walking into quicksand ends a unit's movement for the turn and makes it visible.
I'll bolt them. Took away one. None of them have a lot of movement besides the
genie and the genie flying over here would be like a terrible mistake.
So I'm gonna bring you up here. I think I'm just gonna wait or maybe I'll bring you up
here above and then fly in. Yeah, that's the plan. I'll take you guys out by jumping in.
Because the range is up here. I get to go again. Unbelievable. Okay, just kill them all in one
hit. Or the mages. No, I want to be away from those. Kill them all. 165. I just killed over
a hundred. Didn't I? Wait, only what? I only killed eight? No, who died? Yeah, I killed a
hundred. All right, now we're gonna meet you halfway. I'm coming up this way. What's your
movement here? Five. Seven. I'm gonna move like here. Same with you. You can go that way as well.
Balls into the same thing. Dead. Just dead. Good. Nulls come in. Priority is still the titans so
or yeah they are. I now can let's heal you. Exactly what I wanted you to do.
That's exactly what I wanted. So now I think I'm gonna fly you down here. Let's go from
this angle so I'm not surrounded. Maybe I'll fly you down into the mages. 21 mages perish.
You still have to walk all the way. Good. I don't care if you kill them.
That's fine with me. I'm gonna go genies. Yeah, I definitely attacked the genies from
this side because I want to be able to move the hydras over here too.
13 genies dead. Again. Actually, you know what? Let's kill the genies.
Oh, no, no, no, no. You go up here. These titans are gonna come to the archers. Let me see here.
Ice bolt again on the two. Yeah, you can stick right behind
because he's gonna kill the null and make one swing so might as well just block it so he
can't get to the archers. Absolutely crumbled. One last shot. It's okay. You're not that
strong. Nice. Genies dead. He's not dead. He's still alive. Miraculously. Kill the
genies. Get rid of them. The mage. Now we just have to deal with you.
All right. What do I got? Weakness. I can't cast it. Don't have any more. No, I can do
bloodlust on the greater basilisks. Surround! You're pretty beefy. One left. Can I do like
a magic arrow? Fuck. No bloodlust. Looks like you're just gonna have to hang out over here.
No! Damn it! Come on. One fucking left. You retreat with one person left?
That's so infuriating. I think you shouldn't be able to retreat if you've been in the match for
more than like a minute. What the fuck? If you've been fighting for like two minutes,
I think you retreat is not an option. You could go with one person left and you can run away
and keep all your stuff. Uh-uh. Come on. The game's 20 years old. I know. I know,
but I'm fucking mad. That's pretty good. I'm gonna get that. No, this is mine now.
That's all you got left is this. You don't have anything, really. I'm gonna hang out back here.
No, let me see here. What if you not build? I need this citadel. Capital. But if you come,
he might come back. What about my original house? You know orange? Okay, orange is now
retreating this way. I think orange is gonna come try to take my old house
because I just took his. It's just we're never ending, never ending trade houses with
each other. He didn't even lead me anything. Maybe just get a level two. No capital. Like,
I gotta wait. Um, I need to go out and just start taking stuff. So come on out.
I've got this already. One attack. Yeah, just get out here and get it.
There's a sanctuary right here. Fucking red. Orange. Green. Plus one attack permanently.
That's too luck. Got a gold mine down here. I still can't afford anything. Retake the old capital?
Just AFK in the sanctuary forever. I don't think I can do that. Medusas. I'll take them.
The magic plane. This is also...
Uh, it's been deserted. This cyclops tower. I want to get this.
Shit, I want that gold mine. Or should I just... I'm already up here. Hold on.
War Machine Factory. I already got it. Or this way. Just recruit a thousand chaos hydras. I could.
Observatory. Let's get a good look. So this is a lot of orange and then red is up here.
So I could take this stuff. I want that gold mine. Yeah, let's get the gold mine.
I don't want to be left out in the open here. I'm gonna grab this too.
Is anybody else down here? I don't think anyone else is over here.
New capital! Welcome to the new capital!
4,000 gold a day. It's like we never left. I'm leaving the town undefended.
Yeah, the town is really undefended, but there's nobody really up here.
It would take at least like three or four days for someone to even get over here.
They're all down here. They're all fucking each other up down there.
All right, here we go. We got some population now.
You are here. He's down here. Good. I hope you go down there and fucking have a problem
with Tan. Because I'm going to take you over here. I'm not going to be that
zealous. I'm just going to get this on the way back. Can I get under here?
I can get this too. I have one zombie garrison. Yeah, this. Now I'm going to head back.
I could take that stuff too. Let's just head back. I'm going to the sanctuary.
Chaos hydras. All right, thankfully this guy had everything equipped. Everything was done.
So let's get on. Let's buy some stuff. He doesn't have the lizard warriors though.
He does. Hold on. Yeah, he does. Okay. Okay, let's head back there and try to stock up.
Is he playing with one hero? Well, the problem is I'm trying to get like enough of an army
where I can have a second hero that is safe. So everyone has so much better stuff than I do.
So if I make a new hero right now, right, then I'm going to be thin. And if I get attacked,
then it's all dead. That just happened. I was trying to build a second army to take another
person out, but I keep getting just so far behind because they end up getting over here
much quicker than I can. So I can get another hero here, but I'm going to have like not a
whole lot of stuff. And I just lost my capital, so it's even harder to keep more
than one person. Can I go ahead and snipe these? I can. All right, next day. All right,
Tan just killed somebody. Tan just killed Orange's, I think Orange's last defense.
That's not good. Tan becoming super power. All right, let's take this and then get the
fuck out of here. I have almost this whole upper quadrant here completed. Okay, give me a
tavern. Demaniac. Demaniac. I mean, imps or intelligence. I feel like I'd want this.
It's got like imps. No, I'm going with Andra. Take you out and go exploring because I can't
really wait around. I can head this way. Stack? No, if I stack, I can only stack on like one
person. If I play as one person, I'm too concentrated. If I'm not concentrated,
you know, I have to try to do like two heroes. I can't just like stuff somebody in here and
stack forever. I could try to get the old castle, but look at this. This guy, this dude is,
this dude's ready to rock. I was thinking about going for whatever Orange, this is Orange's
castle. This is Orange's final castle. I might just go try to get it because that,
this is Orange just got killed by Tan. Remember, I might go try to get the other
castle from Orange. Let me see. I've got enough. It's worth a try, I think. Let's save it
because he just got wiped out. Is it worth a shot? Yeah, let's go. I'm going for it.
You did the thing that I did. Are you sure this is not me playing in a different timeline?
All right, I need to take a look. What do you have over here? I can't see. I can't see
what you have. All right, you looking all right. I'll take you out in a minute.
Let's just hope you don't come attack me and kill me. There he is. Okay. I thought that
was another person. Hold on. Who's in there? I just want to see what's in there.
Lots pack, several throng, lots, lots. I can get it. You don't have any big units. I do.
I'm about to destroy, I'm about to wipe out Orange. Orange's gonna be out of the game.
You just killed my hydras. All right. They don't have any big units. They don't have
any. They just have naga queens. Earthquake. Fuck. I don't have any spell points. No.
Okay. Fireball. I had to rest. Yeah, but I had to like go all the way back and then all the
way back down here. I don't have any MP, you know. I can icebolt like the naga queens.
That's all I can do. Or bloodlust somebody. I get bloodlust. They don't really have like
much of a defense though. Bloodlust the bulls. Bloodlust the wyverns. I would probably bloodlust
the wyverns and just get them in there. Or the basilisks. The rangers. Doesn't it only
work on, it's only melee, right? Didn't we find that out before? Hand to hand damage, yeah.
I'm gonna do it on the wyvern and then I'm just gonna fly like almost in there.
Maybe I shouldn't do it yet. I'm not gonna do it yet. I'm gonna do it like when
I'm about to attack somebody. Okay. Just start moving. Get over here. I'm so fucked.
I'm just aiming at him and shoot him. I gotta get rid of the ones that have range. You need to die.
I'm in trouble. I have better units but they can't get in because I don't have any mana.
So we might have to go back to timeline two here unless I can fly in here and just
cause a fucking problem. I can't, I don't have any mana to use spells. Like I have 12 points.
I can't use these. Yeah, I'm safe scum in this. I'm gonna save scum. It's not worth it.
I might eventually get in there but it's not worth it. And I can get some more heroes too.
And then I'll make my way over to orange. Hopefully I don't get attacked by them.
Remember when you said, he's coming in right now. He's fucking right here, isn't he?
Where is he? I just like saw his unit. All right, give me my spell power and I'm going to wipe out.
I'm not sure it's worth taking these and then I could buy more.
All right, back to, this guy doesn't have anything. 10 push-ups for every reload.
All right, how much mana do I have? I have 12 out of 100. Isn't there a way I can
one of the spells kept within? How do I, isn't there a way I can replenish them?
Let me just do this because it's there. I gotta get him out. Is that auto? Who's barking?
Who's barking? Let me see who's barking. I'll be right back.
I want to go see, seems like somebody's in the door or something.
I haven't taken a break yet anyway so let me see what's going on. I'll be right back.
Okay, we're good. We're good. This is really good music, you're right. It's very good.
Okay, so you go into town because you need to be like in the town inside and then you go and
visit the town. All right, everyone's comfortable. Everyone's good. Spend a night and then it's
time to go take over orange. Orange, in fact, is leaving. I don't, I think orange is now
unguarded. This is going to be perfect. So now let's go like this. You got everything.
You got 100 spell points, yep. Come on out of there and let's try to get you some
people next week. You have to stay in there. You, all right, here we go. Let's save it.
That's not a save. That is. This is still timeline two. I'm ready. How do I get over here
without him? Hopefully he doesn't see me. Although I could send the other guy out to
take this stuff back but I feel like I'll just get killed. Somebody will attack me
if it has more stuff. He's down here. He's gonna get implemented straight up. It's gonna
take him a while. It'll take him a while. Now he's coming back down. Tan just has so much.
Tan has a fucking ton of stuff. He's got like three heroes. Me and orange have one. I think
red only has one or two. Okay, well we got some dwellings. I have money so let's just at
least make, let's start a secondary unit here. Okay, wear the gold mine back. I think I can get
this uncontested and then he's fucked. Yep, I think he's gonna have to backtrack and come get
me. Should I? No. Should I leave everybody in the garrison? He won't be able to get through but
no. I don't know if that's a good idea. Just scum it. It might work. Let's see. Okay,
let's see if I, let's see what timeline happens when I don't do that. He's coming up. Time to
change capitals again. He's coming up for this one. He might not. If I can have two castles,
I'll be fucking happy. You ain't got nobody in there, man. There's like not very many people
in there. Give it to me. Here we go. Earthquake. Boom. I'm flying in. Should I not?
How many do I have? 19? No, don't fly in. I only have one range unit. I'm gonna get closer,
though. I'm gonna get closer up this way. You get closer down here. Cast any dumb spells.
That's fine. I'm gonna retaliate. Now you just killed, you just absolutely killed yourself.
So far so good. Let's get closer. We're gonna, I want to get, keep everybody like near the
front door because it's gonna open. Dead? All right, earthquake. Who needs a heal?
Don't do it. What are you doing? He's like, I think I'm gonna open the door. Do you see
them? I don't think I can see them over this height. I'm gonna, not yet. If he opens the
door, I'm not even gonna send them in. No, just wait. I think I'm just gonna wait. If
he opens the door, just come on out. Whatever. There's nobody, nobody else has range.
Oh, I can go in here. You can get in. I didn't even see that. Hey, anybody out here?
Fucking idiot. All right, I'm taking this pretty uncontested. It's fairly uncontested. I'm okay
with this. Anybody hear a noise? Well, now I can go in front door. I'm sitting on the gate.
All right, it's time. Flying. Everybody go in. Now we just have some skeletons.
Uh, yeah, now I killed the skeletons. Orange is about to be in very, very bad place.
Defeated. Tons of experience. I only lost some archers and one. Yeah, I didn't lose very much.
Basic ballistics for expert first aid. I feel like I want to like take expert first
aid just to get it out of here. It's been something to pick. I feel like we can get
better options. So this is what Orange has left. What does your house look like?
It's pretty stacked, actually. Yeah, it's stacked. Wall of knowledge. Yeah.
Oh, look at this. He's got fucking units to spend. All right, now we can make another hero
and I can actually have them with a good army. I've got another castle.
It's protected. Just get in here. Get inside the castle. I also have this, which is starting
to be, I'm having a little bit of trouble, but I've got a okay defense here. Not good,
not great, not fantastic, bad, not good at all. And here he comes, but it's not that good.
It's good. It's good enough. He's got lots of like fucking bone dragon things. I just,
I need him to turn around or I need him to go like somewhere else. Orange is right here.
Please go fight Orange and kill him. And, but I could go kill him. No, he needs to go here.
They need to fight. Now I can start to claim this shit. Wait, do I have any
walking points left? Um, not enough to do that. Not enough. Okay, here we go. Don't come get me.
Oh, where's it going? Orange. Okay. Give me this. Give me this. Give me that. I need more money.
I got, how many marketplaces do I have? I've got tons of wood too. I need more shit. I do.
I have to. I'm going to do 150 of these and then like a hundred of these, 160, 180. I need units.
I just need more. And then I'm going to have a hero there too. All right. So I need, I just need
units. Bang. This is a, this is a decent army. Okay. This is a good, this is a decent fucking
army to defend this house. It's not great, but it's not terrible. I wish I had teleport.
God damn, I wish I had teleport. So bad. If only I had teleport. Imagine if I had teleport.
I could get one, two. I could get them all. It's up and to the right. Okay. Where am I at?
I want to get, I could kill him. I think I'm going to go to, I think I'm going to go for it.
He's got nowhere to retreat to. I'm going to think I'm going to kill him. I'll get his
artifacts. And Orange is dead. How far away is Tan? Tan's right here. All right. I'm going to,
I'm going to sit in my hole. He might, they might actually, they might fight. I'm hiding.
It's time to hide with my two castles and my two armies. Tan claiming Tan. Orange is coming
back here. Orange is on the way back here. He has to claim a castle. He's done. Remember,
he only has a few days left. Anything else I can do up here? I want to save the money.
I mean, okay. Here's a game plan. I could send you out and then make a new hero and start
stacking. I think that is a ding. No. Bad plan. Do you think that's a good plan? I already
have a new, I already have a capital. I could get, how many Titans could I get? One. I
could get one super Titan and replace the Medusa. I need to restart my computer.
Have the other guys stack units of the other. Should I save the game? This is, I'll tell you,
this is crucial because I'm in a spot right now where I can start to stockpile minions and I
can eliminate another player. And then again, the week goes by and I've got like a couple of
really decent sized armies. This is crucial that this decision is done correctly. I have to go,
I have to go this way and start to claim territories that Tan has over here.
Once Orange is done, I need to go this way and I actually, I have to start going over here.
There's no way I'm going to be able to take over Tan. Not right now. I need a few more
castles and I needed a little bit more of a minion stash. This is crucial. Let's go.
This is his last ditch effort. I'm going to get his artifacts. It's over. He loses.
What does he have? Queens. Let's get a little bit of ranged. I'm going to, let's see, Fireball or
I'm going to get rid of the ranged so we can do right here or right here. I can do right
there. That'll take out probably most of the stuff over this way. Do Earthquake on my own
house. That would be so, no, I'm not going to do Earthquake. I could do slow. Always slow.
Reduce the speed of all enemy units. Okay. I'm going to stick around. Just going to wait.
Nobody move. I have some range. Let them come to you. Nobody move. Nobody do anything.
Take out the wizard. Let them explode. We get to go twice. That's fine.
One queen is perished. Jewel Wizardry. It really is Jewel Wizardry. All right, who am I?
Jewel Wizardry! I can do that every time. Ten gargoyles perish. Thank god you're stupid.
Um, all right, just don't do anything. Don't move. Nobody move. They have to come to you.
No! They got the bottom down. That was a mistake. Seven genies dead. What? What are you thinking?
What the fuck even are you thinking? Six genies dead. I get to go again. Let's make it a
double. Minimal damage. Minimal. Minimal. Okay, looking good. He's through. That's fine. He's
dead. Are they? Did he? How did he? Oh, he flew. Okay. Twice. Nice. He's fucked. I wonder if
you're going to step on a landmine. What do you think? Rush him? No, not yet. Not yet.
Not until these guys are dead. If I can not take any damage from like any of these people,
that would be so happy. See, look. He's just like, duck. What the fuck are you doing?
Why would you do that? That was just BM. It was. He knew he was going to lose.
Don't let him come in. Who cares? They're not going to get in.
Let's go for the front, I guess. Why not? I'm actually not going for the majors.
He's to go all the way down. Oh no. Oh no. You punched me a couple times.
I'm scared. I'm scared. Give me all your stuff.
I'm scared. Don't shiver. Hold on. This item renders your
units immune to the curse spell. That's pretty great. One on the torso of this
item increases your power by plus two and the Crest of Valor increases your morale by plus one.
Advanced ballistics. Hey guys, I'm going to have low energy.
Yeah. Look at that. No! Fuck out of my way.
I did that. I vanquished the enemy. These streams are really weird.
Don't fake cry. That made me sad. Why? Because I systematically destroyed him.
I meticulously destroyed him. I was the one that killed Orange. Nobody else did anything
to him. I took out his ground units. I took out his cemented into the ground units,
which are castles. He had no chance. I'm okay with this.
Let me make sure I have all this stuff equipped. I do, right? Power's pretty good.
You going? I just hurt myself. I just like, I can't even describe what I just did. I just
closed my legs tightly around and I spun around and that hurt a lot. All right. We're
almost at a new week. I've got time now. I have enough time to send
you packing. Out here. I'm going to go up to red. I'm going to try to find my way this way.
I'm not going to leave this place empty handed because I'm going to make another
hero and I'm going to make this castle defending. Check it out. All right. Which
like YouTube thumbnail am I going to use? Which YouTuber click this video thumbnail?
They're both equally. There's level four barbarian specialty in ogres. Yeah. All
right. Should I be the YouTuber? Put my face on every thumbnail or every iPad game
that has released in the last three years. This is an important decision.
I think we have to do with the YouTube. Yeah. Well, I got to, I got to move on out.
I got to like move this person out of the way. He's level four too. I mean,
I have to look for bingo. All right. Let's get you some people. How about some titans?
We're going to build you up. I'm going to take this person out of here. All right.
Everything's just fine. We're starting to become a power. Tan is looking very strong.
Red's looking a little on the weak side. I think I'm going to take you.
You need, Oh, you're in town. You know what? What? Everything's claimed. I'm going to leave
that castle protected. Come over here. Get this mine in here. He's fucking diluted.
Hey, I'm, I'm making it to like the final three. I'm okay with that. Tan is a lot
of stuff, but if I can, if Dan, if tan does not end up coming up here immediately,
it's going to be hard for him to take this castle. I wonder if I should just
fuck it and just start moving. I'm going to have to move. I'm going to get this.
And I mean, that's just money. I need it. Tan's got everything. This is going to be,
this is going to be all reds. Red's gone. Orange gone. Red gone. I think,
I don't know who's left. It's just gray, green and tan. I think, no, it is just me.
Oh fuck. It's just me versus tan. No, no. Is it really me and tan? No, no, no.
This is still pink. Red, dead, tan. Pink was the first to die. Well, yeah, pink died in the very
beginning. Is it just me and tan? Did blue die? We're going to have to investigate over here.
It's investigation time. We need, I need to go this way. There's somebody in here.
Yeah, we've got to, it's, I'm investigating. Tan's coming up. Is there nobody left? Well,
get this back. Get the thousand experience. Let's break through this and go on the road.
Not a new week yet. No, what do we need? I need genies. Okay. I'm so, I'm really,
really confused about this. Let's see. Tan's got this all under control. Here he comes.
He's on this road down here. He's going to go this way. All right. Find out what's over
here. Anybody else in the chat smoke weed? All right. Well, I just killed that guy in a second.
What's over here? Nothing. It's not a road. Dwarf college. Where's he heading? No, I don't
know. He's freaking me out. They just met in the middle there. He's coming. No, he went
down again. I don't want any dwarfs. No. What the fuck is that? I've made it across.
Homestead archers. No, this is all tan left. He's here. He won't make it. Get it. One hit.
Nice. Okay. So now we've got a bubbling cauldron. Where am I? Where's tan on this road?
No, not yet. All right. We've got more defense here. More of these stacking up some units.
This one's the one that's in most danger. I think they're ignoring it over here.
Tan? He's going down to get elementals. A thousand experience. Give me it. Fountain of Youth.
Well, I can't tell what's up there. I'm going back to the road. Oh, what's this? Mage tower.
It's mage's uncharted territory. I need to save. No, I have to. More of these wyverns.
More donkeys. Archers. I'm fucking nervous right now. He's got two really, really stacked
heroes. He might even have three. Enchanted Spring. Water wheel. Enchanted Spring. Pegasi.
I don't want Pegasi. Sanctuary. Fuck. You don't have a castle over here? You got this one.
You've got to have a castle back here. Stuffed back here. You have to. Get in the sanctuary.
There's got to be a castle back there. There has to be a stuffed crust castle back there.
Oh, don't say that. I can't eat that. I can't eat any food for like the next
two or three days. This is pretty barren here. I have titans. He's coming up. No,
he's just claiming every resource. He has so much money. He's got so many resources.
I'm fucking... Look at this. He's got the whole map. It's just me and Tan. It has to be.
I've got to snipe some of these resources from him. It's so far away.
That's plus one attack. I've got all I can buy. I've got to go back to the other place.
I'm okay with this defense. I can't do any more titans. I can do naga queens. I can do one.
This is it. He's coming in for the kill. He's coming in for the kill shot right now.
There better be something right at the end of this road. He's coming in for the kill shot.
He's right here. Let's just check. Let's see what's at the end of the road.
Fuck. It's right here. I'm gonna get it. That would have been too far away. I think we abandoned
this castle, I think. I'm gonna get another titan. Do I abandon the castle? Should I
hide over here and then run away? I could take all these units out of here and run the fuck
away. What do I got for resources? It's time to kneel. I'm not kneeling. I don't kneel for
kings I don't believe in. I got 10,000. I can get two more titans. I think I'm gonna get them
out of here. I'm gonna have like somebody sneak out the back. Eight titans. Those are very
damaging. Look at this. They're fucking 40 to 60 damage ranged. Stay in the fort. Just stay
in here. Do not sneak out the back. Make him pay in blood. You think I can win with eight
titans just throwing lightning bolts? I don't know if I can do that. I think I take... Here's
my plan, okay? Let me tell you my plan. I think I take the titans and I fucking run them away.
This is like $80,000 worth of stuff. I'm gonna run them. I'm getting out.
I can get out of here. You're gonna give them the titans? No, no. Let me just...
Just hear me out on this. Just wait. He's right there. Fuck. If he was like over here,
I would have just like ran through the gate. Oh well. Just gonna defend. I might actually
sell some resources to get some more mages. He's coming with like a gigantic fucking force too.
This is so bad. Does this guy have anything like leveled up? I can get some of them.
Well, at least I have more range. Okay. Save the game. This is timeline two. We're just
still in it. I'm about to go up to his castle up here. Maybe he sees, maybe he can
see that. And he's like, wait a minute. That's not a good idea. And he pulls back.
Split up the titans. Should I do like two, four, six, eight? Should I do or like four and four?
Two, four, six, eight? No. Keep them together. No, no. Okay. All right. I'm just thinking
maybe that would be an interesting thing to do. I could send out like an envoy to meet
him with like four fucking orcs. Let him come. This is it. He fucking ran away. He ran away.
He didn't fight me. And now I'm going to get his castle. Oh, you have a lot of people in here.
You've got a few, a horde, lots of throng, lots of throng. This ain't going to happen.
Okay. Earthquake. Here we go. Catapult. Catapult right here. Right there. And that's not
where I aimed. All right. I got to play this smart. I aimed like right here. Why did they go down
here? Chaos hydras. I'm going in. I just have to go in and try. Oh, it can miss.
Everybody just has to try to get in here and kill the hydra as fast as possible. And then
everything else should not be too horrible. Poison. I had to try. I gotta, I have to
get the fuck in here. Uh, what's more favorable? Probably versus the fireflies.
Archers. I can't really get over there. I could fly over here. Just like wait. Good.
They go away. I'm going to, I'm going to keep aiming it down here. The bull. I mean, I'm
just going to try to get the bottom. If I go for here, the fucking hydra. 250.
Get to go again. Take another one down. Open the front door. What are you thinking? Oh my
God. That's so good. Come on. If I get this castle, I'm back in the game for real. And it's
done very, it's very possible. All right. I can do earthquake again, or I can do something else.
But before I do earthquake, let me see if this breaks. If this breaks, then I don't need to do
earthquake. Don't need to do earthquake. I'm in. Now I'm going to do something else. I'm
going to do either fireball or lightning bolt. Fireball on. Now it hits me too. Doesn't
it? What we can do. We have expert, right? Expert stone skin. That's not a good, that's
not a bad idea. Do I have it though? Let's do it. All right. Continue to destroy. I want you
archers. The bulls. Holy fucking hell. The bulls. The bulls. The bulls. I'm going to,
I'm going to get it. I'm going to get this. It's so powerful. They're so powerful.
They're like too powerful. Let's keep killing these guys down. Heal bulls.
That's good. Noel's dead. That's it.
I got way more than you. This is a victory. I'm going to lose the archer's butt.
It's okay. The bull might be the best unit that I have. I'm just going to stack them forever.
Can I? Really? I can hit that guy? I can't. Oh, you can. That's funny. All right. Get in
here. Ow. These ones are still up here. No, sorry. Just wait. Get the bulls in here.
What the hell? No. What the fuck is going on? I can't believe it. I knew that was
going to happen. Don't worry. Oh, I hate this game. I tried to click them. The game's fun.
I just took his capital. Normal maximum spell points by 50%. That's insane. Or expert ballistics.
Two aim shots at maximum damage. Either one of these is really, really good.
Here's the capital. I need bulls. All right. What do you got? You've already cleaned yourself
out completely here. I mean, I can get all of these. Might as well just because I'm running
out of people. Don't have an artifact. I got to make an artifact merchant. So I got three
cities. And now that I have this, I can start to move around a little bit. Is it really just
me and Tan? I'm so fucked. This is not a bad force. I got to come out and start claiming
stuff. I can come out. This person's not scary at all. You know what I mean? Like, I think
I'm pretty sure I can take that person. What do you got? This is the one that has the power.
He has the swarm of the pixies. He has the highest unit. I think he has three heroes.
I could snipe some more of these castles. That's exactly what I'm going to fucking do.
Not that one. I'm going to go down here. See, there we go. Right here. You've got like a
pack. That would be a fight. Here comes a new week. Chaos hydrants. Bulls. Get them all.
This is turning out to be a pretty good army. All right. I need to leave here and
start claiming. I got to start picking stuff up. You know, I got to start to tap into
his resources. At least come out and grab some of the stuff that he took before.
Yeah, I lost my swamp. I could start to come out and go on the open field here.
I have pretty decent army. Who is this guy? This guy that just came in the front door. Who
are you? Several. Horde. Several. This is going to be a fight. I got fucking six chaos dragons.
I can repel them. Ten, eighteen, fifty, four, six. I could sell resources, but I don't
know if he's going to come do it. Several means, what, five to ten? Or is it ten to
twenty? A few is like up to five, right? Up to ten. Five to nine. It's going to be a fight,
but I have it. I think I might, I'll be able to do it. Oh fuck. They're closing in. Hold on a
minute here. What do I got in here? I think I, I got eight titans. I think I meet them in
the open field. I think I can do it. Two more titans. I got to load that guy up with titans.
All right. I'm going to start to claim. I got to start to move around. I haven't been down
here. There might be another castle. It might not even be fortified. Well, time to save. This is
where we find out what might happen here. Let's see what happens. No, he's not coming.
He just wants the resources. Ice bolt, ice bolt, ice bolt, ice bolt, ice bolt. You don't
have ice bolt. How do you not have ice bolt? Ice bolt on the bird. Three. Here we go.
Oh, it's all right. This could happen. They have a lot of ranged. They have a lot of ranged.
I, do I, do I fly out and fucking attack the genie? I could go fly attack this genie right
now. All right. I might just focus on the bird. Bird focus. Come on. Ow. Kill bird.
Kill bird. He's got one left. Kill bird. Kill bird. I have a really good chance now.
Now everybody just fucking relax and hang out and don't do anything dumb.
I've got balls. I do. All right. The most important. These guys don't have range. No,
they do. They do. He split the Titans up. These wizards are the ones that have to die.
I got to get out there. I got it. I have to get out there. I got to fly out there.
I got to kill those wizards. I got to get out there now. You know, I got to get,
I got to get, I got to get out there. 331. Oh my god. All right. I think I, I have to.
Let me, wait. Lightning bolt. Ice bolt. Ice bolt. Ice or lightning? Versus the wizards.
Probably lightning. I could blind them too. Cannot move and cause it to counter attack
at half its normal attack strength. No, that doesn't, he can still attack. No,
blinding isn't going to work. We're going to do, we're going to zap.
Oh, I got, do I just fucking go out there?
I don't know. I think they just have to, just have to wait. Oh, I can hold it or just go in.
That's the only range they have. I'm going in. Oh, I've got to do this. I have to fly over
there and kill. I, I, 58. Oh no. It's like, whoa. They have too many units. There's too
many units. Fucking 400 of these things. Send the balls in. Just somebody kill these.
The titans can't even move. I'm going out the front door with the balls. Next
fucking attempt. They're dead. Dead. Come on. Kill them.
No, you're doing the stupid blessing. Get these pixies out of here. Okay. Should I dispel
or should I try ice bolt? I can't. I'm going to dispel them. I can't blind them.
I can't. I don't have enough spell points.
God damn it. Why was this guy so beefy? That's the only person that's been doing anything.
It's cause this hero like is level two. They realistically only have this. I still have 18
balls and I still have chaos fucking demons. I kind of have to just walk out the front door.
Like that's the sad part of this. I have to get out there. Like just go,
just go out the front door. Get the balls out there. Hurry.
All right. He brought the genies in. 18. Three genies die. I have to bring the balls out.
Or should I just kill the genies? They're just, they're in here. Five genies dead.
No, they just, they have too many of these guys. They have too many. They had so much
range. He just brought it. He had like fucking four ranged units. This is it. I lose.
Well, this person's literally just stepping in the swamp. I should have 2020 hindsight.
I should have only just, I should have brought everybody outside to attack the mages,
but then they would have just died. They would have just died.
Everybody that walked out the door would just die. This is a loss. The balls can't do
this on their own. I love how the shitty archers on the castle can do more damage than
like my people can do. Yeah, this is over. They are weakened. Yeah, but I've lost this
cow. I'm just, this tan owns almost the entire game. I mean, I'm just going to fucking,
whatever. I'm just going to die here. Well, they ain't going to have much, but at this stage,
I don't know. I don't think this is winnable. I don't, they have so much beef. They own the
whole game. I swear to God, if pink is just down here. No, it's all tan. They conquered
everything. Tan conquered. Okay. This is the stupidest damn thing. Listen to what happened here.
So one of these, like two or three of these fucking dumb fuck faces in the beginning of the
game, like pink and blue, whoever it was instantly lost. And I mean like instantly,
they lost everything. Tan just like walked into somebody's castle and just took it over
twice. And then so tan at the very beginning of the game had like three castles down here
and then just started to fucking poison everybody. And then I made it to the finals too. I'm okay
with this. Who's even in here? What's down here? I want to see what's down here. Get out of my way.
It's goddamn tan. Yeah, it's just me and tan. Fucking tan. Unbelievable. I can't believe it.
They took everything. They have everything. No, I can't lose in a 1v1. Who's in here?
Where's the ice pole? There's gotta be some castle that's unguarded. How do you have so
much guard everywhere? Well, I need money to make units. Oh my god. Yeah, from the very
beginning of the game. This is impossible. There's no, this is an unsurmountable no
victory would be. I can't do it. Impossible. I have to restart the game. I'm done. There's no
way. All right, so you know when you play risk and you're on Australia still and one of your
friends has every single other continent and every single other country in the game and it
gives you that look like uh what do you want to do here because you have like 200 troops
right at that bridge. That's just what I'm doing. I'm just pro I'm prolonging the game.
Hey dude, uh you want to get some like food or something? No, I'm not done playing the
game. Uh I mean it's impossible for you to win. I'm not done playing. All right um where do you
want to go? I would like to stay in Australia in fortified please. Okay yeah it is just like
that is no way. I have to just give up. Go to the tree house. Yeah, I didn't even
click that. I'm just I'm I'm clicking it. It's like eight heroes. Oh no they're coming from
my castle. What's wrong? He owns everything. He has like 10 castles. He has every single castle.
What is this? Oh that's me. That's so funny. I'm I made it to the final two. I'll take second
place. That's fine. He's just toying with me. Well, I mean I still have like 10. I could
just put make like 20 fucking titans. It's not over yet. It has not ended. He hasn't taken this
castle and I could I can make 20 titans. Get out of Australia. Stop it. Get get you're
not going to win. It I don't care how many troops you have on Australia. Here we go.
Biggest threat is what the hell is this? They shoot 63 of these fucking things.
Free to the mages. I think the mage is the worst and the ones that can fly. Oh boy. Okay well
hold on a minute here. It's not over yet. Just continue. Just buff the titan. Magic arrow
cure bless. Maximum damage. I haven't lost yet. Give it the titan again. Stay here.
I get to go again. Oh it's been breached. Okay we have blessing. We're gonna do
he already still has blessing right? I guess he's blessed right? Just fucking keep doing it. It's
very I can do this. How many points do I have? 17. I still have plenty. Stone skin on I'm gonna
say probably on the on the naga queens or just all in on the titan. Probably all in on titan.
That's what I'm gonna go for. You're in. It's okay. You're in but it don't matter. Now we all have
to focus on you. No. Get rid of them. Everybody just calm down. Just focus on the dragon that
just climbed in. Fucking pathetic. Pathetic. Absolutely pathetic. 14. Titan come on. Titans
do it. They're just dying. They're just he's killing himself. I'm gonna hold the castle.
I'm gonna hold the castle. This is melee right? I'm gonna swing with the sword. That's technically
melee. Holy shit. I killed so many. It's not over. I'm gonna win. Okay we gotta deal with
the ball coming in the front door. We got just everybody body block the titan. This is gonna
be the problem here. They still have. Yeah they have so many strong units.
Deal with the immediate threat. It's the immediate threat right here. I get to go twice. Die.
I'm gonna have to go with the titan. We're gonna kill the naga queens. Ow. Um cure or
bless again. All right here comes the ball. It's just the titan. Go on. Come on. I think
I can do it. It's possible. Dispel that shit. Cure. Ah. It's still possible. It's still possible.
They have to get over here. It's possible. Bloodlust again. Do it. Kill them. Okay all
right. Here we go. I just need. I'm gonna lose. To kill. I have to get rid of the titans.
Bless. Again. Or should I stone. But stone skin is from melee. Haste.
Bless and then throw. Haste. Do you want to do haste and then walk over here and smash them.
No. Yes. Get rid of the shitty water surface. But I have to get rid of a titan.
They have two titans. Bless titan and then throw at this titan.
Bless titan and throw at this titan because he's got nine titans. I have six titans.
I didn't even fucking hurt him. Just start fucking roping. That was so close. That was close.
Come on. Give me a miracle here. Morale down. Come on. Give me a miracle. The titans resist
the spell. This sucks because the archers are gonna kill this. I actually think I need.
New plan. No. New plan. That's a bad plan. Doesn't matter. So I gotta get out. I'm
gonna get. I'm gonna fucking walk out and start swinging. I'm gonna go. I can't win.
It's not possible. It's impossible to win. This is the same unit. So I had three. No.
It's impossible. Just. I just wanna. He just took it without. It's empty. You're the beetle.
This is it. I got nothing. It's over. Game over. He has every single building.
He forgot about something. What? Wait, wait, wait. Back it up. Back up. Back up. What the
fuck was this? Where'd you. What? Who? How did this happen? Did he just. He just spent
every cent. How much? Five hundred and fifty. Eight two fifty. Where the fuck did you get these?
Final stand here. He has every base and every resource. Fucking stomach. Yeah,
he has every single base and every single resource. Why is this surprising to me? Don't
main one hero. I tried in the beginning. I tried to just make income. It's also something
I mean, I'm playing against eight people. You know, it's like it's a lot more chaotic and crazy.
It's hard to have more than one or two heroes. Just add 200 titans in and we're at 130 percent.
It's true. It's really like when you have an eight person map and the AI, the one AI that
forgets to move gets taken over immediately. And then whoever that AI is that took the
mobile wins the game. It's kind of what happens. All right. I can't really go anywhere.
So he's going to go like this. I'm going to step on the landmine. I'm doing teams this time.
I'm putting tan on my team. I'm doing two V2, V2, V2. Tan or purple? Who do you think?
We're going to shoot. Look, I'm just going to lead the other guy out and go take all
of his stuff. You want to green and purple? OK, that sounds good. We'll do it on a small
map too. Or small enough to go twice. Unfair. Hey, at least I guess I was going to say step
foot in the castle. I was about to hit the end. I was about to hit the fucking surrender
button. I can't go out like that. I made it to the last two. I'm OK with this. Everybody
else gets scooped up by tan's fucking insatiable conquering, whatever. Oh well.
Human players. Eight. Computer. Oh no, no, no. Seven. Other players. Let's do teams.
Water content. Road type. They don't matter. Monster strength. I mean, what does this mean?
Strong guardians. Water content. Normal. On what is this? Select single or two level map.
I'm not sure I want to do that. What does that mean? Underground. No, I don't think.
We're just gonna do extra large. No, we're just gonna do large. Two, four, six. Six players.
One, five. Not eight people. We're gonna do three v three. One v one v one. Three on each.
Two on each team. We're just gonna do a team of two versus team of two versus team of two.
Team two. Two v two v two v two. Two v two v two. I need to do this 130% difficulty. I have
to. Okay, so I'm gonna be green. Can I select green? Do I have to be? Wait, what? Random map.
Oh, team alignment. Okay, there we go. Team one is gonna be, who do I want? Tan or purple?
Who do you think? Purple. Team two. Blue and tan. Orange and green. I want to be green though.
Can I even pick that? Extra large. Okay. Normal, normal. Template.
I have no idea what the fuck this means. Do 100% this time? You think so? 100%?
I feel like with that, I feel like we're all right. I was doing okay. PvP options.
Coin flip. No, I don't want to. 100, that better be fine. We just, we just gotta get more
competent. You're not ready for 130%. Well, that's what we've been doing the whole, you
are in Australia. Extra large. Oh, large. Okay. All right. Now I want to, I want to set up,
I don't want to be red. Advanced options. How do I, I can't choose to be one of these other
players. I guess I just have to be red. Well, what do I want to do? Necropolis?
I've been killed twice in a row. Options. What else we got? Hill force. I don't know
what that even means. Advanced options. I want to, I want to, random map. I want to go back
to where I was just at. Large, one, five, team alignments, team one. So can I do that? Will
that work? Because I'll just be, I'll be green, right? No. Because usually there's a flag next
to every, everybody. I usually can just click it. No, it's because I have to, okay. So hold
on. So I have to, human or computer players. Okay. That's strange. All right. That's good.
That's good. That's good. Normal, normal, normal. Let's do advanced options. There we go. Okay.
Green and purple versus everybody else. Alignment. Yes, that's correct. All right.
Advanced options. Necropolis. What does it put in front of? Uh, too hot. Dungeon.
Stronghold. Fortress is what I just did. Conflux. Elemental. We'll do Necropolis.
Necropolis and what do I want my teammate to be? What was Ares before? There he is. All right.
I'm ready. Let's go. Teams of two. Everything should be good to go. Oh, I got to pick my
hero. Uh, don't even, I don't care what, what this is. This is what it's going to be.
Begin. Uh, that's fine. Creating map. There am I. There's my friend. Necropolis. All right.
Let's go. Let's get a second hero. Can I get a druid? First aid specialty or meteor shower.
Well, let's have you head out here and get the gold. Seer's hut.
Nowadays I have done this myself, but I need your help. A friend of mine recently had a
family heirloom stolen and wants to find it. The problem is that it looks exactly like
the pendant of free will. Please, please bring me any item that fits that description.
The artifact is not the family heirloom. I'll reward your efforts. Interesting. Money. Magic well.
Okay. Let me, let's go back. I want another hero. Let's get another necromancer. Let's,
uh, stack you up, send you up. Will the gremlins recruit lots of gremlins?
Let's actually get a save point here. Oh, it's a new game. All right. Master gremlins.
I think I already lost. Meteor shower. Get in there, skeletons. Come on.
Shit. I can't cast it again. I got this. Nice. 49 battle results. So now I should have
more skeletons. All right. 17 sulfur and then Griffin conservatory. I don't want to attack
the guards. No, I don't. I'm not going to do that right now. Let's get this level up.
It wasn't quite a level up. That's fine. Okay. Harpies. Let's go back here and spend some money.
Town hall. Or should I, I think I'm going to make a graveyard. I need,
I need enemies. I have to start getting people. Last time I did this, when I did town hall and
then I didn't, I need units. I'm going to go with the graveyard. Let's get some, oh no,
whites. Whites are, yeah, let's go. Let's go with whites and let's give those to you. All right.
What is my teammate going to do? All right. He's collecting. Let's get a second hero going out.
All right. Nice. What do you got for heroes here? This guy and this guy. Okay. Cool.
I am going to grab who has more. I'm going to actually give you the whites
and you're going to keep going. Let's grab what is this? A pack of mighty gorgons. Let's
actually grab this. Yeah. I need the wood. Gold, a horde of imps. I don't think I can
take a horde of imps right now, but I can collect this stuff. All right. Graveyard.
Get them made. Nice work. He's just picking up some resources. Very cool. I think I can
take these guys on. Horde of those little turtle enemies. What do you got? You got,
I think I could do it. They're pretty weak. Uh-huh. Wait, wait, wait. Before we do that,
grab this. Crypt. I want to search the graves with this guy. I'm terrified of what could happen
here. All right. Let's get the resources going. But you on the other hand, I have a decent
army. Let's kill him. Just in case of a fucking disaster. 25, 25. Plus I've got
fucking magic arrow too. Yeah, you get pretty weak. Float on over here. That's fine.
Aha. I get the advantage to attack you first. In fact, actually, yeah, dig it on here.
Dead. Resources. Experience. All the good stuff. I think that's all I can do. Estate.
Vampires. Bring them on. I am now going to do a town hall. Wrong building. Wrong building.
Thousand dollars a day. I've got some units here. Let's see. You. How do you, you got,
you don't have a bad selection here. You could probably kill these guys. I don't know if I could
take on the mighty Gorgons though. I'll go back and I'll give you. Oh, there's a bunch
of ton of random fucking people here. I want to give him the vampires. Make your way over
this way. I can take them. 13, 13. Magic arrow. I don't have any spells. It's all right.
Just get out there. Make a text to speech of my voice. No, I've never considered that
because anyone could get me to say literally anything they wanted. Natalia. Good. You're
watching the NBA finals. NBA finals? Who's the, who are the finals? Raptors and the Warriors.
Interesting. Raptors and Warriors. I don't really know much about either one. All right,
now the cover of darkness covers your city with a permanent shroud to all players.
If you get it to Christ Temple, maybe I get the Citadel. I'll probably get um,
blacksmith or marketplace. Start the Citadel up. Try to get through a city hall.
Or what does the mausoleum take? Mage skill level one. Okay, you. We're going to come
in here and take these. Okay, pretty good. Vampires. Me? Yes, you. How you doing over
here? Lots of pixies. Lots of walking dead. Lots of gremlins. Gremlins are weak though.
So random maps really are just all over the place, huh? I think I can.
Lots of walking dead. Can I take them? There's shit just everywhere.
They're just like spammed in every direction. Lots. I could probably take the walking dead.
Can't really move. Okay, let's go up. Lots of harpies. Board of imps. I think I can take
the imps. Let's go, uh, yeah, you up there. Vampire. How far are they? Can they do that?
Not that I'm ranged. Just let them come to me. Come to me. Four vampires. Let's see.
See how four vampires appear. Very well. Uh, I'm gonna wait with you. Oh, you're running
away? No, he's running down here. Well, okay. Very good. 240 exp and touch the obelisk.
Ooh, puzzles. I haven't leveled up for many of this though. I already did something today. Yeah,
I did. Imagine having feet. What do you mean? Everybody has feet. Now they're expanding out
here a little. Uh, let's take on the gremlins. Not strong enough. Good twice, bullshit. No more
spell power. Fuck. Make your way around. Zombies are so slow. Good damage. Keep shuffling
over there. So what, what, uh, what, uh, what is it? How much time is left in the, uh,
finals game? Gem Pond. Board of halflings. A minute and 30 seconds. That's not very long
at all. I need to get by the harpies. I think I'm, I think I'll do one week. Grab some, uh,
troops. I think so. Grab some more vampires and go kill the harpies. Yeah. Citadel. I want,
I get to upgrade. I need an amplifier so I can get better vampires and I can get more
skeletons. So that's good. All right. What are you gonna do, Purple? Just browsing around,
checking out his surroundings. All right. Level two, death knight. Advanced offense.
That's insane. 20% more damage. I kind of have to do that. We got lots of basilisks.
I can't do that. Lots of hobgoblins. Oh, that's just down there. Upgraded estate.
Vampire lords. What's the difference? No enemy retaliation. Undead. Five to eight,
30. Five to eight, 40. Drains life. Oh, they life leech. Okay. That's fucking awesome.
All right. So far so good. Uh, new week. Let's load him up, send him up north.
Oh, dwellings increase their population. Astrologists are playing week of the squirrel.
I'm going to give you the zombies and the skeletons. I'm going to leave the wraiths
because I want the other guy to have the wraiths. This is a pretty decent team.
Although what else can I build here? All right. Now marketplace or upgrade. So I do
wraiths. Grab the mausoleum. Mausoleum. Let's get some glitches. It'll be for the other
hero. We can take out these harpies now. A meteor shower. No reason to do this.
Just throw a magic arrow. And you can, how far can you go? What's your speed? Six versus nine.
So let's just chill for a minute back here. Chill again. You on the other hand, you move.
Boink. I need to go again. I'm just going to heal over and over again.
I forgot they could do that. Wow. That's awesome. These things are ridiculous.
Go. I mean, what can I do with this guy? Not much I can do.
Vampire will take it out anyways. Fly away. Whatever you do. Nice. Should level up from that.
Advanced necromancy or basic luck. 20% of the creatures killed to be brought back as
skeletons. That sounds pretty great. We're unlocked. What is this? Tree of knowledge.
Tears brim in the eyes of the tree. I need 10 gems. Well, come back when you can pay.
10 gems. Is it an empty castle? Is it a castle? Whose castle is this?
There's a fucking castle back there. All right. Um, I'm gonna, let me head back
because I want, I want the liches. I'm going for the castle.
Can I get that castle right now? There's not much in it. Let's just see what happens.
I'm not strong enough to do anything else. Can I get all three of them? Three liches.
I think if I come back and grab these three liches, I can take this castle without a
problem at all. I'm getting it. All right. So why? Pack of serpent flies. I mean,
I could, this should be easy. Pack of serpent flies. Just in case this goes horribly fucking
wrong. These things like suck. No, I wanted to cut, cast a damn spell. Get the first hit.
These things are really weak. Did I bite off more than I can chew here?
If I can attack, I may have bitten off more than I can chew. Maybe. Didn't you kill them?
Really? These little shits. Yeah, there's just too many of them. They just have like
spread out everywhere. I still might do it. Close. I still might do it.
No, I don't think so. There's too many of them. No, that's not, that's not gonna happen.
There's not, I'm sorry guys, that's not gonna happen. I was just curious. It's not gonna happen.
He's gotta do 10 push-ups now. Ow, god damn it. I gotta move this shit. I gotta get like a
different mic stand. I keep doing that. I keep banging my fucking hand. So let's go get that
castle. I'm gonna leave this for the other guy. I think I can get it with just this.
I don't want to be greedy. I could maybe attack the, no, let's get the castle.
Let's get the damn castle. Nobody fucking even in here. All right, you go restock. I can't really
do anything without money. Purple has gone into a portal. Let's see, I'm gonna pack a
Cyclops Kings. I have to start mass producing artifacts, but I gotta have one first copy.
I gotta bring you guys all this crap. This is nice. All right, this is,
blue is up here. Found the enemy. This is unclaimed. It is unclaimed for a very specific reason,
because you have to go through the pack of Cyclops Kings to take this castle. That is why
it is currently not available. You can take them. I don't know if I can take them. I don't
think that's gonna happen. Can I build anything else? Marketplace Skeleton Transformer
allows you to convert any creature into a skeleton. I need to get a marketplace in Blacksmith.
Actually, go rest in here. Just for a day. I don't know. You think it's worth, should I try it?
Blue's right there. I could fucking do this right now. If I have enough resources,
it might be possible. What you got in there? Oh, you got nothing in here.
I can take it right now for free. Go for the Cyclops Kingdom.
Try to get the pack of Cyclops, or go yoink at this city for free.
I don't know. That's so scary. The box that the Cyclops is guarding is OP. All right,
we're gonna split the timeline here. I'm dead. There's no way. That's not gonna happen.
I could just try to go forward, and I don't know. No. Five, four, three, two, one.
It's no use. I mean, if I had a little bit more, if I had a little bit more,
yeah, it's no use. If I had some more, I'm gonna go for Blue. Here's the thing. If I get Blue's
castle, then I can build up a little more, and send somebody else down to take that one.
All right, we're gonna go back to the timeline. Okay. Although there are lots of
gnolls, I could get this. I could do, okay, this is the magical garden. I could take the
gnolls. I'm gonna get it. Okay. Uh, Horde of Skeleton Warriors. I don't think I even need
to pursue them for any reason. How many gems did the tree want? Ten? I'll do it with the
other guy, because I have to bring this other guy up here anyways. I don't want to go to
South, because my buddy's got South covered. Purple's got South covered. You know, I'm
gonna, I'm going up North. Wait a minute, what's this? Hold on. Hold that thought for a
sec. I need Blacksmith. I'm at, yeah, allied with Purple. How many more days? I just feel
like this is not enough to do anything. Maybe like get rid of the gremlins and just,
can I just keep walking? Let's just see what's over here. I might be able to get these
pixies and the gremlins with this. Purple's going up. Where's Purple going? Tree? Let's
see. Plus one level. Ah, an adventurer. I'll be happy to teach you a little of what I
learned over the ages for ten gems. Just bury it around my roots. Or earth magic.
Advanced wisdom. Oh, earth magic. Earth magic's really good. Blue, how you doing? You still
got an empty castle. Yes, you do. Lots of pixies. I think I can handle it. I should
be able to. Yeah, they're weak as absolute fuck. They're terrible. There we go. Instantly
killed and almost. I'll have to lose the skeletons. Okay, cool. Lots of gremlins.
I'm not sure it's worth doing that right this second. What's over here? Monolith
one-way entrance. More pixies. Nah. Citadel. Wait for the city hall, I think. Yeah.
God damn it, he's back. Timeline. Because I went down to the tree. The timeline has
been split. That's why. Because of the tree. Because I went back into the tree. Should
have just went with the plan. Fifty dollars just came in. And a bunch of community subs
at the same time. Holy shit. Cyclops Parker just gave ten community subs and fifty dollars
at the same time. Holy shit. Thank you so much. We're with a huge amount of money.
And they say, German just wanted to thank you so much for playing this game again. It's
one of my all-time favorites. I can see why. It's great. It's really, really fun. It's
super interesting. It's challenging. You've got to manage stuff. The reason why I like
this game is there's a lot of resource management, but it's not overbearing.
It's just fun to collect stuff and look at scenarios and it's really, really fun.
I am going to keep going up. I feel like he's going to leave the castle.
And he's going to go this way. And go back. Because it's a new week here in a second.
I could have sniped the castle. I really could have. But I just didn't. I went back
down to see what the tree did. See, did he leave? Did not leave. Damn it. That
would have been so good, too. Kind of made the bed we have to sleep in, though.
What do I want to do here? I'll do Citadel. Oh, City Hall. We have a new week. Let me
take you back here. But thank you again so much to Cyclops Parker. It's a shitload of money.
Let's stock you up with people and send you back out. Unfortunately, the throng of trolls.
I'm on with two-way. I want this motherfucker to leave. Horde of pixies. Random maps really
are just so odd. It's kind of like somebody just threw up a bunch of stuff everywhere.
Alright, lots of hobgoblins. I'm going to be out here, though. I could probably do both of
these and get the experience. But he might come out and be annoyed by this.
Let's go this way. It's a lot, but I'm pretty sure I'll be fine. That's a pretty good
start. What's her speed? Five. Focus on you. Come on out. You really can't go very far,
can you? Damn it. Well, let's just eat you. They group up. That's good.
Losing a lot for a portal. I thought that was going to be enough. It is.
I'll get him back. Don't worry. These guys are strong, but they're just too slow.
Good amount of experience and a level up. Advanced earth magic or basic offense?
Probably advanced. Offense is good. 10% more damage, but I feel like I need that early.
I feel like this is good early. I need the damage.
Lots of zombies. Where the hell did I end up? This is two-way, right?
Five gems. I'm over on purple side. Quiet. What the hell is this?
It's red. This might be bad. Blue is out of the house. I'm surrounded by red.
Purple. I could use some reinforcements over here. Oh, boy. Wait a minute.
You don't. Oh, excuse me. You got one person. What about you?
Oh, several lots, several. I could wipe them both out. I think I got to what it takes.
Several lots, several. Back to base. Speaking of base. Ah, Citadel. Let's get some. I've got
to get some more units and I'm going to take him out and we're going to go north again.
Ain't nobody fucking in there. Okay, come on. We could really fuck red shit up right
now. Blue's coming down here. I might have to go on the defensive. Several, few, few,
lots, several. I might have to stick it around in here. Add to the forces.
I definitely need vampire lords and liches. I'm going to stick around in here for now.
But you, on the other hand, you. Dwarven treasury.
Dude, I want to attack the dwarven treasury and get like a bunch of money right now.
I think I'm gonna get the difficult one in the corner. You can take care of that.
I'm going up in this corner. No, I'm going to stay down here and protect
because this guy, I don't want to die. I can fly over here with him. I'm going to go
down. He's not going to be able to make it. They're so slow. You don't get to go twice.
God damn it. That sucks. Uh, I'll deal with you later. Really? Why are you guys so fucking
beefy? How much health do you have? I'm in trouble. I mean, I might, I might still do it.
Kill, kill this one. Yeah, I'll do it. I got 17 of these things. He's got the least amount,
but this guy down here. Keep this one occupied. You're going to lose, but I'll get the scalps
back. This might be worth it for the money. Dean, fly up here. Get away from those people.
Why do you get to go twice? I think it's good. It's going to be close, but I'm going to do it.
Oh man. Come on. Do it. Vampires are fucking insane. Especially the upgraded ones.
All right. That was a good fight. I got 1500 experience. I lost everything except the
vampires, but I leveled up. Basic intelligence or advanced wisdom, fourth level spells or
more spell points. Just have full stacks of vampires. Yeah, take the intelligence. 4000
golden three crystals. It was worth it because now I can protect the base. It was worth it.
It was. I had to do it. One way, one way. This, this sucks. Why does everything have to be
so weird and spread out? Now I can afford more, or I can afford a lot of this now.
Bang. I'm very protected at this point. If he comes down here,
I at least got to fortify the base. He's making his way down. What does he have?
Pretty similar. I need to get out of the base. Let me see. Who the fuck are you? Several
pack, pack several. You coming, you fucking, you wanna fuck around? Why is everybody coming
after me? What? I have like a whole other teammate. You got another castle up here?
I'm getting swarmed. I can't take on two defenses. I can, I can get rid of you right now.
On, save this. Original team timeline. Honestly, I should have just taken this base.
I should have, I shouldn't have went back down. That was a mistake. I could have just taken
blue. I, I'm, there are one, two, I'm being swarmed right now. Purple just like went this
way, uncontested and just took this. Okay. Well, I can either, I might just go kill this person
right now and then hope that I can get enough. Cause this is a lot coming in.
Hopefully you just go over here, but then you'll get the fucking castle.
Damn it. Well, we'll see what happens. Here we go. Okay. Now I am going to kill you
cause you're not coming up. Blue's not coming this way. I need to go back
through this portal. Port of imps. I have to fight these zombies to get through the portal again.
How did I get out? First of all, I'm going to delete you. Like I don't like you over here.
I don't like what you're doing. I'm killing her. Here are your ranged units.
Let's go with the eyeball. That's a better shot. I don't have a good angle on anybody.
I'll do it like I could do it here. Get the other ranged. Fly up this way.
The lich. That's fine. Just all focusing on him and he's going to die.
All right. Uh, I'm going straight into here. Or maybe I should get you stone skin to, uh,
you see if I can kill you. Cause you're ranged right here. Flying back. Gotta get you.
Let's go. You up here. I might actually lose. I mean, this motherfucker is just going to walk
around and just take all my resources. I had to do something. Get my rates in there.
Good. There we go. I have one skeleton. Hi. No, I got it. Open. It's going to happen.
Vampire is too strong. It's good. Good to go. You've been defeated. Advanced necromancy
or basic armor. So you've been vanquished. That's good. Five skeletons have been brought in.
I could have got this asshole to deal with though. He went up here. He's just hanging
out over here. He's going to go in the portal. I think. Oh shit. He's going to go in the
portal that I'm standing in front of. I'm screwed. Is it a different one? I hope so. All
right. I need 10,000. I think it's time to upgrade some of these. Let's get,
let's do this up. This is the wraith upgrade. Let's see what happens. Going in the portal. No,
deciding against it. Where's purple going? My buddy perp. The one issue that I have is I,
can I kill lots of zombies with just seven vampires? I'm not sure I can. I know I
can do this. Let me do this first. Everybody collapse on the goblins. Hello. Death. Hurray.
Nice job. Give me that. One way exit. One way entrance. Where the hell is all this stuff
going? They're everywhere. I feel like I'm in the arcane sanctuary. What the hell else is
even over here? Let's see if I can do it. I mean, they're pretty sloppy, but I don't
have enough to do any of this. We just have to fly over there and what's your speed? Four.
I should kill you very quickly. Three zombies perish. I don't think so.
Fifteen. No, I'm gonna lose. It's only maybe. Maybe. If I can keep healing, maybe.
I don't think I'm gonna do it. I can't heal. Yeah, I cannot steal life from dead things.
Yep. Well, this was a mistake. Can't heal from the undead. I didn't even know that.
I just didn't realize that. I know I said I wasn't gonna save scum anymore,
but I am. I'm kind of just fucking stuck back here. I'm stuck back here. I don't have enough to do
anything. Can I like make my way over to purple? Do I have any way to get back to purple?
I really don't think I can go anywhere. Let's see what happens if I go this way.
Is there a place to go down here maybe? Can I build anything? What day is it? Day five.
Hall of Darkness. Six thousand. I'll save it so we can get the growth. One way entrance.
Should I just go in this shit? I'm gonna end up somewhere. I'm gonna end up with like a wall.
I can't even move any further. Maybe it'll be this one. That's the hope, right? Red's coming
over to blue. Red and blue teammates. Let's go back. Power liches. I think I want to get that.
Do I need another castle? Do I need more money? Yeah. Well, let's see. Let's go next week.
Or almost next week. Cross your fingers. Three, two, one. Yes.
I'm fine. Hooray. Thank god. All right, here comes the growth. Before that happens though,
can I get a Hall of Darkness? I cannot, but I can upgrade the mausoleum so power liches
are available. 11, 15, 40. 11, 13, 30. Okay, cool. Let's go. Red has taken over that castle.
It's orange. I haven't seen orange the first time. There's orange right there.
Not very much. And it's empty. All right. Let's get power liches. Actually, no. Let's do
vampires first. I need to go down. No, you need to go back and get like minions. I have
seven fucking things. This other guy's coming up. You've got enough to do something.
Head down. I can start clearing this shit out and actually taking this stuff and then meeting
down with purple here. Let's just go here. No money. You come down here. So let's get these.
Lots of walking dead. Do not engage. That's all I can really do this week.
Don't. He's coming down. Shit. Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. What's he coming down with?
Pack, few, few, several, lots. No, horrible. By the time he gets here, I'll have a force
and he won't be able to get it. I highly doubt that. I think I can get this one too.
Think about engaging. Why would I? It's just free stuff. Lord of Halflings. Let's see what
happens. Here he comes on his way. You're going to be throwing shit. So might as well just fly
over there. You're going to be throwing shit. Ares isn't helping. He's kind of just doing his
own thing down there. I'm not sure he's seen any action at all. I've had like two or three
encounters, which I started at the bottom. I started at the bottom where I got all the stuff
and nobody fought me. No, it's still all right. I'm not like in a great position, but
I mean, what am I going to do? What am I going to cry about it? What am I going to cry?
Lots of hobgoblins. Let's do these first. Six power liches. That's all I can do for now.
I can do some skeletons. I'm afraid of you. I don't think you're going to come over here
though. I could be wrong. I don't think that one has very much stuff though.
All right. Purple. You're fucking walking in circles. Yeah, this is not very much. That's
decent. I might take it. I might go for it. Pack a few, few lots of pixies though.
Let's do this down here first. Some wood down here. Hobgoblins.
Should be easy enough. Pixies of skeleton fuel. Yeah, that's true.
Wood. Campfire. 100 bucks. I'll take it. Pack of zealots. All right.
Pack, pack, few. I think it's time to attempt something here. I can get a couple more.
At least fill up a little bit. It's time to defend the home. The only dangerous thing here
is this. Meteor shower. I can hit up both, except that's ice. I should hit these two down
here. Air. Sprites. He is like made out of fire. I'm probably going to do it down here.
I can't hit him with any spells. I think I should just do it up here.
Might as well. That's fine. Do you have ranged? No, you don't. Anybody have ranged.
None of you have ranged. So let's hang back for a minute. That's your speed. Six.
Six. Get rid of you. This should be pretty clean. Should get first attack advantage on
everybody here. I wonder if I should go just focus on the fire elemental with the
air elemental. Fire elemental. No retaliation. That's good. Yeah, get rid of the elemental.
I really want to get rid of the skeletons, apparently. Well, whatever you do,
you're dead. Let's go with the 20 of the pixies.
Instantly kill it. You're now surrounded. Don't fucking retreat. I was trying to stop that
from happening. Retreated. Dick. I'm taking that castle. I'm going up right fucking now.
That castle is going to be mine in a second. Purple, come up. What do we got down here?
I don't care about that. Hoarder gremlins. I can handle the Hoarder gremlins.
This should be very easy. At least I hope so. Purple's gonna have a huge army.
Yeah, by the time this all is over with, I should have done that. Sorry.
I'm just being the wall right now. I'm just trying to protect everything and try to stop
them from encroaching while Purple gets five million people in his army. Okay, here we go.
Expert necromancy. I want that. And I want the bank. Can't move. Capital. I'm gonna wait.
Don't go in there! Blue's dead. Did Purple just take another castle that wasn't
a neutral castle? There ain't much in here, man. I think I can do it. I'm not as well
to take it. I think I'm gonna be just good. We found a naga bank. Do you wish to attack
the guards? 42, 8, 16, 10. Red has another guy right there. Yeah, Red does have another guy.
Ooh! New castle! I just have to go through the imps. Shit! Okay, things are looking up.
And I'm gonna get a capital. Tans down there. Come on, Purple, keep building. So this is just
a random castle. Can I- do I have enough to take it? I think I do. Do I though? It might
not be. I think I can get it. Let me just make sure- let me just put it in a safe point.
Oh, I thought it was a castle. What is it with this? I thought it was gonna have like a
to-lay siege. It doesn't have a fort. Okay. Well, all right, I'll do it. At least I have
another castle now. I got it. The castle is mine. Perfect. Now let me look up here.
You've left a little bit. This is still down here. He just came out. He was inside.
I'm never gonna get two birds with one stone here. I'm gonna hang out in there for now.
Is he just hanging out in there? Basic resistance or advanced intelligence?
I'm gonna say advanced intelligence. Build a fort. Five grand! How much are these worth?
I can take them all, right? I don't think I even want these things. Well, I mean,
I just got more people. I'm gonna claim some stuff.
Horde of royal griffons. Experience. Okay, this is the point when I decided this is worth
doing. I might be wrong. Just learned fireball. He doesn't even have a fort! He doesn't
have a fucking fort built! What? Why? I got this in the bag. I can take out the...
Yeah, I can probably melt almost all of them. Good. Right off the bat. Go down here. No,
let's go... Yeah, down here. That's fine. Skeletons. I'm gonna stay together. Who is
the threat? Nobody has ranged. I'm just gonna go after you, because you're the strongest.
Bullshit. Didn't you go three fucking times? Fireball? No. Stone skin. Shield.
Magic. It's just stone skin. This is technically melee, right?
All right, surround him. He's not gonna be able to do anything. I guess he is.
Sorry. I'm gonna get it. Focus on the one that we're focusing on.
Now you decide to come over here. I can't attack. Whatever. Just get him.
You really want to get these liches, huh? Should I just run?
Should I just fucking run away? No, I can kill him. He's not gonna retaliate.
This should be it. Castle's mine. 660s? What do you... Oh, it was Luna. I remember Luna.
Basic Scholar! Trading spells between spellbooks or advanced earth magic. Probably
advanced earth magic. Dude, that's... This is fucking two castles in 15 minutes. And I can
get some more creatures. How do you not have a fort? Interesting. All right, well...
Park here for a second. So I got one, two, three. I got three castles now. This one is
down here. All right, I got my buddy going down here. That's our end of our turn. Red's
probably pissed. Purple stills just stop piling. Massive amounts of money. Expert offense!
Oh, we're basic ballistics. I probably would do offense. I just want to be able
to do damage, man. Lots of familiars and horde of harpy hags. I got a pretty decent
army here. Let me go up here though. I need a city hall. Or I need a fort. Five grand? 2020?
I need another hero. Probably just from here. Look at all this. There's so much here.
There's my tavern. Death knight or witch? I mean, I have like three death knights.
I have the... am I supposed to do super necromancer? No, for a second I was like,
what's with the second photo that was taken? That person just lifted their arm up and you
took like three photos at the same time. Just like click click click. Okay, how we doing?
Purple, how we doing? Purple's got lots of shit down here. They still have that. Bastards.
It's time to come out. I'm coming out. Fort. I'm coming out. We're gonna get rid of these
pixies. And there's a bank right there. Orc chieftain. Let's go up. There's a learned land
mine that's good. What's this over here? All right, I think I can take these people on. But
I would just save them just in case something fucking horrible happens. Third level spell.
Murph. Lots of gnolls. Take them easily I think. Show Otto's feet.
Didn't we talk about this like already like a few weeks ago? Yeah, Kim like wrote that and
then it did the the fucking lid blew off. Ban that person. Well, it was my girlfriend.
So Kim's banned. That's who it was. Ban that person. And go. Holy shit. You guys,
I'm not strong. You guys are not strong at all. You're not strong to a point where I'm
embarrassed for even coming over here with the wolf riders. Jeremy, we're gonna get banned to
the couch. Prison. In a dazzling display of daring, you break into the local jail and
free the hero imprisoned here who in return pledges loyalty to your cause. What? Level five,
Malcolm. I got a new hero. Sick. Oh, that's so cool. And I'm at the end down here so
there's nothing else to claim. Court of Harpy. What's their speed? They can go pretty far.
I'm gonna just wait for them. I don't think you can go that far. They're all going down.
Why are you all going down? All of you are going that way? Uh oh. Every single one of
them is. I might, I might run backwards. I did not expect every single one of them to
come down here and get a fucking line. Uh. Shit. I'm gonna fly away with the uh.
I think I have to fly away. I don't have meteor on this character. This character doesn't
have it. I'm screwed. I mean I have 82 skeletons up here but every single one of them flew down
three. Like what the hell is this? This is bullshit. It's what it is. Um. I just sent
people. Whatever. What am I gonna do? Run? I mean I think I am. Am I stand and fight
or do I fly back here to the friends? I think I'm going back to the friends.
Yep. 82 skeletons coming in. Go. What is this dog shit? Why do they get it like every time?
Walls. Get him down here. Just wait till my big brother shows up. And oh why don't you go again?
Just go again. Why don't you just go again? I don't think I've seen that spell on my character in
like fucking a week. Well now I'm gonna head back this way. I just didn't expect this shit.
This is somewhat like kind of dumb fucking strategy that the computer decided to do right
now. How could I have ever expected that this was gonna happen? Get in here. This
necklace better be fucking worth it. All right we're in. I hate these things so much.
One of you die. Jesus. Tally it and kill it. This is so stupid. The idiocy involved in how
this played out. This is dumb. We're in the fucking corner. This is as far in the corner
with everybody. What the hell? I'm gonna hopefully I get a bunch of skeletons for this.
If I lose this, I don't even know man. I'm gonna fucking lose my mind if I don't win this.
No there's no way. I'm gonna win. Thanks for the artifact. Five percent more damage or what?
I mean that's better. Wisdom or spell? I need more spells. I don't have any.
What is it? I can't even look at it. Fucking hell. That fight sucked.
Tan's coming down. Necklace of Dragon Teeth. Please that would be worth something.
Warn about the neck. This item increases your knowledge and power skills by plus
three. That's actually really good. That's really good actually.
I'm not upset by that. I'm actually very happy about that. Now I don't have enough
to get this and I don't think he does either. A horde of... Do I really? I think I have to
come back at another time. Maybe I could combine them together and I could take this.
I could give him the centaurs and orcs. That's like 50 to 100 frogs. No I can't. It's not
gonna happen. Not with like this tiny little group. Let's plant this hero up here. Save
game. Yes I will. I wish it wasn't gonna be like this but it is. What is up here?
Earth elementals. Artifact. Spirit of oppression versus a horde of harpy. I don't
want to fight harpy hags again but I think I'm about to. Am I about to fight a horde of
harpy hags again for another? All right what can I do here? You're ready to come out.
What? In a second. Now you are. No you're not. I want you to get more. I'm gonna put the
dwarf in that building. I'm getting awfully closer. Can I... This is not gonna be good.
He's gonna take the castle probably. I'm fucked. Well just take this and whatever. He's...
I can get it right back. Like what am I gonna do? There's no fort. Yeah he's gonna have to
build a fucking fort. We'll just keep moving on. Little doggie. I think that's Midas. I don't
think that's Otto. Can I do anything else? Hold on let me be right back. Let's see if
something else is like going on. Hold on. Be right back. I have no idea. Midas was just
barking it. A ghost? I don't know. Maybe it was a skeleton. Hmm. All right do I want
you or you? Well I need to... Here. You go here. Okay. Just take this castle while I stare at you.
He doesn't really have that much either. That's the thing that sucks is he just he's
gonna just walk in and take it and then I'm gonna take it back. This is gonna be so dumb.
No he decided against it. He's coming down this way now. Good because now I'll just kill
him. All right purple I'm gonna need you to start swooping around the other side
to stop collecting resources and get over here. Several lots pack several. Who's dead?
26 18 8. I think that's enough. Purple doesn't give a shit about me. I know that's it that's
what like get over here. Kill something. Fight something. You just what are you doing with
this thing? Look at all this around you. You look at you look how many enemies you have.
Wait let me look at these heroes. All right really dude get over here. Orange is just in
your base. I'm going down there. I gotta find a way to get over there. You're right you've been
hiding over here too haven't you? See look I'm just they're attacking me and he's just
collecting fucking. This guy's just hiding back here. Pack lots lots several. God damn
it. I should just stay in the damn castle right? I mean I'm gonna upgrade the I'm gonna
upgrade this. Turn the skeletons into skeleton warriors. Can't do it yet. Well let's just
continue what I was doing here. You go in here. Park yourself that way. I don't have any money
to do anything. I would like for you to get back in here. Collected that thing. Yeah and
then maybe I'll go in that portal. Hang out in here for now. We're gonna be a turtle for a
minute just because of what's going on over here. Lord of swordsmen. Lots of walking dead.
I can't really do anything though. The dwarf will come out and take care of that
tomorrow. We're both just standing here. Purple are you just gonna let him do this?
He's picking strawberries. Well everything is taken from him. I don't think I can beat
the hellhounds. More vampires. That's all I can do at the moment. I need more like money
making castles. All right next thing I'm gonna do is I'm gonna make some more citadels.
Or some more money. Like a town hall. Yeah okay I need a tavern. Tavern town hall down here.
Man am I gonna buy this game? Oh I hope you do. Purple what the fuck are you doing?
They brought the... Purple is gonna lose. I hope you do. It's really really good. It's
a really fun game. It's super fun. Super interesting. It's very very good. I might be
able to get this castle if I try. Am I using the HD mod? Yes I am. This is the original
one from good old games with the complete pack and the HD patch on top of it. I'm gonna
stick with the plan. I'm gonna buy the tavern and then so I could get to the town hall
to make money. I don't know what is left over here. I'm gonna fortify and I'm gonna
come up and kill this guy. Some more liches. Skeletal warriors. I can't.
I think I can kill him right now. I think so. He's not gonna come in the face. I know
that for a fact. Several lots. Several. Yeah he's dead. He doesn't have fucking anything.
Let's get rid of the ranged which is who does more damage? Six to eight and three five.
Let's cast this on you. Try to get rid of you first. I mean like let's go.
Here. Perfect spot. Thanks for going there. Just helped me out so bad. It is a very timeless
game. It is and even though I mean I'm not necessarily like that great at it.
It's just interesting. It's fun. I never really liked games like this. Games with tile based
movement and strategy management. It's not really my type of game but it just is fun.
It's something about it. You know the movement. It's that movement I really like.
Oh my god. Speaking of the movement. I tried to fucking. Hey making a good point for the game
here right now. It's all good. I think I can get in here and do this too. So there goes one.
It's tan. I'm just gonna save it again. I think I can handle this. No I can't. I don't
have any confidence. All right well that gets tan out of here. You need to keep going this way.
What's down here? Is that a peak? Lizard warriors? I can get this stuff. I just need a
pyro that can do it. You. Or you up here. One of you do it. One of you do something.
All right. Harpy hags. After I. You understand? Red just came through again.
I don't know what my teammate is doing. Horde. I wonder if it's enough. There's a fort here right?
Fuck. There's no fort. I don't have a fort. I might as well just walk out and fight him.
He might not even come after me though. And then I'm gonna make the stroll this way.
All right. From here I'm taking. I'm taking these guys out to the right. I'm going for it.
Let's gonna start the journey now. Or maybe I'm gonna. No I'll meet. Where's my other dude?
Yeah you. We're gonna trade here. Trade places. You head into the.
Into the castle. You're gonna help this way. I gotta at least stop moving around man.
All right. This is a decent force. What was I gonna. What was I gonna do here?
No it's down here. A town hall. Right. Town hall. Town hall. Town hall. Town hall. Town hall.
Tomorrow. Tomorrow. Town hall tomorrow. Who's this? Oh fuck. They caught me.
Um. I could just retreat. Yeah. It's not worth it. I'm out. It's not worth it.
That sucked so bad because he didn't have anything. He had like five units.
Keep going this way. I'm not going in there. Coward streamer. Tonight yes.
Phone's ringing now. Hold on a second. What is happening in this household? Okay hi. We're
under attack here. Okay you know when you like investigate. You're like what's happening outside?
You like open up. There's nothing there. Had to let somebody in. We're under attack.
Imagine like opening the door. You think like somebody's out there. Like oh like the dog's
barking. Let me like. We're under attack. You swing the door open. You scream that outside.
It's like a mailman. Hey here's your mail. Oh thanks. Thank you. So let's go. Let me
make it a big picture here. I need a big picture. No you open the door and it's a knight in armor
screaming we're under attack. Uh I would close the door. I'd close the door and I would just
get the phone as fast as I could and dial diamond money as fast as possible and be like
this somebody hit me out of their mind and I think they're going to fucking come after me.
You need to die. No no no no no. Do everything that you're supposed to do.
Town hall. Yes town hall gives me money. Oh shit you can't see. Now you can. That's what I wanted
to do. I don't have any more leftover money. I guess I could buy a little bit of stuff just
in case somebody decides to come to the castle. You're over here. All right I've got to stop
moving people around. You come out. Is there anybody around here? I don't think there is.
You're just gonna go into this fucking portal. Well should I leave him just to defend? You've
got a lot of people though. Maybe not. Maybe not. I got a scout. I have somebody guarding here. I
have nobody in this one but I have somebody about to be building up in here. Those fucking
harpies. Yeah go kill it. I think I can kill them right? I'm just scum. Put it again.
Part two. I like shouldn't have even done this but it is the other hero so that's good.
I'm gonna get slaughtered. I don't know. I'll be all right. I'm not. I ain't gonna move.
Bunch up again please. I hope you do. Bunch up down here. Oh please do it. Let's go right here.
Can German still run at 60 miles per hour? Yeah I think so. I ain't gonna go in. Actually
yeah I am. I'm going on this one. This is going for the uh the genie. Of course do it again.
By all means just go twice. Harpies. All right let's move in. One of these guys.
So there is an artifact behind. I wonder what it is. I will do a single target move on you.
I don't think it's necessary to do anything else. Like for instance we could do ice bolt
on you. No on you. Harpy's dead. It's gonna be decent experience and I'll get the artifact
behind. It should be good enough. At least I think it will. Save. Save. Save. 1200 experience.
1300. No level up but I get this stuff. Spirit of oppression. I can't get it yet but you know
what I mean. That was a plane taking off apparently. We're under attack. Guys like
flying around and take a fucking plane. Yeah it's a one seater plane. Why am I still
streaming? Have I lost my mind? What? It's only been like six and a half hours. It's not been
that long. This is it. After this. This is it. I gotta get a victory here. All right there you
are. We're good. Next day. I'm looking for a collapse from purple. Or can I like to steal
resources? Can I have resources? I can. Right we're on the same team. Can I like take money
from you? Wait why can... Am I using my money for this? Wait a minute. I can make heroes
and use them from odd. Okay well we have a lot of territory. 2000 seagulls saved and that's
when the command gets deleted. Command's gonna get deleted. Horde of sprites. Uh horde of gnolls.
Just head through here. School of magic. Plus one spell power. This is leading us down here
Is it Pandora's box down here? What is it? Spirit of oppression. This item negates all
morale bonuses during combat for both you and your opponent. That is not that good.
But I will take more of these air elementals. What about earth elementals? Lots of earth.
Maybe they'll join me. You think it's a scenario where they'll join? I'm not gonna. Come on.
That's imp cash though. That sounds good. What do we got down here? I have like a fort here,
right? Capital. Okay I need a capital. Do I not have a capital yet? How the fuck have I not
had a capital? City. I don't have a city hall here. All right I need to fuck the city hall.
Tan orange red? Who's left? Well that's all. You screwed down there.
This guy right here is so just I can kill him if I really wanted to. Let's do a ice bolt.
Kill him is weak. I will after I do this. Fly on over here.
Skeletons are just gonna be targets here. So he will kill him, they will kill them,
and this guy will just walk around with a broken foot. Not a big deal. Spell power
plus one. Advanced wisdom or basic scouting. I'm gonna say advanced wisdom which leads us to this
imp cash. We're gonna attack the imps. Perhaps. Let's see what's in there. I might not have enough
to do this. I'm kind of too spread out. It's too thin. I'll try it though. Yeah this is not
bad. Let's do ice bolt on you. Yeah they'll die in one hit or maybe two hits.
We'll make it. So there'll be money in here probably hopefully.
Games are always wins. Yeah they kind of are. These area elementals are pretty good.
This is a pretty good skeleton bait though. Like 160 something like that.
Gives me a pretty decent amount.
2008. Yeah. Hope you guys enjoy it. Hope you enjoy the seagull command there.
Because it's being deleted. It's being deleted. When you hit this, when you hit the year.
Two thousand bucks in four mercury. Pretty good. So I have explored that. I got the money.
Okay let's head back in here for now. Now I'm gonna take you down five gold.
Plus one spell power and uh what do I have for any people here?
Yep. Don't engage. Take the free spell. Whatever it is. Water walk. There's not
really any water here. What does it do? Walk across bodies of water. It's cool.
I'm glad I came all the way down here for that. All right. I got 8,000. City hall needs
level marketplace. Blacksmith. What else do I need here? Resource silo. One ore. I don't
really need it. Upgrade the graveyard. Darkness. All right. Black Knights.
Black Knights are now available here. Recruit some. 2012. We're almost at 2019.
And then it's gone. It's getting deleted. Here what does this have? City hall.
I need five thousand. For this to be a city hall I need a fort. I need to turn that into a
fort first. You're kind of coming in here and taking all my shit. Who's in here? Lots. Pack.
Lots. Several. This guy's dead. If he stays where he is. Someone's coming up here.
You're killable. Oh my god. Just get out of here and kill him. He's so weak. All right. I don't
want them to retreat so I need to get in a position where I can kill them both very quickly.
Don't retreat. Okay. So let me think about this. If I shoot this guy and he's dead and then
I... I'm gonna say like magic arrow should kill him or magic arrow on them. Health five. Health
ten. I'm gonna be just be sure. I'm gonna do ice bolt. Got it. What'd you have? Artifact. Magic.
That was... Tan was coming to try to take the castle because he didn't have anything.
Tan was essentially the guy out in the desert crawling in the sand.
Please. Water. Water. And I just fucking threw a dart at him. And he had magic missile on him.
Great. Well, I don't really know who's left. Purple has kind of gone up here and around.
It's red and orange. I think I can wipe you out here too. I think I can. Nobody in here.
Look at all. I got so much money. I gotta get some people in here because if he comes over,
let's collapse on him. But like, fuck you. You're not taking all this stuff. This is all mine.
There he goes. He's not going in the castle. Hurry. Hurry. I don't need to hurry. You got
20-20. Oh well. Whatever. He ain't going in there. He'll die. He's got dog shit defense.
There's a fort here, right? Yes. I think we're getting close to winning the game.
I did a lot of work this time. A lot. I was making sure I was stopping people. I was
conquering. I was attacking. Purple was just getting resources and running around in circles.
I did a lot of work this time to a point where I'm very proud of what I've been able to
accomplish here. Okay. Let's go and kill this guy. How many heads need to roll here? Can I
do it? I'm gonna be blocking the path, right? And he can't go anywhere. Get him dead. Get
him. Oh, I'm gone. Forget about these artifacts. I need to get up here and continue to win the
game. Next day. Clean this guy out. Orange still has a bunch of shit. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Orange is right up my front door. Where is this orange? Is Purple being destroyed?
How did you get here? What is he doing? Yeah, it's red and orange versus me and
Purple. That's who left. That's it. And he's just not doing anything. This is a decent force.
Like, what are you doing up in the snow? You need to get down here. I'm getting
swarmed by both of them at the same time. I can't kill them both. I can't do this both.
I'm gonna die here. Well, we're gonna fireball. Can I get the other one? No.
I did a lot of work this game. Even when you're on your own,
Ares still fucks you. We're supposed to be on the same damn team. That's definitely what he did
the other game, too. He's just avoiding all conflict somehow. I don't want a retreat
scenario, so let me see here. Can I kill them all quickly here? He's gonna retreat. Not
gonna be enough. Here he goes. No, he's not leaving. Let me kill you. Come on. I still
have plenty of people to do turns. Come on. I'm gonna lose this fucking castle up here.
He's gonna take it for free. Purple's just scratching his ass. No, I can't go down there
and take that. I can't. How do I get down? I gotta get down there somehow.
It's through one of these portals, I think, or through here. I didn't, like,
do anything down here. I didn't have enough money. I think this is another loss.
Did Orange take the Psyquops castle? No, he's about to. Just head in here. I gotta refill some
people. Hang out in there for a day. He's gonna take it. Where's Purple? There he is. He took
it. He just killed Purple. Purple just died. One of his guys just died. He's got nothing.
Purple is now worthless. Dude, like, can I just, like, come take these? I can't even.
Can you deliver them to me? Just deliver them to me, please. So I have a chance here. I could
probably get... What do you have for enemies? All right, here's what we're gonna do. You ready
for this? We're gonna do a little consolidation here. Who has the best... Who's the higher level?
Level nine versus level one. Yeah, just give everybody to him. Pull out some more skeleton
warriors and let's just go kill him. Let's try to kill him. Take the castle back.
He's right up here. I will win this fight. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. That's a good idea. The
butterflies are not worth having. Let's see. Is Purple about to be deleted? And then I have
to fight versus... Is it gonna be 2v1? That's Ares right there. Where'd he go? Where's Ares?
I just saw him. Where'd he go? Where'd he go? No, that's Gem. And I'm gonna upgrade the
butchers. Just right here. Upgrade graveyard. There we go. All right, this is the force to take
the stuff back and keep everything. Hoard, hoard. He's going for this castle. He's gonna...
Let him do it. Let him go die. He actually did it. Okay, so that's weak because those were
like 10 or 15 cyclopses. Yeah, I'm gonna take the box. Give me the box. Give me the box.
Give me the box. Several lots. Give me the box. Open the box. Oh, that's 10,000 experience.
He didn't even care. All right. Expert earth magic. Expert wisdom. Expert necromancy.
Anti-magic. Should I take it? Lots, lots. Hoard packs several. I think I can do it.
I don't think this has a... I did it. I'm gonna get it. Anti-magic. Protects the select
unit from all spells. Now let's meteor shower right here. That'll hit the... It'll be good
down... Yeah, right here. It'll hit the three of it. Should kill that. Almost. Close enough.
All right, get fucking pumped up, boys and girls. Let's go. Target number one. Top and
bottom. I'm on it. Roger that. This is priority now. Wow, that did a lot of damage.
Wow! I'm so... I'm way too excited for this. You got a cool walking sound.
Really? You guys can handle that. I'm gonna say... Let's get up here.
No. They're in the back line. Get rid of this and heal that up.
Skeletons, that's fine. You don't stand a chance. All right. I am gonna fly up here.
I'm gonna take out the... I'm gonna try at least to get rid of this. Not bad. These
glitches do so much damage to the air. I own so much property over here it's kind of ridiculous.
Do some ice bolt just for fun. Let's go. Heroes of might and monopoly.
He hasn't retreated yet. He can't retreat. He's in the castle. Where are you gonna
retreat to? Now I just scared the shit out of myself. Can he run away? He didn't have anything.
Advanced offense or basic tactics? Um... offense. I got it. I got the thing and I took over the
castle. But it doesn't really matter if I've get... You need to pull some weight here.
Honest to god. You gotta start to pull weight. You're starting to get a little sloppy.
Need a marketplace. I can't do everything purple. Okay, he actually took that.
Come on. Good. This doesn't have anything. Look at how fucking shitty this is.
I need a town hall. I need a tavern. Well, might as well just get in. No, I don't even need to.
All right. Next, we're gonna do a mage guild and then I'm gonna make this a town. What
about over here? Power liches. Lots of power liches. These artifacts over here though.
I'm gonna claim some of this stuff because I don't want you to have it. Purple coming in.
Let's get this stuff back in our name.
Artifact. Amulet of the Undertaker. Lots of power liches. Build that. City hall.
More income. More income. More income. Well, I think I can definitely take them. I think
lots of liches. You're right here. You're not that strong though.
You're not gonna be able to get it with what you have here. I highly doubt that.
No, he doesn't have enough to attack. He has like, he doesn't have any people.
I could kill him with just like four black knights. All right, I'm gonna go for it.
I'm gonna go in. Power liches. 22. That's a lot, but hopefully the artifact's worth it.
What are they immune to? What do they hypnotize? Won't affect anybody.
Fireball. Meteor. Fireball is 75. I think it's still Meteor. Forgetfulness. Half of the selected
enemy unit forgets to use their ranged attack. You can't do it. I'm just going for damage.
This is ranged, so we're just gonna get in. Blind makes him unable to move. This is already
not off to a great start, but I hope that artifact is worth getting. Good. Let's go with
another. Let's go to Fireball. Meteor. I'm gonna go back in the house anyways.
Just do a bunch of damage. I'm gonna lose a lot, but it's okay. We're almost actually at the end
game, I think, here. What is it? Amulet of the Undertaker and the Golden Bow. All right. What
about the neck? This amulet increases your necromancy skill by five percent. And then the
That's not that great. That's all right, I guess. He's not going to attack.
They're just so all over the place. I'm gonna lose because Purple's not fucking doing anything.
Purple, they're all over here. What are you still doing up there, Purple?
Just get over here. That's actually incredible. That's fantastic, actually.
Let's get back in here. All right. Did I do this? This is done. Capital. Cannot build a capital yet.
I have... I need a capital. What should I make the capital? Probably this. Yeah.
Ten thousand gold? That's the capital. I need a mage tower.
Don't come over here. Soon 20 bone dragons. It's possible. Purple has entered the server.
Here he is. Oh, great. You have five dwarves, nine riders, and 47, like, dirty, like,
peasant people with pitchforks. Does anybody... You have to have a hero that has something,
right? That's who you send all the way over here. He's probably coming over to look for
food. Hey, we're on the same team. Could I like bum a couple of cigarettes off you?
Oh, get out of here. Okay, see you later, man. This sucks. I'm just gonna bring him down here.
It's almost like I should build this up. Cliff nest, I guess. I'm gonna just build...
Let's build some of this. I can do the citadel, the capital up here in a minute.
Imagine blaming your team in a single player game. Well, they haven't... He hasn't done
anything. He's just died. He's supposed to be really good. Oh, you took a castle.
Good job. Take that one too. Which castles did you take? That's default enemies. Why is it...
He's still got, like, default enemies. When I'm playing against him, he's impossible to overcome.
When I play with him, he's still using default fucking vampires. I mean, I'm just so fucking
upset about this. I'm so upset about these things. Well, it's time just to stockpile.
Upgrade you guys. Not bad. I was supposed to turn this into a
capital. See you next week. Good job. You did great. I'm very proud of you. You just...
Nice work. I can't wait to get the inevitable purple has been deleted from the server.
Gremlin population's double. It's all over the place now? Okay. 4500. I need to start
making other stuff too, though. I need, like, a hall of darkness. I need a capital building!
I'm going in here. When was the last time I saved the game? Oh my god, what am I doing?
I'm so upset. I did not... I, for some reason, I don't... I didn't... What the fuck did I do
that for? It's okay. I can still do this. Health. They don't have very much health.
I am going to bloodlust. I don't have bloodlust. Hypnotize. That's not going to affect anybody?
Holy shit. Hayden Clipfell just gave $115. Thank you so much for the 115 bucks. That's a
ton of fucking money. Uh, they say hello, good night. Thank you. That's an insane amount
of money. Thank you so much. Thank you for the fucking 115. It's not as scary as I thought
it was going to be. Let's collapse on the... Go forward. Yeah, this is not bad. This is going
to be fine. I was scared for a second. I don't know why. I just... I keep thinking
they're like dragons, but they're not. Uh, let's go up here.
Just griffins. These two can handle it.
15, 13. There. And this is probably going to be it. I probably build a, uh,
have a griffins now, right? That's a good amount of experience. Expert offense of basic fire.
I think expert offense. Having defeated the royal griffins, you just got three angels.
Oh damn. I think I'm... Give up the basic skeletons. I wish I could just... The whites
with the zombies. Two to three, 20 health. Three to five. Yeah. Two to three, 20, five, five.
Yeah, the zombies are worse. Can they just stay there? That's a big waste. Uh, but that... I
mean, this is a really big, powerful enemy. 200 health. Three of them. I can get the zombies
back. You see, I can get them back. Citadel. Don't do that. Angels are worth like 9k,
42 zombies are worth like five and a half k. Yeah. Angels are a little out of place for this army.
They'll be fine. And have you ever heard of like a shadow priest? We're gonna be just fine.
We're gonna win. Can do the market. Market. I need a capital. Give me... Let me get the
capital first. It's just me against the world. Let me get a good look at your army. It's not
that great. Armies really not that good. 8,500. Starting to lose the long game here. Just don't
have enough money. Low morale ogres. I need to get out of the castle and just fucking...
I need to start claiming shit back. This is my stuff. Capital. I'll get a note.
Make this the capital and then I'm good to go. I got... No, I'm gonna stack. This is the guy
that's gonna win. This is my mobile destructive unit. Oh, fuck. He's going for the other
castle. Hey, you could blame this on me. But then I would blame this on Purple. And then
Purple would blame it on nothing because he's not a person. He's not alive. Almost done.
What do we got? Anybody near me? You're down here. I can defend this. This is gonna get this.
I have a fort. I'm gonna sell some shit. I'm gonna at least have something here. Let's get
some rocks. Nah, maybe you'll think twice. I bet you walk up the stairs one at a time.
I'm sorry, but you need to be incorrect on that one. I'm gonna sell some more stuff.
I mean, I have lost every time, but I've had a lot of fun doing it. I will say I've had a lot of
fun doing it. They're just stationing out here. They don't have very much that I could get rid
of both of them. Lots, lots. Pack. They're just very spread out. I just need somebody to help
me here. You're not gonna take this. Not even close. It's not gonna happen. I've got
like an absurd army here. All right, this is the last week. And now I'm gonna go and go
for the kill over here. I'm gonna try to take the capital back up here. First, I want to do this.
Better death knights. I can't do it. One more week and then I'm out. I'm gone. And then I'm
gonna just walk. I'm gonna just chase people down and kill them. I'm turning into a hoarder.
There's two people surrounding his castle. Here we go. Much better. Dread knights. I
can get some more of these. I can get some more skeletons. All right, I'm actually,
I'm gonna leave now. I'm gonna bring the fairies too because I just want them to be bait.
Let's take the kingdom back one at a time here. You down here, I want you to come out.
A throng of swordsmen. Let's get over here. Get bone dragons or I will be mildly disappointed.
Don't worry, you won't be disappointed. Well, you may be, you will. Because I might not get
not enough. Ha ha. That's not enough. Rock. Some tree back. I can't swing. That was a mistake.
I can't, well I guess I'm gonna get the dog. I guess about the dwarf. Just get in there and
maybe he'll swing at you. 21, 18, 60 versus 18. Five. Everyone's surrounding you. I can't get
in there. I guess you level them up. This is of course like combat he's seen. Basic scholar.
Basic heir. Probably heir. Can't fire here. We'll get that later. I'm out for blood right now.
Like pure total hatred and vengeance I'm going for. All their armors are not as good as mine.
They're not as cool as mine. They're not as like, handsome as my characters. They're not
as smart as my characters. I don't even, I'm not gonna use a spell that's not even
worth, why would I do that? It's unnecessary. You'll die in one hit. There's no, I don't
even need to do that. All right. Claimed. Again. It's been claimed. Now we're gonna go up.
Several, several, several. What about over here? Several. Right up here. Lots, horde, lots,
throng, horde. We just gotta go straight up. It's now a fort. You. Six of our gold. Can you
handle this? A throng of swordsmen. I don't think you can. Okay, okay. What else am I
gonna do? I want a mage tower. Cover up darkness. No. Convert any creature into a skeleton.
Firebirds. No. Just hang out here because they're gonna come back.
Just convert everybody to skeletons. That'd be insane. Yeah, tomorrow's gonna suck. I'm
not looking forward to tomorrow at all because I have to do the prep tomorrow
and it's absolutely unbearable. It's not gonna be fun. So that's why you're not gonna see
me for like a few days. So I got the prep tomorrow. I've got the procedure the next day and then I'm
probably gonna take another day after that because I'm gonna be on a bunch of drugs today
that day before. Depending. We'll see. I'll keep you updated. Bye. How you doing? You good?
I mean you might as well just take an extra one. You've been in here for a day. Let's go.
Phew. Throng, several, lots, lots. This is gonna be a tough one. It's got dragons though.
Let's get a throng. I think I can do it. Oh, let's go. He only has one dragon.
That's fine with me. I'm gonna kill this one dragon right now with, oh man,
Meteor Shower right here. And I'm gonna kill, watch this. Meteor Shower right in the middle.
That was unbelievable. Then I can kill you with her. That was as perfect as it could have
been. Retaliate. I want you. Yeah, the knights go this way. Take out the Mance Core. Perfect.
Both their strongest units are dead. Just go be bait up here. Perfect. And I'm gonna have you
get down this way. Take out the air. He fled. Damn it. Damn it. What about you,
motherfucker? I'm coming for you. I'm going in that portal. I'm going in the fucking portal.
I'm gonna go kill them. Check this out. I'm going straight in that portal. You think you can run
from me? You can't run from me. I'm gonna go take out Red. Hey, be right back. I'm gonna
go kill Red and wipe him off the map. Head back in there. Let's keep you upgrading.
I'll do here, Citadel. Okay, you're starting to stack up a little.
I'm gonna kill Red. And then it's the two of us versus Orange. We can handle it together.
We can do this together. I just have to do my thing down here. Red does not have another base,
I don't think. I think this is it. I could go up and just remove him. Yep, we're taking
him out one by one. I want them to be... I want nobody to exist. I'm not gonna use any
spells that I need to. This is pathetic. Just get in here. Even if they attack first,
it doesn't matter. I can retaliate and kill them. I've got the burning of a thousand suns in my
blood. I'm going to win this systematically slowly. Yeah, bye. No. This is actually pretty
hard to win because my shit-stained partner is not doing so well. He's doing the best he can.
Yes, but it's gonna be another scenario where I don't... Wait a minute, he just killed somebody.
Here we go. I'm gonna Meteor Shower right here. That's gonna fuck them all up. Beautiful. Now
let's go on the bottom here with the angel. That was a mistake. That was what I wanted to
do, so thanks for doing that. Please. Minimal casualties too. I'll at least go out taking
out red and that's all I care about. I'm going in here. I'm going to give bloodlust
and you're gonna fly in and just kill this right now. What's left? What the hell is left?
We're still alive. Okay, I didn't lose anything. Sorcery or ballistics. I think it's gonna be
ballistics here. Thanks for the castle. I got 53 more skeletons. Oh, I didn't want to do that.
I think that's their only castle. They have seven turns to come and get me.
Good luck. Well, they could try to take this one. Let's see what happens. No,
red has one more up here. You got three... You can get that. Three bone dragons.
They have one more stronghold right there. Hold on a minute. Let me just like fucking
park for a second and like sap you of all your energy. Is this a... Is this a citadel?
It's a good castle. Resource silo mana vortex. Oh yeah, give me that. Park here for now.
I think I can do this. I wonder if I can come out here and just kill him.
Few, few, few. I gotta send the rock down here. Comes. Take him out.
No. Come on. Whack him. Whack him. Another hero done. I wonder if you will retreat.
I hope you don't. I think you can still win. Delusional. Fucking delusional.
Dead. And I got lightning bolt. We didn't have anything?
Advanced air magic allows you here to cast air spells that reduce cost.
Air magic. Let's get back in here. Rest up. I bought everything I can buy here.
I might take you out and send you somewhere, but maybe not yet. This is unguarded.
Protect purple? I mean, where's purple? Purple has one more place. Nothing in it.
He has default enemies in here. I'm gonna lose, but I mean maybe I could at least look
pretty good doing it, you know? If I can stack a ton of people, it might be... Of course you just
leave. Purple? Thanks. Oh, would you know? You would appreciate some gold. Is that what
you'd want? He actually just came in and asked for a cigarette. What the hell are you
gonna spend it on? No, I'm stacking somebody, man. Dragon vault. It's done.
I'm gonna have two stacks. I just got a stacker like the BK stacker. He's dead.
I'm gonna be so hungry. I'm gonna be so hungry. What time is it? 11? Because I can't eat any food
as of tomorrow. He tried to give me his rocks. I don't want his rocks. I want his support
and his fighting power and his help. Yeah, colonoscopy is on Saturday, so
I can't eat any food a day before and it's in the morning. So I have the... My like
last meal is gonna be tonight. So I actually have to go here soon within the next like 40 minutes
because I need to be able to eat something before tomorrow, but I'm not out yet. I can't.
Bone dragon. I just need 15 grand. I'm gonna sell some stuff. No, I don't need to. More.
I don't need to have the super bone dragons. Three regular bone dragons is good
because guess who I'm sending back up there? Me. I'd wrap around this way. Horde. Several pack few.
I don't know if I want to fight this. Give me this castle.
Fuck the resources. Just trying to get bone dragons. He just got the pandora's box. That's
not good. See, I'm getting encroachment here. Take that red castle right now.
Get this red castle. You keep coming over here. Down here. Do I have earthquake? I have meteor
shower. I also have clone. There's a duplicate of the selected unit stack. The image is dispelled
if it is attacked. Oh, that's more like a fire. Armageddon. Brains fire down upon the battlefield
damaging all units. I don't think I want to hurt everybody. That's not it's not time for
Armageddon. Meteor shower. Get this stack right in the middle. I'm gonna kill myself with
Armageddon. Can't get rid of it yet. He might come up and meet me in the middle with this dragon he
will. End it. Perfect. Now they have one ranged. There we go. These are just regular vampires.
There's nothing to be afraid of. Get units that are not affected by magic and use it.
I mean that's we're at the end game here. I'm trying to cycle back around to load up
again on units and then have like an unstoppable force and just run around the
whole map and kill everyone. In here. Locked in. The castle is ours. Inexhaustible cart
of oro. When equipped this cart provides you with an additional one ore per day.
And I got dispelled. Advanced ballistics. Yeah. Thank you for the castle. Too bad you don't
have any goddamn bone dragons in here. Are these advanced bone dragons or are these regular
bone dragons? All right. Hold on. Now I wrap up. Let's go this way then. I got two of these
castles. I'm going this way. I'll take you all out. I can't waste any time here. Purple's
right here with three dwarves. Forget about the resources. I just have to go. I've got a
great army. No one's taking this shit back from me. All right. You want to try? You really
want to try this? Slow. Blind. Blind. To you. On the rocks. Can't do it on the bird.
Now that he can't move now. He's not gonna get it. He's fucked. Damn it. That wasn't it.
That sucks. That's all they got though. This is not that intimidating. I mean they'll
breach eventually here. I can't do it anymore. I can only. That's it. I can't do it anymore.
Back up this way so people don't get stuffed in the corner. All right. I think I'm flying
the dragon over. No. No. I don't think so. Yeah. I got. I'm just gonna use ranged on.
Just get rid of. The towers are taking care of you. On the air. It does a ton of damage to
the air. Oh that hurts. I think it's not. I gotta get out. I can't just sit here all day.
He's gonna do that again. Is that the prison that happened to the unicorn? No.
They can't get in. They're getting hurt by the spikes. I'm gonna kill him eventually here.
Maybe one more. All right. Gates are gonna be breached. Not quite. No. They're gonna
just keep hurting themselves. What the fuck just happened? What was that? Destroy undead?
You are undead. Hold. Just hold. Hold. Is it open? I don't think it's open yet.
It is open. Isn't it? Hold the wall. Hold the wall. Hold the wall. Hold the wall. Hold the wall.
Hold the wall. Oh my god. This can't be. I should have just went out. I didn't think
he was gonna be. It's over. I lost. I did it fucking twice. I just lost. I can't believe it.
I should have just ran out and not held. That's what I should have done.
That's what I should have done. I should have just fucking left and got out and started attacking.
And everybody would have screamed at me if I went out. But you see what happens?
I would have won. Did I save? Well, it doesn't matter. Orange has the entire map.
Purple was fucking walking in circles for the first two hours of the game.
I just lose. I'm supposed to retreat. I don't have armor getting on this guy.
It's a different character. Save scum? No. I actually have to leave here. I have to
clean this up and get out of here. Because I am going to severely fuck up the next three
days if I do not. If I don't eat before 1230, one o'clock in the morning tonight,
I might actually starve. That would not be a good thing. He's got so many, but I still
might be able to. Is there anything else up here? I got that one. Purple's is there. That's mine.
That's his now. I'm going to try to take this. I've got a lot of money. So here,
let's stock up on you. There's like nobody even in here. It's kind of a lost cause at
the moment, to be honest. Spend some money. Make this the new fucking capital.
Got a new hero in there too. He just came into my house. Does he even have one left? He's like,
I guess I'll stop in yours. That sounds fun. All right. This is like the big fight here
because this is going to be it. This is going to be the one. We got, okay, who's back there?
Meteor Shower. They've really bunched up right here. That didn't hit the,
did not hit you. That's weird. Did I just break it? I think I might've just broken it.
Magic resistance. What was that? Air shield. My priority is going to be the archers here.
Let's fly up this way. And you're going to have to eventually get down here.
Yeah, that's not good. We got to get in there. That was a pretty big hit.
Front door, huh? All right. Well, okay. I really want to fight. I want to bring the whole
fight. Same deal down here. Double it up. Nice. Perfect. It's open. I want bloodlust on you.
That was a huge heal. All right, you take out this last one here. Let's get everybody
into the wall now. Get right up in there. We should be able to get this last hit.
You walked right into the 224 skeletons. That was a bad idea.
What's that? He teleports the people? Leave the dwarves alone. Oh, poor dwarf. Batters,
it's already open. He killed that. All right. Dwarves, we're going to now have to deal with
this. I want to do second of the lightning bolt, anti-magic, landmine, ice bolt. I'm
probably just going to do fireball up here. Are you magic resistant? Yeah. Aura of magic
resistance. It might be just lightning bolt. I don't know why I just did that.
I just went Australian for a minute. I think you're the threat here. Centaurs.
Should be good to go. I don't go after the unicorn yet. Good. There's the unicorn.
Walking to the path is the... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Seven of you. Get out of my way. Suicide dwarves. Pretty good battle.
Seagulls are growing stronger. All right, I'm going to get this castle. Sword of Hellfire.
This right-hand weapon increases your attack skill by plus six and sacrifice. Holy shit.
What a sacrifice. Who cares about the one oar? Lightning bolt. No, I don't care about the oar.
All right. What does this do? Sacrifice. Destroys a friendly creature group in order
to resurrect a dead group. Number of resurrected creatures depends on the
caster's spell power and the health of destroyed stack. Jesus. All right. This was
a big deal. There's no more towns up here. Are you going to get this?
Go get it. Go get that town. That's Red's last town. Please just go get it and eliminate Red.
Oh my god. You are so dumb. Why is the computer so dumb on my team?
Can I make you do that? Oh my god. What have you done?
Unfortunately, I have to go. I got to get out of here, guys. I'm sorry. I have to eat
something before it becomes too late. So you will see me. Oh, I want to just play. I have to eat.
Eat and stream at the same time. All right. Hold on. I'll be right back.
I'm going to get something quick. I'll be right back.
I'm back. I've got bread. I've just gotten white bread. That's all I can eat. I'm addicted.
I'm just addicted. And that's what I fucking do about it.
I'm addicted to the game. I'm addicted to bread. I can't stop eating. I eat a loaf every hour.
I just can't help it. I dunked the bread in the water so I can just like slurp it down.
It's fucked up. All right. I'm going for it. Holy shit. There's a fucking lot of stuff. Yeah.
I'm going to do it. He's going to do it. I don't need any help from anybody.
You're eating soggy bread like a duck. I'm dead. I'm addicted to bread. I can't help it.
I need to eat more bread. Dragon! I hate this unit. I just think it's ugly.
Whatever. Do you eat the first and last slice of bread? Yes, I do.
Why do people not eat those? I don't get it. Why would you not eat the first and last slice
of bread? It's just, it's bread. There's nothing wrong with it. What do you throw it away?
If you throw away, okay, if you throw the first and whatever, I'm dead. Who cares?
If you throw away the first and last piece of bread on every loaf, you took the castle.
This shit's like winnable. I think. Hold on. I have to like go to bed.
One more big battle and I have to get out of here. I really do. I'm too addicted. It's too
much fun. I was going to just eat. Eat real food before you sleep. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I'm
going to regret it. I know. Yeah. All right, guys. I have to do the responsible thing. I
really do. I'm going to be feeling this in like a couple of days and I'm going to be
really upset. I have to, I have to prep for my fucking colonoscopy. I have to do this.
This is like, I don't want to leave, but I have to. I really have to.
Two more rounds. Nobody there. There's nobody here either. There's nobody fucking here.
Go get this one for free. Swarm of those. I have to go back into that thing.
What is that portal? What the fuck? That was stupid. All right. I'm going to save it here.
Game is saved. Thank you for watching. I wish I could go more, but I have to go take care
of some things. There's some specific things I have to get ready for. I have to go eat
something more substantial. I have to go make something. I don't have anything ready to eat
tomorrow morning all the way through into Saturday. I have to take these super laxatives.
I need to be prepared for this. I got to go like get ready. Thank you everybody for watching. I
hope you had fun. This game is really fucking fun and addicting. I'll probably do it again.
We'll probably complete that one and then move on to another game. It's probably what will
happen. The next time you will see me will probably be on Sunday or either Sunday or
Monday maybe. One, two, yeah. I would assume you'll probably see me on Monday.
Wish me luck. I'm a little nervous. I actually am. I am a little nervous
just because there's a couple of reasons why. There's a couple of things.
You know, you have to go get put under. It takes like 30 minutes of them going all inside
of your body and your guts and shit. I've done something similar like it before.
Thanks everybody for watching. We actually don't have very many bits so this is not
going to take very long. I'm going to go through them right now. We're not going to
take any time. We had eight hours ago. God, these might and magic streams are just so long.
Thank you. Jerma lied about Taco Bell for the 250. If you need some energy, Jerma,
just eat a Gordita Crunchwrap Deluxe from Taco Bell. I'm just kidding around, Jerma.
I know there's a really high morality with this kind of procedure so I hope you know
we're all pulling for you on this one. Yeah, I'm just going in to get a couple
things looked at. Eating Taco Bell before colonoscopy. I would have to reschedule it.
There are certain, imagine, what did you eat yesterday? Oh, I had some water,
three cheesy Gordita Crunches, and two Big Macs. Okay, well come back in like,
come back next week and don't do that again. But thank you so much. Thank you Epoxy. 47
dollars from Epoxy. This was way earlier in the stream. I didn't catch it. It was 47
fucking dollars. Just shy of 50 bucks. It's a lot. Hey Jerma, today's my brother's birthday
and him and I both love your content and meet a lot of you wished him happy birthday.
Absolutely. I don't know what your brother's name is but happy birthday Epoxy's brother.
Hopefully it's still your birthday and if it's not then happy birthday after your birthday.
You deserve, you should get two birthdays. Thank you so much Epoxy if you're still here
and happy birthday to your brother. Hope you guys had a good day. Hope you had a lot of
fun. Hope you got him something nice. Hope you got him something nice. Thank you for the 47
dollars. I really appreciate it. Freudian weapon thanks for the 250. Good luck with the procedure.
Thank you. I appreciate it. Thank you so much. I get weirdly nervous before procedures and then
it's weird because I two days before the procedure I'm like really nervous and then
when I get in the doctor's office I'm like I don't care whatever. It's just like the two
days before but thank you. Spicy Pepe thanks for the 250. Hey Jerma, I hope you're doing
well. The streams have been great. I have really enjoyed them. I still think you're the best human
and if chat wants to disagree with me on that just remember it's okay to be incorrect chat.
Thank you. One question. Will you be streaming this year's E3 like you did last year?
Hope the colonoscopy goes smoothly and your couple days to relax go well. Yes if I'm not
at E3 I just I don't have any plans to be but we might last minute decide that we're
gonna go. If not then I will do an E3 breakdown stream. You will get it. I will do those streams
again. They were fun. You will get it again. Thank you so much for the 250. Smelly Boy thanks
for 250. If you were able to have this much fun playing a game like this Civilization is a
total totally a viable game of choice. Civ 5 or 6? I feel like Civilization is a little
more complicated than this. Am I wrong in that? Is Civ 4 or Civ 5? Aren't they a little
more? They take a lot longer and they're a little more complicated. Can't a Civilization game last
like 50 hours? 5 is super easy. Heroes of Might and Magic's a little more chill.
Yeah I think it's just I have this predisposed bias just because of how much I love these games
and how much when I was like a young kind of teenager I played them. The game came out
I think when I was like 14 or 15 or something and I played the other ones before too. I
played Heroes of Might and Magic 2. There's a lot of them. There's like seven of them
and three is really the best one by a general consensus. Three is the best one by a margin
I think. That was 14 yeah? Yep. I love it. I think it's great but Civilization maybe. I
don't know. Probably not though. I don't think it's that kind of game that I would like to
play. Neither was this but I'm biased. Also 250 from Era Paradox. Goodbye and good morning
and goodbye to you too. Thank you for the 250. Let's get those credits rolling. Thank you to all
the subs. All the shit load of you that support this stream every single time. You guys are
fucking incredible. Thank you everybody. You guys rock. I know these last couple streams have been
a little more kind of longer and more about like kind of video game and chiller and not
like a whole bunch of crazy stuff going on but I hope you liked it. I loved it and I'll
see you guys real soon. Thank you so much for your subscriptions. Fred Flintstone. I just
thought of the thing again. I just thought of the thing. I just read fucking Flintstone. What the
hell? Thank you to the polar pair for the five dollars. Not 250. The last bit coming in here.
Hey Jerma. I've been watching your vid since eighth grade. Graduated high school in two
days. Pretty nervous anyway. Love your content. You always kept me laughing when I
was struggling with life. No amount of money can repay you for that. Sorry I couldn't give a bunch
saving for college and all. Oregon State. Oregon State. That's a long time to be watching me.
Eighth grade into graduating high school. Congratulations on that. Hope your week of
finals wasn't too stressful and your week of last week of school. I'm happy to be here. Happy
to hang out and enjoy these things together. You don't have to give me a thousand dollars.
You don't have to give me a dollar. If you do, thank you for that. You don't have to.
I love having a community like this. It's a lot of fun. We have a great time. Save for
college and good luck in the future. Thank you so much for your five dollars. You guys
are awesome. Is it stream legends time or how much time do we have left for stream legends?
Sorry I had to cut us off at the end there. There are things I need to prepare for. I wish
I could have finished that. It would have taken probably like another hour though.
2127. What year are we gonna end at? Seven minutes until I can do stream legends. Oh god.
Really? Let me see. I lost every game. I was really getting into that last one
there just because I started to come back and you just get lost in a game like that. You just
so much fun. Let's see stream legends. I don't understand what it is lately. My extensions
don't load anymore. My extension dashboard. I might have to like refresh these.
Yeah six and a half minutes. No stream legends. Six minutes. No. I promise with 100% certainty.
I promise. 100% certainty that I will come back in six minutes and I will press that button.
If I don't just tweet me over and over again until I do. Just send me. Just spam me with
tweets if I don't do it. You guys want some ads? All right. I did promise ads. I did. I
promised ads. Here you go. I'm gonna run. I'm gonna run an ad. Here comes a 30 second ad.
Thanks for supporting the stream. See you next time. Take care. Much love to you.
See you in a few days. Probably on Monday-ish. Check the sus. It'll be updated. Good night.
Take care. Much love to you. Commercial break failed. I cannot run it. Commercial break failed.
Commercial breaks are only allowed once every eight minutes. Did you guys get it? I didn't
get it. Why would I get it? Well that's it. Wish me luck. See you soon guys. Take care.