Hey, what's happening guys? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight gonna be playing as the Brass Beast Heavy.
You know, I've done this a couple of times now. This is the second or third time I've gone over this recording and I keep saying Brass Beast.
I keep saying Brass Beast with a T. Don't know why. I think it's because Beast is right next to that. But anyways, this is the Brass Beast Heavy playing on Badwater right now.
Now, I transitioned to Gold Rush in two or three minutes or so. This is a compilation of clips. This is not a full gameplay.
I want to have something in the background while I talk about what I think about the weapon, when I use it, and general tips as well.
Because this weapon is almost impossible to use in a lot of situations. I'll bring up one or two of those, but the most main important one, the number one thing you need to know about the Brass Beast, is this is not an offensive weapon.
This is a defensive weapon, almost primarily a defensive weapon. And the reason why I say that is because on offense, your main goal as a Heavy is to be the anchor of the team.
You are the linebacker. You are the guy with all the pads on that says, get off your butts, everybody follow me, get behind me, and let's push this goddamn cart over that checkpoint.
That's what I see when I see a Heavy pushing up in the front lines. And if you don't have that, if there is no Heavy backing everybody up or pushing to the front lines, the whole team's in a lot of trouble.
I've been in a lot of teams before where there's no Heavy, and the soldiers are the ones taking the brute of the force, or the Demoman have to kind of take the damage, but it's all about the Heavy.
So that being said, not being able to stay up with the team, so let's say you cap the cart with the Brass Beast, and you spin down, because you might have heard somebody coming around the corner, or you heard someone behind you or something.
When you get to that spin down time, all your entire team is going to be way in front of you, and even with having the default minigun, you can still keep up.
Any of the other miniguns, you can still keep up with the front lines. It is almost impossible to do that with the Brass Beast.
Now it's not totally impossible. It's not impossible to do well with this weapon on offense. It's just tricky. You have to really be aware of everything, and you have to really stay alert and be right up there running without spinning your gun down to the front lines.
And I'm not that type of person, so this is really not my type of minigun, but let's transition from that to talk about defense.
Oh my god, especially with the Crit Scrieg. What you're seeing on the screen is me getting a compilation of Crit Scriegs from a guy that was in one of these games with me.
And as you can tell, it's pretty destructive. You can dish out a lot of damage, even at long ranges. So if somebody is a long ways away from you and you have a Crit Scrieg, or even if you don't, the Brass Beast dishes out a ton of damage.
Heavy versus heavy, you'll win pretty much every single time. And like I said with the Crit Scrieg, you are an insane force to be reckoned with, which is why it is amazing for defense.
If you pop a squat somewhere, you find a corner you want to stick around, you got a medic that's healing you, you turn into a mobile sentry gun. You pretty much are just robot heavy that is sentry heavy.
So I like to give a little bit of backstory, so this is the heavy telling the story.
I regain consciousness only to see Doctor there waiting for me. He told me he could not heal me, and it would not work, and I would have to go see a specialist.
It was Engineer, and Engineer gave me a new pair of regs, and I don't know why I am Count Dracula, or the Count from the cereal. Either or, it does not matter.
Well, what if I happen to be talking about the Crit Scrieg and the Brass Beast? I don't know.
So, the main point of this whole thing is, if you're using the Brass Beast and you're on defense, you are unstoppable with a medic. That's kind of what I'm getting at.
If there's a medic that's going to pocket you, or you have a buddy, or there's a good medic on the team, you will live a very long time.
The only thing you really have to worry about, and it has to be totally conscious in your brain at all times, is snipers and spies.
You are target practice for a sniper, and you are target practice for a spy. You stand almost totally still.
So make sure you keep that in mind, especially if you know there's a couple on the enemy team. It might actually be worth not equipping this and changing over to one of the other options.
So that's going to wrap it up here, guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
I come out here trying to protect the last point, but that's obviously not what happens.
I will see you guys all next time, and take care, everybody.