It was my face when my face when stream starts my face when
What's up? Good afternoon everybody
Or good evening wherever you are in the world
Yeah, he won
Yeah, and you know who won when I say he won, you know who won
There was an internal fight though that I thought in my dreams last night
People were punching each other in the face. There was a brawl up in my brain
And uh
and
German jump wants to continue to jump because he's completely certain
He's close. He's like 60% of the way through the game. He's gonna try he's gonna go for it
He's addicted to the game. And uh, when you get addicted to a game you have to continue
I'm not addicted he is
It's not my fault
Never in my life
Did I ever think?
That there would be a message that would say
nancy drew
waiting room
I don't think I I couldn't I imagine like three weeks ago somebody writing that everyone would be like what are you talking about?
What is that person talking about? Why are they saying that?
Why would he ever do that?
No, we're going back to the drew
Next week. That's what we're gonna do. Don't worry
I told you it was already locked in I I bought them all
I own well, not all of them. I own a lot most of them. I own a lot of nancy drew games
Let's put it that way
I bought the bundle
The next one we're gonna play is nancy. You didn't beat the game. Yes, I did
We I got to the end that was like an eight hour experience. Well, what do you mean? I didn't beat it
That's because I was because I cheated
Whatever. That's fine
If you cheat and you win
You still win
You just cheated and everyone could say well you cheated
But you won I know but you cheated so it doesn't count
Although we still got to see it. So who cares what what cost it's all right
He's mad main game plus the dlc now that I am not going to say
I am going to try to do the main game
If I get it done
then only then
Will we move on to the dlc and I will probably just not complete it
I'll get up to the first two or three screens to go. Nah, no, thanks
The dlc is extra content. So it's not like it has to be there
When you fall back to the start of the drain i'm going to get dinner
That's fair that's fair that does that it's all right that doesn't bother me that's very fair
I can imagine that person just well, I felt all right
Ordering a pizza going downstairs wherever you go. Yeah, we do have some new emotes
I enabled a bunch of uh better twitch tv emotes
They do exist
Does think 10 of them now
I didn't want to go overboard
I didn't want to just enable just to enable them
Because if you see if I start enabling 50 emails, I think that's okay
You guys gotta take them in in little slow drip feeds. Yeah
here it is
all right, I have to keep it together because
um
God that number makes me kind of nauseous already
I gotta keep this together because I haven't played it and yeah my muscle memory
I've got to get back to it. I gotta get back to normal
832 yes. Yes, I know I know. All right. Well, where am I?
I also I took him like a bunch of b vitamins today
I I drank I drank like a quarter of an emergency today. I wanted to get some extra b vitamins
But I feel like I feel worse today
You know what? I mean, I feel like I shouldn't have done that because I feel bad now
I I reverse vitamins myself somehow. How is that even possible?
Yep, well, uh, I should have I can't need to uh, can I open up like a second account?
I need to open up a second account and a second game and just practice
Oh Jesus, okay
No, we're all right
He's already molding stream your practice on secret twitch. Oh, no
This is everyone's asking why dude you gotta you gotta leave man. You gotta take a break
Leave go to bed last night
But when you're in a groove and you have you're capable even though I was molting
It's gonna take a little bit for me to get I might have to fall down a few times. So go get dinner
That guy that was here
Um, just go get dinner now
And then maybe when you come back
It won't be uh
I took these b vitamins. What was in that?
Those who don't learn from history
Oh shit. All right. I'm okay
I don't this is not a bad place to be it's getting up into the snow part is where what's going to be an issue
Okay
No, not mad. I thought he was done with this monkey s
No, i'm i'm close to being in a good
I just got to get back in the groove
I I have to beat the game base the the base game
We will he will never be free
I have to beat the base game before Joel does
Because then guess what?
When he plays this game
I'm gonna watch i'm gonna i'm gonna make sure I take i'm gonna take the i'm gonna take two days off
No, i'm gonna take three days off in a row to watch his whole the whole thing
I have to beat it. So then when he beat when he does it
You guys can all we can all be like I do turbo beat it. He beat the game
We're gonna what has it been six hours and you're still down in the sewer
And then he's gonna be internally like fuck. I gotta beat this
Okay, here we are he's already past you
I'll take things that didn't happen for five hundred dollars, please
put on thunder no, let me just like
I'm in it for the long call tonight guys
I already had a stacum sandwich
Which by the way, can we just talk about stacums for just a second here?
very quickly
I thought that stacums would junk
I thought they would follow up like sodium
And had a bunch of preservatives and shit
That's there's only one ingredient. It's just beef. That's it. Nothing else is in it. There's nothing else in it
They're really easy. It's one minute per side in a pan and you can put it in with eggs
You can you can mush it up into a sandwich
Oh fuck this
This is not an advertisement. This is me telling you what you can do
with the stacums
They're pretty damn good
It's easy you want a quick meal i'm just telling you truth here. What can you do with raid shadow legends?
Nothing
Can you eat raid shadow legends and is it very quick only a hundred calories per sheet?
I don't think so
That's too far. Fuck. All right
Go get you dinner because I I have to I it's gonna take a lot of like practice
Yeah, like is
Does fucking like b vitamins gave me diarrhea?
All right, i'm starting to feel it a little more
It's gonna take probably like, you know, i'll give you here. Look it's gonna take an hour for me to uh
To to get back into this
Those of you know that like when I go to sleep my whole body shuts off to a point
Where when I wake up and move around even like like six hours later
It takes me like eight hours to become like a human after I wake up
It just I don't know why my whole it's just the way it is
He's possessed what?
Why am I possessed?
Dude, I really wish I could just plug myself in
That wouldn't be I i'm not like against that. You know what i'm saying?
Oh, what about the capable robots? We're gonna turn into ai. I hope so
I would love to just glide down and plug the back of my like a socket in my back into the wall
And in eight hours, I could just lie there and just rest
And be fully charged the next day
I would have to worry about my brain having to do that work
No, I've got a battery the thing is you'd have to have surgery
You'd have to have surgery on your back battery to replace your whatever it is lithium
uh, I would buy lithium stock because
That's probably you know, it's not it's finite, isn't it?
That's an ad was that an ad or is that advice?
What's the difference now?
Okay
Hey, I like steakums like you steak was a really quick way to make like some like a protein packed breakfast in the morning
Is that advice or did I give you an ad?
Damn it. Stop being a bionic boomer. I gotta get back up to the snow part. Fuck. I gotta like
Charge up
You know, it's like kind of funny. I think
All right. So yesterday we have to talk about this so yesterday. I think I expelled like four days worth of energy
I'm like up now. I got I took like vitamins and shit and i'm like
Yeah, i'm like slow
I've slowed down so much. I expelled like probably a week worth of energy yesterday
My body heated up and cooled down like 3,500 times
I'm gonna have to like shuffle coal up my ass
How do I power myself?
Excuse me. What what?
All right, let's get up there. Let's get up here. Come on now take a sip of this fucking b vitamin
He's a steam engine
What is nancy drew?
Uh, the next stream is gonna be nancy drew
All right. I gotta be careful here. Let's go. It's like right here, right?
close
Oh
Damn it. Oh, yeah. Yai
Oh my god
I'm already sweating
Thunder don't start thunder yet
Oh god, damn it. Don't do this. No
Oh my god
No, no, no, no go get your dinner. Go get dinner. Go get dinner. Go get dinner. Y'all see in three hours
Go get go eat go heat a whole spread
Go get a chikootery board and put cheese and fucking figs on it and shit. It'll still be here
Don't worry
Oh my god
He's already at a 10. I should have opened a second account. I'm telling you I should have opened a second account
If I open a second account this shit don't happen
I could have just jumped around and been practicing
back in the goddamn sewer
again
At least I know how to get out of here. It's only these parts up here that suck
Do what?
Get up here. I gotta get the timings right too. That's another problem
Did you go to bed and you have like nightmares about wars going on in your brain?
Three people fighting in your brain you wake up like oh fuck
What time is it? I'm like jump king
He's back in the sewer
Oh, I know i'm close though. That's the thing. You know what i'm saying?
I'm close to getting what I where I want to be
Somebody told me that the the snow portion when we get to the snow part
But that's like 70 of the way through the game
If that's real
Then like that's so close
And no i'm not talking dlc. I'm talking just the base video game
Remember, this is a 100 hour experience
No, it's not that was so long
I gotta learn how to ride the bike again
God damn it. I knew I should have just done a 24 hour stream last night. I'm dead serious
Because like all of my muscle memory is gone
I should have just did like a 16 hour stream yesterday
That was a mistake to turn it off
Start using the d-pad now good idea
Holy shit, that's brilliant
What an absolutely brilliant idea. I'm doing it now
D-pad, let's go relearn it
Just relearn the game with the d-pad
I'll not see that i'm getting used to the d-pad. That was a d-pad problem
Hey germo, i'm the guy that went to dinner
Yeah, i'm doing i'm doing an entire i'm doing an entire, uh
Hold on
Let me get up here first
Not too much god damn it man. Come on
Oh, come on
I think I might just go take a cold shower right now
You know what I mean?
I think i'm just gonna go in like freezing cold water. I think that'll help
I think i'm gonna dunk my head into into cold water and then come back
Bring the mic. I I don't think I can
Wait, what if I call myself on discord? Could I do that?
Give me a fucking break
Back in the sewer when you i'm gonna go eat dinner
Uh
Nope, i'm going the other way down again. Oh my fucking god
Trying to get used to the d-pad
Should have done a 16 hour stream last night
Yeah, this is what that should have been the first like 20 hour stream I ever did I would have beat it
You see how far we got last time
It's gonna be a long night
I'm giving it a real attempt here
But I have to spend like an hour or two getting back into the swing of things
This is what I have, you know, if you feel like eating fucking food or feel like going to a movie
You know you check the movie times. There might be a good movie out right now
You could you could go see that movie come back and then I will be back used to how the game works again
That's a fun night
If you have a significant other or something you could go see um
See up. I don't know if you've ever seen up before
And then you come to the stream you can tell me hey germa. I saw the movie up
uh
Why can't you do that? And I'd be like, okay
All right. I'm gonna give you a one criticism for d-pad over analog. I'll tell you what it is
Uh, the d-pad is shiny
It doesn't have grip so
You know, I can already foresee water issue here
You know what I mean? I think there's gonna be a
human solution issue here
Because like sweaty fingers on like a slick
shiny material
You know what i'm saying? That might not this might not be a good thing
It shouldn't even be down here
Just don't sweat
That's impossible for me. All right, i'm gonna
What's the thing that uh people listen to
All right. I'm gonna put them on i'm gonna put on the like the chill beats to like fucking hang out with your friends
Or whatever it's called. Let's go. Let's do
Relaxing beats
No, not thunder. I'm I need to I gotta chill thunder
lo-fi hip-hop radio beats to relax to
um
All right, which one is this? Um, is it gonna be claimed?
thunder lo-fi remix
Thunder acdc lo-fi
No way this exists. I've been no way
That would be so stupid
Thunderstruck remix. No, it doesn't exist
thunderstruck slow remix
Uh, this is
This is just thunderstruck slowed down
by 21 percent
See, we're just chilling on this stream. We're not
Why would you make this you know, what's what's this point? It's so unnecessary
I'm gonna fuck it up again
No
Uh, I think you can only play this game if you've eaten like a piece of salmon the day that you play it
You have to take a blood test before you play jump king and determine what all your vitamin levels are
What am I what's my vitamin d at right now? Like it has to be all at 100 percent
Uh, you gotta take a blood test. What's your potassium level at right now?
Don't play it unless you have like fucking 80 capacity of your like vitamin e levels for the day
i'm ted serious
Hello ted what?
You're like imagine playing this game without like a vitamin e supplement
And then you can use the new emote that I enabled
All right, let's get back into this here I gotta keep it together man. I gotta keep it together. You got it
The more you tell yourself you got to keep it together the less you're gonna keep it together. That's what i'm i'm certain of
All right time to get back to where I was
Up in the snow area get you know, this is actually a good thing. This is a very good thing
Because now i'm not using the analog anymore. I'm actually starting to feel the d-pad and start to get used to the d-pad
So this is this is good. This is hard for me
I get it. Yeah super frog. I gotta take in the super frog vibe
What would super frog do in this scenario? I'll tell you what super frog would do
This just pretend it's this music
It's not even the right music
Oh, there's another this is another super frog
How can there be more than one?
There's more than one super frog
This one's for the omega
what
since when
Enable super frog two
Always that one goddamn jump. Does anybody okay?
Does anybody have just like the guaranteed way to make that jump?
Like there has to be like a full-on guaranteed way to make that jump every time. What is it? Does anybody know?
No one tell him
No, tell me
So I can get out of the sewer reliably every time jump into the spot with the leaking water
What's that?
Damn it. I that looked real
I that looked real. I could that could that could have been real. It really could have been
whiz
I'm gonna try something
Oh, I found the guaranteed secret. I did it. I did it. I actually did it. I did it
I did I did I just guessed and I did it. I'll never miss this jump ever again
I will never miss this jump ever again. Not once it'll never happen again. I will never miss this jump again
It'll never happen. Oh my god. Thank god. Let's get some super frog music
Uh, you go all the way to the right and you do a full left jump
Those are you that i'm gonna save you a lot of pain
Don't try to sneak in here. You put your body all the way to the right do a full jump all the way to the left done
I will never fall down that ever again. Oh, i'm so happy about that. Can we get a guarantee on the other one, too?
Don't give joel the speedrun strats. Yeah, I just realized something
You guys can you guys can tell?
How some you could tell them how to play and how to win and shit. I don't want that to be a thing
I don't want you to be able to tell that the secret to somebody like
Other names starts with a chay then i'm gonna play this game. They're gonna look at the trailer and go. No, that's not for me
Just play the rest in secret. I could do that
Fuck it's not enough
That one's gonna kill me because that just yeah, it's just like relearning the damn game a second time
But that jump it sucks because if you miss it it's over and you're gonna go all the way back down to the dumb sewer
Imagine the whole stream got claimed because of super frog is he still in the sewer after nine hours?
um
technically, no
physically, yes
Uh, I made it up to like the sixth screen in the snow level
And then I fell
And now I have to relearn the whole game again
Damn it, man. Give me a goddamn break
See, they're too small. It's not far enough. It's not too just
You gotta this goldilocks
Guess what?
The thing that people don't understand about goldilocks
That whole story is bullshit
This one's too hot. This one's too cold. No eat eat your breakfast
Eat it. It's what we have
Okay
This bed's too soft. This bed's too cold
This bed's too hard
Well, go get a sleep number bed then
And stop complaining about it. He's breaking. I have to make this goat
No, you motherfucker
Goldilocks into three bears
An unrealistic story if you break into a bear's house in the woods, you're going to get maimed
This porch let me try it
This porch
It's a little it's a little too cold for me. Well, who's house am I in this? Let me try this one
Oh now two. What's that sound outside? Oh, it's a little too cold for me
Who's that?
What is that?
Is it
No, no, this one's too cold
Please go
Oh
That's what happens. Derma. It's a story for kids
Somebody said nice family guy bit. Does that happen? Don't make me laugh right now. Does that happen in family guy?
It probably does
It definitely does that have that that absolutely happens in family guy your app you 100 correct
It has to there's no way it doesn't
Okay, jerma, please
Pay me for your fursuit commission
How many times am I gonna mad before I quit today? Uh, the goal is to just try to win
All right. I listen to me. I have
Let me see
Somebody got it. Let's see
How's your oatmeal honey, you know, it tastes kind of different than usual
Oh my god, that's not the same
That is actually not the same joke that's a
I was doing a goldilocks routine. Well, that was a routine of like waiter
There's a fly in my soup except it's a bear. Look at how big a bear is
How would you not see there was a bear in your soup? I didn't that's not what I did
That was the same sound effect because every sound effect is the same sound effect for a bear
You ever try to record a bear in the wild before of course, there's only one clip that exists everybody else is dead
The one guy that got it close enough and then could run away
All right. Do we have a guaranteed way to get through this?
there has to be
all the way to the right and then
That's not bad
Like give me the fuck up here. Let's go
boys and girls
Can we please?
I'm in the law. I'm in for the long haul tonight. So those of you that are like, oh man, this guy sucks. This guy sucks
Holy shit, this guy sucks. He fell down to the sewer again. This guy sucks
Dude, he fell down to the sewer again. He was up the snow. Oh, this guy scott. This guy sucks
It's all right. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here
This guy's pretty good
No, don't didn't you get the word sky sucks?
Damn it. That's what I if you miss it. You have to I think go to the other side
You gotta hit it. No, I was trying to get a good spot up here
Shit
I wonder is it a better idea to just go from here?
I don't think so. I'll hit my head, right?
I'll hit my head. Can you get up there?
Get up there
Streamer, please stop this fall joke. It's not funny anymore. It's always funny
I'm trying to hit it from the back. It's hard to do
Because once you get up there
You really have to get it from this way
Too much
What are you guys spamming? Hey, is this yesterday's vod?
uh
Sorry, it got replaced with this
Okay, let's go
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah
I know I can get on here from here, but it's got to be so precise. No, I am using dpad now though
So i've gotten used to it
This is the commentary. I you know what?
I've got hey, let's put on the vod from yesterday's audio
And see if it matches up
I wonder
Let's see. I'm gonna get it to a point where it was right here and we'll see if it matches up with what happens on the
screen
Enjoy the stream
Enjoy the pre-recorded live stream
Slow down now. I gotta go from here to there
Holy shit, I fell down so many times. All right. Hold on. Here we are
I'm going to let's make this a little louder
And i'm gonna mute all sounds in this game
Why was that so loud?
Ow my fucking ear. Why is the window sound louder than everything else? It doesn't make any sense
Okay, so i'm back. No, no, no, no
I am now standing in the
This is at if you want to play along this is at four hours 36 minutes and 37 seconds from last night
I'm standing in the exact same spot
Okay
Ready?
Let's go
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I just want to get back to where I was. Why did that happen? It's not about destination. It's about the journey
Now it's about the destination at this point. It's about the destination. I want to get there
It's about getting there about getting to the top. That's that's what it is
That's about
The oh really so i'm driving we're driving across a country trip to go to like disneyworld
And I got four kids screaming in the back singing songs while I got everyone's yelling and I
My wife's in the passenger seat with a map in her hands going like I don't think you went the wrong
I think you went the wrong way. I didn't go the wrong way
No, you want to get to disneyworld fuck the car ride to disneyworld. You want to get to disneyworld and go see goofy?
Uh
Get the coin
Don't get the coin. Don't get the coin. Don't get the coin
Don't get the coin. It's death. It's guaranteed to lose
You're guaranteed to lose if you get that coin in this wind now mean game developer. I told you
I got the coin. I got the coin. I got the coin. I got the coin. I got the coin. Okay coin got it
I have to wait was I not even muted? I've just been laughing
I've been sitting here going
He
So why is there someone just breathing on this vod why is somebody just breathing whose breath is that who's in the who's doing this
Got the coin got the coin
Dermot, can you play this during the next stream?
No, there's not going to be a next stream of this game. I don't think
Got it
All right. We've made it to the snow part
He'll never make any progress
This is not even progress
You should take a nap and come back and play this game guys. I slept six. I slept like
14 hours last night. I think i'm gonna be okay
I know i'm kidding. I would probably wake up and get i'll probably throw up
Here we go
All right. We've been here before
Stop stop stop. Stop. We need christmas music is all christmas new music is royalty free, right?
Yes it is
Oh damn everything
I wish I could pass all my audio through a loud filter
You know what I mean?
Because I have
I'm setting it up right now. I'm putting a filter on the desktop. Here we go. Check this out
i'm putting on a
A compressor on my desktop audio
Because I can I look if I go
It won't go. Ah, it won't go louder than that
But if I compress my desktop audio, it's gonna sound like shit
No, i'm not doing that. That's a bad idea
Just listen, this is by the way, this is on a live channel right now. Someone's live streaming
christmas 24 7 christmas music
Christmas smooth jazz. These are just live channels
Ah, i'm not I gotta move i'm not in a good spot
Oh you
Don't no no, I have to go back
Go max to the left. Why would I do that?
I just did that. What would I do that for?
I'm not i have to jump now ready
now
Oh fuck good. Ah, and I did it everything I wanted to do
I did everything that I wanted to do I did everything that I wanted to do everything that I wanted to do everything that I
Wanted to do everything that I wanted to do everything that I wanted to do
The thunderstruck acapella now hear me out here. This is this is get to the top one, right?
What the fuck was I doing? It's okay. Everything's fine
The music actually kind of helps a little
You know what I mean? It actually kind of does
It's all right
Sound like courage
Stupid dog, you make me look bad parents. There's no reason to be mad at courage
He's a stupid dog
Oh
Okay, everything's fine
Insane he's going insane. He's going insane. He's going insane. I hate this part at least this part
You can sit here for a minute
I have to jump with the snow
I could I can't go straight up from here
Yeah, we're good. Wait for it to change
That was not good enough not good enough. You can do better than that. What are you stupid? What are you an idiot?
I'm gonna hit the ceiling
Get in the discord. Why would I go in the discord so I can hear the loudest sounds?
See if I can get that from here, okay, then we're gonna go forward test the limiter
I didn't bra. Oh my god. What am I doing with my life?
Now I keep messing this one up
Because I get to that one but then not the other one and I feel like I have to be on the
I feel like I have to be on the other one
See what i'm saying here. Do you see what i'm saying there?
What is that?
Shit, let me up a little
Thank you pogchamp you you're now breathing and blinking manually. Don't do that
What the fuck did you do that for?
No, no, you've ruined you've actually ruined everything. Oh my god
Uh, I why did you do this to me?
No shit, it's working
I'm hard blinking
I didn't do it. Yes, I did. No, I didn't get me up there. What are you thinking? Why the fuck is this not working motherfucker?
Is this not working?
It should be working
I'm telling you fucking something should be working right now those kiddies
I gotta save those fucking kiddies ricky. Come on now fucking stupid ricky bubbles the fuck you're doing man
What are you fucking dumb stupid idiot boy?
I tried
I was thinking about it. I was thinking about doing a ricky there, but that didn't work out so well
Calm down slow down. That's okay
You got a bear with you right now. You got a grizzly bear in like a big cage
And it's just big enough for him to be in it and he's freaking out and you're going up to going hey
Hey, yeah, I'm gonna need you to settle down here
Just stop this just calm down just a little
Don't yeah, just calm down
You aren't an animal. Yes, we are. We're all animal guys. What the fuck am I doing here? I know what to do
I know what to do. I did it
Fucking dead ricky. That was the hardest fucking thing i've ever done in my fucking life rick
Shit, not a full jump. Don't go crazy here
Just get over there. You're almost there
Not a full jump to the right
Just a little one just a good one
Why this game have to be like this
Because that jump that jump sucks
That jump sucks. It sucks if you miss that one. Oh boy, you're not getting on the next train until tomorrow afternoon
You're still here. Lol ban that person
If I see that person's name in chat again
I'm gonna have a problem
We're all animals
Even me. Yes
Especially you so yeah, you were you were all furries
Sorry guys. I know you don't want to hear that
Fuck this up. Just a small jump
Holy fuck. Thank god
Thank god for physics based jumping
You shut your devil mouth
Why do I think that's so funny?
Come on do it
It's like a one go
Man this jump. What do you want people to do here, man?
What do you want to do here, man?
What do you want people to do here, man?
What do you expect people to do here, man?
Are you supposed to time that you can't
You just don't
Oh too hard too soft too hard too soft
Do a full jump with no wind. I don't know if I believe that one
That's not true
Holy fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck now full to the left
All right now easy
Easy
Then it's full to the right
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. No, no, not yet. Hold on how many more screens?
a lot
Full to the right. I'd rather undershoot it than overshoot it guys
Oh my fucking god. I'm not going down
Not yet
Croc of shit
What a croc of shit
All right. This is it
Do it you just
What you do? I'm I'm a little too high. I'm a little too low
what
What i'm gonna try what the what that the guy that was trolling said i'm gonna go for it
I'm gonna just do a full jump when there's no goddamn wind
Do it i'm gonna just give me a minute
You can go straight in that. Ah
Relax
All right. What are you saying? Somebody there's somebody screaming
Jeremy said I wouldn't be able to do the first jump on level one
I made it
Okay, relax
Okay, this is it from here, right? This is a good spot. I'm right in the middle
Hot hot hot hot
Pause pause pause. What what do you want? What do you want? What do you want? What pause what why?
What pause pause pause pause pause pause pause pause pause?
Why am I looking at this image? What are you doing?
Is that a real picture of me?
Besides the head no, I don't have legs that big
Why did you make me pause the game for this?
Oh god. All right. It's up. I think I don't know
I think it's it's up and to the right
Wait to the window. I didn't I didn't see I didn't see
No, my fucking god. No, no, no, no, why I just I don't know what's up there
I don't I don't remember what's up there. I don't know what's up there trying to see what's up there
I know but I don't care about you photoshopping my like dick on other people. All right, please stop
Stop this i'm gonna fall down again
Whatever the fuck you're doing
I have to make this jump. I have to I have to make this jump. You understand
Good. Okay. All right, you don't have to photoshop by like bald head on some other guy's dick
I don't know what you're doing. I don't I don't I don't care
All right, i'm gonna click the link. I'm gonna click link. What is it? What is this?
No, this is not gonna this is not gonna help
This has
This video has 3400 views
It's not is this a why does this only have 34 reviews?
This should have like 34 million
I hope he starts going like
I can't guys
It's i'm not going down the sewer again never again
Oh fuck me
Um
It's not good enough I have to jump at the wind a little
Is this good you think I think it might be
Aye, aye. Aye. No, jeremy jeremy
Turn it off turn it off. What the fuck
Aye
What the hell was I what am I doing man? I I tried to oh
Jesus. Oh, I thought I was going all the way down again. Okay, your car is about to hit me
I was like standing in the freeway
And somebody would just like jeremy wait
It's stressful
I hope you're going back to the sewers. How why could you why would you say something like that?
Now, why would you do something like that?
That's that's not funny, that's not funny. Why would you do that? Why would you do something like that?
At least we're about prank video now. Why would you do that though?
I'm giving you my time here and and you're why would you do that? I don't know what to do
I'm in trouble. You guys haven't seen that video when tom cruise gets like sprayed with the water
Okay, got it
Okay, now I can go forward forward jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
Now it's up to the right
I don't know
All right
Fuck man
What am I doing stop moving?
Now what okay
Now we go
I don't think it's straight up. I'm gonna hit the ceiling. You look at that ceiling right there. Do you see that ceiling?
If I go too high i'm gonna hit my head to the ceiling and it's gonna send me back down the sewer
A full jump up. What do you think straight up with the wind? I think so i'm gonna try it
Sorry, just clear my throat for a second
I have to do this. I have to get this
This is the i don't want to slow down one. Why slow down to two? Why there's so many videos of it slowed down
What about another ac dc song?
What thunderstruck is not doing how about this one left
Up left or just drift left drift left. We're going for it
Oh my god, what's up? There's a coin up there. All right, we're there. We're there. We're almost there
And then I can't fall from there did I beat the game? I don't know what to do
My heart is on fire right now i'm not going to get the boots fuck the boots
Guys, I can't fall down. I can't fall down into the sewer anymore. I can't fall down into the sewer
Oh, yes, I can't fall down into the sewer anymore. What a wonderful experience this is
Oh my god, you're almost to the end. Am I yes
Yes
Jump king get it on steam. It's currently 33 up
All right, I gotta
Thank god, you can't fall down. How do I try go probably the second one? I'm so glad you can't fall
Go get the boots. No
No
Nope
Shit, how do I do this?
What do you mean? I need them
You can double jump with the boots
You need the boots. You need the boots to unlock the dragon
You need the boots. You have to get the boots
Do the boots let you fly or something? No. Nope. I don't care
We're doing it. There's a no, but i'm going you do you see how
This I couldn't no
No way. I'm so
Uh, I have to like shake these like cobwebs off my body
I'm still like I can't believe I did that the first jump the first drive
You knew I was destined to fail there. What's the easiest way to do this because you hit your head there
Okay, and then I have to go to this one
And then from here to the over there
Huh?
Can I hit my head off this one? Oh shit
Wait, can I do that? I can do that to all of these
Wow. All right
I get it. Okay. I get it. I get it. I get it
So don't why I want to just do this
Okay, cool. You just have to go blink blink
oops
like that and then
I think I have to get on that one on the left from here. I think I can go over there
Aye. Aye. Aye. I think I can though
With honestly, there's nothing like watching german loses mind while I lose my my mind hatching shinies
I'm not getting the boots. I'm not going back down to the sewer
Guys, I'm not I can't do that
I'm sorry. That's some other streamer. That's better than me. We'll figure it out
That ain't gonna be me. I'm not gonna go get the boots
If I go down and get those boots
What if I open them up again? I'm sorry. I can't
How much space is on these?
Shit. Okay. What's up here? Oh, yeah. Um
Can I make it from here?
Oh, I can
now
Oh, um
and
Get out of town
What what is it? Can I oh there's a slot? Okay. I thought that was part of the background
It's not the boots. I thought it was for a second. I was about to be really really really deflated
Okay, um
I have to get to the left ledge very obvious
So what go from jump from here to the right and then from right to left?
Could I go to the right? Yeah, I can't how do I can't get up to I have to jump from that left platform to the chandelier
So can I do this?
Look at this dude. It seems like a new man
What is up here? What is that? Wait, hold on. I'm I'm I've almost got it. I've almost got it
No, no, no, no, no, that's all right. Sorry. Sorry. I almost just just relax
You gotta you gotta you gotta go off the edge. You gotta go. You gotta go full off the edge
I got it. Watch this shit. Ah
Look at the look at the look at the look at the look at the wait. Look at the wait. Look at the wait
How do I get up there? Um that that falls all the way down that falls all the way down
That falls all the way down. Can I stand on that? No, I can't I can't stand on that
Do I have to fall bounce off the edge on the left side?
Or do I throw my face into the right side and bounce over to the left?
Can I stand on that ledge? I think it'll it'll don't it's gonna dump me
Yeah, okay. Okay. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
It's a you bounce off the edge, but not a full bounce
And I might be in a little bit of trouble here. No, i'm not check this out
a little bit trouble
So you got to bounce off the left not a full bounce shit fuck. Oh damn it. Ah
Fuck because i'm so I think I can still get over this
No, i'm sorry. I'm sorry. Yeah
Look, you gotta you gotta fall down first
How am I supposed to know how to do that jump at the end now I got it
I'll get now just take this takes a little bit of time
It just takes a little bit of time guys. It takes time. Whatever you sounded like my grandma for a second
You actually want to bounce off that? Okay
All right. I'm I swear to god like my heart is still racing
From the highway to hell portion like it's slop slow down
Okay, then we go from here up to there
All right this way
All right now we're up we're up we're up we're up I he oh
Oh, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. There's an ice level in the game. How should I get? Um,
There's ice here. There's ice in the game. There's ice here. Can I go?
Can I go all the way to the right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this is not fun. This is not fun. This is not a fun part
What?
There's a slide now you slide
There's a slide. I can't believe they put a slide here. That's unbelievable
No way
Go for just do it. Go for it. Just don't slide too far. You got to be kidding me. That's difficult
Difficult difficult
Oh, yeah. Okay. Okay fun
Yeah, nice. Cool. Good. Yeah, you dump all the way down here. Cool
They're not gonna make it easy are they?
dick
Goddamn fucking ice level
I'll tell you though that actually sucks absolute ass
Oh that sucks ass
Yeah, hold this sucks ass
I think we're gonna put an ice level in a game that has precision jumping in it
What's wrong with this guy?
What guy? I don't know the guy that made the game
Whoever made this game. What's wrong with you? Why did you do this?
I'm sorry
You didn't make this
Fuck i'm stuck now. Maybe I can
He made it to the chapel. I made it to the the second screen of the
We put slippery ice level in video game
You I've words cannot even describe how angry I am about that scenario
Get in there. Let's go. Get up. I'm just so happy. I don't have to see the sewer anymore ever again
Congrats jerma. That was officially your hundred thousandth swear
Really?
I'm honored
All right, wipe the hands too much too much. Ow
I hate this part sucks
Uh jerma little do you know this is the sewer now
It's just been replaced. Don't fuck this up. I'm gonna hit this now, dude. What are you doing?
Oh my god
Fucking this stupid jump
This it's it's it's only one pixel way to do this. Fuck this part too. All right, slow down
Hey to the right to the right, huh? Now what now what now? What do I do? Uh, do I have to?
Jump over that and I have to hit the slide unless i'm insane that this was springboards or anything, right?
So you hit slide
And then rip to the right
Like hold right how much momentum do you get from sliding down a slide or do I have to jump?
Let's go
Oh, I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I actually did I actually did it. I actually did it
I actually did it. I actually did it. I actually did it
Okay, I don't think i'll ever be able to do that ever again
I have to beat it now. I have to be after I beat this part right now. I'll never do this again
I will never do what I just did ever again at certain
How do I?
You have to baby jump to kill momentum
Hold so it got hold a let go of a hold a let oh that sucks
Do it with the boots. I
Do I actually have to go get the boots?
No, I don't I don't it's so far down. It's gonna be way easier if I get the boots
Yeah, but I mean
But then I might i'm gonna go back down to the sewer
No, there's 100 no way i'm going to get the boots. I have to do it without the boots
Uh, I will it'll be a coin scenario
Do you know how long it will take me to come back up here?
It'll take me probably eight hours to get back up to the chapel
Uh, i'm not getting the boots
I don't care if it saves me four hours tonight. No way
Not gonna happen
Think of all the work you did getting the coin. Yeah, but that was just for like if you guys think I was cool
No, I don't doesn't matter. Whatever
Why am I doing it like this?
There's a very easy solution to this. I don't know why i'm not doing it like this. What the hell am I doing?
There's a 30 there's a 30 000 times faster way to do what i'm doing
Watch this
Like why am I doing it like this?
When I should just be doing it like this
Just get up get up here
And then just jump off the wall
Like why do I care so much about this part like watch already watch this
I mean i've had it
I mean, it's definitely easier. Yes, it is
It was two
That that seriously sucks such asshole. It's like so bad
Why have that there? It's so stupid. It's stupid
It's stupid
You either walk off the cliff or find the two one pixel where you can jump to the left and hit your head on the ceiling
To bounce to the right
You need the boots. I don't need the boots. I don't need the damn boots
Get it. Ah
Why are you so scared of the sewer? Because I did you did you watch the stream yesterday?
You may not have the stream yesterday was about seven hours
Four or five of those hours were in the sewer
I'm I don't want to do that again. I don't ever want to see that screen for the rest of my life
I don't want to see that screen
Never again
I am not all right. I am not going to go down
15 screens to get the boots to make it easier. I just have to do it
I just have to do the ice level without the boots. I am full stop
Not going to go get the boots. I am not going to go get the boots
I will not go get the boots
I will not go get the boots. I will not go get the boots
Okay, does it have to be any more clear than that? I'm not going to go get the boots
Jerm, I think you should go get the boots. Should I what do you think? What do you think I should do?
What do you guys think I should do? I what what what are you guys? What's what's the plan? What's the plan? Huh boots?
He's doing a poll. No, I was just checking the time with my clock app. Do not get the boots
It's bait even if it's not i'm not going i'm gonna i'm gonna do it on hard mode
If the boots make you not slip on the ice, well, then whoop the goddamn do
I didn't get them and I have to deal with my consequences of completing the ice level without the ice boots
I think that's bait. It's definitely bait. I'm being baited
But i'll all right. All right
Damn boots get the boots. It's gonna be hard to judge this. It's from all the way to the back
Oh, fuck. I need christmas music
You guys are making my blood pressure go up
I think it has to be
A full jump to the right i'll hit my head here
I know my head
Is not a full jump but it has to be full jump height
Fuck you beeper get out of here
Is it full right? I don't think it's full right i'll go over the whole thing
I'll hide it. Let me hold on you go. I don't think I can even make that jump
That's no i'm gonna hit the wall
Do I have to hit my face off the edge here? Just do like a boom to the left?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute
If I jump over to the left
And then slide and slide up the whole thing and go to the right will I just go up to shoot?
Or is it a full left into here and bounce my head off this
Do it full right
Full right, but I think a full right from the middle from like right here
I'm scared to do a full right from here. I think i'm gonna soar over the whole thing
It's too much not full right it's too much too much that's way too much
All right. I know for next time. I gotta get back into this way. It doesn't you should have gotten the boots
I'm gonna start i'm gonna start just fucking banning people
You want me to start the bans? I'll bring it on
Oh, I will drop a nuke
That's big
As at least two or three of those firecracker things that you get from the gas station that you throw on the ground and they just pop
Don't make me do that. I like this part. I really like this part
It's the only part of the whole game that I actually like probably. All right, let's go
Buh buh buh buh boots
You guys are killing me here
All right, I got sweaty hands I gotta my hands are sweating you could have beaten the game by now with boots
You I you guys sincerely are overestimating my capability to get back to the cathedral
I'm never coming back here again. If I go 15 screens down
I'll never be back here again. It's gonna be easy if you have boots
Uh, don't fall for it. I don't know what to believe. I I thought you guys were making jokes
I'm gonna go down there and he's gonna go. Oh, sorry. Somebody already bought those boots guaranteed it, right?
That's the whole joke that the game wants to play on me
Sorry, I just ran out of stock. Somebody else bought them. I know it's gonna happen
I've played video games before i'm gonna get baited
First of all, let me get back up to the ice level
Just relax the music for a little bit before I start banning people
You think you think i'm bluffing people think i'm bluffing
You think i'm bluffing mocha is he bluffing mocha? Yeah. Yeah, i'm bluffing
Why would I ban somebody?
For repeating the same sentence over and over again trying to mauled me
I know what your intentions are
Ah, I got up to the first one. I just did I have I never tried that on the jump before
I got up. It's a full it by the way, it is a full right jump to get to that first one
Now the second one that's another story. I have no idea that first jump is all the way to the right, okay
It's definitely possible I just got to concentrate without any
boots
Chairman, please do whatever you think is best. Hey, thanks. I appreciate that
Hey, thank you
I gotta go a little further than that
So it's all right, but is there a is there a shortcut right there?
Can I jump straight into that? Here's the real question. This is the hard jump right here
This is the one because look at that ceiling
Never i've only tried this once
It's okay. All right, so that that's correct, but just a little bit less than that a hair less
Ah, hmm
Walk up the slope funny face
Ah
What about that right side?
Is that a spot or is that an incline?
Is that a spot to stand?
Or is that a troll?
That's an incline. Okay
There are two ways I could I see this playing out
way number one
Try to jump on top of that way number two jump to the all the way
Or jump to the middle one
Three go get the boots
What is it what I want to do?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Now what do I do
Now, what do I do?
I don't think I can make this I have to bounce
off of that
Onto that platform on the left
I have to bounce my face over to the right and hit it and then bounce to the left
Yeah, yeah, yeah. What do you mean? No
No, what do you mean? No, what do you mean? No, what are you talking about? No
No
Jump bounce left
Jump all the way to left bounce off land on the platform, right?
That angle is not possible. No, that angle is not possible
This is no, this is an impossible angle. I can't jump from here. I'm gonna hit the slope
You're gonna slide
Yeah, i'll slide down won't I?
I think i'm going full left
or fall
That's not no. No, I can't fucking believe people actually told me to slide up the platform. Oh my god
You people are killing me
Slide up the platform your god. Yeah, it was such bullshit. That was just an absolute crock of dog
Okay
That doesn't work either drop jumping up normally doesn't work jumping to the right doesn't work to bounce jumping to the left is the only option
That's it. No, that's it. That's correct. That's correct. Now you can small you can small jump you can small jump
Oh my god, fuck this game
You can I have you have to be
Yo
Yo, you really like okay, you can do that. But holy shit
Oh, I gotta calm down here
You got I go get the boots
I'm so close to getting through that without them that I can just memorize that ice level soon
I do I have improved at that part
I have
Remember before how fucked up that was
I was reliably making those jumps. It's okay settle down settle down settle down. It's okay
I'm sweaty
Settle down settle down settle down settle down
It's a little longer than that
Settle down settle down settle down settle down settle down settle down
Fuck
Oh my fucking god
I have it too. I have it just dumps you so far down here. This is the new sewer
It just throws you all the fucking way down
I was in a groove there, too
Does german know there are boots?
Jesus fucking christ
I'm almost above the ice part
That was not the dev
I'm sorry, you're sending too many boot related messages per minute
Please wait for a 10 second cooldown to repeat your boot meme. I'm angry. All right. I'm turning off chat
I'll see you guys in an hour. Somebody gave five. I don't know who it was though
I don't have my chat turned on somebody gave five. Oh, who could it be? My chat's not on
Thank you. Germa sucks for the five community subs. Appreciate that
Hey have a
Great day
Just get over here. Don't even try to make this just get up there
Just get up it don't even try to make the jump from here. It's the dumbest thing to do
Just get on the damn thing
Wipe the hands. What do I do if somebody gives me boots for christmas?
I will put them. I will blend them
Oh fuck didn't have to go that far. I hit the ceiling
Too far. Oh god. Damn it
God damn it. God damn it. God damn it. God damn it. God damn it. God damn it
God damn it. I'm gonna wake up god
Stop saying that my cat is sleeping
Why do you have your why you why do you have your cat lying next to your speakers?
Where is your cat?
He chose to be there
Well, then turn my turn me down
I'm not gonna get i'm not gonna let it happen
I'm not gonna get pressured into getting the boots and getting stuck under sewer again all stream. No
I'm almost through the ice. It's just hard. I ain't gonna let that happen
No, I've made my decision. This is not a I don't care if this takes me the next 12 straight hours
To get up this ice. I'm not going to get the boots. It'll never happen
You're you're wasting your internet data. You're wasting your bandwidth by writing the word boot
I'm just telling you the truth
Just you're wasting data you're using data right now that it doesn't it's not gonna do anything for you
It's i'm not going to get them
You're wasting data. Yeah, good. I I I hope I hope you guys writing boots right now
I hope like you get a you ding on your phone and you look at it. You're like, what's that?
Oh, sorry, you've gone over in your data this month and you go. Oh shit
Probably should stop writing boots a hundred times in a row
What is this chat? Okay, I gotta calm down you guys
I have unlimited data
There's no such thing as unlimited anything
All re everything is finite
All right
It's a little too much
Where do I go from here to the right?
Can I make this fucking jump from here?
I'm gonna hit my head on the ceiling. I missed that I hit I held it the whole time
All the way down again
Back to back to sewer two
Now I don't want to hear anybody say the word boots because I got past the section that I required the boots for
I just have to get through it. What do you boots?
I I beat the section that the boots are required for
I just beat it. I just beat that section now. You can't say that anymore
I I win
I win
Can we can we like I'm I don't want to get all Vince McMahon on you on everybody. Like can we relax?
All right, I got it. Yeah, i'm covered in grease
Yeah
It's all right. It's two hours. You know what that means
Covered in grease my whole body i'm gonna start streaming from the inside of a fucking refrigerator
That would probably be better if I was in like a a negative 12 degree room
That would probably be better
My body temperature right now is probably 150
I should i'm legally dead right now
How I don't understand?
Why does this happen?
Dude, these jumps are worse than anything else. I'll can I just have the snow level back, please?
That's where I belong. It's relaxed. I really am aquaman god
liquid handicap
times five water on body
Life is pain
No, that's not what I wanted to fuck over here
I went to get a snack earlier. Thank you for staying in the church section. You're very you're welcome
I went too hard again
It's like it's so hard to judge when you're bouncing
When you bounce it into a wall it's hard to judge you slow down calm down why is this in the game?
I'm about to go make some mac and cheese. Do you mind getting those boots while i'm gone?
All right, okay
Stop if you if I fall I just need to I just gotta you know, I mean you panic
Because you know, you're gonna be skidding what happened there
I did a full jump. That's that's worked every single time
I did a full jump. What the fuck happened? I did a full jump. That's happened. That's worked every time
Come on, man. What?
That's worked every single time
Don't worry. That's not fucking aggravating
No
Sorry, I forgot i'm playing aggravation simulator. Just rename it just do it. What's what why I call this jump king
Like just rename this game
I'm trying to piss you off. That's it. Just that's what it's that's true. That's what it should be called
This is not about jumping
It's about trying to make as many and many people angry as possible
I think this shit was in an episode of dexter's lab one time
There was like an evil guy that like didn't want to make everybody like sad or like angry and gave them like a video game
To play and it like worked
Oh, no, sorry. That's the that's jump king. Right? I think that's the same thing
That was the powerpuff girls
Whatever whatever was from
That's from phineas and ferb
Is that show still on the air?
Are they still making new phineas and ferb cartoons?
Thank god. No
What what's wrong? Why what's wrong?
What's wrong with phineas and ferb? I've never watched the show, but what's wrong with it?
Phineas and ferb was only good new age. It's the only good new age cartoon show
What are some of the cartoons that were like worth watching? I don't remember
Nope. Holy shit. That's a that's an odd one. How do you get that jump?
Holy fuck. How are you supposed to get that?
Still haven't nailed that down yet. I'll get I will not saved
that set the jump to the
the jump to the
It's just so hard to judge it
Even when you do a little one, it doesn't seem like it's enough
Be back in an hour. Hey, i'm gonna go get some boots. What size are you?
I've got these big ass goofy feet
Didn't make that what why did I not make that?
What the fuck wait
What how did I not make it over that I don't understand
What?
I'm shocked
Why am I so calm?
Because it's wasted breath to be angry at a game
Who was what was it was designed to make you hate everything about your current life what you're doing right now
I'm not gonna let it win. I'm not gonna give it the satisfaction anymore. You know what i'm saying?
This game was created to make you
Scream out loud. I'm not gonna give it the satisfaction of letting it happen
I only gave it the satisfaction maybe two to three thousand times already
You know, so i'm not giving i'm not giving you anymore. You can't get it out of me anymore
Is he so calm?
I think i've reached the breaking point when I told everybody to stop saying the word boots
And then they wouldn't stop. So I was just like, all right fine
All right, I guess
And you know what else this is not even a no bullshit here i'm not kidding
I'm not i'm kidding. I'm not even getting around. I'm serious. I'm not getting
Um, this music is helping. It's great
You see what I mean there? You see what I mean? It's just like is it was that that was too far, right?
That was a little too fucking far
Yeah, why was I playing thunderstruck that was such a bad idea
I should I I need to be calm
Not like pumping my blood
I also can't speak while I jump because it just takes all my concentration
So I will never speak again when i'm in the middle of a jump
We'll stand still to talk
Play blue this game looks fun. Don't buy this game. Don't do it. Please don't
I'm i'm i'm stuck here. Don't buy this
You'll end up like me. I'm trapped
I can't get out of here. You know, you're gonna end up you end up like me. Don't do it
I'm stuck. I'm stuck in a cube right now
All right, stop stop stop stop time
Okay. Um, do I have to jump on the blue thing?
Oh, it's just new content. I've never seen before
You know what I mean? Like that. It's just brand new content that I have never seen
Uh, I should get it though. I got this down pretty pretty reliably. That's hard. Fuck. That's fucking hard
Holy shit, that's such a tiny ledge
Oh, that's such a small ledge. You gotta be perfect
Well, I did I made progress right I made progress
um
You know what i'm saying? I at least got to see this full two screens above
You know
I'm so close
Is that tower somebody give me give me hold on up that tower if I make it up the tower
That's I gotta be close
That's the end. That's the last the end of the game
Oh, man, then I I I'm gonna do it. I've got to do it
I've got to at least be the base game. I can't promise you any dlc or anything, but I gotta I gotta get up there
That's 25%
50% no you guys said 50% was the beginning of the snow level. There's no way that's 50%
All right. I gotta I gotta keep moving gotta keep moving. If you stop you turn to stone. I gotta keep moving
You know what I mean?
If I you can't I can't stop I gotta I gotta move
The the longer you take in between jumps
The more you you overanalyze every electric. Oh, what if I jump over there? What if I try that?
No, no, no, I gotta just go just go and do the jumps
There's no there's nothing. There's no sound though. So it's freaking me out. I need something in the background
um
Put on the christmas shit again. No, no, how about uh
crisp hold on a different playlist that that one was
Slowing me down too much
This is too loud
Here we go, this is why you gotta keep moving back. You can't just stop you have to keep moving
It's like an energy it's like electric bike, you know what I mean? You have to just keep powering
I hate that jump so much more than anything
That may be the worst jump of the game because I I think basketball hoop
Uh sucks, but you don't have to bounce off of one tiny little ledge of like what the fuck
You know what I mean? Like what the fuck is up with that?
I he's mad again. Oh, yes, I am
I hate that jump
I hate it
I hate it. I hate it
If I could put a cheat in right now to just have that junk be done every time
I would put it in right now and I wouldn't even care if you guys were like cheater. He's cheating. I don't care. I don't care
I don't care. I would just win. I would just win. Who cares?
It would be an empty victory
Who cares?
Who cares who cares?
No, i'm this music is like is is not is fucking with me something better
This is what this playlist sucks something else
This one might be worse
I'm not happy. This is not working. It's not working. I we don't need any of this shit
Bah humbug we need a little christmas right this very minute
No, I've made that jump 100 out of 100 times i've made that jump over 100
times
Why?
Why can I not do that now? It's like i've done it a fucking 100
time a
100 fucking times
Not these two times. Oh
You can't be serious
And by the way, there's a guy just yelling in my ear
He's yelling in my ear
Under the tree
What do you see?
I bought some boots
for you
Please don't fall
He doesn't have time for that by the way, uh, santa claus is not gonna come look at your tree
He's gonna eat your food and then he's going to leave your house
He's gonna take a bite out of your cookie
And by the way, just one bite
You leave five cookies at like six carrots out
He takes one bite of one of the cookies and breaks a carrot in half and pretends to give it to rudolph
And then you just have stale ass cookies sitting outside the next day
Who's me?
Okay, i'll show
Saint nick the tree you are
What is what's he talking about?
Who is he talking to this is lagging my game I have to turn it off. Um, okay
That's it
No
That was just a low quality version that was a low quality version why was that so low quality
What
It's such a hard jump
It's so hard to do that one. You gotta sneak in how the fuck do you sneak in that shit?
No progress. No progress. I didn't get I made I made it back to where I was no progress
No, no fucking progress. Oh, there's no
Get throw all these books away. I didn't learn anything
All right, we're back. We're back. We're back. Should I go to the left?
I wonder if I should go to the left, but should I just I don't know
I don't think I can make the left. All right, that's a that's too much money
That's too much money
That's not my that's not the alert
Okay, um freddy dredd
just gave
What the fuck?
226 500 bits
That equates to
265 dollars
That's over a quarter. That's over a quarter of a thousand dollars, by the way
That's a lot of money
That's oh, that's too much money. They say jump higher
I'm trying i'm gonna try my hardest to get to the end of this game
So I can put a stamp on it and say I beat this game and i'm gonna go for it
Look at where I am right now. I'm almost there and I know
I know this dlc
But I don't need to do that
Freddy, uh freddy dredd. That's a ton of money though. Seriously without no joking around
The six six six six viewers right now
Let's put some fucking death metal on
I don't understand that jump
I'll get there over and over again. I don't understand
I gotta get up there. Let's go
Thank you freddy dredd
I bet money on you. I feel so bad laughing at you
Just pause it pause it pause it pause it pause it pause it pause it again. What the fuck happened there it happens so
Man it's that
Oh my god. Damn it. God. Damn it. God. Damn it. God. Damn it. God. Give me why god damn it
God damn it god
Damn it
It's better than the sewer though. I think I do think so because look at how quickly I can come back up to at least here
What's going on man? What why is it doing that? I don't understand. I'm holding it the same amount of time that I did before
What jerma, why am I doing this what playing a video game on twitch?
And trying to beat it. I don't follow you. What does this take me? Where's it taking me? Where are you taking me?
I was trying a new strategy try to go left. You can't go left. You can't go left. You've got you gotta go
All right. You cannot go left. You have to make it through that little spot on the right
I was it was worth an experiment. Damn it. I thought I was going for some reason. I don't know why
I thought I was going all the way back to the sewer or something because that was all the way to the left and
My heart hurts
My like chest is pounding. I really thought I was going all the way back to the sewer
I was getting flashbacks
I tried to speed it up. What are you doing slow down? What are you doing that for?
What are you doing that for why would you do that?
I'm just so sick of the level
And i'm just flowing through it. Why?
You can't do that in this game. It's not possible to do that unless you can speed run the game
My god, i'm so close to getting
I have i've done almost the whole goddamn thing
That's a meltdown voice
I want to find the person that can literally sit here like this and play this game
My cam's not even on
I don't think a person exists
That will just silently sit here and just accept every single horrible thing that happens
like
I guess I fell
Oh, oh well crap
Yeah, what was that? The oh, oh, that's that's the
Yeah, that's like the 2000th time I fallen down that same part. Yeah
Whatever. It's all good
Good to go
Oh god, i'm kind of tired
Garfield
Gamer garfield, maybe yeah
I had such a flow going there too. That sucks
I didn't miss one single jump getting all the way up there from candle to candle
It's all right. You just gotta do it again
That's the nature of this game
Jump king
I got caught on something. It was weird. I missed
Oh god damn it. Oh god damn it. Oh, yeah
Man, what a pain in the dick
I have to go to like that. I'm gonna have to go to like the doctor
It seems to be the trouble mr. Elwood sir
Oh, you know
dick pain
Oh, okay. Well
Yeah, yes, I I besides your hands. They look really calloused
Have you been lifting weights?
Nah
Playing this fucking game called jump king, dude. It's pretty good
It's pretty sick
I have a lot of conversations with my doctor about this guy's stuff
It's always my it's always my doctor that I have to talk to
Too much i'm going too far with that. I have to that's way too long. I'm holding that for way too long
Mr albertson, do you are are you okay? Is there an alien in your stomach? Help me help me help me help me diagnose you
What's wrong?
uh
You fell down the ice level and jump king
Because that's the only reason why you'd be making those fucking noises
The definition of insanity doing the same thing over and over again while expecting the result to differ
I would agree with that diagnosis for uh, but i'm gonna have to decline that diagnosis
because
uh
I'm at the ice level. I have I have progressed
Wait, fuck that was quick
That one's so hard to judge
It really is it's so difficult to judge that
All those are gonna be hard that's gonna be such a pain
what
What the fuck is going on? Oh, it's fun to drive my car very fast
Oh cool
All right. Enjoy your like times five, uh insurance that you have to pay
Cool new sewer. It's the end of the game
There is it's the last yes because i'm at the last part of the video game
Um, there is no chance in hell i'm doing the dlc
If I get here
I'm gonna have to incubate myself for like six months. You know what I mean?
Something's gonna hatch out of me soon
Tower again, man fuck
All right, damn
You're gonna leave let joel beat the dlc before you
Look
This is not that's not going to happen
It's not gonna happen joel if you're listening to this right now
You you go ahead and you you do the dlc that i've been told is 20 times harder than the base game
You you you can do it
And we'll be all root. We'll all gonna be rooting for you
We'll all be rooting for you
It ain't gonna be me. I will for i'll be an audience member on that one
I ain't doing that
Joel's better gamer confirmed. He hasn't done it yet
Wait, you've
You haven't even seen the movie. You don't even know how it ends
Too far. He's not gonna get the boots
No way
He's not going to get those boots, huh?
So I gotta make it to that right platform
Where's the right place to do this from without hitting your head over there?
That's the idea. That's the right idea. That's the right idea. That's the right idea. You're gonna go all the way the little
That's the right idea
Oh god damn. It's so hard. It's so hard. I can't I have to relax. I this is like I can't even
Imagine doing the dlc
I would rather
Ship my pants and leave it there all day then do one minute of the dlc of this game
That's straight facts. I got at least I made progress and now I can't even do the stupid ass candle section
Ah
This game has broken him go download it you want to you see what it's like somebody said no good answer
That's the correct answer
No
No, you should play guitar hero. That's a muted stream. The whole that whole stream is off. Okay. Come on. Come on
Oh man, oh man, I like hit my face so I couldn't recover fucking jump king
Jump left. I already tried that it doesn't work. I jumped out and I went all the way down
That way works. All right. All right. I'm gonna tell you I went left. I couldn't get it
I went right and I got it
Turn the music back on
Yeah, jesus fucking christ
Feeling the stress. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
It this is not a game that you that you play or watch
to like well, maybe it is
Maybe some of you guys are sitting there with popcorn going like yeah, he's never gonna make it to the fucking top
He'll never make it to the fucking top. It's not gonna happen
And then every time I fall you go like yeah
Yeah, you didn't make it. You didn't do it
You didn't make it
Popcorn and you would say popcorn. No, you wouldn't say popcorn when you hate it
It
Would you say popcorn?
Why would you announce it?
It's what if there's already in the room with you
This game is actually something else man
I can't give up at the finish line
And no this frame's not been on for that long, but I I can't give up at the finish
I have to get to the end of the game. I can't give up
I don't know what i'm i'm i might need to put no
I do have to blink like three times really hard though because my eyes are watering
Check you
And almost too much there. There's a lot. Thank god
Thank you soft they're giving 22 community subs. Thanks for the 22 community subs from soft 33. Thanks for the 22
So that's a lot of subs
That's a lot of subs. Thank you for the 22 community subs. It's a ton of subs. Thank you. That's a lot of subs
Thank you so much
damn
Thank you. You can do it. I believe in you. I'm trying
I'm trying to get it done. I'm just gonna just gotta take my time. You're gonna fall
The name of the game is not
Well, who cares?
I'm so scared of hitting my head on that fucking thing
It's the same thing the third time in a row
I I have to jump higher than that. You know what I mean? I'm just so scared to do it
I'm terrified to jump higher than that because I feel like i'm gonna hit my head and fall but i'm gonna fall anyways
If I don't do it enough
Stop saying
God damn it popcorn
I deserve that I do
Stop reading chat. I can't i'm a live streamer. I can't help it
What I do you're gonna tell a fish not to swim getting sweaty
My head's starting to fucking fill with all kinds of like liquid
Oh
Too much too much jump. It's not a little too much just a little too much jump
Just a little bit. I have to pull it back a little bit after that
Too much there, too. And now i'm like i'm like a fucking lightning rod right now
How the fuck do people play this game
Oh, yep. Nah, i'm like electricity right now
Okay
I didn't I didn't fall all the way you can only say popcorn when I go all the way down
That wasn't enough. Why was that not enough?
my
god
Don't put on thunder. No
No, i'm not not there yet. Do it. No, i'm not gonna do it. I can't do it
All right. I i'm so close to beating this god fucking forsaken game
I have to get up there
Yeah
All right, stop he's two screens away and he can't fucking do it. Yes, I can. Yes, I can. Yes, I can
Yes, I can. Yes, I can. Yes, I can. Yes, I can. What are you linking?
What is skyrim ta Skyrim tavern? Why are you linking me skyrim tavern?
That was wrong. Well, i'm not what i'm i'm I don't even know what this is
Let me change my seat. All right. I need to blink a few times. The colors are blending together. I that sucks when that happens
No, shake it off
When like the when the game just everything blends together. Stop just I gotta change out change it
So somebody give me a noun noun noun adjective anything. Give me a noun. Give me a noun. Give me a noun
Boots. Yeah. Yeah house house house house house. We're in a house. We're walking around the house
We're eating popcorn in the house. We have boots on
Popcorn is delicious
Chewing it. I have these nice comfortable new slippers on cool. Cool. Got it in the house
We're walking around. What's that? Oh, I can see the fireplace fireplace is like crackling and
There's people laughing where it's christmas. Okay, I can see the presents
It's a knock on the door knock knock knock. No, who is it? Oh, it's carolers
I gotta close the door. Okay. All right. I'm good
The game just lagged you see that shit put that popcorn down it's not time yet put that popcorn away put the popcorn down
No, I gotta tell you these cookies are absolutely to die for put that cookie down
No
That's enough strength. I need let's go joke. So bad. You failed the jump get get rid of him. Get rid of him. Get rid of him
I think I think I skipped the thing in the middle. I think I skipped the thing in the middle
I think I skipped the thing in the middle. I skipped the thing in the middle. I go for it. I skipped the thing in the middle
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay
It's not okay. It's not okay. I made progress though. Holy fuck man. I I had it I had it I had it
It's just content. I'd never seen before god damn it. It's okay
Damn damn damn damn. Oh you fuck you game
Oh, man. Oh god, it just takes
it takes
laser
lay
laser beam focus for everything laser beam just
Laser focus to do everything you game fuck you game
Fuck you game. No more swearing. Okay. I'm not swearing for the rest of the night. Slow down. Slow down
Slow down. Fuck you god
Oh my god
Damn it, man. Oh my my teeth are just clenching right now. I'm not I'm
I'm
upset
He's actually mad. Yeah, yeah just a little
Just just a little bit. I think I think just a little yeah
I've fallen down 1100 fucking times
I've jumped almost 13 000 times
so
I think I I I could be just a tad
Just slightly
You think you'd get better by now? I'm almost banned that person. I'm at the end of the fucking game
I'm at the end of the game
This is the final like 10 screens
And I have improved you remember the first time I was here. I don't even need to explain myself
I think i'm gonna beat it right now too hard, but it's okay. I don't go left. I go left after that jump
I don't think I can go left guys
No, I can't why would I listen to anyone that says that why would I ever listen to you?
That's the stupidest idea it's guaranteed to fall all the way down. Why would you ever jump left?
Let's so we let's prove that i'm glad we proved that
That if you miss that jump you'll get you go all the way back. Why would anyone go left?
Uh, oh, you'll never see me ever do that again
And if somebody like wants to just go hey dude that paper you should think about god ban them
I don't care if there's only 12 people left in this chat
I
Don't actually do that though go left and then fall all the way down to the bottom. Hey, you're wrong
That was so long, yeah, I just got sorry guys I just got sucked through like a portal
A wormhole opened up behind me and I got sucked into it
Just imagine if I had to go to the sewer. Oh, man. I feel that makes me feel better. I know and
I've lost my mojo thing
I need I need like a a new I need mojo. What do I get it? How do I get it?
I'm not sure where I get it from
I lost my mojo. Oh god damn screens from the end of the game
You man like i'm two screens away from the beating this dumb game
It's okay i'll get it i'm just gonna take me a while
I'll get it. I'm just gonna sit back in the chair
Uh, you guys will hear from me the next time I fall when I scream into my cup again
Two screams away, right?
Sorry, I said there's like there was 200 bugs on my disk I had to get them
There's just there's bugs everywhere. Sorry. I had to get all this shit load of them
Fucking close to never having to open this game ever again
It's I can taste it
And then I can just delete it out of my steam library
dlc
No
Nope
No, thanks
Uh
No, thank you. Hey germa, uh, I punched you in the face like two or three hours ago
Would you like me to punch you in the stomach too like now?
No, I don't think I would like that. Oh, are you sure? Yeah, i'm positive
I don't think that would that's something I would enjoy
Are you sure dude like everyone's doing it? Okay. Good luck to them
Dude everyone's everyone's getting punched in the stomach. Don't you want to get punched in the stomach?
Uh go let's do it
Get me up here
Come on punch me in the face. Did you not learn from your mistake?
i'm trying to get up there
and it takes
A pixel perfect jump to do so i'm trying to find it
Dude, don't you know you shouldn't do that. Why are you doing that?
Oh, i'm not i'm doing it on purpose
I just think figured it would be funny if I fell down the whole thing again had to do like another 20 minutes
Of climbing the whole fucking thing. I wouldn't that be funny
He's admitting it
No, man
You know, all right. Here's the worst part about this game is you can't
You can't just like all right. Let me just like relax and get it. No every jump has to be perfect
You have to do every single jump 100 100 focus
100 focus on everything
You know, you know, it's like god damn it. Can I get a single a single fucking break?
Ricky, all right. It's almost it's almost time for cold water dunk on face
If I fall all the way to the bottom again
I'm gonna go just like put ice cubes down my pants in my underwear
It can't make it any worse
I stuck my head in the freezer
I bobbed for ice cubes
Okay, let's go
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Come on
What am I doing? Don't go that way
oh
Shit, so when I was down, uh putting my head in the freezer. I uh
I I did the not like this emote
unironically
I just was like
Oh not like this
And it wasn't even like a joke
Now I have like a I have i'm not gonna say it but I have
Because like that that's turned into a weird meme on the channel right now, so I don't even want to say what I have
No a coke
Right now i'm having like these flashes
of
Like mowing the lawn
And i'm like damn that sounds pretty good right now
That sounds fun. We're at peak boomer
Yeah, that sounds like a good time and like mowing the lawn and shit
Taking care of my grass. That sounds good to me
Hard I gotta get back into this again. Remember I got up from the chair, so that's bad
You gotta hold it longer, but if you hold it longer than that you hit the wall and bounce back
That's the that's that's the wall right now is going past that shit. I did it once
That's the fucking wall right now
It's trying to figure out like the
The nuanced way to make that jump reliably
Because fuck I can't
No, I held it I held it longer
I did hold it longer though. Fuck man. I did hold it longer
I seriously did
fun game blast
sewer two
sewer three
I just don't get it because if you if you go
Too soft. You just don't make it if you go too hard you hit the wall
There's no in between because there's a block above it and jumping left is guaranteed
You have to get that left jump. Perfect. It's perfect either way
It's just it's you have to be one thousand percent accurate either way
You're just fucked either way
That's the one hang up. That's the only block. That's the one hang up
Just stop being bad
ee-hee
Just stop ee-hee
How's if it's not fun why bother because i'm two screens away from beating the game given up now is in no way
I can't do that
I can't give up with one or two screens of the whole game
I have to finish it. I'm addicted to the pain
I just want to get up there. Please get me up there, please
Please please I can do it
All the suffering will be worth it when I get to the top and I get the the babe or whatever
I'm looking for I went way too far. It's all right. It's okay. It's all right
Think of the oh god
I don't want to think about that
I don't want to think about what you wrote
How did I miss?
I I have to I have to like watch a video. I have to like watch a fucking like
We're watching this for like at least five minutes
Shut up
Like a good neighbor buy every ad slot
What is this two? I'm gonna
What the fuck skip?
All right, give me a minute
Just leave this on no i'll get like i'm gonna get my channel deleted
I just need it for a second. Just a minute
Welcome to jump king. Uh, everybody. No, just kidding. It's a waterfall
This is a copyrighted waterfall
It's too it's going too fast. It's making me anxious
All right, I feel better
He needed that waterfall. I just needed to see something else on the screen. That was not this
Cathedral, you know, I just needed to see anything else
That wasn't this
You need a hero put that hero music on
Why does streamer never read chat?
Why is he not reading chat right now? Is he is he reading does he is he paying attention?
Why is he not reading? Why is he not reading? Why did he read this? I don't understand
What how come he didn't look over here right now? Why did he not do that?
Get on it, please
You have two eyes dummy. Why don't you just multitask?
No, don't don't don't don't
Uh, that's fucking funny. That's very very funny. Let's get another solid attempt in here, please
Fuck i've never been here before
I've never been here before i've never been over here before shit
Oh, no
um
I just make
We're good
So close that was so fucking close
That was so close
That was the closest. Oh man, that sucks
That sucks
That sucks I was there too
Is
It's not about almost there. It's about there
Right. Oops now i'm going too far
You tried your best
Yeah
Yeah, I know
It was true
I'll try we'll try again. I'm going up there again
See if I can do it. I'll try
Do better
All right, I I can't have my own girlfriend mauled me, you know what I mean? Like come on I can't have that
Hey new viewers this guy always is mad
Only when I play games that are just specifically designed to make you hate the game
This is one of them
You know, that's that's the only time I think
No, he's worse than this
That would be bad
All right. What is this sad shit? What is this sad shit?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, don't think so. What is this sad shit?
What was that was that was like?
Uh a transition in friends
It was like an acdc sitcom
What was that?
That's what i'm looking
this is not even the original song how does it make any sense is this a cover I guess
it's a cover all right I'm breaking it out I'm in the spot I'm breaking it out I'm putting
both headphones in both headphones are in right now I don't you know I don't normally
do this it doesn't work half the time but I have to try it I have to try it might give
me the energy that I'm looking for let's see what you're about to hear is encouragement and
praise with cheering applause just for you acknowledging you for a variety of reasons
if there's a situation that does not apply to you just listen and see how you feel so sit back get
ready here it comes we want to thank you for all your hard work you're the one who steps up
and gets things done around you keep your word you deliver what you promise and then you go the
extra mile you're doing a great job where's my cheers for my cheers where my cheers where
my cheers I can't do this about cheers where they go where they go is it seven minutes no
it hasn't has it okay we're good you're probably wondering why we have asked you here today we
want to tell you that we have faith in you and we know you can do it we know you've got
takes to accomplish whatever your heart desires that you're going for that recognition you're
seeking it is yours nobody believes in me I nobody believes me I fucked it up
I can hear the booing I hear booze other booze I can hear booing what no no I tried my hardest
I know you know this want to say it again I'm so glad we're friends are you are you actually
no matter what has ever happened in my life
have always been there for me and that's the greatest gift anyone could ever receive
the greatest gift anyone could ever give you've got the biggest part of anyone I know
for the dictionary and there's your picture thank you my friend
I can't believe that gave you one square to get to the end and there's another one square
it's just a meme it's just a meme it doesn't even matter it's a meme it's just a meme it's
just a meme this whole game is a meme it doesn't even matter congratulations you did it I didn't
you didn't let anyone or anything stop you I didn't I didn't do it hard work has paid off
you knew where you headed and you kept walking a straight line toward that goal you took the
obstacles and made them rungs on a ladder and now success is yours and it's all because of your
commitment to yourself you've earned it I can't believe I got to that final screen and they throw
that absolute dog shit at you at the very end you got to do like a teeny tiny jump onto one
little fucking square that was the final screen of the game oh yeah yeah get the boots oh my god
imagine saying get the boots when the dude got to the final screen of the game
thank you thank you for believing in me thank you for and your persistence and your patience
and your courage when life was the craziest when I didn't have a clue who I was when I kept going
down the wrong road right that's not true you guys have been talking shit all day that's not
even true and you never gave up hope you never said good luck you guys have been talking shit
I don't think I've ever heard this one this is new content I've never I haven't heard this before
I think I only heard the first one there's one out of two I think this shit was 30 bucks like
20 years ago by the way listen listen up yeah all this is for you you know you've been working
really hard and sometimes you think it's never gonna happen but it is it's it so don't give up
you're almost there I am you're right don't stop now just keep going I'm gonna try finish line is
closer than you think it is we can see it I did I already did see it it's my turn I'm gonna be
another streamer that's beating this game it's been like a thousand of them so far
it's true ass is always more than half full you're smart and you're courageous
you tell the truth you stand up for what you believe you learn from your mistakes and you laugh
ha ha ha ha ha ha yes I do
and when you dream you inspire others to dream
no no no no okay is there any more cheers there's one more one more applause with no words
somewhere inside you know the reason why everyone is cheering you I do just remember
remember what remember what remember what remember I don't know remember what remember what
he didn't tell me what I should have he didn't tell me what to remember
he didn't tell me what to remember and there's the bird there's the bird I got the bird too
give me that coin hey hey hey hey I get it I get it I get it I get it always remember you fill in
the blank right unbelievable always remember you fill in the blank after that because you know you
can do it he doesn't need to tell you what you can and can't do he's not going to give you that
advice you have to make that book you have to write that that could be the best piece of media
that's up there uh with the Mona Lisa and Ghostbusters 2 I think for top five media ever
made I believe I fucking did it oh all right give me a second what say it again you did it
good job give me give me a kiss oh you did it good job I can't believe I did it right now
stop talking shit about you thank you I love you god what a what a what a fantastic day
I love you too I just I was in the middle of saying it she's gonna kill me okay oh we're good
I'm okay oh we're good holy shit I can't believe cheers to you worked it just took a little while
took both CDs and that's not even the hard part of the game I didn't even get the coin go get
that damn coin I'll do the DLC I'll give you this I'm gonna go check the DLC up I've only been
live for four and a half hours I'm good 10 hours 43 minutes 14,100 jumps falling 1181 times damn
oh that's a 10 hour experience that's not even DLC what what's is there is there an average
does anybody know what an average is is that is there like a is that good like I don't know
it's an eight percent fall rate yeah 100 falls average no way two hours is an average what
no it's not hold on how long to beat jump king what do we got how long to beat jump king
main story 11 and a half hours is the average I'm an hour under the what I'm an
I'm so happy that I beat that I was getting to that I don't I was thinking I might not be able
to do it and then I got sad and then you know I was I was like and then I I got sad and then I
got happy again that was a lot of fun let's do it again let's do DLC other babes what is that
other babes hold on I need to turn them I need to turn this back on other babes new babe ghost of
the babe new babe plus how do you do new game plus in this game do you just jump I don't how
do you do new game plus new babe plus is jimmer please stop yourself no I don't I completed the
base game jump king that's all I care about I do want to see the dlc though
oh this ghost of the baby no this is the dlc era passage has appeared yeah okay
so that's just explaining to you so why did it just jump me into the game this is the dlc wrong
one should I the new didn't just do new babe plus oh okay don't delete save what what do I do
I said no I'm not deleting the save just go find the entrance yeah I can just go find the entrance
right there are two dlcs oh okay two dlcs blind what let me write there wait wait wait what
oh I thought I was going up okay I thought I was going up to the uh to the other one okay right
right there's two right right right right I'll get it I'll get it I'll get it I'll get it I'll get
it I get it guys I'm coming down from like a huge high right now okay what's this let's go the
philosopher's forest all right fuck it let's just try it new content let's just see it I got a ton
of gifted subs and I'm sorry I missed them all I was too busy being high you know what I mean
all right let's go this way secret yep I got a little mushroom what does a mushroom do
get see hi all right there's a guy up here you look like a dude on my wavelength sure take the
hat keep it bro what you want this cool jacket too I'll be cool did I get a hat cool I have like a
hat now it's only for scholars to really be part of this academy you first got to prove you have
an open mind have you seen those nice mushrooms around this place I got one already they're
hidden every everywhere in this forest yeah that's your right of initiation man bring me
nine mushrooms and you'll be a true member of the forest I don't care I got a free hat I don't give
a shit about anything else somebody just gave 100 bucks stormy to just get 10,000 bits thank
you stormy to thanks for 10,000 100 goddamn doubles thank you they say my internet shit the
bed when I tried to send this earlier but I'm happy I was able to see you reach the end you
deserve this for all the bullshit you put up with it's it's you have to have that kind of relationship
with this game you know I mean you'll you're never gonna get through it you there's a there's a meter
that you don't want to cross of getting angry you gotta bring it back down I crossed that meter
probably 10 times wait I can go up there but stormy to thank you so much for the 100 bucks
can I get up there I missed the first DLC uh I'm not here I'm kind of here already aren't I
this hole what is that what did I just do what's going on fuck ah another innocent victim of her
deceptive scheme is it low gravity in here oh no well you should get comfortable like the rest of
us right away now that's of course you are less intelligent than I had hoped oh boy it's a whole
new way to jump it's not even the same jump mechanic all right oh no that was stormy too
it's just this anti-gravity you have to just float around okay where do I go from here then
I have to play the other one first why so I don't get used to the weird mechanic because I
will probably get used to this and it's not gonna be good okay hold on oops wonder if I should how
do I land on that oh that's gonna be hell no here we go all the way down let me see the other one
new babe plus what
new babe plus are you sure delete save wait whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what's happening
what happened what am I doing what am I doing what am I doing what am I doing sacrifice crown
remain a king what's going on remain a king keep your crown and find your own way to the other
world yes oh I get to keep the hat too nice all right let's go that's kind of cool let me check
out the other one too far no not too far get the boots I could actually get the boots yeah you're
right oops oops oops oops oops oops oops oops oops I got up there real fast damn it
get boots I'll get the boots I'll get the boots I don't know he's gonna get stuck on the tutorial
zone sewer it's been a while since I've been down here I know these jumps aren't hard but it's been
it's been a whole day since I've been down here okay all right all right I got him
should I put on the cheers to you music again yeah for those of you that just joining us
don't tell them just pretend like I found this hat somewhere ready I'm just waiting for like
another person to cycle in that has just joined the stream I don't fucking know man
I don't even know how I even ended up down here I don't think I'm gonna I'm not gonna see the end
of the game though I'm sorry I'm sorry for screaming I know like people are probably
fucking mad at me and I'm gonna lose a bunch of viewers and shit but like I
how did I even fall down here again I have no fucking idea how I fell down here
I was so close to I was like maybe two screens away from being this stupid
fucking dumb shitty game I'm gonna guys I'll give it another like five minutes or so
and then like I'm fuck I have to leave I don't even know what how I don't understand how I
fell down here and damn it just give up give up stop stop stop mods can we get involved please
mods get involved like this I don't I never do this but like seriously stop
give up give up you suck you never do you're never gonna do it the fuck man I'm fucking
believable I I never I never never gets this like like this but like I just you know I have to
fucking like put some bands down here oh I got you where's the entrance to the DLC no it's up
did I go buy it wait wasn't it down here it is up isn't it coin I'm not who cares about the coin
guys I have to go all the way up to the top of the mountain to get the coin
no who cares I'm not getting a coin that sticks I don't care I'm going to DLC
I actually did fall down yeah do the bit again do the bit again do it again do it again
there are you happy I got the stupid coin oh uh by the way guys I'm one of the four percent
of players that beat again that's why it's worth it now I get to be in that elite group I'm sorry
bald assholes who deleted 10 to 12 hours from their life and maybe took a year or two off of
the end of their life because of the stress but I get to be one of them now I get to be one of them
he beat the game without the boots that's right get them all right I'm getting the boots I'm not
going to get the boots why would I get the boots I'm only doing that because it looks cool we're
going to DLC oops forgot about that part bro get the boots maybe I'll get the boots
I'm thinking about it I'm thinking about it now that it doesn't okay well I have to actually play
the game not like a six-year-old that would help you have money yo bro you have money no I don't
thinking about it yeah fuck this jump yeah I mean well I can come back and take a look at you know
my old boots all right let me just get up here yeah the boots the boots saga was
it was interesting to say the least I remember I can't I just why would I get angry none of
this matters I already beat the game who cares it doesn't matter I'll fall another thousand times
it doesn't matter I did it I have the green hat to prove that I've completed everything
there's no reason to get upset about them check my inventory never slip with these expert boots
came all the while down but no reason come on okay here comes DLC what am I doing I'm thinking
about getting the boots so I don't have to ever see that word ever again in my chat room you know
what I mean because I remember this this shouldn't wait I have to go up the whole snow thing don't I
yeah no never mind never mind never mind I have to do the whole snow thing I don't want to do that
again that sucked it's gonna get one attempt and that's it only one one only nothing else no
attempts other than the one you're seeing right now do not let me get away with this that doesn't
count as an attempt after fall don't let me get away with this if I fall once I don't care I'm
doing I'm going to DLC and I'm talking about popcorn fall not falling like three or four
screens I'm talking a full-on actual popcorn fall like that doesn't count remember this part
you guys remember this part oh that part sucks oh that part was horrible damn that part I hated
that part I remember this part yep me too doesn't count remember how much trouble this shit used to
give me doesn't count doesn't count doesn't count doesn't count doesn't count not doesn't count I'm
not all the way down I have to fall I have to do like a like a like a wow he fell the whole way
done no okay done fuck it fuck the coin fuck the coin don't want it okay all right good funny
popcorn good okay good cool hilarious hysterical great very good fun okay fucking DLC time fucking
DLC time let's go DLC I'm imagine going back for the boots like imagine collecting the boots
can you even imagine doing that why would you ever do it I can't even believe somebody would
go back for those and now we're going all the way down I'm about to watch the DLC
well I made it all the way up there pretty quickly that was like seven and a half hours of progress
fuck off this area still sucks so don't worry don't worry this this zone this part still sucks
so don't worry all right let's count on one hand the amount of times that I went to go get a coin
and what a monumental waste of goddamn time that was that's like number five count them
don't go for the coin if you buy this game take it take it from me
as somebody that has abstained from a coin it ain't worth your time you won't slip you won't
slip on four screens of an ice level sick no coins before marriage you want
wait
give me that dumb DLC so I could just end this stream I did it they cheered me on I'm gonna get
addicted to the DLC aren't I I know I am it's inevitable if I made myself play this game two
days in a row why wouldn't I play the DLC it's like what am I gonna pretend like the last few
days didn't happen too much fuck did the last two days mean nothing to you the boots are the
DLC I don't think that's true all right DLC time let's go here it is I remember seeing this part
we already saw this dialogue but why not see it again oh it's like hey you'll never get the you'll
never get the the babe right yes I will oops hmm snow don't you wish you had those boots
oh not really no not really I wonder if I should go from not where this way can I collect oh I can
stand on this shit all right does it really matter just gotta go straight up to the right
and then we're gonna go uh whoa okay we're good go this way again too far shit there we go there
there we go there we go there we go here we go here we go here we go
uh I'm gonna say right yep yep yep yep yep yep fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck do the whole thing
fuck it go with the whole what I did the same thing twice
the DLC DLC
DLC Jesus Christ he's gone completely non-verbal
stop it stop being so funny that didn't work oh that didn't work to the right oh shit what's
up there bird bird bird bird I missed a bird so is that a problem get the bird it's all right
get bird I can't get the fucking bird I can't get I don't care about the bird
I was in a flow there get the goddamn bird fine saved he got bird yeah I did I gotta go right
get bird now look what happens pick up a bird and I lose three screens of progress shit no
come on man what is that who made this I did I did I did oh I did no you didn't I'm gonna hit
my head on this shit I gotta holy fuck got the bird everyone can relax I'm on a roll though
where does this take me oh it's something above my head um shit I have to go to the left of this
I thought this was a DLC this is the DLC this is a DLC like that all right oh there's a there's a
special pod over there oops oops oh shit oh shit it's ice it's ice it's ice of course it's ice
it's ice get the boots oh do the whole DLC with the ice okay cool cool it's a cool game
the colossal dungeon hello there hey hey I haven't seen you around here before if you are anything
like the others this might just make for a good show hey hey hey did they move
can they be jumped in okay uh can I do this with all the boots yeah you can do anything
with all the boots I know but like this is a as a horrible spot to be in trying to just get launched
back and that's it yeah that's it game over that was fun oh fuck was I supposed to get up there
without the boots the boots are for an achievement and that's all so I can get up there boots are
a cosmetic only they're just for show so you I was just getting you guys are just just what
why would you why would you do that to me if that's can't be true that's not true no way
it ha they have to do something right damn it I was trying to skip
google it but you google it I'm busy look I can't you google it hey you google it
that's a lot of money uh that's 5 000 bits from dread octopus derma you are one
herman munster looking beer thanks I guess I'm not sure if I should be happy about what you said
herman munster is frankenstein so cool thanks derma you look like frankenstein
yeah frankenstein had a you know what he was huge I'm okay with that frank said he's broad
ass shoulders I'll take it I'll take it man good that's what I wanted good nice all right get me
back up there I went for it and it was a mistake but it's okay I didn't lose any progress
read frankenstein on stream what all right got can we can we move on from fucking frankenstein
please no I don't I'm trying I'm playing that DLC that you're doing it's getting in my head
I get it read frankenstein no I'll just watch the movie they've made 50 times how come they all
right I'm gonna be real though why is that not been a frankenstein movie that's been made in the last
60 years is it low confidence on frankenstein as being able to pull people into the movie theaters
that has been I don't remember a frankenstein all right let's do this how do I get up here there
have been 10 movies since the year 2000 no way how do I get over there that okay now we got to
get on top of this cage baby oh baby I got up oh boy all right let me take take it slow here I need
to see what this looks like this is just the sewer again okay so if should I go all the way
to the right side okay I don't think I can make that jump I guess I can and then I can go that
way and then on top of this cage easy easy easy and then on top of that cage easy and then into
there easy easy does it and then up there easy does it and then up here easy does it all right
I'm safe here just make sure I always hold the right button hold right button what's up here
okay oh fuck I didn't see that okay oh this is gonna be tricky look at this jump here
for me we got a we got a checkpoint here not a problem for me not a problem at all not a
problem at all don't even need those boots send them okay okay okay okay false king's castle
more snow uh hello there are some books on the shelf mushrooms you should not eat and their best
recipes seven different kinds of poisons they're the guys trying to poison me five steps to an
eternal life you somebody else can read that okay easy sorry that's not a problem against this wall
here got it now huh huh don't fall out that door don't fall right don't fall right I think I have
to go I'm going for it I'm going for this oh no no oh no I'd rather have that happen that's okay
oh no now I'm nervous yeah I'm nervous now I wasn't nervous before but now I am because I
have to make that jump up there and that's gonna suck bad the coin on the chandelier
somebody else will wait I can jump from okay hold on it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine it's fine it's fine I'm back up that's gonna be a horrible job to make though it really is
gonna be terrible I'm not looking forward to that one maybe there's a hole right here no it's not
this is song okay here we are let's make this happen it's okay it's all right it's all right
that the camera fucked with my head there all right this is it no this way this way oh oh no
oh shit you deserve that for ignoring the bird I have to make that jump anyways I have to make
that jump damn it that sucks I'm not done yet now I am no no no no I'm done that's it I'm done
uh I'm done yeah I'm done that's it uh DLC is fun but I don't need to beat it who cares yeah who
cares I mean this I actually think the DLC might be like better than the actual game but I don't
care it was still fun it was fun that's fun game over I'm done now I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm
done I'm done done like absolute 100% done I'm at the beginning of the fucking DLC I'm done done
that's a fun game if I really wanted to I could have dedicated and try and probably got what's
up after that this was not too too bad I think I could probably do it I think I could do that I
mean how many more screens are after that after the castle no I'm not playing the game again don't
worry uh I think I've accomplished what I wanted to accomplish I had a pretty good concentration
there uh halfway up but you know eat my shorts yeah uh the stream's over uh this is just post uh
post stream hangout time see this is not even a stream I'm this is I'm barely live right now
this is just post stream hangout session I can't stop playing this game it just does something to
you and I I beat it already so it's okay this is not even a stream yeah not even this is not
even a live stream you're not even watching right now always remember no that only works once
this level is cool though why couldn't this level just be in the regular game this level is fun to
me damn it you're making the kids cry what kids who's watching what kids are watching jump king
it's it's there's like tons of wicked fucked up blood and guts and gore and people getting killed
they're kids watching this fuck fuck damn it okay I have to stop I have to pull the plug
but no I can't it's only been five and a half hours I can do it for 30 minutes I'm done I'm done
but okay I'm done but I'm not done whatever let's just talk hey so have you guys uh
he's chatting like he's on meth this is what that game this yeah this is what that this is
what the game does to you guys you motherfucker you motherfucker I know I'm never going to turn
this on ever again you know what I'm saying once I'm out I'm out and I ain't going back
so I've got to get by my time in it now because I'm not turning it back on I made it okay
that was jump king what an experience that was folks if you like torturing yourself I would go
get it it's eight dollars to have somebody punch you in the face three times um you do what you
want to do for the yard you do what you'd want to do with your money I'm so glad I beat the base
game I would have been so disappointed if I didn't that was I was that was fun that's it
didn't finish the DLC I know but I've exacerbated all my video game potential close the game
do the DLC uh no no I can't I can't I I can't do it I can't I know I maybe I could have but I have
I think I'm done with this game I'm done with that one I could probably beat it if I really tried
thank you for watching though guys that concludes jump king thank you for putting
up with my frustrations but they were self-inflicted I knew I was gonna be able to beat it
so you will not see me until Friday uh I have a few things I have to take care of for the next
couple of days we'll be going Friday Saturday Sunday this weekend and keep an eye on keep an
eye on the discord over the next couple of days because I'm gonna put up some nominations some
nominee lists for the end of the year war stream awards uh that'll be up there over the next couple
days there's going to be a list of categories and you will be able to discuss what you would
like to nominate play the surge too uh maybe I will uh Nancy Drew is this weekend I don't know
what you're talking about we'll probably do Nancy Drew on like Saturday or something or even Friday
whatever but that's gonna be it there was a ton of I missed a lot of stuff because I was locked in
and and and bolting so we're gonna go over the subs and bits that I missed and I'm gonna go take
a bath and I'm gonna go scream into my pillow and be so happy that I actually beat the at least the
bass game jump king I'm happy about it the ice cubes melt my pants are just wet now so
but anyways let's go back uh five and a half hours ago now let's go we had 500 bits from
guild hero I hope today you make a joke that mutes the vod for eight minutes again germa venus
yeah I did we were playing Christmas music the whole time this vod probably doesn't exist
uh thunder it's evaporated by now I tell you I'm just like a wet hot 150 degree weirdo I don't know
what's wrong with me superintendent Chalmers thanks for the 250 here are two bt tv emotes the
first one I made today and the second one almost three years ago uh the thing about the bt tv
emotes I want to slowly put them in and we're probably gonna do another emote night and the
emote night will specifically be for bt tv slots and instead of picking like five or 10
we'll probably just dump in like 30 like 20 of them there will be more paid sub emotes
if I have at least another five to ten of them in mind but I think opening up bt tv
is makes more sense because I don't I really don't want to have you know obviously if I do
like an emote contest type thing there it's it's not supposed to be a competition
and we got some great emotes last time but I would really rather not have it be a situation
where people are competing against each other for the five to ten emote slots when we can just pick
a shitload of just good ones and just put them in through bt tv why is that backwards oh that's part
of the channel points okay how's the dopamine treating you you junkie streamer I'm fine when
is the green screen stream I have postponed the green screen stream
until I am physically able to move around a lot right now my rib cage and my kind of chest
and back are kind of in pain and I can sit down and mess around like I can move
up on my chair but standing up and like jumping and falling and prat falling and punching and
throwing and diving and flipping I can't I just physically can't do it right now
I would make my issue a lot worse and until I see a physical therapist I have to figure out how I'm
gonna go about doing anything because my it's just annoying I don't want to make it worse
am I gonna play fear too yes I don't know when though but hang on to your bt tv emotes if they're
not enabled now we'll figure it out we'll do like another emote night I do appreciate any emotes
that people throw in there I think there's an emote channel on the discord I think too
you can play red alert hmm probably not red alert one maybe I'll do red alert two and I would want
to do some skirmishes but thank you superintendent Chalmers appreciate it sir can I thanks for the 250
chat germa is holding me hostage but I need you all to know all these streams are pre-recorded
and germa is still stuck in anor londo he makes me watch as he fails over and over non-stop all he
does is play dark souls 24 7 oh no I think he noticed monkey s thank you silent serenity for
the 250 why are you playing this game again you're going to die from the stress hey I'm still here
and I beat it I still I'm still here and he went halfway through the dlc cool pretty cool prove it
you're in hell thank you silent serenity for the two thank you zake the 250 as well this game
didn't look that hard so I decided to buy it and prove everyone wrong by setting a new speed one
world record on the first try you were right I'd rather have a root canal than play this for hours
germa pain it's tough it's tricky it is it's really tricky it's hard what did I say did I
say it was harder than sakiro what did I give sakiro a difficulty like an 89 or like an 88 and
I give us a 100 100 what a fucking psycho yeah I did say I hated all video games you're right I
did why would I do that the guy who rated you yesterday was speedrunning this game
that's awesome well thank you zake enjoy the pain if you must if you would like to uh hi kiko morris
sunday thanks for the 500 bits hi germa I had a dream that I was a senior in high school again
and you were a bus driver driving my class to a field trip we had a heated argument about
egg salad the whole trip which was like an hour and a half and when lunchtime came around I found
you and we had lunch together while talking about life it was pretty cool you know what else is cool
you never changed your heart hey it was a pleasure to share lunch with you in your dream I drove the
bus that's let's have some egg salad because you're epic I'm not saying that oh my god
taeyon thanks for the two dollars and 65 cents 265 bits I worry about you germa I don't know
what's worse watching you play this game with gambling in it oh no watching you play this or
a game with gambling in it no we were at like a seven out of simpsons hit and go we're fine
trust me I would know dr pepper 25 dr pepper thanks for the 250 bits it would be awesome if
you'd play dark souls 2 on stream I know people say it's the worst I'm trying to play it right
now it'd be cool to see I probably won't do dark souls 2 on stream I've beaten dark souls 2 a few
times and I'm it's just I'm not I don't really I don't think I'd want to stream it it's no I've
played it through it already I really don't want to play through it again I did scarlet the first
in when it came out off stream I wasn't I don't think I was even streaming like really back then
I did stream it once though and it was an issue dark souls 2 controls like a sinking boat
uh thank you linda irate gamer screen cap for the 500 bits that's a that's a name uh don't give up
your mom I don't really believe in you but if you believe in yourself you might do better I did it
all it took was some weird guy on a CD from 1994 to tell me that I was worth doing worth it
sometimes it works you got to pull it out when you need it I don't pull out cheers to you unless
it's absolutely necessary and it hasn't worked at least one other time I've done that and I
think that that's the third time you've heard that on the stream it didn't work in hit and run no
no and sometimes it's too powerful first person dark souls 3 oh my god I forgot about that
didn't I die in first person to the abyss watchers like 150 times I don't remember
it was like at least four hours or something and you fought abyss watchers most yeah that stream
went to look at how fun and funny these mods are to I hate dark souls 3 right I was playing
damn all right well thank you error paradox with 300 bits people tomorrow is this the guy that
did jump king without boots on stream I'm assuming I'm probably not the first person to do that
but thank you error paradox with 300 bits an error paradox again 300 bits germa germa in what
is arguably your most favorite famous quote life is pain I hate what is it that you particularly
hate what were you about to say in that clip was it a bit thank you for your time um I don't know
I don't even know what I said life is pain like I think it was I what was it I hate myself yeah
life is pain I hate myself yeah that's what it was yeah you got it easy yeah I did I said I said the
whole quote but the game cut it off thank you though thank you mostly lost with the 250 hey germ
could you do me a favor and google a list of UK pharmacy chains it's for a school project um okay
uh asda pharmacy boots farmers boots pharmacy okay well good job good luck in school gnarly
thanks for the 250 last donation for a while so I'm going to use this as an opportunity to say
play katana zero for one stream and play bowser's inside story at some point even off stream love
the streams big j thank you gnarly katana zero let's see katana zero what's it look like side
scrolling uh don't get hit side scrolling don't get hit game I kind of think these are fun
is it good katana zero is awesome maybe I'll put it on the list put it on the list and bowser's
inside story is it's ds right yeah we'll see how I can do that respected disrespect thanks for the
500 bits see you next fall mostly lost thanks to the 250 what was dora the explorer's sidekicks
name that little monkey guy I forgot uh and that would be boots boots am I winning we also freddy
dread gave almost 300 dollars in bits earlier an insane number an insane amount of money
thank you freddy again for your ridiculous monetary contribution here yoda thank you yoda
for the 250 yoda 985 by the way oh I get it I get your name your name now your name is funny
jerma I spent 20 minutes staring at butts as references to draw your lower half during the
stream I hope to god you laugh if not accept my I accept my ban um okay I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna show that that's uh okay um nice nice uh don't don't ever show me that again
don't ever do that again okay cool good we're clear on that nice sad vega thanks for the 250
jump king has been a real treat he kept me giggling at work and at home so when joel gets
the boots and beats the game with them you are ready to admit defeat no he has to beat them
without the boots like a real gamer really joel's not even gonna get the coins the boots don't do
anything uh soft we had a bunch of community subs roll in near the completion of the game uh soft
33 gave 22 subs thank you uh swiggity tree can thanks for the 500 bits thank you no messages
five five bucks thanks for the 500 bits c4g thanks for 250 I had to make this as fast as I
could when you I heard you make this joke hopefully now you can relax oh no way really
hold on really chill thunder thunder you can hear hold on listen you can hear it sounds like he's
down a hallway screaming you can hear acdc guy going like somewhere in a room that's in like an
abandoned hospital listen to that is that me that's me oh shit hold on
um this is like you went to an acdc concert and you will like black out drunk on a bunch of drugs
just like you can't even enjoy the concert well c4g that was fucking perfect here's a
here's a link to everyone's the lo-fi uh low five beats to uh stream to apparently here it is
thank you c4g uh cream corn thanks for the five community subs adventure mf dan five community
subs mole man five community subs plushy three community subs matters of darkness five community
subs pie matians 10 community subs that was right when I beat the game that's a lot of subs guys
thank you so much all of you for your ridiculous contributions thank you hope you had fun on the
stream I did look at the thumbnail to the song yeah that's from yesterday what a couple of
wacky goddamn streams we hit I think we hit every single emotion today anger sadness excitement
fear happy um cold from ice and underwear that's another one heat hot hot cold slime like slime is
an element right I had like slime all over my hands we had everything we have everything happened
today but thank you seriously uh fluder was taken thanks for the 400 bits no message they just say
pog was ad thanks for the 250 did a great job clap now go to the dlc it got halfway through
the dlc and then I figured out like nah let's show the community subs now and switch over to our
I'm gonna bump you here I'm sorry about this let's get a bump you here come all the subs
thanks again there's still a few more bits to get through but I want to say we'll see you on friday
friday I know that the streams have been starting at four recently instead of the last couple months
of starting at like one or two pacific uh but that's just there's been a few errands that I've had
to run pretty much all week that are taking up time in the beginning of the day so after this
weekend after this friday saturday sunday we will go back to the normal one to two pm but for this
weekend we're gonna stay on about four o'clock pacific there's still a few things that have to
get done but after this weekend we're going back we're going back to the around two o'clock
start time thanks again everybody let's finish up the bits we had uh royal baker thanks for the 500
bits five dollars from royal baker uh pog champ to replace the pants you pogged in oh yeah didn't I
say that I was gonna I was gonna ship my pants and leave it there instead of play the dlc
anyone have that I need to hear that what did I say somebody has to have something I said right
oh hey by the way we need to do this uh we did it yesterday um any can I get some of the some of
the things I should be embarrassed about I'd like to hear them first before I see them like on the
reddit in four days anything that I should know about all right hold on here we go the dream is
yours
okay meltdown let's see this one you can tell when I'm actually mad because I don't say anything
and I'm just like clearing my throat and shit that means I'm like blink blink blink clear throat
fucking clear throat blink manual blinking derma disgust hold on I just need to know be
aware of the things that I said I fucking fell down for another time I shit my pants I gotta go
fuck this game yeah but that's from yesterday that was yesterday I remember that scream jar
let's scream jar damn that that dude's got some pipes I'll tell you all right that's all right
oh he's gulping it down I wonder what this one is
I did the whole bottle holy shit just kept the clip that clip it somebody
my mouth is purple my mouth is purple I did the whole bottle holy shit just kept
I have wine mouth in this oh I love wine it's so great all right back to the music
we'll see you guys on Friday but wait there's a couple more uh pay for discord gave 1500 bits
15 bucks I have never donated to a stream before and I doubted you every step of the way
but watching you keep trying and refusing to quit was inspiring germa but you should have
gotten the boots it's all right everyone has an opinion on how to play the game
I was of the opinion that don't get boots and you're of the opinion get boots
we can just have those different opinions thank you for the 15 dollars thank you pray
oh no it's not it's pray for discord not pay for discord boots would have shaved off an hour
bream bin thanks to the five community subs then we had stormy to give that 100 bucks 10,000 bits
I caught it but thank you again stormy to gameplay loading thanks for 1500 bits
thank you gameplay loading thank you so much for being an entertaining streamer
whenever I'm working at the studio late the laughter you give me always keeps me inspired
when I am building levels people like you make developers happy to keep making games keep on
being the best I hope you didn't make jump king because how many times did I say fuck this is
dumb what's wrong this guy why do you make it like this you should have changed this
I think I actually said why is this here why is this even here why would you make it like that
I think I said that at least 15 times but yeah that's thank you gameplay loading happy to be
um background entertainment you just got me in a tab listening
to my bullshit while you're working thank you again so you're gonna come back to beat the main
game or you're gonna leave it unfinished I'm not gonna get pinwheeled on this I'm not gonna get
pinwheeled on this uh-uh nope not this one asparta escalata thanks to the 250 congratulations
germa985 your gamer license has been conditionally reinstated you are hereby permitted to stream
nancy drew and farming dynasty once again and those games are in brackets good yeah I've earned it
I've earned at least two nancy drew streams thank you for the uh the gamer license uh reinstation
thank you stream tomorrow no I'll be back on friday friday afternoon pacific time we'll probably just
do nancy drew so I can uh just relax or the surge 2 I don't know why I want I don't know why I want
to do that but I'm gonna do it probably this weekend I don't know maybe I'll try it I told
you that name of that stream is going to be this is the second worst stream I've ever done
or like the surge 2 dat like oh like impress me you know what I mean or like I'm willing to give
you a shot that's the uh title I think hey milo chai thanks for the eight community subs
thank you gromicus thanks with 300 bits hey germbo um my little cousin tucker is your biggest fan
can you please shout him out as this this this this this is this this would wait shout him out
as this the this it's his gamer tag please shout him out as this the this uh what well hi tucker
and thanks for being my fan thank you butt squire for the 250 can you explain this
I guess I'll try react and people give me compliments I don't even know how to react
when people give me compliments like this because I don't know I like sit on the couch
and like shit my pants and stuff and like don't get up and like then I I get like fed what this
is from a year ago I don't know I mean that doesn't happen but I guess I said that at some
point I don't I do get fed I guess hey ty tile go maniac thanks for the 500 bits hey germus
want to say that your streams have been extremely helpful keeping my head above water I've been
getting counseling and all sorts of good stuff and you've been helping keep me in the high spirits
on top of that thanks so much for everything you do much love good luck to you you're on the
right path you're doing the right thing keep at it thank you so much for the 500 bits and good luck
you're doing what you need to do right thank you so much for the 500 bits and if I can be
even remotely anything they can make you happier then that makes me happy because as long as we're
all having fun here that's all I care about take care of yourself we also had uh canic canic
the thousand bits thank you for the 10 bucks germa I watched you struggle through the sewers
yesterday and left for hours to come back to you in the same area please buy a pizza and watch a
movie all right I remember that's all right well thank you for the thousand bits that's a lot of
money thank you video game hippopotamus thanks for the 500 bits have you played jedi fall in
order yet no I don't I'm still contemplating if I want to stream that game I was thinking about
adding it to the list but I don't know we'll see we'll see if you don't see jedi fall in order by
this time next week it's probably never gonna happen just saying it did look interesting though
hey yoda 985 thanks for the 250 I'm sorry dad you don't have to be sorry that's that's a funny
username very nice thanks for the 500 bits if I see you in my dreams tonight do I have your
permission to hug you uh what do you mean see you in my dreams tonight if if I see you in my
dreams tonight do I have monkey ass monkey ass all right how about we do how about I give you like a
firm like just handshake you know what I mean like a hey there you go there you go son and what
if I get if I'm gonna shake hand I'm gonna say excellent work and I'm gonna be in a full suit
I'm gonna go thank you excellent work why won't you hug all right all right bring it in let me bring
it in here all right there it is okay nice there there we go and there's a shake too I'll see you
later have a good dream have a good rest of your dream goodbye and then finally snoozing
coffee thanks to 250 I told you you would beat it I'm proud of you stayed up all night
can we do surge to katana zero if surge sucks nancy drew and disco alcium this weekend I am not
sick or anything or dying I'm pretty fine health-wise but if I had a dying wish right now
it would be that also can you say comedies again oh and I downloaded a jump king 2 and you're right
it is strangely addicting uh we'll do surge to no we're doing nancy drew is the next thing you're
going to see when we stream nancy drew and the shadow of the pirate ship whatever the hell that
other one is and then however long that takes us if we do that we can move on maybe we'll play
surge to you what about disco alcium okay I wanted to play it but disco alcium is a commitment you
can't just turn on disco alcium for four hours and be like okay that was fun it's like a 40 hour
game right so I'd have to commit to that for at least a couple of streams at least two or three
it would be fun maybe chat would throw a fit well I haven't decided if I'm gonna do it or not
we'll see but if I've run out of stuff to stream over the next couple weeks you know if nothing's
really coming out or I don't really care that much about anything then we'll start to pull into the
catalog that's why I don't want to say oh I'm never going to play Jedi Fallen Order because
there's a very real possibility that like a week or two from now it's just oh this kind of that's
what I'm going to do today and tomorrow I don't know we'll see but that's my time I'll see you
guys in a couple days see you on Friday have a good rest of your week we will do Friday Saturday
Sunday and we'll see you there have a good rest of your night if you if you end up by the way
somebody that might if you do see Joel tell him he is now allowed to play Jump King and I can't
wait to see how many times he falls and yeah good luck have a great night guys see you in a couple days