Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Shank 2 multiplayer first look, I guess you could call this.
The official release of Shank 2 was, I believe, today or last night, something like that.
And this game is a lot of fun. This game is awesome. So I suggest you try this game out. If you have never played it before, it's awesome.
Playing the multiplayer co-op survival mode with Italics, who's a good friend of mine. His link will be in the description.
So go check him out. He's a cool dude, a good friend of mine. So let's get this started. The live commentary is going to start right now.
I'm going to cut a little bit between some things, but enjoy guys and let me know what you think.
Yeah, we're going to have to explain how the game is played as well.
Yeah.
But you are. You're like a yellow jumpsuit.
I'm like Kill Bill.
That's what I was thinking actually.
Uma Thurman up in this biatch.
Yeah, so I guess for those of you that don't know what is going on right now, this is not Super Smash Bros. Brawl.
This is a...
Doesn't it look like it? It kind of looks like Smash Bros.
I guess Smash for the boat.
Yeah, we're on the boat. But this is the multiplayer.
And the multiplayer is you have to defend waves and waves. You have to defend against waves and waves of people.
And I'm assuming it's going to get increasingly difficult. So we shall see where this goes.
We got to defend these, yeah, these bombs here on the bottom.
This one up top too.
I kind of like this Uma Thurman.
I'm like shooting up into the air.
I'm like celebrating. I'm just like, yeah.
All right, wave one.
New item, tequila. Heal yourself.
Okay.
I've got a fish.
Can you throw these things? I want to butcher somebody in the face.
What do you have?
I have like a butcher knife. I want to throw it at somebody's face.
Oh no, get off that bomb. Oh God, this guy's going to get it.
Oh, we have one down there?
I keep overshooting it.
No, get off that. I got to do more grabs, man.
Look at those combos piling up right there.
I know, geez.
All right, we're good.
I'm going to go up top. You stay down there.
Because there's one up top. If that one goes down, we're in a lot of trouble.
It's a good idea. We get to split up, but watch for health too because you are getting close to dying.
Oh, there's a guy down here.
Oh, disarm that bomb.
Got it, I got it. I'm disarming. Cutting the wire, cutting the red wire.
That's right.
How much money do I have?
Got to buy some tequila.
Yeah, this girl has like minus 25% health or something.
Probably wasn't a great idea to do that.
What is that on the ground next to you flashing?
I think it's a pizza.
What is this? Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles?
Yeah, who wants a pizza?
I'll take pepperoni, onions, mushroom.
You can definitely throw, how do you throw these things?
I am about to die.
I'm up here like being an idiot. I've got to help you, hold on.
I'm retreating.
Don't worry, I've got this thing. It didn't even matter.
I'm doing the jump. No, get off this bomb.
Oh, he threw me off the boat.
Are you dead?
No, I'm still alive, barely.
Oh my god, I am going to die. I'm staying back to my range.
I'm dead.
No, I'm okay. I'm alright, I'm good. I'll revive you.
I've got to use some skills here.
Come on, come on!
Nice.
Got it, we got it.
Oh, I'm down now, I'm down.
Oh, it's right bumper. Right bumper is how you throw stuff.
You need a heal, sir.
Oh my god!
You hop into the...
No, I just jumped down like an idiot.
I'm going to try to lead him up here.
Come on.
Oh, come on big man.
Alright, revive.
Get out of there, just run.
Leave my friend alone.
Oh god, I'm running.
I'm dead, I'm dead.
Alright, I'm going to shop shoot him.
I got him caught like in a glitch.
Okay, yeah, come on, follow me over here.
That's right.
Fell right into my trap.
There you go, alright, sweet.
Oh my god.
I've got to use more range.
Get him under the boat and I'll drop the boat on him.
Nice, nice.
I'm at low health again.
No, I missed that.
Oh my god, I'm dead.
Oh, escape!
I barely escaped.
Oh my god, he can run?
You're not going to call him a boar, are you?
I really want to.
I have enough money.
I'm going to do it.
Here we go.
Alright, let's see what it does.
Battle boar.
That is battle boar right there.
He's defending this crate.
Oh, that wasn't a total waste of money.
Oh no, oh, there he goes.
Just sit back here and unload.
Oh, look at that.
It's going to be sad when that pet dies.
I think he just died.
Oh my god, I'm going to get back broken.
Whoa.
Just going to shoot in the air.
We almost got him.
We almost got him, yes.
Nice, get that money.
Alright, buy some tequila.
Buy some tequila.
Decoy.
Dammit, I'm trying to turn on the fire.
Man, this guy is annoying me.
He's got like this grenade launcher.
There we go.
I can't aim.
I'm just trying to shoot him from afar now.
It's like shooting up in the air for some reason.
Pounce.
Get pounced.
Wait, you can use this thing?
I can use this thing.
This grenade launcher.
That's what I was trying to use, but it was just shooting up in the air.
We have one to defuse up here.
Oh, come on.
Two defused.
I'm defusing this one.
Uh oh.
I got one.
There's another one up here.
No.
Alright, I'm defusing it.
They're planning down there below again.
Oh god, come on now.
Get lit.
I got this one.
Alright, I'm defusing this one.
We're good.
That is teamwork right there.
That is teamwork.
I wish you could high five in this game because we totally would.
Yeah, be a little bit more like Portal 2.
Okay, I still got shots in this thing.
I'm just going to fire and spam them.
We're going to give you all the ranged guns since you have the controller.
Yeah, I am the one with the controller.
Uh oh, fire, fire.
Get out of there.
Alright, I prevented this.
Oh, I blew up.
They got the top one.
Oh, they got it?
I didn't even know it got planted on.
Alright, the guy below is planting.
Not for long.
Oh, I kicked him right off.
I just totally missed every single time.
I'm about to go down again, I think.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not if I bring out Battle Boar.
Awesome.
Alright, there's another bomb engineer.
Alright, we can leave the bottom floor now and focus on the middle and top.
Because Steve the Battle Boar is taking people out.
Quick, you've got no time.
Heavy attacks, man.
2,000 bucks.
I don't get that kind of cash.
Oh, they've got riot shields.
What is this?
Oh, is this Call of Duty?
Uh oh.
They've got like Call of Duty riot shields.
They're planting.
Oh, God.
Is he planting?
He planted.
I can't get up there.
Here we go.
Alright, I'm defusing.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
This could be the end.
I'm just throwing grenades.
I don't even know where they're going.
I'm down.
No, no.
Diffuse it.
I got you.
I got you back.
I got it.
That is clutch.
Clutch right there.
We're about dead.
Oh, yeah?
Turret.
I just built it.
I am dead.
What is it doing?
The turret's not doing anything.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
It's doing something now.
I need to revive down here.
Oh, I can't even get down there.
Oh, my God.
I just jumped it.
I'm so confused right now.
You still got this.
No, I'm dead.
Maybe we are dead.
We just lost it.
Wave 15.
That was wave 15.
That was pretty good.
That was pretty solid right there.
Man, that's embarrassing.
Money earned 10,000 to 4,000.
I got seven disarms though.
Hey, I do have the controller though.
Let's be fair.
Do what you do.