Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with the Q&A video, the answers portion of the Q&A video.
And this is gonna be over some Smite gameplay. This is a 10-3 with the character Zeus.
If you don't know what Smite is, there's gonna be a link in the description to a Smite video that I made a long time ago.
But if you have no idea what's going on, you can watch that either before this video or after this video, during this video.
Whenever you watch that video, that is when you can kind of understand the basics of this game.
But I'm gonna let that sit in the background. We are gonna start talking about the questions now.
And the first one I'm gonna answer is something that I've been asked a lot and I haven't really addressed it in a long time.
And I'm going to right now. It is what do I do for work? What is my job? What do I do? How do I make money?
And that sort of question. So I'm gonna start off, first of all, this answer has changed over the last year and a half or so.
It started out as me doing freelance videography work. I did weddings. I did events.
Like, I was the guy that filmed your sister's wedding. Like, I was that guy.
But now, YouTube has kind of turned into a full-time gig for me.
Now, I need to really say this because there's a lot of misconceptions with the amount of money that people make on YouTube.
There are probably a lot of you guys that think I make a ton of money doing this and I'm just like swimming in money.
I've got like millions of... No, no, no, no, no. I don't make very much money at all from YouTube.
In fact, I would probably guess that most of you guys that have jobs probably make more money than I do.
But I'm not gonna get into that because I can't talk about money. It's against contract. It breaches all kinds of things.
So I don't want to get into any trouble. But I will say that YouTube has become a full-time thing for me.
And while I have another couple seconds here, another minute or so, I'm gonna blow the covers off of one more misconception
that a lot of people have with people that have a YouTube partnership or people that make ad revenue money off of YouTube.
If you like a video or favorite a video of somebody that has a partner channel, you're not making them any money.
That doesn't do anything like that for them. A lot of people think that.
A lot of people think that if they click the like button or favorite button on somebody with a partnership,
they're gonna give them more money. And that's just not the case.
What actually does happen when you like or favorite a video, if you don't know,
the reason why people want likes and people want favorites so much is because it spreads your content around.
It lets other people know that the channel exists, which is really, really important if you're trying to grow a channel, obviously.
You want more people to see it. The more people that see it, the more potential people will subscribe
and the more people will be around to watch your videos.
And you gotta remember, you guys have a lot of power on this website.
Never take for granted the power that you hold on YouTube.
People might try to make it seem like you're not that big of a deal,
but you are a huge deal. You are a massive deal to the success of every single channel on this website.
Every single one. If you watch YouTube videos, even the view, even if you hate a video,
even if you dislike a video or you like a video, whatever you're doing,
you're part of this collective community that keeps this website going strong.
I'm not gonna get into that anymore. I will probably talk about this on a completely different video,
but I want to move on now and get into another question, because it's been question one,
and it's been like three minutes. So we're gonna move on now. Yes, I do YouTube for work.
It's what I do to try to make myself stay alive.
So this next question is a very, very good one. I got this a lot as well.
It is, what is my opinion on Valve's Steam box?
Now, if you don't know, Valve is going to get into the hardware game here.
They're coming out with a console. I don't even think you can call this a console.
They're coming out with a condensed PC. It's gonna run on Linux. It's not gonna run on Windows.
And it's going to be something you hook up to your TV, kind of like a mini gaming PC, I guess you could call it.
I really don't know the details of this, but if you want my opinions on it, I think it's amazing.
I love Valve. I think Valve is an incredible company. I think this thing is going to be fantastic.
It's gonna make the people, because PC gaming has kind of this in-between period,
where if you don't have a lot of money, it's hard to get the most out of PC gaming.
If you can't spend, like, at least $500, $600, $700, you're not gonna get, like, a good gaming PC.
Now, some people might be able to throw a PC together for $325 and have it run.
Crisis at low settings or something like that.
But I'm talking about the real genuine PC gaming experience, where you have, like, a 24, 25, 27-inch monitor
running your game at a sick graphics card, 1080p, with all the settings up.
You really cannot hold a candle to that if you spend, like, $300 or $400 on a gaming PC,
but this SteamBox that's coming out could solve a lot of those problems.
It could make PC gaming completely viable to a bigger, broader mainstream market,
which is awesome because that means there's gonna be more development into PC gaming.
There's gonna be more eyeballs on PC gaming. We're not gonna be in that minority, really, anymore.
Well, I think, guys, it depends on how well the SteamBox does when it gets to retail.
If it ever does, it's still kind of in the development stage.
But it's gonna be really interesting to see where that goes.
I cannot wait to see all the crazy things that happen with that.
They're gonna take over. Valve is gonna take over the gaming market, and it's gonna be fantastic
because they are probably my favorite company, at least in gaming, of all time.
So we'll end on that. We're gonna move on to the next question.
The next question is by a guy named Erland. Erland D. Erland, maybe, but I'm not sure.
It's about Otto. I'm gonna go over a couple questions on Otto.
Otto is my little dog, if you don't know. And he does big adventures.
He has two big adventures, if you didn't know about those crazy movies.
But whatever, we're gonna get going here.
If, for some reason, I had to change Otto's name, what would I change it to?
That's pretty easy because my family was talking about this when we got the dog.
If it wasn't gonna be Otto, it was going to be Bandit, like a little bandit, or Pickles.
Little Pickles. I actually really like that name. Oh, look, it's Little Pickles.
But we stuck with Otto, and I like the name Otto because it's a very quick name.
It's a very short, two-syllable dog name.
I've met people before that have dogs with, like, a six-syllable name.
Oh, look, it's Mr. Wigglesonworth. How the hell do you call that dog?
Oh, come in, Mr. Wigglesonworth. Just call him Wigman.
Oh, like Wiggles or something. I don't know.
And follow-up to this, got this question a lot, too, is what breed is Otto?
Is he a dachshund? Is he a pincher, a mini-pincher?
What we think he is, and this is after research with his traits,
how he looks, how his body is, his body type, everything like that,
because with a rescue, because he is a rescue, it's hard to tell exactly what they are.
And those blood test DNA things that you can order from online or you send it into somewhere,
they're not always 100% accurate.
So what we think he is is a Chihuahua dachshund. We think he's a Chowinny.
He might have some beagle in him, maybe some pincher, we don't know,
but he has all the Chihuahua traits. He's got the curly, cute tail.
He's got the big head, big eyes.
And if you look up a Chowinny and you look at this dog face-to-face, back-to-back,
they look identical. So Chowinny, that's what we think he is.
So the next question is from A.E. Samuel, and he or she asks,
who is my favorite film director?
And they ask that because they're currently in film school.
They're learning communication and videography and stuff like that,
which is really cool. That's what I did.
So if you're doing that, cool, two thumbs up for you.
But my favorite film director is Christopher Nolan,
and most notably because not really the Batman movies,
but the stuff that he did before the Batman movies.
Don't get me wrong, I love the Batman movies.
The Dark Knight, Dark Knight Rises, Batman Begins.
They're fantastic films.
But before that, he made something specifically called Memento.
If you've never seen Memento, you go right now and Netflix the hell out of this movie right now.
Is it on Netflix? I hope it is.
Go watch it. It's one of the most mind freak movies I've ever seen in my life.
You have to watch it a couple of times, but it's the reason why I got into Christopher Nolan.
And another one of his movies that's really insane is Inception.
But we all know that. A lot of us have already seen Inception.
I still haven't even figured out what the hell is going on with that movie.
I've watched that movie three times now, and I think I get it, but I don't get it. Inception, baby.
But yeah, Christopher Nolan is my favorite film director.
So this next question was asked by a lot of people as well.
It is, where is Grandpa's face? Where's the face cam video?
Where is that freaking video?
And I already touched upon this in a video last week, but I'm going to touch upon it again.
Grandpa's face cam video is coming, but I want to make sure it's done right.
I want it to be a really, really big production movie.
I don't want it to be just a sloppy video where I throw it together and oh, there it is.
I'd rather do it the way that it should be done and the way that Grandpa would be proud of.
So it is coming. Don't worry. Just you're going to have to wait a little longer.
I don't know the exact time frame, but it is going to be soon.
I promise you that.
So the next question is, can you play an instrument?
And if so, can you do it on the video?
Well, let's see.
No, I cannot play a musical instrument, as you can see by that little clip there.
I've always wanted to though.
One of the instruments I've always wanted to play was either the guitar or the drums.
But I could never, it never really came to fruition.
I just am not that good at that.
I can't do the hand-eye coordination required to play the drums and my brain is like swish cheese.
So I can't like make my fingers go in the right spot when I'm playing the guitar.
I've tried both though, but both things, it just was not for me.
I could not do it.
But after trying a couple of times and trying to learn how to play an instrument,
I have such respect for people that can play instruments because knowing how difficult it is
and how much practice it requires, it's just my hat's off to you.
If you can play an instrument, hell yeah, that's awesome because I cannot do it.
So the final question for this particular Q&A is going to be from Chakra Cannon 97.
And they ask, would I ever discuss my political views or social issues
or things that are considered of higher importance?
And the real answer to this one, guys, is probably not.
I want to separate my social issue, my beliefs and my political beliefs away from this channel
because what you do when, let's just talk about politics for a second.
If I were to say I root for a certain political party, the other half, the other parties,
whether it's Republican, Democrat, Independent, whatever you consider yourself as,
at least in the United States, you're going to see me in a more negative light.
And I don't want to bring politics into a channel that's around fun
and just hanging out and having a good time.
I don't want to be like, well, you know, let's talk about abortion and gay rights.
And I really don't want to bring that into the discussion here.
I would rather keep it very neutral and just kind of have fun.
And that's the same reason why I don't do videos on news stories or drama in the community.
Like, I really just don't care.
I like to stay as far away from that as possible because this channel was never really designed that way.
It's always been about just gameplay, fun, funny moments, funny things.
It's never been the rant channel where I talk about like this asshole in the community.
No, it's never really been like that.
So I don't know why I would change it now.
But that is going to wrap up this Q&A, guys.
Thank you all so much for your questions.
The way I'm going to do future Q&A videos is ask another question in this video
down there in the comments section to prevent me from having to do another video
where I ask you to do questions.
We'll just kind of pile them on top of each other.
So each Q&A video I do just shlops you more questions down in the bottom there.
So thank you guys again for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.