Hey guys, how are you? Resident sleeper. Resident sleeper. I'm so highly trying to get up. I'm
trying to wake up. You know when you're like, yeah. And you do like, with aftershave. In fact,
I did that already. Didn't work. You know what I'm talking about? You put aftershave in your hands,
and you rub it together, and you go. Nobody has ever done that before. It's in every movie,
with like a kid that learns how to shave. That doesn't happen. I didn't even use aftershave,
until I was like 30. Anyways. Hi, how are you? How you doing? Hold on, let me move this for a
second. Somebody just said, okay, buddy. Okay, buddy. Why is my mic in the wrong spot every time?
I don't understand. Hold on, let me move this. Okay. I got my controller. I'm ready to go. Sorry,
I am about 40 minutes late. I woke up 55 minutes ago. I was up all night last night,
for a bunch of different reasons. I've been very, very excited. Maybe, if I'm honest,
maybe a little overwhelmed by some things. Don't call me a 3k, Andy. Just wait 10 minutes. Sorry,
like when people talk about my low view count, it automatically just triggers a fucking rage
response. Sorry, let's continue. Yeah, I was up all night last night and I'll be real with you.
There's a lot going on. God damn it. I'm trying to be real and I do a fucking voice crack and
everyone's gonna laugh at it. Without getting into details, there's a lot of stuff going on
behind the scenes in my life right now. All very, very wonderful things. Wonderful things.
Not, I'm not talking about just, oh, he's talking about like projects. There's a lot of great things
going on. Some that I'll talk about soon, probably. But I'm getting, I'm getting kind
of overwhelmed. There's so many fucking cool things. And then I get up yesterday, or the day
before, and I see that I'm like on the front page of all of Reddit with like 50,000 uploads,
the serial killer image. And like everybody thinks of a serial killer. And I gotta tell you,
I gotta be careful with my next wish from the chat genie. Because, oh please, please, please,
oh please, oh chat genie, please make the stupid face go away that I don't like.
The monkey pot curls, there it is. There's the among us face, right? Oh please, please chat genie,
please make the among us face go away. I don't like the sus guy. Okay, fine. You're every serial
killer that's ever been combined together in an AI image. I am, I am not gonna use my third chat
genie wish on anything else. And I thought about this in the shower. I was like, you know, all
right, what if I like wish for world like hunger to be over, right? Somehow the monkey pot would
curl. And so we would all fucking die. And like the aliens would come get us, like and eat our
like fucking the soil in the ground. I'm not making any more fucking wishes. Never again.
Like aliens would find this planet a million years from now and the soil would be fucking so
good. It would solve their alien world hunger. Nope. No more wishes. Zero. What was he talking
about? I'm talking about serial killer AI image. I was on the toilet. I'm not, I was taking a
going to the bathroom on the second number and I'm scrolling down. I didn't know it was there.
It's the second time it was there in the month. I'm sitting there. I'm going to the bathroom. I'm
scrolling down and I just see my like, my like arrest picture. It has like 30 something thousand
upvotes on the front page. I audibly gasped. It was like, that's how I found out it was there.
I'm not wishing for anything else. Never again. Never again. This guy's ego is out of hand.
No more wishes. I'm never asking for anything ever again.
Why did you wish to be a serial killer? I didn't. Yes, you did. I know I didn't. What are you
talking about? You just wished for the sus face to come back. No, I did not. Do you wish to be sus?
And I don't know, weirdly enough, me saying this, me like talking about this and being like,
holy shit, I don't know if I like that one. So it's, there's going to be like a combination.
Nope. Don't say it. Don't say it. I'm not going to, I'm done. All right. Let's play Saints Row 2.
Hi guys. Welcome to the stream. Nope. No. Okay. Saints Row 2 coming up here. We're going to go
right where we left off, which should be, I don't know what we like 5% of the way through the game.
Does it matter which one we pick? Probably this one, right? Yeah. But it's, it's been, it's been a
while, a few weeks, few months. I'm very, very excited. I can't wait for all this stuff. I've
been, I was up all night. I couldn't go to sleep. I forgot this is what the character looked like.
All right. What are the buttons again? All right. Oh shit. Okay. So we do a mission. No, let me,
let me get, let me get my bearings. Hold on. Let's sprint. Let's throw. Okay.
What are you saying? Hold on. Somebody, somebody wrote something. They were very concerned about
me. Hold on. Remember what started out as a joke has escalated over the last few weeks
of something concerning. A friend of mine began watching you at a friend's recommendation sheet.
All right. I'm not gonna, nevermind. Oh, did the game crash? No, it didn't. Webcam or naked?
The second one. I didn't mean to shoot. All right. Let's go to, I forgot how fun this game was.
A welcome to the stream, everybody. I've got my coffee here. Let me take a sip. All right. So
let's take a look at the map. I could do this Ronan mission. I could go get some food. Oh,
15% off sale. Let's go. You know when you get up and you realize that you're supposed to be somewhere
and you have, your body's in slow motion, your brain is in slow motion too.
And you always wake up and you go, ah, everybody does that. Ah, and then you have to like close
one eye and like blink them a bunch of times because your eyes aren't ready. Yeah, that happened.
All right. What we got? Put the gun away, please. Put the gun away. Whoa, wait a minute. Once you
own a hood, you can buy a share of each business in that hood. Owning a share of the business will
give you a discount on their items. I can own this place? 5,000 bucks. Did I get it? I got it.
You now get a piece of the action of the store and we'll see $200 a day.
What the fuck is this guy doing? I'm in the middle of a cut scene, dude. Leave me alone.
They're coming back. No, they're not. Okay, so what is happening out here? Why am I this person now?
I just became this person. What? What's going on? Okay, I got absorbed. So I get a discount here
now. Yeah, we need some new clothes for sure. I gotta not be the Happy Wheels character. All right,
hats. What do we got? How about the 3D movie maker hat? Okay, I like these. Okay, shirts. Nothing
looks correct on this character. Why is it screaming outside? What the fuck is happening?
That one just looks like skin. Okay, over shirts. Coats. Denim vest. Fear and loathing in McDonald's.
That's pretty good. Get the swords. Does it come with the swords? You're just a tent.
What about lower? I need different pants. God. Why am I- whatever. Why am I T-posing? What the fuck?
Shit, I forgot about that. Somebody said the outfits crash the game no matter what.
I- whatever. I gotta go buy that place again. Fuck, come on. All right, I'm never touching
outfits. I forgot about that. If you touch- if you look at an outfit, if an outfit gets previewed,
it crashes the game every single time no matter what. Okay. Well, should I- maybe should I save
my money? Or should I not buy that place? A bunch of people saying go to the mall. Where's the mall?
Up here? All right, there's a mission over here, which I'll do that. It says mall on the map. It
does. I end retail district. Boardwalk. The beach. No, I'm not going to the casino right now. No.
It says mall. Yeah, but I- okay. Yeah, it says mall, but it's covered up by like a flag. There it is.
Okay, mall. Go that way. You can take a motorcycle into the mall. Oh shit, we're definitely doing
that. There's a funny costume store? Okay. I think I'm gonna take like the hamburger mobile.
Does this do- can I like- no, it just looks cool. Oh, it- oh, dude, Rick. All right, going to the mall.
And then I'm gonna- after that, I'm gonna do the Ronin mission that's right there, because everyone
said do the Ronin missions. They're the best. A crush lizard. Thanks for the 20 community subs.
Would you eat a hamburger with a fork? No. I'm not- I'm not a twisted, twisted fuck. What about pizza?
Depends on the kind of pizza. A really sloppy soup pizza? Yeah, maybe. Sometimes you have to. All
right, so this is mall? Cool. All right, so what's- where's the mall? What's this? Enter the
Altord Depot shopping mall. Oh shit, okay. So we're in- now here we are. I was watching.
What was the problem? What was the matter? I was watching him do that. Okay, that was-
that was aggressive. It was. I'm not gonna- that was aggressive. I bumped him. Wait, this roller
skating? How come I can't- I have roller skates on right now. Can I do that? Oh, cool. Mall is- oh,
I almost just took that lady out. All right, so where's the- oh, there we go. I want to go over
there. So we gotta go take a right. Go down this way. It's over there. Does this hurt if I do this?
Can I jump over this? The auto show? Cool. Yeah, all right, so we gotta go across. There are three
stores in the mall that sell unique clothes. Oh, cool. I always feel weird when I do this in a mall.
Anybody else relate to this? Sitting down in one of these benches and one of these sofas at the mall
it almost to me internally feels like I'm not supposed to be here. I'm not supposed to be in
the mall. I don't know why I have this thing in my brain where like if you're at a mall you need to
be walking around and like shopping and looking at stuff. I feel like sitting down it's almost
like what am I- why am I here? It feels weird. I feel like people are walking by and judging me.
Like, you're not buying anything. You're just sitting down in the bench and the only way that
you get a pass doing that is if you're holding an ice cream. Oh, okay, you've got an ice cream.
You're shopping here, aren't you? You're like hanging- okay, you've got an ice cream. You're
fine. I don't know why I feel like that. Oh, like a pretzel. Yeah. Oh, like you- oh, you've got a big
pretzel. I do not go to outfits with the love of god. You're nuts. Okay, what do we got? The bike
helmet, the cap, dirt bike helmet. Why does this have a respirator? Should I get that one with a
respirator? I want to be able to see his face though. I like- I like his- I want to see his face.
I want this one. Solid silk shirt. Oh, okay. Wait, maybe. I'll come back to it. Oh, these swishy
pants? I loved swishy pants when I was younger. Guys, every single middle school in America,
if you just sit there and listen in the hallway, it just sounds like this.
All the fucking kids walking around with these swishy pants on. I kind of want the blood vial.
You can't even see it. I'm too big. I forget without the hat. I gotta take the hat off.
It's so much better without the hat on. It's so much better. A million times better.
I have to take- that just hurt. Okay, hold on. I take off the hat. How do I take- how do I get no
hat? Can I? I think I have to go to my wardrobe, right? Don't touch outfits. How do I skip outfits?
Okay, miscellaneous. Wallet chain? No. No tattoos. No, all right. Let's get out of here.
Do suits count as outfits? I'm terrified to go look at it. I think so, yeah. No. Hmm. Suits
are fine. Are you sure? Yes, they do. All right, where else can we go? Over here. I want to go
this way. We gotta go downstairs. That'd be so fucked up if you saw that. Is it all the way
down or is it just right here? Wait, is this a weapons store, Hoover? This is a weapons store.
I had to get it out of my system by punching the air first. Whoa, there's different stuff in here.
Oh, shit. All right, here we go. What do you got? I already have that. SMGs, shotguns, rifles,
special, throne. No, you don't have anything new. Get out of here. What the fuck? What? Increase
elevation. Decrease elevation. Rotate the helicopter. Why am I in this? Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Get out! I'm trapped! I'm trapped! Holy shit, you don't even care. Can I flip it? I can't flip it.
No, it's over. I've ruined it. No, I ruined it. What the hell? Whatever. That's why you wanted me
to come here and it's been like 10 straight minutes of buildup of you telling me to go to the mall
for me to flip it in less than two seconds. Just reload the save. What? What did you say? Who said
that? I want to see what the other store is though. I can't reload. It's not even gonna put me in the
mall. You guys are shit crazy. Watch this. More can spawn. Okay, cool. Okay, I'll just come back.
Reload the gun, not the save. Wait, I'm going the wrong way. Where is this place? Down here. Okay.
Why am I so- I'm so out of breath every second. Hurry up. I watched Ernest's Scared Stupid and
it sucked. Get out of here. You don't even know anything about movies. What do you know about
movies? All right, I'm sorry. Ernest- the Ernest franchise is better than the entire phase four of
Marvel. I'm just gonna be honest. What happened? What? Like the Ernest cinematic universe phase
one I think is better than the Marvel cinematic universe phase four. I think- I think that's not
like an unpopular opinion. How do I get rid of this guy? Oh, I'm on the wrong side.
All right, just beat this guy up. Doesn't everybody care that I did this? I don't think so. All right,
hurry up. Let's go. The Eternals Scared Stupid. What do you think is gonna happen with Marvel?
Do you think there's gonna be a phase five? Like phase six? I don't know. I wonder. Oh my god. I
don't want to go too fast. I don't want to attract attention. I don't want to attract attention so I
gotta go slow. Oops. Okay, this way. How are you still alive? I just hit you with a fucking sludge
hammer. What? No, I don't want to shoot- I didn't even shoot him. The game did that on its own.
The game, I swear to god, did that on its own. I didn't press any buttons. I didn't- that was
his decision, not mine. I didn't press that. I swear to god. I didn't press anything. A chainsaw?
Oh my goodness gracious. All right, I'm sorry but how do you advertise a chainsaw but not have it
in st- in- in- in store? Where's the chainsaw? Look at the- you have so many in stock. What the
fuck? How do you not- get away from me. How do you not have that in stock? That's annoying.
I didn't even steal anything. Why did that alarm go off? I didn't take anything out of the store.
What the fuck is that thing? I'm so sorry I didn't mean to. So stupid. Take the AT- I want the UFO.
Is it back- is it spawned again? I'll take- I'll take a couple of donut holes. I'll take- I'll take a
donut. How do I get out of this without a problem? Get out. Leave me alone. Give me one of the little
security wagons. What are you doing? Get in the security wagon. It's smaller. It's tighter. It's
easy- it's like easier to like maneuver. You got tighter handling. Stop! Oh my god. I'm gonna fucking
flip out. I'm sorry. I'm gonna- leave me alone. All right, I went to the mall and then nothing
happened. I just wasted 20 minutes. I want to do a mission. Go back please. Wait, can I take the UFO
out of the mall? Oh this is- Misty Lane is under attack. What? What do you mean it's under attack?
By who? Oh my god. Wait a minute. This must- I think this might be an Avengers level threat.
I gotta go protect- I gotta go protect my home. I want to play the Avengers theme song,
but I feel like that would be like- I would- they'd come after me somehow. Play the Ernest theme song.
I don't think he even had a- I don't think he had a theme song. Hey Vern, I'm coming
Ernest B Warl to save everybody down here. Now Vern, I have a sledgehammer. I'm gonna cock it back
behind my back and swing where the fences burn. This is an Ernest level threat. Oh shit,
we've got an Ernest level threat here. That's so stupid. During a pushback, an enemy gang is trying
to reclaim their neighborhood. Contested neighborhood will be flashing on the city map.
Okay. In order to retake the contested area, you must enter the neighborhood and kill the
enemy lieutenants. Until you do, you- you will earn no money for controlling that neighborhood.
Oh shit, that's actually a big deal. All right, I gotta- I gotta do this. Oh no, what about the
caterers? Hey Vern, this car- I can't even turn this car. This car is handling. I can't turn it.
Wait, I have like a bazooka. I might as well use it. Where is he? Right there? What's alt fire?
What's alt fire? How do I use- what is right click? Am I- is this working? Can I not go through the
fence? Oh shit! Got it. Got it. Oh my god, that's so far away. Stop! Like, whoa! Eat, eat, eat! I have
like fucking cheeseburgers. Eat as many as I can. All right, somebody just gave me a wedgie. That
was- that was the sound I just made. All right, that lieutenant's gone. All right, we gotta go.
Is there a time limit? Why am I running here? I need to get a car. Hey, get in. Get in the car.
I wanna- I want someone to come with me. What the fuck? Oh my god. I'm sorry. Shit. There's two
lieutenants over here by the gas station or whatever this is. Stop. Stop it. Oh my goodness,
he's trying to pull me out. There's so many of these sandwiched men. Holy shit. I have to throw
a grenade or something. Do I have any grenades? How do I not have grenades? Did they get it? Not
yet. Get back over there. Turn the sound up. Yeah, I'll turn the audio up on the game. Game audio's
going up. I need to- no. I need ammo first. Because honestly, these weapons are not loaded
very well. This game is too hard for you. No, it's not. The game is perfectly fine. Put on Christmas
music now. I love the Ernest level threat. That's like my favorite thing so far today.
I feel like my- ugh. Okay. Take this out. I have to go- I have money that I've collected, don't I?
The stash somewhere? Please move. Why are you suddenly Ernest's number one fan?
I don't think that's suddenly. I think I made it pretty clear over the years that
Ernest is like one of the most talented showmen. One thing that I'm really afraid of is them doing
like a young Ernest, right? Like, I don't want them to make another Ernest movie. Don't replace
Ernest. Don't make a new Ernest, right? Don't do that. There's real a lot of potential for that
to happen. I feel the same way about Gumby. Don't do Gumby again. They're gonna do it. I hope they
don't. They upstairs? Fuck. I need a flashbang or something. Don't I have flashbangs? I bought
like three of them. How much bullet- this is one bullet? Shoot the gun! I'm not ready for this one.
This is too much. What was that? There's still- no, they're already killed. Okay, good. There's
one more person upstairs. Maybe not. Where are you? Are you down? Did I run by this person?
How did I- all right, we're good. Move. Can I get one of these? Save. Holy shit. Thank you so much.
That would have been a disaster. I would have quit. I would have literally quit streaming right
there. Who the fuck are you? I need a car, of course. Give me this car. I picked the word- I
picked the car. The only- this car is so old. Give me that bike. That's what I want. I can shoot off
the bike. Go. I fucking hate- I'm quitting. I'm done streaming. Been a good run. It's over. I'm
done. Get off of me. I have to stay on the bike. Jesus, what the fuck? How come I don't have any
people here defending this with me? Why is it just Ernest? I understand that this is like my movie,
and- oh, where's- where's Dr. Strain? He's off world. Oh, what about Captain Marvel? Oh,
out of galaxy. But like seriously, where the fuck are they? Where are the other revengers?
Get off of me! Get in! Is that the lieutenant? Oh, I got him. I didn't. Where is this person?
I'm- are they inside? That's it? Now I'm stuck in here. I'm in- I'm in so much trouble.
All the- you can call your gang in the pause menu. Oh god, well, I'm gonna need them. Activities?
Hitman? No. Diversions? Where is it? Ernest starts a gang war. The phone? Where's my phone?
How do I get the phone? It's tab? What's that on controller? Select? It's in the menu. Oh,
fuck. Okay. All right. Phone. I need, uh, okay, homies. Call. I don't have any friends. Who do I
call? Do I call the police? Does that work? No, I don't want- I'm doing- I'm bad. I'm doing bad
things. I want a different gun. I think I cleared it out. All right, we're good. I need to make some
friends. Hey, there's a friend. Help me. Oh, this one sucked. I gotta hide somewhere. I'm gonna put
the car up right here and then hide behind it as cover. This is such a bad idea, isn't it?
That was gonna be so cool, but I missed every shot after that. Fuck. Oh, look at how many people
are here. How am I supposed to do this on my own? Is there anything back here I can use? Look at
the trail. How do you hit that fence? Oh no. Eat something. Eat something quick. Oh my fucking
god, dude. Give me a break. I'm about to drive up there. Fuck. There's too many. They're just
appearing now. Get in the car. Get in the- Please. Don't. Eat something quick. How am I supposed- I
don't understand how I'm gonna do this. They don't stop. There's more gang members right here than
there are people that live in this whole city. They keep coming. Did I get them? I got everybody.
Go. Please. Yeah, nice shot. You got them. Don't. You. They're relentless. They're relentless.
They're relentless. They're relentless. I can't get away from them. They're relentless.
I can't stop this. That was ridiculous. They were glued to my bumper.
Actually glued to the bumper and I have to go back and do this again? Oh, I'm going- No,
get weapons first. I keep losing money. All right, snap this person's neck because I'm pissed right
now. Okay, I want weapons. Give me weapons. I'm not going over there with the double magnum. It's not
gonna happen. Which way- Which store has good weapons? Uh, I don't- Brass Knuckles is good.
I think there's one here too, isn't there? Let's find out. Oh, do the Fight Club. Don't worry. I've
got- We got plenty of time. Oh, do insurance fraud? Maybe in a little bit. Just load the save.
I guess that would give me $17,000, but I have to sleep in the bed that I made, don't I?
I can't just- I gotta live with this. Somebody said if I do this- Let me see. Does this work?
Oh, hell yeah. Finally. How many can I have? All right, I got- I've got one member. Finally.
Let's go get some weapons. Clothing. Is this a weapons store? I have to reveal these on the map.
Let's see. No. All right, is this a weapons store? I don't- That one's melee. Name him? Uh,
double barrel. That's lame. What? You don't- I don't care. Is this a weapons store?
Does he use a shotgun? No, he's non-violent. All right, it's right here. Get rid of that
sussy shotgun. That shotgun really is awful. Okay, that's not it. Is there- Where is the
other weapons stores up here? There's only one? What the hell? I'm just gonna keep looking for one.
One of the mall? I guess that's right, but I don't want to go in the mall. Why did I say it like that?
Okay. I think it'd be fun to ride on a motorcycle with somebody. Am I getting more respect because
somebody's watching me do this? Oh, that's not one. Clothing store and- God damn. Shit. I guess I'm
gonna have to go to the mall. This is one over here, right? Stop cursing? Okay. All right,
every time I- No, I'm not doing that. That'd be fun though. I thought this game was about boating.
I was gonna name the stream Row Row Row Ya Boat, but that was probably not very good,
and it's probably wouldn't have been that funny. So I just said serving up some fresh games.
My voice is gone already. I didn't even do anything because I just woke up.
A hamburger joint. We're gonna just go to the mall. We're gonna wrap around to it already.
It's inevitable that we're gonna go there. It's 3 30 p.m. and you just woke up. Well, I woke up at
like 1 40. I was up all night. A Tesla? What is this place? Oh, it's Tattoos. Okay. I thought
it was a Tesla logo. There we go. That's what I want. Let's go. Please. Please.
Thanks. I love that. Please bring that back. It makes me look tough. Don't crash.
It didn't even crash. He's dead. I didn't. That was barely a crash, right? That was nothing.
Oh my God. That was nothing. I wasn't even going. That was going two miles per hour. Why would we
fly off like that? There's a diamond. Okay. It's the mall. Let's go. Wait, I have to see if he can
hit his head on this. Does that be funny? Okay. So, I drive straight from here. I wonder if I can
like take his head off. Okay. Ready? It needs to be right here. I mean, he scraped his head, but not
really. Where's the entrance? Right here? Mall entrance. No, that's like a front door. Where is
it? This thing goes too fast. Just go in? Yeah, there's a front door to this. I can't just go in?
I think it's up. Where's the entrance? There was a huge sign for mall entrance and you didn't go
in it. I can't even. All right. I'm fucking seriously considering fucking just abandoning
that area and who cares? I don't care if we lose it. It's like a hundred dollars a day. I'm going
to go do a mission. It's right here. We're doing a mission. I need like seven people to be in a car
with me. I'm just going to go do a mission. Mall entrance is beneath you. You can't lose areas. Oh,
well they made it seem like there was like time limit. I need this more than you. Oh no, double
barrels gone. Oh shit, that's right. Poor double barrel. He didn't last five minutes. All right,
let's do a mission. So check it out. You're looking at the old toy institute for science
and innovation, but the place isn't all Jacob's ladder and irrigation shit. In the center of it
all is a bunch of servers that run the Ronin's web porn ring. Those assholes are making serious
bank off their sites. So if you can take those bad boys out, the Ronin are definitely gonna be
hurting. So I gotta take out the porn servers. Yeah, I don't think I don't know about about this
one. Maybe we should attack one of their other site or one of their other zones. I don't think
this is gonna do very much. I don't I think we should hit him somewhere else. I don't have any
weapons. This is an airplane. I don't have any food either. And of course, of course, you're just
gonna show I have to take your guns. Give me their weapons. The weapons are better. They're faster.
That's oh my god. Why did I not do that in the first place? You kidding me?
No, put that person down. Put that person down. I'm not gonna shoot that person.
Get out. Revive, please. This person is walking around with a newspaper. What are you doing, man?
Good. All right. I thought that was a bad guy. I thought sorry. I'm really sorry. I'm really
sorry. I'm really sorry. But what I get out of here. I didn't I thought that was a bad guy. I
really did. He had like he had like a shirt on. All right. Can I order food from this? I can.
Where did you come from? Show that guy because he's wearing a shirt. No, I he ran he ran at me.
Okay, we're good. What the fuck was that? What's going on down there? You see the indicator?
Is somebody in here with a bike? All right, where's that server? This way. Oh, what is going on?
Look at the mini map. What the fuck is that? I need to see. There's nothing there. It's
cars beneath you. Oh, but I thought it was a helicopter, too. Yeah. I didn't mean to shoot
that guy, but whatever. He's all right. Destroy the servers. That's not a server. That was a gas
tank. I thought it was a server. All right, here we go. They don't know you can shoot through glass.
Not this class. I just alerted all of them. All right, we got a bunch of up here. Hey,
leave me alone. This is the standoff. Open it. Open the door. Open it. I dare you. I dare you
to open this door. Go on. You won't do it. Can they not open? I can't get hit. Let's hit.
Imagine you're in the middle of a gigantic action shootout and you're the guy that dies
by getting hit in the face by an empty recycling bin. I don't know what that was, but whatever.
No, not the porn. All right, I gotta get out. Head for the doors. I'm out of bullets. Hold on.
I gotta reload. There's definitely gonna be a confrontation outside. Is that it? I feel like
way more people were shot in here. Give me this thing. Yeah. All right, there we go. Perfect.
That's like seven years of bad luck. Whatever. I don't want to worry about that.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Please get up. You can play that game.
Get the ammo. This game's hard. Sign. Oh, shit. Go. I barely hit anybody. Just fell over.
This is kind of how I feel like when I used to play Left 4 Dead.
So Left 4 Dead really can only work if you all are holding the piece of furniture together
and not one person's holding all the furniture, right? But, man, there were so many times where
I was just kind of lazy and was just kind of shooting around everything. Just kind of shooting
bullets so people knew that I was playing. Okay, wait. You have four people. All four of you have
to pull your weight. If not, you're gonna lose. If four of us are bringing a big couch into a living
room, all four of us have to pull our weight or someone's gonna be bad. You're always the dead
weight. I think one of the helicopters crashed. It's a very simple concept. What are you talking
about? If four of us are bringing a big couch into a living room, we all have to put weight into it
so not one person does everything and not one person can't lift a couch. Oh, my fucking god.
That guy just jumped. I thought you were talking about holding furniture in the game.
In Left 4 Dead.
You know, that actually would be kind of a fun game. What do I have to do?
Like, carry furniture together? A simulator? That might be fun. What am I supposed to do about this?
Oh, that was a bad idea. Where's the explosion? Why was that one done? Holy fucking shit. That was
bad. This is really bad. What do I do? I have to take this out? Did I miss something? I have to go
back to the bridge. Really? Now I can just shoot it? It'd be great if I had any bullets for any
gun and it takes a hundred years to reload this. It's finally reloaded. Jesus. Oh, my god. Oh, my
god. Oh, my god. This thing's still not reloaded. This gun's so bad. Why did I get two of these? What
a stupid idea. Do I have grenades in this? This is so bad. I need a gang member. Yeah, I'll be back.
Do I have any gang members? I had grenades. I got it. Don't worry. I'm gonna slowly take them out.
Watch out. I think they despawned. Yeah, they do. They despawned. I want that machine gun. Come here.
Got it. Nice. It's an easy two grand, I think. That was an hour later. I'll be here all day.
No, you won't. Don't call me out on things that are true. Got it. Save. We're good. What the? What
the hell is that? What is this like animated emote of like me with that like a handsome filter?
Where'd you get that? How do you have that? Whose is that? Where'd you get that? I'm so confused.
You finally saw it. Someone else put it on their channel.
That's illegal. That ain't that's illegal. Okay, now what? Okay, it's time to go to the weapon store
in the mall. Go buy a bunch of ammo and grenades and shit. Don't walk around the entrance and go,
I don't know where the entrance is. Just go in. Don't be an idiot.
You're good. You have to name this friend. Sean Silencer. How come they always have to have such
you know bad like weapon kill hurt names? Why can't it be like tree planting Andy or something?
Yeah, like Carl Conservationist. That's hippies.
There goes the finish on this baby. All right, how do we get into the mall?
How do I get into the mall? I'm so dumb. I'm sorry. Mall entrance. I'm just gonna go here
because this is underground though. I don't want to go in the garage. You can take the UFO through
here. Really? Holy shit. This is it? Riding with you is awesome. Wait, why would you be able? Why
would there be an opening for cars to the actual mall? All right, where's the weapon store? Right
here. Holy shit. That's cool. Okay, load up. I'm not fucking around now. I'm seriously not messing
around. Let's go. I want. Okay, I have one of these dudes. Is there something I'm missing? Get
get rid of this 12 gauge. Put the tombstone back on. Flashbangs. 10 flashbangs. All right, I want
SMG ammo. I'm using all my money. Right? I don't care. Use it all. I need to be able to do this.
What if I die? A melee I want. This is good. Pistol I want. What were the?
Yeah, if I double vice nines. SMG. How is there no SMG available? Tombstone. Whoa, what's that?
AR 40? Which one's better? 50 is higher than 40. So I'm gonna say 50. Okay, but do I have enough
ammo? Should I get pistol ammo? All right, I have a ton of. I have no money. I'm out of money.
I used $15,000. Was this worth it? Where's my buddy? Let's go. Where's the UFO? Can he get in
the UFO too? Where's the UFO? Didn't buy pistol ammo. I mean, I have almost a thousand rifle ammo.
I think I'm gonna be all right. Where's that UFO? What spot's the UFO on? Down here. What are the burgers?
Where is it? Turn around. Is it right here? Oh, right. I think this way. I just saved. I did.
Unedited Andy in the top right. What do you mean unedited? That's where one of the cars is. I think
it's right here. Shit, it's not right there. Where is it? Down there? Right ahead? I'm not going to
shoot anybody. I'm just using to see far further. Whoa, what's this place? That's good. That's good
too. That's good. No, I want to be able to see the face. Fireman. Whoa, this looks like a chef hat.
Cat ears. The lizard. Hold your helmet. Viking helmet. No. If I'm going to do something, I'm
going to do the... I want to be able to see the hair. Trubs. I can't look at outfits though.
Please do ski mask. Oh my god, this is Matthew Lesko. Hey, everyone. Me, Matthew Lesko. And I mean,
I got these crazy government things you can get. You want to go to $20,000 to go back to school.
I can get that for you. $40,000 to start a new job. I should be Matthew Lesko. I really should.
Cat's too zoomer to know who Matthew Lesko is. It's great. Matthew Lesko is actually a really,
really like wonderful person. Free money. Yeah. You know him? No, I don't. All right. Yeah. Okay.
I don't know him, but he seems like a really, really nice person. Parasocial Andy. No, I'm just
saying like the way that the person's presented. Just quiet or I'm going to, I'll ban everybody.
Paris. I kind of want the lab coat. Flasher coat. Oh, all right. This is, I think I'm going to go
with the, with the Matthew Lesko. I got style level one. Okay. Oh shit. I get 5% more respect
during activities. Okay. I need to do this. I got to change this to the same color. Is it like purple?
Like a dark purple, like a purple pink. Where is it? Where's the green? Is it yellow? Where's yellow?
This is darker. There it is. Oh shit. I can just look at the color right there.
Solid. Oh, the hearts. I think solid because the question marks will clash.
Okay. I need a better hat though. Human eyes. Oh. Do cat ears, please. Ski mask. Fine. I'll do the
ski mask. What is it? Under, over shirts? Yeah. Under shirts. Oh, it takes off the coat. I can't
do the ski mask. Does it take, it takes the coat off, right? I don't think it does. Okay. Well,
I'll try it. Let's see. Okay. It's just, it's, I'm just in a grim, I'm just grimace. Is that
going to work? I have to take this hat off though. It's a spy. Gentlemen. This is one of those like,
you, you like combine two or three costumes. You're like the spy in another universe.
I'm the spy, but I'm in the Batman universe. No, you, okay. Okay. I think we're ready.
We're ready to go take back the, uh, the territory. Now we just need to find the UFO.
We can skedaddle. Save. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got
it. So I'm just going to sit here on this map because I'm, I'm, I'll walk around in a circle
for the next 10 minutes. Where is the UFO on here? Where is it? Top right, right here.
It's a random spawn. Oh, top left, middle and right. Like up here, up your ass. Fuck you.
You know what? No, let me freeze for a second. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. You know what
I mean? All right. It's right there. Let's try it. Oh shit. That's a nice car. Fuck you. You know
what I mean? No, that's where I came in with the car. It's not a top right. It's a random. I,
I'm just going to get in the car and just drive around and who cares. I thought German was the
nice guy. I am. I really am. I'm, I've just been having fun, right? It's all just a joke.
Nothing I say is really, you should never take seriously. Fuck you. You know what I mean?
I want people to know that this is a place for positivity. Fuck you. You know what I mean? And
for us to come together and be good friends. Fuck you. You know what I mean?
Where is the UFO? I'm just like, this car is insane. We're just taking this thing. Are you
kidding me? We're just going to keep this. Why would I take something else? Let's get the hell
out of here. UFO or riot. I don't know what it's, it's a random spawn somewhere. Wait, what's called
UFO? No. Oh, that was cool. All right. I get, I have to leave. I have to get out of this. I've,
you want to know something? Here's a little insight. I'm not kidding. When I say this,
this is for real. Listen to me. Even at a real mall, a real one. If I, even if I've been there
500 times, I don't know where I am. I don't know where I am because everything's the same.
What the fuck is going on in here? It doesn't matter if I've been there 10 times, 50 times,
a thousand times. I don't know where the Auntie Anne's pretzel is, if you ask me.
And it sucks so bad in these positions when like stuff like kind of in the say is the same.
When everything like looks the same, everything like is the same. Jesus Christ. Because people
will ask me, people will ask me, Hey dude. Oh yeah. Oh, you, you know this place. Where's the
Auntie Anne? And I have to pretend like I know where it is yet. Help me. It's like getting stuck
in snow. Just pick up a few chairs and get rid of them. Um, but yeah, like anything that is a bunch
of stores or a bunch of stuff that looks very similar, my brain cannot put it into long-term
memory because it's one gigantic place. It's not multiple places in one. It's not multiple places
inside of one place. It's one place and I can't differentiate it. Is that enough? You have to be,
you actually have to be kidding. Can I shoot them? Maybe I can shoot them away. Jesus dude.
Okay. Almost there. Got it. I almost just blew up and screamed. Where's the exit?
How do I get out of here? Help me please. Is it right? I'm in tears. What are you laughing this
hard? How? What? Why are you laughing so hard? What do you mean you're in tears?
Is it on the second level? I think it's up here because remember
I came in this way I think. Um, I think right like this way over here. This is the top floor.
Okay then up this way. All right there it is. Is this it? Is this it? Get the fuck out of here.
I'm never going in there ever again. It's the concrete. It's the different leveled concrete
with everything same in there. I'm not going to freak out. Those of you that saw the Hitman 3
playthrough. That's uh, that's one of the maddest I've been in the entire year I think. And I
pretended I was high. So people wouldn't even think I was an idiot. All right you ready? Let's
go. Save the game. We're going. We're gonna uh, whatever. Get in there. What's wrong with the- oh
tire. Not fucking around this time. I swear to god. Open up. Open up. Good. Go. 20 fps. Let's go.
Get. Oh no you have like a hostage. What was that? Was that an explosion? Like I'm too,
I'm too much like a fat guy to turn and spray faster so I just hold it down.
All right we gotta have to have a new plan here I think. It's the grenade launcher. Oh right right
right right right. We need a new car. This brake. We have to get a new car like right now. Are you
out of the way? Get out of there. What's this guy's name? Sleepy? Sleepy Sean? I forget what
his name was. Let's go. In. He's in. Good. Silencer Sean. Okay. I'm out of. We're losing control. We
gotta get out. It's gonna explode in a minute. They're everywhere. This is unbelievable. Get in
this one. Silencer let's go. Come on silencer. Get in the car. How did you have the top down
in this car? I don't understand. Do you see how relentless they are? They're glued to you.
He's not even looking. Oh shit. Okay hold on. They're up. Up up up up up up up right here. I'm
gonna shoot a grenade. Who was shooting who there? That was confusing. I think that did that person
have a hostage? I have no idea. We got it. Thank god. How do you feel about Garfield precisely?
Um Garfield should have been a mini series that lasted like a year. I think people would be
happier. All right we got our everything back. Tiny face cam. There's no face cam.
Where do you guys see a face cam? What? Up right? Yeah. All right now that's taken care of. I'm
gonna do the other the next Roman mission. Face cam over the guy's face. You can call an ambulance
to heal. I need to make friends. I want to be able to call people to come help me in situations.
Looking stupid. For one second I thought the guy in the passenger seat was driving and there was
a blanket in the front seat. Well that was custom upholstery for the seat. Like this is what I saw
for a second. It was like a weird angle. Where's Johnny? Oh I sent him out to the store. You should
be back. Who the hell is that? Yo that's our new houseguest baby. I caught this asshole riding
around our turf. Got something you want to tell me? Go to hell. That wasn't very nice.
That was so loud my head hurts now. Why the fuck are you here? Whatever you do to me is nothing
compared to what Mr. Okuji will do to you. The oil burn? No shit. When's he coming? I'll die before
I tell you. Yep. It better. You get okay. You don't you say you're gonna do it you don't do it
you see if he tells you anything. You gotta give me at least two or three chances. This guy's a
fucking boogeyman. When I was in jail I would listen to some of the Ronin talk about what this
guy did in Japan. It's not pretty. You think he's old talk? I don't know but I'm looking forward
to finding out. You cool taking out those fuckers by yourself. Or oh here's an idea.
No problem man. Level with the guy. Put the gun down. Set him down. Be like look here's where
we're coming from. Like like order like order like pizza. Talk about everything. Be like look
we can level here. Then when they give you the information you might have you might have already
to remember. Oh you got somebody on the inside. I was gonna say then you throw him out the window
but no I didn't want to say that. I have to destroy all these right? I wasn't why was I
wasn't looking to chat he's dead oh no. What the fuck? How do I get back on the bike? You're about
to abandon a follower? Where is he? I don't even know where he is. What? Where is he? You want to
come here? I have no idea where he is. Abandoned apparently. Old up to dismiss party. Oh okay here
we go. Let's go. Don't shoot. Christ. Get on the right side of the road you idiot. New friend.
Whatever. Let's go. Oh wait we got we got slimy Sean back. What was the point of that entire U-turn?
These missions are kind of hard. Here we go. All right four to four.
No here it is. Here's four. I don't think that's so close to me. Why is this not disabled? Uh huh.
What? What are you talking about? That was four. How is he dead? It was the wrong bike?
He's dead. How am I gonna pull it out of the concrete? Get on. Okay if I get close enough
he should be able to shoot them right? Theoretically. I didn't hit anything. The guy was lying.
I guess I- my god fuck you. Fuck you god damn it. All right there's only one more come on.
Don't please do not fly. Dread air. Am I gonna catch up? I did it. Okay we're good.
Not for long. Why's that? I've got my best man working on that now.
Do some of the other missions. We've been doing most of the Ronin stuff.
Maybe we'll start somewhere else. Ronins have the best missions though. What is it Shogo?
I'll take care of it like always.
I want to buy a car that's mine that I keep in a garage. I don't just want to steal cars for the
entire game. Okay this is the loft. It's for sale. How about another Ronin mission? Why not?
You can literally steal any car for free in store. Yeah aren't there some cars you can only buy?
Aren't there some kind of- because this is Gentleman of the Row. So isn't there some things
that I can only get from Gentleman of the Row? Is this better than Saints Row 3? Um I don't-
people feel the same way about Saints Row that people feel about Dark Souls. Very contested.
Very heated. Saints Row 2 is the best. No that's an idiotic opinion. Saints Row 4 is the best.
Are you serious? That's the worst one. From my understanding, from what I've been told and
because I've never lived- I've never played these. Saints Row 2 is the combination of the seriousness
of Saints Row 1 potentially with like a little bit of the more cartoony weird wacky shit that
they did in the later games. I've heard that's the middle ground here is Saints Row 2. Sorry
I was reading chat. This is the middle ground. Um if you don't know the Saints Row franchise
eventually you can run up buildings and fly and stuff. You actually have superpowers.
It's a superhero game. They're kind of rebooting the whole franchise right? And didn't they say
that uh we can't- we have to like reel it back to reality because they went too far in the fourth
one? I have no idea how that one's going to turn out. That was stupid. What does Dark Souls have
to do with this? Um well that's easy. There's like four games in the Dark Souls quote series.
You count Demon's Souls. Uh and everybody thinks that Dark Souls 1 is the best. But then you have
people that think Dark Souls 3 is better than Dark Souls 1. Then you have people that say that uh
that Demon's Souls is better than all of them. And you've got the weirdos that think that Dark
Souls 2 is the best one right? Pleasureness. Then let me go. That depends on you. Dark Souls 2 is
the best one. I can't take anything going on seriously. Like I- should I like
drag the sliders back a little? You should go to a plastic surgeon.
The person just like landed on their neck. The person just put themselves in the hospital.
Oh shit. This is really making me understand that like nobody kind of- nobody looks cool
in a superhero costume doing stuff. You can't hear me. I know. Oh shit no. Of course it doesn't work.
You didn't pull the trigger. Oh all right. Good- good thing- good thing Sli-Sli-Slippery
is here with me. Protect Gat? Where- oh he's back there.
We have to- get off- get off the bike. Get off the bike. Get off the bike. You gotta go. You gotta go.
You gotta go. You gotta go. You gotta go. Who- where are you? Where are they? Where are they?
Do I have to pick him up? What do we do? Is he all right? What's happening? Why is it a countdown?
Why is there a countdown? Is it gonna explode? What? Flash man go now!
What are you calling me? Are you kidding me? Did it- what the fuck?
Watch where you're shooting. You're gonna shoot him in the head. You're gonna shoot him in the head.
It's easy with where you're aiming the gun. What the fuck was that? Oh I have a bazooka.
I didn't know I had a bazooka. They just give you these weapons. I didn't know I had this.
That's- those aren't even enemies. He's gonna hit him in the head.
Just focus on driving the car you fucking idiot. This is so stupid. I can't even aim this. He's-
what's happening? Who's in front of us? Why are we on fire? I can't shoot anybody with this
because it's too close. We're gonna die. We're supposed to be going to the hospital. I think
he's driven in a circle. I can't fire at this close. What? Stop jerking the car around. For
the love of god just drives normally. We're driving on somebody's house? Holy shit. That was
unbelievable. Crazy taxi. Here we go. Sorry that was 1080 snowboarding. I mixed them up together.
Can we get out? Oh my god he's running people over. Play the America's Funniest Home Videos
theme song right now. No. Where's he going? I don't know. I'm not driving. I think he's
driving to the hospital. I think? This guy is absolutely- he's gonna stick around. What's
this guy's name? Slobber and Sam? No no no that's a 90s kids board game. Whatever his name is. Who
cares? Doesn't matter. Oh that was a stupid idea but we're okay. John Silencer. That's right.
I look so happy. I have a big smile. Where's the hospital? Can I switch weapons? I can't switch
weapons. This guy's lost? It kind of feels that way. I don't have to do anything do I? Check the
map. Is it hospital right here? Oh there it is. Okay we made it. Can we get out? All right we're
good. Taking him to plastic surgery. He just comes out with like a cheek implant or something.
He's dead.
Must be so sweaty and hot under that mask. 500 cash per day. I get 6,000. Should I do an activity?
Maybe I should. What's this one? Please go to the plastic surgeon. Should I? Yes finally finally
finally finally yes finally finally finally. What do you mean finally? Okay. Let me just design
allows you to change your appearance, customize your movement, combat style, taunts and compliments.
Oh okay. It also removes your notoriety. Well I don't want to change. I don't want to change
my- I don't want to change Grimace. I wanted to do this though whatever it was. What do we want here?
The the grill? The griddler? Like a mcriddle? The mcriddler? Thank god I just saved because
the game crashed. I like the mcriddler. That's a good one. Please put the sliders back a little
bit. I don't think we- I can't do that. Crashed again? Shit. That's not good. Ooh too powerful.
Take a pee break. Uh maybe in a minute. I'm locked in. This game's boring you should play Fortnite.
Yeah I see you right here. All right can I- isn't there something I can do?
Right? This is- why is it so bright in here? Holy goodness. What the hell? It's so bright.
Is this illuminated paint in here? What? Whoa. It was 10 grand in that. Oh that's awesome.
All right nice. I got money now. I'm gonna go buy something. I finally went into a house and took
the money. Yeah. Is there anything in the garage? Probably not. No. Nothing. Gamble it all the way?
No. Oh what's this here? Oh wait there's the the hitman activities. Let me see what they were.
Trailer park hitman. Okay. You know the security security guard for the trailer park. Start a fight
in the area and someone is bound to call them over to settle the argument. Okay go to the trailer
park district and fight the security guard. The trailer park district is where? Insurance fraud
activities are really fun. It's the crutches icon. Have I found one? It's the left side? Okay.
Check the south. Okay. Change filters on the map. Well here's mayhem. I don't think I've even seen
a crutches. Should we go here? I haven't found any you know. Let's go see what this is. The McRiddler.
McRiddler absolutely is confirmed for the end of the year rumble by the way.
Kind of a hundred and all stats. Oh by the way let's talk about that real quick. This weekend
probably before Sunday's stream the New Year's Eve categories are going to be up.
Probably this will be on Sunday and you're going to be able to do them. We're going to go through
the nominating process again and then a week or two later voting will open and then obviously
two or three weeks later we'll do the award show. So look for the nominees to open up this weekend.
If a lot of people are probably new to the channel in the last year.
Every year we do an event on New Year's Eve. That is the worst of the year and some best of the
year as well. Talking the worst stream of the year. Worst noise I've made the whole year.
The worst face I've made the whole year. The annual tradition. We're going to keep it up again
this year. If you'd like to participate. You remember an exact moment in time where
you were like that face was awful and it was disgusting. He looked terrible. His hair looked
awful. Worst hair. Give us the timestamp. Give us the clip. We'll go from there. Annual cyber
bullying of the streamer. The worst hair ever was last year. I know and it'll never get. I don't
think you'll ever find one that's worse. What is this? That's a new icon. Fight club. Are you
going to stream the game awards on the 9th? Yeah I would say so.
The right idea. Horse pussy man. I can break any of those assholes that are fighting if I was
cleared. The fight's going on now. Yeah. Shit I might as well take your spot. Hey you can't do
that. Yeah why don't you run and catch up. Hey fuck you asshole. Okay. Compete in brutal fighting
matches for cash and respect. Pick up and eat food to recover health. Kill all the fighters and
survive. Two one. I got a good tactic. It's called run and let them fight each other first. Oh wait
it's 2v1 never mind. Is that illegal? Wait you can kick people in the balls. That's not illegal.
I feel like it would be really. Oh shit. They just dropped that on his head. Finish opponents
after a knockdown to take them out of the fight. I don't know what one is. It's A. Where'd you go?
That guy didn't have a chance. I feel like I'm going to be really good at this.
A hundred bucks. That's a lot of respect. Let's keep going. Okay level two. Three two one.
Go get style points for taunting. Come on give me the trash. Put that down. Get out of here.
Shit he has it. That thing's too hard to swing. Wait what's two? Oh no that's bad. A or is it B?
Okay it's X. Two is X. Dude I just keep changing. I don't know what these are.
With the command prompts. I'm just gonna have to pick up the fucking mouse and do it.
What is it? Game. I just fucking. If I press. I just right clicked and the fucking window minimized.
What is right click on the controller? Right click. It would be left trigger. Yep. Blunt.
That didn't. That hurt me. That didn't even do anything good for me. Oh very cool. Nice. This is
a really good way to farm respect. 3v1. All right this is gonna get hard. Especially because of the
not knowing what the buttons are. Hit him. Oh rock bottom. Rock bottom. Why did I stand up and fall?
This is an unfair weight class. Left. Left click is right trigger. Right? Yeah. It's just confusing.
What is it? That's. No god it's left. What is that? Left trigger. Left click is right trigger.
Because that's. Shoot. That's. Okay I'm pissed. Left trigger is aim. It is?
So it'll be right. Left. So it'll be right trigger. Okay. There we go. All right. We're good.
I got a little weird. Left is right. Yeah. It's confusing me. Yeah the button prompts are supposed
to be in the mod. I looked back at the um like at the mod files. It's supposed to be there.
You've unlocked the nut punch. Okay. There's an option in the installer. Yeah. You didn't pick
that option. The installer I was kind of scared of. Because it was like just build it the default mod
the way that the mod is meant to be played. Or you could go through and pick stuff and it would
add it but it wouldn't. I don't know. It was confusing. As you play Saints Row 2 you unlock
rewards. To see them press the pause menu. Is it going to be impossible? Maybe they actually are
fighting each other. They are. All right. Just run away. Come on gridler. You need to save.
All right. That guy. That's the guy to beat right there. The Hurricane Rana guy. It's the Abyss
Watchers. It is. I just hit myself in the face with the trash can. Are you kidding me?
I need a hamburger on the ground. What is it? Two. Start. Give me it. Drink it. That feels like
cheating. I feel like I'm drinking Estus. Fight. Fight each other. Don't just fight me. This guy's
close. All right. This guy's done. That was the really scary guy. He was doing like roundhouse
kicks and shit. How many levels are there? Ten. You can switch your fighting style at the surgeon.
If you drank the Estus flask at any point in Dark Souls you're not a real gamer.
That's fine. Five people. I'm not going to be able to string any combos together on anybody.
I don't think at least. I'm just spamming. I don't even know who I'm hitting. Dark Souls
Resident Sleeper. Really? People love that game. What do you mean?
There's one guy that doesn't like Dark Souls. You know there's one guy for everything. Always
remember that you are the one guy for something. Always. No matter what. I'm trying to think of
what I'm the one guy for. There's probably a few things. What am I the one guy of?
What opinion do I have? What thing would I say? The sus guy. Well I'm not though.
I hope they booed that. Damn it. This is really easy to do though. I'm farming respect. Get him.
Get him. Wait hold on. I'm trying to hit an audience member. Are you streaming the game awards?
Yes. In my special outfit. 11,000 respect. Nice. There's more. One, two, three, four, five, six.
Are we really going to put ten people in here? No way. I have $20,000. This is awesome. All right.
Focus. The second somebody kicks somebody in the balls everything's stopping and then this person
is gonna get thrown out. I'm gonna get fucking beat up on the way out of this place. I'm gonna
get my fucking face kicked in all the way outside of the restaurant. Save the game. Whatever. Like
the arena. I don't know why I said restaurant. That's true. Kick him. Let me up. Get away from me.
God damn it. See I kicked somebody in the balls and now everybody wants to kill me.
I'm gonna lose. Oh wait he's got me. He's gonna break my neck. I didn't know they could do it to you
too. I'm just gonna be a vulture. What the? Oh it changes. No I wanted that. Give me that.
Omega low five-year-old. What do you mean five-year-old? I'm okay. Everything's fine.
Presidency. I know I'm just like doing this over and over again but I'm getting so much
money and so much respect. It's barely really helpful. Game's gonna crash. I hope not.
Can I save it right now? What? Progress during this activity will not save. That's annoying.
Please. Okay there we go. Saves what level you got up to. All right. Holy shit. Five grand. Holy shit
this is awesome. I unlocked pump. Your melee attacks now do a lot more damage. So okay somebody
correct me here. If I exit this, save it, and then go back. Can I play at level six or do I have to
start at level one? Well that was it. That actually was the whole thing. Oh okay. Nice. I got a ton of
respect for that. I'm at time seven respect. Cool. All right let's go. Where should I do the...
What else is down here? I'll do insurance fraud. Yeah yeah yeah. Over here? Do insurance. I'm going.
This is so much fun. Can I tell you guys that? Can we just talk? I didn't get very much sleep
last night. I'm so fucking excited. I can't wait. It's gonna be so much fun.
Ugh. There's so much fun shit to do. I just want to scream it at you. You know what I mean? I want to
scream it so loud. I want to yell at you. It's all I can think about. I can't think of anything else.
Is that it? Immolation derby. That sounds like fun. I'm doing it. What are you talking about?
I'm talking about 2022. It is going to be a lot of fun. Where is this? The streamer is vague. Yeah I
know. Congrats on the kid. You know there was one point where I wanted to hire like a five-year-old
actor to come in the room and be like. Like dad. Like can you. I'm scared. Can you read me a story?
And I was gonna be like it's okay son. I'll be in there in a minute. I was gonna have like a
five-year-old actor like be on stream and pretend to be like my son. People would be like what the
you have like a six-year-old? What? And I'd be like yeah I just got I've kept it private you know.
Okay select your car for the demo. Oh I select my car. There's gonna be an actor. It was gonna be
an actor. That would have been fucked up. Okay car. I want this. Level one. Level two. Oh wait
I only have one point? What do you mean one point? Make it a fully grown adult actor?
You don't think that would have been weird? You don't think that was it's weird if a full
grown adult walked in here and was like asking me to like read um are you serious? My version
was weird but that one's the the funny one. I think I'm gonna do defense. Eight car demolition
derby and destroy your opponent's cars. Let's do it. Three two get an elderly actor.
Just let them fight each other. Oh no. Have hire an entire family. I already did that.
I already did that stream. You may not have been here when I did but I did that already.
Those of you that want some lore uh go to go type in the family dinner. German985 into like
YouTube or Google. I already did that and people hated it. People fucking hated that stream.
They were like it was so awkward and scary. I hated every second of it. The editor of that
video said that's my least favorite thing that I've ever done for the channel. I was like I'm
sorry. Oh my god dude. What the fuck? What are they all doing? They're all going after me.
I'm gonna explode. You have a money goal I have to hit? Yeah but these guys all have
additions to their car. This car sucks. This one sucks. Why are my ears ringing? Get me out of here.
Why are my ears ringing? All right so is it this one? Come on what is it? Is this what is
the heart? What is this? Oh um uh I think we're gonna walk by this one for now. Where's the
insurance fraud? All right if it's not this one then it's gonna do the brown emission. It's not
TOS. Yeah I escort activity to me feels like something I would need to be careful of on stream.
It's 1500 bucks? What? Oh okay there's somebody very very there's somebody in the car.
Don't crash. I'm trying not to. It sounds like the Macho Man Randy Savage videos where he's
breathing and just it's only the breaths that are edited. It's just like no Jesus god no 12
seconds please. 12 seconds please. It's enough to take me to the boiling point.
1500 dollars I'll take it. How come? Give me my money. What's it doing? This. It's like jeep. Hold on
stop. It's my favorite shitty rift. Anybody else have a favorite shitty default rift?
Shake it. Riff riff. Yeah whatever. You know what I meant. Okay right there. Let's go. There's
nobody driving that. Oh I was about to let go. There's nobody driving that. What's up?
That's not that one. Okay I'm so fucking done with this. I just it's the sex palace. I don't
want to go in there. All right you guys keep talking about this insurance fraud mission
but it's not on the map. Is it just is it rare? How rare is this? It's above the burger.
I could have pissed so bad. What's down here? I swear to fucking god arrest me. Just take me to
jail. Arrest me right now. I'll go to jail willingly. Please. I just almost I peed.
I actually that little drop of piss came out that scared the shit out of me.
There was no reason why I was going to get struck by lightning underground or anything.
I almost peed and I think I may have. It's not there. Off left island. How do I get here?
Is this like the prison? A power plant. Top right museum district. Okay right here.
This is really far away from where I am right now. I'm gonna take a pee break after this.
I'm not gonna do the mission. I'm just gonna get up there. Yeah why is it so bright? I want
a motorcycle. It'll be faster. Never mind because my gpu is fucked up. You should bottle and sell
your urine. You guys are actually fucking crazy. It's just a constant stream of just nonsense.
What have I done to you? Ah here it is. I'm gonna like once a week or something I'm gonna start
doing like math problems on stream. We're gonna talk about like logic problems. We're gonna talk
about like life skills. All I see over here now is like serial killer. Pee. Drink his pee. I'm
gonna drink his piss. I'm gonna put his piss in my mouth. Like I gotta like teach you guys stuff.
He pooped his diaper. But diaper poo poo. Like I gotta teach you guys some things.
But I don't think I can change the way an entire profession thinks about gender.
If I get in the brilliant book of world records for most patients served,
I think that would send a message that women are just as proficient if not more so than their male
counterparts. All right. Weren't you literally a teacher? Where are you going? No I literally
handed out worksheets and didn't know anything going on in the class. Oh no surgery takes a
lot of time. I need you to fake multiple injuries so I can treat you faster than I normally could.
It actually terrified me terrified me when a student had a question.
It was so sad and it was so wholesome. They come up they'd be like oh I need help with this one.
And I'd just be I feel like okay yeah I don't I don't know anything but you need help and I
want someone to be able to teach you and help you. And I think I would say you know how about you
try your best and try do what you can and when the teacher's back you'll be able to
go back and forth with the teacher. But how do I do it? Well I mean I I know but I want to make
sure that you know so you're prepared and I'm just here to make sure that you can figure it out on
your own. I didn't listen to a single thing in that cut scene so I'm just gonna go pee.
But anytime I'd say I'd hear the sound because I'd be looking down just gonna look at the desk and
shifting papers around pretending I was an important adult you'd hear the
of a chair moving back. I'd be sitting there going no no no no please don't come up here
please don't come up here and tell me how to do algebra or like how to do like long division
please god. And then then you'd hear a couple steps to the desk they're coming up here and
they're gonna ask a question please don't please please ask anything else. Uh can I go to the
bathroom? Yep oh absolutely I'll give you a hall pass for that. Come over here have a seat. Oh yeah
let me give it a big signature on it. Oh Mr. Albertson here it is take that. I am a teacher
go ahead. And you by the way you got five ten fifteen minutes whatever it takes go do what
you need to do I can sign that I'm an adult. And I felt great I was like thank god it wasn't a
question because you're just teaching a preschool. No I shouldn't teach at all. It was like a thing
that I did because I was just trying to do something like that I thought was interesting.
I was like oh that sounds like an interesting job. I mean I'll try that teach us something.
Okay I do teach you guys things all the time I think. I feel like you guys have taken some
things from this stream very important stuff. Of course you have. For instance one of the things
you take from the stream is that holding your urine is not good. Your teacher has peed his pants
like pee came out. So you take from the learning experience here you've learned that. That if you
need to go you should go and you should not waste any time just do it get up there and use the
bathroom. I'll be back. The game crashed. I don't know when I saved it but I think it was I think
it was pretty recently. I think we're fine I'll be back. I didn't pee my pants. I'm a comedian.
I'm a comedian. I tell jokes. That's what I do for a living. I'm a comedian.
Come see me at the fucking funny factory okay. I'm there every Friday. I hope that I don't I don't
actually do that goodbye. Kind of hot in this room right now. Teacher's gone for 15 minutes we can
leave. I wasn't gone for 15 minutes. I'm here. All jokes aside I hope I still saw Jermad do stand up
once. I went to the funny factory hoping to see my favorite streamer dish up some comedy. The entire
time he just wouldn't stop talking about his uh penis. I guess he kept saying it like that. Nobody
laughed. You know what you said there is is a sadly inaccurate because like jokes like oh my dick
oh my oh my dick. The audience will be rolling. Let me tell you guys something about my dick.
People just start laughing. We're just so much more high brow than that here.
I'm shitting and screaming. Yeah that's much higher. Higher. What was that? I just breathed
pretty hard out of my nose. I think you're right. Say happy birthday to uh some spinach.
Something spinach. Happy birthday spinach. All right let's go back to what we're doing.
We'll play some more Saints Row. By the way uh Sunday. Sunday is confirmed I'm playing uh
Resident Evil 6 co-op with Salix. We're not going to beat the game. We're going to play it until we
both complain enough that we both just leave. Are the course really? You know. You mind if I sleep?
No go for it. I apologize if I wake you up when I scream or laugh really loud at a car accident.
All right let's open the game back up. Which it crashed. Hopefully we didn't lose too much
progress. I don't think we did. Resident Evil 6 is so bad that it's a good game. Yeah I played
it once years ago. I was going to make a video on it but the game was so bad that I was like I
don't even care. I don't want to play more than 40 minutes but we're going to stomach through it.
We're going to force ourselves to do it. Uh good they're both exactly the same place. Um
might as well just go for it right. We're right here.
Insurance fraud oh you're right. I'll go back.
This mask is skin grafted onto my face.
You should upgrade your base.
I've been streaming for three hours. Wow that's surprising. I didn't want to hurt anybody.
Nothing. There's nothing on the radio.
What you did now. That was me humming the whole time.
Excuse me. Now what are you doing? Stop it. Don't don't make me do it.
Don't make I'm a pirate. I know I'm a pirate. Don't make me look at that thing you wrote in
chat. No what are you doing? Stop my Wellington. Stop that. What are you doing in my Wellington?
Stop it. You know everybody hates it. I do too. I'm so fucked up I have to say it though. I'm
a fucking goddamn. No what am I? I like impulsively have to do something that I see. What is it called?
A monkey? You're a sadist? All right we have to. Oh it's an earnest level threat. Orange threat
level is that what is that? Okay I see a guy like this walking around. I'm what the fuck is going
on? What the fuck? Jesus Christ. Eat eat eat eat eat eat drink eat eat eat something. Eat eat
something. Eat something. Eat something. What the fuck? I it's just shocking to me. I don't even
take a fucking anything. I can't even walk. I didn't god damn it. I didn't want to. I wanted
to right click. Right not. I wanted to right trigger. Oh my fucking god. I'm fucking leaving
this mission. Oh my god. Is it like body armor? Don't right. Don't left trigger. Please watch out.
Please. Yeah please watch out. Please god. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Please. Put you
motherfucker. Put down. Put him down. Put them down. Put them. I was trying to melee. I was
trying to melee. I was trying to melee. I was trying to melee. I was trying to melee. I was I
thought it was melee. I thought it was melee. Melee. Melee. I was trying to melee. Oh my god.
I was trying to melee. I thought it was melee. It's not. I'm so fucking sorry. I was trying to
do the melee attack. Get me out of here. Oh my god. I was trying to go up and do it. Where are
we? What? How are we driving around like this? Will you please get. Okay. All right. We got him.
No we didn't. This is going to explode. Isn't it? Don't worry. You're playing a game. I don't. I
don't want to die. I don't want to hurt anybody. We win. They're not real. I die. I don't hurt
anybody. He thinks it's real. It's not. Hello. What happened? You've run over probably 500 people.
Why do you. I went to the airport to save. I can't. Once I saw the leader of the saints making a move
towards the terminal. I made my way to the plane so I could evacuate your father. His entourage
willingly gave their lives to ensure safety. What happens when the matrix happens? No. Your
father made it quite clear he doesn't wish to speak to you. Anything you have to say to him
will go through me. Sayonara. Oh the fucking McRiddler. Yeah. The McRiddler is a fucking
menace. Jerma has overdosed on normal pills. What do you mean? What does that mean?
What does that mean? I don't even know what that means. The McRiddler is a terrorist. No.
The McRiddler is a chaotic good character. Okay. Like every other character that anyone has ever
made. Every single person's chaotic good. Nobody wants to be lawful good. Nobody wants to be lawful
neutral. Nobody wants to be neutral. Everybody's chaotic good. I'm chaotic good. I'm a good person
but I'm on my own rules and I'm kind of crazy and I do crazy things. Is this a customer? I was
waiting for him to get out of the way but I don't care. You're faithful to good boy. Yeah. Where is
this customer? Yeah good we went over this before. Good boy but a bad guy. You can be a bad guy and
a good boy and uh-uh. What's the difference? Slow and steady. Not this again please. How am I supposed
to get there in a minute? This is a this is ten dollars. Did you want to drive in a circle?
Hold on. I gotta read this. What are you saying? Remember the McRiddler was only chaotic good for
one writer's run back in 1972 to 1974 and it wasn't even that good. The definitive version of
this character has existed for over 50 years and no one agrees that a two-year run has any bearing
on who he was made to be okay? Just because your uncle wrote the run doesn't make it right. Oh
really? Uh so the Dark Knight trilogy considered to be the best run of Batman ever and we don't
say that though. Everything no. Everything else is is is the right one right? You're excused. Game
crashed. Good thing I saved it right there. I wonder how um the new Batman movie will be. I feel like
it's gonna be pretty good. I didn't watch Ernest Saves Christmas yet. Am I allowed to be here? You
have until the 25th. So you got plenty of time. The McRiddler is the worst of the rat man's rogues
gallery. Yeah you got plenty of time. You have the whole month of December. You're good but this
has something happening outside. All right insurance fraud right? Are these guys on my team?
Oh my Jesus Christ. Where are they going? Don't shoot the gun. Did I kill the guy in the front
seat? Oh wait they didn't see me steal this car. Does that mean that? Of course you did.
I didn't think I could roll up in the car they were just in as a guy that wasn't a police officer
and did what? They I I'm not gonna get in trouble for this. They don't know it was me.
What am I smoking? What's what am I talking about? All right where was that? I was over here.
Oh I'm just an officer except I'm the McRiddler. If the McRiddler pulls up in a cop car he took it.
He's not a police officer. All the normal pills. What are you talking about? Why you keep saying
that? Where's the insurance fraud? There's too many things on the map. It's the crutches right?
Where are they? Where are they? Museum district. Oh it's because okay it's because the game crashed
before it saved. I understand. What's this McDonald's car? What is this? Holy shit I want that.
The McRiddler has to have this car. This is I'm gonna I have to save this one.
Holy moly. I gotta go to a garage right now. Where's the nearest garage? Up here. What's
this place? Oh a penthouse loft? Where should I save it? I'm gonna buy this place whatever it is.
It's downtown left. Let's go. Don't mess this car up. Remember you're not a fan of the McRiddler
unless you know his whatever. That's really funny but I don't even want to read it. I swear to
god some of you guys are the funniest motherfuckers ever. Everyone talks about chat like oh chat's like
yeah fuck fuck chat chat's like oh fucked up I don't like it. A lot of you are right? But man
there's a huge percentage of you guys that are fucking absolutely hysterical. $50,000 god damn
it. I'm not going to tell you the the percentage that I think that is because I don't want you else
to get your egos inflated. I can't afford that. What can I afford? Can I afford this one? This is
a penthouse. I highly doubt that. We're just gonna bring it back here. No crashes at all please.
I really liked Nolan's Batman. Yeah okay on a rewatch recently it was like yeah this is still
really good. I have some issues with it. I think it's probably the best version of Batman although
I do like the Michael Keaton Batman. I think that was still really good too.
It's tough. Danny DeVito as the penguin is I don't think you can ever get something that's better.
Dude scratch this car. I scratch your life out. Just make sure you know that. Get out of the way.
I don't want you to don't smudge up the paint. All right we made it. Okay bring the car here
into the garage. Yes yes. So why am I zooming in there? I don't know. I did not mean to do that.
So will this always be here? Okay if this explodes outside somewhere will it still be in
this garage? Oh that's amazing. Thank god. That's incredible. All right so now let's go over here.
This way right? Yeah now I can just drive around like an asshole. Perfect. Geez it's fast. I'm
going through the bottom of the car. Saved. I just saved. I did didn't I? Hot dog Batmobile.
It's not even the right one. Wait it's not the destination never mind. Not the destination.
Clean. Very clean. Being chat spam a copy pasta.
Would you like to know the percentage of the funny people?
All right let's actually do this this time. I'm gonna fight to the death for the Hamburg Larini.
It's not bad.
Most patients served. I think that would send a message that women are just as proficient if
not more so than their male counterparts. All right. Where are you going? You said you were
planning on treating more patients so I figured you wanted me to hurt some people. Oh god no.
Surgery takes a lot of time. I need you to fake multiple injuries so I can treat you faster than
I normally could. Fake multiple injuries? Does that make sense? Just checking.
Throw yourself into harm's way to earn cash. Okay so just to beat myself up. Where's my car?
There it is. I keep hearing bottle rockets go off. Been like that the whole game. I haven't
ever mentioned it. Friendly. Friendly. Friendly. Friendly. Friendly. Friendly. To take a dive?
What does it what do you mean press? I have to press to take a dive. Oh shit this is time
limit. Okay so am I to do it now? Do it now. Do it now. I'm gonna go so fast I'm gonna go
right into a wall. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. That doesn't count? Why are we all doing the same thing?
Oh shit oh you you fall into stuff. I get it. Oh my god this is amazing. That's so stupid. What
about hold on. Nice. I got plenty of time. I have an idea. I'm gonna go in the supercar. I'm gonna
go a million miles per hour and throw myself out of the map. Does this count? Oh shit. That's
actually not a bad idea. I have to get some air though. How do I get air? That's a good question.
Shit. It's gonna be close. Come on get over here. I'm not gonna get it. I don't okay. Now I know
what they want me to do. I get it. I understand. You need to bounce off of cars. Okay well I didn't
get it. I'll try it again. I understand what they want. Okay all right. I need I want my good car.
This will do. The more hits you chain the more you get. How do you bounce from car to car? Drive
head into head on to a car. Will I fly out of the windshield? I think it's gonna start. You idiot.
You can move around while you're rag-dulled. Okay. Fuck. Motorcycle. That's better. That's a
good idea. That doesn't even do anything. Works better from near a fast road. I fucking can't do
this. Don't drive. That kind of worked. Just go to the highway. Will that be too far away? Stop
driving. But the cars are not going fast enough to make me do anything. Juggle yourself in an
intersection. Okay hold on. I gotta like get this down first. All right so there's a bunch of cars
here. Fucking god I jumped over it. How the fuck am I missing that? Come here. Oh come on. Oh this
is gonna be fun. I get it. I get it. Here we go. Here we go. Come on. These people need to get out
of the way. They're actually making them go crazy. This is actually good. This is good for me. Hey
what? I didn't count. How is this not counting? Oh you have to die first. Okay this intersection's
fucked up. There's no more cars. I need more spawns. Spawns come on. Oh hurry up you fucking
slow asshole. Go. Run. I didn't even. Hurry up and drive. Oh my god I'm not gonna do it am I?
I want to get in the car and drive. No one's driving. Nobody is driving their cars.
Let's do it in the marked location. All right I'll get it this time. Let's go. Hurry up. I know. I get
it. Just go to the highway. Ignore the location. Where the fuck is this taking me? Where do I have
to go? The suburbs. Is there a highway that I can do that's right? I could do right here maybe.
Will this count? Any highway? It has to be in this location though. It can't be over here.
Jump off of a building. Wait I can do it right here? No I can't. Location doesn't matter. The timer's
not going. Yeah go to the city. What are you talking about? Go to the site. Chat. It's wrong. Again.
Look at that. Always. You have to do it in the district. Chat is lying to you. Yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh that you can't vote for that for the worst thing of the
year you can't vote for that it's already be i've already vetoed it i've vetoed that you can't vote
for that for the worst of the year nope i vetoed that one because that one doesn't count because
i told you it counts nope okay so i'm coming up here now let me see if i can go in that bonus
intersection i feel like i can get string some stuff together you get bonus adrenaline in the
marked intersection okay and i'm absolutely taking this motorcycle motorcycle is guaranteed
flying off it's kind of i have another person okay here we go there's the highway i think i
think i'm going to just get on the highway and can i take the road no i guess not all right i'm
ready it does go in it does right here let me try this part first you dick yeah timer's going i know
i'm gonna get there come on hurry up get to the location quick please i'm wasting so much
fucking time you idiot jeremy what all right i'm in the middle of the intersection i'm
that was looney tunes wiley coyote just stepped over the cliff and fell come on hit me they're
not going fast enough this is bad this is really bad he fucking scooped me he scooped me up it's
gonna happen i'm gonna be fine i'm just gonna stay inside i'm gonna stay in here don't move
what the are you serious scoop me again go go go go go go drive drive drive why is it doing that
now fuck you give me the car stop you fucking idiot i need to get scooped again hit me hit me
hit me run me over please adrenaline mode has been activated what does that mean chain together
amplified hits how how do i do that how do i do this what's that mean shit i got it all right i
get it this is fun oh thank god for the scoop strat earn a hundred thousand dollars for the
time of three minutes and 45 seconds holy goodness so there is a highway right here this is a good
opportunity i think right here let's get it save between all of these give me the pickup build the
adrenaline first yeah i'm starting to understand what the game actually wants you to do this is
german 985 car somebody just came in here and said they did surgery on a grape and i'm remembering
two or three years ago when people were all saying that yeah they did they did surgery on a grape
that time remember that that was from a few years ago how do i get on this oh it's the train never
mind okay a lot i'm getting old yeah me too it happens it's okay though all right i need to get
over there give me that car too late waste of time run me over run my head over run over my head
please shit i need a fast car that's a fast car right there giving me you you fuckers stop jumping
over the cars i can't what a waste of time i don't want that goddamn shit beat up sedan i want a fast
car stop stop i need a car huh he's still there none of these are giving me points
why is everybody naked what's going on get out of the car oh they they won't stop
it's part of the game mode they're not going to stop i have to get my own fucking car
i'm in a lot of trouble now there we go please keep it going keep it going keep it going
drive first yeah they all are going 100 miles per hour though i can't get any cars
old germa would have been dying laughing at this yeah well old germa ain't here right now
this is reformed new germa why did it what's going on with that that was that was dog shit
what was that stop jumping over the cars almost there come on turn turn turn turn get up here
that'll do it here we go i was just not in adrenaline mode i was just not adrenaline mode yet
how are we not in adrenaline mode yet thank you oh hurry please please please do it
why did that not count what the fuck hit me somebody hit me if i'm in a combo does it keep
going i hope so where's the fucking god why it's it's stupid i do timer still goes
oh
i did it yes thank god this is fun 200 000 this time i can't be a dumb ass this is gonna be hard
well if i can actually get the adrenaline built up it should be pretty easy the problem with the
last one was for a minute straight i was stuck in the intersection not being able to get a car
this time i'm gonna keep this car doesn't matter make sure you do nothing for two
minutes again no i know i don't want a car no i want a car to get to the adrenaline zone
then once i'm in the adrenaline zone i build up adrenaline and then we just go
so do not lose the car because if you get out of the car everybody i'm in the zone right now so
everybody's driving like a maniac you can't get another car i need to get to this place quickly
quickly there's one right here all right let's go run me over run me over run please
here we go you gotta wait till it's a big concentration like right here good almost
there i have three minutes to do this one more you need to move holy shit that guy just
oh the ambulance would have been huge oh yeah it's gonna explode i think it already did come here
this reminds me of a flat out one two stay on the roof huge oh this is huge this is huge at what
point do you stop the car i feel like i'm playing tony hawk i gotta get to a million points in one
combo oh 150 nice let's do it again clown prince of crime five minutes for 300 000 if we string
something like that together that's easy okay i'm just making sure that didn't hurt me in real life
again we get a car drive to that place build up the adrenaline and then go for it
motorcycle seems like the best idea because i can just fly off the bike and get an initial
how far away is this not that far okay go this just looks like a burger king or mcdonald's
character the big legs see if i turned around right now there's a gigantic face two circles
and one big smiley like the purple among us character and i'm not saying that to be like
funny and make a reference to among us i'm just trying to help you visualize what i'm talking
about okay there this is close i think yeah here it is bring it on come on what's with the spawn
bullshit this rng nonsense come on wasting time come on drive all right i got plenty of time
no i should do it almost and go hit me come on shit can we drive fast so long face i need
to get one of those people that drive really fast like that idiot just did fuck it's okay this time
drive forget about the light is there a light here drive is it because the bike's in the way
oh this is not gonna be good just hurry up now come on hurry up what the fuck were there no cars
that i have to leave i gotta go somewhere else why would you break drive straight ahead why are
they breaking this then they're not so considerate of my well-being now okay i gotta bring it together
now big truck he don't give a fuck come on come on go somebody somebody somebody that's not gonna
happen if five cars spawn here what a shitty and i'm not going to this one again this one sucks
i'm going to this one go to the triangle next time what a piece of shit intersection i never
say ever i i've been that's make that makes me very angry i don't know why that happened
that's incredibly that's infuriating what just happened it took me off really why what's the
point of that why would it like spawn you out what a piece of crap well what a fucking flop
cars only spawn when you're not looking yeah i think i've just after i get adrenaline i think
i have to just leave and just try to get flown into another intersection i wonder i'm going for
a curve ball here sorry it's okay go build it the trucks truly don't give a shit always aim for a
truck look at how much they just don't give a fuck about anything here we go let me up come on speed
speed speed give me a truck that's going fast like that one that's not a bad place to be right now
there's a bunch of spawning truck psychos right here there we go finally go keep moving keep going
please ah sorry you tripped we have to build it again it's okay come on let me get one more on
the adrenaline let me get one more this runs not over not yet depends how fast i can build this
don't nobody move come on one more should get it back in and we should get 150 perfect timing
for this guy get up no what the fuck are you doing why would you do that idiot just ruined
everything like i've ruined the entire run by cutting that fucking guy off hit me there's still
a chance there's still a chance there's still a chance there's still a chance somebody drive
their car fast for the love of god okay i'm in i got it i got level four completed excellent
excellent excellent this is intense i like this level six is really really hard well let's hope i
can get to level six downtown district oh you know what i want to do i know that this is just
like kind of like bandwagon andy i want to do i mean we're doing the baby sensory stuff i wonder
if i can incorporate that into like a you laugh you lose thing okay i already did all right time
to concentrate here we go where is this where of course you break you idiot there's a highway
right here this is golden huge opportunity come on hurry up please just run me over this is not
working as well this because there's a fucking there's a light here if i get it this is gonna
be huge i'm doing there's way too much momentum that should do it let's go all right oh get the
fucking car out of the way oh my god are you kidding me just no this is nothing no cars
there was probably 40 or 50 in a row another zero you what's going on why would what kind of
physics is that shit what i bounced over you bounced over the car on the second hop yeah
come on go you all these cars are going so slow this is a terrible place to be this is it come on
this place sucks like this this part this place actually sucks it's too shitty of a location
because they have to all break so this is like the end of the highway this is an awful place to do
this i gotta go the other way on the highway i got a plan i have to get in the car and drive all the
way over there good i want to punch the algorithm in the face like spawn some cars i was running oh
there they are how am i not in this please just bring something together you're gonna give
yourself a migraine no i'm okay i have to get like 200 000 fucking points right now or it's
in trouble get out of the fucking car what if you get out of the car this is not even have any
fucking points someone please stop the i can't get them to stop why is this happening why is
that happening i'm so fucking pissed right now i'm furious somebody hit me this way but there's no
cars that spawn this way come on come on hit me again stop changing direction i'm i weigh like
600 pounds it's gonna move me i love they avoid me too this is stupid you should go ragdoll to a
new adrenaline zone they're like they're too far away the problem is the game spawns like 10 cars
in a row and then you just sit there for a minute game crashed i was saving it after every mission
though that's okay right it's okay right the bridges on the highway is the best place to do
it in the game uh this is accurate right just fuck the circle cars infinitely spawn on the highway
one problem with the highway is where's the entrance to the highway the gps in this game
literally may as well just be like a two-year-old yelling fucking their favorite song in the back
seat so the gps does not have any idea where to go where's the highway entrance yellow is the real
tracks this is a highway how do i get onto this oh my god uh i'm all right i'm gonna go do a mission
i'm gonna eat the i'm gonna eat the controller if i don't i gotta change it up what about the
casino uh after this mission i'll go to the casino oh that's right customize this car hell yeah let's
do that how do i do that i'll take it how do i do it it's the wrong business oh shit well what did
i just buy oh man nice 90 000 oh i love it not bad not bad who's this is a brawl going on over here
that was just every single person that's ever tried to learn how to ride a bike that was the
first time you got on it uh okay well this thing is fucking stupid i don't want this
okay do i get to keep this did i just spend eight grand for no reason do i have to bring it to a
garage okay i have to bring it i have to bring it to a garage how many cars can fit here there's no
limit okay just have to get it there if i do a wheelie my ass is gonna hit the ground i want to
just ride that as long as i can this thing is smoking this is bad what the fuck can these
explode i want to go off a jump like this just get huge air somebody said this bike is working
over time store it how do i store it there we go all right now i want my other car no i want a
garage nice gps although i did get there pretty quickly this car is too fast it actually kind of
hurts my head playing it like this all right customize repair vehicles let's do it i mean
notoriety oh shit okay how do you get rid of the cops how much is this going for take it i think
it's almost gone yeah i'm good all right nitrous upgrade i've upgraded nitrous hydraulics upgrade
oh you cannot equip both hydraulics and nitrous better bumper a reinforced frame better torque
higher durability body mods what's going on outside okay body mods front i don't even see
what does it mean oh okay i see what do i want deep dish pizza yeah i definitely want a deep dish
that one that one nice big ass wheels okay what about the uh what about the hood i feel like i
don't like that i feel like that would detach one day and decapitate me i like this one keep it front
bumper i like the air filter air purifier like this one i don't know what that just did our rear
mods like oh air filter what about the what about the roof uh can i not i want to see the top of
the car oh is this on roof whoa that's weird i like it no no spoiler it's good license plate
uh i guess this one exhaust tips i like that mirrors i like that decal uh i don't know here
we go color the only orange oh that's good let's get the germa green you say what do you say the
color it's probably more like that like this no like this like it's like here or here like here
it's not a puke car what are you talking about this is my channel and it's like a blue it's the
joker it's not the joker it is are those the same colors green blue and like pink i do have the
joker colors don't i okay let's get out of here i really am just a shitty batman villain i'm
realizing right now this is the exact person that would be in this car so who somebody called me
now i'm that guy in your town that like runs his own business and he has like that crazy car with
all this business stuff all over it and it's like a wild color scheme then he's like walks
around he's actually dressed like in this like like color scheme too is this number all over
his car and all over his jacket and stuff his license plate is like like the handyman or
something i what is going on with these wheels i did not even notice these i didn't even touch
that guy okay uh let's do the ronin mission this thing's reinforced too this is a good car now
i have nitrous how do i use it oh my god turn it off that's insane all right let's go
game's too quiet i'll turn it up
did you have fun doing the kit boga calls would you do something like that again oh yeah
that was a lot of fun bogus hilarious uh does the game crash i think it did did it come on i
can see it right here it just won't oh there it goes was that reason that was last year
at least i saved it right there oh so let me talk about this if i want to do like a baby
sensory you laugh you lose video or do you guys should we do like a compilation where i sit there
and um no emotion they always look so fun let's try that again if you laugh you have to quit your
streaming career i don't think i want to commit to that one let's put the la la la dog on
i've seen a lot of the compilations of like you laugh you lose like streamer lat like i've seen
like the xqc like actually laughs at memes compilations like i have it on like repeat
those are good he is he really is such a funny motherfucker he really is like he's just he i
i think his channel is fucking hilarious why is it woman what's he doing oh wait we have to get
this guy well well let's go what are you doing oh germa's a juicer uh why am i supposed to go in
here you might be the don't mention other streamers it breaks my immersion you why i
thought it was if that's a casino i can't go in the casino well i'm not allowed to talk about
other streamers that i think are good now i'll tell you xqc has said some very very nice things
about this channel he's he's said some wonderful things and it kind of it actually does kind of
mean a lot and somebody like that is says nice things about you so i mean it just break them
wait i have to revive my homie all right i'm gonna die if i don't if i do that again how
much where is he i i swear to god i put the hostage down man put the hostage down i just
want to break the stuff did i do it destroy the next room all right we already did it let's go
this is the next room i have to go you have a really shitty batman you have a problem with
the mick riddler where am i going we love the mick riddler i i love the mick riddler too this
way the image i'm just trying to do damage everyone leave stop why not the mick what was it i'm not
trying to injure anyone i'm just trying to destroy the machine do the counting room okay wait let
me do this right can i have flash bangs that i use them all why would i destroy the money take it
destroy the money well for what it's sending a message if i'm the mick riddler i'm not the
joker who's using a chair to block all right let's get out take the elevator leave the hand leave
a hamburger as your calling card it's like a wrapped mcdouble shit all right hold on
have it unwrapped but take one bite out of it i like that very important right this is probably
an achievement right holy smokes get this guy on the olympic team that was insane i he handballed
that and threw it you should be with the shell on did you just call the wrapper of a hamburger a
shell with the shell is it a peanut what is it a walnut with the shell i'm sorry i went all the way
up i didn't even know there were people up there it's not gonna happen i don't care fuck it
nobody move eating the shell is a delicacy we talked about this before i think but i gotta
make sure i get this in my brain reiterate it there was a gum that i don't know if i was lied to when
i was a little kid there was a gum that you were supposed to chew with the wrapper on because it
made it better am i crazy it was back in like the mid 90s i'm just gonna quit gaming for i'm
gonna quit i literally quit i'm crazy i quit streaming i quit forever like i need i've how
could that is it possible it's not even possible to do that as like a game or a live streamer
okay um where are we that was a myth but what was the gum it was a specific gum because it
had like little crystals in it i don't think it was stride if there was there were crystals
it was a little like flavor crystals not fruit stripe well i don't think it was an original
stride i don't think so it was flavor crystals and it wasn't stride hey i'll tell the story for the
new people what i used to um i thought that was too bad guys i used to lie to the dentist
and i was i thought i thought i was being really healthy and really really smart because nobody
who the fuck flosses right and they were like oh so you've been flossing yeah of course i have
also i've been chewing trident too this is a lie i don't even know why i said that because trident
ran these ads that made it seem like if you chewed trident gum it was good for you it was like you
cleaned your tooth and shit so i would tell the dentist that i've been chewing trident and they
go oh really wow yeah i'm just trying to be bad i'm trying to chew trident everything no not orbit
this is before orbit my brother used to give me shit for it all the time be like oh yeah i'm
chewing trident because he'd be in the other chair like it'd be like one chair in the other
chair that we were in the appointments at like the same time i just got ten thousand dollars for
that i know you should floss i'm just messing around i was ten grand damn do i have enough to
do the next one whatever this is i'm doing it is it icebreakers it might have been i'll give you
some more uh hints on what it could have been protect the oh this is in danger you're right
i'm gonna go do it let's get that guy back in here it was in it was not a gum that was in a box
or in one of those cans it was gum that was in individual little foil wrappers well but they
weren't foil it was paper and you were supposed to chew the paper too you weren't supposed to
eat it was i really just bullied yeah you chewed the paper and they just watched me do it and they
were like holy shit this kid is stupid i swear more people were doing that uh because i don't
want nothing i'm not doing the casino right now cineburst you're on the right track i think that
same era bazooka no that wasn't bazooka hear me you were probably the type of kid that put ketchup
on corn don't move and you'll be okay i'm not gonna hit the gas all right you're good why would
you put ketchup on corn what are you talking about that's disgusting why would you have your house
right here why is there a house right here okay and cineburst is the gum i you might think you're
probably on the right track i don't know if you're right but you i think you're close you're in the
same realm just put ketchup on broccoli i ketchup i don't really like on anything besides sometimes
a hamburger a lot of times french fries and that's kind of it like what else do you put
ketchup on besides a burger and fries what else do you use it for oh yeah chicken nuggets that's
another one grilled cheese yeah i could see that pizza no i don't think so meatloaf you're starting
to lose me replace that with gravy and we can be friends again those beachfront property over here
i want to take a look ketchup goes inside of a meatloaf you don't you don't like drizzle it on
top like chocolate syrup or something ketchup goes on shitty meatloaf oh auto burped in my face and
it tasted like a beyond burger and i could never eat beyond meat ever again i forgot to tell that
story okay so i was taking so auto sits on the couch we hang out he's like oh let's watch tv
and he falls asleep so i picked him up he like i kind of get him i cradle him he's really tired
and i bring him up to bed right like okay it's time let's bring him up to let's go to bed
so i cradle him i pick him up really gently i curl him over so his face is kind of i'm holding like
a baby and he's up looking at me with his face kind of pointing at me he's like eyes are a little
groggy right so i picked him up like okay let's go and at the same time i breathed in i was like
and he and blew his burp into my mouth and i inhaled it and it was the worst thing that's
ever happened i think in my whole life it was it i i almost puked instantly i was but i obviously
i don't want to like i want to make sure i hold him and i was like i don't want to you know cause
a problem so i was like holding him very very steadily but at the same time i was like oh my
god i'm gonna puke so i like got him up into i put him down in the bed and he was like nice and
comfortable and i almost puked like three times it was seriously it tasted and smelled like beyond
burgers and i love beyond burgers and it sucks because now i can like never eat it again because
that's all i'm gonna think about is my dog burping down into my lungs it's disgusting what is this
oh i just bought this it sucks because i said i really truly i love beyond burgers like i think
they're great oh nice 27 000 but something about the exact combination of the moment
maybe it was something that was in the air too i don't know i have no idea it was awful
how can i not buy that oh why does it put me so far away
i'm trying to eat stop don't you know this is a stream that you should never consume anything
while watching that's important to know unless it's like candy because who gives nothing is
going to gross you out from eating candy if you're eating a bowl of spaghetti yes but if you're
eating like a bag of m&m's then i could say anything and it wouldn't matter except for when
you're done eating the m&m's smell the bag and it smells like somebody's shit in your house 30
minutes ago besides that though oh that's really not that cool double cedar holy shit you sicko
what are you doing get out of here that guy almost just took me out oh well i like it oh what what
no hey hey that's good i got a friend on here with me there is stuff to do over here put it
in the garage first good call yep how do you not get hurt by that i've wanted the fishing pole but
i don't think you can get it no there's no fishing never mind why did you do that why did you do
that because i wanted to see if i get the fishing pole whatever happened to germa it's not real it's
not a real you're punching people you're hurting people in germany well you're freaking out for
nothing it's just pixels gerba i was scolded by chat for that an hour ago we were kidding but
this was real so this is is this a prison i think this is yeah so what's here there's a couple of
activities here nice oh that's a rare tag right there this is the prison from the beginning oh
okay great let's go cinnaburst mintaburst and frutaburst all had edible wrappers and flavor
crystals they are the gum you are thinking of 100 so i wasn't crazy oh it's assassination
mission okay i feel like they weren't edible though because after a while it would still be
paper and i would want to fish it out of my mouth let me get up there what is this just a rock and
this there's a lot of enemies here whoa what's that like a tacos what is that it's like food
oh it's a fight club okay i thought it was like four tacos maybe i'll do this first three two
one i gotta go faster than this shit i'm glad you can't fall off that wasn't bad gold medal let's
go and i'm not i wonder if i can get in here now let's go around the other side what happened to
my friend i can buy the prison how much is it how to get up here be a doc i guess i could just
climb up this all right i made it now where oh lighthouse how much is it thirty thousand dollars
access your stored cash weapons clothes and vehicles here customize increase your style rank
that's very expensive oh i don't have enough to do anything i have money they'll store don't i
get out the fucking way uh the boss is here you step out of the way he was standing in front of
the cash dash i said out loud where's the cash dash mate look for the cash didn't say anything
stood in the way and i tried to get by him and he stood in the way and didn't move talking about
the i'm the joker you're like one of the guys with the masks on you're gonna get punched in the face
nothing up here holy shit i can climb that
stupid cannonball am i in jail why am i in the prison
i wanted to play with them i didn't mean to puke yeah this is the beginning of the game
is there anything else i can do in here they own this lighthouse hey man i let you out can't open
it doors don't open i'm trying i press a button just let everybody out i'm lost shit i don't know
how to get out of here yard oh there it is fight club getting hungry what should i eat
oh my goodness oh they're gonna arrest me if i do that oh no fight club time wait back out and save
all right too excited i'm not planning on staying long well we'll see what troy has to say about that
but you know jail ain't all bad yeah i'll take your word for it how long of walks do i take
you get fresh air that's 10 minutes 15 no rent a high chance of getting shanked now you just
being a pussy listen we got better ways of letting the inmates vent some frustration
conjugal's with the warden's daughter you know that ain't half bad but nah we got ourselves a
little fight club and the guards might bet on the side right that's right and you know were you
fighting and me front in the cash i bet we could make some only 10 minutes yeah stuff's a competition
nothing you can't handle i think this is a good walk three two one i did get that 30
increase which is showing itself i've got much more damage i'm doing this is awesome well this
is just like the mast singer of like prison fights like who am i right somebody put a stage light
just fall on my head although you probably could guess who i was judging by how large i am in
comparison to everybody else i wonder who the giant fat guy in the purple question mark suit
is there's no way he's the giant fat guy in the prison yeah it wouldn't even work i'm stupid
whatever three two one pieces of shit like you eat pieces of shit for breakfast classic classic
comeback it's an adam sandler joke i didn't claim that i said that's a classic joke i didn't say it
i didn't make it up i need more moves eating these pretty quick in fact you mentioned adam
sandler and i am almost certain that there is a character in billy madison from the movie that
movie where the principal is just this guy the principal of of billy madison is the character
i'm playing his name was the blob he had a purple mask three two one the revolting blob
he was a former pro wrestler called the blob yeah you know i haven't seen those movies in a long
time it's been years i wonder if my rose colored glasses whatever are showing but i remember those
movies being funny they were actually humorous this part where a dog the funniest part of the
whole movie for me was adam sandler's watching a tv show and it's like a family sitcom and there's
a real just regular dog that like they got to like they gave it like a treat or something or
they like barked on camera and they dubbed over it and the dog goes no so speak for yourself
moron and he starts laughing hysterically at it and i thought it was the funniest thing i'd ever
seen when i was like 15 i did a podcast last year where i watched all 62 adam sandler films
in 62 days that well this is a funny joke but there's not that there's like 15 it was funny
everybody's just so negative i thought it was funny if i remember he's made a ton of movies
one i don't think i don't think there's 62 adam sandler movies let me see if i can name
10 okay let's think billy madison hold on i need to pause for this billy madison happy gilmore
uh little nicky hunch drunk love 51st dates waterboy pac-man movie right the pixel one
the one where he just like went on vacation with david spade and they were like grown-ups or
something uh another one that had like um that's eight click uncut gems uh big daddy that's 11
zoltan that's 12 anger management 13 eight crazy nights 14 jack and jill 15 mr deeds 16 wedding
singer 17 through the tier list i that's 17 bedtime stories 18 this is not spanglish that's
19 that's not 62 of these airheads adam sandler has like 20 movies hotel transylvania one and two
all right that's 20 21 grown-ups two all right 23 andy say andy wexler all right 24 there's this
many there's not 62 no way google it here's the filmography what i'm gonna the game's gonna crash
yep that's fucked the game's fucked let's crash i saved it though adam sandler filmography what
the fuck what one two three four five well ones that didn't come out yet don't count one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty fourteen five sixteen seven
nine thirty thirty one thirty sixty three thirty four thirty five thirty six thirty seven thirty
nine forty forty one forty two forty three forty four forty five thirty six thirty seven
oh my god there is 62 yeah but okay hold on this also is counting times where he was a producer
and not in the movie like as adam sandler is adam sandler in adam sandler so he probably is in like
40 i was so confident that he was in like 15 the webcam is pointing at me and the light is on
and i had a panic attack because i'm sitting here with no clothes on you notice i was kind of just
silent for like two seconds right there that was terrifying all right well i don't want to do the
fight club stuff it's kind of boring so newspaper oh you can replay missions that's cool how do i
get out of here it was easy to get here but this is gonna be kind of is there always a motorboat
here pull over wasn't it is it a cop in there are these all security officers who is oh my god
aren't these that don't they all work here why are there so many police why are they just shooting
at everybody what is this guy's problem what does the ester i lied okay i need to go uh this way
does that actually kill me with the parachute open don't want to open the parachute parachute
parachute parachute i fucking hate this why i thought i had a parachute or something it
said parachute last time i jumped off that high i'm stuck in the goddamn prison again get me out
of here can i fast travel i just wanted to just hurry up and get down there i just didn't want to
be up there anymore get me out of here i fit through the window i'm actually stuck here again
get me out please why can't i just jump over this why i don't know how to get out of here okay i'm
gonna turn around we're gonna go this way and then i'm gonna go this way i'm trapped here doesn't
know where to go it's the infirmary i need the yard where's the yard holding area and there's no
map vodka is gross dad vodka sucks it's awful the only thing that's good about vodka is if you get
like a decent vodka you can kind of mix it with stuff lord get me out of here i actually think
vodka is probably up in est here for me just because it's the base of a lot of things that
i like like i really like moscow mule it's good uh i like a vodka pineapple vodka cranberry i i
drink realistically maybe five to ten times a year i'm still stuck here i didn't know these
opened all right let's go i did the same thing i just i just should have just went on the road
i just saw red again no i know i know i'm so sorry it's just dude not even a joke anymore
i'm trying just to now i'm stuck again no i'm not i know where to go stop pretending i got
shit to do later i'm not i'm steward i'm serious my my like puny like pea-sized bird brain thought
i could get out and jump over there like i was like i can make the jump i didn't the last time
i did that i didn't truly try to jump i kind of fell and i'm like no i can make the jump this
time right like my brain was like you can just make the jump it's fine thinking that i that he
was i didn't know i was gonna rag doll you just went in a circle get me the fuck out of here
i'm never coming back to this island again it's not a way out it's because this one way to get
out of here they're trying to keep us in here of course they are it's a prison but i need to
get out of here can i activate a cheat code fly and just fly please you spawn next to it go in
the holding cell because it's like oh i'm in the yard now but there's no map in here like i can't
this i there's no map in this place i want to be able to look all i can see is this little
minimap i can't zoom out or zoom in i'm fucking swimming i don't even care oh my god give me my
car oh yes leave this place in the dust i'm gonna go here i think you might need a casino break
oh are you faster than a jet ski how did you survive but i did i did too you're one more
mission to completing the whole ronin storyline really i want to watch this guy hit the invisible
wall and then i'll go back and want to make sure it exists are both of us already there and i just
don't know yet is this an optical illusion oh wait hold on oh wait i think what's that other boat
where did this come from wait we're not no we're not there where the fuck did i go okay i made it
i thought i was back in the president i was about to be really upset it was like an oil tanker or
something you have 13 respect doom missions you dickhead i know i'm just having a blast all right
you let me have a little bit fun i don't have to do only missions this is a mayhem mission
you guys feel like hand breaking a car like that would just snap the handbrake off
is this normal are you in a hazmat suit so what can i do for you
what that's bullshit so what do you need me to do i refuse to acknowledge it i think that's the
play you get a bonus for destroying compact cars oh big combo are you fucking kidding me
really do it again i'm just gonna do this fuck it i have an infinite amount your grenade cheating
there's no such thing oh take that out how did it how did i just for anything
holy fucking shit oh my god dude i did it end the mission truck yard district fences are worth 50
times more than anything else for some reason i start saying holy freaking shit instead of holy
wait a minute there are this is a new weapon place anything new here what's that oh no oh yeah
oh i need money k6 all tov what do you think k6 i think what is this gold plated gdhc how did i
get these okay cool but i do want to buy i think i want that this looks like battle pass where are
my golden pistols here we go all right equip that shit this does look like a battle pass
i was looking for fences that's all i care about just hit these there we go get the fuck out of
here with this no you sprayed yourself in the face what an idiot there it is that's what i'm
saying what are you saying that's what i'm saying that's what i'm saying i'll do one more what's the
that's what i'm saying thing search it online i don't use the internet rots your brain anything
with that disgusting dirty satanic television i'm looking for friends fences need some fence
we guarantee actually get out i got a combo why would you swing a rocket launcher you fucking
moron are you kidding me you are gonna baseball swing a rocket launcher holy shit oh almost
screaming like that it's just it sounds excited didn't hit anybody uh oh flamethrower now available
at your crib weapon cache nice after i'm done with this we're gonna go and finish the ronin
storyline and then that'll probably be it that point of play would be six or seven hours by them
bonus i need way more than this i gotta get a better spot not enough shit over here
not enough shit over here like fucked everything up didn't you i need more shit to destroy there's
not much very much there ain't much here oh there we go very much i'm so pissed here we go very
much here we go i'll get it right here jeez there's still so much more that i have to destroy
i gotta get this place i can string together there's not much over here there really ain't much
there's not much fences i know i'm looking for them here we go fence these fences not count
are you kidding me how do these not count i'm not even in the right place oh my god i didn't i'm
sorry i went outside of my zone where is it get in the car quick what are you doing
i got plenty of time i'm fine get up so fucking many of you oh what is that a fence i don't think
i'm gonna do it it's gonna be close 450 oh i got it i got it i got it iron thousand
that was tight two more levels after that too all right all right all right i think i'll give this
one i think i'm gonna leave i'm gonna leave because i don't want the game to crash that'll
be a disaster we're gonna go do the last couple of ronin missions i need a car use cheats i don't
need to use cheats there are way more are there oh shit there's 15 more missions forget them and
play around with the amazing supply of cheats okay all right yeah it's time it's cheat and d
how do i activate them player ability vehicles weapons weather world key code activate how do
i turn them on thanks road to eats all the cell phone cheat codes okay what are some cool ones
to do full health car mass hole your vehicle has infinites mass and smashes other vehicles out of
the way infinite sprint unlimited clip infinite ammo heaven bound these don't say how to activate
them oh here we go all right you have you guys just feed them to me i don't even care feed them
to me nine six nine all 200 the number you have got pound 200 giant mode oh god okay what else
we got what is it nine six nine fucked it up on giant pimp slap okay okay seven pounds seven eight
i'm sorry the number you slap is amazing all right hold on let me i'm giant they're not under
under player abilities weapons this is this is stupid i'm not even that big
oh i can't see where they are i'm too tall all right i gotta deactivate this okay get out oh my
goodness so dumb you 20 and 20 and six nine 16 for funny cars what's wrong with me all right 16
for funny cars evil cars all cars try to run you over 20 raining pedestrians oh my goodness okay
that means a 202 everybody must get scrunk all people all over the world get scrunk 18
low gravity all right let me put some of these on all right i'll turn on evil cars
raining pedestrians and then everybody gets scrunk i'm i fucking died what does everybody
get scrunk mean well why am i so small what is everybody scrunk fuck wait what does it say
wait hold on everybody what i thought it was like like drunk or like everyone's like fucked up or
something like i thought it was gonna get like like crunk i don't know like scrunk i don't know
what that means i don't know what that means everybody gets scrunk like oh that must mean
like some something going on there must be something we're gonna get drunk and oh my
how did i not read that correctly what else we got this person is way smaller than me
okay everybody gets scrunk what's that what else should i do something exploded all right number
19 i'm gonna turn some of these off 19 is pedestrian war okay i'm turning off scrunk turning
off low gravity i'm turning on turn off raining pedestrians okay evil cars is fine and pedestrian
war is fine too we said do three milk bones milk bones on number two do 944 imp cane
car mass hole do 666 wrath of god all right let's try these uh our mass hole imp cane
wrath of god and all right that's good for now holy shit this imp cane
jesus what happened to the pedestrian war what are you doing
that's what makes me fall off the tree do 36 so you don't die never die okay but i couldn't die
yeah it's on i couldn't beat the bike all right the evil cars are stupid they just crash into
each other over and over again there's a walk with the cane when i feel like a weird like
mcdonald's monopoly character i don't think i feel like this is a mcdonald's toy so i should
i get on oh wait ufo give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give
me give me ufo what's the ufo seven two eight one two six two eight two three seven destroy
that's not it i have to go to the garage all right so where's my where's my garage
did you go to my garage there is a garage does that have a garage
oh the car is indestructible we can never go back yeah it's a helicopter i need a garage with a
helicopter i don't have one all right i'm turning the evil cars off they're just an annoyance
how did i get all the way down here get the stupid cars where did i where am i
oh i wanted i thought the wrath of god was already on how do i turn it off this is it's wrong
you're not allowed to disable it i'm not are you kidding me i can't turn it off i need to
the saint's hideout has it somebody said i'm just gonna take forever to get there
is there a flying cheat how do i just fly seven eight six seventy oh thank goodness
i didn't do anything one oh eight one is fly didn't do anything the thunder stopped seven
seven to make explosions manum you just do boobs sands one is the underground one not the house
oh okay okay explain that like i'm a one-year-old on this map where's that clever
i cannot use it wherever the this is the same title doesn't have uh i can't do it i have to go
on the roof oh how can you go i hate the sound though yeah this sounds make me want to throw up
it's a binaural beats it's a yeah it's a binder i'm jetsons meet the jetsons
it's fun stones what's the jetsons song it's like there's roger there's
it what is it it's like and l roy and l roy how does it go meet george how is it
he has a dog named elmo oh like i what i will i refuse to look it up i need to get it jane
his wife but i don't know how the main song goes
is
meet the jetsons
wait what imagine arresting this guy and not asking like please like what do i what's the
prayer what's the lord's prayer that i need to say for you because you're obviously like a new god
that came down going back up i don't like this world oh shit fucking sprung it all right what
are the cool vehicles are i want like an insane vehicle or an insane weapon that was my i was
waiting so to say rick and morty 306 jane his wife jetsons theme song is there one is there
one point where it goes that's the simpsons how does it go i think they're similar aren't they
they're incredibly similar songs yeah how come they're singing george jetson
jane his wife this is the sister
yeah this i thought they had those lyrics there's only like four things that they say
yeah okay i thought i don't know i thought it was a whole song i feel like a dmc aid for the george
for the george jetson theme song and like the 11 cents that they're gonna make like who is even
listening to that right now like who cares to listen to that what you really it's the theme
song to the jetsons nobody like and by the way that was playing through my phone through the
microphone and i added uh i added i added a i changed it did you hear the new lyrics that i
gave it that was very intentional remember the part where i said it's the sister yep
all right was it 306 all right one more and i'm gonna i gotta get out of here
i need to get some food i'll be back on sunday it didn't do anything 7 13 okay guys i'm sorry
five is funny oh you can do the balls okay let's do that do they all do it oh you got me
just fucking kidding bro oh i can't fire the gun all right i'm out of here i'm done that's it i'll
see you later i missed the scrunk i think i don't know if i'm gonna complete sates row 2 i think i
got what i wanted out of it are you gonna do the you laugh you lose baby sensory stream we'll do
that after sunday sunday we're gonna do a co-op stream of italics we're gonna do resident evil
six four or five hours maybe six hours depending on how much we hate it then after that i will plan
the you laugh you lose baby sensory extraordinary extraordinary because i'm gonna do one of those
i did it like years ago and i thought it was fun don't get too scrunk this weekend
i won't thanks for watching everybody appreciate it it's been a very very exciting couple weeks
i'm rolling around in bed sleepless i'm very excited i will see you guys this weekend have
a good weekend see you on sunday i don't really have time locked in yet we might start a little
later maybe like around three or four pacific so maybe i i gotta talk to italics but yeah uh i will
see you guys on sunday have a good one as always let's raid someone sure let's raid somebody let
me open up my twitch open up the twitch something we haven't read it in a while
york's oh yeah the york's cast is doing that uh they're doing that stream right it's a good
place to go where are they streaming that on the on their main channel or yeah the jingle jam yeah
it's a rebroadcast right now though you know what i've been actually been watching i've been
watching super mario 64 speedruns i've been watching mischief do it i know boxbox is doing it
it's very entertaining so i think it's been a while since we've said hello to boxbox go say hi to
boxbox mario 64 is just the best speedrun to watch because it's just it's there's like five
different ways to speedrun it you got like the the 20 minute runs you got like the hour long runs
you got the star runs it's like a it's a it's awesome i've been getting back into it again
recently i i'm never gonna do it ever it's never gonna happen but it's cool to watch uh go say hello
to boxbox it's been a long time since you said hi to boxbox i'll see you on sunday good night goodbye
take care of yourselves have a good one