I did it. I'm good.
Hey, what would you guys don't know is before every stream,
with the mic muted, I sit here and I get ready. It's an old
theater technique, where you kind of sit, you hype yourself
up and you get yourself ready for the day and for the
performance. Everybody has their own thing that they do. Me, I
go like this. This is how we do it. This is how we do it. This
is how we do it. This is how we do it. And then I press start
streaming. I do it every single time.
Hi, guys. Welcome. I got we got some stuff to talk about. Do
you actually though? What do you think? Yeah, I'm something of
an actor myself. Talking stream, not a talking stream, but an
explanation stream. They're out there today. That must be like a
fucking rumor convention today. I'll tell you. Twitch has been
acting up today. Well, my thing that I want to talk about has to
do with the stream that was planned today. You said Twitch is
acting like a doofus. Well, Jeremy is acting like a doofus
too. Because, sorry to say this, scratch tickets are not sold in
Nevada. There is no state run lottery. There is no lottery.
There are no scratch tickets in the state of Nevada. It's one of
only six states in the country. So I can't buy scratch tickets.
There's too much gambling. So there are a few things here to
discuss that that was planned. Well, I just did this is coming
from remember, I'm a recent transplant to Las Vegas. I lived
in Massachusetts my whole life. And every gas station, every
convenience store just had scratch tickets, all of them.
Every single one. So I'm just used to seeing scratch tickets.
And I just assumed completely that they're just everywhere,
every state, every county. And they don't exist in this state
at all. So what here's a possible scenario, and I'm going
to tell you a possible scenario. It's not illegal for me to
scratch scratch tickets in the state of Nevada. But I cannot
buy them here and I can't cash them in here. So what I might
have to here's two possible scenarios. Scenario one, we
retroactively just say, every death in Sekiro was a dollar to
the Nevada Humane Society. $221 goes right to the Nevada Humane
Society. Okay, that's option one. Option two is have
somebody buy me $221 worth of tickets in Massachusetts, send
them to me. I scratch them here. And then when I go visit
Massachusetts, which I plan on doing in the next like 30 to 45
days, I have a plan to go visit my family. I cash them in there.
Because it's not illegal for me to actually scratch a ticket
here. I just can't I just can't do anything with it here. Go to
the California state line. Yeah, but the California state line
is still that that's like a three hour drive. It's like a
two hour. That's a boomer tapped tactic. I don't know. I'm not
sure what we're gonna do. I haven't figured it out yet. I was
very defeated this morning when I realized what was gonna happen.
But listen, listen, listen, listen, listen. And somebody
says just do it online. I think there's a I don't like gambling
online. I mean, I could do that. But I don't really I don't want
to do like online gambling. I feel like that's another level
up versus just kind of scratching scratch tickets for
charity kind of thing. I don't really want to go to like an
online slot vendor and just I don't know. I'm not comfortable
with it. I have nothing. I have no problem with gambling. I live
in Las Vegas. And I hit up casinos every so often, right. But
I don't really want to do it. But on stream. I don't really
want to. It's not necessarily about like promoting gambling,
but like, Oh, big win. I did it, guys. I don't know. It just
doesn't sit too completely well with me. So don't have a problem
with it. I just don't personally want to do that. But regardless,
that's how that stands today. 2020 hindsight should have
probably but why but why would I have tried to research that? You
know what I mean? Like our scratch tickets legal in Nevada.
It's the state it's a gambling state. This is the state of
gambling in the country. I but regardless, I can be dejected
all I want. But doesn't matter. Today was still German slots is
still on the table today. We're still gonna play that. If you
don't know what that is. Somebody in the community just
made an entire video game. And it's been working on it for a
long time. They've been given updates in discord. And there's
a lot of interesting things in it. Apparently, I don't I
haven't played it. So we're going to kind of experience it
together. And there's a lot of interesting things in it.
Apparently, it seems fun. It's apparently there's like over an
hour or two of content. So it's it's like a full on video
game. Actual dev and oh, I would assume that the actual dev in
the chat is an actual member of the community. So real dev in
chat. So we're not gonna we're doing that later. Because I
figured I'd rather play Mr. Mosquito, which is a game I've
been trying to kind of throw in for a while now. So play Mr.
Mosquito until we're kind of sick of it. However long that
takes, you know, maybe a couple hours, two or three hours, I
don't know, maybe an hour. Who knows? I might play the game
for 10 minutes and go I want to do something else. So
Jermisloft will come after Mr. Mosquito. It's not very long.
Yeah, but we'll see. So with that said, hopefully you guys
have listened to my whole spiel here. And we're going to start
off with Mr. Mosquito. This is an old game about being
mosquito in somebody's house. That's the whole game. There's
nothing else in it. You just have to try to drink blood from
people in a house. So we might as well just get it started.
Open crates? No, no, no, that's not the same. The whole idea
was I was going to donate the money to charity and if I open
like a hundred TF2 crates, what the hell am I going to do with
like 40 McDonald's shotguns? Flip them on the e-market. Yeah,
I'll get like 12 cents for each one of those like re-skinned
color. You know what I mean? It's like, that's bad. This is
blinding in here. That's a reference to one of my old
videos. Yeah, you picked up on it. It's from Fresh Games. You
wouldn't get two cents. Zoom computer create. What did that
say? This game contains... Okay, for a second, I just got a
little nervous because a bunch of people would... Caution! Why
are there so many warnings? When using insecticide, you should
not only read the directions, but you should also follow them
carefully. That was a couple of scary moments there. All right.
Mr. Mosquito, the Yamada's summer. Loud birds. Are you ready?
Welcome to the home of the Yamada family. It's summer. Do you
like summer?
That cat is just fighting on the roof.
Summer drives people crazy. And that makes them commit
terrible acts.
What?
Take the tiny harmless mosquito, for example. It doesn't
have enough time to do much during its one precious short
life. Yet with one swipe, a human can snatch such a priceless
life away without a second's thought.
Is this like mosquito propaganda?
I'm sure that you may already realize...
Mosquitoes suck.
...that you are a mosquito. The insect that bites people and
makes them feel itchy. The insect that creates a trail of
swollen bites. As a mosquito, there is something that you
naturally have to do. You have to suck blood. You must suck and
store away as much human blood as possible in order to survive
the winter and see another spring. However, blood sucking is
accompanied with much danger.
I'm sure it is.
It may come as a surprise to you, but you're not welcome in
the Yamada family home.
She's been talking for a full day.
Because you make people feel itchy. Bear in mind that they
will go to great lengths to protect themselves from you.
Nevertheless, please enjoy your summer of blood sucking.
Is that a person just yelling or is it a crow at...
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's me. It's Mr. Mosquito.
Mosquito spread disease.
Yeah, they just bite, suck blood, reproduce, hurt you, hurt
your family. Start stage briefing for the next stage.
Change mosquito color. I want to get a color scheme. You still
only have one color. To win battles within the battle time
attack set. This is a mosquito. This looks like a woodpecker.
Okay. Stage.
This is Rena's room.
Rena is the daughter of the Yamada family. She went on a
school trip today, and she sprayed herself with bug
repellent. But that was some time ago. So it's likely to be
wearing off in some places. You should suck from those spots.
Good luck in finding them.
Okay. So how do I play?
You're too close to me. It's so hot today.
Am I? Are they looking at me?
It's time over here to take a family picture. I've been
looking forward to it. How about taking a picture of just
you and dad? I don't want to be in it.
What are you talking about? Why not?
Oh, they're looking at me.
I just want to see why we have to take the same old pictures
year after year. We take a picture every year. That's
enough of a reason. Back me up here, Kenichi.
Are they lying down or are they leaning in?
It's such a pain.
Let's not do that this year.
Are they lying down in like a triangle?
With their heads together?
It's because of me, isn't it?
You don't want to be in the photo with me, do you?
There's the crow.
I want nothing to do with this. I'm going to my room.
I'm so confused.
Okay. So they've spread out.
You've ruined another family gathering. Not yet.
So this bug spray in parts of the room. So that's me.
I'm so tired.
I'm huge.
If a mosquito was that big, I'm getting a baseball bat
and I will tear off drywall from my walls to get rid of that thing.
This is like a killer bee.
Stage one. I need to get two tanks of blood.
There is one EX. What?
I don't even know how to fly.
There's no... It didn't teach me anything.
L, R1? Okay, R1 is fly.
L1 is stop. Read the manual.
God damn it. Getting started.
Ouch. Set up your PlayStation 2 controllers.
Okay, ouch.
It's summer, hot and humid.
A mosquito is patrolling the Yamada house.
It must suck blood to survive, so it attacks the Yamada at every opportunity.
Mr. and Mrs. Yamada and their daughter Rina are sick of itching.
Every member of the family is ready to stand up and swat you to avoid those nasty bites.
This mosquito faces life and death battles on an hourly basis.
Okay. About insecticides.
God damn it. I forgot you had to read this shit back.
Seamen again.
When using insecticide in real life, be sure to refer to the manufacturer's instructions.
Why are they so concerned about that?
Do people just like... Okay, here we go.
Rear view. Okay, 180... R2 is 180 degree turn.
R1 is accelerate. L1 is decelerate and reverse.
Triangle is change camera angle and take off.
I'm just going to have this right here.
Circle is attack and stabilize.
X button is take off.
Square is take off.
So R1, L1 and then circle.
Who fucking cares?
Can you see me?
Did I get crashed into her face?
What?
Attack all the points?
I don't... I can turn the lights off?
I don't understand.
Why does she sound like she weighs 5000 pounds?
Why are we having a battle?
How do I attack?
Bite!
Bite it!
Circle is supposed to be attack.
Okay.
Attack and stabilize.
Accelerate. Select is not used.
Menu controls. Mosquito... All right, listen.
Push the left analog stick to point the view. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Press R1 to speed up. L1 to slow down.
Press L1 button when stationary to reverse.
Move around. Yeah, okay.
Press the R2 button to perform 180s.
Lock on. A red frame highlights relax points,
blood sucking points and gimmicks in the room.
With the left analog stick, align the green lock on cursor with the red frames to lock on.
Press the circle button to attack a locked on target.
So I can't just do it anywhere.
Press the circle button to alleviate temporary loss of control when you crash into walls.
Push the right analog stick.
R3 button.
Once you land on a blood sucking point,
pierce your host's skin with a needle-like proboscis.
Rotate the right analog stick to suck blood.
To suck blood faster, rotate the right analog stick faster.
To suck slower, rotate slower.
Blood sucking causes your host's stress level to increase.
Jesus Christ.
Just redo it.
I'm not done.
So slowly stealth. I'm gonna turn the lights off.
So I'm gonna kill the lights.
So that you can't see.
And then it's R3.
Okay, I'm ready.
We're gonna hit the lights.
Suck the light bulb.
No, I'm gonna get like light bulb juice in me.
Okay, now that I had to read the instructional manual.
Let's turn the lights off.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna be careful.
So get the cursor in there. Lock on.
It's locked on. Let's decelerate.
I can't see anything though.
This is bad for me.
What did I just run into?
Where is that? I need a lock on point.
Lock on point.
What's the point of turning...
Okay, I see it.
Why would you just...
Okay, why would you sleep with the lights on?
Keep the ball in the blue.
This is a lot.
Area of the meter you can press.
What did that say?
How much blood am I gonna take?
Okay, two tanks.
Okay, let's go.
How was it the first time?
I hope you enjoyed your first blood suck.
Okay, that's fucking creepy.
Take all of it.
This is not a porn game.
Guys, on the back of the box,
I'm gonna read this to you.
Are you ready?
Mr. Mosquito.
Rated T for teen.
Published by Eidos Interactive.
Comic mischief, mild violence.
There's somebody in a tub on the back of this though.
Is this comic mischief?
I don't have any clothes on.
I gotta be careful here.
That's on the back of the box.
It's rated T for teen.
This is the Yamada's storeroom.
Rina's mother Kaneo is looking for their family albums.
The storeroom is full of toxic clothing inside.
Try to avoid the toxic air as you fly around.
No, you didn't.
No, you did not.
Look, how would it reflect off a PlayStation case?
Not possible.
It reflected off itself.
There's no way you guys saw anything.
Nice chest hair.
Let's see, I'm covered in chest hair.
I'm covered in chest hair.
It's on my legs.
I got chest hair on my back.
But if there's a mosquito here, you'll be next.
You must be kidding.
Why do all these...
I don't understand this whole heads in frame thing.
I'm looking for something.
What are you looking for?
All right, get fucked, Jerma.
You actually got me there.
No, you don't have to lip sync any animations.
That's true.
All right, you got your T-pose.
Why is this scary?
Stage two, look out for the poison in the air.
Suck two tanks of blood.
Well, Jesus.
We got first spot.
Ow.
Okay, easy.
You don't have any, like, points of interest.
Right here?
Battle.
What did I just do?
I don't understand.
I had to hit you in the stomach?
I got to hit you right in the forehead.
All right, I can't go up that high.
I have to hit you in a bunch of pressure points.
Oh, this is so dumb.
Watch out for the poison.
I, it's, I...
Got you, headshot.
Now what?
What the fuck is going on?
Where am I supposed to bite?
I don't see any marker.
There's no red marker.
Down there, got it.
Fuck that up.
What?
I pressed the button.
Where did...
Where did that marker go?
Hello? What?
Okay.
Why can I not do this?
Is it on the other leg?
Oh my god.
Why?
Which leg is this?
It's not this one.
Okay, I have another opportunity, apparently.
No, I don't.
Dude, what?
What?
Lady, by the way, I don't think you should be in a closed
off room with a bunch of poison in it.
Get out of here.
You're breathing in all
these fumes.
Oh shit.
This lady is breathing in.
Just raid.
This is a nice porn game.
It's not a porn game.
Yes, it is.
This is not a porn game.
It's not a porn game.
This is not porn.
Stop this.
You're making me self-conscious.
Keep saying porn.
Don't worry, though.
Based on your actions,
you will have plenty of chances
to suck his blood.
If we're just gonna play this game,
this game was like $75.
Okay?
I've wasted a lot of money on these PlayStation 2
porn games, okay?
Get them out again?
You like doing that, don't you?
You've got an insect bite mark. It's swollen.
Oh dear.
It wasn't $75. It was like $50.
Rub some aloe on it.
Hate it.
I can't believe that's on there. You have to rub some aloe on it.
Honestly.
Is he working out at the gym?
This is a good gym playlist.
Next time you come home late, I won't say a word
about it to your father.
Really?
Default cartoon Tom and Jerry sound effects.
The horn.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
I gotta stay focused.
What are you watching?
That's what was coming out of the TV.
What a wacky weather report.
Be careful of the air current coming from the air conditioner.
Suck three tanks of blood this time.
Right from the top of his head.
Let's get in there.
I'm bored.
Did he just punch himself in the face?
Stay focused.
Fuck.
Okay. Here it is.
Got it.
Three pints of blood.
What?
He just instantly killed me.
Why did I just instantly die?
You didn't do the...
You didn't counter it.
Wait for him to punch himself in the face.
After he punches himself in the face.
This is freaking me out.
I got it.
Telephone call.
Distraction.
He's gonna get up and answer the phone.
Put this in there.
Come on.
Why?
Why couldn't I do that?
Wait till he punches himself in the face.
He punches himself right in the mouth.
What?
Here it comes.
Punch in face.
What's wrong with me?
What's going on?
What?
Maybe not the head.
Maybe it's somewhere else.
My stress levels...
Their stress levels are too high.
He can hear you.
That's his stress level.
We gotta get in there quick.
He goes, I'm bored.
We gotta get in there.
Air current coming from the air...
That doesn't seem like it matters.
Here we go.
His stress is fine.
Get in there.
He's bored.
Stress is alright.
Easy.
Where's that indicator?
Oh my fucking god.
Is there anywhere else I can bite him?
Maybe the head is just not the one to do.
Can I get him in the foot?
Or in the ankle or something?
I think I have to distract him.
Let me see.
Oh, I'm gonna change the channel on him.
He's gonna get really mad about this.
Turn.
Okay, I'm high enough where I should be able to get an indicator here.
There it is.
God damn it.
Stress is fine.
Come on, give me the indicator.
Give it to me!
What are you doing?
There it is.
Okay, hold on.
He's stressed.
Got it.
Watch that stress level.
How many are there?
Three?
I'm not gonna get all three right now.
Don't do it.
What's his level like?
He's getting a little stressed.
I'm gonna back off.
Yeah, I'm backing off.
Oh!
I'm gonna turn the phone on.
Oh shit, he just turned on the AC.
He turned on the air conditioner somehow.
Where's the AC come from?
He's not gonna see me, right?
I can't get it from here.
The AC's off.
Let's get it.
What?
How?
Same deal. Far away.
The stress level should be good and manageable.
And three, two, one.
Last off.
He's good?
Give me one more.
And then tutorial dad is done.
They get more stressed if you don't keep it in the blue.
Don't swap me, please.
Thank god.
Alright, get up.
That was loud.
I did it.
Can I change my...
No, I only have one color.
Okay.
Just trying to get something ready here.
Just in case I need it.
I don't think I can...
Those have to see.
It's alright.
Let's make this quick.
Get out! Out! Out!
Alright, we're fine.
It's all, like, blurred out.
Don't look over here.
I keep hitting the bubbles, don't make those noises.
Just let me get all three.
I gotta get out.
Why is everybody so bored?
Give me this last one, then get out.
Out, out, get out, get out now.
Nope!
And when you pop a bubble, guys, it goes...
SHIT!
Get out.
Where is she?
Fuck you!
I only have a minute left?
Alright, no more jokes.
You can't even see anything anyways, who cares?
I can't see anything at all.
Right here, come on.
29 seconds.
Give me the indicator.
It's just a floating hair.
It looks so much worse.
Drink the bath water?
Like, as the mosquito, that would...
Mosquitoes don't need that.
Mosquitoes don't drink water.
Mosquitoes don't drink water?
Mosquitoes don't drink water, they drink blood.
There's water in blood.
Don't read chat right now.
Yeah!
I know!
This is how I feel, yeah, I'm here too.
This is how I feel reading chat right now.
I think that there is a mosquito in the house.
You think?
Go and buy some insecticide, Kanaeo.
And make sure it works.
No way that you could go and buy some yourself?
Mom, weren't you going to cook dinner now?
I'd like to eat potato cakes tonight.
Really?
Let's have potato cakes for dinner then.
That's great!
But mom, I'm not sure about the way you make them.
What are you saying?
There's nothing wrong with the way that I make them.
Well, okay.
I'm going to light a mosquito coil in the kitchen.
What?
Typical.
Ugh.
Nobody knew what they were saying.
That's weird.
What happened to my stream labs?
Dashboard!
There it is, okay.
Cooking.
Wow.
This mother is insane.
That was four or five front flips.
Without touching any of the shit.
Stay away from the mosquito coil fumes.
There are two blo-
Okay.
What did that even say?
The mom is a god gamer.
Is that a god gamer?
Or is-
What do you mean, god gamer?
Okay, I gotta get both knees.
She did a front flip.
What does that have to do with gaming?
Come on, let's see it.
It's right when she goes to the front of the sink.
Hold on, can I distract her with something?
Can I fuck with the hot dogs?
Only a god gamer could-
Alright, I have to get the feet.
So it's both feet.
How-
I'm gonna get killed here.
Alright, here we go.
How long does she do this for?
She's eventually gonna stop doing this pose.
Why would you do this pose for this long?
There's no way.
You still going?
Alright, there we go.
Okay, that's right.
Here we go.
Let's do the other one this time.
Actually, no, we're just gonna do it together.
They even feel it.
They go, ow.
That's it?
Now what?
What was the briefing? How many do I need?
Oh shit, careful.
The other one, okay.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Right there.
Really?
God damn it. Alright, it's-
I can get it.
What? I gotta go from the top.
Uh oh, bad news.
So I gotta go right in front.
What?
Why?
How did I fail that?
This is not a porn game!
Do I get an indicator of when she's gonna move?
One more.
Got it.
You're a degenerate.
Why is she doing this twice?
Did she get hurt? Did she fall down?
What are we implying here?
That she did a couple backflips or frontflips and landed her head?
Now I feel guilty?
Is that what that was?
Alright.
She's armed with an insecticide.
Oh great.
So now they have weapons.
The potato cakes are ruined.
I'm sorry, degenerates.
I don't mind.
Just as long as you are safe.
Kenichi.
You're bothering the neighbors. Keep it down.
Did she just say that?
Don't break that bag, Zappa.
It's new, you know?
Really?
A wolf?
She's just like her mother.
In fact, wolves just walk by the house.
Alright.
So we're in her room.
She has bug spray and a zapper.
Is she screaming that?
The cuckoo clock?
Okay, that's VR game level of involvement there.
What's with this posture?
What?
Alright, we're easy.
You just turned this into a lot more difficult for me.
I made a lot.
Let me get the bug zapper.
And then, where am I supposed to bite?
Do you see it?
The neck maybe?
Bone?
Turn it off?
Let me turn it off.
What do we got? What am I supposed to get?
Oh, it's that.
I thought that was a toaster.
Let's see what we can do here.
The leg?
I don't see anything.
It's probably arm, neck?
Face?
Watch out.
Shoulder?
Oh, she hit me.
I don't have any idea.
Answer the phone?
Got it.
Wait, who called her?
She's pretending to answer the phone.
I just hit the button.
There's nobody on that phone.
Okay, so I called somebody else and then she's acting.
I don't understand that.
Got it.
I'm going to still be in here, right?
Even when she hangs the phone up?
Out.
Yeah, what kind of conversation was that?
Was she taking a delivery order?
I'll take a sausage and onion.
Yes, okay.
And I'll also take a side of french fries, too.
Oh, yes, okay.
And I also want an Italian sub.
Yes, okay.
Can you mash up a mosquito and grind it up and put it in the fucking smoothie for me?
I gotta get out.
There we go.
I just have to keep doing this.
Yeah, this is rockin' music.
Fuck.
I gotta go back further.
Risky. Too risky. Too risky out.
I gotta try to put it on the spot.
She keeps answering the phone.
Maybe I can just get it without...
Nah, I definitely have to do. Anything else in the room I can do?
I can turn the lights off, but that sucks.
I'll try it.
She's just entertaining herself.
You already got over here?
Oh, no.
Nah, phone is definitely the best tactic.
I just gotta go further up.
Turn it on.
No!
Just keep calling her.
At what point would you really...
What about...
Can I do something on the other side?
Right here on the shoulder.
Come on.
That wasn't the shoulder.
Goddammit.
Fuck.
This one's hard.
She's stressed, but I gotta do it.
Ow.
Alright, we're fine.
I wonder if this will work better, too.
Let me try this.
Can I do it from here, too?
Let me see.
On the shoulder?
What? No.
It's only phone?
How is phone the only thing...
It has to be the phone.
Turn off the TV?
I don't think I can.
This is the only way this is gonna work.
It's risky, but I gotta do it.
Give me one, give me one, give me one, give me one.
Out.
Whoa! I just barely missed it.
No, I'm... Oh, no.
Get out.
Quick, turn off the lights.
Okay, she can't reach this high.
Holy shit, she has the spray.
What did I just do?
Right in the chest.
Like, right in the heart.
She just counter-punched me.
Holy shit. You gotta be kidding me.
She's gonna spray me!
Did it work?
I gotta get her in the knee, I think.
One more spot, right? I think right in the knee.
Where is it? Where is it?
Where's this last spot?
Okay, behind her.
Damn it!
I got it.
Wait.
Oh, that's the phone.
Alright, saved it.
I can't do it anymore, I gotta do the shoulder.
Oh my god, no way.
I can't do the neck anymore.
I gotta do the shoulder.
But how am I gonna...
Ooh!
Whoosh!
Oh, come on! Holy shit!
Why? Jesus!
That went quick!
Oh my god.
I'm gonna die.
No, I still have hearts.
I didn't get it.
Oh no, this is bad.
Why can't I turn her on? Turn her on!
This is one.
One behind, two.
I gotta do the star fox turn around and go right.
Like this.
This is so hard.
Damn it!
No!
Snake, there are only 20 seconds left.
Come on!
I gotta wait till she takes the can out.
Okay, can's out. Now I can get the arm.
Holy shit.
Get it!
Alright, there's one more down here.
No, I didn't get that!
I'm right here!
So I can only do the top of the finger for three or four seconds.
Game. What the hell? Why?
Okay, almost.
That's it.
There's the hang up. Got it.
Do it. Hit the phone.
You should do it.
I gotta do another one?
What's the other one?
Where is it?
Is it the hand again? No, it's the hand again.
Try something besides phone.
I did the stereo.
It didn't do anything.
I couldn't bite her anywhere.
It's the hand again.
Okay, talk to you soon.
Here it comes.
Check on the pillow?
I don't see an indicator.
I'm just gonna do this.
The only indicator is the phone and the stereo.
Shit. Not good.
Yeah.
Don't risk it.
Yeah, there's nothing else in here.
I can't mess around with something on the table.
Nothing in the trash.
Stereo is the only one. I can't even press the stereo.
But she kind of kneels down for a second.
This tactic is working.
This will be it.
That's it. Close it up.
Got it.
That was 15 minutes?
Holy shit.
Yeah, but I'm dumb and blame games.
What are you talking about?
There were only two things to activate in the room.
What else could I have done besides the phone and the stereo?
The TV didn't have an indicator on it.
Don't touch anything.
Avoid everything.
Yeah, no feet.
Not this time.
Stop all hobbies that cause injuries.
Flower arranging is the spirit of Japan.
What do you think, Rena?
Would you like to try it?
No way.
Genichi, I covered the tummy mats in the Japanese room with tick insecticide.
There's no way that I'm going to be beaten.
That makes me feel a lot better.
I wonder if it's a tick though.
Why is this guy wearing glasses with no lenses?
I don't know. That's a good question.
Who names their room the Japanese room?
All right. Don't touch anything.
This is going to be difficult. How am I going to get in here?
Why is he just staring at this?
What's going on?
Is this like meditation or something?
Stay away from the floor mats and mosquito coil fumes.
Okay. So we can't do that.
So we have to stay away from the fumes.
Let's see. I can't do anything there.
He's breathing in the fumes?
Oh, shit. Okay.
I'm like trapped in here.
It's hot.
What points of interest?
On his back?
That might be his chest.
Maybe this way.
I think it might be his chest.
Then over there.
I can't touch anything there.
Maybe this way.
Does he hurt thorns?
I have to bite him in the eye?
No. What about over here?
Can I activate this?
Nothing I can activate.
There's no button to press.
What about behind me? Can I turn the light off?
I have no idea what this guy is doing.
I have to bite him in the mouth.
Do I have to bite him in the lips?
I don't understand.
There were no points to attack him.
I don't think I might have to sneak around when he's trying to put the flower in.
I'm almost dead.
I exploded.
Okay.
What happened at the end there?
I just got aquatined.
Doesn't Master Shake do that to everybody?
After Season 3?
It was his chest.
It was somewhere in his stomach.
It was either his stomach or his back.
Don't touch the floor, don't touch the fumes.
There are two points.
Maybe can I go through?
Alright.
I don't even know where the game is.
Maybe this way.
Maybe I can fly through his legs.
This might be Finesse.
He's so stressed out.
It's hot.
You again!
I thought maybe I could go through his legs.
This? What are you doing?
I was just practicing.
Rage Quit?
It's faster for me to reload.
Next game?
No.
The next game is Germa Slots.
I want to play this for a little longer.
That's what's going to happen.
I need to beat these people.
I need to at least get to a point where I'm satisfied sucking all their blood.
This game is a 15 hour game.
I'm not going to play this game for 15 hours.
It's been like an hour and 15 minutes.
Alright.
Maybe this way.
Give me an indicator.
How am I supposed to...
It feels like you can't avoid any of that stuff.
It's hot.
What is that?
When he says it's hot.
He goes it's hot.
Maybe this way.
This game is only like 3 hours.
It's not like 15 hours.
Where are you getting the 15 hours from?
There's 12 stages.
Why are people saying this is like a 10 hour game?
I'm waiting for an indicator.
Nothing?
Right in the hand.
How long does that last for though?
Maybe this way.
How much time do I have?
That's like 3 or 4 seconds.
Indicator's gone in his hand now.
Maybe this way.
He's starting to see me.
He pricks his finger on the rose but how come I didn't see it last time?
I'm just sitting there waiting for it.
It's hot.
I can do his face too.
Maybe this way.
Alright, here it is.
My finger.
And no indicator.
That's only on for 2 seconds.
Maybe this way.
It's hot.
I'm frightened of his lips.
I should not be able to do it like this.
That's happened to me before though.
How often is a mosquito flown into your mouth?
Then you go like
It happens at least once or twice.
A season.
It does.
Let me get it all in one go.
Let's see if we can do it.
There goes another one.
I don't know why it's gone.
It's very hot.
Here it is.
I'm going to turn on the indicator.
If I can actually do this.
I'm going to do an indicator.
See that?
What aE HP.
Come on!
Wait.
Oh no, I'm going to do the indicator.
Come on, right in his... right there, right there.
I didn't hit that.
What is going on with this camera?
One more.
Was it on his back?
Probably.
It's probably like on his ass or something.
Alright, I gotta be careful.
I just need to do this like one more time.
Right in his mouth.
Right in his mouth, same deal.
Right in his lip.
And we need one more.
That's it for that one.
I need the other one now.
What?
Oh, come on.
Didn't get it.
Come on, it's right there.
No!
I'm gonna die from these fumes.
I'm dead.
Oh, god damn it.
This level sucks.
No, not next!
No, I gotta beat this guy!
I have to beat this guy.
The only thing is, where's the other...
It's gotta be the hand, right?
So it's his hand and his mouth.
Sunk cost fallacy.
wait to talk about some cost balancing before we get into a turn of flux burning seven mosquito
coils at the same time is roughly equivalent to burning 700 cigarettes that's insane okay now the
question is just i'm not even near these coils i need to do what i did before just get out
sneak through here spin it around through the mouth again try to get i'm gonna try to get all
three of them all right good right in the brother right in the middle right in the middle of the
blue give me all three and then how am i going to get out of this
after i get out what's the best way to leave
through his shoulder whoa excuse me you what what it's because the wind i don't understand
what happened that was going so well and then it just instant went hard that was an instant
now go well i don't understand what happened there though what was the problem
i did that last time for am i getting pissed a little
this i have to beat this guy i got a new color he's getting mad at a porn game
it's not important i'm gonna do it this time that was bullshit though last what was that all right
i'm gonna try this one more time do this one more time this way it's hot
so
he says it's hot i gotta get out
it's
i did it just a couple more of those maybe this way
you stupid game there's nothing even there there's nothing even here i'm getting hit by
imaginary things if that wasn't even on the air conditioner wasn't even turned on unbelievable
what are these hitboxes what are these fucking gigantic hitbox i'm gonna die
and then i'm gonna break this disc in half you gotta be kidding me maybe this way literally he
doesn't even see the air can why would i complain about a game that's like 15 years old that was
developed and it's just invisible shit i'm gonna break the disc in half this is the japanese
this is the japanese what i how much does this game cost uh like 60 dollars because it's rare
it's the stupid smoke things you can't even see i there's no point in trying to explain myself
okay if i don't do it this time we're moving on this is seriously enraging my fucking god he
didn't even say anything what the hell i didn't what i'm just uh if this blows this way i'm gonna
fucking scream maybe this way it's no i i know the air conditioner is blowing the smoke but the smoke
has hitboxes that are like five times as big as its particle that's what i'm saying oh my god
just get no man give me a break i didn't even do anything he just decided to do it
i'm reselling that on ebay it just went immediately right to red it he just killed
i want to watch that i want to see it i want i'm curious i want to see what that looks like
i can't believe it what happened here green we're green we're in the green i'm perfectly in the blue
perfectly in the blue now it's just red death oh my god i don't understand that was a fun game
though let's watch it together blowing the smoke but the smoke has hitboxes that are like five
times as big as its particle that's what i'm saying green in the blue green green in the blue
green green green oh my god just get you had plenty of time why did it what it was red for like
a half a second it was plenty watch it again i want you to watch it again we're gonna blowing
the smoke but the smoke has hitboxes that are like five times as big as its particle
that's what i'm saying 16 it wasn't even a full second ready 17 red and by the way look at it
it's off the screen now it's okay that was not even one second that was like maybe a 70 percent
of a second and there's no indicators i'm doing everything correctly all right your reaction
why would i why would i think that that was gonna happen i'm in the blue he's not stressed he just
instantly decides he's gonna kill me do the all right i'm fucking moving on get mr mosquito that
was actually really fun i highly recommend you buy that on ebay and break it like i did i didn't
break it it's perfect i got i'm not gonna break i don't break things guys i just complain about
them i'm not gonna snap why would i this game was expensive i'm not gonna break that okay if this is
an endangered species video game there are probably only like 150 of these out in the wild
i'm not going to contribute to the like endangering of a video game species