Oh, where does he live again? God damn it. I just never remember where he lives.
I think it's this one up here. Gotta pick up my colleague. There he is.
Hey, Pinkerton!
Come on, get in!
I'm getting in, I'm getting in. You gotta pull up to the sidewalk.
Listen, Moby, Moby, we're gonna be late to work. If you just shut up for a minute,
I gotta talk to you about something really important.
All right, what is it about those reports again? I told you I had the reports in.
Is it this right? Is it straight or right?
It's no, you go straight.
Okay, straight. You live in such a weird area, I just never know where to actually go. Straight still?
Yes, keep going straight.
Am I going straight?
Yes, you're going straight.
I swear we've hit every single red light in Liberty City.
Just go. No one will notice. There's no cops around. Just go.
Do you really think we can get out of here?
Just make a quick right. Just go. Burn out. You don't buy a car. It's expensive.
And then you sassy Susan this stuff.
Okay, I got through the red light. What is with you and sassy Susan, by the way?
I don't know. Get out the car. I have a knife.
Look at my face close up.
Get like a rifle and zoom onto this face.
What are you doing?
My face hurts.
How do you do that? How do you do that? Everything about this is so broken.
Can you believe that there's a road swamp? It's unbelievable. I've got water all over me.
I haven't seen a road swamp this bad since Brazil.
I haven't seen a road swamp that bad in a long time, but anyways.
Yeah, hello, Geico. Yes, I need one of those automatic repairs of my car.
Yeah, you're honestly using Geico.
I'm on the phone. Be quiet. I need to get one of those automatic repairs.
I'm a million dollar businessman. I do. Thank you.
Yes. Yes. Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you. Okay. Yes. Sure. Yes.
I don't know. I'm not sure. Yes. I'm pretty positive, but it's not. Yes.
To be honest with you, I think it could be. Yes. Maybe a different thing. Maybe something else.
Yes. Yeah, I guess you could be right. Yes. Could you be wrong? Yes. No. Yes.
Nick, stop running so fast.
My legs. Look at this cute little hippo.
Where's the hippo? I don't even see a hippo.
To the right.
What? Oh my goodness. This little hippo is so beautiful. I wish I had one just like it.
All right. Come on. Don't throw the fingers at me like that. Like you do that sometimes.
All right. We need to cross the street. Be careful.
Be careful. There could be a car coming. Look both ways. Left and right. Good job.
Hold on. It's completely. It was never even
opened and never used and it's already ruined.
This guy's like clone just came over here. Can I make these two fat guys fight each other?
Oh my God. I think I can. Come on. Hey, you fat guy. Fight this fat guy.
Oh no. I have like the fat shit Mario brothers like attacking me. Here we go. Come on. Punch
him. There it is. Okay. Here we go. Place your bets, everybody. All right. I got the fat guy in
the blue jacket. Oh, salty bets.com. Come on. Do you actually know what that is? Come on,
dude. Will you please? I got a lot of money on you. Wow. You are terrible. There you go.
Give him a left hook. Place your bets. Wow. You suck, dude. Stop like throwing the long
haymaker. That's like your downfall. No, I lost. Every day we do the same trip to work and you
always tell me I'm the fun guy. I'm the fun guy. It's not about being the fun guy. It's about being
the hard worker like me that gets a job done. I mean, I can't believe this. That you would be
stupid about everything. And you know, every time you're in the office, you always get too much
water. You take too many breaks. You're going to make my blood pressure go through the roof.
What do you think about that? Well, you know, as a salesman, it's not entirely about getting work
done. It's the people interaction, the people you're selling. You got to be the fun guy.
Uh, no, nothing about this should be, should be a thing. No, this is, I'm just going to move on.
Make the right turn. No, I know a better way to go. We have to go right anyway, eventually.
No, listen, I know where I'm going. I've worked in this building for more than 30 years. What are
you a second year? Yeah, but I've been earning more than you weekly, monthly and yearly. This
right, you go down the street and then it's going to be on our left. We're going to get a ticket.
I don't care. I'm so sorry. It's a green light. No, it's yellow. It's yellow and that turns red,
which means you cannot go any further. We had a chance to go. You want me to go? Yeah, go.
You want me to go through this red light? No, no, no, no, no. You want me to go?
Is that what you wanted? Is this what you wanted? You wanted me to go?
Okay, we're at work. Okay, we're at work. Thank you. Yeah, that was a good trip.