Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Spy, and there's a bonus clip after this, and it's something I never really see any time I play the game, but it's gonna be a Scout bonus clip at the end here.
This is a very short round. I think it's like only three or four minutes as the Spy, but I do okay. I get about ten backstabs in the three or four minutes, so it's a pretty good run.
Also, the loadout is going to be the Kniver's Kunai, which is, if you don't know, my favorite knife in this game. If you're new to this channel or you've never seen a Spy video I've ever done, this is pretty much my default knife, so it's gonna be on here nine times out of ten when I play Spy.
Also, I got on the Default Spy Revolver, which is, I'm pretty shocked watching this back. I never used this thing, and there's no reason really behind that. I think I just like the Ambassador. The Ambassador has kind of that little mini-game in it where you shoot people in the head, but this thing gets the job done, and I think a lot of times, because obviously I'm giving away my backpack, so I have to use some of the defaults now, but I'll touch on that in a second, but the defaults are really good.
This whole backpack giveaway has taught me one really important thing, and that is the defaults in this game are pretty much perfect. They're all very, very balanced, and you forget that sometimes. You got on your crazy hats and your crazy rocket launchers and your insane old flex machine gun, and you lose touch of your defaults, and they kind of sit in your backpack and they rot for a while.
And some of those items, I can totally understand that. The Default Medic Bonesaw, there's absolutely no reason to equip it. And I think, weren't they talking about in the beta? I remember reading somewhere that they were going to buff a lot of the old kind of pointless default weapons right now.
I could be living in a total dream world, but I don't think I am. I'm pretty positive. I read somewhere, at least for the Medic, that the old Bonesaw was going to get a sea enemy health buff, and maybe they turned that into the Solemn Vow or something like that. I don't remember, but I know I read somewhere that they were thinking about doing that to a lot of the old items.
Kind of went off on a little tangent right there, but it's in the same ballpark as what I wanted to discuss right now, and that is my plan for my item retrieval after all of my items are given away.
In the comments section, let me know what you think about this idea. I want to do an uncrating video. I have a lot of friends in Team Fortress, and I've met a lot of people, and everyone has been so supportive and so awesome, especially with this channel.
So if you have offered me to give me something, or if you want to hand me some items or something like that, I really do appreciate it, so thank you so much, everybody.
But on top of that, I want to do an uncrating video, and the stipulation to the uncrating video would be something like this.
I would buy 30 or 40 keys or something, a huge amount of keys, get a bunch of crates, unbox all the crates live and do a live comm over it, and anything that I got in the crate that was worth a lot, like for instance, if I unboxed an unusual, I would give the unusual away.
And the reason why I decided to do this is I kind of want some of the new strangers, because I like strangers. I don't know, I'm just a strange person. I'm a weirdo, so I like strange weapons.
But you know, you can only get the strangers in the crates. I figured I would do an unboxing video, so that's my plan, and let me know what you think about that. If you think there's a different way I could do it, or if you think of some other interesting way, then definitely shoot me a comment on this video.
So now let's transition to this scout gameplay, and if you remember from a few days ago, I did a soda popper video, and this is from that series I was just recording a lot, trying to get some good footage, and this is one of the things I got.
And I totally forgot about this, and actually somebody brought this up, Boo, we were on a call, and he asked me, he said, let me do my Boo impression,
Jerma, did you save that scout gameplay at all, where you killed two or three people in one shot?
That wasn't very good, but I remembered it, and I said, oh my god, you're right, dude, I gotta go back and look at that, and what happens in this video, this is a pretty good string of kills, I get a scout collateral,
and I originally thought it was three people in one shot, but it's actually two, and I was so bumming about this, because I saw a Community Fortress video not that long ago, and it was a scout, it was one of those top ten of the month or something,
and one of them was a scout, and he got a three kill collateral in one shot, and I really thought to myself, I said, oh my god, I did this crazy feat, this is awesome, I can't wait to see it,
and when I played it back, it was obviously not the case, but still, two is better than one, and one is better than zero, so I slowed it down for you so you could check out what I was talking about,
but anyways guys, yeah, I will see you guys all soon, that's gonna wrap up this video, and leave me some comments if you wanna see some unboxing stuff, or if you have a better idea, definitely shoot me a comment, so I will see you guys all soon, and take care, everybody.