Somebody said, I was waiting for you to cancel the stream because you suck.
Why would you wait here for me to cancel the stream?
Okay, hold on. How long has it been?
It's been 45 minutes now. Wait, hold on. Hold on. Where is he?
He cancelled. All right. Nice. Now I can go back to my life.
Oh, he's like, he's kind of late today.
Wow. It's been like two hours.
Fuck.
Anyways, um, wait, we got like, there's too much music going on right now.
I just spoiled it for you.
We've got a cozy stream ahead. Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like we've been, um, we've been hitting the gas for the last couple of weeks.
It might be time if just for, just for like the next couple of days to sit back and relax and play
one of these old fucking games.
It's probably going to be a very, very cozy stream.
Whoops. I don't want to relax.
Zoo. This is Zoo Tycoon 2. All the animals edition.
This is the ultimate edition. It has everything, every expansion.
I got to learn how to play. This is going to be, we're going to be like in the tutorial for like
30 minutes because I want to know what I'm doing.
Do you ever wish it was just a little bit colder?
Nah, I like the temperature the way it is.
But so let's, let's, let's break down the next week here.
Okay. So we've got Zoo, Zoo, Zoo Calamity 2, whatever the hell it's called.
Zoo Tycoon 2 for today.
And then if Red Dead Online works tomorrow, then I'm going to play that.
Or I don't know, maybe, maybe I won't.
Maybe I'll keep playing Zoo Tycoon 2.
Maybe I'll just bury my Twitch channel into the ground and play Zoo Tycoon 2 for the next like four weeks.
But then obviously, so we're going to go, we're going to go today, tomorrow.
And then I'm going to take, so that'd be Tuesday, Wednesday.
I'm going to take Thursday off.
And then I'm going to get, make sure I'm prepared Friday and Saturday.
Saturday is by the way, the green screen movie night is on Sunday.
So as of Thursday, the 29th here, you've got to get a submission.
And if you have a submission, make sure you read those rules.
It's pinned in that discord.
You only got another couple of days here.
So we got every weekend, we've had something fun to do.
That's what I want to do, man.
I want to make every fucking weekend.
I want to do something interesting.
Free shit.
We got free shit coming in.
What do you mean?
What do you mean free shit?
Where's the free shit?
I missed the context.
It was somebody just trolling.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I thought like, I thought I was in the middle of a giveaway.
I'm like, really?
What are they giving away?
Can I get something?
What do we, how do I join?
I want a fucking new five button mouse.
All right.
Don't get a five button mouse, by the way.
Just not comfortable.
Two is all you need.
Two and then the third button on top.
All right.
Let's play Zooka.
I can't say this fucking word.
The C.
The tycoon.
Zooka.
It's like somebody just snips a portion of my brain
that makes it so I can't say zoo tycoon.
Zoo tycoon.
That sounds wrong.
Is that correct?
Am I saying that word right?
Zoo tycoon.
I'm losing my mind.
All right.
Let's go.
Thanks for joining us.
Get this off.
And hey, look at that.
Here's zoo tycoon.
Why can't they just make it tycoon of zoo?
You got hit on the head too many times during the green screen.
Listen to that music.
This is old school.
You have to spin the world around.
I'm all right.
Whoa!
Does anybody think that was funny?
Did anybody else feel that?
All right.
Let's learn how to control the game.
That's the kind of joke you make with your son.
Hey, here we are.
Here we are, Daniel.
And watch that.
Whoa!
I can feel the earth moving underneath my legs, Daniel.
And Daniel's probably two or three years old
and thinks it's really happening.
What?
But dad, what happened?
And dad's like, I'm just kidding, Daniel.
Go to bed so dad can play zoo tycoon.
Gamer dad.
Fuck you, dad.
I want to play Fortnite.
Get out of here with that Fortnite shit.
Zoo tycoon.
I have 6100 hours in zoo tycoon 2, Daniel.
How many hours do you have in Fortnite?
Oh, what's that, Daniel?
Oh, only like 40 hours
because I only allow you to use the computer an hour a day.
Get out of here.
Dad's got work to do.
All right.
Learning how to control the video game.
Welcome to zoo tycoon.
I fucking can't say it.
Guys, you understand.
We're not even getting past the title of the game.
That's how this stream is starting.
I can't even get past the title.
In the following tutorials, you'll learn the basics
of how to control the camera.
Then you'll move on to construction techniques
and accessing all the information
available to you about your zoo.
Let's get started.
Okay.
All right.
So it's click move, open the goal panel
by clicking on the scenario goals button.
So here's scenario goals.
Click display information about the current goals
and challenges.
So that's the challenge button.
Your scenario challenge goals will fill here
when you play a campaign or challenge game.
Normally this panel will update whenever you succeed
or fail to complete a goal.
The tutorials are a little different though.
So for now, this is the only thing that's going to be here.
Cheese goal.
Okay.
Close the goal panel.
Great.
Return to the goal panel anytime you see
what your current goals are.
Easy enough.
Now we can learn how to move the camera around the game.
We'll check the button.
I told you this is chill.
This is going to be a chill stream.
I'm going to learn how to take care of the animals.
See, this is me right there.
Now we need to practice moving the camera around.
Scroll the map by using the arrow keys or WASD.
That's more comfortable.
Uh-huh.
And this is zoom in and zoom out.
You can do zoom in and it's the mouse wheel.
Got it.
Rotate the camera by pressing on the primary game button panel
or click and hold the left mouse while you move.
Look at that.
Okay.
That's that easy.
Guest mode.
Enter zoo guest mode by clicking on the zoo guest mode button.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
This thing made me so much more excited.
In zoo guest mode, you can walk around your zoo
by pressing the left mouse button.
Normally when you enter zoo guest mode,
the mouse cursor is hidden so that your view is unobstructed.
To toggle your mouse cursor on and off or to view
or to switch to photo safari view, right click the mouse.
This turns into a first person game.
Oh man, this is going to be fun.
You can also take on the duties of a maintenance worker
to sweep trash and empty trash cans.
When you approach something that you can interact with,
it'll automatically be selected.
Just hit space bar to perform the action.
Now it's your turn.
Press the left mouse button or use the moving keys
to walk up to a piece of trash.
Is that person stuck in there?
Holy shit, that person almost died.
That was like almost a vicious camel attack.
All right.
Pick it.
Great.
You can also perform zookeeper dirties.
You can also do dirty zookeeper things.
You can feed and water animals,
groom them, heal them, rake poop.
Okay.
We're going to be here for a while.
Same way.
Heal them and of course rake.
Doing these things yourself could mean
that you don't need to pay a staff member to do it.
Very helpful for a financially struggling zoo,
but I can do it all myself.
I'm not going to have any staff.
I always get so fucking destroyed in these games
because I hire too many people.
You got five janitors, four maintenance guys,
six zookeepers.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just going to walk around
and if something needs to be done, I'm going to do it myself.
I can walk around with a portable hose.
That's all you need is a hose.
Don't understand?
Every single thing,
every single job you could possibly think of
in the world just requires a hose.
Just spray it.
Ah, there's like dirt all over my deck.
Fucking spray it with a hose.
It's done.
Oh, I, my car.
I need to get a car.
Why don't you spray it with a fucking hose, dude?
Don't worry about it.
It's easy.
Oh, my taxes aren't done on time.
Just spray your taxes with the hose.
Time check of photo safari mode.
Click on the photo safari view button.
Okay.
So here's the photo mode.
You can take pictures and shit.
This is just going to be Hey You Pikachu, right?
What's the game that just came out?
Let's Go Pikachu, right?
In this photo, so you can zoom your camera in,
take photographs of everything.
You just press spacebar to take a picture.
Okay.
Let's return.
So I want to move this.
That's a pretty cool photo.
Hold on.
This is such a spy cam.
I got it.
Just hose the trash.
It's fine.
All right.
Click the overhead button.
It's this one right here.
That's the big circle is the overhead mode.
You need the overview map by clicking on the overview.
This one, click to switch the overview,
which allows you to jump directly to any exhibit
or specific zoo area.
Okay.
The overview map gives you a broad layout of your zoo.
You can quickly jump around from place to place in your zoo.
Okay.
So there's a crocodile exhibit.
Oops, a daisy.
Press F1 to open the zoopedia.
This is fucking a ton of information.
That information about game controls, animals in the zoo.
Press F1 to open zoopedia and some panels.
You can click on some shit and learn some stuff.
Okay.
F1 is...
All right.
We did it.
I know how to play.
Never mind.
Click the next...
Yeah.
Let's just go.
Let's bang them all up.
What time...
What'd that take?
Seven minutes?
The following, you will learn the basics of construction,
how to make a basic exhibit, change terrain.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You don't start, buddy.
Let's go.
Select the recycle objects and buildings button.
So this is this one.
All right.
Somebody...
Somebody correct me here.
I need to be corrected if I'm wrong.
This is like the Windows 3.1 panel, isn't it?
Like the Windows...
This is an old Windows panel.
That used to exist.
This is my computer.
This is the undo button.
Yes, it is.
Like this used to be there.
This is the panel for Windows 3.1.
He's a boomer.
40-year-old streamer.
Getting real fucking close.
Sooner or later, I have to stop saying the F word.
After 40, you can't say the F word anymore.
What 40-year-old do you know that says the F word?
I don't know very many.
They're like,
Oh, hi.
Yes, how are you?
I'm a 40-year-old guy.
They're not like,
Hey, what's up, you fucking dude?
I gotta stop doing that.
All right.
Remove unwanted objects from your zoo.
Click the button.
Look for the solitary tree inside a rectangular area enclosed by a path.
It's marked with an X painted in the dirt.
The baobab tree is right in the center of this area.
Move your cursor over the baobab tree and click to recycle it.
Okay.
We're looking for an X.
We're looking for...
I don't, please.
I'm fucking kidding.
Good job.
You received cash for recycled objects,
but it will only be a portion of its full purchase price.
Note that you can't recycle animals.
That just wouldn't be right.
Click the check button on this panel to continue.
Yeah.
I mean, it's kind of can't...
Is like eating animals, recycling them?
Think about that for a second.
That is essentially like recycling.
You consume, you don't waste, reusing.
And then you plant the bones and then a tree grows out of the bone.
And that's how, where animals come from.
A cow tree.
All right.
Well, I wish we weren't really...
We wouldn't have wanted that tree.
We can get it back though.
Click on the undo button right now.
I wonder how far, how many times you can do that.
That dinosaur pee was recycled over the next few thousand years
to become your coffee.
That's fine.
I don't care.
You could tell me that coffee was like rat shit mixed in water
and I'd still drink it.
I would.
How would that change anything?
Right?
Oh my God.
No, there's no, I would not eat that.
I wouldn't drink.
Yes, you would.
What changed?
How does that change?
Coffee is actually, it's burnt cigarette ashes
and rat shit mixed in water.
There's a huge study that just a big whistleblower came out.
I'd be like, I don't care.
All right, undo.
You can use undo to reverse the last thing you did.
This is very handy.
Yeah, I know.
Wait.
Note that you can only undo the last thing you did.
So you can't just control Z, Z, Z, Z, Z, Z.
You can only do one thing.
Video games weren't that advanced yet.
So you can't only go back one time.
Which, I mean, this is one of the greatest games ever made.
So who cares?
All right, let's build a building.
The construction panel is where you'll want to place fences, paths,
zoo building scenarios.
I'm sorry.
You know what keeps happening?
Is my fucking cigarette ash rat shit is,
there's a little bit on the bottom that I didn't wipe up
and I have it on a coaster.
And every time I pick up the glass,
the coaster sticks to the bottom of the coffee
and then falls off after I pick it up for a second.
There's nothing I can do about it.
All right, fences, paths, zoos, you know,
all kinds of the manmade objects in the zoo.
Click the check button.
Let's go.
Fence is the most common way to keep your animals in
and your guests out.
Click on the rectangle fence.
So this is the rectangle fence placement.
This is free form.
I gotta like pay attention.
I am, I am.
Easily create an enclosed habitat.
So find the rectangle area enclosed by a path.
It's the same area where you just replaced the bob tree.
Let's create a fenced area.
Select the chain link fence
and they click on the ground to anchor the corner.
So I want to do it like here.
All right, but here's that.
Do I want it on the Mario Kart track
or do I want it off the Mario Kart track?
Off the Mario Kart track, right?
On the Mario Kart track.
No, but how is Luigi gonna get in first place?
Anchor the corner.
It's just right here.
It's fine, whatever.
Will your mouse see a preview of the enclosure
and click again to place the fence?
Make a fenced area as large as the rectangle.
Great.
Basic enclosure.
Later, you can try the octagonal placement mode
to make an octagonal shape with the rubber band mode
to place single sections.
Click the check button to continue.
Now it's time to place a gate.
This is where this is just the key line staff gate.
I guess it could really just go like right here.
Place it over the fenced area you just made.
The gate preview will snap into place.
How about right there?
You want to make sure that your enclosed areas
have gates that your staff can get in
and take care of the animals.
Right now we're only using the chain link fence.
But there are all kinds of different fences.
The staff gate will automatically work on any of them.
Just get out.
Get out.
Whatever.
All right, here's the scenery tab.
So this is the fence tab.
That's where you keep animals in.
Here's the scenery tab.
Somebody just said chain link.
No, we don't talk about cryptocurrency anymore
on this channel.
We don't discuss crypto assets anymore, okay?
It's all right.
Everything's fine.
That's how you know he lost big.
I didn't lose anything.
Up here, upstairs, inside of the skull,
there's a device up there.
There's a thing up there that has so much, so much in it.
And I, let me tell you, I got fucking coaster.
I'm, I got out, all right?
I left some in, I got out.
I was interested, not invested.
Let's make that very clear.
I have to put this, I'm changing coaster.
All right, I have a different coaster now.
Mom says it's my turn.
No, it's not.
All right, nobody'd see many objects
on the scenery by panel.
But for now, we've narrowed it down
to just one, the donation box.
Click the, all right, the donation box.
Okay, okay, I can get by on this one.
You have a donation box selected.
Move your mouse over the world to see a preview.
Okay, you can rotate it with the keys of those.
Okay, that's weird.
Oh shit, you should place donation boxes
near every single stream.
If viewers can't find a donation box,
make sure to put an overlay on your stream,
telling them exactly where to go,
and maybe even in your title as well.
So then they are absolutely certain
of the correct way to give you
any amount of money during the whole stream,
is what I, I'm sorry, that's all I saw.
All right, it's often a good idea
to place multiple donation boxes
so that guests won't be inconvenienced in any way.
So if guests can't find a donation,
the cash will stay in their pockets.
So this is how you make money.
Okay, pathing tab.
You'll see that there are a number
of different paths that you can choose from.
Guests don't so much care
what type of path surfaces in your zoo,
but they do care that there is one.
Click check button on this panel.
Paths work like fences do.
Click on the ground to anchor the path,
then move the mouse.
Yeah, yeah, so this is a standard asphalt path.
Now I'm not going to do it.
I don't know why I thought that would be funny.
Yeah, I'm just going to say it,
like, and then delete it, okay?
You know, I had diarrhea last night.
Yeah, well, it was my leg's fault.
It was my ass fault.
And now you can delete it
because there's no context,
it makes no sense.
Then move the mouse to see a preview of the path.
What does that have to do with like concrete though?
Somebody make that joke funny,
like change it to like I had diarrhea
on the ground or something.
Like I, or like I fell down on the ground
and I landed on my bum.
And so it wasn't, somebody will figure it out.
And then I want a 10% commission.
I don't know what's wrong with me tonight.
Then move the mouse to see a preview.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, click and place it.
Notice that the path on the map is very narrow
around the rectangular exhibit area.
Place some new path to make it wider for your guests.
Wait, it wants me to like do this, okay.
You want to make sure that your path
lead to your exhibits.
Guests stand on paths to view exhibits.
They stand around.
So if your paths are far too away,
your guests won't see your exhibits.
You'll miss out on your great animals
and you'll miss out on their donations.
Yep, you'll want those paths
leading to your donation boxes too.
Click the check button on this panel to continue.
Why do I keep reading that of all the things?
All right, here's the building.
So this is the fence tab, path tab, building tab.
There's all kinds of buildings.
Jerma, calm down.
I'm all right.
Okay, from food and drinks stands to restrooms and more.
I purchased a hot dog food stand,
a pretzel cart and a soda drink stand.
You already have the hot dog stand.
Move your mouse over the zoo to see a preview.
Yeah, yeah.
Notice the green access arrow which shows
side that guests will approach.
Okay, so this is the side that they approach.
Go ahead and place one of each building now.
So we want to have that be completely accessible.
So one right here.
Let's get one right here.
This is just the tutorial.
That'll be a fucking brilliant design.
Don't worry.
Guests get hungry, thirsty and need to use the bathroom
while visiting your zoo.
If you don't, the asphalt.
If you don't provide them with amenities to meet these needs,
they may leave prematurely and take their cash with them.
Like exhibits and donation boxes.
Hold on, someone's gonna steal the donation box?
Make sure the guests are happy.
Otherwise they'll sprint out of the park with,
it's stuck on the bottom of that one too.
I don't know why that's happening.
They may sprint out of your store
with the donation box laughing the whole time.
Make sure that you have pass
leading to all your great amenities.
Click on the pretzel cart you just placed in your zoo.
Pretzel cart guy for the next one on bullets.
Where'd I go?
Great, you have the pretzel cart selected.
Note that an information panel opens up
showing the item you have selected.
Don't worry about all the things on this panel for now.
We'll come back to this later.
So you can pick up a building.
This is to move it if you want to change where it is.
Click the object.
Yeah, that's fine.
So we just go like this if we want to move it.
Yep, yep, yep.
Clicking and holding the left mouse button.
Okay, that makes it easier.
Let me test that out.
Okay, yeah, so that's how you do it.
You can just move the mouse around.
All right, adopting animals.
Click on the animals button
to open the animal adoption tab.
This is where you'll obtain animals for your zoo.
Great, now let's adopt an animal.
Click on the button to continue.
Okay, so you can do male or female.
You'll see that you already have the African elephant
selected on the adoption panel.
Move your mouse cursor over to the fenced area
that you made earlier and place the African elephant
inside of the other enclosure and cause a huge problem
because an elephant and a camel are gonna fight.
Excellent, now you have a new animal.
Guests come to see animals.
So if you have no animals, you'll have no guests.
Let them fight.
No, we didn't look.
Those of you that might be new to the stream,
or those of you that are old to the stream,
you gotta give me like at least an hour or two
to play the game because once it goes off the rails
and I start putting like birds inside
of the elephant enclosure
and the elephants start picking birds out of the air
and eating them with their trunks.
I'm never gonna go back and play the game ever again
the way it's meant to be played.
So it's already off the rails.
I'm just in the tutorial.
What do you mean it's off the rails?
I'm in the tutorial.
I made an asphalt joke and it was very bad
and I was corrected.
I'm willing to admit when I'm incorrect
and wrong about something.
I was not correct.
Check ass.
All animals require food and water
but they won't eat just anything, will you?
That's true.
Okay, how to determine what an animal eats later.
All right.
So we got hay or we got water.
I'm assuming we need both.
Purchase food and water.
Place a food trough with hay and food
through with water near the elephant
by clicking on the dish
and then clicking inside of the enclosure.
So it can just kind of be anywhere, right?
We'll do two of these and then two of these.
Oh, one of those actually.
That's fine.
Select the animal shelters tab
to open up the animal shelter panel.
So here is while an exhausted animal might...
What is he doing?
He's spraying it with like poison.
What are you?
Oh, no, it's a hose.
See, portable hose.
Portable hose.
While an exhausted animal might just sleep anywhere.
Most animals require a shelter.
So this is the elephant shelter.
Certain advanced objects need to be studied
more carefully before you have access to them.
You do this by choosing to research the object.
Objects that need to be researched
have a small beaker appearing over their icon.
Press the research button on the object.
Info panel will begin research on it.
I don't have it yet.
So let's go ahead and research it.
It costs a thousand bucks to research time and money.
Once the research has been completed,
the object is available for purchase.
Click the check button.
Stop reading that.
Why is that even there?
Wait for it to be done.
Wait for your units to be ready and your RTS.
Okay, now you can place it.
All right, you can do other things
while the objects are being researched.
This would be a great time to take a look around the zoo.
Okay, it's done.
So I need to be...
Let's put it like...
Put it like in the corner right here.
All right, animal enrichment tab.
Hold on, wait.
What is this?
An enrichment objects enhance an exhibit area
for many species of animals
by keeping them active and entertained
in their environment.
So this is a pursuit ball.
There are many enrichment objects available
in Zoo Tycoon 2,
but for now we've narrowed the selection down to one.
An exercise ball.
All right, so let's watch them play with it.
Can I play with them in here?
They have different levels of interest.
We'll go into more detail later
about how to find out about what they do.
Okay, open the landscaping tab.
Jesus.
All the tools you need to create a proper habitat,
also known as a biome.
Click the check.
Okay, I need a savanna biome.
Savanna, okay.
So it needs to be a savanna in here.
After you find it,
move the cursor into the African Elephant's enclosure
and click and drag to start painting with the land
appropriate to the savanna biome.
Okay, so like this.
Does it matter?
It really is painting.
Are we sure?
This looks like hamster spray spread stuff.
Are we trying to trick the animal into thinking
this is just the bag of shit
that you get for your hamster?
That's not the savanna.
It's a pretty big hamster.
Imagine you had one hamster in here.
This is some richy rich asshole.
Didn't that happen in that movie?
He had like a little chipmunk friend
and he had a giant enclosure for it.
And the thing, it was like CG.
In the beginning of the movie,
they did this elaborate like four or five minute intro sequence
where he was doing like jumping
and flipping around on bars
and going to the ball pits and stuff.
It was like a fully animated sequence.
Great.
If real life beckons,
you can pause the game and never miss the action.
Keep in mind though that you can also build
while the game is paused.
Oh, that's good.
Like the Sims.
It can be helpful if guests or animals
move into an area where you want to build.
Just pause the game and move them out of the way
with the check button panel to continue.
Hire staff.
Okay.
There are a lot of different workers.
We're just like the Sims.
We've got mascots, construction workers, crime, and musician.
That's the only four things anyone ever does in The Sims.
So that's good.
Maintenance, animal care, and guest education.
I kind of want the dinosaur guy.
Should I not have put him in there?
Should I not have put like dinosaur Gumby
inside of the elephant enclosure?
The zookeeper staff member specializes in animal care
and will make sure that your animals receive food
and water as needed.
It will also treat illnesses and groom dirty animals.
Okay.
So I want to put this is zookeeper staff.
Specialized in animal care.
Educator will enhance the educational experience
for your guests.
Place them somewhere.
Great.
You have an educator.
Educators need an educator podium to speak from.
Otherwise, the guests won't be able to hear them.
Now we need to make a podium.
So we need an educator podium.
I almost just put, okay.
I put down, let's put it on a soft drink stand.
Purchase an educator podium, click on the podium,
and give mouse over to see, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So don't forget the green screen.
Shows the position where the educator will stand
to speak to the guests.
So that has to be kind of right here.
They can go to work educating your guests
by educating your guests.
You can increase the amount of money you receive
from educational donations.
Great job.
This is the end of the construction tutorial.
The next tutorial will teach you a few things
about accessing information about your zoo.
Almost done.
To continue playing the next tutorial,
click the check mark.
Hold on.
We're almost done.
This is three of three.
And then I'm going to install mods
to make a 700 foot tall dinosaur.
Okay.
I'm not going to actually do that though.
Let's see.
We'll level it up in the world here.
Getting information.
In the following tutorial,
you learn the information about animal staff,
guest buildings, and your zoo stats.
Let's get started.
Click the check.
Okay.
All right.
I got a question for you.
Would you guys rather me continue like
to read these and talk
or silent for the next 10 minutes
and burn through this?
Because I'll just like zone in
and just like download this all into my brain.
All right.
I'll be quiet.
Here we go.
Okay.
See, I'm going much faster than I was before.
Great.
When you open the first animal band for me,
I'm on Moitakon's
in a state of the animal's needs.
They have needs.
What? He must...
His needs are a camel?
Click on the picture of the animal
information panel.
This enables tracking
and your camera will begin following this.
So he wants to eat the camel.
Okay.
Is this the tracking panel?
Now zoom in on the selected animal.
Get a better view.
Do I not already have a good view?
How is this?
I mean, I got a pretty great view right now.
I know you're hungry, but I...
No, no.
Don't put him in a crate.
Get him out of the crate.
What?
A closer view will help you see the animal's
emoticons.
Emote of what?
Is that a disease?
Well, you know, fast forward 15, 20 years
after this game came out.
Some people would argue.
Yeah, it is.
About how animals tell you about their needs
and will tell you more about needs in a second.
When you're all through watching your animal,
click the check button.
Great.
Time to move on to learning
about the animal's needs.
Satisfied need.
The icons on the animal information panel
represent the animal's needs.
So here, just like the sims,
this is just animal sims.
I got it.
It means that the need is satisfied
and is all good.
Click the check button.
So when it's yellow,
it means they really have to,
they have to really have to go to the bathroom.
You need to make an animal bathroom for them.
Animal's thirst.
Oh, no.
The icon shown in this story
represents the animal's thirst.
When it's shown with a yellow overlay,
it means that the animal needs pressing.
This means that the animal will lie on his side
and you will squeeze on his stomach
until the juice is pressed out of his...
Soon trying to satisfy this need.
Click the check button.
The icon shown here represents the animal's hungry.
Yep.
Thirsty, hungry.
I don't know what that means.
Tired and needs exercise.
I already know.
It means that the need is critical
and the animal has not been able to satisfy it.
It's a good time to check your exhibit area.
Make sure the right objects,
in this case the right kind of foods,
are available.
This shows their heart rate.
Here's the status.
Current activity.
Resting under the shade.
Exiting the shade.
Just like a rollercoaster tycoon.
Condition that you want to be aware of.
This is where you see whether an animal is ill
or expecting a new addition.
Oh, you can see if they're pregnant.
Well, I don't...
They lay eggs.
So you wouldn't be pregnant.
All animals lay eggs.
So at least I think they do.
The last tab on this panel
will take you to the animal's general information.
It's really fine information
about the animal's gender, preferred biome,
and which part of the world it originates in.
Quick check button on this panel.
Oh, I think my zookeeper is about to lay an egg.
Get a lot of helpful information
about an animal's preferences
using the zookeeper recommendations panel.
Okay.
So the zookeeper will tell you what they need,
what they want.
It's pretty easy.
Filter to include only those that are useful
to the animal you have selected.
You can choose objects from this panel
and place them in your zoo
just as you do with the other.
The biopanel is covered in the second tutorial.
Check the box on this panel to close it.
Mini tabs on the zookeeper
to see which foods, shelters, plants,
trees, and enrichment objects the animal prefers.
So here we go.
Foods they prefer.
$75 for a bunch of leaves.
What the fuck?
What?
Oh, I got.
All right.
I'm good.
You can use the mini tabs and close.
Recommend close the panel after.
This is all the stuff.
Rocks.
They like rocks.
See?
They're fans of those.
All right.
Close that up.
Locate a zookeeper in your zoo.
If they're not in the middle
of performing a specific task,
you might find them sitting on one of your benches.
They're a lot like real people after all.
Otherwise, they'll be walking around
tending to your exhibits,
clicking on a zookeeper
to open the zookeeper panel.
Okay.
This is Keeper Van Houten.
Staff status panels
where you see your zookeeper's current duty.
This is what your zookeeper is doing right now.
Click the check.
I can't wait to have a hundred bears in the set.
No.
What?
Are we going too far?
Slow down.
Click the check button.
This is the current duty.
Staff assignments if your zookeeper has assignments.
Okay.
You can assign zookeepers to specific exhibit areas
but assigning them,
let's stay there.
Keep them focused on the exhibits that you select.
If a zookeeper does not have an assignment,
they'll just head for an exhibit that needs attention.
Depending on your zoo,
this could mean that they do a lot of walking.
That's okay.
So here's how you make an assignment.
Cursor turns into a flag post.
Place the flag post in your zoo
to assign a zookeeper to an exhibit area.
When finished, right-click the mouse to clear the cursor.
If you assign a zookeeper to more than one exhibit area,
it may become ineffective.
Click the check.
Okay.
So we realistically only just one here.
So that's good.
Staff thoughts.
I love my job.
This bench is comfortable.
Does it?
Yeah, man.
That's pretty good.
That's all you're thinking about.
This is a comfortable bench.
I love my job.
Nothing else?
That's a pretty clear mind.
The staff thoughts panel is what you see,
what you staff are thinking.
Here you might get a bit of insight on
whether there is something standing in the way of them
caring for the animals, right?
Staff salary.
This is where you see the salary,
how long they've been employed.
$500 a month to be a zookeeper.
Melissi loves that bench.
Select a guest.
Let's move on to the guests.
Kid.
Should we do kid or adult?
How about Railmaster Rex BBQ?
The guest activities and needs panel shows you
what the guest is currently doing.
Okay, yeah.
Guest needs.
Need a screen that's satisfied.
If it's yellow, it's pressing.
And if it's red, it's critical.
Going to buy the soda.
It's fucking Chad.
Why does Chad have to appear in every video game?
This is like 15 years ago.
All right, this is status tab.
This is hungry, hunger needs, thirst, rest,
amusement, bathroom.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, select guest.
Wow, this guy's loaded.
This guy has in his bank account
the amount of money that this guy,
my zookeeper makes in a month.
Jesus.
That's like a lot of money in this universe.
On this panel, you can see how much cash to get.
NileCrocodile1 has been put in a crate.
Why?
What did he do?
I don't know what that means yet.
If the guest has purchased a souvenir in your zoo,
click the check button.
Click on the guest favorites tab.
They really like camels.
Okay.
Guest favorite animal.
Guests are likely to make larger donations
if they see their favorite animals.
So stay on top of your guest favorites.
You'll reap the reward of money
coming in from donations and guest thoughts.
You can see, don't you wish you could read
everyone's mind this way?
Not really.
I really don't.
I do not wish I could read everybody's mind
because imagine if you could do that.
Imagine like just shaking somebody's hand at the bank.
Like, oh yeah, I'm banker one.
Oh, hi, I'm guy.
I'm guy one.
Oh, nice to meet you.
And you can read his mind.
I don't like your nose.
Your nose is ugly.
It's just like, what the fuck?
And then you can't even talk to the guy anymore.
Or like, oh, I'm welcome to the bank.
How you doing?
Like, I'm going to shit my pants.
I would laugh.
How would you be able to do anything?
Nothing would ever work.
You would never be able to have a conversation ever again.
If I could read people's minds, I wouldn't.
No, that's a power I don't want.
All right.
So we need to hope the small restroom one line
moves quickly.
I really need to use the bathroom.
I need to throw away this trash.
I prefer something other than soda.
I want something other than soda.
All we got is soda.
We just have Pepsi.
That's it.
All right.
Select a food stand.
Yeah.
Buildings have information as well.
Which, where are the food stands?
That's a pretty good zoo setup.
Here's a status panel.
It's how much money things are.
Yep.
Items being sold.
Some buildings may display slightly different information.
Finance tab.
Let's see how much it is.
So this is price, low, moderate, or high prices.
This is the balance sheet, which I will always be in the red for.
To show whether it's turning a profit or not.
Yep.
Get a complete overview about how your zoo is doing.
The zoo status page.
Here's the money tab.
This is going to just, yeah, it's how much money you spent versus how much you've received.
Mark your zoo is open or closed.
This is how you open the zoo.
Good to, that's actually really good to know.
And an altered level of your admission prices.
So wait, it costs money to come in and people are expected to give a bunch of money?
I thought it was okay.
When you close the zoo, all your guests will begin to leave.
Click the check button on this panel to continue.
Income and expenses tab.
Monthly tally of your financial comings and goings.
If you're seeing lots of red, your zoo is probably spending more than it's receiving.
Remember green is good.
And this is one place where you don't want to be looking through rose colored glasses.
Click the check button on this panel to continue.
Zoo fame.
Shows you how many animals you have, how happy people are.
There's an award ceremony probably at the end of the year.
Like in every single one of these video games.
You can mouse over them.
The more animals you have in your zoo, the more famous it becomes.
Animal happiness, guest education.
Releasing animals into the wild really increase fame for your zoo.
Does that mean like open the gates to the elephant enclosure and just watch what happens?
I mean, of course your zoo would be famous.
I'll release them.
I'm the omnipotent owner of the zoo.
Here's like the nuclear launch code to unlock all the doors.
I'll be so famous.
All right.
Zoo quick stats.
This shows pretty much everything here.
Illnesses can be very helpful at giving you an overview.
So crocodile one.
Uh oh.
This represents the animals current privacy.
Animals can use shelters or lion grass or shade to regain their privacy as more guests view them.
The crocodile wants more privacy.
I know this is going to be fun.
All right.
This guest list.
It shows everybody all the thing.
Can't wait to see some animals.
The camera will jump to that person if you click on it.
And track the movements of the animal the person selected.
Maybe another one of those don't you wish you could things.
Why do you want this?
What the fuck are you talking about?
The guy that wrote the tutorial.
You want to read everybody's mind and track everyone.
Did Mark Zuckerberg make this game?
Eventually, you know, his superpower started to become a reality.
We got information on staff.
You can see everybody, what everybody wants.
Whereabouts have you staffed in the zoo?
Camera will jump to that location and over there.
Stamp information, what you can do.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Waiting for job, waiting for job, waiting for job.
What the hell was that?
Which is fucking flashed by my screen.
Okay.
All right.
I think we're ready.
It's time to learn more about the photo safari.
Photo mode.
You can take a picture of this, yeah.
When a photo challenge is available,
you can right click to view the challenge.
Take a picture of a drum dairy camel.
This challenge asks you to take a picture of a drum dairy camel.
Think you're up for the challenge.
You can walk around using the left mouse button of the movie key.
Locate a camel in your zoo.
You can adjust the zoom of your camera in and out using the wheel.
All right.
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Was that kid just like going to the,
was that, were you just like pissing over there?
Hey, not allowed.
You fucking idiot.
Why'd you move?
That was a good photo.
Photo, yeah.
This way you can take another look at the picture
that you took for the photo challenge.
Right click, photo challenge.
Got it.
You can view any of the photographs you've ever taken
by opening your photo album tab.
I don't recommend doing this on stream.
Why?
For the photo, the photos that you've just taken
are shown in the film strip below the top of the screen.
You can click and drag them into empty slots in your photo album.
30 animals, 10 different boomers,
hundreds of objects, and more.
Be sure to refer to the Zoo Tycoon 2 manual
for even more in-depth information.
Tutorials are marked with the book icon.
I'm ready.
Let's do it.
Okay, here we go.
Welcome to the stream, everybody.
Feel like I have to run on a stage
and start like screaming and pointing into the audience.
It's been an hour.
It's been, holy shit, it's been an hour.
Whatever.
We're ready.
Play, when do we start with the campaign?
Oh, fuck.
There's like probably 10 tutorials.
I don't know how to fucking play.
Sandbox game?
Oh, God.
I'm not ready for this.
No.
Let's get away with it.
No tutorial.
Zookeeper in training.
See, you have a great opportunity to take over a small zoo,
but you need to prove that you understand
that animals have individual biome needs.
Make sure each animal is moved into its appropriate biome exhibit
and run your new zoo for one month.
Complete all scenarios in this campaign
and you'll get like 50 times somebody's income.
I need to understand.
You will play and you'll like it.
Just wait.
I need to, let me just get,
let me just ease into the game.
$30,000 a month.
Just let me do this first.
I need to, I can't just jump into sandbox mode.
Look, I need to learn the very basics of like color
and paint and canvases.
Don't just dump the most expensive tools into my backyard and say,
I expect the Mona Lisa in 10 minutes.
So I don't even know how,
I don't even know what the, what RGB means.
What does it even stand for?
All right, great opportunity to take over a small local zoo.
For however, the current owner wants to be sure
that you understand that animals have individual needs.
He's provided you with three animals
that need to be placed in their appropriate biome exhibit.
Each animal can be found in a crate
at the front entrance of your zoo.
When you select the crate,
the information panel indicates what kind of animals inside.
Pick up the crate and move it like any other object.
To release an animal from its crate, click on crate.
You need to move and release each animal.
Yeah, yeah, to verify you can handle the basics.
You've also been tasked to run the zoo for one month
and ensure the animals survive.
Tip, in the interest of keeping your animals alive,
you want to provide them with food and water.
I get, I don't, I don't understand.
Do the things need to eat and drink?
Release each animal from its crate
and place an appropriate exhibit.
That's, I got 15 minutes to do this.
Okay, I accept the challenge.
Here we go.
Welcome to Zoo Tycoon 2.
Where are those crates?
These are at the entrance, right?
Oh, here are the three animals.
Okay, how do I grab them?
Where's the music?
Okay, this is a hippopotamus
and needs to be in a wetlands biome.
No, don't, no, no, go back in.
So this looks pretty wet over here.
Don't just drop them in the ocean.
All right, here we go.
This looks pretty, this is wetlands right here.
Okay, looks good.
Let's uncrate the hippopotamus.
I hope you like your new area.
We got, this is a polar bear.
It needs to be in a tundra, which is right here.
And we need to put the lion into the savanna.
I did it.
Polar bear needs more space.
What?
Run the zoo for one month
and ensure that you have all three animals
in your zoo at the end of the month.
What do you mean he needs more space?
Do you have the biggest exhibit here?
This is, this is enough for like 25 polar bears.
All right, that's, you're good.
Let's open the zoo.
The zoo is open.
I'm ready to make this first challenge
and then we can move on to the more difficult tasks.
All right, so we need buildings.
I want to get, we need educator podium
right at the beginning here.
Now release them.
I'm not going to release the animals.
Look, I need to make the person in the video game
that you walk by in the first five to 10 minutes
of the story and it's the guy sitting there preaching
in front of the first, like after the first cut scene
that you walk by right there.
Okay, we need an educator.
There's one person, Jeremy Albertson.
Holy shit, that was close.
All right, what do you need?
I can't wait to see some animals
going right for the hippopotamus.
All right, two guests now.
How much is this place?
Okay, how much is it?
$50.
No, it's, just make it 20 bucks.
Okay, here's Jim Ben Dixon wants to see a warthog.
Well, hold on a minute here.
Warthog.
Do I have access to warthog?
Velociraptor.
Why would a velociraptor be here right now?
What is he going?
He's going to take a shit in the corn.
He's going to kill guests.
No, I'll take care of this.
Hey, get out of here.
Oh, he wants to go in.
You want to go in there?
No, you can't go in there yet.
There's nothing in there.
He wants to go in and eat the hippopotamus.
Where is it?
Does that help?
Where is he going?
Uh-oh, there's one random guy.
Hey, come on in and see our new mascot, the velociraptor.
This biome is not suitable for velociraptor one.
What's he thinking about?
Family tree.
No family tree yet.
All right, well, I told you I can't go off the rails yet.
Get rid of the raptor.
What do I do?
How do I get rid of him?
Hold on.
Why is there like no audio?
There's no audio in this game.
There's no guns in this game.
Line one is not contained.
What do you mean line one is not contained?
Oh, wait, I deleted the fence.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
He's figuring it out.
I guess I could walk through here.
Where is he going?
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
He's sprinting.
Who is he sprinting?
This guy's going to shit his pants.
He's like, I can smell it.
I need to turn the fucking audio up.
Polar bear is hungry.
All right, delete game.
Whatever, save game.
The whole game closed.
I need to turn the sound up.
All you can hear is every so often you hear.
All right, I'll get in the sandbox.
I know how the game works.
There it comes.
Hopefully, it's not loud when you hear this.
It probably will be, though.
So just brace yourself.
Oh, I told you I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
I tried to warn you.
That's better.
That's actually kind of loud.
That's too loud now.
40 and like 43, 35, 38.
All right, let's play.
I don't know how to take care of dinosaurs,
but I'll figure it out.
How about no, let's go.
What's wrong with the world right now?
What does this take place?
Half the world is under water.
Oh shit.
Is this like post-apocalyptic?
This is what's left.
One giant road through Russia.
Filters.
All right, let's do.
We can't just go right to the extinct animals.
We'll do medium.
Medium in Western Europe.
Let me just do something normal.
You know what I mean?
No dinosaurs, no aliens.
Okay, here we go.
Trying to make my park.
I don't like this place.
This is like a 2007 World of Warcraft zone.
I don't want to do this one.
All right, well, whatever.
Let's just, we'll work with what we got.
Start the process.
Landscaping.
I want, let's get some paths here.
No, no, no, no.
I want a path.
There's so many people parked out here
waiting for this to open.
What was the pathing tool?
Right here.
Okay, so asphalt path.
I'm going to just simply,
I'm going to follow the tutorial here.
I can expand up there later.
That looks good.
All right.
And then we're going to come across this way.
We're going to have small exhibits.
Very small, not huge.
This is, this is going to have rabbits in here.
If you think I'm going to put lions and polar bears, no.
We're going to have goats, rabbits,
and then a couple of pigs.
This is going to be essentially the
part of the county fair that you go to
that has the shitty pumpkin contest
and then the random pigs.
No, whoops.
How do I, how do I delete you?
This is not, how are people going to get up there?
That's so ugly.
What have I done?
What's the, what's the bulldoze button?
There it is.
Okay, that's better.
But turbo, that side's not, it's not exact.
That's fine.
Whatever.
We just make like a fucking spatula.
I'll move this one over.
Now it'll be fine.
Everyone can relax.
So that means it needs to be one, two, three, four.
So we need one, two, we need one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Oh, fuck me.
What, a turbo?
You did a good job, man.
Could I pick a shittier level?
I just picked a random place in Europe.
Let's start with the amenities.
Extinct research lab.
Entertainer stage.
Absolutely.
But this is a dinosaur one though.
So how we're going to make this is you have to cross this path.
So you're going to get bang, bang.
There's no way to go around it.
You have to go like this.
And it's going to be a donation box, donation box.
We're going to start the donation process the second you enter.
So we got, I need like three, hold on a minute.
Dino capture team bunker.
What, what the hell is that?
Sabertooth tiger, paleontologist.
We have to have the dinosaur entertainer here.
How am I going to have on one stage?
We have to make an entire ensemble children's television show cast.
That's all you do.
You just dance forever.
Coming up next on Disney Jr.
The dinosaur troop.
All right, so that's fine.
Why are they running around wild?
Now, you know what?
You're fired.
Anybody that gets off that stage is fired.
We found the one employee.
That was a test.
That was a test to find out who really was dedicated.
I'm going to see you.
Dinosaur Kimmy.
And that means you get a raise.
I don't think I can.
How do I, I can't raise.
I love my job.
I hope the crowd likes my show.
It's time to do a show.
That's so, that park didn't even open yet.
All right, hold on.
Why, why did that happen?
Why am I in water now?
Okay.
All right.
Now we need, uh, no, stop running away.
Whatever.
You'll figure it out.
Transportation.
We can do jeeps.
Jeep vehicle station.
Are you serious?
Where did you come from?
Hold on.
Did that person just trade?
We're going to have a jeep.
It's too much.
Hold on.
And you get in here.
Jeep vehicle station.
Oh, I gotta get rid of this.
All right.
So then now, crossing gate road.
Click dislike.
Then place a crossing gate.
We keep pedestrians from crossing a road where a jeep is.
Hold on there.
Which allows jeep vehicles to enter and exit animal exhibits.
Holy shit.
This is going to be so boring.
No, undo.
Oh, come on, man.
I'm trying to move.
I'm trying to move this.
What the fuck are you doing?
Why?
What?
Okay.
Here we go.
I can't beat that.
Just absolutely.
I mean, giving people a chance.
All right.
Jeep transportation circuit is complete.
So let's put in.
We gotta have at least one.
All right.
Here we go.
I don't think I can put one here.
This is going to get so backed up.
This ride is going to take forever.
Two strands of Sky Team cable.
What?
You can do a cable car too?
Oh, this is just a lawsuit.
We just need to see what happens.
All right.
Uh, so you got the two dinosaurs
running around in circles.
Tank building.
Wall for water.
This is why I didn't want all the painters tools.
This is why I didn't want all the tools at once.
All right.
Let's make some, let's make some habitats.
So this is going to be, let's get a, okay.
Fence.
This is chain link fence on a tight budget.
I mean, we're not, but just that's fine.
Let's go here.
That looks good.
Get an entrance.
Another, let's just do chain link fence for now.
Oh, whoops.
So it has to go down to here.
That's enough room for a half of a chimpanzee.
Well, that's fine because it's not the right climate.
These are tiny, but that's for the gerbil.
Look, I'm just trying to, this isn't set in stone yet.
Okay.
I just want to make sure I know what I'm doing.
We can make habitats and staff members.
There you go.
Just directionless.
Absolutely no direction.
It doesn't know what time it is.
It doesn't know what day it is.
It doesn't know the last time.
I told you, I told you, I can't see in the suit that well.
He's just running into shit.
He doesn't have eye holes.
What is he doing?
He's just panicking.
I only know how to do one thing.
Might as well do the one thing I know.
Look at that sweat mark.
Okay.
So we need a couple more of these habitats.
Do I need somebody to drive?
Okay.
There we go.
Now, animals.
Let's see what we got.
Armadillo.
I mean, that's not a cool animal.
We need small animals.
So beaver.
Beaver would work.
I need rabbits.
Here, what's this?
Fox.
That's a little too big.
Oh, there's turkeys.
Okay.
Maybe a bunch of turkeys.
It's penguins.
There's so many different animals.
Now, let's start small because I was supposed to start small.
Ostrich.
No.
Beaver.
We need something a little.
Fox is fine.
Fox is a little.
I don't need that much space.
A water loving rodent from North America needs wetlands biome.
Okay.
So let's make wetlands biome.
We need wetlands.
That's going to be the main attraction, by the way.
And this is going to make some water.
Like shallow water over here.
And then make it a little deep.
Make it shallow in the ends.
Oops.
All right.
Looks good.
Deep, shallow, and then dirt.
We need, let's go like that.
All right.
Putting our first animal in the exhibit.
American beaver.
An American beaver in Europe.
That's too many.
You're fired.
They need more space.
No, don't let them out.
Now we just got to get rid of these fences here and extend the habitat.
There you go, guys.
Okay.
Habitat.
Wetlands.
Ah, I know.
Don't worry.
That's not enough space for you.
How is there a guest in here?
How did you get in here?
Why are you angry?
Who the fuck are you?
This park's not even open.
It doesn't look like American beaver has enough space.
American beaver looks unhappy.
I'm going home.
This park is, did you let, is this like the dinosaur's family?
No, it's closed.
Get out of here.
One of these idiots opened the park.
Okay, hold on.
Let's get some food here.
Animal food for a beaver.
I need, oh wait, I need a zookeeper.
Let's get a couple of zookeepers.
Why the fuck are you running away?
How do you need more space than this?
Okay.
Food.
What does, what does beaver eat?
I need to like click on their tab here.
All right.
Uh, space is critical.
What are you doing?
Are you breaking up shit in the bottom?
Are they dead?
Why are they lying down?
Are they breaking shit up on the bottom of the ocean?
Okay, hold on, hold on.
Deep water.
That's not deep enough.
The zoo only has beavers.
Well, the zoo only has beavers because it, they're angry with me.
This one's happy.
All right, we need food.
We need branches.
So we can put like branches here.
Hollow log with lettuce.
Oh, they're all going for it.
Quick.
It's a race to get the food.
Who's the alpha beaver?
Uh, lettuce pile.
There we go.
See now they're happy.
Food, dish.
They really are fighting each other.
All right.
They need more space though.
Is this going to be just a beaver zoo?
Look, pile of branches.
You guys can like play over here.
Animal shelters.
They don't need an animal shelter.
They're, they, they, they need more land.
Okay.
Well, I'll take down this shit then.
You need more land?
Pause the game.
I'll give you more land.
I get complaints now.
Then I'm going to be very upset.
Wetlands.
Go with the grass.
Let's extend the big pool.
Let's do, let's get shallow water this way.
Because then I'll do deep here.
So they can at least hang out over there.
Oh, the stupid fucking thing's in the way.
Okay.
Shallow water.
American beaver is not contained.
Well, it's, the game's paused.
Everything's fine.
All right, here we go.
We need to get this one closed in.
And then this needs to be closed in.
I don't, why did I even build this?
The road thing.
I was just, I'm like a child.
I had to make it.
All right.
That's enclosed.
I'm ready to turn it back on.
Let's get some food in here for them.
Okay.
Mr. Ranger.
We've got, uh, let's, the food.
Let's put some rocks.
Let's give them a couple of rocks.
That's too big of a rock.
That's also too big of a rock.
Just get like two or three, like,
dinosaur droppings over here for you to play with.
Uh, plants.
All right.
Uh, a little log that I'm sure they're going to love that.
And then let's get some toys.
This doesn't go in the water.
It goes just like going to the edge here.
We'll put one down here.
Uh, Misty Spring.
That's a huge log.
Beavers love logs.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Right in the corner here.
And then we need, I think we need more food.
Hollow log with lettuce.
Yeah, we'll put the, that's like a little snack for them over here.
All right.
No more complaints.
Why do they sound like pigs?
All right.
What can I see?
What do you need?
Comfortable the animal is.
Hygiene needs.
All right.
We're good.
This is just barely big enough for them, by the way.
How?
Social needs.
They need to be social with other animals.
Current simulation level.
They'll spread out.
Expand.
I thought I can't expand.
This is not going to be Beaver Park.
This is a great exhibit right here.
How is it?
How are you not contained?
You're in here.
Social.
What's your problem?
Put it up for adoption.
I need more fresh trees.
All right.
Let's put in some fresh trees.
Where's the ranger?
I need ranger to tell me, uh, some help me here.
All right.
American Beaver.
Uh, tree.
All right.
Here we go.
They're going to have you get one, two trees and that should be good.
They're all females.
What?
What do you mean they're all female?
I only put in females?
Uh, that's it.
And that was enough to make it fine.
I just deleted a beaver.
I think I just killed a beaver.
I just killed a beaver.
I think they're going to kill each other.
No, they're not.
This is part one.
I'm going to delete this stupid fucking thing.
And that's going to make more room.
I'll put some food and, and drinks down here.
Over here is going to be the entrance with dinosaurs.
It's going to be two dinosaur dancers.
And then we're going to go up.
We're going to take a little monorail up this way.
It's not just going to be Beaver Park.
It's be it's the Beaver Park for the first five seconds.
Contain it.
Just contain it.
I build this later.
American Beaver is not contained.
It will be very soon.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's actually get this built.
And then I'm going to do extend the water.
And then I'm going to have a little island over here for them to hang out.
And on the island is going to be a fucking grizzly bear.
So good luck beavers.
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's not going to happen.
Hey, you know, like I said, I wasn't going to go off the rails or the first like hour.
I wonder what happened with that.
Oh, this is too far.
Right here, right here.
Is that enough?
How many beavers do I have?
I haven't even checked that.
Wetlands.
Quick to include plants.
Oh, wait, I can.
Oh, hold on a minute here.
Oh, it does it automatically.
Would you look at that?
See, but we need water.
It's making little lily pads for them.
I need it.
I want like a little hangout zone here though.
Like they can come over to the other shore.
They can swim to the other shore.
All right.
Let's put food over here.
What's this thing?
No, I don't want to do that.
Let's get some food over here.
Needs more space.
You'll get it in a second.
How about, uh, let's put some food dish with roots.
Now let's put, how many do we have?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
There's like fourteen or like fifteen.
Let's go see.
Look at that.
And, and there's going to be a fun log over here.
They're enclosed, right?
What do you say now?
They need more space.
Move triangle.
Hold on.
I'm going to remove the triangle.
I need more space.
How many are in here?
All right.
I'm sorry.
How do I pick?
No, these are like pigs.
No, I don't want to get rid of this one.
This one's fun.
This one's, oh, I like them all.
All right.
How do I, uh, how do I put them up for adoption?
I did it.
I think I did it.
No, I didn't.
Did I do it?
How?
You still need space.
I'm trying to fire the beavers.
They still need space.
Oh, okay.
Look at that.
Done.
Very cool.
Okay.
So now, interestingly enough, okay.
Let's, um, I'm just kidding.
Let's go.
Spin out their numbers.
Put in a crocodile.
No, I'm not going to fuck with the beaver exhibit.
It's the best thing we got.
Okay.
I've been doing this for so long.
Get out of here.
All right.
Now we need, um, we have our beaver exhibit.
Is that worth $50 to come in and see shitty beavers?
Let's go back to this.
I can't just have it drive through the exhibit, guys.
I just started.
I can't ruin everything.
You know what I mean?
We need to at least make this.
I can't do that right now.
That's too much.
Maybe it, that's not safe, apparently.
There we go.
It just needs to go around it.
People still need to,
I need an enjoyable ride in this park.
You understand?
Everything here sucks.
Nothing here is good.
Everything sucks.
You drive around in a go-kart around a beaver exhibit and it's 50 bucks.
Actually, that's kind of cool.
That actually is pretty cool.
Never mind.
Staying corrected by myself.
All right.
Uh, open it.
Click to close the station.
No guests can enter when the station is closed.
I think we need, but can we use it?
Incomplete circuit.
Oh, it's because of this.
Okay, I need to build.
Change circuit direction.
That's fine.
So this should complete the circuit.
Incomplete circuit.
Where?
Fuck.
Oh well.
Stupid motherfucker.
Okay.
Open.
So how do we test it?
What kind of jeep do we want to use?
Definitely the Jurassic Park one.
Click select and then place the decorated jeep.
Yeah, place it, man.
I should know this one.
This one.
How many can I have?
I guess I can have like more than five.
Nobody who's even in these.
I'm wasting so much money.
Are these guys going to never end just drive around the track with nobody?
Can I get in?
How do I get in?
Wait, I own the place.
Let me in.
Oh, I can get on.
See, we're taking a tour of Beaver Park.
What's this guy's problem?
Get back to work.
What's going on?
What's happening here?
Hey, how do I beep the horn?
Actual traffic.
What's the issue here?
Oh, look at how cute that is.
Pick with my photo.
I missed it.
How do I fix this?
Okay.
The terrain is impassable.
How do I take care of that?
All right.
I think I know how to take care of it.
Capacity six.
Capacity.
So, that's the ride there.
Looking good.
Watch out.
And now we just need guests to ride in the gigantic Jurassic Park funeral caravan, apparently.
This is just like...
I thought...
Didn't I fire you?
Oh, no.
You're the other one.
Dino is back.
All right.
We're good.
So now I got to make some decent roads.
Let's go up here because this will take you then straight through and then up here into
the next exhibit, which we will determine what that is very soon.
I don't know what the hell it's going to be, but it's going to be right here.
Okay.
Looking good.
So, at this point...
What the fuck?
Okay.
That looks fine.
Zoo does...
I don't want to open it yet.
I need...
That guy just fell out of the gate.
Wait, he swam to the gate.
The gate...
Where's the gate?
Oh, for the love of God.
I need more than one gate.
Do they have food in here?
Where?
I feel like this is a people habitat as much as it is a beaver one.
Watch out.
I have 25 employees whose job it is just to drive in a circle all day.
So they can't be hurt.
That's good.
That's very good to know.
All right.
So now I'm like lost on what I want to do next here.
Let's make this a double just so there's enough room for people to watch.
I want to have a donation exhibit here.
I need some food, some stalls.
Let's try to get around this somehow.
That has to go.
I'm so...
I'm so glad that they can't get run over.
It's just a beaver prison.
No, it's not.
This is making me so nervous.
I feel like someone's going to get fucking run over.
It's a beaver prison that is being constantly patrolled.
Like a caravan of staff.
Okay.
People can cross that.
That's fine.
High security.
High security for the beavers.
Make sure nobody gets out of there.
So how much electricity have I wasted so far?
Let's take a look at my finances.
Are you kidding me?
$260,000.
At least I got a deductible of $7,700 this year in taxes.
What is...
The beavers are that expensive?
That's how much 10 beavers cost?
That's not true.
A beaver is like probably $60.
They had to be imported from America because this is Europe.
It was the dinosaurs.
All right.
Well, that's a wash though.
This month doesn't count.
Okay.
Honestly, that's more confusing than if it was beavers because
a T-Rex is definitely worth more than probably $50 million.
How much was a T-Rex?
10 grand?
20 grand?
No, don't...
You can't...
You can't fire.
No, don't fire.
All right.
We need...
I need some kiosks here.
We need ATM.
Yeah, we want to clean them out.
Right behind that is the donation machine.
Where's the donation machine?
Yeah, you take out money from the ATM and you go directly
to the fucking donation machine behind you.
Where is it?
That's an educator podium.
Family restroom ATM.
Is the zoo open yet?
No.
Research lab.
Am I missing something here?
Wireless headsets?
Maybe it's over here.
Gift cart.
Wireless headsets.
Cave painting hall.
Oh, here it is.
Okay.
Donation box.
So let's spin this around over here and then do one over here as well.
Guys, if you like the show, you know, consider wiping out your checking account.
Does this cost money to use?
No, don't sell it.
Okay.
That's good.
All right.
So I got money.
I need food.
Picnic table.
We'll put it...
We'll make a little spot over here.
Let's get some concrete, dirt, sand, brick, stone.
This would be like the food area.
This guy's dancing in the road.
He's just getting beeped at.
Get out of the way.
Hey, come on.
You got to make a living.
So stone path.
This is going to be the food court.
So we're going to go this way.
That's fine over there.
That's good.
So there's going to be food, drinks, right at the beginning.
Put a bathroom over here.
Oh, maybe we won't.
Elevated paths.
Okay.
Buildings.
So we need a...
I need an educator podium in front of the beavers.
That's going to be over here.
Really important.
This is all I have.
I need an educator.
I need some maintenance workers too.
A trainer.
We can teach them tricks.
Cool.
Okay.
There's the educator podium for the beaver exhibit.
I'm just poisoning with the carbon.
No, they're far enough away.
Everything's going to be fine.
All right.
I'm almost ready to open my zoo.
Almost time.
Small restroom.
Staff center.
This is huge.
It's going up here.
Okay.
Name of the beavers.
Not yet.
I gotta build some more stuff though.
Okay, we need food.
What do we get?
I can't look at this.
I'm going to get hungry.
I really will get hungry looking at this.
A sub sandwich.
Subs are meat-filled sandwiches that are commonly devoured for lunch.
Why would you word it like that?
Weird.
Okay.
Sub shop.
Uh, sushi.
I need to put the sushi place in front of like an aquarium exhibit, don't I?
Well, that's really fun.
Why would I want to do that?
No, that's normal, right?
Salads.
Coffee.
And water.
Make sure water is...
We need water over here.
Cotton candy.
Candy can cart.
No.
Soda drinks.
And hot dogs.
All right.
I think I'm almost ready to open the park.
I'm ready.
No, not yet.
These are luxurious food stands.
Yeah, you're going to be paying for quality.
It's not shitty quality.
Going to staff center for supplies.
Okay, I think I have the staff center.
All right, I need one more exhibit before I open the zoo.
And it's going to be something that I can handle it.
How about one beluga?
No.
A whale.
A huge whale.
Orca.
A giant warthog.
I don't know.
Should I make a beluga whale?
What the hell?
Cave lion.
Komodo dragon.
Gigantopithecus.
What?
What about...
I mean, I kind of want to do the gigantopithecus.
This thing...
This is huge.
60 grand.
All right.
What biome does it need?
Tropical rainforest.
So let's do...
Let's get the area secure.
Okay.
What does he eat?
He needs a better habitat.
He needs a habitat.
He eats beavers.
What do you eat?
He's extinct.
He's...
I'm bringing it...
Look, I'm bringing him back.
No, he eats...
Lurbo.
Dinosaur meat.
Shrimp.
He's got a lot of options here.
Hollow log with...
Look, I'm just getting one of those dog toys
and filling it with different foods.
And peanut butter and stuff.
He's...
It's really hard for him to do.
And he's sticking his tongue in there like,
I can't get it.
All right.
So he eats fish.
Let's go ahead and get him in there.
Pause the game though.
Holy shit.
He's huge.
All right.
So we need roots.
Food dish.
Bamboo.
Is this what you eat?
What happened to like the dinosaur head?
Squeaky toy.
Okay.
He's an artist.
A feeder ball.
Okay.
Feeder ball.
Squeaky toys.
Habitat.
Shade structure.
Rock shelter.
Or a lion top of...
This is big.
What about this?
Here we go.
I wish I could put it here.
Only let him have the easel?
Oh, this is what it's gonna have to do.
No, wait, hold on.
That's gonna have to do for now.
I can expand later.
Food.
We're gonna put branches over here.
We'll put some food dish.
Let's put some yummy leaves.
Okay.
Let's give him some little trees.
All right.
Looks good.
Let's give him a rock.
Oh!
Okay.
I thought I just killed him.
That scared the shit out of me for some reason.
All right.
Okay.
So now he needs a...
We need this...
What is it?
What does he need?
The tundra?
Family tree.
Wait, they're gonna have babies?
All right.
I need...
What does he need?
What biome?
I forget what the hell it was.
Or it was tropical rainforest.
There it is.
All right.
Let's go with this.
What the fuck?
Let's get...
I can put a few of these trees in here.
Just...
Actually, this is elevated now.
Let's go up here.
Actually, he should be happy.
I'd be happy.
Put him in like the golden seeds.
I think he...
Okay.
So let's see how that happens.
So let's get the exhibit out.
I need to put a entrance here.
Right here.
Actually, let's put it...
Yeah.
Right there.
All right.
I've got my first giganthosaurus.
I'm gonna think of a good name.
Is he ready to paint?
Who's a painter's name?
Michelangelo?
Picasso?
How about Bigasso?
Because he's big.
Bigasco.
Okay.
He's unable to reach the leaves.
Maybe too close to another object.
Beaver is pregnant?
Where?
Who's pregnant?
Oh, this is...
He's like, oh, wow.
I got a good view of that.
What are these?
What are these fishes?
Where did they come from?
Why are you so angry?
Going to pee.
You're not gonna go pee in somebody's food, are you?
What food bowl is he about to piss in?
Oh, there he goes.
Peeing on dirt.
Okay.
Good pee.
What the hell is this?
They made their own beaver lodge.
I didn't do this, did I?
Who's in there?
Resting in the beaver lodge.
They just made this.
I want to go in there.
Am I allowed in here?
American Beaver 3 is pregnant.
They're just having sex with each other in here.
This is...
Okay, this is kind of like not good.
Replenish.
That's a VR game quality.
All right, we're good.
Yep.
These two just create...
They're creating babies over here.
I'm going to have to keep expanding this.
They're just going to keep having sex with each other.
And they're going to keep having babies.
I'm going to have to keep expanding this.
The bark isn't even open yet.
Well, how's my other guy doing?
I was like, why is he not here?
Going to pee.
Squeaky toy.
Where's he going to pee?
He's going to piss on the easel and make art.
Let's visit him.
Whoa, easy.
I want to groom him.
How do I groom him?
He's getting antsy.
I don't like this.
No, he's happy.
Look how happy.
50!
Look, he's like, I can lift so much weight.
All right, well, you're good.
Currently sitting.
Draw something.
All right, I need to...
It's time to open the park.
Wait, I need an education stand and a donation machine.
Educator platform can go here.
We need another educator.
And I need some donation machines as well.
Donation box.
Go ahead.
Right in front.
I think it's time to actually open this place.
I'm going to save it.
Another beaver is pregnant.
Save game.
All right, beavers and big guys.
All right, it's time to open the park.
Wait, I need a toilet.
I need a bathroom.
It's really important.
Uh, let's do family restroom.
This is huge.
All right, good enough.
It's a couple's restroom?
What?
All right, what's wrong with the leaves?
You apparently can't reach these leaves because they're too high.
Okay.
Well, then let's make that terrain better then.
I need to lower the ground.
I may have just fucked it all up.
Whatever.
Open the park.
The park is now officially...
Let's go!
Rack in the money.
I can't wait to see some animals.
Beaver and butt head.
One person.
After months and months in development.
One, one guy.
Well, I hope you enjoy yourself.
Get to work.
The first guess, you've been training for so long.
For this exact moment right here.
And you're missing your opportunity.
Where's it going?
We're going to follow this guy around.
No ATM.
Skip the ATM.
Skipping the donation machine.
Okay.
I think this person is so dehydrated and foodless at this point.
Ooh, I like seeing animal American beaver 13 eat from the substrate pile.
It's neat seeing American beaver 2 resting in the beaver lodge.
I can't wait to see some more animals.
Wait, track him.
He likes it.
Kimmy is high.
Well, we got another guest.
See, this guy just tweeted out that he was here and how fun it was.
And his five followers just said it to come.
I can't wait to what people have to say about...
Is nobody going to get on that ride?
I want someone to get...
How do I get them on the ride?
Is it possible?
At least they're happy.
I need like benches.
I need a place to sit down.
American beaver 4 is about to give birth.
Come on, come on, this is first time.
This is my first ever time that I'm going to...
I got it.
Oh, now there's not enough space.
I have...
There's not enough space.
More space.
Many animals don't have enough space because they're a beaver
and they're inside of this giant beaver enclosure.
Another birth.
Oh, god damn it.
I can stay on top of this.
What the fuck's going on here?
Here comes another one.
Okay.
Here comes the magic of birth.
More space.
No, the park is open.
The park is currently open.
Hold on.
Set them all free.
No, I'm not going to set them all free.
Free.
Now, no one can even walk in the park.
There needs to be a path that now leads up here
and then around...
I got to level this whole thing.
Hold on, let me...
I'm making sure that I'm going to future proof
this whole exhibit here.
Oh, fuck.
Uh, sorry about that, guys.
I'll fix this, don't worry.
Those guys just drove around in a circle until they were evaporated.
And now, this is going to come out all the way to here,
right there,
and then up here.
It's like this.
Look at how much more space this is going to be.
Down here, the path is going to go around
to make sure this doesn't happen for like another at least 30 minutes.
That's done.
No one even...
No, people are going to walk in this park
and say, well, the beaver exhibit is stupid, and they leave.
A little do they know
that I have an extinct animal up here
that is wildly intelligent.
He can paint paintings.
Sell some beavers.
I can't.
They just have to put them up for adoption.
See?
Big Osco has no water.
Well, I'll get to that in a second.
I'll get to that in just a second.
All right, we need not tropical rainforest.
We need wetlands.
Take the trees off.
Uh, I'm okay with a little bit of rocks.
Now, I can expand the water a little bit.
Actually, let's have a nice little, uh,
little spot for them to go like up here.
Yeah, so that looks good.
Maybe a little bit deeper.
Give them some more room.
All right.
Okay.
Now, there's no problem.
We just need to put a...
Put crocodiles in there.
What?
Will a crocodile eat a beaver
in the same amount of time it takes for a beaver to come out of
a conception?
You know what I mean?
Like, to be conceived.
To be birthed, born.
Is that going to be the same?
Probably not.
Okay, so let's get...
I need the entrance.
So, we need one here.
We need one up here.
All righty, let's go.
Oh, shit.
You have to be out here.
I need to move this.
You need to move this.
I need fucking a road.
Not contained.
How is American Beaver 4 not contained?
Yes, you are.
They're all happy.
They can't get to the ape.
Wait.
Now they can.
I need an elevated path.
I wonder if I can...
Okay, they can make it.
Just need to get rid of this.
It looks a little ugly, but I'll fix it later.
More birth.
I don't think I can possibly get up here.
I need to make an elevated path.
Stone elevated path.
Okay, so we're gonna go right here.
And then this is gonna ramp down.
This is gonna be down, yeah, like that.
And then that leads to here.
All right.
We're good.
They can make it up here.
Oh, you dummy.
I need to really get in there.
The park is still open, isn't it?
Just make the bridge go over the beavers.
I mean, I was thinking about that.
It's a pretty good idea.
Okay, that looks good.
It's probably good.
I mean, not good at all.
It's all right.
That looks...
Look at that.
That's fine.
I'm just gonna fix this one later.
How are we doing?
We got any...
I don't like this zoo.
It's time for me to go home.
I don't think he's...
I don't think he's aggressive.
He just thinks it's funny.
He's just laughing.
Whoa, no way.
What?
What are you doing?
No, you're fired.
All right.
Hey, how do I make you happy?
I need to give him water.
I can't.
Whatever.
I'm not even gonna say anything.
Look at this painting.
Oh, that looks like shit.
What happened to the kid?
Where'd the guest go?
All right.
I gotta get back to this.
Tied.
No, we just gave him a little tap on the face.
And look at me, racking in mad dough over here.
Angry.
I think coffee drink one is overpriced.
Oh, action.
Fucking shot him.
It's...
Oh, I really need to use the bathroom.
I'm upset at the lack of trash cans.
I hope hot...
I hope dog hot...
I hope hot dog food stand.
Guests would like a place to sit.
Hey, littering?
You're gonna litter at my park?
This area smells.
He's just like, that is funny.
People are screaming.
I want to get over there.
He hasn't done anything wrong.
He's just listening to what she's saying.
He's very entertained.
Uh-oh.
He doesn't like this person.
I don't know why.
He just wants to eat leaves.
I wonder...
All right, let's let her out of here.
Well, he really doesn't care at all.
Help.
Big Asko is chasing me.
Well, that's not real.
He's chasing me.
All right, you're fine.
It was a fake Yelp complaint.
He needs food.
He doesn't have any food left?
What's he doing?
What happened?
What's wrong with him?
Oh, he's just sleeping.
Okay.
Uh, let's get some food in here for you.
How about like a bowl of leaves?
Here.
There.
Now you can eat.
And yet you've got water.
There's water here.
There's still water in there.
Yeah, he's fine.
What are you talking about?
So now this is how you get reviews.
This is how you get attention to your park.
Everybody's reading in the newspaper about
the guy that got pushed over
and the lady that was screaming.
And now everyone just needs to come see for themselves.
Marketing.
One-on-one.
All right, how about even with the, uh, beavers?
The beavers in attraction?
Yeah, people like the beavers.
Seems to be going pretty well.
Uh, how do I get rid of this fucking thing?
I'm not going to use it.
All right, what's the next attraction?
People need to be able to get up there first.
I guarantee I turn a profit this next month.
All right, the track is gone.
It's just an annoyance.
Let's get some benches.
So bench.
Just sit it.
We need to make these a little wider.
And the food court.
There's got to be some benches.
Why are you so angry about?
Relax.
I don't have a place to sit down and drink my tea.
Uh, I need trash bins.
All right.
Finally, people can throw their trash away.
It's been like two hours.
American beaver 13 is really thirsty.
American beaver 5 is unable to reach the hollow log.
Just drink water.
There's running water right here.
Just just drink water.
All right, I need to refill.
Now this is full.
Is there really one water dish?
Nobody needs it fulfilled.
This is the only one.
Everyone's drinking out of the same water dish.
Oh, for the love of God.
Okay, hold on.
I didn't know that.
I thought they just went underwater and just went.
He's gonna fill it.
I need like a bunch of these.
I need them over here.
Uh, food dish with water.
Put it next to the foods.
I don't have to go that far.
That looks good.
All right.
How we doing with money?
Whatever.
$175 for a tuna can with water in it.
Yeah, all they're doing guys is the zookeepers are going over here and
dumping the dish in there and just putting it over there.
That's $175 middleman.
All right, let's go see how he's doing.
Your needs are good.
Not that thirsty.
Everything's good to go.
All right, I think it's time to add onto the zoo.
The next thing is going to be a water exhibit over here.
After another, I need another bathroom.
Family restroom right here.
And then take a path up this way.
And this is our first water exhibit.
It's going to be right here.
It's going to be like five killer whales.
Let's see what we need.
What kind of habitat do you need?
Can perform in shows.
We should get a flavor bird exhibit.
No, that's not bad.
That's not a bad idea.
Just like a stegosaurus, manatee, mastodon.
I mean, that's kind of a flavor bird right there.
No, that's the real flavor bird.
I want a water exhibit though.
Whale shark.
That's the biggest shark in the world, right?
Yeah.
I want a whale shark exhibit.
Maybe some sort of water dinosaur.
Tyrannosaurus rex.
This is so huge.
I kind of need this though.
The t-rex is going to be over here.
Up.
You have to go all the way up to see him.
What a brilliant strategy that is.
I like that strategy a lot.
I became famous.
Did it.
All right.
We need to do.
I'm going to do like two t-rexes up here.
This whole entire area.
The whole viewing angle is going to be from right here.
We're going to have two t-rexes up here.
So you can either go up to the t-rex or right to the gosko.
So let's start with this down here.
Because it kind of needs to be like this.
Well, that didn't fucking do anything.
I think I'm going to have to go from here.
Hmm.
No.
Not quite.
What about the manatee exhibit?
No, don't worry.
I'll get it.
Really.
How do I level this whole thing?
Can I like level this place?
Just fucking trash it.
Just make it flat.
Guest mode.
Terrain.
Editor.
Here we go.
Flattened terrain.
There it is.
I mean, I kind of fucked this.
I don't even need this bridge.
This bridge makes no sense.
No.
Kill that person for no reason.
Okay.
Here we go.
Flattened terrain.
Flatten it.
You dick.
How did I?
I'm trying to flatten the terrain.
I'll just have to go like this.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
What have I done?
That's good.
Now I got to go back to here.
Where does this come out from?
No, this is not going to go up.
This has to go straight across.
And then down into right like here.
How much higher do you have to go?
No.
This is not what I wanted.
I'm going to go from here.
That makes most sense.
Beaver's pregnant.
All right.
That's good.
Are you telling me I can't go forward from here?
That is so close that it's infuriating me.
How is that possible?
I got a better idea.
Smooth this whole damn thing out.
So now I can just go straight down.
Right here.
Cross the earth onto your fist.
All right.
Can we do this again?
Guests need bathrooms.
Well, I'm trying to make a T-Rex exhibit.
So you're going to have to wait.
Here we go.
Got it.
All right.
Now we just need a regular path.
Let's get some more viewing angle for the beavers until it splits.
Which is going to split this way.
Fuck you, game.
How do I get rid of you?
I can't get rid of you.
I try to flatten you and it don't work.
Flatten.
Why is that one piece just sitting there?
Why are you doing this to me?
Dear Lord.
Oh, God.
Just keep it there.
Who cares?
Oh, no, no, no.
Now they're going to get out.
Look, you thought about it.
Okay.
So now we have this entrance this way.
This goes up to the, uh, vagasco.
Now it's time to make the T-Rex inhabitant.
Inhabit, uh, yeah.
Okay.
This needs a path.
Can I walk up this?
Okay.
It works.
Good.
Bath.
The path that needs to go.
The hell?
Why is it green?
Why did I just lose it?
I just lost a star.
For what?
Why did I lose it?
You can't lose accolades.
That's absolute dog shit.
All right.
Hold on.
I guess they need more bathrooms, huh?
Sure.
I'll make you more bathrooms.
Is this what you want?
How many more do you need?
What's that?
What are you guys doing over here?
Are people going and pissing in the bushes or like shitting in the woods?
Something is blocking the restroom.
What is blocking?
What's blocking the restroom?
All right.
The beavers are fine.
Everyone's doing well.
Guess it needs more bathrooms.
Well, you're gonna have to settle for what's there for now.
All right.
We need...
This is huge.
Ah, that sucks.
Wait a second.
Have I tried pressing G?
This terrain is so fucked up.
Got water?
Yeah.
No, you're fine.
Everybody's fine.
All right.
What does the T-Rex need?
T-Rex needs a tropical rainforest biome.
So tropical rainforest.
Trees in here.
That looks pretty nice.
And a little shallow water right in the corner.
A little pool.
American beaver six is pregnant again.
They're just having non-stop children in here.
This is the...
How can I tell how much money this has made?
Is there a way for me to tell?
How much money has the beaver attracted?
Was there even a donation machine here?
Has this just been for free the whole fucking time?
It has been.
This has been free the entire time.
Unless I get that...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Never mind.
We're doing just fine.
American beaver has received 2,165.
Let's flatten this out.
Make it look a little better.
Make a large viewing angle.
Delete that.
See like that.
Okay, so there's a lot of people that can be up here.
We need somebody to give tips on the T-Rex.
So we need a education kiosk.
Just did it right here.
Right here is fine, I think.
Let's get an educator.
And a donation box.
Because this is going to be worth...
This is going to be a lot of money.
So pay up.
Seriously.
All right.
So this is the walk up to the T-Rex exhibit.
Road splits.
Here's the person to tell you all about T-Rex.
Here's the donation machine.
So now I'm going to make sure there's like food in there.
All right, I can do that.
Okay.
$80,000 for a T-Rex.
All right.
Carnivorous predatory dinosaur.
What do they eat?
What does a T-Rex eat?
Male and female.
Okay.
T-Rex eats meat.
Right, makes sense.
Something is blocking the meat.
Nothing is blocking the meat.
Do they need more space?
They can eat, right?
There we go, yeah.
See, now let's get some water in there.
Get some toys.
Live food.
Okay.
Live lizards.
A block of ice.
A spring.
It needs to be a little bigger, but that's okay.
Dinosaur prey dummy?
Oh, that's going to be quite the show.
Put it right in front.
I'm blocking the pepperoni.
Look at how famous I am.
American Beaver wants to reproduce, but can't find a mate.
That's sad.
What are you two doing?
It's, I can't reach the food trough.
How?
It's right here.
Oh, this is probably in the way.
Are they going to start fighting?
Okay.
I put them both in this thing to have dinosaur sex and have dinosaur babies.
All right, well, 100, uh, I got 100, 100 guests have visited Yuzu.
That's good.
Cool.
How much am I going to get for this?
$860.
Thanks.
Is this, are you injured?
Social needs.
My, oh, my poor social needs.
I wonder.
Oh no, what have I done?
I killed the only friend I had.
He just broke out of the exhibit.
Well, he ain't going anywhere.
Okay.
Well, my social needs.
Who does it, how come he's not going anywhere?
Who does a T-Rex have a friend with?
Who can be a friend with?
What?
See, they all want to come up here now.
Beavers.
I can't put a beaver in here.
Get more space.
How am I going to get more space?
I need to go like this.
The keeper can't reach the T-Rex.
Oh, cause there's no gate on it.
Right.
I'm sorry about that.
Now you can reach the T-Rex.
I need to expand a little bit.
Let's get like a broken leg.
What?
I just saw like the, oh nevermind.
Okay.
So let's, uh, fix this.
And then I need the terrain tool.
And let's go like this.
There.
Now there's enough room for you.
Let's get you fenced back in.
Okay.
Non-contained.
Yes, you are.
That's good.
Let's get the actual terrain sprayer.
Tropical rainforest.
Oh, fuck.
Whatever.
Okay.
Now you should be happy.
This person got lost.
All right.
Can't reach the, oh, the dinosaur shit.
I'll get it.
I can go right here.
See?
He gets to scream at everybody from across the park.
You know how crazy that would be?
Okay.
I'll get it.
What does he need?
Well, I gotta pick up dinosaur poop.
All right.
Uh, let's wash his body.
I feel like this would be very unsafe.
All right.
He's good.
Just got some more water.
Okay.
We're good.
I can't leave.
I need to move this.
That's why the keeper can't reach him.
This has to go on the other side.
This guy's not talking to anyone.
All right.
We need to get some attraction up here.
We need to get some people up here.
You.
Help.
The Tyrus T-Rex is chasing me.
This zoo is great.
Well, that feels better.
So I got the T-Rex exhibit up here.
He oversees the whole park.
Fix the hole.
I'm almost at two stars.
Getting closer.
All right.
You're good.
We got already have more money than the American Beaver exhibit.
Which there needs to be.
What was wrong?
More birth.
How many Beavers do I have?
Is there a way I can tell how many Beavers I have?
16.
Where's the family tree?
What?
He's still in.
He's still.
Where did you come from?
All right.
It's time to close you up for real.
Where's like the actual fence?
Rail fence.
We need like a dinosaur fence.
There.
No, I don't want to do an electric fence.
Dinosaur fence.
There it is.
He got out.
He actually got out.
All right.
He's contained.
Where was he going to go?
Nowhere.
All the way up here.
I need to like replace this whole fence.
From here.
Here we go.
He wants to be free.
Well, he should have thought about that before he murdered his cellmate.
I mean his roommate.
His roommate.
His other...
All right.
He's closed off.
We have a real fence now.
Actually, I can probably delete this and then expand it a little more.
His habitat...
I'll put his actual habitat back here.
Oops.
Okay.
So his actual place to sleep is gonna go right here.
Where are you?
There you go.
Right in the corner there.
Hey, look at that.
Have a good restful sleep, T-Rex.
You have toys.
You got stuff to do.
You got food.
Let's give him a ball.
Look, he's going for a bath.
See?
Look.
Why can't you...
This is a dinosaur fence.
Specifically to hold dinosaurs.
How did you get out of here?
He found the weak point in the structure.
He's not gonna be able to go anywhere anyways.
Where are you going?
Are you going?
Hold on.
He's escaping the whole zoo.
Is he?
This biome is not suitable for the T-Rex.
Well, that's his own fault.
Get back in there where you belong.
You don't belong out here.
What are you mad at?
What's he angry with?
What's happening?
Who's he angry with?
Here, I'll give you a bath.
American Bee before is pregnant.
Okay.
Is this where you want to be?
I'll put a fence around you here.
No, he's going back.
I think he's realizing that this is not where I wanted to go at all.
He needs to go back to his habitat.
You're going the long way.
Where is he going?
He's going all the way around.
What's the correct biome?
Tropical.
Uh-oh, he's getting closer to civilization here.
He looks so tired though.
What's he going to do?
He smells the customers.
He's doing stealth.
He's sneaking up on everybody.
Nobody knows he's here.
This is the stealthiest T-Rex ever.
He just wants to go to the zoo.
Oh, look at that over there.
That's a cool gorilla.
What about the beavers?
He goes to the front, takes money out of the ATM.
Why is nobody upset about this?
He just turned into a customer.
The lady up there is still giving the educational course on the T-Rex.
If this T-Rex goes into a car and the car drives off, I'm going to shit my pants.
No, don't shit on somebody.
Okay, good.
He's just leaving the park.
Uh-oh, he's getting angry.
I can't find my car.
Did I park it in B1?
Should have taken a picture of it.
One dinosaur has roamed the earth.
No, no, he's going to the beaver enclosure.
The beavers are going to get out now.
He got an extra life.
He is the car.
Here goes the beaver.
Oh no, a beaver escaped.
The beaver is not going to hurt anybody, right?
If the T-Rex is less aggressive than a fucking beaver, I'm going to be fucking so pissed off.
Who's beatboxing?
Oh shit.
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
He actually woke up.
He woke up.
He's going to drink water.
He's going to drink water out of his phone.
He was just thirsty.
That's all he wanted.
I'll put more water in the food dish.
Look at how pissed off the beaver is.
The beaver is going to fight him.
That's a territorial beaver.
He's strutting his ass out.
American beaver has been put in a crate.
Why would you come in the exhibit here?
Where's the nearest beaver?
All right, just yeah.
Don't fuck with me.
I gotta get a photo of that.
Wait, did you just, did you just come over?
That's kind of scary.
I'm not going to lie.
Honey, I think it's getting closer.
Out of film.
We're just filming a movie over here.
Don't worry.
He really is just so fucked up.
Like what's his deal?
Another birth.
Let the beaver out.
You know what?
Fuck it.
It's time for a battle.
Who's going to win?
It's time for a real battle.
What if they start having sex?
Uh-oh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, don't fight the T-Rex.
Oh my god.
He's freaking out.
They're working together.
They should not be working together.
The T-Rex was just put in a crate.
All right, it's time to.
Oh, I need to.
I need to.
Where's my list of staff?
I want to get rid of this staff.
I need my staff list.
No, I don't want more of them.
Where is it?
How do I get there?
From here, right?
No.
Zoo stats, zoo status, photo album, zoo fame.
There we go.
Okay.
So we need some new staff.
I need to.
I want to fire literally everybody.
You're gone.
You know what I'm saying?
Let them fight.
Dude, is this King Kong versus Godzilla?
I thought that was the T-Rex.
It wasn't, apparently.
Where's the T-Rex?
Everybody wants to come in here
and drink out of the same water bowl.
All right, let's go.
What are they doing?
They're just like walking around in circles.
Tyrannosaurus 1 is really hungry.
He's going all the way up there.
Hold on.
Uh-oh.
Oh no.
No, he's just breaking through fences.
He's coming in to steal his food.
Where are they all going?
They're just eating the food.
They're just sharing the food.
This kid is so excited.
Yeah, I can't believe it.
It's just like Jurassic Park.
What are they eating over there?
There are more animals outside than people.
This lady's still giving me a presentation.
This is the line for the bathroom.
Oh God.
I'm up in my fort.
They can't get up here.
All right.
Well, that was fun.
I want to try one more thing.
Hold on.
No, don't save the current game.
Almost half a star.
I know, right?
Doing well.
You need to go back in here.
Let me fix this.
So what's the deal here?
He can't...
Electric fence.
Is this the only way I can contain a T-Rex?
What if he starts to smash through it?
Oh, come on.
Move out of the way.
I can't believe you can put dinosaurs in this game.
He's going to get a shock.
I forget everything we were just doing.
Something about a place for them to go up to see the T-Rex or something.
What's my favorite wild animal?
What is my favorite wild animal?
It was legal to own five of them.
Favorite wild animal.
Definitely a...
Probably a laptop.
Yeah, like a HP laptop.
What was your question?
What's my favorite...
What's my favorite animal?
Probably like a...
I don't know.
Armadillo.
Be cool.
I missed a spot?
No, I didn't.
Everything's fine.
Oh, I did miss a spot.
You're right.
Good catch there.
Okay.
He's contained and he's not very happy, but that's his own problem.
Exercise level.
So go interact with this thing.
What do you think I put it here for?
Okay, now I need to get in.
Now you can get in.
Food, water, dinosaur.
45 cents.
Hello, people.
What the fuck are they doing?
Why are they walking in circles up here?
Are they making a whirlpool on the way up?
All right, now let's get...
What was I gonna...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want whales.
That sounds like fun.
So I need a tank enclosure, right?
Of some sort.
What do I need for that?
I want to make a couple of whale sharks.
All right, biome and benthic.
Okay, I need water.
What?
Can I just put them in a lake?
I don't know.
This biome is not suitable for whale shark.
Well, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There.
Okay, tank.
There it is.
All right.
I need to...
What the hell am I thinking?
I can make a diving board.
All right, I need to get rid of this then.
So let's go back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I replace this?
Can I fill this up?
I can't fill this.
I don't know what the hell I've done here.
I created a huge problem for myself.
So I need a new biome.
Get rid of all this shit.
All right, biome.
What biome?
This is tank.
Tank, tank, tank, tank, tank.
So this is tank wall.
Raise tank wall.
No.
All right, let's go like this.
What the fuck are you doing?
I need to extend this shit out.
Hold on.
It's on like a cliff.
It's not going to work.
I need to flatten this out.
Flatten it.
That should work.
Get rid of the rocks.
Ah!
Oh!
What?
It's all right.
Okay, here we go.
What is going on?
Raw fucking rectangle.
It's because I was on the rectangle mode.
I need to be on free form.
Good luck.
How am I even going to fix this?
Okay, I can fix it like this.
No, I can't.
Jesus Christ.
All right, we're good.
All right, let's do it.
I'm sorry.
That was fucking loud.
So now I need to go back here.
Free form mode.
Tank wall.
Bingo.
More beaver pregnancies.
Perfect.
Why is this not suitable for whale shark?
What's wrong with it?
What's the problem?
Salt water.
How do I?
Does there a check a box for salt water?
Change the biome.
They can't survive in pools.
So you're telling me that benthic.
So I did have...
Problem solved.
I turned the water benthic.
That's a 3000 IQ play right there.
All right.
So what do you eat?
Let me get some help here.
Oh, we got a reef.
Food box with plankton.
We got a little toy or something.
A buoy.
Weird clam thing.
You don't need a habitat.
You just sleep on the ground.
A couple of cool rocks.
Nice fireworks.
Get some starfish in here.
All right, nice.
So this is ready to go.
Let's make some money.
I need this to keep going across.
See, look it.
I should be a video game designer.
Imagine this is a town.
All right, that's good.
In fact, go all the way up.
So we can look at the glass.
Why is it just a rock in the middle of the road?
Get out of here.
So here's the bathroom.
Now we need...
Oh, fuck.
I forgot.
Did I fire?
No, I didn't fire everybody.
What does American people want to do?
For...
Okay, for one second, I thought that was blood
all over that and pouring out of the front.
Say, what the hell happened?
So wait, you can't find a good mate?
Why not?
What's wrong?
You need a mate.
You're doing fine.
Here, I'll help you.
Name the beavers after chat.
There's like 40 of them.
No, I can't do like...
I can't do like Beaver Rick.
Because that's...
I'm not doing Beaver Rick.
Uh, Bevo.
Bevo, Stevo, Ornelius.
Uh, okay.
Uh, so long.
Uh, no.
No, no, no, not not schlaw.
No.
Uh, uh...
All right, there are your names.
They're done.
All right, what happened since I was gone?
I need to make...
I need to make money over here.
Come on.
You need a friend.
Okay.
So I need a...
This is a...
Okay, so we're gonna do...
We're gonna do...
We need left and right here.
So this is...
I need...
Okay.
Yin and Yang, left and right.
Up and down.
Should just name them Yin and Yang.
All right, so now the baby needs to be called middle.
Good.
More American beavers.
Now I want to add...
Let me see what it looks like from afar.
Pretty cool.
Where's T-Rex?
T-Rex happy?
Actually, yeah.
The T-Rex is actually having a good time.
I mean, at this point, I think it, like, seriously.
This zoo needs some dessert carts.
I'm exhausted.
I need a place to rest.
Maybe if you didn't walk in circles the whole entire time.
What do I do about this?
Because they're just clogging the whole thing.
Just get out of the way.
Just get up there.
Why is he sprinting over here so fast?
What's his problem?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with him?
That's what...
That's what this was for, huh?
I gotta get over there right now
because I gotta rake this shit as fast as I can.
All right, well, whatever.
I need to use the bathroom.
I can't wait to see some animals.
Now he's running in circles.
Thank God.
I shouldn't have to do this.
It's time to go home.
Well, they...
Was that guy's name Sandler?
I thought it was Adam Sandler.
Well, when this first came up,
I thought they said I can smell the restroom from here.
Oh, that's disgusting.
That's absolutely revolting.
They're not gonna ever leave here.
I don't really have a solution.
Hold on, are you gonna get like a big roar or no?
No one's even giving me any money.
Need more water for right and left over here.
I will add it.
I'm going for it, I'm going for it.
It's kind of in a weird spot, isn't it?
It's not the right biome.
Will it mix the water together?
There we go.
Look at that.
I don't even have to do anything.
Artifact is looking great.
Artifact?
I'm not gonna play artifact.
No, today was just the chill day
where I wanted just to play something.
Hang out.
Why would I ever play artifact?
I really want to get rid of this.
There we go.
All right.
Now you get enough room, right?
Need more places to rest.
Well, shit.
There's plenty of...
No one's even using them.
Am I really getting complaints
about there's nowhere for me to rest
and all the benches are empty?
Empty.
All of them.
Oh, really?
Was it you that complained?
That dude myself.
Put it in the bag.
I just had the bag out.
I'm tired.
Fine.
Do you want...
Am I gonna put out like beds and shit here?
All right.
Where is giant bed?
Ooh, no, that's fine.
I can stay there.
Park information.
That's kind of important.
What about like just sitting down here?
Can I lose this game?
Not when I have infinite money.
More places to rest.
What the fuck?
I need a place to rest.
Is this the only thing they can see?
Fat is going to give birth.
All right.
That's good.
There ain't nobody listening.
Those people are still complaining about the bench.
That's a great move.
How do I up your salary?
And so what else can we do for him?
Okay.
Now.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Oh, they're just having babies.
It was inevitable.
Oh my god.
It's too many beavers.
They're really...
And it's ruining my whole aesthetic here.
Oh, Steve-O needs more space.
I better take it seriously now.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
It's not the Chad beaver.
Don't go after the Chad beaver.
Oh, no.
He's gonna get him.
How's the space looking now?
We still out of space?
From race and has died.
Of old age.
We're good?
He's not even eating them.
He's just killing them for no reason.
Well, don't worry.
I have a solution for that.
Remember we talked about recycling?
The natural order of the world?
All right.
After he kills like three more people, you'll see.
I think that won't...
I think that beaver was about to give birth.
How do they still need more space?
Hold on.
How do I get to my photo album?
No, I want to get to the photo album.
How do I delete pictures?
Look, these are so awful.
Delete them all.
I have like four pictures of the trash.
I want to keep those ones.
I like that one.
I like this string.
Picture the ground.
All right.
Let's see if I can get it.
I want to get a mid-jump tiger shot.
Into the water.
Jesus.
No, no.
Don't...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Who's he going for?
Right here.
Oh, he's gonna kill them all.
I gotta get him out of here.
He's gonna kill them all, actually.
He really might.
Okay, good work.
Remember we talked about recycling?
Not wasted.
See, somebody adopted a cave line.
Don't ask me who the hell would do that.
See, he's got food.
He's got food for probably the next five or six days.
See, he's giving it a sniff.
He's not like it.
No, he likes it.
See, he's happy.
This is the biggest traction here.
$4,400 of donations.
That's pretty great considering...
I don't think the beaver exhibit has even come close.
Not even half.
The guests are crying.
Well, maybe if the guests actually listened to their own advice
and sat on the benches that are here,
ready for them to be sat on.
They're available.
I've had just about enough of...
What are they saying?
I'm exhausted.
You exhausted now?
Holy shit, they're running off to the end.
They...
It worked.
Fixed the ramp?
What's wrong with the ramp?
They were just sprinting off the edges.
Okay, I fixed it.
Sacrifices must be made.
Sorry, guys.
I mean, that's up there, isn't it?
Maybe the 70-foot plateau wasn't necessary.
No, it really wasn't, but this was already here,
and I thought it might have been cool.
Pave over the people.
Can they get up now?
I don't know.
I can't tell.
That looks pretty flush.
We'll see.
No, they're bumping into the...
This is not going to work.
They're bumping into the lip here when they come up.
That's all right.
No, it's not going to work.
All right, fixed it.
Does it work?
I think so.
Now it's steeper than before,
but now at least they can cross it.
The beavers are dying.
Look, I just don't think...
I don't think they're smart enough to understand.
Well, this is actually a much better view of the exhibit.
Maybe this is a good idea.
You can see over the fence.
No, people are going up and down.
Rescue these people.
Just make it go into the enclosure,
but just drop off into the enclosure.
For the path around the whale sharks.
Look at how far that is, though.
I have to put that up here and then go around.
No one is...
No one's even coming over here.
Is this some educational thing?
Hold on.
Yeah, I need a donation machine as well.
Okay.
Then nobody cares that this exists.
Hold on.
I'll try it.
All right, fine.
This game's fun, though.
There's a fun game.
Connect the path to the ladder.
Is that really what was preventing people from going over here?
For a second, I thought this person's name was Quindelius.
Uh, a little angry.
He's waving to the sharks.
Is this guy just part of the exhibit now?
He's not even scared.
I'm gonna get a donation here.
Maybe.
He just pet the shark.
This is the crazy guy that comes to the aquarium.
He dives in.
He actually touched the shark.
He did it.
I can't see any animals from here.
He's just swimming.
This guy's a pretty damn good swimmer.
All right, well, let me come in there.
Can I dive?
It's kind of relaxing.
I'm kind of just relaxed.
Everybody else is feeling, like, relaxed right now.
He's like, whatever.
He did a T-pose.
He did not do a T-pose.
Well, it's about to get far less relaxing.
I'm sorry.
Are we gonna get a Jaws scenario?
It's possible.
Oh, my God.
He's okay.
He's not injured.
He's actually not injured.
He just doesn't even care.
He just puts his hands up.
Ah, whatever.
It's still kind of fun in here.
It picked him up.
In his mouth.
That's it.
And bit down really, really, really fucking hard.
He's yawning.
All right.
Good.
This is what Bill Crazy would do voluntarily.
Yeah.
Where is the whale shark?
Or any shark, for that matter.
Okay.
Let's see how you handle that now.
That is fucking terrifying.
My God.
Look below.
Oh, my goodness.
I wouldn't do this for a hundred million dollars.
The notifications are playing the Jaws theme.
What's this?
That's fucking so funny.
Um, I don't know what else.
I don't know how to do.
Where'd he go?
Did he get out?
Oh, fuck.
This might actually be bad for the computer.
No, no.
It should be bad for my computer.
How do I take care of this?
I don't know.
Coffins.
I'm trying to hold on.
Is this what I'm doing in the game right now?
It is, isn't it?
No, this is going to take so long.
I was about to write out each shit in their coffins.
No, just like, just sell them.
I can't sell.
That's not, that's it.
No, put it back in.
He's fine.
Uh, put him in the lake with the beavers.
I'm not going to show you that.
What have I done?
Well, did I save it somewhere before that fucking weirdo got in the water?
I got jumped through the water.
Like, what are you doing?
Fucking beaver scenario again.
All right, that's good.
Now the bridge is messed up again.
Well, then it's time.
Hold on.
Is there any, what are the animals I want to play around with?
Is there anything else I want to do?
I could just put penguins in until the game crashes.
Like until my computer physically like turns off.
All right.
Let's, uh, the penguins or, it needs to be small enough where I can put a lot of them.
And then put a t-rex right in the middle.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, let's get, let's get a new, let's get a clean slate here.
On a flat ground, a small in loves this music.
It's so great.
Sour pleased.
I've seen a lot of sour pleases.
All right.
Let's see if we can turn my computer into dust.
Let's flatten everything out.
I need a bigger brush size than that.
As big as it can be.
It's going to be one exhibit only.
We're not even going to get this far here.
Not that looks good.
So where is the penguin?
All right.
Rockhopper penguin.
How big are you?
Kind of small.
Uh, emperor penguin.
Start in the corner.
This is going to be bad.
This is going to stop in about five seconds.
I'm just creating the opening scene from Happy Feet.
How was my day?
It was good.
Just kind of relaxing.
Just having a chill day today.
They're not all dudes.
Look, see?
You want me to go faster than that?
Well, I can do it.
I can do it.
Hold on.
Nobody move.
Don't move.
No, they're moving.
This hurts already.
Eat salt.
No, not eat salt.
Let's get down to ground level.
This is fucking dumb.
I don't know why I thought this was going to be interesting.
And presents for everybody.
I was speaking of presents.
You, uh, Mr. Peanut.
On Christmas Eve, it's going to be a stream.
I don't think you're going to want to miss.
Christmas Eve is the day that the absolutely wonderful Christmas special will be.
Elf bowling.
What, what, what?
What did I do this for again?
Oh yeah, put like five tigers in.
Florida Panther in the middle of the tundra.
Florida in winter.
We'll lose enough.
What are those sounds?
That's a lion sound.
That doesn't sound like a lion.
No, that's the penguin.
Why are they going to the presents?
They don't care about the penguins.
They just want to open the presents.
Oh, he's inside of one.
It's a birthday party.
This did not go as planned.
Oh, well.
Oh my God.
My amazable play.
Well, I'm going to play that epic battle simulator.
Like that's what I'm trying to do right now.
Okay.
Let's see how angry that makes everybody.
What do they get to meet?
Just playing sport.
Have I really been in this game for four hours?
Holy shit.
I just groomed a fish.
All right.
I think we've peaked here.
It's time to open the zoo.
That's right.
Come on in, everybody.
What the fuck are they doing?
What are you doing over here?
Come on in.
It already is open.
People looking over the railing and going, no thanks.
Club Penguin.
Wait, whoa, he just dove in.
This guy just dove in here.
What is going on in the center?
All right.
Water bowl.
They're all stuck on each other.
They can't move.
Put a cage around them.
No, that's cruel.
This one's dead.
No, no one's eating anybody.
They're just sleeping and playing with presents
and having birthday parties and not doing anything else.
All right.
That's it for that.
Sell the fish.
Zoo Tycoon 1 has more murder.
More murder.
What time does the Red Dead beta start tomorrow?
Anybody know?
That's the end of the stream voice coming up here.
It's just out.
The end of the stream voice.
Let me see.
Boomer Streamer is tired at 8 PM.
No, no, that's not what it is.
What can I do for another hour or so?
Because I can't play Red Dead.
I want to do that tomorrow.
So Red Dead will be tomorrow.
And then Friday.
Oh, yeah, I think I might do Dreamcast on Friday.
I might pull it out.
Red Dead.
Yeah, you know, I could play single player in Red Dead
to prepare for tomorrow.
But I don't know.
Hey, let me do this.
Let me grab.
I'm going to let me.
It's been like four and a half hours almost.
Let me grab a water and I'll be right back.
And we can figure out what the hell we're going to do.
See you in a second.