Welcome to Car Shield Field where we have German Baseball Association action for you
tonight. A big time matchup between the California Circus and the Maryland
Magicians. Maryland comes in at 27 and 22 the circus 11 games over 500. I'm joined
by former Phoenix caveman great Gary Grunt. I am Storm Williamson and Gary we
should have a big time great matchup on the field tonight. Yeah very good ball
clubs on the field here this evening Storm. We throw out the record books when
these two teams get together. They're just two vastly different ball clubs.
They win different ways. The circus is more of a clown show. They kind of try to
trick you into some different pitches whereas on the other side the Magicians
they win with their clever illusions. I'd like to see what the big tall
right-hander has on the mound here tonight. What kind of tricks they have up
their sleeve and of course the power cards will play a big part of tonight's
game. Get a look at Joy Hansome right now the manager of the Maryland Magicians.
He's guided his club to a five game over 500 mark so far this year and a coastal
clash these teams coming from across the country to meet tonight. There you get a
look at Fred Big Top the leader of the California Circus and don't let that
face fool you he has been plenty happy this year. We talked about that record of
30 and 19 for them on the year and we go from Big Top to Big Boy on the mound. Big
Boy Buckle gets the call for the circus. He has been outstanding all year long to
the tune of a 9 and 6 record 2.81 ERA. What are the Magicians going to have to
do to try to put a dent in what this man has done this year? Well for the the man
on the mound here tonight he's obviously a very dominant right-hander. Look for
the off-speed pitches to be really key to his arsenal tonight and on the other
side for the Magicians they just need to make contact. There's a lot of movement from
from Big Boy and we'll see what kind of contact they can make here tonight. So
Donald Strange will come to the plate the first batter for the Maryland
Magicians and the first pitch of our game just a little bit high and already
Chief Albertson having a word with our pitcher we've only gotten one pitch
through the game. Yeah he's gonna have to take care of that control problem he
needs to get that lower and over the plate or else the Magicians players
are gonna be in for a long night dipping and diving and trying to get out of the
way that some of these pitches. Crew chief Albertson you get a look at him
right there chief of the one-man crew tonight so doing a great job and maybe
not so great of a job on that call. Yeah questionable call there but Albertson
he's the crew chief tonight so what he says go what he says go and that ball
was maybe a little inside the plate. 258 hitting Donald Strange took a big rip at
that one couldn't quite connect and the count to one ball and two strikes now.
A big cut there from Strange playing for the Magicians third baseman tonight
playing the hot corner. Xavier McMagic awaits on deck here comes the next pitch
from Big Boy. Big Rock a couple of them make it three is the third a charm a hot
shot towards the hole at second base what a play and they rob him of a hit
outstanding from Paul Laffington no laughing matter on the middle infield.
Absolutely no laughing matter got over to his left got to the ball and then
great release from glove to arm to make that throw first out of the inning great
play going to his left. And Donald Strange had to be thinking look I've done my job
we've got a base hit to lead off this game uh-uh the circus who had some
trouble getting to this game tonight having no trouble getting settled in.
Yeah they had a lot of trouble apparently they put the wrong gas in the
car it was uh someone had put petroleum gas and they're looking for laughing gas.
Hold on hold on crew chief Albertson is down. Oh no we've seen some issues with
Albertson. And this is you know again we need to mention here a crew chief of one
so he's saying he's all right but but we'll have to see how he goes about this
moving on that could be a lingering injury. Yeah Albertson the only umpire
here tonight has to cover home plate first base second base third base the
outfield as well. Laffington charging in and he bubbles flips to the back
Albertson calls him out. Great play again there from the second baseman for the
circus. Seen some errant wands flying here and there and Albertson yells safe
into the dugout with the out signal and now all of a sudden coming out of the
dugout Joy Handsome has got some words. Yeah might have to go into the magic
spellbook here to figure out how to break this defense and get past the
adversity that the umpire and crew chief has created here so far. Joy back to the
bench and now we get our first look at Zeke Flash a couple of bounces in and
Albertson thinking about it but he will rule it ball one. That's what happens
here in the JBA sometimes a little cricket can bounce out you just never
know what's gonna happen. I want to thank all of you for tuning into the
Germa Baseball Association ripping a hot shot just foul past the third base bag
count to one and one now on Zeke Flash the shortstop for the Maryland
Magicians is hitting 246 on the year with a slugging percentage of 365.
Flash very capable of putting the ball over the seats we'll see what
kind of pitch he gets here. It's an interesting one from Buckle and kicking
his heel out it. Couldn't get a piece of it trying to get a board first base
with the hit by pitch but he can't come up with it. We don't expect
runs to be at a premium but if you can get on base any way you can stick a leg
foot anything wand anything you can get a baseball on. And we get a pop fly into
shallow right field moving towards right center the play is made by Lenny Munson
so one two three big boy Buckle great work in the top half of the first he
gets them in order the California Circus will come to the plate when we return
you're watching Germa Baseball Association. Welcome back to Car Shield
Field this is the Germa Baseball Association Maryland Magicians and the
California Circus through one half inning of play a one two three top half
of the first for big boy Buckle on the mound and now he gives way to Doug Dubb
the right-handed pitcher for the Maryland Magicians stands at five foot
nine a hundred sixty pounds we talked about that great record for big boy how
about an eight and three record for Doug Dubb. Yeah Doug Dubb known for pulling it
out the Dubb out of the hat can really fired in there with a fastball has a
good change up mixes in his pitches very nicely can also throw a four seam sinker
that sinks away from left-handed hitters and as well as cut into righties so
we'll see how Mr. Dubb handles his top half of the inning we saw relatively easy
inning for big boy in the first the top half of the first inning here we'll see
how Doug Dubb does here as you see his stats on the board 18 games pitched eight
and three record look at that strikeout to walk ratio as we mentioned the stuff
and the kind of creativity he has on the mound he can really smoke it by the
batter. And so now Hunter Sweets the leadoff man for the California Circus
he'll be followed by Percy Polkadot and then David Honk batting in the three
spot for the California Circus and Hunter Sweet has brought quite a bit of
power to the table on the season while only hitting 216 a 341 slug due to five
home runs and you saw crew chief Albertson taking a good look at that bat
prior maybe just to make sure hey is this thing corked what's going on here
yeah I can't have any illegal play here can't have a cork bat that wouldn't be
good it wouldn't level the playing field here tonight as Dubb fires it in there
as Doug has really been one of the top magicians in the JBA in terms of
pitching he really focuses on his craft. The Hocus Pocus on point two and one
with that swing and a miss get a look there at crew chief Albertson as Dubb
peers in for the next. Changing the wind up here trying to keep the hitter off
balance and does. Oh my goodness you talked about that heat hello. You can see
the two different styles of the pitchers we saw big boy a little bit
more crafty. Dubb here in the bottom half of the first just throwing gas. The Cape
Crusader hits him with the breaking ball and Sweets is down. Oh he's thinking
about it there goes the bat Dubb kicks it right back towards him and hitting in
between them Roy Flushman says hey fellas let's simmer it now we're only in
the first. Yeah don't let anything let cooler heads prevail here as Albertson
gives him the bases we'll get a replay on this you see the curveball just got
away from him it's him it's the batter in the left shoulder goes down. A great
time to point out that safety and security really important aspects in
every part of your life we have to deal with them on a daily basis and it can be
hard to find the right solutions wouldn't it be great if there was one
solution that gets rid of those problems most internet users aren't sure of the
amount of surveillance limitation and data mining done with their personal
information but surf shark can solve all of those problems for you that's surf
shark go ahead and check them out and make sure that your data is safe.
Polkadot taking a strike to begin this at bat runner over at first base is
Hunter Sweets after being hit by the pitch they check on him and he slides
back in safe. A great curveball thrown by Dubb there just went 12 to 6 no chance
for the hitter. So we saw the magicians go down in order first base runner of
this game Sweets over at first base a bit outside but did appear that her
chief Albertson called that a strike it's to Owen too and Polkadot wants to
have an extra look back at Albertson as he yells towards the dugout of the
magicians. You got to keep the runner on as well so a lot dealing dealing with a lot
here this one's hit high and deep left side but that'll get foul. That ball was blasted.
Polkadot yes. Percy not playing get a look at that big red nose of his and he
was going to really really be happy if he could send that one over the fence a
good start here though for the California circus. Dubb turns and throws
the first base Sweets back in time again really keeping tabs on him. Yeah
absolutely don't want to give up a stalled base here still early on in the
game so runs out of premium and can't give up can't give them away here. Dubb's
pitch a breaking ball that is fouled away to the right side that will reach
the seats. Notice the equipment change from the Klanza I'm used to seeing them
and games pass for they've got you know bigger shoes on comically large shoes
they got normal shoes on here tonight so it could be another tactic implemented
by the managing staff to get some more wins for this California circus. And what
a job out of the circus dugout there you see great job running out those balls
to crew chief Albertson doing a great job himself behind home plate despite a
couple of controversial calls and that might be another one called out on
strikes. Polkadot the first out of the bottom of the first inning. Well Albertson's
been consistent with the zone so far he's calling him high he's calling him low
calling him outside and inside so consistency is the name of the game when
near the umpire and look at this one catches the outside corner. Great frame
job by the catcher. That's a great point that you make there I want to go back to
that though Gary a former great in this game how much does that consistency from
the umpire matter you know you know that any given pitch is going to be a strike
whether it is or not and that helps you out a lot as a batter. Yeah it keeps you
on your toes it really focuses you in on the the spin rate of the ball and you
really want to try to make contact as we have a stolen base attempt here. Hunter Sweets is out!
Albertson he took some time with it I thought he might pull out the safe call
but he does rule him out a stolen base caught stealing I should say on the
steal attempt from Hunter Sweets. Yeah not a great jump and a fantastic throw
down right into the glove of the second baseman there and the tag is applied and
the second out of the bottom of the half of the first inning here great throw.
Just like that two down Albertson having to keep both of these dugouts in check
early on a lot of jawing going on from both sides. Well the stakes are high here
Storm these teams need a victory. They need a victory and you know we're
talking about two of the best teams in this league as well we're getting closer
to postseason play and you want to be in the correct form when you go into
postseason play and we'll see if these teams can get back to the style of
baseball that we're used to seeing. Yeah jockeying for playoff positioning as
this one's in there for they call that a strike. Three one is the count. Yeah
games playing elsewhere the drunkards are playing the Mimes this evening as
well as the K-Band my former squad and the old ladies matched it up we'll have
crunch time after this to give us the full breakdown on all the highlights of
the JPA games that are happening this afternoon. And it goes into foul
territory. Should mention here you know we've got our standard defensive
alignment for the most part and a man on stilts out in left center for the
magicians you know that is your weapon one of those tricks that you can pull
out when you need it time and time again and against these right-handed batters
power hitters trying to put a gapper out there and score a run not today. Yeah
it's the JBA's version of almost of a defensive shift where they hit the man
and stilts out in left field again he can get those wall scrapers anything
going over that wall on that left side he can get to and track down. And what is
this? They called it a strike in David Honk. He got the umpire got the
count wrong. And you know that's one of those things oh strike call and that
will set down David Honk and do it for this first inning so we did get our
first baserunner of the game but a pair of strikeouts in the caught stealing
they go in order once again do the California Circus back with more JBA
action after this. And we are back at car shield field this is the germa baseball
association I am Storm Williamson joined by former caveman great Gary grunt soon
to be Hall of Famer next year they're gonna have that induction for you we got
some noise coming from the circus dugout Elbertson trying to check this
bat right now from Roy Flushman we saw Flushman get in between what could have
been an altercation in that first inning. Look at that defensive lineup for the circus. Buckle
towing the rubber helium on first laughing kid on second. Oh the circus with
some noise from the dugout but it's booted it's short unable to make the
play polka dot. Polka dot very upset with the shortstop unable to make that play
just a slow roller to that left side you could argue the play should have been
made as look right toward the shortstop for the circus. And you know we have we
have security just beyond the first base bag he was patting down Roy Flushman
right there just to make sure that nothing nefarious was going on have
anything illegal on the field there's no chewing gum no no sunflower seeds they
got to make sure we keep this field clean. You never know where these
magicians are going to hide something that might give them the advantage look
at him drop the bunt pull it back and put it in the left field that is a
beautiful piece of hitting by Craig mystery keeping it a mystery what he's
gonna do with the play. Yeah Craig doing a very good job showed bunt pulled it
back and roped a single now Elbertson looking at him now he's coming over to
talk to him. Is Elbertson saying something illegal? Not on the field dugout dugout
you can't I don't know how it works. Oh no smoking on the field I guess uh he was
trying to have a smoke at a pancake which that's not allowed here so great
job by Elbertson to keep it clean here. Yeah they're gonna have to have a talk with the
manager for the magicians. Yeah he is not gonna have this. That's a warning.
Joy Hansen you know tobacco products allowed on the field in this game. He's
saying look just a little bit can't can't we just have just a couple of
puffs when we get to first base you know just a little like a first base break I
mean look at this we got some pipe action going on in the other dugout
what's the big deal? There's no puffing the magic dragon or any dragon here in
the car shard field car shield field so there'll be no puffing. Slow one comes in
it's fouled back off the bat Ronnie Smith. Now we're gonna have a mascot
battle behind home plate between the clowns excuse me for the circus and the
magicians as you can see the looks like Dumbledore and Dumbledore has stolen a
fan sign and used it as a weapon here that is a lot of action on the field and
in the stands here security has to come over maybe separate the two mascots
behind home plate so the pitcher doesn't get distracted. You see big boy going with
that split grip to start how hard is it for a guy like him to to keep things
under control when there's so much going on with the call strike. A lot of distraction but we
see it all the time in the JPA so these guys are used to it they could stay
locked in stay laser focused on the task at hand and big boys got a chance to
for a double play here. Albertson is rightfully calling out look we have a
team called the circus yet it's the magicians that have been the circus in
the dugout. Yeah absolutely a clown show right now for the magicians creating a
lot of havoc talking a lot of smack directing a lot of their hostilities
towards Albertson. You know they are the circus but this is a team that's won 30
games this year and you think about a circus maybe being disorganized this
might be one of the more organized circuses you'll find out there is big
off balance as he comes home with it and that go it's all the way to the
backstop so runners advanced to second and third base in our count goes to two
and two so that was a call strike. So big chance for the magicians now to get on
the board two runners in scoring position let's see if they can get this
ball in play no out still here at the top of the second. You know one-man crew
just how clean this home plate is for a one-man crew truly incredible big
boy buckle still waiting for this plate to get wiped off and you know we talked
about some of the distractions now the stoppage in play he looks like he's in
rhythm out there. And he's starting to find his tempo find that rhythm see if he
floats one across play again the two different styles of pitchers is on
display here tonight as you know a big boy just kind of lost it over the plate
relies on his on his off-speed stuff doesn't throw anything overpowering has
to hit his spots and he walks the batter here yeah big boys not happy with
that he thought that one bounced up into the zone and Albertson is trying to show
him that big boys still not buying it and now our bases are loaded over there
at first base trying to make sure that the magicians have everything together
we have a power card we have a power card being played Albertson there it is
what card is being played here let's see it's a common card all opposing
outfielders are removed for the next at-bat what a card to play that is the
kind of managing we love to see here in the JBA and you know this is just a
veteran move by joy handsome you see why this team has been so successful all
year long bases loaded jam nobody out how are how are we gonna do this poof
that's how we're gonna do it we're gonna put that poof card out there and see if
they can't even capitalize even more here for the magicians smart time to
play this card poof the outfielders are gone and a big chance for the magicians
to get some runs on the board and interesting the Fred Big Top was you
know coming out as if to show that he was not happy with that call that is
well within league rules there's supposed to be a power court has to be
played before the batter steps into the batter's box look at first pitch
swinging there's nobody out there all the way to the surf shark sign and they
are not going to be able to do anything about it look at the big man chug here
goes Donovan Slate into third base with the triple all the bases are still
loaded and the bases are still loaded three runs come around to score and two
more runners out on the path they just kept going around the clowns are trying
to settle the show right now and playing that these up now we got a look
out run down run down here in the infield it's a mystery as to what's
going on Craig mystery being chased he's single to get a board he later came
around to score Albertson trying to gain control of this mess right now and he
gets those players off the field so what a triple there from the magicians here's
another look at it lined in the left field smoked nobody out there again the
card was played no outfielders for that that the magicians capitalize just like
that our first runs of the ballgame they belong to the Maryland magicians it's a
three nothing score in the top of the second inning still nobody out here for
the magicians and the circus now have their outfielders back see how big boy
buckle respond here trying to put a little mustard on the ball like that
little slap swag with that last delivery excuse me is we're gonna fly
ball into right it's caught tagging and holding at third base that gun of an
arm from Lenny Munson keeps him put Munson doesn't mess around as a great
right arm really flight that ball into home plate so good job keep the runner
at third base and we still stay at three nothing with one out here at the top of
the second I don't know about you Gary but I do not test people named Lenny
Munson is one of those don't test them and don't trust them that one comes in
just a touch low from big boy buckle he's been varying his not only his
delivery but the speed of his pitches as well yeah has featured a couple of
different wind-ups here this one's smoked back up the middle that'll score
another run for the magicians look at that off the bat of Barry bedazzle he's
got the magicians up for nil gotta wonder if the circus is thinking about
getting someone warmed up at the bullpen now as buckle has struggled here in the
first inning and two-thirds Wow what a promising start for big boy buckle and
as the nine hitter Mike salmon comes to the plate he is motioning for his
outfielders hey come in this guy can't hit the ball anywhere yet they're
staying out there salmon likes to hit the ball upriver you know I would think
that a downstream approach might be the path of least resistance but this is a
guy that has seeked out adversity his entire career yeah really puts a lot of
power behind the ball can really whip that bat through the strike zone and
plant the baseball wherever he wants puts it on the ground to the right side
laughing tin to the bag at second a perfect one hop throw gets the lead
runner turn to first base not in time two down now so feelers choice there
couldn't get the double play for the ball over there in the California
circus another replay here is just getting over the top of that and again
crew chief Elbertson having to take charge and really make sure that these
teams understand who's in charge out here yeah let's keep both managers in
check is having another conversation with the circus right now that facial
expression for Fred big top a little bit more fitting now that we moved into the
second inning down for nil take the slow walk back to the top of the dugout and
what's this what's this Elbertson is stopping play there's a drone on the
field oh no Albertson doesn't like likes to keep it again within the rules of
play and right now we just have a drone hovering over come on field and
Albertson is I think he's afraid that this could affect play maybe the ball
could potentially hit the the drone and affect where it lands and as they're
trying to get this drone out of here these are some of the things you have to
appreciate about in Albertson called game there is some chaos in this league
from time to time Albertson keeps things under wraps and now we get big top with
a happy Gilmore style Oh Ichiro's it off the belt and it's caught then dropped
in right what's the call what is Albertson saying there's some confusion
on the base pass they're ruling him out three hours three hours he called them
out so wow the cricket style delivery from buckle gets the out and the inning
is over on the damage has been believable stuff this is why you tune in
to the germa baseball association don't go anywhere we've got more next the
magicians have jumped out to a four-nothing lead as we are through one
and a half innings of baseball out here at car shield field in the germa
baseball association fans we want to remind you about our favorite adult
friendly platform fans Lee expand your social network gain followers and earn
additional income by connecting one-on-one with your subscribers in
unique and intimate ways post safe for work picks by day and spice it up by
night or both with tons of optimal features like sub tiers paid messaging
and more plus sign up now for twitch or Twitter and fans Lee will automatically
recommend creators you already follow on other platforms so what are you waiting
for join fans Lee today first pitch fouled off by Sean Giggles so he's down
Giggles takes a ball so Doug Dove back to work for the magicians and what looked
like you know that leadoff baserunner for California in the bottom of the
first inning that they might be the first to crack the scoreboard wouldn't
really expect this four-nothing score as Albertson might get done with this call
sometime tonight it was a big-time strike so he had to emphasize the call
man it was a great pitch on the outside corner another one of the reasons why
you tune in to Albertson games maybe just a little bit more than others
throughout this league on the ground back up the middle Giggles gets it past
the glove of the diving shortstop in the centerfield a leadoff base it nice job
by Giggles to get a take with the pitcher gave him just drove it right back
up the middle you can see great swing here got enough power behind that pass
the diving shortstop and into the centerfield no wand is gonna get that
ball Zeke flash gave it a look but even he not fast enough now Manny up Chuck
and he's getting the crowd pumped they love it up Chuck trying to create an
uppercut type swing here they circus needs to get back into this game
uppercut strike call from Albertson oh and one ten bombs on the year for up
Chuck he looks for another runner on first base is Sean Giggles and he puts a
charge into this one into deep centerfield turned around on it but the
play made out there good job by Xavier McMagic yeah great footwork out there by
McMagic Sean why he's a center fielder great form was turned around a little
bit but that ball was driven into that deep left center and Giggles will remain
his first basal still one runner on as a good catch there from McMagic the
center fielder for the magicians and not sure if we're dealing with an injury for
Doug Dove right now but he's been shoving now they're all at the mound for a meeting
oh something has come out here this is a little magic potion maybe a little elixir
oh for the team the feel-good juice as if Doug Dove wasn't in enough of a groove
already and now look at this the circus getting involved here on the mound yeah
the jesters want to get in on that a magic elixir see a pie out there as well
oh Albertson trying to get the pie off the field I've got a feeling somebody is
going to get served not with a paper but a pie sooner than later here sir as long
as it's got a little whipped cream on there maybe it's a banana split pie and
cream pie key lime pie either way we'll serve it up slices here tonight
car shield stadium so up Chuck retired for the first out in the inning and here
comes Harry helium helium having some words with Albertson wants to make sure
the zones right dove after the magic elixir drops in a strike over the inside
corner the clown mascot really trying to encourage the circus to get some runs
get some hits and get back to this game trailing for nothing by the second dove
looking energized his pitch just a touch tall he went with the heater that time
the next to Harry off the end of his bat he'll poke it foul up the right side
Harry helium hitting 254 on the season that on base percentage all the way up
at 355 though that gets plenty of air underneath his batted balls has a high
pitched voice as well as he tries to combine all that in to a nice power
stroke there's nothing like the hairy helium high when he sends one long we'll
see if you can put a charge into one here with his next one to count and now
all of a sudden some consternation behind home plate I believe hunter
sweets is what are they I think you just want to know what count was make sure you
had it right okay so Harry helium to decide what pitch you wanted to put down
for dub the throw and now the pitch popped up back behind home plate out of
play off the bat of helium one ball two strikes to helium going with the
interesting makeup can't really get some makeup around that beard so going with
the quarter face makeup the dark eyes it's a beard that would make a former
caveman proud you know what I was born but was born came out of the mama's
womb with a with a with a beard and that's most cavemen doing and you were
telling me before the game little known fact about Phoenix cavemen players there
is a minimum back hair requirement in order to even even get a call to the
trial yes you have to have at least a good three inch thick fur on the back
especially across the shoulder blades from left to right that will really get
you into the league of cavemen but if you got those patches down on the left
right near the backside of the ribs too we'll take you as well not too picky and
helium takes it outside so two and two the count now to Harry helium and right
now Doug Dove just having his way with this circus lineup something we're not
used to seeing from California no not at all looking for laughing gas matter this
ball is drilled into center field but should be easy work for the magic the
hat off and everything a little flair without number two I got good wood to it
unfortunately gets got a little too underneath that ball and a great play by
big magic to get to that one and stay scoreless here is the circus in danger
of leaving a runner on base here they need runs there is no doubt this
Maryland team knows how to put on a show as it brings in Larry Munson Munson
sends a third fly ball into centerfield hat off again Mick magic has done it
all three of the outs in this inning awfully impressive we'll head to break
when we come back we'll have the third inning from car shield field welcome back
to car shield field this is the germa baseball association I am storm
Williamson joined by Gary grunt a 4-0 lead for the magicians and it's been
some good baseball this far very good baseball and I was able to get downed
into the locker room I asked if I can interview some of the players and they
said be with you in a minute so Richard Looney out there unicycling in center
field actually we've got three outfielders unicycling currently first
ball hit hard on the ground by Mick magic who recorded all three outs in the
last half inning he's retired by a strong throw from polka dot to open up
the third you can see what he was trying to do they're trying to get it to the
outfield where the outfielders are in on unicycle so he was a high chopping swing
just got over that ball and hit it to the shorts that great play that first
out worth noting that our only runs or first runs of this game I should say
came from a poof card and now we've got our second card of the game being played
this time by the circus who the understudy card looks to be being played
here from the circus we're gonna need we're gonna need the magicians mascot
you're on this one is opposing teams mascot much must pitch for this
happening this is a rare card and the California circus was able to pull this
power card and pregame and now we'll see Dumbledore look at this guy ill pitch
for at least this batter is at the entire inning look out knuckleball
pitcher heading to the mound your you have to be Dumbledore can
unspin it with the best of them wonderful bring his wand out or he'll
just use his hand some interesting moves there is he's gonna have to give way to
big boy buckle and you know before that poof card big boy buckle has really done
everything in his power to keep his California circus in this game yeah he's
changed up his delivery style he's gone quicker he's gone faster he tried to
cricket style delivery he's tried dealing it from the left side of the
mound right side of the mound he's really been trying to switch it up and
keep these magician batters from getting comfortable inside that box and he's
calling a shot shot call there from number 31 I think so and he's gonna lay
down the bunt look at this Zeke flash hot dog beating it out the fake call your
shot he went Babe Ruth with it and he pulls down the bunt single what a play
the clowns are definitely caught off guard there magicians at it again take
a look on the fans Lee instant replay that's as good as it gets from the
flash what a what a trick pulled out of the hat there for the magicians getting
a runner on board a chance to add to their lead and as Dumbledore will face
batter number two Roy Flushman puts a bat on it and off the unicycle it goes
over the head artificial surface it's bouncy out there he ditched the
unicycle as well the runners will hold up at third base they do hold so we'll
see if Albertson wants to go out make sure make sure that's not an automatic
run or anything is again the right fielder was not on the unicycle dropped
it right there user error got over the head lost the wig boy what a clown show
oh we got our first pie in the face Albertson pie in the face Albertson the
circus one of that play called dead because oh and he is tossed he's gone
Albertson don't have any of that look at that Schmidt Papo Papo with the pie to the face and now
the magicians and excuse me now the mascots are chasing one another around
the field chaos has broken out here as a pie in the face I think that's Albertson's
50th pie to the face this season but he's no stranger to the pie in the face
he wears it well let's take another look at this pie in the face see the argument
happening at boom right there right in to the face is that shaving cream or
whipped cream he's not eating it so I can only assume that it's shaving cream
you know you would think a lot of umpires might be a little bit more upset
oh now he's just now he's just upset the turf monster got him tripped him up a
little bit he's tossing the rubber he's tossing the turf out of this game as
well
unbelievable and we'll see now maybe this gets maybe this gets joy handsome back
in the good graces of Albertson
of course Albertson an ultimate professional doesn't want to wipe that
off just wants to keep play going in our official score if you're wondering if
you're scoring at home 9 on that play e9 on that play for your keep track at
home for this broadcast here tonight glad you're with us storm it's always a
pleasure to be alongside you and this is a real issue mascot now we had one of
these mascots called out for the card there's a reason yeah for double doors
should be there double doors should be there but the clown mascot needs to exit
the field he's holding up the pace of play here and now Albertson just just
exasperated here and I got a new batter coming to the plate says Ronnie Smith
first in to him hit on the ground sharply to short look him back poke it
out across the diamond it's too tall and it bounces into the stands
boy Ronnie with the least clever name on the magicians but that's a great
baseball play they're showing the aggressiveness as Albertson now trying
to explain what happens here so they're going to give second base to Smith and
run another run scored I do believe so it should be five nothing run score run
Albertson confirms right on top of it polka dot apologize for the language our
effects Mike sometimes picks up some of the the on field language and we
apologize to our younger viewers if anyone was offended by that from the
umpire the heat of the battle you know there are a lot of things to learn out
here and as a ballplayer learning to curse at the right time is a big part of
the game yep and that'll be out number two run will score though on the chopper
to the left side what's the third base been doing it I don't think he thought
the hit or touch base and bringing it over to the first baseman guess he's
not confident and the throw across the diamond didn't want another run
advancing there is again the circus was just charged with another air on that
overthrow in the first baseman looks another runner at first now for the
magicians Percy throwing it all over the yard and now Donovan Slate comes to the
plate he had that big bases clearing triple back in the second inning still
dealing with with that really is a lot of pie in the face there for out here
crew chief Albertson and he's calling time and now he's headed out towards
towards right field I believe he's asked for the grounds crew something wrong
with the field right now and he'll go out for some inspection and as he's
calling the Empire is calling for the grounds crew and of course when you're
involved with any baseball league the grounds crew guy is really that makes
really makes the game go the way they keep up the field how they paint the
lines take care of the turf I'm not sure what Albertson sees out in the outfield
here it looks like there's an errant sheet there is here comes the grounds
keeper out of the right field bullpen oh look out look out breaks are on the
right side sir it's right just kidding around the lot it's right here so look oh
man yeah that's an arid piece an arid piece of grass here let's see what he
has to say you can get to listen in here on what Albertson has to say to the
grounds crew definitely an artificial piece of grass has been placed on the
turf oh look at the tool he's getting out now you're gonna do a little no
okay okay unbelievable it's a manscaping I believe he is manscaping this field
right now that is that is the manscape trip look at the job it's doing I mean
that's a great job out of that trip maybe he could have used that manscaped
razor behind home plate you know we saw him tripping on earlier I think we're
having mic problems I think the pie to the face has affected the audio here so
what a good job of manscaping that piece of lawn pulling the pie right out of his
mic yeah and you saw Harry helium got a little swab of that pie on his way out
there and he approved maybe that's why crew chief Albertson not too upset about
that pie see in the background there the center fielder and right fielder trying
to stay warm as they get back on the unicycles left fielder right fielder
using a boxing gloves here in this half inning so technical difficulties on the field Albertson is trying to get it
straight but he stopped time here he called time is again there's a out of
nowhere just a random piece of sod laid on the field and we can't have that as
it's not the same level as the artificial turf here so Albertson had to
do some manscaping this grounds crew you know a great job except for that one
patch and it makes you wonder here Gary is there ill intent to have this entire
place so pristine and almost as if they're trying to pull something on
Albertson here we saw behind home plate and now out in right field this is just
ridiculous could be one of the classic magician illusions here just came out of
nowhere has to make you wonder if Isaac illusion had something to do with this
you it does make you wonder I did see a wand in the dugout oh look out for the
grounds crew guy who's gonna look out look out oh boy I mean he's got the
security man with them this is a lawsuit waiting to happen yeah driving
around and look out for the players now as I think now we need to get the
grounds crew guy and off the field security guy making sure everyone stays
off as well so as I was saying right of course I forget about the fact that the
clowns the circus team thought it was really funny to knock the microphone out
with the five really great probably from the replay but anyways this is the
lawnmower and today's event by the way is brought to you by Manscaped.com
don't look at me like that statement Manscaped is the premium brand for
men's grooming hygiene products they just launched the new lawnmower 4.0
trimmer I'm excited to be the first one to check it out and see the new features
I will throw people in the audience out too I want to make that really clear you
can instantly tell the lawnmower 4.0 trimmer is a work of art very easily
check out the two-tone black and hot foil stamp Manscaped logo it works
really well by the way the 4.0 trimmer features ceramic blades with skin safe
technology this helps reduce say you know Nixon and cuts where they matter
most so it's waterproof by the way if you didn't know and cordless so you can
trip in the shower this makes clean up oh by the way join over two million men
worldwide who trust Manscaped the right tools for your family jewels by the way
if you stop throwing pictures get 20% off if you use the code
Manscaped.com slash Jerma or using Jerma at checkout 20% off in free
international shipping Manscaped.com the 4.0 trimmer totally had that memorized
no cue cards involved in that read just another one of the reasons why
Albertson the star crew chief in this league excuse me storm I gotta go buy a
Manscaped that's a good call we do have a former caveman on our broadcast if you
haven't heard there is quite a bit of hair on his back that he does need to
tend to so we will hear from Gary a little bit later actually I believe he
is taking care of that rather quick says quite a bit about how well a job that
that Manscaped Razor does for you I was due for a shave at the back life
certainly appreciate it when I get home tonight nice smooth back of those hands
right down I think she might be knocking on my door I think that that hairy back
might have been what was doing it for you yeah playmate over there at third
base magicians will take their five to nothing lead to the bottom half of this
inning remember this game brought to you by fans Lee a spicy social network be
sure to check out the link and chat in the panel below to discover exclusive
content welcome back to car shield field a five-nothing lead for the Maryland
magicians over the California circus I'm storm Williamson joined by my partner
Gary grunt and now the circus need to get something going here yeah
absolutely surely by five runs here they're half of the third inning this is
no more of a laughing matter they have got to get some runs and it has to start
right now Paul laughing tin we'll try to get it going he cracks one foul on to
the green stuff out in the left field territory foul territory excuse me
almost hit the basketball hoop on that left side of the field there's a
playground as well done that left side is how we're doing we'll get some more
balls to home plate as we've seen a couple of now hard-hit balls find the
stands some of that feel-good juice again for the magicians the elixir of
life if you will it makes you wonder if if Doug Dove is getting an unfair
advantage out here performance enhancing elixir is that what you're saying and
you know what the juice it does make you wonder as well is there a potential deal
with the drunkards in the works that's true too again the drunkards played the
bimes here a crunch time will be following our broadcast here tonight
Tom Chairman and Dickie Dreck will have highlights and full breakdowns of the
games around the JBA today get the drunkards played the bimes not quite
sure how many sober players the drunkards had today and then the caveman
versus the old ladies as well happening in the JBA get a look at that lineup for
the California circus so a reminder that postgame show coming your way after this
crunch time Dove Oh hidden ball trick it looked like
flight into right field long run hack comes off and the catch is made great
running catch by mystery the right fielder to go a long way
losses had in the process but kept the focus all magicians do with that play
Xavier McMagic giving his approval from Centerfield we saw him make three
straight catches out there in Centerfield in the second inning Dove
more hidden ball tricks as that one's fouled straight back off the pole by
Greg Taffy yeah Greg Laffy Taffy at the plate right now has plenty different
flavors and he can be successful with I think there's no doubt that the banana
flavor is hands down the best so he would love to pull a banana flavored hit
out of his pocket right here go down there from Taffy and you like that that
call from Elbertson behind home plate sometimes you're not sure where the
pitch missed Elbertson always lets you know make magic slowly the magical
elixir into the glove Xavier McMagic beer in hand this guy can do it all what a
slab oh what a play falling down part of that entire plate not one drop of beer
lost not one even the circus have some appreciation for that is a man's play
right there what way the circus players getting involved with the fans here I
mean that look like I could be a good reason why they're trailing here five
nothing they're more focused on the antics of the game rather than playing
the game hunter sweets looking for a word of encouragement from his lady out
in the stands after getting caught stealing at second base earlier so after
the outstanding play here comes sweets trying to steal a little candy from fans
here to a knee for that one huge swing from hunter sweets but he comes up empty
the circus have been nothing short of a clown show thus far no I know it's a
moonwalk moonwalk strike call there from chief umpire Elbertson fall back play I
see the security guard now walking in the around the stands you can see him
there he's enjoying some of that nice elixir as well passes it off
we are in good hands here tonight nothing gonna happen here
security has done a nice job going with the backwards hat now keep within the
rules and regulations of the game and the ballpark fair oh two and sweets is
hit again breaks his bat stop stop them yeah wisely throws the broken bat away
doesn't want to get caught with a weapon security might have to come to the
field again to keep the fireworks up exploding here so the second time he's
been hit and warnings have been issued by Albertson doesn't want this hand
game to get out of hand and you wonder if frustration might boil over here for
the circus they're losing this game big they've been hit by a pitch for the
second straight time and now their dugout gets worn for getting hit by the
pitch I think the magicians were trying to say he dove into that he wasn't
really hit by it okay they're going bonkers yeah try to break out the jack
hammer there's handsome on the mound trying to settle his group down he took
the pie to the face well but I don't know how well that jack hammer is gonna
go no no and that is exactly what the magicians are arguing they don't think
that he was actually hit by the pitch they think it hit the bat and that's why
the bat broke so we'll see what Albertson comes what kind of conclusion
he comes to well we have a runner-on first for the California circus
joy handsome has made his way back onto the bad side of Albertson let's go let's
go let's go Joey handsome manager for the magicians
don't have an assistant here they're highly sought after though polka dot who
has popped nine home runs this year
trick the third out of the inning the magicians pull out the wand create a
little magic and illusion and they're out of this inning store we saw dub do
it on the mound and now they do it at first base Albertson all over it we're
still at a five nothing score as we go to the fourth inning a big argument come
in here you can just see it right now you can see the unhappiness written all
over the face of the circus manager we'll bring in the conclusion of this
showdown when we come back you're watching JBA baseball welcome back to
the German Baseball Association a five-nothing lead for the Maryland
magicians over the California circus and here is Mike Salmon leading things off
and oh my this could go on for a while oh my goodness this this is not this is
not good all that all came out of his eyeball ribbon in the eye that's no fun
you might need some eye drops to the field really makes you wonder he reached
base his first time up with all of that in in the back was that hiding in his
brain where where did that come from even more impressive that he was able to
get the first inning single with all that and his eye unbelievable we talked
he loves the adversity we talked about him swimming upstream and now he takes
it in the ass oh no nobody who ever wants to take it that way hit by the
pitch and big top or excuse me big boy buckle thrown out of the game and
the magicians are out of the office or out of their dugout they want buckle
out of this game is again both teams have been warned here buckle has been
ushered to the turf his catcher trying to restrain him void hunch is being
thrown don't need a long-term suspension here for the circus skin
playing for playoff positioning so Albertson letting the next pitcher
down there's no messing around he already warned both dugouts in the
previous inning no more hit batters and the first batter of this top half of
this fourth inning gets drilled as you said it says you said storm right in the
ass goodness that that cannot feel good first of all and second big boy on the
mound I mean there was no fear in crew chief Albertson right there when he
tossed him out of the game I don't want big boy buckle coming after me I don't
know about you I'm just not gonna throw him out of the game and I want to be
taking the dinner before someone goes after my ass now we got another card
being played here and and dying oh boy our card it's a rare power card let's
let's get a closer look at this one got to run backwards to the bases the whole
happening backwards through the bases hole any so all base runners will be
running backwards this could be big-time trouble we've already seen hunter suites
caught stealing running forwards I can only imagine backwards yeah I believe
this is the third power card we've seen here in this game so both managers have
done a nice job of implementing and choosing and picking their spots wisely
of when to play that power card oh big boy buckle back on the field he can't
do this I believe this is Greg Taffy oh who has come in to replace oh goodness
and we got more theatrics going on now I believe this is big boys come out back
yeah big boy felt bad for his teammates thought they needed some refreshments
they you know they've obviously seen the magicians drink on the field so why not
give it a try the other team you know it ain't cheating ain't trying so
Albertson's patience is wearing thin here see yep she's trying to oh he's out
there buckle brought the pie yeah oh oh goodness I think he was just bringing
some drinks to his fellow partners exactly what he was doing and we've seen
the turf monster pop up a couple of times here tonight so all the more
reason to get that manscaper back out exactly that that manscaped razor did
wonders out in right field we've seen some nice plays out there in right field
and got some uneven blades out there right now the manscape for 4.0 would be
a great job speaking of right field by the way right now it's unmanned now the
right fielder is retreating back to his position but I'm worried about left
field and center field right now they just do not look very engaged right now
partner hey you saw no they don't they they've checked out of this game and now
we see another pitcher going into the bullpen with the backup catcher so Taffy
gets tapped here the tall right-hander has a rotor on first base and the power
card was played so all runners will now have to run backwards this entire inning
throw down the first hold on he retreated back to that bag in a forward style
crew chief Albertson has not called him on it no he has not and the first baseman
wanted to call there didn't get it and that is one of the really important
things to note here Gary is in these situations you have to turn yourself
around to run backwards back to the bag you can't just run back forward you have
to go back to the training field you know this doesn't happen all the time so
you have to rely on your training relying on what you've done get you to
this moment and just focus on making sure you're back pedaling toes to the
ground first each toe back pedal left right left right focus on that and you
should be fine almost muscle memory for Mike salmon over at first base the pitch
to Donald strange and it's a call strike a big wind-up strike there from Albertson
more impressive wind-up taffy or Albertson on the ground chopped towards
second base of backpedaling salmon tagged out and they turned to what a
double play there again the power card and doing magic right now for on the
other side for the for the circuses they played they run for our making sure
those runners run backwards great tag great throw over and just just speed
from number 20 there is again the on the base passing at the back pedal all the
way to the dugout as well oh here come the mascots again oh my
goodness we've got a big-time brawl about to break out the mascots are going
at it oh they catch her for the circus got a couple unnecessary shots in there
on Dumbledore oh no this this could be huge problems they are now they have now
exited the field of play and I don't think this is ending anytime soon
partner we've seen this before these two have got some serious beef they've gone
at it the last few times these teams have gotten together this could end
ugly a couple of right-handed uppercuts from Dumbledore and they are going at it
on the dugout for the California circuses what no one told you about
Dumbledore is that in his younger days he was a boxing he was a boxer training
with Mike Tyson he's showing off the moves this is Nolan Ryan and ask yeah
continue Robin Ventura and Nolan Ryan basically right there as Dumbledore
continuing to pummel with the rights security guard is going to get the
jackhammer is and you know what at least California has something to be happy
about at this point indeed as they're trying to throw show some fight show some
spirit but unfortunately Dumbledore was a little too much for the clown and
mascot showdown let's circle back to the manager for the circus Fred Big Top how
about the timing of that card that he pulls out there with the runner on first
to lead off the inning they get the double play now two outs and nobody on
as that one is shot down the left field line slicing into the corner it's a
fair ball and it hops over the wall for a ground rule double that ground rule
double it so yeah a little backpedal into second base as it's given to him
sprayed that ball down the left side of the field that you see a good cut here
off of the breaking ball did a nice job to stay back make good contact and ride
over the Grotto Beast sign the way he keeps his hands inside the baseball
there on that fans Lee replay but going back to what you're talking about there
store William said about that power card being played at the right time the
manager for the California circus oh no it's gone into the locker down with the
mascots oh boy and this is what we always wanted to see look at this right
those uppercuts in time oh no the counter now the Dumbledore finally
taking some shots this has gotten interesting he stays he's dazed and
confused look at this now they're making out oh my goodness a hate fest is turned
into all love I don't even want to know what's happening there porn stuff is
this and the backpedaling player gets past third base coming home it's a good
throw the backwards slide he's out unbelievable play Xavier McMagic gun down
at the plate yeah McMagic just a step to slow there a great throw from the left
fielder to end that inning it all goes back to that power card being played got
that double play is this the momentum changer the circus beat up the
magicians mascot and trail it by five we head to the fifth inning you're watching
Jerma Baseball Association
you
welcome back you get a look at crew chief Albertson in command of this game
we're in the bottom of the fourth inning it's a five-nothing lead for the
Maryland magicians over the California circus another look at Doug Dove on the
mound he will go to work once again against this circus order he has had
all kinds of success so far and former Hall of Fame caveman Gary grunt tell us
what's been going so well for them so far in this game well the additions have
done a very good job of you know taking advantage of getting good pitches to hit
and then driving those balls in the gap scoring those runs and you hope on the
other side right now if you're a circus fan they string together some
consecutive hits here only one hit right now through the first four innings Percy
polka dot hitting a robust 282 on the year in slugging for 44 you'd have to
think this would be the guy to break them out if anyone yeah the magicians
are employer have deployed an interesting outfield strategy here that's
three center fielders right now nobody in left or right field so we'll see how
this works out for the magicians you know there's a lot of conversation out
there in center field I think they all just want to play center field they're
kind of pointing towards the other outfield positions trying to get each
other to go out there but they have all been determined to play centerfield in
this anyway that's the position you want to play they don't want to give it up
and you know ballplayers you know aren't really they want to fight for their for
that position that they play they want they don't want another position they
want to play center field right now we've got three of them for the magicians
out of course out of Maryland as you mentioned earlier it's a coastal battle
with California taking on a team squad the magicians out of Maryland and
meanwhile Doug Dove has lost his command a bit on the mound he opens up this
bottom of the fourth with a four-pitch walk to the leadoff man and now it's the
three-hitter David Honk coming up for the circus it feels like this is their
chance right here and we're getting some beer man beer man is on the field
bringing some libations out to those three centerfielders they needed a
he's wet that whistle the hard work out there in center and I'll tell you what
the more impaired these magicians seem to get the better they seem to play
yeah until now a blast in the left center field and it will one hop the wall he
was pipping that one the whole way David Honk not running out of the box
they had him at second base if it was an accurate throw he's still going to third
as the throw got away he's thinking home here he comes no tag
oh good move the circus is on the board the swift move the offensive lineman
going up against a defensive lineman gets to the quarterback and a run is scored
David Honk showing off the defensive end skills look at that blast off of the
bat yeah you got not quite all of it but enough to get it to the wall and the
three centerfielders went to track that one down surprised didn't get it over
for a ground rule double but good hustle around the base pass to get that run
across the board two runs across the board magicians manager joy handsome
contesting the call but indeed that ball was dropped as you get a look at Doug
Doug there's a swim move we talked about just could not handle that swim too
powerful yeah it's way too powerful from David Honk and you know some of you out
there may have played a little MLB slugfest in your day great move there
from David Honk one of the classic moves that you will ever see in the JBA he
basically pulled many of our viewers may have played slugfest but what about some
NFL blitz pulled out a nice NFL blitz move there well he pulled out to bomb
with the bat in his hands and then he turned on the Jets coming home so two
runs across for the circus you know storm my friend worked in a circus one
time he was a human cannonball when he retired it didn't replace him I couldn't
find anyone else's the same caliber that that is just really a shame you know the
caliber of this circus team incredible but they have it's heating up right now
they try to stay off of her try to get another run on first base but a great
play by the magicians and maybe they've settled back down and as we have another
break in the action here is here comes the jest the clown gestures from the
California circus heading to the mound the jugglers oh this now this is
something that could really get dub dub off of his game he surrendered his first
two runs of the game in this inning and now we talked about some of those
distractions that the starting pitcher big boy buckle had to deal with well now
the tables have turned let's see how the magicians can deal I mean this is
this is not an easy thing it's hard to juggle those pins in the first place but
to try to pitch with them going in front of you behind you and now look at this
another cop power card look like a baby card being played but the baby that's a
legendary card chosen player must wear a baby bib and baby bonnet for their next
bat if they do not get a hit and add three runs for your team score and I'll
tell you what there's a reason why this is a legendary card Gary this is the
most demoralizing card in JBA play if you do not successfully complete the
baby bib hit it is one of the biggest game changers in this sport we could see
a tie ball game after this at bat yeah we absolutely could and certainly don't
want the embarrassment of having to wear a grown-up having to wear a baby bib but
that's just the way we played here in the JBA and I'm just super impressed
right now with the jugglers oh they just knocked the hat off of Doug Dove getting
a little chirping out for the magicians bench the circus is really rounding into
form right now in town right now look at all this look at the skill are you
kidding me crew chief Albertson I think he called himself out umpire panda well
you know what when you when you have an out call as legendary as crew chief
Albertson you can't help but call yourself out time and time again no no
and Albertson showing off the the multi-talented skills that he has and
maybe we have seen him in the past do the spinning plate trick with a unicycle
so he toned it down just a little bit there we've seen him in the earlier this
season where he did it with a unicycle and now the beer guy the magician side
of it there's our baby bib there this is a huge moment in this game yep there's
the baby bottle Manny up Chuck where's that bib as good as any of them that's a
large nipple on that bottle our fabulous crew helping out as well what size
diaper do you think that is Gary that is a 38 large for sure
that can hold some liquid 38 large and you know we know can hold some liquid
the problem is you know if up Chuck deposits some solids into that thing how
long will it last not very long we've had some bleed-through issues with a
recall problem with these particular branded diapers so as far as I understand
the payload is is 30 pounds so as long as Manny up Chuck does not exceed that
weight he should be okay up chucking is fine they don't any down chucking right
now that is a great point and that's why we bring oh he maybe wanted to bring the
bottle to the bait to the to the plate so you're not allowed to do that no
bottles only libation bottles elixir bottles no baby bottles allow that
hopefully so here we go should be a lot of action in the hips here if up Chuck
does not pick up a hit excuse me it would be Maryland to pick up the three
runs and be out to an eight to two lead up Chuck calls time understanding this
is a veteran move here by up Chuck he may be wearing a diaper but this this is
not his first time in the box no sir love the bonnet first pitch from dove
skips in and he pops it up just past the shortstop tough play but it's made
and that'll add three more onto the board for the Magicians yeah you have to
wonder if he should have just taken that pitch it bounced in front of the plate
maybe got a little antsy wanted to create something for his team is see
bouncing well in front of home plate it's a sand wedge to short center field
we saw some some Vlad Guerrero types theatrics earlier in this game I called
out each year oh at the time both of them have had their their call at it and
now Doug Dove looking back towards his defense oh what do we got going on here
you'll spin turn fire for a strike trying to change up the delivery here in
the California Circus now trailing eight to two they've got to start
stringing together some consecutive hits only two hits in the ball game right
now for the circus Harry helium at the dish dove very slow methodical molasses
like as he shakes off the pitch a little shimmy the EFIS is grounded toward short
charging in and the play is not made because now all of a sudden he's trying
to row row row the boat down that first baseline not enough water to get him to
first it was it was not working well you know if if maybe up Chuck had left a
trail of tears deep enough for him he could have been able to paddle his way
but it will fans another reminder this game brought to you by fans Lee a spicy
social network be sure to check out the link and chat at the paddle at the
panel below to discover exclusive content from your favorite creators right
back after this
welcome back to car shield field where the Maryland magicians own an eight to
two lead over the California Circus I'm storm Williamson alongside Gary grunt
get a look at crew chief Albertson down there on the field and this has been a
game owned by the magicians that baby card pulled out the legendary card and
the baby bib did not treat the circus well just when it looked like they were
getting some momentum three runs right back on the board to the magicians a two
lead down for the magicians a slight delay here before we start the top of
the fifth year I believe there was a bathroom break that had to be had for
some of the players so the pregame meal was some hot spicy food so I think some
players had to run to the restroom to take care of that yeah some some things
definitely that needed to be taken care of we're not sure how much of it ended up
in the dive uh-oh uh-oh look at this illusion put out the tricks now up still
pulling up still pulling oh Roy Flushman no no wait wait come on here's all this
coming from there we go the hats for bats keep bats warm
fans we want to remind you about surf shark you know what geo blocking is
Disney Plus or Netflix for example have movies for each country access should
not be tied to nationality surf shark gives you all the access you need just
connect the service and refresh the page access granted I use surf shark every
day it automatically starts up whenever I start my PC and whenever I need it I
activate it with just one click if it's good enough for storm it's good enough
for you absolutely I love me you got to love you some you oh look at this look
at this a little backhanded fake throw and it goes for a ball but you love the
idea from a Laffy Taffy yep absolutely as it is Flushman at the plate drone
screaming behind home plate and that one's taken up so Flushman has found
himself ahead in the count he's you know against Greg Taffy ahead of the comp had
a nice little pull out the ribbon trick out of the tin can oh babe has called his
shot Flushman oh right over right over the surf surf shark sign and he pops it
up in the shallow center he was just pointing to the shallow center that's
where he was pointing so that's exactly what he wanted to do and he pulls it off
the shallow centerfield pop-up so that's exactly what he wanted to do that's not
one you see executed every day no no you have to keep yourself up out like that
it's such an unselfish thing to do for your team and it takes some guts to call
that shot it's not one you see every day so I guess he said look I got this in my
back pocket no problem he left all this magic in his pre-game pre at bat routine
they're pulling all that yarn out of the can see what kind of magic mystery has
in store for us Craig gets jammed on the first pitch from behind it before it hit
the ground he's got it in his glove we're trying to get rid of his gear oh
this is why you tune into the JBA immediately out of the dugout Joy
Handsome is livid we saw the whole way that ball never touched the ground that
in glove he heard it right there from Albertson net glove at the same time
that's an hour on believable play made by a hunter sweets he's been plunked by
two pitches in this game and now some payback I think it's about the eight or
ninth warning that Albertson is given toward the magicians bench for all the
talking they've been doing got two outs here in the top of the fifth inning
nobody aboard I think it's after the 10th in or the 10th warning or someone
will get thrown out so a couple more warnings before someone gets tossed
it floats in there and it's a call strike the circus in town creating a
little magic of their own and I think you know during that bathroom break Taffy
may have drug out a little tissue with him as well
you'll toilet paper on the heel of the shoe trick huh the left handers it's
called himself out and that's the second time he's done that so Albertson is is
down to one out now in this game three outs and you're done we all know how
that works Taffy with a one-in-one count facing Ronnie Smith the pitch Ronnie
tattoos it into the gap in left center field it gets down for a base hit
another hit for the magicians good piece of hitting and what is this
that's some camaraderie there between opposing teams Wow and we'll see how
these opposing dugouts take to this as you see I do know he's a free agent at
the end of the year perhaps some collusion going on some tampering
perhaps they come play for the California Circus Harry he'll play for
the magicians anymore helium trying to plead his case over there hit sharply
towards second base another nice play made over there solid as can be all day
long for Paul Laffington we're going to break here we'll be back with the bottom
of the fifth inning when we come back eight to two Maryland on top of
California you're watching JBA action the magic out to an eight to two lead
over the California Circus you're watching JBA baseball with the bunny on
screen for you right there that's as good as it gets that's a great illusion
what was he gonna do let's see another trick sir it reminds me of the time back
in my caveman playing days where we tried to order a pizza big game and the
operator in the other end we made the call from the dugout we ordered a large
pepperoni and he said do you want that in 16 slices or in eight slices so I
said I don't think we need 16 slices let's just make it eight you know that's
that's a real a good call you would think though that the cavemen would have
the appetite to put down 16 slices but you know eight far far less pizza to eat
yes large pizza cut into eight pieces instead of 16 it's much more manageable
for a group of our the team that we had back there for the caveman certainly
certainly you know I can't wait to get the postgame report from the crunch time
and see how the caveman did today that is a really really important thing for
fans to look forward to germination we have a postgame show coming your way at
the conclusion of this one crunch time as you heard Gary grunt allude to it and
Gary on his way to the cavemen Hall of Fame and that's got to be not only a
great honor for you Gary but it's gonna be a lot of fun to go out there and be
back with the guys that you won a championship back when in 2017 with yeah
it was a great time and a great journey to be with the caveman and I'm happy to
donate my back hair to the Hall of Fame for the caveman as well so it should be
a fun ceremony libations will be had and be good to see some of my old teammates
and a lot of people don't know this but we're actually suffering in our world
today from a back hair shortage and if it weren't for people like you Gary
there there just wouldn't be enough to go around so we appreciate what you do
for the good people of not only the German Baseball Association but looking
out for the greater good as well and so it's not locks of love you know it's
curly curly hair for love is curly back hair for love is what we're trying to
do it just trying to ways awareness that you know some men out there can't grow
back hair and others like myself have some to give and just trying to help the
community make them a little hairier that's a little bit more caveman from
from the heart of our Hall of Famer Gary grunt three and one the count to Lenny
Munson you hear that that famed little grunt there from Gary and you know when
you play behind home plate there there are plenty of times where hey you got a
reach for that baseball you got to do this or that just a natural grunt it's
the job done in those situations it really started as kind of a joke as you
know as I tended to pass a lot of gas you know behind home plate so it'd be a
little loud and I didn't want Albertson to hear it so I would grunt a little bit
and then a little you know a little so he couldn't tell the difference if it
was Gary that that is a poof card that Albertson was just never ready for no
no and I had a lot of poofs in my day so check this out we got all the circus
trying to get into the Magicians dugout and a balloon fight balloon sword fight
has broken out here Albertson tried to get this under order but the circus has
broken loose is that is that poppo Schmidt poppo after being thrown out of
the game gets back out there to get involved in the in the balloon fight
the league will take notice of that once you've been ejected you come back on
the field you could face suspension so we'll see if the league wants to take a
look at that look at it Albertson even appreciates this gag here from the
circus so we'll see if if you know that positive reinforcement from our crew
chief gives them that momentum we've been talking about it for quite a while
now this is a circus team that came into this game with three more wins than the
Maryland Magicians still no outs here run around first for the California
Circus three centerfielders once again for the Magicians they imported in the
last couple innings now and I think the guys are just having a good time just
gabbing like a couple of schoolgirls out there and you know when you're up by
six a little socialization is is in play so the Magicians take advantage and look out
another hit batter look out oh false alarm false alarm and you know that was that was a
really aggressive run towards the mound by Paul Laffington he took a 90 degree
turn towards first pace right as he got close to our picture Victor vanish on the
mound for the Maryland Magicians and decided to make a no laughing matter for
Laughington as we now have runners on first and second for the California
Circus they'll try and trapeze themselves into a couple of runs here a
catapulting effort would be the one that they're looking for right now and here
comes Fred Big Top and now he's joined with Joy Hansel now look Joy clearly has
the better looks and he's going to try to demoralize Fred Big Top call him a
crybaby there you saw the crybaby motion I was just gonna say move for the
power move on top of the power car being played this other coach must wear a bag
on his head for the rest of the inning so the bulk managers go at it and the
circus manager pulls out the lights out car and this is the type of stuff that
has Fred Big Top in the discussion for manager of the year in the JBA this year
look at this he shoves joy handsome down to the turf and now personally goes
over to put the bag on his head emphatically coach is definitely in the
bag now as that was bag tastic Elbertson the manager getting it into it with one
of the fans the magician fans near the dugout so you got to wonder how the
magicians manager can manage this game he can't see right now so see what kind of
defense he wants to implement as you can see the shot right there he is in the
bag right now can't see he's got his bag but you know his his outfielder is still
on that same page they are just doing whatever they want out there and you
know that was that was pre bag on the head as well so maybe the magicians have
just been in their bag this entire time. Good pitch. Taffy tips it into the mitt
there Vanish feeling himself after that delivery and Vanish does like to feel
himself a lot although he seems to disappear rather quickly we have seen a
lot of hit batters in this game check behind the runner at second base it
bounces off of the shortstop and stays right in his general vicinity so thought
that one was going to center field is it looked like it took a bad hop there
you're going to look at this from the knees Donovan Slate is in a straight
jacket at second base so you know double play situation that's going to make it
really tough to turn very tough but we've seen the likes of a player with
his caliber make good plays with his feet and kick the ball over nicely so no
stranger to the straight jacket and that's something that the JBA really
brings out is you know you watch players in regular baseball leagues and it's
it's just not that impressive the skill set does not need to be that wide you
better run backwards in this league get a fly ball out into center field all
three of them have a look at it the center center fielder chucked his glove
but didn't come up with it it's the left center fielder with the play yeah and
they fire home to keep the runners put a selfish play by the center center
fielder they're trying to make the play without his glove trying to put a hex on
the glove to make that catch you'll see it right here the guy in the center of
the center field almost caught it but the left center fielder got it and made
the out two down here bag is still on oh my goodness
trichotomous this is a game-breaker all runs now we're three in this half inning
wow this could easily put the circus right back into this game should we get
a base hit here game tying run standing at second base with only one out here
in the bottom of the fifth inning and all the while joy handsome has a bag
over his head hunter sweets like candy is got a golden opportunity for the
California circus right here hunter sweets came to the plate as the leadoff
man for the circus in the bottom of the first inning hit by a pitch on an o2
count came up in his second at bat in the third with an o2 count he was hit by
the pitch and here he grabs it and he's gonna fire it deep in the right field
and it's off the glove of the right fielder and they are rounding second and third one run comes home
that's three and another three we're tied what I don't even know what to call that he snatched
that right out of thin air hunter sweets literally a circus catches it and launches
this ball the right center unbelievable play by a hunter sweets that is not
something you see every day and what a risky play to jump out in front of the
plate if you do not grab that cleanly disaster breaks loose in an inning where
all runs count for three enjoy handsome wants to protest this call but he can't
even find Elbertson with the bag on his head he didn't even see it he's just
being told what happened and he's trying to figure out that the legal player not
I think I was gonna let it go it's not buying this argument I mean you have to
you have to come with the sync logical argument and handsome just never got a
look at that play six runs scored off of the base hit what a time again the
power cards have been played at the exact right time the exact right moment
they have made a huge impact in this game playing the run card is sweet for
sweets aren't we all sir aren't we all what a play unbelievable and now the go
ahead three runs standing on second base right for Percy polka dot chance to take
the lead here for the circus he takes ball one Percy polka dot walked earlier
in this game starting to turn into the greatest show here it's great to show on
dirt or turf and dirt turf pellets pellets bounce towards third base
charging hard off balance the throw is spiked three more runs will come home this
circus have the lead a level a nine-run inning on three runs scored has the
circus on top I've been reading the comments and a lot of folks out there
really didn't think that the circus was gonna go away and sure enough right back
in this thing with the lead Fred Big Top one of the best in the business for a
reason pulls two power cards out of his back pocket the timing just
scintillating here in the bottom of the fifth a three run lead now for California
11 to 8 the second baseman for the magicians doing getting a little bit
more free out of that straight jacket and you know that's that's a frustrating
situation partner I know you've been hit with that straight jacket a few times in
your playing days it gets a little claustrophobic by the end of the inning
it's tough to get off but there is a secret obviously this player doesn't
know and it's a secret of the pros that we like to call of oh that's a terrible
throw David Hawk goes down for it golfs it out and that one has been thrown out
of the ballpark I hope there's some insurance on that van over there you may
have drilled it that was an Aaron throw just took off on the center-center
fielder and he might have an insurance bill coming his way that's that ball
cleared the entire stance let's see if we get a shot of the card almost hit oh
oh my gosh what a what a look from our production crew here great camera work
out there center field Jerma baseball as professional as it gets oh he's trying
to stay on first base here he's out but trying to oh and oh he's out look at
him he's got out of the straight jacket just in time to play some defense with
two outs left and there was some confusion over who's gonna be on first
base look like that polka dot trying to or was honk excuse me standing up first
base didn't think that they forgot the crew chief Albertson is well in control
of this game he's letting everyone know also a great job by the second baseman
for the magicians to get out of that straight jacket now he's an integral
part once again of this defense look at the form from Albertson pure athlete
makes you wonder how he's not on this field playing right now absolutely could
easily be play for either one of these oh my goodness he got two of them two
for one fan is not happy picks up his trash and throws it towards Albertson and
exits the game as he's now been thrown out so Albertson has issued a lot of
warnings his first ejection of the game except me excuse me second ejection of
the game this time a fan that's correct we saw Papa tossed earlier in the game
he did come back out of the dugout in the balloon fight that we saw earlier and
we want to remind everyone this is all going on with a bag on top of joy
handsome the head coach of the Maryland Magicians set yeah I can't see what's
happening can't employ any shifts in the defense can't give his pitcher a signal
all I could do is listen and clap and not only that it here Gary grunt future
Hall of Famer for the Phoenix cavemen you can't make the necessary adjustments
as vanish pulls the hidden ball trick oh he's got it in his glove what's
Albertson gonna come it's a strikeout what an illusion for the Magicians now
you see it now you don't and you're out Victor vanish out of nowhere he gets
them out of the pickle still a three-run game the california circus Oh big top
absolutely hates it we'll see what he thinks in the sixth inning we'll be
back after this on JVA
you
come back to car shield field this is the German Baseball Association I am
Scott Williamson joined by future Hall of Famer from the cavemen Gary grunt and
carry a nine run inning for the circus to jump back on top 11 to 8 all started
with that power card being played meaning that each run that was scored
would count as three runs and hit three runs across the board so three times
three is nine they are now in the lead 11 day and how about the big-time play
that we had behind home plate it was a diving catch made falling into the
screen by Roy Flushman and or excuse me it was it was made by rather see that
was Hunter sweets who made that play in in the dugout for the Magicians joy
handsome had no shot of arguing the call he had a bag over his head he could not
see anything that was going on trickery going on here now on our screen
bird oh yeah oh and the suck it okay okay all right the double bird suck it
and now some teepee being flowed on our on the field
haven't done that oh another one another clown toss didn't like the toll paper on
the field I think that I think he was trying to throw him at the umpires been
shit tonight so I think that's why I was trying to throw the teepee on the field
let him know to wipe it up roll in hand you know he was praising the the circus
earlier for how funny they were with their antics now that it's directed at
Elbertson he's not so happy about it and you know I hate to bring this up here
Gary Grunt but is this maybe a little too much ego from Elbertson here yeah we
stand it from time to time where some buttons could be pushed and that's just
the wrong button to push for Albertson and he didn't appreciate the gesture
that he's been shit tonight laffy taffy brings it home it's in there for a call
strike Albertson you know he spent a long time in that bathroom between innings
and you have to say it's well timed from California you can't be that upset I'm
thinking it was at least a four or five flusher for Albertson because he was in
there way too long and and let's hope that he dropped in a couple of curtsy
flushes because we saw his free game meal and that was probably a stinky
stinky poo poo and you know on the year Albertson is is averaging two point
seven three flushes per dump and if he exceeded that amount you have to say
that is pretty warranted from California yeah you don't want too many bowel
movements and we'll see how the umpire responds here mr. Albertson pitch comes
in and it's a ball low and outside this is Mike Salmon at the plate we saw him
back his way over to first base for a single and runner off with the pitch it
is fouled out of play to the right side so a stolen base attempt make sure that
more information stays safe use promo code Jerma to get 83% off three extra
months for free of surf shark they offer a 30-day money back guarantee so there's
no risk surf with your own set of rules that is surf shark use the promo code
Jerma to get 83% off three extra months for free it comes in a little bit high
as well to count to two and one nobody out and one man on or the magicians here
in the top of the sixth let's see what kind of response the magicians have here
is trailing by three now after that big inning runner on the move again the
fifth don't have to send him right back to first base bedazzle Mike Salmon five
foot ten hundred ninety pounds a 291 hitter including that base hit today the
two-two pitch put on the ground towards short this could be two to second base
for one laughington turns around one hopper to first and just not quite in
time as thought about so yeah out and safe out at second base safe at first
base the official call from Albert sentence trying to regain control is
well is he trying to dry his you know a little swamp ass in the behind the plate
right now and you know we talked about that being you know one of your signature
moves the swamp this can be really a game-changer and the magicians are at
again oh my gosh endless amounts of Kleenex I mean that's Donnie strange
they might want to say that I give it to mr. or umpire Albertson that maybe soak
up some of that swamp ass he's got rocking hunter sweets is feeling a
little sour after that so now strange will step in and try to come up with a
hit one out in the end it's all strange and BP taking some big hacks he's
swung and miss it around five in a row and make some contact here so we were
wondering what kind of adjustments strange would make he did not look good
and BP made contact there certainly an integral part for the magicians and
worked there by the ball clown the ball clown really for my money he has been
the best execution of anyone tonight yeah time and time again he comes up
same form exactly I was just gonna say he's not afraid to take that extra step
make sure he's in the right position to hand the balls to Albertson yeah it does
a nice job of getting to Albertson to dug out oh nearly took his head off taffy
ducking for cover and that would have been a colorful experience had that come
to fruition another look strange just rips the cover off that ball and taffy
do nothing but duck out of the way big chance here for the magicians to get
back in this all they need is a three run shot I have to wonder if they I
don't know how many power cards have been played for them as it's one spring
in the way just inside the line of fair ball one run coming home here comes the
second getting the wave around third headed towards third base himself Xavier
make magic and as he chugs the beer he's coming home he sucks the can at the
catcher and scores and dabs what a spray chart this guy has knocks it down the
left field wall three runs scored and we are tied 11 11 of the top of the six
what a great job of hitting right here going oppo field check that spray chart
that was done that hooked him up and we know old dougie has had his way with the
elixir throughout this game he knew exactly what make magic needed that
extra oomph to get him across home plate we are all tied he did that feel good
juice and they've been anytime that something specials happen for the
magicians that feel good juice has been a part of it to hopper to third no
problem over there for giggles and Sean put it in the dirt tag is applied and
German with the emphatic call for chief Albertson now we can see handsome can
see now and doing the the swan the swan move the figure skating swan move as
he's trying to tell him that he swan dive this see the initial play here is
bobbled but a great recovery and right there the tag is applied and you can see
the ball we're going to move down that line by the runner trying to evade the
tag or the tag and just couldn't and that is the kind of call that ends up
getting crew chief Albertson into the championship game to be the the crew
chief time and time again just a big big play he's all over all over it good call
by Albertson Dumbledore really hates it but look at that just loading on the
other side and this one's stung past the shortstop a tough hop Roy Fluschman
caught it flush been a lot of flushes here tonight between the bathroom and
flushman there really have and that's another thing that we've got to really
take into account here are these restrooms still usable by the ninth
inning we're just hoping for our fans sake that we can get through this one
yeah maybe get a plumber in here to pipe the you know what right out of this
field well we know Roy's a little bit busy but we'll see if he can get some
some help for us out here first pitch to mystery and he puts it through the hole
between first and second two outs in the inning and two runners now for the
Magicians that mystery is taking some good at bats here extends the inning for
the Magicians they're trying to get a rally here they led for a majority of
this game the circus came back with nine runs in the fifth inning and a good
response here by the Magicians already putting up three they have two on with
two out now with a big-time hitter coming to the plate Smith Ronnie Smith
singled back in the fifth inning he's won for two today the pitch from Taffy
bounces low and away new ballgame as we are into the sixth inning all kinds of
scoring in the last two frames the last two innings in particular nine runs in
the bottom of the last inning this is bounced back up the middle shift on with
the runner or with the fielder excuse me covering at second base and with the
foot on the bag that is out number three we go to the bottom of the six we're all
tied at 11 you're watching the German Baseball Association all tied at 11 look
at all that scoring in the last two and a half innings out here at car shield
field I am storm Williamson reminding you that today's game is brought to you
by fans Lee an innovative social platform where you can connect with
creators chat one-on-one unlock exclusive content and discover new faves
for the for you page it's like tick-tock for spicy content sign up through twitch
or Twitter today to see if your favorite creators are already having fun on fans
league so it'll be Victor vanished back to the mound he was outstanding in that
last half inning of work despite the nine runs being put up on the board
because of a power card and now we've got another yep the upgrade it's a rare
card being played right now by the Magicians it replaced bats with a much
larger bat with more service area for this half inning so it's more of a club
that they'll be using a caveman club and Gary you might have I had the inside
info on how to use this correct as with my favorite bat to use when I was
playing for the caveman it's the obviously thick bat I used to call mine
the Fred Flintstone because it was just made of bedrock and could really put
some power behind the ball and that's where I why I hit a lot of home runs
over my career playing for the caveman so they were implemented that bat cup
check here to make sure it works I don't think actually he's wearing a cup he's
just beating himself with balls right now and you know what sometimes you get
to the bottom of the sixth inning and you need a good shot between the legs to
wake you up the pace of play has slowed a little bit with all the scoring that
we've had here lately and a nice shot to the nuts wake you up right away as we
have number 69 Manny Upchuck coming to the plate and we talked about so much
when you use this club the hair to bat ratio has to be correct and it looks
pretty good here first pitch swinging throw up the line was the tag applied
yes what a defensive play the club does not pull through there for the circus
oh the comedy live motion for the swipe just like in his playing days
Elbertson like it was yesterday yeah yeah former first baseman turned umpire
used to call him scoops of the field while the deer and now they're scooping
something else up back in the bathroom after the debacle that we had a while
ago again we apologize to you fans that's just something we can't control
you know and it's one of those things it'll catch up to Elbertson what maybe
once every five games or so and he just needs that extended time in between
innings so forgot to take the money made he's got a little runs his jeans right
now so that's right so now Harry helium oh man he's feeling so there's a juice
and feel good juice oh boy vanish here we go what kind of illusion are we gonna
see a two swagger look out and behind inside g-double-o-d-e-y-e-o Torkin oh
there's the beer man beer man and the booty yeah now he's the hot dog man out
on the field showing bunt I don't know if you want to bump oh and he takes a
strike nasty slider there from vanish oh Elbertson thought about running over to
the magician's bench I guess we're still chirping there
yeah of his mind and meanwhile vanish is just hammering this beer on the mount
beer man's got them all ready for the next inning that one comes in letter
high call strike I was that the homeless guy is the beer guy the homeless guy
from happy Gilmore because that's what it looks like and you know what that
that homeless guy needs some more love because he has provided so many of
these magicians with the tools necessary those tools being that magic elixir
magic elixir it's working now as the count is back in the favor of vanish it's
one and two could use a strikeout here highlight kick the fish the helium and
it caught him in the front thigh whoa well the ball yes they said it didn't
hit it didn't look at this it did look no argument from helium he wants to use
this club yeah it looked like he was gonna trot down first base but he
avoided the pitch just barely I thought maybe he got his pants but Elbertson
says no ran it in on him and you could hear the loud crack of the bat chucks
it in vanish and look at this he's gonna get a word from helium oh he tosses him
from the game just just when you thought you had some sportsmanship vanish
vanishes from the handshake yeah he went in there for the handshake say it's all
good psych see ya did the hair slick back oh and you wonder if this is Harry
helium again he has really been trying to coax some of these magicians to join
the circus and upcoming helium has been tossed from this game oh my gosh he has
seen he has been good guy helium throughout this contest and he's been
high as a kite now he's at the lowest close throwing out of this game oh look
at this oh push up off okay and as a former player Gary grunt how do you
break that for not sure of the form there the pump was a little too low for
my like and look at this Elbertson and try again he's got to do it again yeah
look at this we got too much booty action in the back yeah it's like a big
castle but it's not low enough no there we go that's a little bit is accepting
these back in okay he did get the necessary amount of push-ups okay he's
back in so helium is high once again and you know what not
everyone can manage ten push-ups at a time especially if you're high the way
that Harry helium is right now that would have been a big loss for the circus
if helium left this game but thankfully he's able to keep his cardio up treats
the body right and not only that his good nature will will continue throughout
this game it appears that that our shortstop has gotten enough of this
elixir in his energy is spread into the outfield there are no shirts on for half
of our defense right now for the magic yeah it's a it's a warm night it's cooled
off just a little bit but you know with all the drinking that the magicians have
been doing it can't get a little sweaty out there so nice little dance there
from the shortstop yeah we got we got some you know when the shirts come off
you've got to give the female audience something to really write home about you
got to give him a reason to tune in again one of the reasons why the JVA
does it better than anyone that's a fair ball down the line takes a weird bounce
off the wall this is Lenny Munson headed into second base with a stand-up
two-out double Munson with a great hit nice double down that left field side of
course all players are using the club here the bat best known for from the
caveman someone got a hold of them and you know what that's celebratory clown
music that starts going can be a bit unnerving for the opponents that's when
California starts to feel it securities digging it and we're equal opportunity
beer man a beer man here and we can't forget that you know shirts off can go
both ways so wild pitch allows the runner to advance from second to third
and that's something else to keep in mind here we saw that hot start for the
Maryland magicians and that elixir you know it brings you a good boost initially
do they start to lose it as this game goes along as that elixir takes more
effect I think that's why you just keep drinking it you know the more elixir you
take the better you get you know the more elixir you have within your system
the more chance you're gonna be able to put up some runs put up some big time
hits and Gary correct me if I'm wrong but it's the decision-making that that
elixir you know if you don't have enough of it you can't make the right decisions
out there as we see a bunt attempt push foul at the first base side count to one
and two says Paul Laffington at the plate hitting 308 now on the year I did
notice that some of those shots the the cleanliness and the smoothness of the
bodies as you see there no hair whatsoever those guys would not make
the caveman no they wouldn't and that's why you see them here on the their
they are manscaped not the only thing that razor went to work on as this is
bounced back in front of the plate vanish underhand flips to the bag at
first force out and tag applied for the end of the inning we go to the seventh
we're all tied at 11 we'll be right back with more germa baseball association
oh
switch yourself up with a fuck you turn me off I know it's just a figure of speech
but don't you know how to feel just as hard as tattooing when it's this one's
burning up my skin inside of my heart till the end of time I'll be fire fire
cuz you're my human life
welcome back to car shield field where we are tied at 11 we got a baseball game
going on between the lines but meanwhile in the dugout a fight has broken loose
yeah back in the locker room right now the mascots have been going at it for
quite some time it's like a WWE battle is broken out oh chair right to the nuts
ouch excuse me a trash can to the nuts that's never good no doubt about it and
you know that I wouldn't wish a trash can to the nuts on anybody and not only
that that's again one of those momentum changes in this game you know that your
mascot has just been blown to smithereens down in the dugout that
that's a big shot to the spirit of your squad look at that laughy taffy as he
comes out with the pitch and we got a couple of clowns right behind old plate
yeah the ball clowns are on the field trying to create havoc one just sitting
enjoying some peanuts and crackerjacks yeah he's got his crackerjacks out there
this is the backup ball clown is playing over there's a crackerjack ball clown
oh it looks like cheese it's not sure if those are extra crunchy or not but look
like some cheese it's being had there there's outstanding stuff one of the
best snacks in the snack universe he leans into that one and Albertsons all
over it look at this oh no is he going he is going to award him first base
sweets is giving his argument from behind home plate look at this taffy's
coming at him taffy's trying to get that out but they never want to see a player
go after the referee and if we let taffy know how many times the Albertsons been
running to the bathroom he may not want to get too close yeah exactly you end up
tackling that man and you could get back to your feet with all kinds of mess and
we got another player thrown out look at this two of them are we gonna have
enough players for the clown or the circus they are running finishes game
they are running very thin at this point I believe right now they are at the
minimum for active players it is a total of meditation going on ten players
right now for the circus someone is trying to realign his center and find
his cheek Fred circus Fred circus has come out of the pen there's the right
fielder just standing up all that's good balance there not only good balance we
talked about you know some of the outfielders for the magicians not
staying engaged kind of taking a nap out there especially on left field you're
balancing on that box who ball you have no choice another player the ball one
of the ball clowns one of the three ball clowns he took the cheese it's cheese it
look out he's got that hey those are white cheddar cheese it's taken easy put
those in my red my second place so the ball clown has been tossed wait a second
is is that your salary for this game was supposed to be a box of white cheddar
cheese it is that the box supposed to be one of the parting gifts absolutely I
better not be my cheese it's I don't know if we're ever gonna get Gary grunt
back into this booth if he does not leave this venue without his cheese it's
in my contract box cheese it's every game for postgame meal and some people
said just an elixir storm huh hey you know some people said cavemen were dumb
no hey we met sign language pop to second base oh he's gonna let about he
wants to get the lead runner here oh look at the trickery as they get the
force smart play no clowning around out there right now great play by the second
baseman really well done that's David Honk who has shifted over to second
base he started this game out in center field it shows the diversity for the
circus first pitch comes high and inside off and stealing second base it is a
stolen base out there for the magicians and a reminder that if you want both
protection and freedom online that same kind of protection that you saw there
sliding in safely to second base click the link in the description and use code
Jerma it only gives you a whopping 83% off the regular price but also three
months of service totally for free that's surf shark oh is this we've got a
streaker we've got a streaker ladies and gentlemen he came up through the quad
through the gymnasium outside the field and onto the ball field now oh my
goodness you've got to be kidding me and you know what it for for any of those
fans Lee fans out there this is the type of stuff that you dream of the kind
of content that this man is going to have on his page is unmatched as he
slides in safely in the securities chasing after him and he just cannot get
anywhere near him look at it look at the speed from this streaker security he's
got to get in the gym yeah it's something written on his chest and
something about fans Lee so obviously a big fan wanting people to come to his
page to see his content he's in the dugout right now we'll see if he makes
another appearance is that being told by the booth at dump truck Danny a dump
truck Danny sighting you heard that right folks
dump truck Danny is in the house doesn't get any better than this all tied late
innings little flair shout out to right field hopping off the basu ball little
late break on it as he was trying to keep his balance before it got to him
one run comes home the magicians are back on top throw in the third base
there is no throw as they mishandled it how about that Maryland back on top
dump truck Danny getting a little spark for the magicians as they retake the
lead here in the top half of the seventh inning to be the bottom you know that
puts Fred circus on the hook now in this game circus comes into this game two
wins no losses but he has picked up two tie decisions on the year yeah a rare
occasion you'll see a tie in this game but it happens this this is don't adjust
your screen it's not reloading your twitch feed is not reloading that was
a strategy from the circus pitcher Fred outside two and one a swarm of beases
around the field I get a look at it now it's just the that drone we saw earlier
just been getting shots from above the park and base hit up the middle infield
pulled in with one out in the runner at third leaves a wide open hole up the
middle for Donald strange and he exploits it 13 to 12 Maryland on top of
California a good piece of hitting there help back up still going at it in the
locker room or the mascots look like another it's in a circle race fighting
it stopped over the chair over the training table a move just wearing them
out that is well done so that fight continues to twist and turn we'll keep
you updated what's going on down in the dugout talk about a royal rumble that
thing has been going on for quite some time and you know it's it's one of those
two when these two teams get together to watch those two mascots not only it's
all part of it you know the reason why these teams are one of the best in the
league is because of those mascots they have done their fair share of just
molly whopping opposing mascots all year long great matchup and the
streaker has made another appearance streaker's back oh look at him he's
haunting oh my goodness he's pulling those he's pulling Twix right out of his
package and chucking them at the security guard oh my goodness that's
even better ground ball to second base meanwhile the streaker backpedaling in
left field as the out is recorded for the second of the inning dump truck
Danny reading havoc out there I think this is just gonna have to happen as
the players continue to play here and dump truck Danny out left field still
having a good time I mean he is just baiting security out there look at this
free him three free dump truck Danny the fans have made their voices heard look
at this Albertson wants him off this field but I don't think it's gonna
happen a fans Lee all-star I mean you you just cannot say enough about this
guy that page has got to be just on fire tonight it's reminds me with this golden
thong if you remember a great baseball hitter in the major league baseball
named by Jason Giambi and whenever he would get into a slump or a teammate
would get into a slump they put on a golden underwear golden thong that's
very much like what dump truck Danny's wearing out there right now blast into
deep left field unicycling towards it he can't make it in time it one hops the
wall and the magicians have tacked on a third in this inning he turns on the
Jets thinking three and Martin majestic coming off the bench with a pinch hit
RBI triple what a majestic slide into third base we'll get another look at
this is roped into left field the streaker right now paying dividends for
the magicians as it really has the circus caught off guard here and it has
to be it really has to do with that golden underwear that's just flailing
around right off the fans Lee side and it's another hit by pitch this time
getting hit Albertson just beside itself can't believe it that another pitcher
would hit a batter here he's awarding for space now takes a look over into the
circus dugout you've been flushman and you know what he's probably gonna have a
sore ass tomorrow too yeah yeah we lost our asses out there between drunk drunk
dump truck Danny and these players getting rear-ended in the ass these
pitches this is escalating rather quickly and golden underwear guys
wearing it in the rear end coach Hanson went over to talk about why how come
nobody has been thrown out yet especially with all the umpteenth time
that these teams have been warned about hitting somebody and I believe the
response was they have no other players they can't throw anybody else out
Albertson once talked to the shortstop once to make sure everyone's on the same
page he's threatening to throw out again Harry helium Albertson doesn't want to
talk back it's an ump show now nice things to say all game long what's
going on back here oh they're they're wanting to know about the mascot fight
we've been showing you highlights throughout it's a royal rumble I'm not
quite sure which locker room but the Dumbledore mascot and the Dopey the
clown I've been going at it and Albertson is back again Dopey Oh to the
face oh my goodness I think if whoever wins this battle gets a run tacked on
to their trying to steal home they get them oh my goodness utter craziness
happening on both fronts oh my gosh look at this out with an argument here comes
joy handsome again he is so handsome he can't help but argue with a huge smile I
don't believe what I just saw in the locker room and on the field a steal of
home plate you don't see it too often what a play and good work by the circus
mascot here we go Dumbledore could be out that's a run that is a run for the circus so attack one
we'll talk to the score where people tack one on for the circus and that is
pulled back within two we'll be right back on JBA welcome back to car shield
field as you see germination out in droves here to take in this contest
between the Maryland magicians and the California circus that big nine run
inning in the fifth momentarily put the circus on top but the magicians have
answered back a back-and-forth grinder of a game and the pin gets California
another run so they're back within two after that mascot duel down in the
dugout yeah the battle of mascots the win goes to the circus so and now we've
got the streaker in a yoga session right now with some of the players getting
them stretched out this is the seventh inning stretch so it completely makes
sense that dump truck Danny would lead the some of the squad members in some
Pilates type yoga and you don't get a dump truck like Danny has for no reason
he is taking the clowns through his routine and look out for some of these
circus members on fans Lee after the game they will have certainly learned a
thing or two from dump truck and dump truck one of the finer instructors in
the country and you got to look out to you know I understand that that our crew
chief Elbertson might not be appreciating this but you never know how
many extra hot dogs are our guide dump truck Danny has hidden down in that
package yeah there's a look like too many maybe one medium-sized one but
we'll see you never quite know it hasn't been fully cooked yet still that's that's
made no one wants to know how the hot dogs made this one eat it you know the
raw dog does have a different volume you know it's we won't get into it it's it's
the Maryland magicians of 14 to 12 over the California circus we're trying to
play ball here so we don't have enough players for California I don't know the
rulebook but you were talking about get the magicians led right now send
somebody on loan as they do in European soccer loan a player to the circus see
what happens here kind of this is a tough situation I'm not sure what the
solution and Elbertson has a bat in his hands right now no no umpires about to
enter this game for California okay this is you know we've seen over the course of
this year but this is this might be a step far look at this now this is this
is true dedication to the league you know they don't have enough players he
says the show must go on I'm digging up some stats you know the JBA does a good
job of keeping random stats this is actually Elbertson's third at bat in his
career as an umpire so not unheard of that he's done this before he's over to
in his career let's see what he gets his first hit he bats from the right side
slightly open stance first pitch tried to frame it up and he calls it high
calls it you know that looked to be just underneath the letters for a call
striking Elbertson hey surprise surprise it's ball one ball one of course as
Albert to in the player at bat pinch hitting for the circus you know he
called another ball Elbertson may only have three at bats as an umpire but
he's hitting 238 so as good as the stats that they keep here for for the JBA the
math may be a little bit off look at this he's pulled it down the line it's
fair Albertson speeding past first he's thinking to throw comes in the second
oh he takes a quick turnaround in a good decision by crew chief Albertson he
rules himself safe at first now you gotta wonder if he's gonna call ball
strikes in the first base but a trickler down the left side found an open hole
pass the diving third baseman and into the outfield thankfully the left dealer
good you can see the wheels there good stop and track back there not sure if
he knows what to do with his hands quite when he's right I love the technique
it's like he's getting mad at the air he's karate chopping the air as he goes
around and it just fires you up so the up is on first base and he's calling
balls and strikes in there well he has a little bit better view from over there
is something that he told me I actually caught up with crew chief Albertson
before this game and you know I raised that question as we get another look at
dump truck Danny he's hanging out with with joy handsome and wonder if Joy's
rubbing off on him a little bit that'll up that that fans Lee page content even
more I gotta tell you dumpster Danny's double-dipping he's going he's seducing
the circus bench with hot yoga and now he's over in the magicians bench there
you see right there in the dugout there's dump truck Danny well you know
the ball found the ball players have been known to not be able to turn down a
dump truck easily and when a guy like Danny walks into your life it's just
hard to say no it's hard to say no and you know and he's doing it for a good
cause we got to free the ball handler outside bring one count here and not
only that fondling abilities really translates well to this game and we'll
see if you know he can give a few fondling lessons down in the dugout yeah
you really want to you know make sure to tickle it just a little bit look at it
look at the showboating down to second base and you know Albertson he wouldn't
have none of this from one of the players in the game yet here he goes
himself showboating on a walk down to second base I mean come on come on yeah
that's not something Albertson tolerates when he's behind the plate but now that
he's thrust into a position player role he has to play both roles now has to
play umpire crew chief and try score a run here for the California circus yeah
that may get lost in all of this we got a two run ballgame in the bottom of the
seventh inning these are crunch crunch time moments and don't forget to tune
into crunch time after this game that's our postgame show we'll get you updates
from other scores around the league and highlights and maybe even unpack a
little bit more of some of the craziness that's going on in this one yeah plenty
games around the league here tonight well I've crunched on the postgame it's
Tom chair but it's Dickie direct well have your highlights from all across the
league here in the JBA Victor vanish with the pitch to Percy polka dot and the
calls being made from second base Oh dump truck Danny get another look at
that scoreboard real quick see he's double-dipping he's going in between
benches given the each bench a little taste of the dump truck and you notice
how there is just zero protest from either dugout they are with wide open
arms welcoming him as we get called third strike caught off of second base
uh-oh problems in a run down oh he's gonna try to take third he's still
caught in the pickle he's headed back the other way he's chopping air
furiously great drop drop drop drop oh wait a second is there another ball out
there does Albertson know that he's out or safe let's see what he's gonna call
here he's been tagged out twice by two separate balls safe oh my goodness have
another look at this fans Lee brings you it oh you'll slide a hand but you would
expect nothing less from the magicians right back into his pocket unbeknownst
to Albertson and that's the kind of stuff that have made the Maryland
magicians a winning ball club year in and year out yeah and you got to wonder
if somebody other general managers managers are on the league and they see
Albertson playing such an impactful role right now maybe he'll get a call up and
this is a really big moment in this game we've seen some of the power cards that
have been played that have made a really big impact on this game and now with
Albertson running on the base pass for California down by two there's got to be
a lot of strategy being discussed there on the mound and we're seeing it right
now a new new elixir has been brewed by the magicians has been given to their
keeper or excuse me their pitcher they're pulling rabbits out of hats
elixirs out of bottles well you know and this is why I defer to the future Hall
of Famer Gary Grunt I wrote brought up the question earlier in this game is
that elixir going to be a detriment to this magicians team you said no no no
this is this is something that this team needs to be consistent with
throughout the game and we're starting to see that here now in the late in yeah
we used to live it by this and for the old cavemen you know the more elixir the
better oh finish just pulled another trick it's still in his hand oh the
tech comes from behind Albertson tagged out he didn't even know oh boy he
recognizes now there's two balls in play Albertson is privy to what's going on
here how does it turn out look at this the old two balls
oh same two balls change the drawers if there's anyone who understands that it
should be joy handsome after hanging out with dump truck Danny just seconds ago
I don't know if he's just telling everyone he has two balls or there was
actually two balls on the field either way you think that he would have to
understand and Albertson has made this a one run ballgame 1413 two ball track
others stricker and that is a dump truck if I have ever seen one my goodness
pretty flat though if you ask me I don't know nothing really happened it back
there you must see must have a dump truck must have come from a different
nickname if you know what I mean well you know Danny he's he's seen his career
really change over the years he's he used to have that huge badonkadon
now he's got to get it done in different ways should call him no ass
well we know ask Danny security thinking look this is my chance look at look at
Danny just haunting him yeah bring it on the dump truck says look I got a look at
that jiggle jiggle you know what his money don't jiggle jiggle it folds makes
you wiggle wiggle riding in his fiat oh my goodness thought this security
chasing him all game long in dump truck gets the piggy the piggyback ride he's
on the loose again you can't stop this he's just glowing right now with just a
sexy sweat Xavier McMagic has moved to the mound and in the blink of an eye he
has delivered ball one low some serious heat coming from the right-hander and
dump truck starting to look a little bit worn out now that stamina starting to
take a hit and certainly get a little buggy the dew point is high here in the
in the area right now is Xavier McMagic on the rubber now for the magicians two
point three one ERA three wins and one loss for the six foot two two and her
five-pound right-hander saw McMagic make some great plays in the field and
certainly that stamina is running down Danny dump truck a guy that's been known
to go all night long earlier in his career again that that career arc just
changing and progressing you have to learn to get it done in different ways
you know he used to be able to just make it happen any amount of physical force
needed all night long he could get it done he's got to do it in more subtle
ways now I can't tell if the security guards trying to play defense for the
magicians or he's just trying to work his way over to dump truck Danny and
he's on the move once again yeah Danny was not gonna be fooled by that security
guard not quite fleet of foot so back into the magicians dugout goes dump
truck and we had a strikeout meanwhile so two outs in the inning runner advances
to second base on that steel high chopper McMagic there hands it and oh my
goodness what would you consider that to be about feet to play the game oh my
gosh it's up there no doubt about it between that and when the circus catcher
ran over into the netting to get that foul ball but that's a great play right
we love that play by hunter sweets as well that'll do it here for the seventh
inning when we come back we've got the eighth coming your way you're watching
the German Baseball Association right here on Twitch we've got a one-run ball
game here at car shield field as we come to play here in the eighth inning fans
in the ocean of online content there's a lot of websites and little crabs that
can take your info without you even knowing it but you can swim under their
radar using surf shark VPN and oh my goodness you're gonna want to keep a
whole lot of stuff safe we got a fire show of sorts going on out here what is
this this this cannot this cannot be safe drones heading over there try to
get a fire off here he is fire breathing we talked about fire breathing dragons
we've got fire breathing circus it's a firefight oh my goodness and Albertson
just trying to get the batter up here magicians trying to figure out who
they're trying to send to the plate but look at this danger danger Will Robinson
oh my goodness whoa I've always wondered what they've you know put in their mouth
to you and obviously it's not gasoline is it or are they drinking gasoline and
then blowing it into his mouth I'd love to know what he's drinking and then
spitting to make that happen it's got to be ever clear and look at that right
some type of really hard-licking moonshine meanwhile dropping the bat
down on this one on high deep fly ball in a right field but Craig mystery has
put away with the fly out for the first out of the top of the eighth looks like
it's just water I didn't know water did that now you do water maybe that's the
elixir of life the magicians and as a don't try this at home kids you have to
appreciate another way for you to light that fire yeah a car being played here
it's the playing tag there are no force outs for this half inning so all outs
have to come via the tag and going to go back to the cavemen creating fire
absolutely was going through some cold nights on the road for the caveman and
we certainly could have used a fire starter like that on our squad for back
of the day maybe explain to the fans right now for those that don't quite
understand how difficult it is to leave your hut where you're used to being
where you're comfortable to have to go on the road and learn how you're going
to find a source of fire all these different things that cavemen have to
worry about well it's not for everyone and only the finest caveman can really
escape the cave so there's a couple of tests you have to take you know you have
to count to ten can you do your ABCDs can you sing twinkle twinkle little star
so there's a couple of things that you have to to get done before you can leave
the cave and I was fortunate enough to be blessed with just an undenying ability
to club the baseball as well as have a couple of smarts in my brain as well
the voice of Gary grunt future Hall of Famer as we had a scorched single the
second hit of the ball game for Ronnie Smith and look at this we got another
card being played this time by the circus oh beach balls and life's the
beach and we're gonna break them out so the opposing pitcher must use a beach
ball for this next how about this strategy only tagouts go to the beach
ball yeah brilliant move now we just need the beach ball so I don't know if
someone has a blown up how it comes out the magicians dug out oh how convenient
coach handsome bringing the ball out oh taunting you know joy he's no he's done
a nice job though pushing the line not getting too far on Elbertson's bad side
as we saw the circus just took it over the top in those middle innings
look at this defensive alignment yep they're thinking this is gonna be an
easy out the amoeba defense a knuckleball didn't quite make it to the
play pitch and it's a 30-footer oh no say just inside they call it a ball it's
a ball yeah it's so important with this beach ball you got to get the right
spin if there's any kind of slider or downward action on it you see you see
there he's not getting the proper backspin that's never gonna make it the
home plate can't get over the top of the ball right now and runner on third as
again all circus position players are in the infield at Fred circus he's
sitting at a three four five ERA but this beach ball is threatening to balloon
his ERA dump truck doesn't like it oh Danny's trying to get involved oh he
can't get it oh look at this Elbertson put a hand on him I think Elbertson just wanted to
get a hold of the dump truck Elbertson grasping for that dump truck as hard as
he can yeah I can't grab those dump trucks too sweaty right now too misty
elusive you got to watch out the the swamp ass factor is a big thing in these
kind of situations you grab anywhere around the waist it's gonna be tough to
corral let's just be thankful that the umpire Elbertson did get any of the
waste action because we could have seen a lot more than a golden thong oh my
goodness they're coming home with it he tags him out oh my goodness what a half
fitting the power cards being played it does not matter the California circus
are still alive going to the bottom of the eighth it's a one run ball game you
will not want to miss it what a play have another look as we go to break
that's up Chuck with the play we'll be right back after this on twitch and how
about that you make an amazing play in the field and right after that Manny up
Chuck 69 to the plate 69 ha ha ha we did a lot of that in my play in David the
caveman certainly no doubt about it and now the magicians have just been teepee
absolutely teepee to hell is that the new version of a being rick rolled
they've been they've been rolled there's no doubt about that up Chuck watches it
sail over his head there's a lot going on in tonight's game and you know that's
that's all part of it it's it's the level of focus that you bring in the
late innings in a game like this one run ball game toilet paper being thrown
people are getting pied in the face straight now a 90 mile an hour fastball
right at the knees just all in one games play here at the JBA by the way this is
jack port on the mount 8.76 ERA for the season as up Chuck tips it into the mid
69 not the correct number right now no not at all as you see ports numbers
their opponent average of 168 is whip at 110 that's exactly where you want your
numbers to be a successful to be if you want to be a successful pitcher up check
take strike three hates the outside corner
guys swing the bat you can't if you're if you're gonna wear a number 69 you
can't just go down without a swing no look you're gonna wear number 69 you
gotta have the cojones the big marbles to be able to swing the bat
speaking of big marbles he's loose again dump truck Danny I mean this guy you
almost feel bad for the security guard trying to keep this well you know what
I feel bad for dump truck Danny that I was dogging his stamina earlier in this
game look at this dude go he does hot yoga so he's got the stamina and people
don't realize just how sweaty you get when you do hot yoga dump truck Danny
has those pores just permanently open as this is booted it short and that will
allow him at first base to reach that's hairy helium dump truck Danny back at
it again look at this guy security guy just no chance for this look oh my that
is a beautiful job and you know what Gary you have to appreciate that yeah oh
here we go right right through into the cave there he goes and dump truck is
gone oh I see it's like a looney tunes Warner Brothers thing yeah you can't go
in sorry access D9 sorry that's only dump truck Danny's oh my look at this
that's dump truck Danny's territory no entering that cave I mean if bugs had
just a golden speedo it's dump truck Danny the golden speedo of love the
pitch comes in high sweaty nasty smelly love and let's not forget the role that
crew chief Albertson played in this game to keep this within reach for
California he was huge coming in when they didn't have enough players to play
this one's popped into foul territory third baseman going back on it and he
makes the play down to his knees well done and the Maryland Magicians now have
two outs in the inning here in the top of the earth see me the bottom of the
eighth inning mystery doesn't spend a lot of time on his knees but does a
great job here dump truck Danny knows a thing or two about that and he would
approve two outs runner at first base is Harry helium and now Paul Laffington
grounded out his last time up he's 0 for 2 that pitch gets away and helium into
scoring position now with two downs the game the game's potential tying run at
second base you get a look at that scoreboard it is 16 hits for the
Magicians as high as we get as high as we get it's 15 so as soon as we get to 16
they turned it upside down so I wonder if they get 17 hits is it the upside
down 14 they go the other way do they go back down and just put the numbers
upside down Harry we haven't seen this many runs scored in quite some time or this
many hits at least I mean this league is known for low scoring and really good
pitching but tonight that that storyline has been flown out the window you see
it with the point seven six ERA from Jack Port as he delivers a nasty one
underneath the hands of Laffington all he could do was foul it away and try to
live for another one into his account here it's something else that's that's
really important I think as a ballplayer you see that quick grab between the legs
in between pitches adjust your nuts adjust your swing that that's typically
the approach yeah pretty much you know you want to get comfortable and sometimes
you got long balls up there you got to keep it short I got to keep the wide
stance of the hang and you're just looking to make contact contact is the
key all the pickoff moving they got him in second base what a play the magicians
pulling out of their sleeve to get out of the inning fans this inning is brought
to you by fans Lee a spicy social network be sure to check out the link
and chat at the panel below to discover exclusive content from your favorite
creators back for more after this this is the J.B.A.
we have entered the final and ninth inning of a wild 14 13 ball game even
Elbertson starting to run a little bit short fused out here yeah there's been a
lot of antics which we are known to see here the J.B.A. sometimes they can get a
little too wacky and you know every man has its limit and Elbertson you know it
may have been reached right now you know I gotta say for a one-man crew chief on
an artificial field this is the cleanest home plate I have ever seen kept he's
done a nice job clean keeping the home plate clean you know you think that his
wife appreciates the cleanliness when he gets back home to the sugar mama
tonight salmon trying to bunt his way aboard to lead off this top of the
ninth but to no avail and Elbertson has injured himself and whoever he has to
come in for next will probably not want that injured Elbertson on their squat
shaking it off in the left hand I don't think we have an ambulance on site here
so you may have to make that call should it get any worse for Elbertson
this is Fred circus on the mound delivering inside one and one the count
fans another reminder that after this game we have got coverage from around
the league for you it's crunch time it'll be Tom Chairman joined by Dickie
Drek coming your way right after this one and that Mike salmon is contesting
that that one hit him in the arm now as he is acting as if it hit him in the arm
I thought it caught a little bit of his jersey but didn't catch him in the arm I
didn't think he saw that he sold it salmon has sold it we'll get a replay of
it here and Elbertson buying it look at it it definitely came inside right in
that armpit area and it may have caught him in the arm hit the left arm look
like you hit the back of his right arm so first base has been awarded ball
clown back on the field it's black up more balls for Elbertson you know that
was a little bit of a cheap shot from Elbertson I mean this guy has been
helping him out retrieving balls all game long and rewards him with a swift
kick to the nuts like I said every man has its limits and right now I think
Elbertson has reached his now he's going over to talk to the fans leadoff man has
reached in this inning and Mike salmon it's now Donald strange at the plate
here in the ninth inning and this one is driven in the left field going back on
it the catch is made for the first out of the unit good wood there just not
enough height underneath that ball to get over the left fielder's head and a
good play out and left field routine play for the left fielder here about ten
steps back position make that snag good play and there is the victorious
mascot oh yeah took it to Dumbledore earlier now he's enjoying the fruits of
his victory trying to distract his own picture apparently it's working after
a ball look oh that's maybe he's just giving crew chief Elbertson exactly
what he needs here well contact oh oh oh oh Dumbledore wants revenge oh my
goodness oh yeah that that turned rather quickly yeah this is supposed to be
family show apologize to the kids out there oh hammered in the ass the mascot
mascot love it happening here nobody wants to see that on live television
that's why they go to the internet for that stuff this is technically live
television on the internet that's the way you do expect it just another day in
the JBA some some people say backdoor guests are best inside with that bitch
borderline from Fred circus he removes the hat unhappy with the call here comes
another one this time it's outside and circus leaning can't believe it it's a
walk no three and one now big cut in a miss from Xavier make magic big magic
had the ground rule double back in the fourth inning the payoff is spoiled big
moments in this game one out runner at second base in a one-run game the
magicians trying to add insurance here in the top half of the ninth come for
the baseball stay for the mascot love it or should I say mascot humping that
one's filed off oh oh that was surely gonna hit the car over there would have
been a point the insurance claim yeah how did your car windshield break well
the JBA and pitch got filed off next thing you know if I replace my windshield
people would understand get a look over there oh the late swing but they call
ball for Wow they award him first base and look at this Fred circus not even
contesting that call I have no words for this that hunter sweets is just not up
in arms here runners on first and second for the
magicians in front here in the top half of the ninth inning Martin majestic came
in as a pinch hitter a couple innings ago he comes to the dish once again now
look at Fred big top he's like look he's one we are approaching a four-hour game
time here now Roger with us this JBA all-important game here playoff
complications on the line oh majestic taken by surprise by the pitch but it's
high ball one the next from circus in for a strike in majestic looking up
above his head high fly ball in the medium-depth center field towards right
center the catch is made both runners tag fire towards third base in the pick
unable to be made it skips over the sidewall out of play and home plate is
awarded it's a 15-13 magicians lead and that was a nice arm from out in
centerfield from David Hawk just caught it on the in-between hot yeah not this
kind of scoops you want to see from a third baseman there short hopped him
almost like a Roger Dorn he gave you the ole bullshit and you know they they may
get him some extra work back in the bathroom I know Albertson has certainly
provided some work for someone and we'll see if it'll be scoops over at third
base Sean giggles might not be laughing about that one after the game giggling
after that especially the run scores one and oh the count it's Roy Flushman
again as he takes up and throw down to second base it is a stolen base late
throw I believe that was Mitch Mick magic luring that throw kind of stopped
about three quarters of the way he did the 2-0 pitch pulled on the ground foul
down the third base side and ball clown to home plates lying fresh set of balls
gives a tweet of the horn it wasn't a fart that was a tweet long turn in a
pitch is fouled back out of play to to count here oh quick pitch try to catch
him off guard play made by the third baseman throw across is away and another
error on the circus there's gonna have to be some serious poop and scoop and
going on after this game for the circus oh my goodness he lost the ball doesn't
know where it is no one knows where it is we're all doing 360s out here
Albertson oh oh it's a pickle throw it back home he's caught in the rundown
it's another great play by up Chuck he has been on point defensively in this
game for the circus yeah a mental mistake there for the magicians opens
the door up a little bit here for the circus as they had an easy run there
instead of a three run lead it's now just a two run lead as Aaron base
running costing costing the magician just when you thought the magicians have
seen this one a million times they get caught off guard and that'll do it for
the top half of the night one last chance for the circus when we come back
you're watching the German Baseball Association on Twitch welcome back
entering the ninth inning of play we've got a two run ballgame the California
circus trying to get back into this one against the Maryland magicians I am
Storm Williamson joined by my partner here Gary grunt the Phoenix caveman
great we've been treated to some tremendous baseball tonight and you
would expect a fireworks finish in this one yeah a lot of run score with the
magicians going into this final half inning with a two run lead circus still
with a chance it could easily tie this one up we'll see if they can close it
out Paul at car shield field Paul laughing tin first to the dish he ducks
out of the way of all one still Jack port on the mound for the Maryland
magicians it's two and oh to laughing to make it three and oh not what you want
to see out of your guy in the ninth inning with a two run lead and three
straight balls your top closer you want him coming in pump and strikes oh my
gosh jackhammers that one but yanks it well foul three and one laughing tin is
over to ground it out his last time up in the sixth pops it up behind home
plate Flushman can't locate it and it'll land foul harmlessly it'll stay alive
here good work to take that all right yeah Austin lights catcher couldn't find
it three and to the count now to Paul laughing tin extremely shallow in the
outfield for laughing tin as he pops it up on the infield pitcher coming in for
it and makes the grab first out Jack board comes back from three and oh to
record the first out so the circus down to the last two outs need to find some
of that magic and steal it from the magicians and get it into their bats oh
we're gonna have another at bat here from look at this okay oh and we're
getting a power card played oh the power card 5x being played by the circus
manager the player at bat is allowed five strikes before they're out not three
strikes in your out it's five strikes and you're out for this next at bat saved
it for just the right time yeah near desperation mode you got to create a
spark and you know might as well give one of your better hitters a better
chance to put something in play take some packs as well so now Greg shake
that Laffy Taffy will have a couple extra strikes to work with check that it
is it's Albertson in the game he threw out the Laffy Taffy unfortunately
Albert's gonna hit again he's got the five strikes so it was one for one on the
day you see the umpires got five home runs on the air they could use one of
those right now to tie this game first pitch to him ties him up in nuts if you
saw that storm but there was a waft of smoke going home going on behind home
played don't know if someone's got the wacky weed going out the devil's lettuce
but pop fly on the infield again couldn't get to it dribbling towards
first base and that's why they are not professional basketball players he's
safe not a professional track player either as Albertson tripping over his
own feet down that first base line eventually did make it though good run
here but we'll watch the lack of form here from the umpire Albertson I mean
Jack Ford he nearly pulled that off it would have been awfully impressive but
you know Albertson for an umpire you think he'd understand that you can run
through first base sure yeah one would think but who knows what's going on in
the mind of Albertson how sweets would it be if Hunter after being plunked by
two pitches in this game ends up being the hero it's a fly ball in the left
field they were playing extremely shallow it's over his head look out
Albertson rounding second he's headed towards third the throw in from right
field is high Albertson is going for home nobody there covering a late throw
home and Albertson is safe we've got a one run game in advancing to third is
Hunter sweets with just one out I got just more impressed with some of the
shaving cream or the pie the face still Albertson out there still running hard
he's got pie remnants on his jersey pie remnants on his deck still able to make
it first at home great speed from Albertson you have never seen it look he's I can't
shake hand he's got he has to stay impartial so great job there from I have
never seen I have never seen better professionality from a from an umpire
in this league in all of my years in this I you know what Gary this is my
third year in this league I've never seen anything like that and meanwhile we
get another drive that'll split the gap in left-center David Honk has done it he
has tied us up 15 all this game it can't get any more bunkers we've had
streakers 15 runs now a piece this game is crazy and we were tied here with one
down in the bottom of the ninth inning extra innings looming here at Cardio
field and that was a drive right there great swing you know I feel like we
haven't seen a streaker in a while I wonder if he's gonna make another
appearance but you think he did provide a spark for the magicians and if you're
the you're the manager for the magicians coach handsome you're wondering where
that streaker is maybe get some of that hot yoga lovin and any ballplayer would
tell you nothing to spark a rally like a good dump truck sir one out runner at
second base line shot towards short it's off the end of his webbing into
centerfield and the throw into third base they've got him caught in a pickle
but it gets past his glove off the facing of the dugout so that nearly
would have been another run home in a potential game ender but instead we've
got runners on the corners with one down yeah a heads-up play to take that
third base on that left side the winning run now just 90 feet away that just ate
the shortstop up couldn't get the glove out on it and Aaron throw a good throw
just too much mustard on that bun and got beyond the glove of the third
baseman a fastball thrown by the center fielder third baseman unable to haul it
in so a fantastic chance here California circus to sneak in a victory
and come from behind victory they were down 8 to 2 at one point in this game
they were up 11 to 8 then they were trailed again and they tied it so back
and forth we go in this seesaw battle between the magicians and the circus
enjoy handsome is telling his team look guys I was standing on the top step step
of the dugout looking pretty up by two and now what have you guys done to me
handsome is as handsome does and right now the play of the magicians not so
handsome all knotted at 15 in the bottom of the night majestic man oh look at
this a whole bundle of bats for Sean Giggles and it looks like crew chief
Elbertson is allowing this I think it's a ten bat max moving can have so he's
still under the limit here and now they're gonna say the third baseman is
out in another hidden ball trick oh my goodness two down now the magicians pull
a rabbit out of their hat at the most crucial point of this game boy the
magicians Alliance is really gonna like that one the game winning run cut down
from third base now that game winner would have to come from first a heavy
batter here in a multitude of ways the first pitch comes in tall g-double-o-d-e-y-e
good eye good eye the pitch and he dribbles it back to the mound no problem for
Jack Port you gotta we've got free baseball you gotta wonder what the weight
of the bats you know implementer you know really affected that hit you'd have
to think a little bit as we get set for the 10th inning of play you're watching
the JVA on Twitch welcome back to car shield field in the extra innings of a
15-15 ball game and another power card coming out the start extras triple
vision there will be three pitchers on the mound for the circus here in the top
half of the 10th I've heard of the foreigner double vision but the triple
vision is a new one on me so we'll see how this affects the circus as two more
pitchers have been called in or see the effects the magicians is two more
pitchers will be called to the mound to make it a free spot and it will only be
for one at bat so this lead-off batter will have to face three pitchers
simultaneously
he's not on the roster let's see if Albertson will allow this I do believe
there are shorts and players need extra baseballs here as well the clown boy ran
out of balls leave it to the clown boy there's clown boy the great job of
replenishing Albertson's balls here tonight really been a big favorite of
mine throughout my years in this league just a model of consistency and one of
the all-time good guys in this league yeah it gets a lot of respect around the
league does a good job shining the bats rubbing the balls down getting them
ready for a BP and just doing whatever a clown boy can do to help the team you
know another one of those things that goes unnoticed who would rub these
balls down if it weren't for him nope I mean it had to be one of the players
maybe they had to rub their own balls so look at this first three pitches come
in and Albertson nearly wore three of them so so we got strike one as well as
a couple of balls delivered there so a two-and-one count here to Craig mystery
who is two for five in this game mystery hasn't been a mystery at the plate so
far so if it's a good wood on a couple of heads and had some bad ball luck on
the others just unmatched here they come oh he made contact one-on-ones in play
look out here and with the power card he still reaches first Aaron throw he's
headed to second base still ever retrieve that baseball mystery headed to
third and the leadoff man is just 90 feet away still nobody out waiting for
the throw and home oh but the other two balls are still in play
boy applies the time
oh you did all three balls only going at two of the three balls gonna have three
balls to complete the cycle oh my goodness how could they have forgotten
it look now this is this is unwarranted Hunter sweets taking his anger out on
clown boy clown boy was in the right spot at the right time yeah right spot
the right time he can't blame clown boy on this one and you wonder how that that
affects this the team chemistry moving forward I know it's not every day that
clown boy gets into the game but he's got to feel awfully unappreciated in a
moment like this I mean look at the way a hunter sweets ran into his own pitcher
and then he's gonna try to clown clown boy yeah you know come on come play
there's no climbing club that's just terrible so that should have been the
winning run but we're continuing here we're still in the top half yeah we're
gonna oh it's top half of the 10th inning here my bad it has been a long
night of baseball I will I just keep thinking I'm hoping Dumbledore is okay
I mean he got pinned in the locker room and just hope he's fine
he's found the elder one and that one's in for the call strike oh two and oh my
goodness everyone clearing the bench for the magicians oh my goodness this is bad
and the pitcher goes down in a heap Fred circus just clinging for his life what
is happening all the mascots are looking for one another oh they're taking their
mascot oh boy this utter chaos all the mascots are stripping down to their
skivvies and going at it every player from every from the magicians and the
circus are on the field right now how is Albertson going to handle this one he's
just tossing people left and right now the magicians have cleared the dugout
beer man is on the field fans have stormed the playing surface this is
insane boy the mascots are really going at a little hanky-panky play played right
now I have never seen a higher stakes game of hanky-panky in my life oh and a
big field goal kick of the clown mascot head oh and a takedown by the wizard
this is an absolute mess the crunch time is gonna have a one hell of a time
breaking down this game to see crunch time our postgame analysis coming right
after this yeah Albertson's called it Albertson has called this oh my goodness
we'll sort it all out in postgame this this is insane into the clown show this
game has been called it what really no surprise that this one would end this
way in 10 innings what a game we're gonna toss it to studio Tom Chairman and
Dickie Dreck take it away back to another episode of crunch time I'm Tom
Chairman and I'm Dickie Dreck and once again it's that time time to take a look
at some league highlights from today's games and boy oh boy it was a heck of a
day on the ball field indeed it was a doozy of a day Dickie let's dive right
in go to the diamond for the first game of the afternoon where the Delaware
drunkards dally with the Montpellier Mimes well fans were treated to another
classic matchup as the Mimes outfoxed the drunkards in all aspects of the game
as they usually do hitting pitching fielding and stealing pitcher Marvin
Mute was in marvelous midseason form pitching a true no-hitter and the
outfield posted another error-free game yeah it certainly didn't help that the
drunkards played true to form fielding only four semi-sober players against a
full complement of Mimes at least the drunkards have consistency going for
them with a record of one win and 39 straight losses their only victory
resulting from a forfeit on their home opener when the circus were forced to
forfeit due to their teen bus breaking down on the highway now let's move
across the country to where the powerful and primal Phoenix cavemen hosted the
lovely and long in the tooth Ohio old ladies it was yet another epically long
contest between these teams that we affectionately call beauty and the beast
the cavemen played true to form meaning all brawn absolutely no brains and the
old ladies were as always their charming generous selves valuing hospitality
camaraderie and friendship over competition as they usually do it's
really a wonder the cavemen survive in the league after so many years of still
not understanding at all how the game is played but there's no denying that
hitting is where their strength lies caveman left fielder Thronk and short
stop Booga currently lead the league in home runs and runs batted in and today's
game was another eight-hour ordeal with fans certainly getting their money's
worth as both teams had no issues with pace of gameplay yep the fans truly
appreciate the joy just all around Midwest Ohio niceness the old ladies
bring to the field every night have you Ohio old ladies are leading the league
in number of walks and strikeouts due to I say this nicely being very selective
at the plate also leading the league in number of times telling you you look
like skin and bones eat something but today fans were treated to a rare bases
loaded hit by Clara crinoline her hit forced old lady catcher Ethel Laflame
who was on third base due to a walk and then a block to speed toward home
unfortunately cavemen designated hitter duty was confused by the base runner and
mistakenly thought she was heading toward the dugout to steal his turkey
leg so he left out of the dugout to defend what he saw as his territory good
news is the umpire awarded Ethel home plate and Clara got her first RBI of
the season what a moment yeah real team player that Ethel what a spirit and
what a turkey like yeah the cavemen beat more than just Ethel they beat the
entire team in a 26 to 1 clubbing all right before we wrap up crunch time we
have some new details we'd like to share with you surrounding the all out benches
clearing brawl during the California circus and Maryland magicians game
today what a mess taking absolute mess you hate to see it the melee of merry
men as it's already becoming known or Jeremy Albertson did his best to quell
the two teams but for the history they've got against each other this is
quite a task a bean for a bean you said it both teams believing they're the
better but least appreciated entertainers this folly turn fracas
surpassed all previous skirmishes both benches cleared as did the bullpen and
the locker rooms and it's kind of unfortunate to note here what we're
learning now the magicians initially charged out of their dugout not with
any violent intent but seems desperately attempting to escape what looks like an
animal of some sort that got into their dugout what is that tensions flaring
that high it's no wonder the circus went right into action but again just
unfortunate to think of all the kids there too and the animals will soon see
how the league's going to respond but you have to figure at least a handful of
suspensions will come out of this debacle but that's all the time we have
to crunch today we'll be back tomorrow with more league highlights and until
then I'm Tom Chairman and I'm Dicky Dreck and you've been watching crunch
time