Well hello there, happy new year to some of you. At least those of you in EU.
We're not celebrating yet. I'm not ready to celebrate yet. It's only 7.25 pacific time.
I've got time. We're not on my time yet. But hello. We are early. We're going to start soon
for about five minutes. I don't want to just go live and then out here I've got the best
new character. No, no, no. We're going to take our time. This is going to be a long one.
I'm going to tell you right now. Let's just go over a few things while we turn the stream on.
Are you drinking? I drink four times a year. Christmas, New Year's, and weddings. That's it.
I can live a little. Early what the fuck? We're pretty early but we're going to just sit here
for a few minutes. What I'm about to tell you is, just listen. There are 26 categories this year.
Last year I think there were 18. Now some of these categories are fucking stupid, right? Let's be
honest. Did Worse Peter really have to be on here this year? Yes. I don't care if I don't say it.
It's going to be on here every single year. But there's a lot of categories to go through.
And at the same time, there's a whole Germania wrestling event to go through too. There are
eight matches including the Rumble this year. And there are, I believe, at last count,
55 characters in this year's Rumble. Well, in this year's card. Because obviously you can't
have more than 30 people in a Rumble. It's going to get a little weird. It's going to be mayhem.
There are seven matches before the Rumble. We're going to be here all night.
That's why I started early so that at 7 30 when people trickle in, we can just fucking get out
of here and get started. But hope you're having a good day. Hope you're having a good New Year's
Eve. I got like all these characters. I got all these cards in front of me. I'm excited. I'm very
excited about this. 7 30. You know, do face cam? Of course I will. I'll be full cam for a huge portion
of the stream. You know what I mean? I'm all dressed up too. I dressed up for this. I don't
just have a suit jacket on. Do a little fedora. No, no, no. I dressed up today. I'll show you.
I'll stand up and I'll show you the whole outfit. You better be in an Among Us costume.
You look like shit. I ain't even on camera yet. So you can't even say that. We're getting a ton of
community subs. You don't have to be doing this. 25 community subs from ChebIsDead. Thanks for the
25 subs. And we have so many. We have five from Juice, five from Skippy, five from Pink, five from
Jenny, five from 8bit, 10 from Onymos. All right. Sorry. I'm not going to read these anymore.
No more. I'm not reading any more community subs. I'll just make that really clear.
Fourslash just gave 50. No more. I'm not reading any more community subs. You guys are spoiling me.
We're not even in the new year yet. Thank you so much, everybody, for the insane amount
of community subs. But I'm no longer going to read them. I'm making that clear,
clear as day. He hates his community. No, I love this community. I don't want to see this community
go broke. Are you up in fart already? I was thinking about just trying as hard as I could
right there. Are we going to watch The Croods? No, I didn't have a plan on watching The Croods
today on stream. Why would I watch The Croods? Thanks a lot, everybody. It's unnecessary. You
guys are too good to me. Why not? I'm not going to watch The Croods. I don't even want to watch
that movie in my off time, let alone on the stream. That's not to say the movie's bad. I
just don't. I don't want to watch The Croods. Somebody typed the exact same thing as me. Is
that what somebody said? What did you type? I'm actually kind of curious. Are you sure it's not
just you on a second account? What about The Croods, too? No, I'm not going to watch either
one of those movies. All right. Are you ready? It's 730. I think it's time to begin the festivities.
What do you think? I did my hair. Or at least I tried to. Are we ready to begin the festivities?
No, hold on. Get a drink. Go get a drink. Go, go, go, go. Hurry up. I'm giving you one minute.
One minute. You're down to about 40 seconds, man. You got to pee. Go, go, go. Stop. Oh, stop doing
this. That's too much. That's too many community subs. That's way too many. That's enough. No more.
No more community subs ever again. After that one. That's a hundred from Repetio. That's enough.
That's enough. All right. I'm putting my fork down and I'm putting my knife down at the table.
All right. That's enough. You guys ready? Back from the bathroom? That's a shitload of money.
Thank you. I don't. Don't stop doing this. Stop doing this. Stop doing it. I demand it. OK,
here we go. I know how to stop this. I've got to get on camera so people can talk about how
well I did my hair today. So let's go ahead and do it. Here we go. Hey, look at me. All right.
Told you I dressed up. Told you I... Did I fly up? OK, it is. I got... I have like suit pants on,
guys. I'm not messing around. I got my bands. I'm ready. I'm ready for the new year. You look like
you're going through a job interview. I don't think you would wear these at a job interview.
That'd be a little weird, I think. I don't know if these would be on. Blue man... Yeah, it's
New Year's. It isn't New Year's. Don't you do blue stuff on New Year's? Or kind of? And guess what I
got? I'll give you a hint. It's a ring light! OK, that's so much. All right, let me explain.
The reason... All right, first of all, this says finally 21 on it. I don't know if you can see that.
It's 2022. I think that was on clearance somewhere. I'm over 21. But the cup is big enough
to fit a whole bottle of champagne. I don't want to be moving around. I don't want to go like
up and down and throw it into the refrigerator. No, I'm just... It's right here. I don't need to
refill it. Why would I need to refill it? I'm not going to chug it. You're going to make me puke.
I needed a glass that could fit the entire bottle of champagne, just in case I needed it. And it's
right here in case I need it. You like the decorations? Look, can you see? You see the
glow sticks on the ground? Spill joke? No, I cannot fuck around. This is prop comedy. This is... I'm
telling you right now, this is not... This is not prop comedy. I actually wanted this to hold this
much. And I know you're only supposed to do like that much, but I don't give a shit. I'm not a prop
comedian. If this spills, I'm going to have to like hire a professional cleaner to clean this whole
room. A professional cleaning company is going to have to come in because this is a whole bottle
of champagne. All right, I am excited. Are you guys excited to find out some of the things that
we've voted on for the last five or six days? I am up right now. I'm very excited. Where's Otto?
Otto is in the other room and he's lying down and he's very happy. I didn't want to move him.
He's in his Sunday best. You want me to stand up? Should I give you the whole thing?
I'll give you the whole thing. I'll give you the whole thing. You, hey, you, yeah. I know you.
All right. Messing up. He looks like a youth pastor. Let me tell you about the dangers of alcohol,
boys and girls. This is just grape juice. This is grape juice. I've had this shirt since I was
like fucking 19 and it still fits. That should be a good thing to all of you. I should be able
to flex that. I've had this shirt since I was like 20. Wow. Do I still have that body? You know what
I'm saying? Even though this is a little big and I got like a pregnant stomach, if I suck that in,
well, I'm not going to spill it. All right. First. All right. Listen to me. We've got a lot to do.
I can't stall anymore. If you're here, you're here. If you're not, you're not. Welcome to the
stream, everybody. A legendary spill joke in the making. Don't even fuck around like an idiot.
We have, we're going to start now. We're going to start, we're going to do like three or four
categories. Then we're going to move on to do a couple of matches. And then we're going to kind
of go back, bounce back and forth. So the first category we're going to do, this is a good one.
There's so many categories we got to go now. Otherwise I'll be here till four in the morning,
Pacific time. What time is it? Bingo. Our first category is best new character.
We've seen a lot of new characters this year considering some of the larger streams that
you've seen on this channel. And we can just go ahead and get started. Ladies and gentlemen,
here are the nominees for best new character. And I'm joined by Josh from ScienceCenterNevada.org.
Josh, good to see you. So, um, I guess as a archeologist, you could probably give us a-
Well, wait, wait, wait. This isn't archeology. It's not?
No, we're, we're dealing with rocks. Oh, okay.
Archeology is people stuff. Rock stuff, that's geology.
So this is, this is not archeology? Not at all.
Come on out. Catboy German.
Where, where am I? I need to wink into this. Ow, my head, my brain just hurt.
Hi. Hi. I, I'm assuming that you're, you must be the maid. I heard you ordered a sexy maid service.
Why don't you grab a piece of bread? I want you to eat. Well, I've been cleaning. I wouldn't dare
touch it with my hands. Right. But if you just, but just eat with wash your hands and then eat.
I'm not putting it in your mouth. Right. No.
The name's Amelia. It's Amelia. Amelia. Okay. Amelia. Thank you. I appreciate it.
But I need to come out of the shower now. That's a good one already. That's a good one.
It's like a little guy. Oh, I'm sorry. Ow, my face.
I'm really sorry. I didn't mean to. Don't do that again.
Okay. I won't. Oh, no. My God. Oh, my fucking God.
Huh? You want to do what? I don't know. I'm not going out there. What the fuck am I?
Hey there, you're in deep shit. Yeah.
How about Strong Henry? Strong Henry Flush. Just fucking break his neck.
Break his fucking neck. Just kill him. You got voted off. You're up. Goodbye. He's done.
What? What are you doing? What are you doing?
This is my no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. This is my house. I'm like,
why am I hiding outside of my own house? I'm hiding. I need to eat out of that peanut
butter later. No, I'm not going to. I'm not eating out of that peanut butter.
All right. This is fucked up because I feel like this person is like their boogers just
go right into their mouth. That's fucked up. If this person's asleep on the train
and they have a runny nose, they're just pooling the runny nose directly into their mouth.
No, this doesn't look like. Oh, my God. This does not. Somebody said this looks like
Adam Driver. What are you talking about? How do you see Adam Driver? Adam Driver is like a handsome
dashing man. What are you talking about? Dude, that is zoom in on you. I know who had my vote.
I know who had my praying mantis baby decided to sit up here and stay here. Take a look.
Look at how look at how big our boy has gotten. He stuck around for the whole four months and then
one day he just wasn't there. Oops, we're live. Sorry about that. Oh, yeah. There were a lot of
new characters. There's a lot of every his thing about every category had so many nominees.
We had to drop. I'll just tell you, I think there were 200 best and worst noise nominees.
How do you even narrow those down? Like it took it took a week straight of narrowing that down.
And there's still like 25 nominees. Anyways, the winner, ladies and gentlemen, of best new character.
Let me do that again. With 35% of the vote, ladies and gentlemen, the winner,
Catboy Jerma. Amelia came in at second at 18% and the shadow movers at 13%. This also was the
least skipped question. Almost everybody, almost everybody answered this. Catboy Jerma. Here you
go. I'll give it to you. Take a look. Best new character, Catboy Jerma. It was a landslide.
It was just an absolute landslide. Um, oh well. I like to see when they're close, you know? Oh,
well. I love Catboy Jerma. I voted, I voted for, I voted for Cromwell. All right, we're going to do
this one right now because this one's stupid. Cromwell was robbed. Ah, let's fucking go.
I don't even want to do this category. Uh, the next, we're going to go, let's just do it now.
The next category is best ooh ooh. And if you don't know what that is, that is the first boss
in the Simpsons arcade game. It's a noise that he makes and I just can't stop doing it. Uh, I just
can't stop making the sound. So instead of having this show up like 10 times in best and worst noise,
it was just removed and gave its own damn category. I've apparently done this so many times
that it had to have its own category. Let's just go. The nominees for best ooh, ah, you know,
just, here it is.
Here comes a rage stream. Watch out.
Can you please spell the sound? It's just ooh. Oh, just spell it.
Ooh. Oh, the category is best ooh. I, this is not, I didn't put that for a category.
So ladies and gentlemen, the winner. I thought like embarrassed me. I like turned red.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of best ooh, ah, you, ooh for this, uh, this year.
We probably won't be back, but we'll do it for 2021. Wait, that's cute. The winner is,
this is like a three-way tie. I don't even remember which ones these were for a three-way tie
pretty much between rage stream, which was the resident evil six one spelling explanation,
which is the one where I was explaining it during monster rancher. And then the real voice one were
just me saying it. Look at that. It was a 50 vote difference, 25, 25. It's cause it's all the same
sound. It's literal. Hold on. I want, where's real voice. I probably should have had a clip
for who won. Who cares? Okay. All right. We'll do one more. Then we're going to get to two more,
two more. We got a long way to go. How much was that skipped? No. All right. Coming up next,
we have rumble stuff. We have wrestling stuff to do too. So I'm this 26 fucking categories.
Best accident is coming up here. Uh, that includes spelling something. That includes
doing something I probably shouldn't have done on camera. There's been a lot of those over the
years. They were quite a few in 2021. So this is for what you have decided was the best accident
that has happened on this stream. And surprisingly, one of them didn't make it.
We'll find out which one best accident nominees are these juggles. Oh, how do you guys think about
that? What do you think? That was a good play. I know what you guys want. I know what you're
looking for. I drank two Gatorades before the stream. This context for the people that don't
know what that is. This context, I promise. Does anybody else feel a slight breeze?
They saw me having sex with death in my bed. And I just want to say that that's not me. That's not
me. That's not who I am. I don't have sex with like three different people and like lie to everybody
as of a week ago. It was three days ago, but that's not me. I'm not. That's not who I am.
I woohooed him. We can't say that word. That's foam. Time for a foam party. But again,
this sucked. It got in the eye again. How? How did that happen twice? Spray it in the tub,
in the tub, in the tub, inside. How did this happen twice? You know what it looks like? Have
you ever seen those, those optical illusions where it's like the huge guy is standing here
and there's like a tiny little person in the corner and it's just like, oh wow, oh my god,
this is, and they're in a room and the furniture looks all weird. Like it's because the room is
like 50 feet long and it's like slanted. That's what's going on here. Cause look at, no, I'm
normal person, but when I go back here, I don't know why. I don't understand. It looks so bizarre.
Whatever. People are very, very ignorant of dead ringer spies. They never check and they always
lose their ground. So I get that sniper. I get this scout, pull the dead ringer out. We turn around
and we try and do it again. God damn it. Get the cat, get the cat. Come on, keep going. Move.
You're almost there. You're almost out of the range. You're almost out. You're almost out. You're
almost out. You're almost out. Good, good, good, good. Oh, thank God. Thank God you made it.
What does this guy look like? There. All right. There you go. You got what you wanted. Everybody
that was here, you got the imposter is fucking stupid ass subspace that you got it. I did. I
just realized that's what I just did. There it is. You've been asking for that for like two hours
and I didn't, I just did it. God. See what I'm talking about? This guy just rolled that guy.
That guy just rolled that guy up in a burrito and ate his ass off. That guy just rolled that guy
See what I'm talking about? This guy just rolled that guy. That guy just rolled that guy up in a
burrito and ate his ass. Ate him. I ate him up. I swallowed him up. I swallowed him up. And I
killed him. There's so many of these. Holy shit. All right. So there's your accident nominees for
best accident. Look at these. Look at how cute these are. The winner for best accident 2021 is
I keep making it. I keep muting the fucking goddamn thing. Have I ever streamed before ever
in my life? It's been like 12 years. The winner. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The juggles zerk with
25% of the vote. It was just, all right, listen, but I'm not gonna, let me tell you who the,
let me, let me give some context. I made up this guy named juggles who streams like a streamer.
And what he does is he drinks like a bunch of Gatorades and just like goes on IRL just chatting
like we are now. And he fucking shakes his stomach and all like the liquid sounds pick
up on his microphone and people like donate money to him and shit. And it looked really,
really weird when I did that on camera without the bottom part. There's your context for all
the new viewers. There's a lot of people here. In second place, sex with death at 16%. And then
cat meteor, cat meteor at 14%. There are your top three. There they are. That one ran away with it
too. We're going to do one more and then we're going to move on to wrestling. I got a lot.
This one's best POG face. Instead of worst face, we added a category called best POG face.
Do I even need to run the video for this one? Honest to God, do I, I don't think I, do I even
need to, I don't think I have to run the video. I mean, I'm going to because like I, uh, uh,
Dazzle made a bunch of awesome videos for this. But I mean, like, I think it was like 60% of the
vote won this. You all know what it is. But just let's watch it. Best POG face of 2021 incoming,
hear it out. That one was pretty good too. I will say too much and I just put a kink in my neck.
Oh, dude, the thing that everybody onion, onion ring. I got an onion ring.
Where are my manners? Sonic meat knuckles. Please welcome the chief creative officer
from Epic games. Donald. What happened? Right. Okay. Okay. Drum roll, please.
This is fucking crazy. Hey, the winner. This is the, by the way, this is the most,
this is the most ever that something has ever won in the four years annually. We've been doing
this for, oh, you couldn't hear it. I, I, I took the audio off. Sorry. It was muted. I was doing
the drum roll. Fuck. What the fuck, man. Maybe look like an idiot. Okay. With 58% of the vote.
That's the highest we've ever seen was the onion ring, the onion ring. Slime rancher two reaction
was 9% and then treasure map was 8%. This is also one of the least skipped questions. 58% of the
vote. That's almost everybody. And there were like 20 plus thousand responses or something,
at least 18,000 responses. So that's ridiculous. I can't believe that. That's actually crazy.
All right. Now we're going to do, we're going to take a small little interlude away from
the categories. We got through four. We got a long way to go. We're going to start the
Germany event. We're going to do two matches. Then we're going to come back and we're going
to do worst face when we come back. So I'm ready to go. Now everybody, I need everyone's collective
energy here. Please. Everyone put your hands together and pray. All of you. That this does
not crash. Everybody, we need all of our energy. There's 30,000 people here. I need collective
energy that the game won't crash. Because holy shit, there's like 60 characters inside of this
universe mode right now. And it's really having a, it's, it's struggling a lot. Please pray.
Please pray. I'm going to move this over here. We are about to start. Just give me one second.
Everybody pray. Please pray. Are we praying? Our first matchup is going to be a tag team match.
Can you hear it? Let's hope you can. I think you can. It's going to be a tag team match.
You'll see who the entrants are. Let me, everybody pray. You praying?
Germania 2021 can help again. There's so many characters this year too. Here we go. It's
loading. It's loading. It's loading. I think we're good. Yes, we are good. Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Germania 2021. My name is Germa985. How are you? Welcome to the show.
We got quite a big one for you here. Eight matches, including the rumble.
Our first match. What the hell is that? Why was it so huge? And why is the Statue of Liberty here?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I just saved the whole stream. I just saved the entire fucking stream.
It just leaked everything. Everything is on the screen right now. Every match,
every participant. I just saved the whole stream. Thank God. Here we go. I can't show the screen
because there's a leak. Holy shit. I'm so glad I did that. That would have been a disaster.
Huge thanks. I got to get, wow, this is loading. Tag team match 2v2. I would call this one a scary,
scary match. One would call this one a horrifying match. Horrifying.
Uh, Opster. I got, here we go. Let's, let's shout everybody out. Opster, Leather Jacket, Kroski,
VR Josh. Huge shout out to you guys. Uh, this doesn't happen without them because they made
literally fucking everybody. Like I didn't think I was going to be able to get to do a rumble this
year because I've been so busy with all this other shit. Everybody seriously like, okay,
here we go. Here we go. Huge thanks to those guys. This is literally, this does not happen
unless they do it. So huge thanks. Are you ready? Let's go. Coming up first,
we have, uh, Chris Redfield in his, uh, I think that's, uh,
in his official, uh, star's uniform. Chris Redfield. Chris R. Chris R. Chris Redfield.
Those of you that know, uh, one of the most classic meme videos I think I've ever seen.
Now who is Chris Redfield's partner? You're probably asking. You're probably wondering.
Well, that's easy. Was a big fan of Resident Evil 8. Thought it was a potentially game of the year.
Got the Grotto Beast chairs, which is really cool. His partner, Lady Dimitrescu. Lady Dimitrescu.
Lady Destro- I think I spelled the name wrong too, by the way. I can't even see the chat now.
Shit. My computer crashed. Am I still live? I hope so. I'm going to open up on my phone. I
can see chat on the phone. Yeah. I can see chat on the phone. Oh, hell yeah. Perfect. Yep. I can
see chat right here. Perfect. I think, uh, I think Lady Dimitrescu is as big as you can possibly make
a wrestler. I think she's like eight feet tall. I have no idea. It's going to be insane. So who
are they fighting against? You're probably wondering. Well, a couple of fan favorites,
I think. One in particular is a very large fan favorite. You're not even live. I'm live.
Jigsaw. I love how that takes up the whole screen. Jigsaw's 200 pounds. Jigsaw and someone else. And
can you guess who that someone else is? Who would be the perfect, terrifying, horrifying partner to
Jigsaw? I'm going to tell you, you're going to have to be careful here. I mean, a lot of us are
going to think this is really funny, but money is going to die. And there's nothing I can do about
that, unfortunately. Jigsaw's partner in the tag team match is none other than, then, then, then.
WWE 2K likes to do this thing where it loads the next thing. The horror. Don't look at it. Don't
look at it. Don't look at it. It's hilarious. I know, but turn off your screen for a few minutes.
So we've got Lady Demetrius and Banana Chris Redfield versus Jigsaw and the horror in the
first match. Just to get us started here. I don't think there's any extreme rules or anything. This
is just to get us going because there's too many characters. I am going to say we could probably
get predictions going too if we want on some of these matches. I would start it now if you could.
Horror. I am peeping hard. And here we go, ladies and gentlemen, the first match.
I feel the power. Chris Redfield, Jigsaw, tag team match and begin. Welcome. So if you want to
look at everybody's stats, everybody is pretty much in the same stat category. Some people are
stronger than others, obviously, because they are stronger than others. Jigsaw's starting to get
off with it. Chris Redfield is barely even doing it. Going to tag out already. Peeping the horror
at the very first 5 to 10 seconds. Not confident. Oh, the horror with a horrific kick to the stomach
as he pummels into Chris Redfield's midsection, going down to a knee.
Now, the tag rules apply here. You cannot come into the ring unless you're tagged in.
Otherwise, you're disqualified. I need to start making referees. Big bear hug here by the horror
on Chris Redfield. Did he just tap out? I hope not. With a thunder clap to the ears. Oh, my god,
the horror does not care at all. Going to go for the next snap. No, he's going to go for the ear,
right ear scrunch. Maybe a power bomb. No, spinning neck breaker from the horror.
Lady Demetrious goes for the tag. Here we go. Now, this is an even match. We've got Lady Demetrious.
Oh, no. Caught it. Both enormous wrestlers. Lady Demetrious, I think, is the highest you
can possibly make a wrestler. A horror might be as well. Jigsaw going to come in and wants
to play a little game here. How do you even do a move to somebody this much bigger?
I guess like that. Chris Redfield's out on the outside. There are rules in this fight.
I love where the banana is on Chris Redfield. It's perfect. Jigsaw is really timid.
Honestly, I would do the same thing. Why would you ever fight when you have this demonic,
otherworldly, godlike character that can just go in? The two humans are letting the two demon
people fight, which is, I think, a great strategy. I'm going over to the ropes.
Going to go to the top rope. Did she get it? She got it. Chris Redfield in the ring now.
Horror up on the turnbuckle. I'm an idiot. Why would you do that? Knee to the face.
He's throwing. I know. What the hell? Big right hand by Chris Redfield. Caught it. We got momentum
here from Banana Chris Redfield. Setting him up to a seated position. Going to go for the...
Going to go for the... I don't even know what this is. I don't even want to say what I think
it is. I don't know. He was like squishing his head. He's going to do it again? No, he's going
for that CQC that he learned at the Starz training facility. No, no. He's bumping into
and attacking Lady Dimitrisu. Horror is in a bad place right now. Lady Dimitrisu's got him in a
crab. Will we see a tap out from the horror? I hope not. Oh, it's going to be close. No, big
reversal by the horror. Momentum shift incoming possibly here. Oh, he's grabbing it by the face.
She's peeping. She's peeping the horror right now. That's all she can see. That's it.
No, wait a minute. Oh, big reversal. She's got him. Almost threw him over the top rope. What a
huge comeback. What an absolutely insane reversal. No way. Huge. Absolutely massive.
You don't peep the horror and live. Although a little bit of a reversal here. Chris Redfield
may be going to go for some kind of tomfoolery on the top ropes here. No, Jigsaw's coming in.
He just tagged him into pin. What are you doing, Jigsaw? What are you thinking?
Oh, we're going to see a breather here. No. Punching her in the stomach, but it did not
faze her at all. She is a demon. Jigsaw's just a guy in a suit and it's not even a guy. It's a
little toy thing. This match is going longer than I thought it was too. This is actually pretty
exciting. Big toss across the ring. I wonder if we're going to go see a finishing move here.
No, let's see. He's telling him to leave it alone, Ethan. Yep. I think he's getting ready to use.
You better leave it alone, Ethan. I think he's right here. He's going to go for it. Why does he
keep doing the same move? He just keeps kicking him in the chest. The horror is reaching so
desperately and it cannot reach even though he's huge. Oh, no. German suplex number one.
German suplex number two. German suplex number three. You're not getting up from that one.
Just destroyed. Oh, reversal. Got to get him out of there. Yeah. Jigsaw's got to get out or it's over.
No, he broke it away. I love how Chris Redfield just kicks people. He just puts them on the ground
and kicks them in the back of the head. No, no. Trying to go for that submission move.
Jigsaw is throwing right now. Jigsaw is pretty weak. This is really balanced right now because
Peep the Horror is really, really powerful. Going for the armbar. Is he going to get it?
No. Hold on for dear life, Jigsaw. Can you do it? Can you stay or is it over? No help from horror.
Peep the Horror doesn't even care. All the while, Demetrius is getting health increases as well.
Recovering lots of damage. Going for another one. Going for that. Going for another armbar.
That's all. The horror. Broke it up. Beautiful play by the horror. You can't let that happen.
He's a trained military professional. You can't let him do those moves.
It's over if you do. What is going on? That could be it. There's one. There's two.
Oh, that was close. Was that it? No, he didn't get it. He didn't do three. He only, what's going on?
He only did two. He did two and a half. Chris Redfield on the top rope. Okay. Okay, just pin
him. Pin him and let's get over, get it on with. Give me a fucking break. Yes. You know, there's a
match to win. There's a match to win and he's on the ground right now for you to pin. But apparently
you don't care about that. Chris Redfield just going for some taunting and that's going to be
the downfall. Could have had the victory right there. Jigsaw now doing the same terrible move
he did earlier, which is a series of really weak punches to the chest, which don't even hurt.
It's the equivalent of when a little kid throws like a magic wand at you and you pretend like it
hurt to make them laugh. Exact same scenario. What is going on here? Why are they going outside?
There's no count outs. Oh, there is count outs. What are you doing outside? He's just grabbing
his head. Submissions do not happen outside. Even if it works, he could hurt him. I think a count
out is 10, I believe. This is bad. Get back in the ring, Harv. What are you doing? Oh, this is
going to be it. That's it. That's it. He's going to get counted out. The referee's slowing the
countdown apparently. That was the longest eight I think I've ever seen in the entire time I played
these games. Why are you out here counting yourself out? Is this double elimination? Two?
What are you talking about? That was bullshit. That was so messed up. Why did he start the count
over? The horror is not in good shape. He thinks he's out of energy. Jigsaw does not even want to
put a hand out. This is a bad team situation here. He won't even put a hand out. Bad blood
forming here between horror and Jigsaw while Chris Redfield's got him in a power bomb.
That's bad. Quadruple power bomb. Unless Jigsaw does something about this, this is the end here.
That's it. One, two. Finally, Jigsaw decides to do something. He doesn't even care about anything
else in the whole match. Oh, that's it. That's it. He's got him. He's got him. He's got him.
There's no way the horror. That's it. Game over. Chris Redfield, ladies and gentlemen, got him
in the arm bar. I told you he was militarily trained. You got to watch out for that one.
I don't know what they were doing in the outside. It was stupid. Why would they not count?
That was really strange. There are your winners. Chris Redfield and Lady Demetrius. Sorry, sorry,
hold on. Demetrius. Weird that they did. Oh, they're getting booed. This is a huge boo.
All right. We're going to move on to the next match really quickly. We're going to do two
because there are eight matches, so we've got to get through these. We're going to move right
onto the next one. I don't want any spoilers, so we're going to go back to full cam here for
just a second. That was kind of an upset. I think a lot of people expected the horror to win that.
Let me go like this real quick. Hopefully, this doesn't crash. I hope not. Please,
God. I know I've seen a lot of boos. Yeah, a lot of you guys are not happy about that.
All right, next match. We're going to keep moving forward. This one's going to be wacky.
Uh, I get to see it. You don't. Here comes a payout. Yeah, if you bet on that, then yeah.
Why does he have a urinal in the side, in the corner of his room? It's like a fan, man. It
gets hot in here. It's Las Vegas. It's a fan. All right, the next one coming up is a four-way
extreme rules match. Anything goes, any weapon, any way to beat your opponent. I'm looking
forward to this one. This one's going to be fun. Here we go. Ladies and gentlemen, match two of
Drew Many at 2021 is incoming just as fast as this year went, it seems. Here we go.
Fatal four-way. Uh, this one is, uh, first contestant is Armin, Aaron Armlet.
So good. Uh, we have Armin from Attack on Titan. You might be able to guess what this fatal four-way
is, maybe after the next contestant. Uh, but yeah, we have Armin, Aaron Arlet as the first
contestant. I love this character so much. Somebody got it already. I'm surprised that you,
uh, could call it already. This is the battle of the sounds. We've already seen one of these
categories this year. No spoilers, but it's the battle of the sounds. The next contestant coming
up, Lala dog. Lala. That is their name. That is actually technically their name. Don't try this
at home. Please don't. You're going to get hurt. So we have Aaron, Lala, and who else could be in
this fatal four-way of the sound effects from 2021? That's the worst character. Yeah. I mean,
they're all pretty bad. They're all the worst character. I actually think they are. I think
they turned out great. Everybody in the whole, every rumble is, whoa, every rumble is worst
character. The hell was that? Who is the third contestant? Let's find out right now in our battle
of the sound effects. Lala is pissed at this entrance. Who is it? All the way from the
Simpsons, the Simpsons arcade game. This is actually their name. It's Warner Van Braun or something.
It's the oon or oon guy. It's the first boss of the Simpsons arcade game. Still one more person to
go. No, it's, are you, people are hooing Warner right now? Are you kidding me? We're getting a lot
of hoo mega lols right now. That, that's not, what are you talking about? This is where that,
this is the oon or oon guy. This is the guy that makes that noise. How dare you? Our final
contestant I think is going to really make people a little angry. Some of you are expecting somebody
else and that's not who you're getting. Who you are getting is oops. It's the wrong outfit.
It's the Tasmanian devil. It's the wrong outfit though. I put, I put the wrong outfit on.
Uh, they're, they are going to look a little different when they're in the ring,
but it's the Tasmanian devil. It's, no, I promise it's not the worst character. I screwed up.
I messed up and I'm, I, it won't be there. Make each sound? No. Welcome to Tasmanian devil. This
is the battle of the sound effects. Uh, the sound effects I probably did the most this year. Besides
doi doi doi, doi doi doi robbed. Well, that's too bad. Wait till 2022 is rumble. Uh, there are no
rules in this match. You can hurt each other as much as you want, which I mean, who really cares?
Hopefully somebody throws a fucking table at somebody's head. We have Armin, the la la dog.
And the Tasmanian devil. There we go. There it is. Hardcore match. Bring it on. Nothing
matters here. It's just a battle to the death. The first person I, is it, I don't think it's
elimination. I think it's just whoever pins wins. I'm not sure you can do predictions on this one
either. Oh, already outside the ring, la la dog. The two animals are fighting outside.
It's bizarre that the la la dog can handle the Tasmanian devil considering the la la dog is,
I'd say 150 pounds lighter than a Tasmanian devil. Maybe not. You're not going to end it already,
are you? No. La la dog, I would say was worst, most hated sound effect I did when I first did it.
And turned out to be everyone's fan favorite now. Uh, it gets requested. He's breaking Armin's neck.
I get requested to do la la more than any sound effect. And all you hated it when I first did it,
so. Sorry that, you know, you need to trust me. I thought he was going to punch the referee in
the face. And out goes Tasmanian devil to the outside of the ring. Now we're going to, ooh.
I'm sorry. If I get to, it's 2022 in like four hours. Let me have this for like another hour or
two. Just for like another hour. I promise I'll try not to ever do these sounds ever again.
This is my way to get it out of my system and never think about it again. So let me just get
over it. I'm hoping we see some weapons here. Maybe Armin might take out his, uh, his. God,
I've seen the anime and I know everything about it. I just don't know what they're called.
The stuff that they wear when they attach it to trees and they fly around.
There's an O. Oh, he's going for it. What's he going to get? He's got himself a stick.
And he missed completely. Missed completely again. Armin was never a fighter.
Armin was always, uh, the brains and the strategist. He was never the one that picked
up the sword. Two complete whiffs. We're paying a lot of attention to outside, but not the inside
and what's happening. They keep just throwing each other. Big pot. Holy shit. Oh my God.
He just threw him across the ring. Going under is actually, is ooh, ooh,
going to get something from under the ring. Is it going to be a bat?
Is it going to be a, what are you doing? You can't find what it's, what are you stupid?
There's like a hundred items under there. He's got a bat. He's got a bat.
Oh my God. Useless. Four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Ooh.
You gave him a neck massage for 15 seconds. Oh no. Don't let him win right now, please.
Armin's got the kendo stick. I think he hit him both. I don't know. Armin, you're supposed to,
come on Armin. You're not supposed to be aggressive like that. Two weapons in the
ring right now and ooh, ooh, ooh on the Lala dog. Now on top punching him in the face over and over
again. While the Tasmanian devil's in the corner and Aaron. Oh, big move by Aaron. Armin, whatever.
I think we're going to see potentially some weapon usage here. Oh, he missed. Big whiff
right there on the Tasmanian devil. Kicks him into the groin, I think. Big clothesline by Armin.
Oh, the dog has a weapon. No, doesn't want to use it. He tripped. I think he just tripped over it.
Reverse chin breaker there. Big DDT. Now you got to hit him in the head with the bat and then you
got to pin him. Everyone's so tired right now. But no, take him all the way across.
Go into the corner and nice move. All right, Tasmanian devil's got the bat now.
Lala going for the pin. Tasmanian devil not going to let that happen.
I think there are tables under the ring too. So I don't know what they're going to do.
Big scoop slam. I think this ladder is this tables. There's all kinds of crazy shit under
the ring. It looks like Lala might be going to get something. And that was way softer than I
thought it was going to be. And they make a table tower. I think they can do something like that.
Everybody is so tired. Ooh, ooh, ooh has a big advantage here. If he can get Tas on the ground,
I think this is it. This actually could be it. Now Armin's back up. Got the weapon again.
Oh, this is so dumb. Just keep the weapon with you. Carry it with you. Finally somebody just
hold on to it. Don't put it on the ground. Did he miss? Oh shit. Oh, he is just going rage mode on
Werner right now. That could be it. No, throw him out of the ring. He's got a bone to pick with him
right now for some reason. I don't know why. Armin now searching for something. He's got a
ladder. Ladder going into the ring. Where is Tas? Oh, outside. Okay. There it is. Ladder getting
set up. I wonder, Armin, could we could see some theatrics here? He's thinking about what he wants
to do. He might put it up and jump off out to the outside of the ring, which would be insane.
But it looks like he's stuck. His brain got frozen for a second. Those of you that want to know the
AI in these WWE games is about the intelligence level of a baby squirrel.
It's some of the worst. They're just so brain dead. Big. Oh my God. That was a huge move by the
Tasmanian devil. Break this up. Break it up. He almost just won it right there. Werner going
under the ring now. Oh, that's a steel chair. This is going to put somebody in the hospital.
He's going to put him in the hospital. Lala outside. Not getting up. Werner trying to find
his next target, his next victim. It's going to be the Tasmanian devil right in the head. Steel
chair shot right in the forehead. Now what? He's wedging the chair into the corner. This could get
ugly. No, he's going to fit him. No, not even close. Somebody's going to run into that chair
accidentally. I love when they use the weapons. It's so stupid. I don't know who's going to win
this. He's going for a sharpshooter. You got to break that up. This could be a tap out right now.
Break it up, Lala. Nice job. Sludge hammer. Armand's got a sludge hammer. Didn't know who
to use it on. What the fuck was that? What was that? Why did he just do that? What the hell was
that? He just screamed at him. And now he's got like streamers on his back. What is going on?
He's got caught. Oh, he's going full sick almost. Do falls count anywhere? I don't think they do.
I read that from chat, by the way, so don't be mad at me if you didn't think it was funny. I read
that from chat. Where's the chair? That's a good question. I think Lala's going to put it away here.
No, they're all so tired. If anybody goes for a pin, that's it. Armand's getting a little pumped
up here. I say go for the bat, hit him in the head, and then cover him. No, he's just choking
him with his boot on his tooth for stealing content. I didn't, what are you talking about?
I read that. I hope Armand loses. Well, you might see your opportunity right here.
Oh, everyone's back in the ring again. Cover him. Pin him. Cover him. This is it. Oh, no.
Not quite. He can't believe it either. He's so shocked. He can't believe it.
All right. Armand, get up. No. Is this it? How is this going to end? Weapon.
Cas stole, stole it from Armand, but watch out for the, I don't even know what to even say. They
all have weapons. That's all you need to know. Stop putting the weapons on the ground.
There are three weapons on the ground. Just pick one up. You don't have to steal it from the other
person. Big clothesline. I think that could be the end. It's not the end. Just pin him.
Stop being so stupid. What are you doing? Why would you walk away from that? Big reversal.
Hit him once and it's over. Double reversal. Triple reversal. Just hit him.
Pin him. Please pin him, Armand. Pin him, please. Please pin somebody. Pin someone.
Toss him out of the ring, for God's sake. That move doesn't even hurt. I've jumped into a hotel bed
harder than that. It doesn't hurt. There's nothing wrong with what you just did.
Chug him out. Chug him out. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. No.
Where's Armand? Oh, he's outside. Outside. These are spoilers for Attack on Titan.
I don't know what just happened, but that could be it. Too busy getting a weapon and he's going
to lose. That's it. That's definitely it. As he gets a table. No, that's it. Werner von Braun
from the Simpsons Arcade Game, ladies and gentlemen, is your sound of the whatever.
It's one of the sounds I've made last year. One of the many sounds I've made.
Very nice match. Congratulations to Werner. I get to do it one more time
and I won't do it ever again for the rest of the year. I promise.
I won't do that ever again. You'll never hear me make that sound ever again. One more. Wait,
one more. One more. One more. Okay. I'll never do it ever again. All right. Let's get back to
some categories. That was two matches. We still have six more to do, including the rumble.
We're going to go over here for now. I hope it does not crash. I'll be very sad if it does.
We're going to leave it. I'm going to be incredibly upset if it crashes. Cross your fingers and pray.
All right. We've got some categories. The next one we're going to do, we're going to go through.
This is worst face incoming. If you're new to the channel, worst face is usually a category that.
And when I'm in the corner, when I do my face cam, have you noticed that when I put face cam on,
every time I've had face cam, there's been a nominee for this. Anytime I put my face cam on,
people nominate a worst face that I've made. They range from excited to angry to like blowing
bubbles or something. I don't know, whatever it is. So these are your nominees for worst face
of the year. What does this guy look like? There. All right. There you go. You got what you wanted,
everybody that was here. You got the imposter is fucking stupid ass sus face that you got it.
I didn't, I just realized that's what I just did.
Somebody came in the room. The T-Rex walked in. It didn't matter what I was doing. I had to be
very still or I was dead. Or you don't have a place to put your cardboard cutout of German 985.
I guess it's going to go over here and lean against the wall while I clean the fucking room.
There's 50 subs. I missed 50 subs. Well, thank you.
You. Oh, that one was bad. It looks like somebody's like fucking threatening me to like,
like, yeah, you're not dense. Doesn't it look like somebody's going to fucking kill me off camera?
Oh, my funny bone. Oh, my funny bone. My funny bone. I just hit my funny bone and my arm is dumb.
Hainsaw sucks. What do we do? What do we do with him? You decide. What do we do with him?
What do we do with him? What do we do with him? I just went like cross-eyed.
What? What? What do we do with that guy? What do we do with him? What do we do with that guy?
Doesn't want me to do it. Just sit there. You have a huge inventory in this game. That's good.
It's like, oh, that guy is. Oh, wait a minute. I'm trying to get. I'm trying to get it.
Like, somebody snatched me. Somebody snatched me. I was in the middle and like,
before they took the photo, somebody like fucking snatched me and pulled me.
Some good ones this year. So the winner of the worst face of the year. I actually don't know.
I don't remember who won this. I don't know who won this. We're going to find out together.
It was close, but Eye Contact Whopper Bite was number one with 22%.
Eye Contact Whopper Bite with 22% of the vote.
Cartoon Anger and Accidental Susface are your winners. Hey, I made some deity very angry.
Eye Contact Whopper. 22% of the vote, which I can. I get it. I can understand. Nobody likes to watch
other people eat and nobody likes to have eye contact while somebody else eats. I don't. I can't.
I get it. I really do. I hate sitting across from somebody and we both have dinners in front of us
and we're both eating. I like, oh no, fucking get out of it. Let's go somewhere else.
I just want to just get takeout and sit on the couch. I don't fucking want to go to a
goddamn restaurant. The only time I like going to a restaurant seriously is if there's like
eight people and everyone's like, oh, did you try this? Try the lobster. Oh yeah. Did you get any
of that? Hey, you got to try this drink. And like you, you, you, it's everyone's just talking and
yelling at each other and shit. I like going to a restaurant with like six people. It was sweating.
Holy fucking moly. Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ. I got to get this off. Jesus Christ. What? What
happened? What happened? I got to get this off. I got to get this off. What happened? What happened?
What's going on recently? I've been sweating my ass off. Hold on. Let me turn on my urinal.
Let me turn the urinal on. I think I need it. Turn the urinal on. Jesus
God. Turn on your face. I just turned it on. Look, all right. I'm sitting. Look, let me explain.
I'm sitting down in a chair and I'm like, I'm sweating and shit. Like I got this ring light
now. I got this new ring light. I'm in like full lighting. This is not like a normal scenario. I'm
out at a dinner table with six people having fun. Anyways, there's your winner. But no, I like going
to a restaurant with like five or six people. You get to converse. You get to share. You get to talk.
You get to point at the person all the way at the end. Hey, oh, dude, did you try the chicken thighs?
And they go, mm-hmm, mm-hmm. And you go, yeah, man, that's my guy over there in the corner.
I like that environment. I hate the other environment. I'm sweating, so who cares?
Going up next is best dancing. Sometimes I get on camera and I decide to move a little bit,
shake a little bit. What do you want about? Those that get it, get it. Those that don't,
they never will. So this is for the best dancing of the year. I don't know even how many times I've
danced this year total. We're about to find out. And no, I swear to God, I'm not a lizard person.
I just blinked weird for a second. All right, these are the nominees for best dancing of the year.
I actually forget what was nominated. Let's find out.
All right, there's a guy right now going like this, like way in the back.
There's a guy just like fucking freaking out over there. There's something, there's always like
bending down too. You know, like it's always just like, it's like,
it's like, and their hair is like going fucking crazy.
You didn't even let me choreograph this with me. I wasn't here at the rehearsal.
Oh, whatever. I'm tired. I'm done. Okay. I've trended on TikTok three different times in the
last fucking three years. Okay. Bring this one to the fucking front page. Oh, this one,
the goddamn orangutan. I'm sweaty as hell on this one too. Why am I sweating so much?
I swear to God, this is like a new thing for the last six months. Why am I so sweaty now?
I want them to see me Fortnite dancing before they die. Come on. They need to see this before
they go. Oh my God. That was epic. I'll give you the shake. It's the old fucking 36 year old shake.
The guy that paid $1,200 for a front row seat.
Okay. This is going to put the TV down for a second. Go have a good day. Go ahead. Take it.
I'm not paying. Fine. You can take it. I don't know if you've heard of that Tic-Tac or whatever.
Keep going. Don't talk to me. Don't talk to me. Fine. But I gotta do it. Are you tick talking?
Are you tick talking now? Uh, yeah, I think so. I don't know how it works.
It mills them in the back. It's so fucking late. Please. All right. All right. I'm the one in
handcuffs, bro. And he took us all by the hand. And then we started dancing.
And then we started dancing.
It's got the spirit. Remix. Remix. When God came down to the land in the land.
God came down to the land in the land. I can't believe what's happening right now.
I can't believe what's happening right now.
Somebody said something really, really important. And I have to address it because I'm going to
address these things. And yeah, I've taken it off a little bit. I don't want to see my sweat box.
Somebody said something really important. They said, I love how Derma's interpretation of dancing
is doing different poses. I mean, what even is dancing? Dancing is just doing different
poses in succession to make a new animation, like a new human animation. How is that? How's
it any different? That's what dancing is. It's doing different poses in a row to create a dance.
If I were to go like this, that's me doing different poses and animating with keyframes
in between. Anyways, the winner. That's not the right sound. The winner of the 2021 Best
Dancing Award goes to... What do you think? What do you think? Stop playing the fucking Among Us,
I'm the Impostor sound. Fuck out of here. I don't want to hear that ever again.
Breakdancing with 27% of the vote. And then in second place with 20% was the goddamn Orangatang,
the TikTok one. And then 12%, no rehearsal, no problem. So breakdancing during the dollhouse was
the winner. At 27% of the vote, a lot. Fair enough. I don't even want to do this one,
but we're going to do it. This is worse, Peter. There are a lot of people here watching and I
need to give context to this because I feel like you'd probably just think I was a fucking psycho
if I didn't. So pretty much, we're at the end game now, Peter. Game almost crashed. You have
to punish me for doing what I just did and saying what I just said. It's the mustache,
Peter. Peter, it's the mustache. You're probably also probably wondering if worse Peter's on there.
Of course it is. I don't think I said it once. I think that's the only time I said it the whole
year. This is on there. It has to be on there. I don't even care. Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dremacraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
Peter, this is going to be a single player. Let's play. Oh, it turned into a different animal.
Oh, Peter. Keith, Mark, Zane, Evan. How could we have forgotten Peter? Please, to make your
acquaintance. I was a rancher here for years, but I can... Hey, hey, Peter. Sorry. You have
your own empire. Cool. Oh, this is cool. We're in the end game now, Peter. So I mean, this is like,
cool. I swear to fucking God, if I play that sound again, I'm going to freak out.
The award for worst Peter of the year goes to... Why would... Okay, I have a question.
Why was this such a huge percentage? I don't understand. Obama reads Dremacraft, Peter,
with 41% of the vote. They were all the same exact thing. All of them were the same. There was no
difference. Why was that so much higher than all the others? 41%? Did you all collectively
get in discord or something and say, oh, hey, by the way, we're all going to vote for the Obama
one? End game, Peter. And then, hey, Peter. Who knows what the fuck that one was? Who cares,
though? Does it matter? I think I just paper cut in my neck. Oh, the price we pay for fucking
showmanship. Coming up next, we have Otto. We have best Otto moment, which is every time that
the dog has been... I got a dog, Otto. He's a little wiener dog. I'm fine. Look, there's nothing. It's
fine. I'm fine. This is best Otto moment when my dog was on screen or maybe not. Maybe it's just
when Otto was mentioned or Otto was like some type of... It's in spirit, right? Here are the nominees
for best Otto. I can do that better. I can do that better. Here are the nominees for best Otto
moment. Oh, look at it. It's Otto. Let's take it. We'll go to Tokyo. Yeah, I want to do the mango.
Oh, nice, Otto. I want to sneeze. I'm not about to sneeze. I'm going to pet Mr. Otto.
You have a scratchy bum? Do you? Do you? Oh, my goodness. I got to get out of the way. He's
doing something cute. Hello, Mr. Toe. Hey, what are you doing over there? What are you doing over
there? What the fuck? Are you dead? Nope. Almost, though. Are you petting him? If you die right now.
I'm going to die. You understand? Bobbleheads? Oh, Otto. I can't believe there's an Otto. Oh,
I missed. Oh, it's a dachshund. Oh, it's Otto. It's little Otto. Where's Otto?
Who's a good boy? Otto. You guys want to see something funny? That bed was like $200.
That bed was like 30. Move out of the way for Otto. It's the same clip, except he's in the $200 bed.
That's my favorite part about that. He was in... Okay, whatever. Ladies and gentlemen, the winner
of Best Otto Moment goes to Orange Blanket Otto with 25% of the vote. Really? Wow. A pet Otto was
15%, which I would assume that would be higher. And then Otto sneezes off camera, 14%. Orange
Blanket with 25% of the vote. By the way, keep in mind, these have been rounded up. So Orange
Blanket probably got like 25.9% of the vote. So just for your viewership, you're able to see
and process because I needed to have round numbers. That just tried to kill me. This just
tried to wrap around my neck and kill me. Round numbers are easier for me, so hopefully they're
easier for you. All right, we'll do one more. We're going to get through this one right now.
This is the last, I think, of the shit categories. I think this is the last of the dumb shitty
categories. I have to warn some of the new viewers here. I know there's 36,000 fucking people here.
Listen to me. You're probably going to want to leave the stream after this. But stay. I promise
that this community is one of the funnest communities I've ever had the pleasure of being
part of. You're going to probably leave the stream during this because you're probably like,
I hate this sound. I don't like this. This guy sucks. I hate listening to this guy.
Why is he doing this? This is the best Aaron of the year. We just saw Armin play in the rumble.
I'm going to give you what exactly what I mean by this. So best Aaron is, okay, how do I explain
this? So in the Attack on Titan English dub, the actor that does Armin and Mikasa too, if you've
ever seen Attack on Titan, they're always yelling for Aaron. They're always yelling his name and
they're always doing it very loudly and very, you know what? Whatever. You understand. Thanks for
watching. TLDR. I just like, I don't know. It's stuck in my brain and I had to say it all the time.
I swear to God, I say this every day. That's a good, you're right. Freeze. Freeze. It's
midnight EST in like three minutes. Freeze. Nobody move. Oh my God. I need the thing.
Was it Lang Syne? Okay, I gotta get ready. I gotta get ready. It's in two minutes.
How? This is like guitar. What's it called? Old Lang Syne? Old Lang Syne? Why are they all this?
It's all this one. Is this a popular one? Two minutes until New Year's on East Coast.
Old Lang Syne. Old Lang Syne. This is like Scottish. I just need old Lang Syne. I just need
royalty free with no lyrics. Royalty free, no lyrics. Old Lang Syne. Royalty free. Okay. All
right. Okay. Here we go. Welcome to 2021 in two minutes. We have two minutes. It's a Scottish
poem. It is. I don't want to even see that fucking underarm bullshit. We got one minute. I gotta,
we gotta count this down. We're almost there. We're getting close. These are like almost done.
Should I take these off? We're probably gonna be able to count down the Pacific one too because
there's like lots left for me to do here. 30 seconds till New Year's. I'm in Pacific so it's
not New Year's for me but we'll celebrate East Coast nonetheless. Here we go. The ball's about
to drop in New York City. Do it in your Boston accent. All right. Yeah. You want me to do it in
the old Lang Syne in my Boston accent? All right. Let's see if I can get it back. And a five, four,
three, two, one. Happy fucking New Year. And a
their old Lang Syne. And all the Red Sox players should fucking get paid more than the Yankees do.
And all the Patriots who cares about Tom Brady. He's a fucking loser. I don't even fucking care.
And all the Revolution was a soccer team and the Bruins. And fuck you for fucking talking shit to
me about my mother behind my back that one time that year and I fucking never forgot. Happy New
Year. Happy New Year all you East Coasters. We'll keep going. Thanks for spending it here with me.
We'll keep moving on. Acquaintance be forgot and all before Lang Syne and all acquaintance be
for God and I lots of time. I don't, nobody knows the lyrics. They all just hum it. Whenever you see
people like shifting back and forth and the big crowds at New Year's, none of them know what the
song is. They're all just going like this. Nobody knows what the fuck the lyrics are to this song.
And let me be the first to ruin your New Year with best Aaron. That's a good, you're right.
I'm just shit my pants when I did that. I actually almost just shit my pants for real.
I'm not kidding. That was actually almost. I almost shit my pants right now on. Thank God it
wasn't on camera. Someone that goes, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron.
I've never done that. I'm back to easy. We, we, that's
Aaron. Um, stop. Stop. It's a test. Aaron. What is that? What's Aaron? What's Aaron?
What is that? What's Aaron? Why are they saying Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron. Oh shit. You're gonna
know who I am. No. Oh, what I meant to say was,
that's fun. That's not funny. I'm doing an impression of Armin from attack on Titan.
I'm just doing it. I just got, I have to, I'll do it over here. So it's not as loud.
I'm sorry. I have, I do have no idea. You know what it's like to fucking live with me.
Oh, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, run away, Aaron. Do Hercule. Oh, I can do that. Look,
that's, I love that character in attack on Titan. Oh, right. I love when that character shows up
and says, I am the strongest person on earth. What do you know about that one? Aaron, Aaron, Aaron.
Didn't say it in the funny voice. Aaron. No, that wasn't even the right one. Aaron. There you go.
You get that like once a week. Those whose eyes are clouded are besieged by the ghosts that haunt them.
Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron.
Okay. There you go. So I know you said, shut up. You must be one of the two. You should have voted
no. Why did you want me to do that? 76% of you told me to do that. The winner this year and the
only year for best Aaron is at 17% of the vote. 76% of you voted for this. The last one you just
heard. It was bad. I didn't stop. I just kept going. I kept doing it. I didn't pause. Microphone Aaron
was at 13 and Goku Aaron was at 12. All right. We're going to do one more. No, no, we're not.
No, we're not. Oh my God. Yeah, we should. We did two more. All right. Sometimes on this stream,
I like to do impressions. Sometimes on this stream, I like to do impressions. Whether that's Obama,
or whether that's Homer Simpson, or whether that's how much you've lost on a coin toss.
I like to do impressions. I like to just kind of say things and do things, right?
Sometimes they're better than others. Sometimes impressions are bad. I'm just giving context to
people. That's not me doing an impression. That was context. Sometimes I do impressions and we're
going to start with the best. So these are the best. No, we're going to start with the worst
because I want people to see how good I am later. These are the worst impressions of the year.
Sometimes they're good. Sometimes they're bad. I can't tell you how to feel either way, but we're
going to start with the worst. No, let's start with the best foot forward. Best foot forward.
These are the nominees for best impression of the year. Here we go. Best impression.
Banned me if I'm wrong. I bet you can't do a perfect wolf howl on stream right now.
Banned that guy for life. Banned that guy again if he's still here. Banned that guy for life.
Banned him for life. He doesn't get to come back. Banned him if he's here right now. He
does not get to come back. Banned that guy permanently. He does not get to come back.
You go play the sounds that I just made. The ones I just made.
Play it. I want to hear it. Clip it. I want to hear it. I never yelled. It was like...
I'd just be sitting there going like...
Vodwatcher right now was able to go like this.
Okay, so we're going to play Deltarune now. We're going to start the game now.
My territory. And I will let you leave.
You imitate the sounds of shoes squeaking on a basketball court. Yeah.
Oh, hey, guys. Hey, you ever pick up the phone and somebody... It's a wrong number.
And you say, oh, hey, wrong number. Hey, screw you, buddy. You know what I mean? That's plus two.
No, no, no, no, no. Get the fuck out of here.
Car noise. It's like...
This one's not going to be close. The winner for best impression of the year
goes to... You probably could guess it. It was Spampton. At 31% of the vote, Spampton, which
I've seen a lot of people say they liked the Spampton voice. I was just kind of fucking around.
If you liked it, I'm glad you did. I was just having fun. Chat chimps at 12% and then skipping
through the VOD at 15%. Here are your best impressions of the year, apparently. It was
an interpretation. Yeah, yeah, exactly. That's what I said. Chimps got robbed. Well, you just
want chimps to win because you are a chat chimp. You got bias. So with the best comes the worst.
And these are the ones... It's funny because people are probably watching right now going,
oh, dude, half of those were dog shit. Well, just wait till you hear the ones that weren't
nominated for best of the year. Wait till you see the ones that were nominated for the worst
of the year. And I gotta... Okay, I have to defend myself right now. I don't... Sometimes I just sit
here and I just talk and I just like do somebody else's voice or something. And I'm not even trying
to do it. I'm not trying to do an impression. I just do Donald Duck. I'm just like, all right,
I'm going to do... I'll do Donald Duck right now. That sounds like kind of a fun time.
And then people go, oh, hey, that sucked. And I go, all right, well then fucking nominate it already.
Here are your nominees for worst impression of the year. And you all know who won. So who cares?
Let's go. Worst impression of the year. Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode
one of JermaCraft, the series where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single player
let's play. And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this
game. What are you talking about? Are you sure we don't have to go fix the grandma's recipe?
No, Chippendale. You've got to go to a foreign fucking land and you've got to start
shooting at stuff. What are you talking about? That's how you treat it.
You want to impression Bowser? Okay. Peter Dactyl. I've turned into a pterodactyl. I am now
Peter Dactyl. He flies and smashes right into the side of like Cleveland's house.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of JermaCraft,
the series where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single player let's play. And I say,
when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I am a stupid idiot dumb ass
in this game. You're going to see lots of you. That's a fake one. Audition for Waluigi right
now. All right. Everybody cheated, but me. Jesus Christ. This should have won. That should have won.
Did I get the part? You sound like Homer Simpson today. Well, thanks. I appreciate that.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. There it is. Fuck off. I got it. Oh, Joe, Joe, the Bionicles.
They're never going to make it. I don't think they're going to make it, Joe.
Chad, what do you guys think? Will you just shut up, man?
What? Trying to watch the movie here. Ah, of course they're going to make it.
They're the damn Bionicles. Now hear me. Morning. How are you? It should be pleased you to know that
the purple Pikmin are lodged safely in my home. That wasn't Bernie. That was supposed to be
Arnold Schwarzenegger. Good morning. How are you? Fuck. That is Bernie. Good morning. How are you?
How are you? How are you? Good morning. Good morning. Fuck. Did you do Tommy Lee Jones?
I'll try. You do an impression of Daniel Day-Lewis in Where There Will Be Blood. Sure.
All right. I don't think the Daniel Day-Lewis one was that bad. Can I be honest? The Daniel
Day-Lewis one was more like feeling and like mannerism. It was more like an emotion.
It was. I wasn't. You know what I mean? Whatever. By the way, anybody that does an Arnold Schwarzenegger
impression, they're just going to do Bernie Sanders. Listen for it. If you can differentiate
yourself from Arnold to Bernie, you got a great fucking Arnold impression. Lois won with 21% of
the vote. And then Homer Simpson with 13. And then Chip and Dale. Chip and Dale. I think Chip
and Dale was the worst. That's cope. Yeah, that's fine. There it is. Lois is your winner with 21%.
Homer Simpson 13. Chip and Dale with 11. I think Chip and Dale was the worst by far. Chip and Dale
was so bad it hurt my ears listening back when I got the video to compile into OBS. It was awful.
And with that, we're going to move back to Germanium. We're going to go back to the German
Rumble. We still have about five or six matches to do before the Rumble. So we're going to move
this over here. Let's keep this going here. I hope you can't see it. All right. I think we're good.
On to the next match. This one's going to be interesting. Mitch McConnell should have been
on there. I think that was last year. I think it was. I think it was on last year. I just burped
and I'm so glad I fucking got rid of it. I'm going to need a refill soon here. We are definitely
going to count down the Pacific New Year's, by the way. There's no way we don't miss it.
There's so much more to do. You didn't see shit. I drink five times a year. Will you let me have
this? I drink five times a year. All right. The next is going to be a one on three tag match,
which could be very interesting. Here we go. Our next match is a one on three tag match,
handicap match. For those in the audience that were Dollhouse fans, this is a Dollhouse themed
matchup. Our first contestant is going to be Jerma from the Dollhouse, specifically wearing the
Cherubianship belt. That is Dollhouse Jerma. That's true. That's not true. One half of the
Jeremy? Is there another half? Yeah, that's me in the day one Dollhouse outfit and I am facing three
people at the same time. Well, it's a tag match. Trying to think of who I would really be kind of
annoyed with. Three people in particular that I just, God, they got on my nerves. They were
always around me. They were always causing problems. I could sense them. I heard them.
I could feel them in the room with me. And even still, when I go back and watch footage,
I'm still surprised of their existence. And I don't believe it a lot of the time. People tell me,
oh, no, this happened. This happened. I'm like, no, it didn't. That's so weird. And I got the belt
too. Some of you are guessing what it is and some of you got it right. Bald is beautiful. I'm not
bald and I'm 36. Do you understand how awesome that is? I am not bald and I'm 36. Holy smokes.
I can say that. That's awesome. I probably won't make it to 40, but who knows? We'll find out.
Thank you for joining me on this New Year's, by the way. And I'm doing my tuber voice because
we're doing commentary on the wrestling, of course. And who I am facing is the dastardly,
the sneaky, the strange, the out of the ordinary, the paralysis demon-like shadow moving people.
Three of the shadow movers in a furniture matchup. I believe this is a tables,
ladders, and chairs match. This is shadow mover one. And I think they have the same entrance,
so I don't know if we need to do shadow mover two and threes entrance, but they are terrifying.
Get them. I will skip this because it's two more of the same intro, but we'll wait for the
prediction to be over because I don't want to start the match yet. I don't know if I would
vote for me. It's one V three. Although you might make money if I win. That'd be great.
How much pyrotechnics? Oh my God. Relax. He's using a lot of gas. Jesus. Yeah, it's three.
There are three shadow movers versus me. Let's go. Let's go. Just to prove it, it's three
shadow movers. Yeah. We're not going to do this three times. I'm not doing that three times.
Tables, ladders, and chairs match one V three handicap tag. Here we go.
All house, Jerma versus three shadow movers. Begin. Tag rules apply right off the bat.
Immediate pin. So I have to be careful here because I have to slow down.
Don't use all my strength. Don't miss kicks to the ground for no reason.
These are the guys that I heard about that were walking around during the dollhouse and moving
furniture. That's what I was told. What a weird experience that was. It's my revenge time.
Don't just stand there. What are you stupid? I got to go through three of them and I got good
stats. Let me tell you. Choking Jerma, dollhouse Jerma on the ropes while one of the three big
right hand onto Jerma nine eight five dollhouse Jerma nine eight five eight one. Tagging in one
of the other movers, which I believe they move in unison. I don't know if they're a single unit,
if they're a collective unit. They could be a hive mind. I don't know. This is sad.
Why is it sad? I didn't lose yet. Don't say that. I've only got a ladder in the goddamn ring.
Don't count me out just yet. Come on. Look at me. I'm getting really excited.
Oh, I just choked his neck. Okay. The ducky shirt is perfect. It really is.
Don't get stuck on the ropes and crash the damn game. Where else do you choke people?
Um, I don't know. You can choke them in the water. Don't win. Dude, you must have huge
sweat marks right now. I do. And you should have seen the sweat mark of the dollhouse.
I'm glad I get to change clothes. Now dollhouse Jerma going into the corner.
Does the gentle drop that you hear? I'm talking into my wine glass right now. Try deodorant.
Look, there's a huge difference between sitting around with a blaring ring light
and a hot ass room. And you're wicked excited for the rumble and the look at me, by the way.
Look at me taking fucking names here. I am taking names here. Or at least I was until you said
something. You probably have high blood sugar. No. All right. I don't need any medical Andes
to tell me what's wrong with me. I'm fine. Yeah. Let me go get a blood glue close monitor and
prick my finger. False count anywhere. I almost just won. What? My glue close my glue. Whatever.
Glenn close. What am I saying? You know what I'm saying. Big DDT on dollhouse Jerma. If I get pinned
I'm gonna be pissed. Don't lose right now. Are you fucking kidding me? What a shitty match.
That was awful. That was terrible. What was this move supposed to be?
What? Maybe if I grab him by his waist and hold him down on top of me, how am I not being pinned?
Was he pinning me? That was so stupid. What a terrible move. It was awful. The shadow movers
are your winner. We're not doing a rematch because that match was terrible. They didn't even get any
ladders, any chairs, or any tables. It was supposed to be a furniture match.
They did not care to take any of the furniture from under the ring. I just lost in five minutes.
Okay. On to the next one. Oh, this is gonna be good. This one's gonna be good. You got bodied.
It's a 3v1, man. I was gonna get my ass kicked no matter what. Unless I could get a table or
something. Let's go. Willem Dafoe. I almost spelt that all over me. All right. The next one coming
up is a false count anywhere for fatal four way. L ratio. Give me your keys. I'm not going. What
are you talking about? I'm gonna, my ass is going to be planted in this seat for the next like three
hours. I ain't going anywhere. All right. Here we go. The next match is a fatal four way.
And I would call this one the gamer match because I mean, here comes Pac-Man 99.
Pac-Man 99 from the fifth dimension. He what? P-A-C, man.
Pac-Man 99 is your first contestant. This is the gamer battle, like I told you. Fatal,
fatal four way. Let me copyright. Oh, please. Copyright. Our second contestant in this is,
of course, who could forget Cosmic Calamity from Monster Rancher 2.
I don't know how well this is going to play out because block wrestlers can crash the game
and they can fuck up the whole game. So if the game crashes, that's a huge problem.
That is Jerma's, why am I speaking in third person? It's mine. That is my Monster Rancher 2
character. Third person? What the fuck was that? Oh, that's Jerma's, the idea of mind?
That is Cosmic Calamity. Don't, stop chanting crash. I don't want the game to crash. Don't say
that. Captain Olimar from the Wii. I don't know what he's holding. What is that? Are they Pikmin
in that sack? What's in the sack? That's kind of fucked up. It's a great Olimar, by the way.
It's the Pikmin. Don't swing it around. What are you doing? If you missed my Pikmin playthrough,
I thought the Wii sucks and I thought the game sucks. I hate the Wii and I hate Pikmin.
Our next contestant is Anubis from Smite. My favorite Smite character, Anoa Bass?
Okay, I didn't know that. I didn't know that it was Anoa Bass. So we have Anubis,
Pacman99, Olimar, and Cosmic Calamity in a four-way. All right. I think it's Extreme
Rules 2. We'll find out in a second. I got my money on Cosmic Calamity or Anubis because I love
Smite. Everybody else hates it. It was nominated for worst stream of the year, by the way.
Four-way. Don't pin immediately. I actually kind of hope it happens. So Anubis and Cosmic
Calamity now in the corner. Already some drama. Prediction. I don't think we can do prediction.
Crash. Don't stop. I don't want the game to crash. Stop saying that. The Rumble is... Okay,
let me tell you something about the Rumble. The Rumble this year is like 22 characters that you
are not going to see. None of these fucking idiots are in the Rumble. Let me make that really clear.
None of these dickheads are in the Rumble. There were just so many characters this year.
All falls count anywhere. Who just hit their head? Please, I don't want the game to crash. God,
what you idiots. And Cosmic... I can't. Somebody said, where's the Among Us match?
You'll never see one on this channel. Never. So in the corner, Cosmic Calamity in Olimar.
Let's just throw somebody into the stairs 10 times in a row. That's great. Yeah, go ahead.
Hey, throw into the stairs again. Does anybody else want to throw somebody into the stairs?
Throw them into the stairs again. Will they do anything else? Do something besides throw into
stairs. Oh my God. I got an idea. I'll throw them into the stairs and then I'll try to pin them.
That'll work. Hey, you guys want them over there? I'll throw them over there. There's no stairs
over there, but I'll throw them that way. And then I'll do a fucking Fortnite dance.
Hi, dear. Leave me alone. I got an idea. Hey, I got an idea. How about Olimar grasping by the neck
and fucking twisting? All right, back in the ring. Olimar now throwing Calamity. No, reversal on the
ropes. Interesting. Put them into the turlet. I have no idea who... I think there's extreme rules
on this too. Big DDT by Cosmic Calamity while Lanubis and Pac-Man 99 are in the corner pushing
his foot into his neck or whatever that is. I don't know if he has a face. How come Cosmic's
not one-shotting everybody? Well, Cosmic Calamity has, I believe, like a hundred strength and zero
everything else, I think. So it's there. Going for the pin already. Threatening. Anubis Smite,
by the way, voted for one of the worst streams of the year. It is nominated for one of the worst
streams of the whole year. We'll find out what that is later on tonight. Big pin covering by
Anubis. No, huge suplex off the top turnbuckle by Olimar to Cosmic Calamity. How are we going
to see a victory already? No way. Anubis breaks that up. We've not seen a weapon. We've not seen
any attacks, chairs, sludge hammers. He just repeated himself three times. He's drunk.
That was a tombstone, but I'm going to start saying differently. I think Anubis just won.
I think Anubis almost just won right there. Anubis, you guys are fucking with me. Okay,
I got to relax. You're being too funny. All right, everybody relax. What is happening?
Big splash. No, only a two count. I'm not high. Just give me a second so I can reconvene my
brain. What did he do that for? Why did he do that? A big right hand by Anubis into a leg drop here.
Now, remember, false count anywhere. You guys are making me laugh. I got to fucking,
I got to hit the brakes. I just got it. What did I miss? A lot of categories, a lot of fun stuff.
Why did the referee is down? Watch the referee. Don't be an idiot. Don't hit the referee. He's
stupid. All right, somebody go through that table. I want someone to go through that table. Look at
how nice they look. They got the German 95 branded logo. Get them through the table for God's sakes.
Anubis with Cosmic Calamity into the stairs again. What else is new? The referee is like,
I should have to work. Your stream is lagging. I don't know why that shouldn't be happening.
All right, get back in the ring. Let's go back to zero. I'm fine. I'm having a great fucking time.
This is so much fun. Hope you're having a good time too. Anubis outside with Cosmic Calamity.
That's not even the right person. Oh my God, Jeremy. Fucking give me a break.
Olimar and Cosmic Calamity in the front of the ring, inside the middle as Calamity gets caught.
I'm not muted. Shut up. Olimar is waiting for it. Oh, that's a stunner. He got him with a stunner.
That's a stunner. Hackman99 is completely clueless, but finally got over there.
That was a stunner. That's his finishing move. Game's not muted. Leave me alone.
Big spin. You're doing your best. I'm surprised. Why has nobody been pinned?
I did not think this was going to go this long as Anubis and Cosmic Calamity.
All right, get him on the top rope. Suplex on the top rope. Let's see it, Anubis.
Oh, I'm not stupid. I can see the OBS meters going up. I'm not dumb.
Big hurricane run of reverse. No, back. Belly to back suplex off the top rope. Anubis to Cosmic
Calamity. That's huge. He may as well just use his ult. Anubis just ulted Cosmic Calamity. Can he?
Why? Don't. Just keep him on the ground, you idiot. What a fucking idiot. What a dumb ass.
Why would you not pin him? I'm not muted. Stop minus twoing. What's wrong with you guys?
Leave me alone. Who is being pinned? You can't even see that from here.
That referee could not even see the pin he was counting. What's happening? He can't even
see. As Olimar grabs Pac-Man 99 going up onto the top here under his shoulders.
That's huge. Olimar could take it away right now. Olimar, take it away right now.
Go for a pin. End it. Stop throwing people into... Oh my god. Pin. Somebody pin.
Big suplex. No. What was that? That's it. But who wins? I don't know. What?
What? He's been pinning for way longer. It was over. Olimar wins. Olimar wins. What the
fuck was that? He started counting for the guys on the left and didn't do Olimar's pin. What?
The ref is drunk too? All right. Hide the champagne bottles from the rest of them. All of us.
I can't believe Olimar didn't win. The ref is shit faced. Another stunner. All right.
Olimar win the game right now. Oh my god. Everybody's shit faced. They were taking
shots of fireball backstage and that's always a bad idea. Don't ever let anyone convince you
that's a good idea. Hey man, you want to take shots of fireball? No is always the answer.
No is always the answer. Always. There's a two count. That's it. Cosmic calamity. I don't
know why they didn't count the Olimar outside. That was horseshit. Cosmic calamity is your
winner of the four person gamer battle. That was rigged. I'll be honest. That was fucked up.
There is no reason why Olimar should not have won. I agree with you. It's really messed up. Not
cool. I mean, I love Cosmic Calamity. They're a great character, but I don't think they should
have won. Not a chance. You did not have to be in the ring. You just had to pin somebody somewhere.
And that is that one. We only have a few more matches left till the rumble. We have a lot of
categories to get through. So we'll go back to the categories. I didn't rig it. I swear to god.
Okay. P break. All right. We'll take one P break here. Go pee. Go put some water on your face.
You know, go take a second. We'll be right back. He's plastered. I'm really not though. I'm just
having a good time. It's been a fucking blast. I'm happy to share it with all of you. I'll be right
back. I'm all right. I'm all right. Don't worry about me. I'll be right back. Okay. Hello. How
are you? Welcome back. We have more categories to go through. Quite a few more. So let's get them
done. Let me make sure this is in the right spot. It is. Okay. Cool. Looks good. Okay. Not much
longer till we have to get rid of the Christmas BRB screen. How was my poop? It was awesome.
Now we're good. Okay. Hi. How are you? Coming up next. This is the meaty categories. No. Oh yeah.
These are meaty. We're going to start with the best joke. Taking more than five minutes to set up.
Seven minutes. Seven minutes for what? Oh shit. Yeah, you're right. Central time. That's right.
All right. So every year there's a lot of jokes that I do. A lot of things that I think are funny
that I hope are funny. But sometimes they're good. Sometimes they're bad. So this is what
people have nominated for the best jokes of the year. Best jokes of the year. So we're getting
into a big category here. This is a huge category. So here are your nominees for best joke of the
year. Taking more than five minutes to set up. Was it blood in my stool? Griffin family. Stewie,
it's time for school. I should not have to go to school. We got this new friend,
German985. He's here hanging out with us. I will make my secret hot tuck it Pete beer cheese
pretzels. Give me that. Come on. 71 million sprints. And that's a coin.
That's 3.1 million limes. Hey, get yourself some nice. This is why he's green.
Only funny voices. Wait, only funny voices for 20 straight minutes. I don't know if I can do that.
It's very difficult to do this and still play the video game at the same time. I'll tell you it's
not easy. This is Bernie. This is Bernie. If Bernie is morphing into a bunch of things,
Bernie is morphing into German guy again. Not a slip. This is non-slip. This is
rockabob. That's not a slip. That sounds sort of like the way that I kind of talk a little.
But now you make me go. Here we go. You grab her. Please eat her. Eat her, please.
Wait, he's still in the cut scene. He's still in the cut scene. Wait, he's blocking.
Okay. I'm going to go for a bite. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God. It's so good.
Okay. So I was at the store yesterday and I got a Dunkin Donuts large iced coffee.
And dude, I'm telling you, it was fucking gross. It was the grossest coffee I've ever had in my life.
It was disgusting. Oh, hey guys. Hey, you ever pick up the phone and somebody, it's a wrong number
and you say, oh, hey, wrong number. Hey, I screw you buddy. You know what I mean? Like that's plus
two. We're not going to use this anywhere, Roger. You don't need to hear me. Oh, but go hit that
follow button if you could. Aaron, Aaron, Aaron, Aaron. Oh shit. You're going to know who I am.
No. Oh, what I meant to say was, oh, no, I just, you don't know who I am. I'm the secret streamer.
I figured you out. I'm contacting the thieves. Oh yeah. Look at you. Look at me. Look at you.
You think you know who this is? What an idiot. What an idiot. You guys want to fuck with new
viewers? Okay. So I'm going to get a royalty free song. That's like with a bit, like a lot of drums.
I will, I'm going to full cam and just be like fucking like playing like air drums and like
people get into it and shit. I can't, I can't, I can't do it. I can't.
Yo, German on a five here. Just want to say, Oh, I did. I said, excuse me. Is it somebody's birthday
today? Oh, of course it is. Happy birthday. I'm so happy to see you on your birthday. I was told
you're a big fan and I'm, I'm coming to you personally. Tyler. Hey, Tyler, Lois. I'm fucking
done. I'm done. There's a, how many names are there in existence? There's too many. Hey, Bernie,
Thanos. Wishing happy birthday to Thanos. Paul. Paul. You can hear me laughing. You can hear me
laughing. Paul. Why is this one so hard? Paul. What the fuck is wrong with me? You ready for the great
fucking reveal? Collectible monster card packs. Holy shit. Pokemon cards. What is this? What is
Grotto Beasts? Razzle Puss? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Look at this
one. Look at this one. This one, this is a cut to my face. Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick cut to
my face. A foil Razzle Puss. You found the company. How much is it worth? Like $350,000.
$350,000. It's $350,000 for the GrottoBeasts.com is what we found. Yeah, buy it. Buy it. Buy it right
now. You got, you got access to my checking account. Get it. Come on up here. Come on.
Happy new year. You'll get up here eventually. I know you will. He's picking the tables up.
Come on up here. This is it. It's in this area here. I'm gonna find that goddamn treasure and
I'll be the first one to close that out. I don't want to go backwards. Oh, I can't believe.
Jerma, how do you know how to use that? But you don't think I fucking know everything?
You don't think I know how to use one of these? I worked for 10 years in the industry.
Give me a break. Okay, so this one is pretty interesting because, uh, happy new year.
Central. Oh, hold on.
Happy new year, Central. The best joke taking more than five minutes to set up.
Which is, this is actually really surprising. I am shocked by this one. The winner of the best joke
taking more than five minutes. This is a shocker. I think a lot of people get this an upset.
It's an upset. What? Leave me alone. Bought a Whopper and ate it on stream with 19% of the vote.
That's the winner. Drumming, rock out break and grotto beasts were pretty much tied. Buying a
Whopper and eating it on stream, you guys thought was better than anything else of the whole year.
I just ate a Whopper on camera. I ate Burger King on camera. I ate Burger King on camera.
Uh, drumming was 12% in second place. That was a pretty good one. I thought that wasn't fun.
That one was very fun. It was rigged. It was not rigged. So just like the best,
let's go ahead and do the worst. These are the worst things I did the whole year.
These are the worst jokes I've ever made in all of 2021. Not proud of these. I'm ashamed of these.
Uh, here are your nominees, just like the best. Here are your nominees for the worst jokes
of the year. That took more than five minutes to set up. Embarrassing. Here we go.
And then we'll do, hmm, it's going to be a cake. Fuck the haters, right? Fuck the haters. I'm
putting marshmallows on my building. Fuck the haters. And they have to be different sizes too.
Oh my God. This is so omega ooey gooey. Dripping. That was cheesy. What, are people bored? Are you
bored? Oh, well I'm whatever. Look at this. I'm making a masterpiece. No, all right. I'm not,
I'm not messing with it anymore. I'm not messing with it anymore. It's over. I did it. There it is.
The Gronk's ice cream city hall. I don't know why I want to like make two cams. I have one of them
be blue and the other one be red and put them right next to each other transparent and like
give you like a 3d show. I'm coming at you. I'm coming at you.
Okay. I'm going to go for a bite. Oh my God. Why is this here? You can't have best and worst joke
of the year. It's so stupid. Oh my God. It's so good. You guys want to fuck with new viewers?
Okay. So I'm going to get a royalty free song. That's like with a bit, like a lot of drums.
I will, I'm going to full can also on best of the year be like fucking like playing like air drums
and like people get into it and shit. Look at how split of a community we really have.
It was people hated this, but they loved it on the other side. Right. It's so funny.
Okay. I will do a, I will do a welcome to German craft as the entire Griffin family. Hello,
ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of German craft, the series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player. Let's play. And I say, when I say let's play,
I use that term pretty loosely because I have a stupid idiot dumb ass in this game.
You're going to see lots of you. That's a fake one. All right. I'm starting to see residence
sleepers. I got to go. I have to get this done right now. I don't care. It's a billion off the
dead. I don't give a shit how it sounds. I'm seeing residents sleepers. I gotta go. Hello,
ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of German craft. This is fucking Jesus Christ.
Oh, one, two, three.
What's in there? I'm not sure. Oh my God. It's, it's Minecraft diamond. This is like what I see
when I look down in the bathtub. Okay. Like it's just like, Oh, there it is. A deformed penis.
That's not, this is like what your dick does when you just are sitting around hanging out in your
living room. Okay. This is what it looks like. It's like pushed up against your pants. All right.
I'm done. If you sit in the bathtub, if you're lying in the bathtub and you are lying back and
you look down, it's going to look like this. I'm sorry, but I have to do this. It's like,
what do you want me to say? That's TOS. That is a piece of frosting that I can't wait to never mind.
Oh shit. And then we'll do.
Fuck the haters, right? Fuck the haters. I didn't mean to click. I'm so sorry. I'm putting marshmallows
in my building. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll fix it. I'll fix it.
Different sizes too. Oh my God. This is so omega ooey gooey. Just dripping. I didn't mean to click
that. God damn it. Are you bored? Oh, well, I'm whatever. I guess we're going to watch it again.
I'm making a mess. I'm so pissed. It was one more. I'm not messing with it anymore. It's over.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got it. I got it. There it is. The Gronk's ice cream city hall.
We'll get there. Hold on. I can't. Son of a. God damn it. I didn't mean to. I swear to God,
didn't mean to do that. While that's on, we have to get to the last part. Just played in VLC.
It'll take two seconds. Just relax. It's got five seconds. Relax.
I did not. I'm sorry. I promise. I did not mean to do that. I promise.
An idiot. I'll be on cam for a minute. Okay. It's in the background. That's fine.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's fine. Sure. Minecraft series where I play it. Yep. I got to
go. Resident sleepers. Yep. Yep. He's still going. Okay. We saw that one. Okay. Okay. Okay.
The winner of the worst. I'll just tell you. Who cares? It was by a landslide.
It was by a goddamn landslide. Who cares? Wait, stop. Stop. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down.
Why won't it slow down? Oh my God. You piece of crap. It won't slow down. And your winner of worst
joke of the year, taking more than five minutes to set up with 26% of the vote.
Family guy. Germacraft. Y'all know it was going to win. And then bought a whopper and aided on
stream. It's insane. It's insane. Because the whopper, like it was like 20% in both worst and
best. That doesn't make any sense. And then the archaeology Minecraft diamond at 14%.
The family guy germacraft thing was a disaster. I'm embarrassed publicly. It was awful. Best
accident. It was best and worst. But yeah, but that just shows how like completely disconnected
everybody is here. Half of you thought it was the best. Half of you thought it was the worst.
Let's do two more. Two more categories. This is so fucked. Okay. These two. Don't even look at the
label of these two. There's no reason to look at the label. You don't have to look. It's the same
damn category. It doesn't matter. There were 200, 200 nominees for best and worst noise of the year.
The most we've ever seen. The most noise nominations ever by plus 100. There were so many
nominees. I have to like reel it in in 2022. I'm going to reel it in. I'm going to relax.
I'm going to try to stop, make it because I'm going to try to be a normal human being in 2022.
How much of a crazy person do you have to be? Do you have your best noise category? Have a hundred
and fucking 25 nominations. We had to drop it down to like 20 and that's all that's that's still
that's too many. That's way too many. Here are your nominees for best noise of the year. That
includes burps, sneezes, like yells, pukes. Best noise of the year. Here we go. Aaron, excuse me.
I think all whipped cream is great. I don't know what's the hate to whipped cream.
Am I muted right now? Oh, hey, you are. You were muted for a second. Sorry. What were you saying?
Yeah, I was just saying.
Hijack the data. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
What are you trying to do? Rip me off?
Don't get sucked into a war hole. Do a funny sound effect.
I'm going to stealth kill the mortar guy.
Oh my God. All right, we're fine. Come out here. Get rid of the rabbit.
Oh, what happened? No, I was trying to fill the dead air.
Now watch. She's going to come try to like kiss me and I'm going to go.
And I'm going to push her away. Watch. I'm not going to do anything. That's the quickest way to
get disinvited to anything else in the future is being in that general chat with like 15 people
and being like, Hey, hey, pick the beaver and that's the kind of the beaver goes.
If he breaks that down and then he goes on the corn.
And then I put the horse in there and they'd be like, all right,
you're like, okay, fucking can you stop like, can you leave the call? Like, stop.
We're trying to like set this up. Watch him go on the right side.
Oh, no. No, he did it. He did the same exact arrows that he got hit with.
Oh, la la. Damn it.
I don't have enough room.
He does this only for the power.
He got me killed.
Somebody came in here and like killed me and muted the microphone right by.
How?
Oh a burger.
Can you talk while inhaling at the same time?
Hi.
Nope.
Please don't.
So not to confuse you, that was best noise of the year.
The winner of best noise of 2021 deranged with laughter followed closely by lala at
10% deranged with 11% and fill the dead air with 10%.
This was so close, it was impossible to even just differentiate.
Lala lost by like 0.8% the deranged laughter one and then filled the dead air right after.
So pretend like you didn't hear the category, if you're like oh noise, best noise, yeah
don't matter.
Here's the worst noise of the year.
I would put your volume down like 10 to 20% I would say, maybe 5%.
Some of these are probably really annoying.
Here are the nominees for the worst noise of the year.
Alright now you pissed me off.
Wouldn't be the first time you abandoned the channel.
Kill it!
I'm basing the opinion of bringing the fox up, not because I want to be the contrarian,
but because of that video of the fox going like, that's such a cute video, I love it.
It just keeps going.
What's up dog?
You just made like the lemur behind me laugh, I forgot to tell you guys I got a lemur.
Oh here's every single mukbang video you've ever watched in your entire life.
What about people that were in the Jerma Rumble?
I don't think I have the other stones.
Yes, yes I'll get the stones, I'll go after those stones, yes of course I'll get the stones.
Hello hello hello hello hello, oh no!
Jesus, oh my god!
Go to the workshop at the back and buy the streaming function!
Wait, let me take a guess, is thrumming like this like
Is that what it might be?
Your winner of this year's Worst Noise of the Year.
I've got it right here.
Oh wow this was close.
My god.
There was a 37 vote difference.
With 16.6% of the vote, it's the Spampton Request Accepted.
Right after that was the Cursed Mukbang, 16.6% and 16.3%.
Very far away was Saucon D's Nuts.
That was a 37 vote difference.
By the way, something funny to note about the best and worst noise category, some of
the most skipped, 1270 people skipped this question.
Which is a lot of people.
Alright, let's get back to the rumble.
Nooooooo you know what, fuck it.
We got, we'll do two more.
Two more categories.
Yeah, a bunch of, I mean would you want to take that test?
I don't want to listen to like 25 of this annoying dude's sounds.
It makes perfect sense.
Alright, we will do two more.
Cause there's still, oh my god there's like 12 more categories holy shit.
All right, coming up next is a popular one, very popular.
This is best one guy moment of the year, if you don't know what a one guy moment is.
A one guy moment is when somebody in chat derails the stream to a point where we spend
about five to 10 plus minutes potentially, even maybe less, maybe more, dealing with
the fact that this person derailed the stream.
It's the best chat kind of, I guess, chat message, chat derailment.
It's the best one guy moment of the year.
And there was a lot of great categories this year.
Holy smokes.
We'll see them right now.
No, wait, I don't have a Rubik's Cube.
Guys, I have no fucking idea how to do a Rubik's Cube.
I have absolutely no idea.
I've only picked them up and just mushed them around in my hands for two minutes.
I don't even know how it works.
I don't understand how it works.
We're on times two speed.
Is that what you say next game?
Yeah, let me load up Yakuza.
I'm just telling you that I finally ate in and out the way that I was told I was supposed
to quote order special the burger.
And it was better than just ordering it off the menu, which makes me want to put it down
here.
Even the animal style dick, please apologize for typing me up for 10 minutes.
All right, so the pre stream chat, I timed somebody over 10 minutes.
But hold on.
Yes, I apologize for timing you out for 10 minutes in pre stream.
But let's talk about the context first.
You asked me to play Destiny 2 PVP tomorrow.
Do you think that is that it?
Should I have timed you up for an hour?
My little sister is afraid of you.
Why is your little sister watching this stream?
Does your little sister hate me now?
I've got somebody here.
Come on over here.
It's me, Elmo.
Hey, Elmo.
What are you doing here?
Well, I want to teach everybody some sharing and how to share your milk.
She's 24.
Press the button next to it.
She really does look like a GTA mod.
It still makes me laugh.
Flying Dutchman sucks so bad.
GTA mod.
I can't get over it.
Okay, perfect game.
Come on.
Please designate a corner of the screen for bird watching videos.
Well, this is it.
The fucking bird video is distracting me.
I keep looking at it.
I keep looking over here at these birds.
Hey, get out of there.
That's not yours.
That's not for you.
Stop eating the bird's bird seed.
I'm more interested.
Wait.
He's like, hey, get out of here.
This is our bird team.
My absolute favorite part of Harry Potter was Voldemort's strange sounds he would make.
Did somebody make a compilation?
It's over Simpson.
It's not over Simpson.
Jerma, I would rather see you in the hospital than on TikTok.
That's so fucked up.
Holy shit, dude.
What the fuck?
I'm just going to read this.
Had a dream last night.
Jerma became like a mainstream celebrity by pioneering a new type of stream.
He would play a game like normal.
But every once in a while, he'd let chat keep the horror and put this like red and black
pulsating mass on screen.
Kind of looked like an AI generated image.
And the whole deal was that everyone who saw it thought it was the funniest thing they'd
ever seen.
But every time he'd show it, one viewer who saw it would die.
It ended when he showed it on stream and dropped dead.
The stream was left on for 72 hours to honor his memory.
It was dead quiet with just his body and a slowly pulsating red mass on screen beside
him.
Stop pretending to be interested.
You're not going to play any of these games.
You'll be too busy playing like fart simulator 2013.
I gotta hide.
I gotta get out and hide.
I'm on the ground.
Is this the Union?
We've unionized.
Cigarette?
It's just a used, a done cigarette.
No, that's a banana.
That's a banana.
Relax.
When it gets to this face, however, the TV froze.
So I tried turning it on and off to restart it, but the TV just won't turn off.
And it's stuck on this fucked up image of Jerma's face.
Okay, I don't know how that happened.
A couple hours pass, and I don't know why it took me a while, but I finally decide to
unplug the TV.
And then I realized that the face is permanently burned onto the screen.
Like it's just stuck there.
My parents aren't back until later in the night.
So now I'm freaking out trying to cover the screen so that they don't see the stupid
face burned onto their thousand dollar TV.
What do I do?
If only it was real.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of the best one guy moment of the year.
Oh, there are a lot of good ones too.
There were a lot of good ones.
With 27% of the vote, Peep the Horror.
Peep the Horror is your winner at 27%.
Jigsaw's Rubik's Cube at 17.6%.
And then right below it is the weird face burn-in at 17.3.
There was a 45 vote difference between 2 and 3.
They're all winners to me.
These are all winners to me.
The Rubik's Cube, that was some of the funniest shit I've ever seen in my life.
The burn-in shit was some of the funniest shit.
I will tell you right now, I know that people say this about their communities.
They say, oh man, my community is so funny.
Some of you guys just come up with some of the most fucked up funny shit I've ever heard of.
And it is an honor to be able to see it and laugh at it.
So let me just be clear about that.
We will do the rest of these in a little bit.
We'll go back to the rumble.
There are a few more matches to do.
Hopefully it doesn't crash.
Hopefully you can hear it.
Yeah, it's so hard to pick between what the community jokes that you guys make.
It's genuinely funny shit.
Let's do a couple more matches in the rumble.
Well, not the rumble.
The rumble's not till later.
We're not there yet.
Let us peep the horror.
Peep the Horror wins.
That's just such an insane concept to me.
What a wild thing to come up with.
Is this going to be a 7-hour stream?
We'll definitely do the Pacific countdown.
But I don't know how much longer after that.
I'm having a great time.
This is a fucking blast.
Hopefully you're having fun, too.
Let us continue with the rumble.
We have, I think, three more matches to do in the Germania card.
Oh, God.
Fuck this match.
Okay.
This is a ladder match.
This is a six-man ladder match.
This could go on for a very long time.
I hope it does not last that long.
Remember, tell me I'm funny now.
You're probably funny.
I don't know.
Is it mountain time in 30 minutes?
Yeah.
25 minutes.
30 minutes.
There were so many characters.
I had to just...
We had to do so many matches because you can only do 30 people in a rumble.
Almost all of the people in the rumble are people that you haven't seen yet.
I was like, damn, we have fucking 60 characters.
We have to put them in somewhere.
And this is where we put them in.
So without further ado, we got another match here.
We got a ladder match.
Six-man ladder match.
Here we go.
There were so many characters.
This is a ladder match, which means you have to climb to the top of the ladder,
grab the money in the bank, and this is between Rathu Flush,
of course, from the Flush family, the Sims family.
Here's Rathu Flush.
Quite a few Flushes.
Nice bugeyes, yeah.
There's Rathu Flush.
Who could possibly come in next?
I wonder if it's anybody else in the Flush family.
It could be the entire Flush family.
Could be.
Of course, that's Grunty Flush.
Where did he just go?
Never give up.
Okay.
Thanks, Grunty.
That's good advice.
Don't ever give up.
Grunty Flush, Rathu Flush.
You probably see where this is going.
There's Ratchet Flush.
Yeah, they're all 220 pounds.
It's to make sure nobody has an advantage in the actual matches.
Some are actually, they weigh a lot less.
Any other Flush family members we should be aware of?
Oh my God, that's Strong Henry Flush.
He was nominated Top Character of the Year.
I hope he dies in this match.
I hope somebody breaks his neck in this match.
Alright, fuck this guy. Let's go.
Who could forget Bumpy Flush?
The cat.
This just burped so loud.
This is the character I dropped the meteor on.
I dropped a meteor on Bumpy Flush accidentally.
Not on purpose, accidentally.
And finally, who could forget Sus Flush?
Or the sus guy?
Either one, who cares.
It doesn't matter.
Sus Flush.
I hope this does not go 40 goddamn minutes.
I'm hoping this is over in 10 minutes.
That would be ideal.
That'd be great.
Here we go, the six man ladder match between the sus family.
That's not them.
It's the Flush family.
Sus Flush, Grunty Flush, Ratchet Flush, Rathew Flush, Strong Henry Flush, Bumpy Flush.
Here they go.
The only way you can win this match if you climb to the top of the ladder,
grab that money in the bag briefcase.
The sus dynasty.
Already we have a few problems.
Sus Flush going after Strong Henry.
Gets double dropkick for his trouble.
No, you can't predict all four.
No, you can't.
This is from that dogshit Sims game I did.
Grunty, going for the ladder immediately.
Oh my goodness.
Bumpy Flush with a belly to back suplex.
I don't think they'll ever be a winner of this match.
I have to be honest.
This is shit mid card serpent bullshit.
Fuck.
Just be happy there's not six serpents for the love of God.
It's the entire slush family for God's sake.
Whatever the dumb name is, who cares?
I don't even know the names.
Bumpy is the cat.
Sus is that guy, me right there.
I think that's Rathew.
Is Rathew going to take it right now?
No, no, no.
Going up.
He could get it right now.
Rathew going for the belt right now.
Why is he giving me indicators?
I'm not playing.
I swear to God.
Oh, and down goes Rathew Flush.
Ratchet Flush has got the briefcase.
There's no way he gets it right now.
No way.
Somebody stop him.
Stop him right now.
Grunty.
Stop there and stop him from playing his weird minigame.
Thank goodness Grunty with a couple of abdomen punches.
I think Ratchet is through.
I don't know why the indicators are on screen.
I swear to God.
It's a fake match.
Now Sus Flush has the ladder.
Thinking about going up himself maybe.
No, strong Henry.
Voted best character of the year.
Going to show why it seems like.
No, no, no, no, Sus Flush.
A couple of elbows into his head.
There he goes over the top ropes.
Pumpy Flush gets a double dropkick and Ratchet Flush picks up.
No, he gets killed by strong Henry Flush.
No one's ever going to get this ladder up.
It's not going to happen.
I may as well skip this match.
Because there's not a chance in hell that this ladder goes up and somebody climbs it.
Prove I'm not cheating.
See?
Pumpy Flush takes a backhand to the back of the back by Sus Flush.
I'm actually, I wonder who wins this.
I have no idea who could possibly win this.
They all have such shit stats too.
I made sure of it.
As Sus Flush, I can't, indeed it's hard to say that after a bottle of champagne.
Give me a break.
Rathew Flush takes Ratchet Flush.
From the top turnbuckle in Grunty now.
Resting on the side here.
No one's going to win.
As Rathew and Ratchet are on the top rope.
Big suplex incoming, here it goes.
On his back, onto the ladder potentially.
Oh, there it is.
Huge.
Big pain there on Ratchet Flush.
Wait, why did that ladder fall?
As Bumpy grabs the ladder.
Oh no, Bumpy now going to maybe think about going to the top.
I think it's going to happen here.
Bumpy thinking about climbing that ladder to grab the money in the bank.
Is it possible?
Sus Flush is going to, no, has something to say about it.
A strong Henry.
Does anyone care about a single character in this match?
I don't.
A meteor could hit the arena right now.
And kill everybody in the ring.
And I would not care.
As strong Henry Flush takes the ladder away from Bumpy Flush.
Setting it up.
Trying to get to the top.
No!
Closing it down.
Setting it up again.
And not climbing it for some reason.
I think the fan favorite might be Bumpy Flush.
Nope.
Going to close it up again.
Going to open it again.
I don't think it's in the right spot.
Strong Henry.
No, no.
You can't get it from there.
And I have to move it.
You're going to have to move it.
Yep.
There it is.
Okay.
Thank you.
Move it.
Just, okay.
Doesn't care.
Doesn't seem to mind.
Bumpy the Betrayer.
As Grunty has Sus on the ground.
Look at the kicks to the sternum.
Eye rake.
No, throwing him outside.
What is Ratchet doing up there?
I think strong, no, no, no.
Ratchet's going to go to the outside.
What are you?
Why would you do that?
Go into the ring where Strong Henry has got the money in the bank right now.
He's got it.
Let's see if he does this little weird puzzle.
Don't think so.
As Grunty and Strong Henry flush.
I don't know their names.
I killed them all in one day in Sims.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care if any of these guys die.
They could live or die and I don't care.
Strong Henry?
Bumpy Henry?
I don't know their names.
You guys all want the Sus guy to win anyways.
He's going up there right now.
And as the Sus guy reaches the top of the money in the bank.
Will Sus Flush win?
And win as best?
Flush?
Shit?
Dumb fucking loser family?
I don't know.
No.
Will he take it?
No, he will not.
That was so stupid.
Out goes Ratty Flush.
Strong Henry got Sus Flush by the neck.
Flipping up into the back.
And...
Whoa!
Make noises because you can't do commentary anymore.
As Bumpy Flush taking the ladder.
I think Bumpy might get it here.
Everybody's distracted.
Not in a great place.
But Bumpy is unhatching the latch on the money in the bank.
Will Bumpy Flush take it?
Ratchet and Strong Henry have something to say.
No.
As Grunty throws Bumpy out of...
I don't even know their names.
I'm going to be honest.
As Green Guy takes Elf Guy and throws Green Guy out of the ring.
We've only got two left in the ring as Ratchet and Rathew.
I think Rathew has a good opportunity here.
To set the ladder up in the middle of the ring.
Looks like he does.
As Grunty rolls in.
Can somebody throw a grenade into the ring?
Can somebody throw a grenade?
As Bumpy Flush gets to the top of the ladder.
Grabbing the briefcase.
Will Bumpy...
What are you doing, you idiot?
Just grab it for God's sake.
Bumpy!
Two right hands.
Three right hands.
Raking home.
This is never going to end.
Alright.
Ratchet set it up and get the damn money.
Ratchet, Flush getting the ladder set up.
As Bumpy is not happy about it.
Six man ladder may have been not a great idea.
I will say.
Although Ratchet going up there now.
Not going to be able to do it as Sus Flush takes it.
Nope.
What?
That's Rathew?
Who cares?
As Bumpy Flush, I think Bumpy is the favorite.
Sus Flush over the top ropes by Rathew.
We've got Strong, we've got Grunty, we've got Rathew in the ring right now.
Who will set the ladder up and who will actually win this?
Grunty got the ladder now going in the middle of the ring.
Thinking about climbing the ropes.
No, don't you...
Oh my God.
What are you doing?
Grunty outside.
Why would you throw Bumpy back in the ring?
You don't want to put people...
You want to climb the ladder.
You don't want to put people back in the ring.
Get up there.
Grunty is thinking about winning here.
Will we see a victory?
I don't think so.
There are too many people.
The AI will always knock you down unless...
I guess not.
I don't know.
Bumpy, get up there and win, please.
Bumpy, I got a show to run.
You got to get up there.
Come on, Bumpy.
Bumpy, I got a show to move on with, so get up there.
Bumpy Flush the cat, the meatier cat that you all love.
And Ratchet Flush fighting now for the briefcase.
Who will get the briefcase?
I wonder what's it going to be?
Punch in the face to Bumpy.
Bumpy takes another right hand.
Two more.
Will Bumpy go down in a strong...
AI push over ladder.
AI, I fucking moron.
You get off.
Okay.
Now I push you over top rope and Bumpy win.
Bumpy's got it.
Bumpy's got the briefcase.
Someone set it up, please.
Lord, use the ladder as a weapon.
Stop just trying to climb it, you idiots.
Call the firing squad.
Grunty's finishing him.
Call an air strike him.
All right, Ratchet's going up now.
Finally, Ratchet's going to get the band.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Bumpy's underneath there.
I have no idea who wins this.
No idea.
I think Ratchet's got it.
It's never going to end.
I think I have to intervene.
It's not going to end.
I have to intervene because I don't think it's going to end.
As Grunty sets the ladder up, it's Bumpy now.
Outside the ring, Grunty go.
Go, get it.
Complete it.
End it.
As Grunty, no, Strong Henry has something to say about it.
Potentially, no.
I don't think so.
Might get up there in a fast enough time.
And there goes Grunty falling back down.
No, stop pushing the ladder over you dickheads.
Oh, my God.
Someone please win.
This is so sus.
Okay.
Throw dice in the air to find out who wins.
Because I don't know.
Oh, Matthew.
Stop.
Walk.
You're having a lot of trouble right now.
You're having a lot of trouble.
I wish you would end it, but you just won't.
Yeah, okay.
You could grab the ladder and set it up.
Maybe climb up there and grab the bunny in the bank
and we could do the next few awards.
Or you could just get...
Okay.
There are other weapons they could use, too.
Someone said, this is awesome.
All right.
Wait.
Strong Henry Flush going to the top,
trying to grab the money in the bank.
Will he get it?
He's got his hands on it.
He got it.
Strong Henry Flush is your winner.
Didn't win best character of the year,
but won in this match.
Congratulations, Strong Henry Flush.
Man, what an upset.
It could have been Matthew.
It could have been Ratchet two times.
This is what we call delete six characters from the Rumble.
Because there's like 30 new characters you haven't seen in the Rumble.
Okay.
Let's go to the next one.
Why not?
Let's go.
We got so many more categories.
There's so many more.
Oh, this one's going to be big.
This is a Tornado Tag Steel Cage match.
And I am very interested in this one.
I'm locked in.
I'm laser focused on this one.
New Year coming up for Mountain Central.
What is it?
Mountain Time?
We'll get them all.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Can you punish Rathew?
He's already punished he exists.
There are 30,000 people here right now.
My God.
All right.
Tornado Tag Steel Cage.
This is a food related match.
Should we wait till the New Year for Mountain?
There are only two matches after this.
We're getting close.
We're like another hour or two out.
I'll wait.
All right.
Let's wait.
So this is for Mountain Time coming up here.
Nobody lives in Mountain Time.
Lots of people live in Mountain Time.
Come on.
Here we go.
Two minutes till New Year's Mountain Time.
It's just a mountain.
What is Mountain?
What states are in Mountain Time?
Arizona?
Colorado?
Oh, who fucking cares about Mountain Time?
Fuck it.
Midnight in Mountain Time.
And all the 1200 people that live in Mountain Time.
Happy New Year to Mountain Time.
I'm kidding.
We'll wait.
Just wait.
One minute.
And then we got we got Pacific right after in less than an hour.
Bunch of what?
I'm on like a fucking McDonald's double cheeseburger right now.
So bad.
All right.
30 seconds until Mountain Time New Year's.
Let's count it down.
Let's get it.
You skipped Central?
No, I didn't.
We did Central.
Here we go.
All you Mountainers.
Ten seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Happy New Year Mountain Time.
The next match coming up here is a big one.
Food related like I said before.
Let me make sure this is on the screen so you can see it.
Oh!
Link!
Fuck it.
Who cares?
Who gives a shit?
Oh, that was Gordon Ramsay.
The guy that's going to get us all banned from Twitch.
The guy that's going to get all our channels shut down.
The Easy Bake Oven and Gordon Ramsay.
There's the Easy Bake Oven.
Nice one, Ron.
Was the Easy Bake Oven 2021?
No, but it made the most sense to pair with Gordon Ramsay.
This game sucks.
Play NFL.
No, we got Gordon Ramsay.
All the way from Hell's Kitchen.
California.
Las Vegas.
Wellington.
It's unbelievable.
Don't mess with the dough.
Don't send him a TikTok.
Showing you messing with his Wellington.
What are you doing to my Wellington?
Don't do that.
Going to get us all cancelled on Twitch.
This is a cage match, by the way.
They ain't getting out.
So Gordon Ramsay and the Easy Bake Oven versus the McRiddler.
Huge fast food fan.
Big into McDonald's.
Wendy's.
Burger King.
Big Burger King fan himself.
There's the McRiddler from Saints Row 2.
His partner is none other than...
You probably saw it.
I leaked it for a second.
But the point still stands.
That's the Burger King Long Chicken Sandwich.
That's the only thing you should order at Burger King.
Everything else at Burger King sucks.
Absolute asshole.
There's two menu items at Burger King that you should order.
This is one of them.
The other one is just their french fries.
Nothing else on that whole menu is good.
I'm not going to lie to you. I have to be real.
But the Long Chicken Burger King Sandwich,
and their french fries,
and their onion rings,
get them up to a C tier.
Or a B tier, at least.
The only way you win this match is if you escape the ring.
No pins.
No knockouts.
You gotta climb that cage and get out.
Close the cage down on our four combatants.
Let's see what happens.
Gordon Ramsay, Easy Bake Oven,
Long Chicken Sandwich, and the McRiddler.
Somebody has to get out.
You just have to escape.
I thought he threw him over the edge.
Long Chicken Sandwich is already going up there.
McRiddler and the Long Chicken are leaving already.
JKJ...
I'm getting indicators already.
I'm not playing the game as they're trying to both leave at the same time.
Gordon Ramsay not going to have that though.
Or the Easy Bake Oven.
One could say they're in a gigantic oven.
Closed.
Afraid.
Trying to get out of this oven.
Juan Gordo.
Yep, Gordon has a big advantage here.
The last week or two he's had over 430,000 concurrent viewers on Twitch.
He's got a lot of power behind him.
He's got a lot of momentum behind him.
Although I'm not really sure that can fight against the McRiddler.
Who had...
A month ago.
16,000 concurrent viewers.
That's pretty good.
Trying to get out.
Immediately can't get out.
Has the long...
No, Gordon now going out.
Trying to climb out.
Long Chicken Sandwich gets him by the foot.
Throws him into that rough steel cage.
There he goes in his Hell's Kitchen garb.
The McRiddler must be so sweaty.
The McChicken is too tall.
Up in the air, Hurricane Rana onto the Easy Bake oven.
20 community subs from Mr. Sark.
Mr. Sark, how the fuck are you?
Wait a minute.
We have two people on opposite teams trying to get out at the same time.
Will one of them get out?
They have free reign.
Who can climb faster?
Will Gordon Ramsay get out or will the Long Chicken Sandwich get out first?
Why would you punch him out when he's stupid?
Pull him back into the ring.
Gordon Ramsay going under the top rubs.
No.
Oh, this is bad.
Long Chicken Sandwich making his way over McRiddler.
Has got Gordon Ramsay.
Who is going to go over first?
Gordon can't.
McRiddler is distracting Gordon Ramsay.
As Long Chicken Sandwich is going over.
Easy Bake oven now has...
Oh, it's over.
That's it. It's over.
You cannot come back. That's it.
Long Chicken Sandwich gets over the edge.
Which...
Why is it not over?
Wait, the McRiddler has to get over there too.
Oh, shit.
They both have to get over the ropes.
Gordon, what are you doing?
No, no, no, no. Go over.
Go over. What are you doing?
Don't come back in.
I thought only one had to make it across.
No.
They both have to go.
Still fighting for his life.
Gordon trying to get over the top ropes.
Will he get over there still?
Oh, this is going to get very interesting.
Gordon Ramsay, I think, made his way over into the cage.
That's it.
It just now comes down to these two in the middle of the ring.
Gordon Ramsay definitely making it over.
Easy Bake oven now trying to climb up.
No.
This is going to be tough.
I have no idea who's going to win.
Ramsay out.
Long Chicken out.
McRiddler on the way out.
Will we see an end to this match right now?
McRiddler getting his leg over the top of the cage.
Easy Bake oven now climbing up.
You've got to pull him back.
Don't punch him.
Pull him back.
Oh, shit.
Oh, what an upset.
If the Easy Bake oven pulls him over, this is a huge deal.
Both going at the same exact time.
No.
Start fighting.
Punch, push.
What are you doing?
Oh, they're on the top, sitting, straddling the top of the cage.
Who's going to win?
The McRiddler.
The Easy Bake oven.
What are they?
It's too tense.
Be careful you don't knock your opponent to the left because they will win.
I have no...
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
Long Chicken Sandwich and the McRiddler have won this.
Unless a New Year's miracle happens, I don't think we're going to see anything else.
McRiddler and Long Chicken Sandwich have beaten Gordon Ramsay in the Easy Bake oven for Victor
on the food match.
That's the end of that one.
McRiddler and Long Chicken Sandwich.
That could have gone either way.
Either way.
Congratulations to the McRiddler and Long Chicken Sandwich.
Nice work.
Fan favorites.
Scripted.
What do you mean scripted?
I didn't script any of this.
It's all random.
Okay.
It's now time to get to the big categories, the meaty ones, the real meaty ones.
Going up next.
We've got a long way to go, but we're going to push forward.
Best Scare Moment of the Year, which is...
You can probably guess.
Ummmm...
Scary Moments.
VR.
Non-VR.
Horror Games.
Scared.
I get scared.
My voice is junk.
Hold on.
God, I talked for three hours.
My voice is junk.
What the fuck?
This is the nominees for Best Scare Moment of the Year.
Wait, did I not mute?
I muted, right?
I hope I did.
Okay.
Thank God.
Here are your nominees for Best Scare Moment of the Year.
Horror Games.
Jumpscares.
Did I do it?
Nobody picked me up.
I'm like a microphone in an office complex being like, the job is done.
I just blew it.
I got too close.
I was talking.
Alright.
Let go!
Oh, I was holding on to it.
Let's get this shit out of me.
I didn't let it go.
Easy.
Don't let me get the spray can.
Don't let me get the fucking spray can.
If everyone wants to talk shit...
Stop it!
What the fuck is he doing?
That's to get the shit out of me.
And I did it.
What the fuck was that?
I still...
I don't know if this is addictive.
It could be addictive.
Did he just launch those back at me?
I don't know.
Holy shit.
How are you doing that?
Where'd he go?
Why are you alive?
Ooh, we can break that.
You're almost boring.
Let me just see if I...
I lost!
Oh!
Are we alright?
It's stuck on me!
Get it off me!
Oh, no.
It's alright.
Is it open?
Now it is.
Look out the window.
04.
What happened?
I didn't pull the pin.
Did I?
When did I pull the pin?
I didn't pull the pin.
What happened?
Look.
I was just holding it in my hand.
Did the pin come out?
No, it didn't.
What the fuck is happening, dude?
Oh my god!
It's not even opening!
I hate this shit.
I hated this.
Mama!
Yeah, I agree.
He got me!
Oh my god!
That baby...
This shit's so fucked up.
That was a good game, though.
Big fan.
Alright, your winner for best scare of the year is...
I haven't broken the seal.
Oops.
Ooh, close.
Very close.
Why?
Why was this one of the most skipped?
This is the second most skipped category the whole year.
Why?
Monster Baby Eats Germa at 15%, Accidental Zerk Escape at 14%, and Cat Twerk Glitch at
13%.
Second most skipped.
Why?
Too scary?
Because it's scary.
Okay, whatever.
Monster Baby Eats Germa.
That game is so fucked up.
That part in particular, oh my god, that messed me up.
I hated that part.
Not even a big deal, but my god.
I felt so awful playing through that part.
Alright, meaty category number five.
We've got best singing.
There's best and worst singing, by the way.
So these are back to back, so get ready.
Kind of like best noise, worst noise.
They could be...
You look like John from Garfield.
You know what?
Fuck off, okay?
I'm getting this off.
I'm not John from Garfield, for god's sakes.
Get it off.
Get it off me.
I don't want it on anymore.
Sometimes I sing.
You've heard me sing maybe once or twice on this stream already.
Here are your nominees for the best time that I've...
Oh, god damn it.
Fucking god damn John Arbuckle.
Fuck!
No!
It is!
Fuck!
No!
It can't be!
It is.
I'll stand up.
Fine.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
Who cares?
God damn it!
I fucking quit.
I quit streaming.
Best...
Here's the nominees for best singing of the year.
Best singing of the year.
Here we go.
Caves, caves.
How about Minecraft Steve?
Alright, quiet.
Caves.
Sure, but you can find it in that cave.
Cave.
Where can I get it?
I'm going to warm myself up to be Mario because I'm a huge fan.
Before I say anything, I get into the audition booth.
I get into the room.
They're all like, okay, so we're waiting.
They're waiting for me.
I just put the headphones on.
I start the audition.
I just start going...
Da da da da da da da da.
Da da da da da da da.
Music.
Da da da da da da da da.
Da da da da da da da da da...
Something like that, right?
And it goes...
Here we go.
Da da da da da da da da da da.
Oh, that's the remix, but you know.
Hurry!
Do the famous Javr Dine cheat code.
Oh, you're right!
Up, up, up down, down, down.
Up, up, up, up, down, down, down, down, down.
B-A-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-A-B-A-B-A-B.
Left, right, left, right, left, right, B-A-B.
B-A-B-I-B-I-B-I-B-O-B-O-B-B-B-O-B-B-B-B-B-I-BO-BO.
Did I get it?
Oh, we got our number one Victory Royale,
Yeah, Fortnite, we bout to get down.
Ten kills on the board right now,
just wiped out Tomato Town.
My friend just got down.
I revived Hamon, we're going southbound.
Out of the park we're going south, sweet.
Look at the map. Look at the mark sheet.
The doi version of Duel of Fates.
I'm going to sing Happy Birthday to you, but I'm going to replace a word in there with binary.
Happy one, zero, one, one, zero, one, zero to you.
Happy one, zero, zero, one, zero, one, one, zero, zero to you.
Happy one, zero, one, one, zero, zero, one, zero.
Dear Baldy, happy one, zero, zero, one, zero, one, zero to you.
I kept calling this guy Baldy and that's not, that wasn't their name.
Will they be pyrotechnics? Yeah.
Um, I don't know.
Oh, here we go. Star Wars.
You can't DM, see, a, this stream because it's in a video game, not a real fucking movie.
You can't. I've read all kinds of threads about how this works and this is allowed.
Uh, is it?
Nope.
I got something. We got one.
Give me that. Come on. 71 million a sprint and that's a coin.
Oh,
the best singing of the year goes to, it wasn't even close.
Chug Jug with 32% of the vote killed it.
Giant enemy beatpox remix and the hamster dance at 17 and 11% respectively.
Chug Jug at 32%. God damn.
Well, that was a meme. It was a meme last year. Of course, people are going to vote for the meme.
Chug Jug won best singer of the year. Now with the bad comes the bad, worse.
Here are your nominees for worst singing of the year.
Not looking forward to this one.
Worst singing of the year, your nominees are
This is purged up on her face. She got her hair tied up in braids.
I am the ace of spades. Wait, is that the
Right without music, this looks fucking really weird. I look like a fucking creep.
I can't do this.
Welcome to the stream. You've all shown your bare faces. It's all
Buzzard lyrics.
I got swinging steps and I'm swinging back. I got cross steps and we're gonna shoulder shake.
Don't get too close to me. Drop it down. Pop it up. Pop it up.
Play nice and you swim back and you bring it on up. Then you think twice.
Then you got altered thoughts and no flutter. Don't you dare. What's on your mind? It's disturbia.
Give me that. Come on. 71 million a sprint.
Why is this here?
And that's a coin.
Oh,
so split. So split. All right. The winner of the worst singing of the year goes to
uh with uh 59 percent of the vote not even close hair tied up in braids from WarioWare
and the raid 2.0 song with 16 not even not even close and then hey Mickey acapella at seven
what it's pretty big landslides this year really big landslides all right moving on we'll do uh
we've got we'll do probably four more five more coming to x's worst cat puke which if you don't
know is this 30 000 people heard me do that which i can't believe there are this many people fucking
here watching this but okay here we are uh these are the worst times of the whole year that i did
just that into the microphone and pissed thousands of people off in one fell swoop so uh all the times
i gulped all the times i made it very uh very aware that i was doing a cat puke sound here are
your worst versions of this for the whole year i have no idea what won this by the way i have
not a single clue we're gonna find out together here we go food oh how about a piece of bread
because it's the easiest thing to make just shake shake shake shake
oh uh have i eaten what was the last time i ate i don't know fuck it i'm not ready
hello it's me daughter killer i'd like to talk to you i'd like to have a little bit of conversation
that one was pretty bad oh fucking chugging his blood oh i have two toilet water my favorite
quality okay why did i read that because it was there and it was for me i could see it
i could see it cat puke somebody nominated oh cotton candy ice cream let me leave my mouth under
cotton candy i promised that i wouldn't fucking cry when i turned the stream on but
what i hate this one oh god somebody said why is this a category dude there's like nine categories
in this stream that don't need to exist but they do for no i don't know why they do
and your winner for worst cat puke of the year buy a lot weirdly toilet water
my favorite one with 29 percent of the vote that's a lot crying cat puke and then shake
shake and this is also the most skipped category 1700 people skipped this category this is the most
skipped category the whole year all right these are the ones you want to see these are the big
ones we are down to our final one two three four five categories these are huge best gaming moment
of the year worst gaming moment of the year and worst meltdown are you ready germa arbuckle god
damn it i swear to god i'm not i did not do that on purpose i feel so it's i'm so cringed out of my
mind it's time to reveal the nominees for the best gaming moment of the year i might be a little tipsy
it's new years you got a problem hope not i'm having a grand old time here we go the nominees
and by the way gaming moment can mean like i did something really good big fucking like kill streak
oh i did something nobody else does huge moment in gaming huge gaming moment is he drunk do you
really care that much it's new year's eve i'm fucking hanging out my goddamn office
best gaming moment of the year here we go okay that's going to be like 100
oh nobody checked that guy for a cannon go let it roll oh let me make sure it's actually going to
work just make sure that's it yeah game over right way get out of here oh i gotta keep it going i
got a first try the secret bosses in every chapter right i have to let's go yeah all right all right
okay okay got 73 oh shit
if you fly i'll just be teleported to the backseat what why are things exploding on the
side you ran over all i got 15 trees oh what i got you with that no i didn't i changed my zoom
button what i okay control i shot the arrow and his head that should be a cliff get back on that
fucking field if i don't win this add 10 billion to the debt yeah i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm
done i'm done that's it i'm done fucking practice makes perfect baby uh someone said my edible just
kicked in germa what do i do relax sit back and sit back just breathe and just watch and hang out
relax man you're good you're gonna be fine just chill the winner for best gaming moment of the
year let's break it i don't have this info close very close delta rune chapter two secret boss first
try again at 26 and then mario 64 bomb and owlless in the same minute at 23 percent and then wario
where 73 super hard mode at 16 spampton spampton spampton that was pretty good i who else has done
that first try spampton give me a break all right let's see the dog shit stuff i did this year too
so if i did really good then i could also do really bad uh last year i think not reading an analog
clock correctly was pretty high up there does not need to be specifically video this could be
anything this does not need to be strictly video games because i couldn't read eight o'clock on an
analog clock and holy shit i got raked over the coals for that one so here are your nominees for
worst gamer moment of the year let's see the opposite what oh shit the fucking are the balloons
keeping me up go down god damn it what do i do i can't attached how do i get out of here
we're gonna do some jumping jacks to get your heart rate up let your arms hang at your side
with your feet shoulder width apart oh no it's up motion jump bringing your arms up and spreading
i don't know how to do that ready go 60 seconds
is he talking he's talking how is how is he still talking
am i supposed to be sitting down oh shit oops grab the pistol and shoot who you
ha ha iowa nope pennsylvania is right here california that's not what do you mean not
california that's what i just clicked i just clicked right here hit him fucking swing at him
what happened oh my controller unplugged that's why i couldn't swing at it are you guys ready
we're not on like a time limit or anything but i don't want to be slow so hold on let me turn this
all right so turn one i uh all right there is a timer there's wait wait wait wait wait what
do you see time don't say that stop lying to me oh i did i do it i didn't know there was a
timer what the fuck this looks i look so stupid i like this this is somebody that's never installed
the game once i can't fucking believe it the interior angles of a triangle always add up to
how many degrees the interior angles of a triangle add up to 180 what did you guys put oh no oh they
add up to oh shit when was the last time anyone even thought of a triangle like a fucking dorito
you ate last week yeah no shit thank you oh now i'm in trouble this is bad this is so bad look at
how shitty this looks like i don't care about this game if you play tetris for 10 minutes
you can do this okay okay ladies and gentlemen the winner of the worst gaming moment of the year
yeah i mean that sucked but is this my fault or did i just get screwed the mario kart last second
shell at 24 percent of the vote that's that but that's not even my fault i got i got absolutely
decimated that's not my fault it sucked but whatever 24 of the vote mario kart last second
shell and then accidental war crime in vr and then a jedi lost to a tree i can understand the next
two but that i how am i what am i supposed to do about that that just happens in mario
kart you get what am i supposed to do all right our final category before we do the last bit of
the rumble actually you know what there's four categories left
there's two matches all right here we go we're going to do the next match of the rumble
so this is the final match of the rumble but until the rumble we got 15 minutes till new year is oh
god i knew this is gonna be a long one i'll keep this on for now we got 15 minutes until the new
year so give me one second there's one more match to see and it's a dollhouse match one would say
it is the dollhouse match i have no idea what's gonna happen here one more before the rumble we
should be able to do this and then say happy new year do the last few categories and then do the
rumble this is an eight man there's an eight person dollhouse rumble what about intermission
we'll do that after this i promise after this match you can go take a piss get a water chill
for a second this is the last um break we're gonna take after this here we go are you gonna
be done at midnight no more like 1 a.m pacific what the hell is going on what all right that's
community jake by the way i don't know why he needs this much security it's kind of weird
i don't know why they're being escorted by this many people
okay eight person brawl community jake if you don't know community jake is the person that
put together the dollhouse and the archaeology and the halloween stream and the bugleberry cauldron
that this is literally my manager this is my production manager on the screen right now and
i i wish him luck because he got a lot more to deal with so he's the funny one don't ever say
that self insert intro community jake making his debut in the germa rumble there are eight people
so we gotta go quick who could be next in our dollhouse rumble i wonder getting a little dark
in here that could be uh if i have my eyes or not need to be checked or anything that could be
who's that oh that's death i had sex with this person on stream i had sex with this person on
camera death is your second contestant the eight person rumble weird flex
who's next one of the clowns clown man one of the two clowns remember there are two clowns
not just one clown man two clowns seven serpents god where's emilia just hold on a minute
we've got edna kit boga making their first appearance in the rumble e edna edna it's the
same dress too which is crazy i can't believe the same dress is here where are all the fans
have they all look at these empty seats what the fuck is the bear pretty good announcement
somebody said this is a jobber match i don't think so this could be pretty crazy i wonder
if this takes us to the new year i hope it does who's next that is oh it's uncle ted by the way
uncle ted making his debut in the germa rumble from las vegas back from the dead welcome uncle
ted how are you good to see you again he lives uh in some universes he does in some universes
who's next is this the germa multiverse that's the regular verse coming up next is emilia with
the bread that they wanted to have put in their mouth serving it up on a tray emilia ladies and
gentlemen welcome to the rumble emilia emilia throwing those pancakes okay very good the game
has a very limited name selection who's next it's the second clown clown lady instead of clown man
clown lady we got both clowns here by the way clown too that's right i mean couldn't be anybody
outside i don't i don't think so eight man dollhouse brawl here we go ring that bell as edna
goes right for death the two clowns might have the advantage by the way because they're both working
together eight people in the ring absolute carnage is unfolding edna going for the pin on death
immediately not even spending one second as we got action outside the ring not even focused
community jake and the bear outside fighting i don't think there are very there are no rules by the
way zero weapons count furniture counts false count anywhere it's going to be hard to pay
attention to what's going on on the screen as uncle ted is already dead for the third time
good luck paying attention to any of this balls count anywhere edna and clown lady outside was
oh no no no no no sorry emilia clown lady outside edna with death in the middle of the ring
the ref doesn't even know where to go this is not flush family this is the dollhouse
i got my money on edna if i would have bet uh five dollars it would go on edna right now
edna right now we got five minutes to the new year in pacific time i am ready i'm waiting for
it it's gonna be carnage here as emilia and community emilia with a big uppercut on community
jack's face right in his chin right directly on the ball of his chin weapon time emilia going
under the ropes into the apron looking for a weapon no clown lady picks up emilia no weapons
so far going for a pin clown man on death willy get it i don't know who's being pinned right now
but somebody is it's gonna be hard for the referee it's gonna be like babysitting children
why is the ref not over here go over here what he's all the way to the left there's all the
actions on the right man get over there the bear ted is in a submission right now
he USA edna's got somebody's being pinned while edna power bomb on the clown man will they get the
pin referee where's the referee no not even close not even remotely close not even a one count
somebody else being pinned outside good luck knowing who's gonna win this shit uncle ted and
the bear where uncle ted is technically dead it might have some it might have some ghostly
abilities i'm not sure as edna throwing two people into the ring edna now really fired up
i'd love to see a pin right here from edna big belly to back suplex on the clown man
three minutes till new years that's right haunting just who's being pinned clown lady has
emilia almost got pinned there that was damn that was close that was the closest one so far
that was like two and a quarter as community jake and death fighting out there and oh what
a unbelievable knee smashing move by edna edna going for a pin will they get it too no oh so
close who what whose camera is this go fucking zoom in idiot who's pinned who is filming this
this camera sucks lean forward two seats man throw the camera down five rows what the hell
are you doing oh my god what a terrible camera edna now going into the staircase as uh community
jake is being pinned right now by death no what what happened somebody got eliminated who got
eliminated who what what the fuck happened everybody sit down in front of me i can't see
shit the bear got eliminated oh my god like a great view what's happening
30 seconds till new years the bear has been eliminated by the way happy fucking new year
to all you pacific coasters thanks for watching 10 seconds will you move the camera for god's
sakes i can't see anything and all acquaintance me forgot i'd love this camera to move
i have no idea who's winning this game somebody just got eliminated and we don't know who
i guess it was death it's they need to come from again now happy new year seriously guys
thanks for watching cheers to you bottoms up to you thanks for watching the channel
i think too who jake's lip who's what no death no community jake got eliminated damn
can we move maybe to the ring it would be great if we could move to the ring that'd be amazing
go into the ring what are you doing oh my god death is pinning somebody the game cannot handle
this edna's still in the ring the two clowns are fighting on the left side this is not supposed to
be happening you would think they would work together but no they're fighting they want to
eliminate each other as amelia and death are fighting clowns fighting edna and uncle ted
where's the ref the cameraman is zonked where's the referee he's counting he's counting the clowns
uncle ted's got amelia no no no no that's the wrong character i'm sorry it's kind of
fucked up i it's hard to pay attention to what's going on right now clowns are just playing death
and amelia edna and uncle ted and the two clowns the two senior citizens fighting it over on the
right side well the two clowns and left side death and amelia in the middle that was a big roar get
in the ring edna is pinning uncle ted one two nope almost it's not one of the clowns is being
pinned the chairs are back yep i have no idea who wins this the ref was counting and nobody was
pinned clown lady on clown man let's go no no pin can i play terraria
jesus ban that guy ban that guy for 10 minutes i'm not gonna play terraria right now dude i don't
know where to look there's so many places to look i don't know where to look i think uncle ted is
the upper hand i think clown man is the upper hand amelia going full ham on death right now
big pin amelia's got the pin here i keep saying amelia it's edna you idiot fireworks are going
off right now well this is it this is new year now what happened what wait did edna get did
edna get killed what did ted kill edna wait what why are they out they shouldn't be out right now
uncle ted going for the pin on clown lady no death does not want any part of that at all
oh poor edna edna has been eliminated down to five they were eight they don't want to get back in
the ring i guess god damn it man i think clown lady has uncle ted pinned right now
the ref get over here what's the ref doing big reversal by clown lady onto death i think uncle
ted has this in the bag if i bet money it goes on uncle ted for sure you should do simpsons
versus griffins i'm not going to do that we got another pin on amelia only a two count i wish
they would get back in the ring it's just come on man give me a break death on uncle ted will we
see ted eliminated here no two count can you do commentary and buy it wait what what happened who
left zero one zero zero one one one zero zero one one one what the fuck i can't what happened
zero zero zero one one one zero one zero one zero one zero one oh edna left okay they're double
teaming uncle ted right now yeah happy new year teacher happy new year oh my god the referee is
so slow one two nope two clowns both in death still in amelia still into amelia though
close you gotta figure they're getting tired you can't keep going forever
it's so far away from the ring at this point oh amelia could go for a ping a pin right now
i know no that reverse punch in the face someone's going very soon here then i don't think can they
go backstage i don't think i can i'm not sure they actually can make it backstage big dropping knee
on death pin them let's see it come on elimination let's go uncle ted and clown lady somebody pin
death get rid of death let's go somebody do something that's not punching please all right
finally they're bullying death yeah i would love to see a pin that's a reversal i don't think uncle
ted can take more than that though the fatigue has to be setting in amelia now oh ow oh yes getting
pinned why would you break that up don't break it up but he's stupid you dumb idiot what's wrong
with you why it might come down to the two clowns it might amelia just barely getting up now
uncle ted if you right hands or left hands probably left hand had gone crazy right now
death with a big reversal and amelia is holding the clown man well clown lady double team here
someone pin someone for the love of god here we go it's a one oh my goodness there is some
history here with ted and death there's a lot of history if we see a ted pinning death here this
is a big deal here and clown pinning elimina i can't even say words oh amelia barely gets out
because of the length of time it please come on pin somebody okay pin death somebody said
if this doesn't make you want to play destiny 2 pvp what will i will never open that game please
just i'm not gonna play it come on dude leave me alone big clothesline from amelia onto the
clown man can somebody do something please someone please do something please yes nope oh we're gonna
pin nope kicked out i don't think this is this is not gonna end somebody said this might actually
be bugged i don't i don't think so yes pinning uncle ted will we get to see the rectification
of no no oh jeez a choke slam somebody off the balcony come on kill someone someone die
someone die right now you should do the categories while this continues no no no i want these are
special categories oh my god death is pinning uncle ted why i don't know why they're not winning
should i take control and move to the ring do picture in picture all right i'm a little
starved for time right now we're gonna have to move on wait clown lady just pinned clown man
clown man eliminated we're down to four as uncle ted going for a submission amelia with a pin on
clown lady one two one two oh someone's going out again here now uncle ted now on the ground
all of them zero fatigue zero energy uncle ted now from the receiving end no breaks out
this is not the rumble we still have that to do that's coming up next after we do the final
categories that is where we will end the stream in about 30 minutes from now i would love to
claim a victor for the dollhouse brawl wait we gotta pin i don't know who's pinning who
i have no idea 30 minutes will probably end somewhere around 1 a.m pacific i don't what's
going on in the right here i have no idea please somebody win they've been punching each other in
the face out of the ring for 10 straight minutes someone just pull out a grenade or a gun already
uncle ted's got death oh my god just shoot somebody with a gun all right that's it
pin death uncle ted let's go let's go amelia lasted this long down to the final four
losing viewers it's because it's like three o'clock in the morning eastern don't worry we're
gonna be all right someone will win pin somebody we're gonna move on to the finale in just the
second once there's a winner crown of the dollhouse brawl someone just needs to pin somebody
all right death has got uncle ted on the ropes oh fuck you i'm about to get control and start
fucking punching people oh my god why is this game so bad someone get pinned do something i
that's the i can't do anything about this what are they doing please win someone it's been 20
minutes we have a pin i don't i don't know why they're doing this i have no control of this
scenario i have no control this game sucks and i know they waited two years to make the new one
i don't fucking buy it it's gonna be just as bad another pin here we go oh god i broke it i
crashed it i think i think it actually was bugged because i just crashed the game oh my fucking god
you gotta be kidding me i think it actually was bugged out i i think it was waiting for me to
intervene so it could crash god the 2k games are fucking dog shit i'm gonna hold my breath for 2k
22 because i expect it to be fucking horse shit i i expect it to be the worst fucking game ever made
at this point those are your four winners of the dollhouse brawl i gotta pee i'll be right back i'll
be right back we're gonna get this sorted and then i'm gonna do the last categories and i'm gonna go
pee see you guys in two minutes hello i have returned uncle ted was robbed oh shit hot mic
okay so what we're gonna do hey john how's your cat doing garfield i fuck garfield i don't care
so we're gonna go right to the rumble no you know we'll do the categories first that makes the most
sense i think right i think so we are down i want to get through these we're we're at the final
categories we're at worst meltdown now the heck i gotta have good hair it's 12 30 in the morning
but let's go so uh worst meltdown is the uh you look good thanks man i i can't believe there are
this many people still here at like fucking three o'clock in the morning eastern so worst meltdown
of the year in 2021 you look like shit i'm coming after you uh this is as you know times when i got
pissed i got annoyed i had a little maybe too much to say about a certain video game or i mean i just
said that 2k20 was a fucking bag of shit i can't believe they sold that game for 60 dollars in fact
it's fucking insulting that that game was sold for more than five dollars i believe that for real i
can't believe that game was sold for more than ten dollars okay um get off the screen i don't
want to see that your nominees for worst meltdown of the year are as follows
that character the characters like why am i supposed to what the character that character
says what i was like what the fuck can't change the fucking rules you can't change the rules like
i'm touching the what the fuck what he was two people he just did ringer kill that spy
i don't i'm done i'm done i'm skipping the level i'm skipping the level what shit oh my god i hate
this place you fucking suck stop saying that it's making me it's making me unconscious it's making
me self-conscious stop saying that you this game sucks this game fucking sucks it's awful it's
awful it's awful this was so intense what a fucking storybook ending this would have been but i forgot
the game's terrible ah great catch danny phantom great catch danny wow he just jumped in and grabbed
really just tell him just jumped into the ball danny and the uh the dromedary
what am i doing here what am i doing here ludd said we can be 10 minutes late so i'm assuming
we're starting in 10 minutes okay cool guys are freaking out i just muted indefinite i'm freaking
out all right i'm gonna try i just spilled coffee all over me i'm not even fucking ready
oh all right all right um no i'm not i'm tired i just woke up how is that how can there not be
90 fov in a 1920 by 1080 game like the ability to have it without it being it doesn't make any
sense i would have fuck capcom fuck you capcom capcom sucks that would i just ruined my game
experience that would have like scared me and i would have been like holy shit that was so scary
are you fucking kidding me i'm sorry i have no fucking i have absolutely no sympathy for any
of this shit if a game is going to release on pc and it's after 2008 if you if it's not 90 fov
just throw the whole thing to garbage and start over it's the worst console it's the worst console
it's the worst console they've got to make them little like little fucking like hamburger slices
oh look it's cute oh it's the switch oh yeah it's in a baby's hand
it just keeps going no come on right when i got the star off give me a fucking break
is one of us in 10 speak now i'm about to grip it
ah some pretty bad ones this year uh the worst in particular though by a lot this was not even
close which is really surprising your worst meltdown of the entire year is warrior wear
warrior wear with 38 percent of the vote swept it destroyed everybody else nick tunes baseball
and the capcom rant we're at two and three 38 22 and 13 respectively warrior where i took it
i mean i i i was melting my brain during that stream all right the next one is pretty special
to me because obviously um it's not best stream of the year it's not worst stream of the year
it's best dollhouse moment of the year um every time i see clips of this show and clips of people
hey that was fun that was a cool the dollhouse thing um this could have won probably every
category it could have won best joke best stream best meltdown like i didn't want to have it
nominated for every single category but it has a huge place in my heart as some of the most fun i
probably ever had in my life so watching you know the music play and different characters come on
screen and stuff it was uh it's really fun to watch because i have not really seen it i don't
really um i don't watch a whole lot of the stuff that i do really so seeing like random clips
every now and then is like oh yeah that was like that was a lot of fun uh so this one is like kind
of special because this gets its own category it does not get it would have swept every other
category so we made it its own category um it's it's got a special place here right here so this
is the best dollhouse moment from the dollhouse streams and here we go i'm very curious what's
the what scene oh so would you like to spend an evening together is what i'm asking
would you still respect me if i said yes absolutely
no no no no no i don't want to fight him he's huge he's huge he's a huge guy
he's a huge fire stay away from oh fuck
no no no no no no no okay all right all right i need two shadows in here oh yeah that's a bad
dream for jerma then jerma poops himself he poops himself in front of everybody no no i didn't put
a cowboy comes out of the shower
very easy hey jeff let me see that for a second let me show you something
hey jeff get along with it i've never been more afraid in my life than right now
back in like during like school plays there'd be like fucking 40 people in the audience
there
wait what do i am i sick do i do i have like the norovirus like what's happening sir yeah is are
you all right i'm okay in here don't you have to come in do you have a big mess you need cleaning
why don't you grab a piece of bread i want you to eat well i've been cleaning i wouldn't dare touch
you with my hands right but i think just but just eat with wash your hands and then eat
i'm not putting it in your mouth right no of course what did you i don't know what did you steal
did you steal anything what are you doing my house is like you give me a drink or something and i'm
gonna head out give me one you want to drink let me give me give me a glass of water or something
you give me i'll get you glasses where do you keep your glass like a glass of water i'll get
you a glass of water jesus for life okay oh how about that it's right there okay get a glass of
water what uh what are you doing what are you doing this is my no no no no no excuse me this is
my house i'm like why am i hiding outside of my own house i'm hiding i need to eat out of that
peanut butter later now i'm not going to i'm not eating out of that peanut butter
hey hey oh amelia sorry get extended what amelia how are you who is that that's just a bunch of
pillows that's just a bunch of pillows yeah look it's just like just pillows like it's a collection
of moving sentient pillows i can't believe this you can take this you can take him you shitter no
no i hope it was amelia just wait wait wait wait wait wait no i you missed your chance
you don't know how high i can fly that shit was so much fun so the winner for best dollhouse
moment of the year well the best dollhouse moment of that show is landslide going through the window
at 45 percent of the vote almost half of you guys said going through the window and then under that
woohooing death and caught by amelia with 13 and 10 percent of the vote that was awesome that was
so much fun i can't wait to try to do more stuff like that in 2022 that's the goal the goal is if
you like dollhouse i mean there won't be a dollhouse 2 necessarily but i'm trying to do more
shit like that in the next year it was so much fun ludwig was fucking unbelievable such a fucking
class act so funny milton kit boga these are people these are people that are unbelievably
talented and should get all the credit because that shit was fucking hilarious to me all right
it's time to get fucking sentimental boys and girls time to get sentimental uh here comes the
best no here comes the worst dream of the year why would i get sentimental on this one um worst
dream of the year is the next one coming up here now this was what everybody thought was the worst
thing i did all of last year this one you can't say that every year every year somebody says ah
this stream this stream sucks you can't say that every year you can't not every year it can't be
every year here are your nominees for worst dream of the year i know that people don't like certain
video games people don't like certain fucking impressions and noises i make fine i'll shut up
fine burger day secret lab what about the i'm gonna i need to go to the convention
great i'm stuck here forever i think i can sleep in the bed i think yeah we're good yeah i missed
a trend oh come the fuck on what the hell if a hotel does not have at least three stars on
well i'm walking in a circle one brain andy i can't do anything i can't fucking do anything
hey what is going on everybody jerma here with smite sunday welcome to the first smite sunday on
this channel when i break down the god i got with a time machine where i can like not
queue up for conquest if i had three wishes one of them would be to not play conquest tonight
that's exactly what we needed to have happen good job that was the achilles in the gilgamesh nice job
i'm not even looking at the screen oh my god please don't kill me i can't wait for next week
smite thursday this is never happening ever again fix it fix it fix it there's nothing
to fix i can't i can't don't you get it i can't the mic that i was using just broke and it doesn't
work anymore i have to get a new one eventually but you have to deal with this for now sorry what
the fuck he's getting closer he's gonna get close oh look at how close the one in the middle is
getting to the camera
what i don't want to watch this one fart on stream when your debt is erased how about i fart into
the microphone with the echo just put it under there i it that's cleared the debt is now clear
that's clear come on you can make it it's getting to be nighttime no it is a tree i
didn't even load in my game fuck no there's a tree on every side this is the worst possible
thing i could have done where's the road i'm not even halfway i turned around how did i turn around
i'm facing this way now how what what does this guy look like there all right there you go you
got what you wanted everybody that was here you got the imposter as fucking stupid ass sus face
that you got it i did i just realized that's what i just did 500 million dollars in research um
like 10 years of developing this place telescopes equipment radars light speed we can see into the
distance and i picked a shoe up on the ground and that's how i found them okay i have to stop
look this is just the shit i do i'm wait i'm trying to get to fucking seven percent phone
battery okay this is the shit that we have to do i have to fill time start turning things off you
aren't using what what do you mean turn things off that i'm not what that's how this works
oh my god yo teach what is it lunch all right i'm looking at uh one ricky morty keychain
uh one tickle rick and uh i'm working uh and uh a poster uh from season two this was actually
a terrible stream have a nice day king of retail king of retail logos germa sus fatal error the
game has crashed what the fuck stand and face the ball until a customer comes in
okay let's find out who what the worst stream of the year was here we go your least favorite
stream of the year is going to of the whole year smite with 35 percent of the vote and then
youtuber's life with 25 percent and then in king of retail with 12 smite was the worst stream of
the year apparently by a lot which is fine because i know that like people don't like
mobas they fucking hate those games mobas suck dude and fucking boring and i sucked at the game
i think i think i killed one person smite sunday canceled forever shit smite was the worst stream
of the year i'm gonna take a few seconds with this one this is the best stream of the year dollhouse
is not on this list because dollhouse was excluded from this list i didn't want there to be
just dollhouse dollhouse dollhouse dollhouse as much as it was one of my favorite experiences
ever we've got to give opportunity to other people and other streams so this is the final
category this is the nominees for the best stream of the whole year besides dollhouse i wonder what
this category looks like next year because i'm going to be really really emotional and real with
you there's a lot of shit that i'm gonna do in 2022 i don't even know how we do this in 2022
i think a lot of stuff is gonna be really fun i hope so if i can keep going if people still
think that this stream is worth watching i hope i can make you happy i hope so there are 27 000
people here watching at like one o'clock in the morning pacific i can't believe you're fucking
here i hope i can continue to do the things that you enjoy i really do i'm gonna try that's all
i can tell you some of them might be i might swing and i might miss and it might be a strikeout
right but i promise you something one thing really important i promise i will try to make streams
that i think are fun to watch will that happen we'll find out we'll see i don't know but there's a
lot of crazy shit that hopefully you see in the next month or two here are the nominees
the best stream of the year besides dollhouse
oh god damn it what zip why would you ever get this close
shoot am i supposed to be sitting down
shit grab the pistol and shoot who you
do in this area here i'm gonna find that goddamn treasure and i'll be the first one
collectible monster card packs holy shit pokemon cards what is this what is grotto beasts so those
are really clear quartz crystals which tells us that that's a really pure mineral so that's why
you're getting kind of that glassy appearance of them that looks incredible what's in there
oh my god it's it's minecraft diamonds come on 71 million a sprint and that's a coin
that's 3.1 million limes hey and get yourself something nice buy more limes
listen here's another 2,500 i'm gonna give you another 2,500 don't buy any more limes please
what do you say buy limes at market value where where i need to wink into the spirit
oh my head my brain just hurts i'm getting this strong incredible urge to receive donations
subscriptions i don't even know what that means fill fill got in the eye again
how how did that happen twice spray it in the tub in the tub in the tub inside how did it happen
twice oh i just read the characters fucking the character the characters like why was most
of what the character that character does what i was but
all right all right okay okay got 73
she got her hair tied up in braids
i hit the gas i press the gas way too hard i don't think jui jui can't use powers if i
you it's wait he's blocking
all right see you later have fun thanks for coming
hold on wait oh my god what the what the fuck excuse me um excuse me why is there a big shit
log on the ground it's so close one or two more pushes this should be it got it game over
this is so weird it's a wicked shitty skeleton just push it it's so fragile
you're not gonna fall in the acid all right get the luggage run times two speed
i'm not saying that because we're playing resident evil it really was he's a tyrant
he's a terrible guy we're not gonna use this anywhere right where you're gonna make sure
you don't even hear me
hey i don't think i will i think i will drop the scissors i just blew it i got too close i was
talking oh how can i get you you know every year that we've done this i've sat here going
there ain't no fucking way it's that much fun next year and every year
it seems to get even more fun for me um i hope that continues i told you guys a long time ago
when this is not fun for me anymore i'm gonna stop that has not happened yet uh but same thing
like last year i'm sitting here going am i gonna have this are we gonna have this much fun next
year i hope we can um but this is four years in a row and i don't take this shit for granted at
all we've seen a lot of new people this year in particular and i'll put the same message forward
to those people that i did last year and that's i don't really try to do anything else here besides
have fun if that continues great please let me know if it doesn't please i hope you let me know
if i fuck up and this is not a fun fucking place anymore i mean it because that's all i really
want to do so let's find out what was the best stream of last year or this year right what do
you think besides dollhouse ladies and gentlemen the winner it was close closer than i thought
because one of them was a big event with 25 percent of the vote the archaeology stream is
your winner right behind it at 22 percent was wrestling empire that was very close
eugleberry's cauldron was underneath that at 10 but the archaeology stream takes it
besides dollhouse obviously right but i still can't fucking believe i'm sitting here right now
um i hope this next 2022 is as fun as i had this year i hope so i'm gonna try to do more fun stuff
i don't know how good it's gonna be but we'll find out without further ado ladies and gentlemen
i'm not gonna get all sappy i won't get emotional i'm not gonna get sappy people saying cry
if you're gonna stick around for next year if you're gonna stick around on the channel
thanks that's all i can say that's there's nothing else i can really tell you besides
thanks for watching it's so much fun to do this every year it's so much fun to stream
let's keep going to 2022 i have so much fun with this community you guys do such wild shit
i have bad days right i have bad days and i have good days just like everybody else does but as a
whole holy fucking moly this is one of the funniest goddamn places i've ever been
and i cherish it every single fucking day just be aware of that so it is time it is time
ladies and gentlemen it's time for the rumble the 2021 rumble we're gonna end on this i'm very
excited we had some really fucked up matches a couple of them got a little bugged out but it's
okay here we go are you ready the rumble to end the stream tonight here we go i don't hear any
sounds oh i don't hear any sounds because i turn the volume down hold on let me fix it why can't
i hear it there you go your first contestant in the germa rumble 2021 hopefully it doesn't crash
out 30 contestants only one can remain very late 1 a.m pacific time but we're going for it
that doesn't really work here we just kind of have people fighting a ring
it's a very polite crowd oh no bugleberry hot tub bugleberry is number one
that sucks unfortunate for bugleberry i don't think he's gonna make it very far
one and two usually are guaranteed to lose in the first 10 seconds 10 minutes bf bugleberry
from new york right i wonder who's too though i don't know these are all random he's an eu
streamer now the next contestant is gonna be none other than who is it who is number two oh that's
joe biden that's joe bionicle biden he's guaranteed to lose coming into his suit but i know for a fact
he's got a bionicle t-shirt on underneath that i'm pretty certain of that we'll see joe bionicle biden
here with bf bugleberry two unfortunate souls he's waving the american flag okay just wait
till you see the shirt it's really him he's here in the ring right now bf bugleberry joe biden
welcome to the 2021 rumble germa rumble ladies and gentlemen joe bionicle biden versus bf bugleberry
hot tub version thanks for staying up late with me here in a wild night a lot of interesting stuff
going on as bf bugleberry will he remove joe bionicle biden all right he's gone he's gone
he's got he's gone so i i'm glad you got to see the shirt for five seconds uh in comes the
sunflower germa's sunflower from the summertime as contestant number three really took care of
those sunflowers loved them cared for them so it's bf bugleberry and the sunflower
one elimination for bugleberry so far big reversal by the sunflower though look at those wings
already another coming in the ring we're just going crazy right now i'm going forward in five
seconds three two one don't look at it just know what's in the ring our fourth contestant
is the horror heap the horror is number four as bf bugleberry and the sunflower are trading blows
here while the horror just kind of sits in it's just gauging the scene to see how it is i'd love
to see the sunflower last a little while here as another it's immediately this is they're coming
in hot hot hot hot hot we're gonna have four people in the ring in no time here here comes
amelia from the dollhouse amelia coming in at number five which rounds us out here we got five
people in the ring amelia sunflower bf bugleberry and the horror hopefully nobody died and amelia
going right for the sunflower trying to get eliminate immediately no just barely holds on
for dear life is the sunflower another contestant coming in i said five there are four i'm my brain
is slow i'm sorry and that's silly silly wonka from the chocolatier stream filling the ring up
the more people the better obviously there's silly silly wonka ended up making about four or five
billion dollars trading chocolate lots of money silly silly wonka welcome first appearance in
the rumble how are you good to see you peep the horror going over the ropes no sunflower
uh we might see a removal of the sunflower no silly silly wonka almost going over the top rubs
while the horror barely and catboy germa coming at number seven keep the horror swinging at
absolutely nobody as catboy germa comes in a fan favorite not a great place to come into the rumble
at number seven you really want to come in at least at 15 sunflower getting pushed over by bf
bugle hot tub bugleberry oh there it goes that's the second elimination from bf bugleberry hot tub
version really had high hopes for the sunflower sunflower is now eliminated and now here comes
chris banana redfield at number eight we saw chris redfield win the match previously
with lady denitra sue tag team win here trying to come in and stake his victory stake his claim to
the germa 985 rumble throne potentially oh amelia out eliminated with a big punch by silly silly
wonka that did not take very much time at all as chris redfield grabs bf bugleberry belly to belly
suplex our next contestant coming in now is armin from attack on titan erin erin the last time you
hear that ever as silly silly wonka going over the top ropes by catboy and the horror bugleberry
still safe are still safe although maybe not for long as chris redfield trying to dump him over
the top ropes very strong character is chris banana redfield but catboy now they're double
teaming bf bugleberry together trying to eliminate him and will they get it no they will not
and here comes jex fan favorite rumble favorite number 10 jex is in the building ready to cause
havoc and mayhem and show his gamer skills by potentially dumping bugleberry not over the top
ropes simply smushing his neck and there goes the horror chris redfield eliminated the horror
with a big right hand and taunting in the middle of the ring as jex is recovering just barely
getting in the ring and here comes joel from vinesauce was supposed to be in the rumble last
year but i fucked it up so here comes joel for the first time ever from vine wrestle and there
goes bugleberry bugleberry is out eliminated first contestant it sucks it's too bad there goes hot
tub bugleberry almost at number 12 i think 11 armin still in the ring and representing the grotto
beasts introducing miaudi still where is miaudi why is miaudi not in the ring okay
it took you a little longer representing grotto beasts is miaudi if miaudi eliminates jex they're
the favorite jex is 100 stats let's be very clear about this big suplex from armin on joel
as miaudi can i don't know what now he's doing i would say top seed three cat people are in the
ring right now homer simpson all of you were looking for homer you finally got your homer
simpson was not going to put homer in a match but there they are picking up joel and doing a suplex
to joel swinging belly to back suplex but chris redfield now i i kind of have high hopes for chris
redfield i say that until oh please don't do it homer homer simpson now is threatening to
throw chris redfield over the top ropes looks like they might get it and here comes tier list
andy oh shit he actually did it no uh tier list andy is just a tier list as homer simpson just
absolutely decimates crisp banana redfield really sad stuff that we're seeing here what tier list
is on tier list andy i don't know it's hard to tell i don't know what what is on his back
as miaudi eliminates cat boy germa cat eliminates cat who could see that coming from a while away i
don't know cat boy gone miaudi eliminates cat boy when i told you top seed i meant it i was not
messing around i really meant it as homer simpson now in the corner jex gets a get gets armin armin
i think from the last match really kind of got annoyed at me talking about how shitty he was
and how not strong that armin was trying to go for jex which is a huge mistake you don't go for
jex in quotes that's how you die as miaudi and homer simpson with tier list andy in the mix as
well joel from vinesauce also is there still fighting for his life against tier list andy
if homer simpson wins the rumble i will eat glass on stream make that clear
it's the fucking way as miaudi now is over on the right side who's the next competitor it's mr
green or mr greens and depending on who you are you can say it however you want here's mr greens
he's in the last rumble making his second or third appearance in the germa rumble here going right
for armin armin now over the top ropes might oh there goes jex miaudi's top seed i would be
terrified of miaudi right now homer simpson and mr green trying to get armin out we will never
hear erin again hopefully thank god we'll never hear it again armin has been eliminated by homer
simpson and mr green as josh from science center nevada science josh making his first appearance
in the germa rumble there he is the archaeologist geologist whatever i'm sorry science center josh
making his appearance as armin is really slowly getting up here hopefully not injured just to go
homer missed completely science center nevada josh just powerbomb joel outside the ring there goes joel
joel has been eliminated from the germa rumble sorry joel it's been a pleasure to have you but
good luck next time please someone kill homer simpson so i don't have to eat glass please
someone get rid of it miaudi will take care of it i'm certain of it miaudi is going to be fine
science josh is on the ropes here homer simpson now but tier list andy miaudi looking for their
i think fifth or sixth elimination no don't powerbomb josh out oh fuck homer simpson powerbomb
science center josh outside the ring but torgo making their appearance coming in hot
here comes torgo high hopes for torgo from mano's hands of fate mr green now looking at
homer simpson trying to get him out of here i hope we see it please get rid of homer
homer cannot win it can't happen where's the music somebody just grab the ropes and dump him over
oh my god the mcgriddler at number 18 coming in saw the mcgriddler earlier but i would love to see
a few eliminations from the from the mcgriddler now in trouble with the tier list now
is it possible we could see a miaudi elimination no not yet as torgo now has homer get rid of homer
now use that fucked up cane that you have no what oh my goodness the sus guy coming in but
who cares miaudi is out that's really sad here comes a sus guy this is not sus flush this is
the sus guy different i will take the sus guy winning over homer simpson i swear to god
sorry miaudi that's that's very unfortunate i would have liked to see miaudi go all the way
at least the top five here comes germadillo a bttv emote i'm probably we'll probably see it a few
god who just got thrown out what what happened who got eliminated what happened
oh mr green is gone germadillo i will literally make you a real emote if you get rid of homer
simpson right now oh two back-to-back eliminations who was that the sus guy and tier list andy
i'm not kidding i will make germadillo a paid emote if he eliminates homer simpson sus guy
and tier list andy both gone getting down to the final i believe 12 competitors in this rumble
homer simpson still in it torgo now and germadillo please mcridler get rid of him
do not let homer simpson win let's see a double elimination it's possible although i don't know
how probable there goes no he saved it still held on william carslough i'm sure a bunch of
people probably saying who right now that's fine because that's the battleship captain from the
battleship meta that is the battleship captain he's got a name you know going right for the
mcridler the failed meta that meta was fine for like a week it was like two or three weeks give
me a break this is a real guy i is it a real guy i don't know number 22 coming in dollhouse germa
please get rid of homer simpson as the mcridler gets him in the top he's on the turnbuckle this
is really bad spot to be for homer help him go help him william carslough whatever your goddamn
name is real historical landing oh my god wait no like it's spampton from delta rune chapter two
spampton is joining the rumble for the first time ever i thought he threw out immediately
spampton welcome everybody spampton homer simpson is still in this rumble as william carslough
really trying to just trying to find out is he c3 is he d5 i doesn't know where homer's battleship
he's really trying to find it didn't find it unfortunately here comes fish bastard
at number 24 from the hot tub stream one of bugleberry's many disgusting absurd
horrific creations of all the things it looks like the mcridler is gonna have to deal with
the fish bastard one-on-one here will the fish bastard take out the mcridler with the help of
spampton they really went this is potentially a newfound alliance we're seeing here
warner von brawn is the oh oh oh oh guy there goes torgo by homer simpson
oh oh makes up number 24 second simpson's character that's right so if there's somebody
to eliminate homer simpson it's definitely him torgo i don't think you'll be in the next rumble
but it was really nice to have you thanks for coming spampton fish bastard mcridler and
warner von brawn no just barely hangs on is the mcridler while dollhouse germa is still fighting
the battleship captain which is strange because i mean that's his meta he created that meta that's
just like that's his meta it's weird that he'd be fighting against that meta i mean you could argue
that like ludwig and others made that meta happen because germa's an irrelevant andy
and really didn't have much pull at all but just decided to ask in a relevant brain he's gone
germa's gone fuck him who cares who gives a shit about that guy well there goes dollhouse germa
i don't think germa's ever going to win a competition why would he big big what's that
called the gold gold rush i don't know whatever the guy's name is goldman what's the guy's name
goldberg big goldberg jackhammer on homer simpson has the battleship captain really
taken it to homer simpson now here this would be a real big relief for me there he goes
goodbye homer simpson goodbye spampton battleship captain and eliminate finally homer simpson
thank god here comes anubis from smite getting us to 26 characters i saw anubis earlier in the
evening i don't have to eat glass anymore good somebody in this ring could be your 2021 champion
of this and there goes mick redler i'm sad about that i think a lot of other people might be too
i'm not happy about what i just saw that's sad i was rooting for the mick redler the whole time
still four contestants that have yet to come out it's all random by the way i have no control
over any of the things you're seeing on screen i just put them into the rumble fish bastard down
no just going for a taunt stupid move hockey um um will you put him down it's his year well
it very well could be considering that glue man is number 27 in the rumble 2021
great opportunity for glue man is it glue man's year this year will we see a glue man victory for
the first time in almost seven years that's to be determined i don't want to get my hopes up
but this could be glue man's year 27 welcome back glue man for the seventh or eighth annual time
i hope oh my that's gets tricky here when you get mr satan comes in from wrestling empire
mr satan is now in the ring not only has experience in wrestling but also has experience
being the strongest man in the non-state or whatever it doesn't matter oh boy that's bad
mr satan eliminates ooh oh we are about to see the final two competitors in this rumble who will
they be promwell the guardian praying mantis at number 29 it's a great place to come in
he might be small or praying mantis eat each other and they kill each other and pound for pound
he could pick up two fucking mac trucks promwell welcome to the germa rumble as mr satan with
anubis in the corner here there goes anubis we are down to our final competitor of the year
and it's the lala dog oh no the lala dog is number 30 battleship captain cromwell the praying
mantis guardian the lala dog fish bastard glue man and the game crashed okay uh so what we're
going to do what we're going to do is we're going to do a five-man brawl with who is in the ring
right there okay excellent this fucking game sucks we're just gonna do a a over the top rope
rumble you crash right there at the right at that moment 2k all right let's get it gone
let me make sure i get the right people in there at how many were in there it was cromwell i think
it was five or six right five it was the final five homer was not in it it was in it homer was
not there it was cromwell you fucking goddamn game i swear to god yeah glue man was there
okay homer was not there i'm not going to add homer anubis just got eliminated right there yep
the battleship captain thank you what a buzzkill seriously all right who else mr satan that's
right what a buzzkill the final five you're going to crash why because the lala dog went up on the
top rope and did a taunt i'm not i'm going to hold my tongue yeah the lala dog who was the
final person oh my god this is such a good show and fish bastard really was that the final five
okay let's go fish bastard it was six almost shit you're right there were six okay hold on i
got i got i got i got i got i got i got it yep you're right okay so let me get this one more
time cromwell uh cromwell fish bastard bear with me here the uh captain uh not the sus guy
homer is not going in the lala dog yep that's right uh glue man we'll get the winner we'll get
the real winner and the last one was who cromwell fish bastard battleship captain lala dog glue man
and who else mantis no mr satan yep all right good luck good luck everybody here we go let's
crown the champion for 2021 let's go glue man it could happen i don't know how i don't know if it
will it is so late too thanks for staying up everybody i hope you had a good time i've had
a blast i've been just having a fucking ball hopefully you have to i love these streams
it's like a culmination of the whole year i just have i just i might be a little tipsy
right now but thanks for sticking around let's see who the uh let's crown the champion here
it's in the nxt arena who cares let's go is this glue man's year we'll find out the final five
here we go mr satan glue man battleship captain fish bastard cromwell the praying mantis guardian
and the lala dog looks like we might see an immediate elimination in this final five
there goes cromwell for this be the year of the glue man i've been doing this every year
since like 2012 and glue man has been there since the very beginning
will we actually get a glue man germa rumble victory i don't know but we're down to the final
five blue man picking up the lala dog looks like lala could see the end here
yeah all right final four no fish bastard has glue man up on the ropes
this is glue man's year it can't be oh fish bastard like the worst character made in the cauldron
you can't eliminate glue man thank goodness the battleship captain has glue man now we have to see
a momentum change here or this is a huge problem mr satan fish bastard glue man's gotta get every
need to give glue man our strength there goes fish bastard down to the final three mr satan
battleship captain and glue man i have no idea what's gonna happen but i have an outcome that
i want i don't know if it's outcome we're gonna get as mr satan grabs glue man now by the wrist
big reversal by glue man no no you gotta reverse these glue man there it is big reversal
gets clothesline for his effort so much energy so much effort from glue man
slow to get up though which is bad which means the fatigue is really high
as mr satan goes into the ropes battleship captain holy shit mr satan no double reversal here
a triple reversal they're gonna double team and get him over the ropes mr satan is about
to eliminate the battleship captain as glue man watches on no still gaining some strength it seems
big russian sweet whatever that's called oh no mr satan with the big double arm tiger suplex
you gotta be shitting me glue man gonna go for a throw mr satan over the top ropes
he's hungry this year he's starving for it no it's not gonna be enough he gets reversed
don't be an idiot glue man no he's getting too cocky oh shit you've been here for seven straight
years glue man you can't just be cocky and go taunt mr satan big reversal though elbow to the
face of mr satan i'm actually kind of nervous for glue man right now this is kind of bad
two belly-to-belly suplexes mr satan is stacked cleaning up the ring right now
i'm surprised the battleship captain has lasted this long one of these three will be crowned
champion of the rumble and we all know who we want it to be go for it glue man stop being cocky go
for it cool you know i think the problem is he's never had this much screen time before
he's milking the audience and it's going to be his downfall this is the most screen time he's
ever had he's hoping to get a book deal after this is over big belly to back suplex will the
cockiness oh god it's over he's gone glue man has been eliminated see you later that's very sad
battleship captain and mr satan are the final two competitors this year better luck next year
yeah unfortunate the hubris i know what was he doing he's like taunting he's going on the
top ropes like get down man what's wrong with you rip rip rip yeah sad you hate to see it
it looks like mr satan is going no he's not this would be quite an upset if william carslark the
battleship captain wins the game what an upset uh i need to take it that was so i didn't think
he's gonna do it that quickly he is the strongest man on earth so it makes sense right
i am the strongest man on earth i'm the strongest man a wrestler
check out next episode uh when i billy the bellic suplex and that guy over the top rope
mr satan is your 2021 germa rumble champion mr satan i'm not putting home it's no we gotta
go to bed we gotta get out of here it's so late you glue man versus mr satan it's not gonna happen
all right fine fine fine you're gonna get one more match you'll get glue man versus mr satan
no you won't because the game crashed that's it what a crazy year yeah it's like two it's like
2 a.m pacific we gotta go a lot of you guys have been up for a long time
mr satan is your 2021 rumble champion there were a lot of categories this year i had a great
fucking time i will see you guys in the new year 2k20 yeah i think the worst thing about 2k20
and any of the other games that they've made oh i don't want to be like a dick no it's new
years it's new years let's just say goodbye and like that was a lot of fun i had a blast
i'm not gonna be like oh this company just have a great night hopefully you celebrated your new
year well with friends and family and if not then if you stayed here glad to have you we will see
you guys what when am i gonna stream next let's see three four days maybe on wednesday i'll see
you guys on wednesday the fifth have a great new year's thanks for watching you guys are the best
i i got nothing else to say besides i look forward to 2022 i have a lot of things that i want to do
if they come to fruition then great if not then who cares let's just keep having fun
fuck it doesn't matter i'll be here as long as i'm having a good time and if we see some of your
faces again then cool i've done a lot of that today have you noticed that like and if we see
again then okay like limit like can i just put my i gotta keep my hands up thanks for an unbelievable
new year's it's always a blast glad i got to spend it with you guys sorry we kept you up so late but
yeah i'm very happy i wake up every day and think about just how much fun this place really is hope
it stays that way in 2022 have a great night i don't even know if there's anybody to raid
because it's 2 a.m pacific so i'm just gonna go on to 2022 take care of yourselves good night to you
much love to you and we'll see you soon we'll see you on wednesday have a great one and good night