Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some binding of Isaac, Wrath of the
Lamb DLC. Now, before the video gets going, you're probably wondering, Jerma, why are
you post-comming this game? This is very much a should-be-doing-alive comma, a let's play
or something like that. And the reason behind that is I want to do a breakdown of the DLC
and tell you all the new things because there's not really a whole lot of press about this.
And I'm not sure why because this game is incredibly, incredibly well done. And I never
did a video explaining what this game actually was, but I will do that as well in this video.
So the Binding of Isaac is sort of an action RPG. It's really the only thing you can think
of. It's sort of like a cross between Zelda and Star Tropics and Diablo and there's so
many different genres of game in this game. So it's very hard to describe it. But there
is one thing that you need to know if you buy this game. If you die one time, you have
to start over from the very beginning. And they call those rogue-like RPGs. So if you
die, you start from the beginning. And how you start this game, how you play this game,
is you go through randomly generated rooms. Room to room, you have to clear all the monsters,
just like in Star Tropics or Zelda. So you clear all the monsters in the room, you get
to move on to the next room and the next room and the next room. And finally, there is a
boss at the end and you go down deeper into the dungeon. Now you do this until you complete
the whole game. And like I said, if you die halfway through, there are no checkpoints.
You end up starting over at the very beginning with none of your required items and none
of your required extra health globes. Now you might be wondering to yourself, well,
that sounds great. That sounds fun. But why would you ever want to play that game more
than one or two times in a row? You might see everything you want to see within the
first couple of times. Well, that's because of the item system in this game. So during
the course of the playthrough, you're going to find randomly generated items. There are
this DLC, there are over 235 randomly generated items that have many different properties
to them. Some make you shoot faster. Some make you do more damage. Some actually do
worse things. They take your health away. They bring your range down. There are a lot
of different variables and that's why this game is so addicting. And not to mention what
it does to your character, because every single item in this game adds something to your character
or takes it away. Let's put it this way. If you get something called toothpicks, which
is a new item in the DLC, it literally pries your character's eyes open with toothpicks.
It is very gruesome and very ridiculous, but every single item does something to your character
model that no other item in the game does. And very, very subtly, this game has become
one of my favorite PC games of all time. It's just so addicting. It's so much fun. Oh,
you died halfway through with this amount of items and these amount of things. It's
okay cause you can start over again and get a totally new experience. Okay, so now that
you heard me praise the game and how much I love it so much, let's talk about the DLC,
the Wrath of the Lamb DLC. Should you get this DLC? Yes. Apsa positiva lutely, yes.
It is only $3, $2.99 on the Steam store right now. And the game itself is only five. So
the whole entire package is only eight bucks for hours and hours and hours and hours of
enjoyable content. I have spent $60 on some games that are not nearly as fun or nearly
as time-sync as this game. And that's a really good thing. So now I'm talking about the content
of the DLC. This is not the Binding of Isaac 2. They just added a bunch of new items, new
content to expand on the replayability of the original game. Now that is not a bad thing.
That is an incredible thing because here's what they did. So there used to be about 135
items. There are now over 100 new ones. So now there's 235 plus. There's five new chapters
to the game to play through. Over 20 new enemies, 25 new achievements, 15 new bosses, 6 new
room types, 5 new music tracks from that guy Danny B, who is an incredibly talented musician.
A new item type called trinkets that it's a passive ability. You can only have one of
them at a time. There are new unlockable characters. There's a ton of new secrets, some of which
I don't even know. I've only played through it about two times now, and there's so much
more stuff that I cannot wait to see. So yes, if you own the Binding of Isaac, go buy this
DLC right now. Because if you love that game, it only makes the game 10 times more interesting.
And like I said, it's only $3 for this expansion. So I mean, I spend that money every day on
cheeseburgers with Burger Boy anyways. So might as well use it to get some fun. So before
I end the video, I do have to bring this up because it is obviously very, very apparent.
This game is incredibly graphic. There are a lot of violent images, a lot of disturbing
images. So viewer discretion is strongly advised when you're going to pick up this game. And
if you're wondering what type of videos I'm going to be doing for Wrath of the Lamb, I'm
probably going to stream this game. So I'll probably intertwine this between Diablo III,
King Fortress 2, Binding of Isaac, GTA. So this will end up being part of the stream
team, I guess. So yeah, that wraps up this video, guys. Go enjoy this game. If you have
it already, then right on. But I'll see you guys all soon. So take care, everybody.