Okay, I am back. So we're gonna hang out. I believe... when's the Bethesda
conference? It's in like an hour, right? 4 p.m. Pacific? So in like two hours? Okay.
So I'm gonna play Cooking Simulator. We're gonna pick up right where I left
off in the meantime. And then we're gonna do the Bethesda conference. And
then that's probably... I don't think I'm gonna do Devolver. Because Devolver
every year kind of has... it's not necessarily a live conference, right? It's
kind of like a edited video. They do like a little special thing, right? But
I'll be back tomorrow for Square Enix and... what's the other one? What the hell
is they doing? At Ubisoft, right? We'll do that tomorrow as well. Let's get
Cooking Simulator open while we just chill. By the way, remind me when
we're like 10 minutes out, because I will forget and I will be late to the
conference. Let's get it open. You should see it on the screen. Very shortly. Like
as in right now. Hey, there it is. No one tell him anything. You have to
remind me. I'm not gonna be able to remember. Are we still doing the floor
soup? Yes. Corporate? What do you mean corporate streamer? Which is
soup yard, right? A 12 balance. Which one is it? This one, right? He's not
gonna know. No, I'm paying attention. I got a clock right in front of me.
This is loud. Hold on. Loud, loud, loud, loud, loud. There we go. That's better. It's not as
loud now. Okay, so for those of you that have no idea what the hell is going on,
you may be just still hanging out here after the Microsoft conference. This
is a soup house. And I got... hold on. There's stuff already going on. Duck broth.
I already got that made, right? Why are there eggs in here? Oh, there's oil in there still.
Why? What's going on? All right, here we go. The duck is right here. I got my
duck broth right here. And it's just a few pieces of this, right? All right,
that's done. Floor organization. Yeah, I... I pre-made a bunch of this shit. And,
okay, it's... I don't know why it's doing this. I just lost fame for that.
That's... I'm reloading. That's bullshit. That's absolutely fucking stupid.
How long till Bethesda? Just about two hours. I do not deserve that.
Let's try this again. Grab the soup. Grab a few pieces of duck. Okay.
Some of the pieces of duck don't stay in. I don't know why. I can't... I don't know why.
You get two. Can I put three in here? All right, these are all in here. They're not moving.
Go. Oh my fucking god. I can't do anything about it. I can't. I'm gonna lose fame every
time. You saw... I tried. I really did. All right, here we go. I need to make a pork chop.
Pork rabbit. Do I have one ready? I got one of these ready. What is it? Uh, eight? I don't
remember. It's eight. Yeah. Eight chive. Yeah. There's probably a bunch of people that are just
like, what the hell are you doing? Why is everything on the floor? This game...
I just like threw it at them. What just happened? What's going on? Did it dump? No,
it dumped. It was forward dumping. They didn't patch it. This makes no sense. They
did not patch out the floor soup. No way. It's only been like two days. Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna start with the pork chops first. Pork chop. Grab one. Get this seasoned up. It is
four salt, four pepper. There is four salt. There's already a pork chop out here, but
whatever. I can use it later. And then it's time, right? Six time. Yep. If this thing
falls off a plate, I'm gonna go play pick-ross. Okay, how much oil? There's plenty of oil. There's
plenty of oil in the pan already. Turn it on. Get this cooked up. I already have the potatoes
ready. All right, that's going. Uh, potatoes are already done over here. I have my potato
section, right? Right here. They're good. And then, okay, now the duck. This should... I don't
know why this is not working. They definitely did not patch this. Somebody go look at their
notes. If you have food that's been sitting out for more than four days, does it just
disappear? Pull it up. Okay, it's still... it's fine. Got it. Finally. See? It's fine. That's
like a four-star meal. Bachelor. I'm gonna flip this in a few seconds. Gaspacho comes in next.
No, another duck. Some of these pieces just don't stay in. That's the issue. Okay, this
is good too. Yeah, the strategy here is the game doesn't really care that much if your
food is four or five days old. Oh, here we go. So I just made a ton of shit in advance.
Got it. Okay. Uh, what's next? What was it? Oh, it's fish, fish, fish, fish, fish. That'll
be done soon. And I got the plate. I got the, uh, trout. Uh, I want to get this off.
There we go. It's a pepper thyme dill. Almost. Pepper thyme dill, pepper thyme dill, dill,
dill, dill, dill. Oh shit. That's pepper again. What? How did I just do that? How did I just do
that? I don't know how I even just did that. It's because there's two peppers. I think...
Where's dill? Dill, dill, dill. I don't think I even have it out. Cayenne. Salt. Where's dill?
Well, I gotta take this out. I need a plate. Come here. All right. Potatoes. Six, right?
I need to make more of these. There's nothing bold on it. That's just spices.
It's seasoning. All right, now I need to make the trout. I have a little to work fast on this one.
Oh, come on. Fine. I don't care. Uh, this is... I don't have any dill. Did I lose the dill?
Do I actually have to buy dill again? Did I throw it away? Okay, get this in the oven.
Come on. Get in there. No, pick it up. Okay, that's gonna cook. And then I need
a lemon. How's that doing? That's doing fine. Where's my knife? I threw it the last time I played
somewhere. Sh**. This is not good. Didn't I throw it out the window? I think I threw the knife
out the window last time. I have no idea. I gotta buy one though. Okay, um, get that
cut into fours. Good. And a plate. Which one's gonna be done first? I gotta flip that. Oh,
fuck. where's my spatula? quick quick quick quick quick go go go go cook. are you cooking? thank you.
okay get this out. and then what's the little herb that goes on it? parsley? i don't remember.
it's uh parsley. eight? six. presentation is lacking but it's okay. that was pretty good.
i didn't put horseradish on it. oh well. what i still have to make? what? pork chop. oh tomato
soup. i got that. ready to go. i have a lot of tomato soups actually. don't have to do
anything. that looks fucking gross. it's not gross. it's called preparation. tuna cake.
this is almost done. open. okay this is salt and pepper and that's it. right let's get this out of
plate. plate and then i don't have any potatoes. uh yeah i do. same fucking thing. sorry we ran
out of potato chips. we have baked potatoes. didn't lose any fame. that's fine. all right
let's get this tuna right. salt and pepper five grams. you got it. duck i got that ready
to go. there it is. one two three four five. stick it. get rid of it. salt. i wouldn't eat
here. yes you would. oh shit. a little too much. it's okay. throw it on the grill for how long?
80 seconds aside. throw it on the grill. now we need uh lemon cut into slices. four slices
of lemon. i got that. okay one two three whatever. i can clean them up. they're not
lucky. i can clean them up. watch this. ready. how much time? almost time. any more food that came
in? or is it just this? no duck. i need to make more duck broth. here's the guy with the horn.
plus one. all right i need. that's all done. just oregano twig on top. oh shit. salmon.
this is uh salt and pepper. good thing i have one ready to go here. let's see four or five.
five. start a fire. waste the salt. running a kitchen is way too hard. why why? i thought
it was salt. i didn't. what? what's going on? why am i? what fucking weird mystery world is this?
i don't understand. why was it? it was already salt and pepper on it. i don't. when did i do that?
oh. did i do? i must have done that like five days ago. well this is. no they'll be fine.
they don't. i gotta clean this though. all right. 10 oil. that's good enough. all right.
get it in there. one hour aside. all right. and then i have the potatoes. i still have
potatoes cooked. how's this doing? it's a deep bowl. no i don't want that. i gotta turn this
halfway right? need a plate. okay then we have the lemon. four lemon slices. one two three four.
did four get on there? no. okay four and oregano. where the hell is it? right down here.
heat up. almost five stars. salmon needs to be flipped right now.
just do it right. it's literally right next to me. i was just like slingshot it. i was just like
all right. any more? i got the potatoes already. get a plate. two baked potatoes. and any.
nothing else right? no. just wait for this to be done. grab it up and then go. cook the
piano. what piano? chop the potatoes. no you don't. look. look at the picture. it's two
it's two big potatoes. that's it. potato. that's it. all right. my inventory is low on soup. i gotta
get ready for that. what am i missing? duck broth? okay. i got i got 11 minutes. i gotta make
i got plenty of tomato. how much gazpacho do i have? all right. running low on gazpacho. i gotta
make uh duck broth, duck breast, and gazpacho. let's get that going. duck broth. so i need
water. 1.3 liters. wait. what do you mean? i can't pronounce. can't pronounce what?
no. not yet. i need uh other shit in here. i need a carrot. what's it? a carrot and an onion?
and then the duck breasts? that's it, right? carrot, onion, and then two duck breasts.
and then salt the hell out of it. what if i just put like five duck breasts in here
and then have them forever? i'll never have to cook these ever again. i'll get like five.
okay. now move it around a little just so i can. did i just pull the water out? 50 50
milliliters of duck breast. okay. this is good, right? i gotta salt the water too. don't forget
that. how much time do i got? plenty. add a loaf of bread. 10? that's enough salt. let's go.
these are all cooking. good good good. all right. now we're gonna do gazpacho. do i
remember the gazpacho? i can't even say that fucking word. let's see if i remember it.
it was two cucumbers, three tomatoes, a loaf of bread. i forget the rest. is it two bell peppers
or three bell peppers? i think it's three. and that's it, right? or is there an onion?
and then one onion. oh no, that's garlic. garlic. that's it. and then i go over here,
grind it up. okay. then i add this shit. i think it's 30 of this, right? and then
where's the other one? it's like some kind of oil. give me a break. okay. three. this is fucking
dumb. the whole thing wouldn't spill. it's salt, pepper, and then there's an oil? where's my oil?
right here. okay. and then 10 salt, 10 pepper. grind it up again. that's dill. oh shit. oh my
god. okay. it's done. yeah. right? laugh. everybody laugh. please laugh. please clap. all
right. it's done. that's good. it's just sitting there a little overcooked on the onions, but
some people like crispy onions. that looks good. don't need more than two. we have 120, 250.
that's good. put this down for a minute. i could probably do two more, three more. let's find
out. this might be it. can i get one more in here? okay. that's good. that should be
enough. almost almost landed perfectly. these are all capped up. all right. now i need to
duck broth. how much time? five. i got plenty of time. this is fine. all right. i want to put
the broth over here where it was before. that's tomato. let's get this over here.
all right. i need like three or four more plates. plates do not break anymore, right?
yeah. i got that upgrade. just get them over there. i gotta be careful though because i will
knock over all the tomato soups. one more? okay. let's set them up. oof. that frame rate.
i think i'm just gonna cook like five tuna steaks too if i have time.
let's get all these out so i can cut them. where's my cutting board? we're gonna skimp the
absolute fuck out of this too. i'm gonna have duck breast for like a month. it's gonna be
great. the onions doesn't need it. it's fine. i mean the knife. nice and thin. nice and thin.
ready? check it. it's so much duck. all right. put the knife down. it's so tender. is this
all gonna fit on here? no. no, it's not. just give me... hold on. let me get another... i need
to get another plate. that's not gonna happen. i need a big plate. here we go. that's raw. no,
this is what duck is supposed to look like. you ever had duck before? it looks like this.
there's a couple more pieces of duck on the table. it doesn't? yes it does. duck is like
green in the middle. it's not. okay. got my duck ready. my broth is ready to be poured
into the bowls. is there an extra duck breast under there? nice. there is. all right. 230.
let's see if i can spread this out around 5. 250. 220. 380. it's still a little more. what's
when this one needs a little more? let's transfer some of these into here. and then
i'm gonna cook up like a bunch of meat too. easy with this. don't fucking drop it. all
right. so i got my broth. i got one more breast in here. where is it? let's cut it up.
oops. let's make this one even thinner. i want paper thin slices of duck. i still got a minute left.
jeremy, no. wait, why not? you trick your brain into thinking there's more food.
this is a really good technique. i'm telling you. did that not even cut? no, it did. okay.
that looks pretty good. i would eat this. see, you got two different kinds of duck. you get
like breast meat and like thigh meat. all right. almost time to go. uh what do i need
to do before this continues? um okay. i got time in the beginning. 130 bucks. i have a bunch of
time in the beginning of this day too. uncooked versus cooked. some people want raw meat.
i want more time in the beginning of the day. maybe fame points. let's see. how much is it
for more time during the day? better tips. faster repairs. uh easier. where is it? extended
cleaning phase. extended preparation phase. here we go. yeah. that's important. and then
i'm gonna do the fame one. more fame points. where is it? where is it? come on. this one right
here. all right. shitty fame is still fame. yeah. hey. any publicity is good publicity, right?
people really like our salmon steak and boiled potatoes. so it's our dish of the day. all
right. that's i'm gonna make like 10 of them. okay. uh let's get two burners going. three
burners going. i gotta change the music. that's okay. that's good. triple burner. 10 oil in
each one. a little bit. no. that's fine. oops. okay. got oil in each one. let's get three salmon
steaks out here. one, two, three. potatoes. i'm gonna boil the fuck out of a bunch of
potatoes too. okay. we need potatoes in the back. i only have one potato. so let's fill a pot
with potatoes. water and salt. from the floor to your mouth. yes. all right. it's 20. 20
salt or 10 salt. i think it's 20. okay. now i'm gonna fit as many as i can fit in this
jar. potato. here we go. ready? how many can i fit in here? i need at least this many. all right.
that's... i don't think i can fit much more. no. okay. that's all i can fit.
are these gonna cook? let's hope so. all right. get them all going. wait. no, no, no. not yet.
yeah. just boil the potatoes. are these cooking? some of them are. give me another one.
whatever. i'll just move them around. it's fine. all right. uh i need my salmon steaks.
salt and pepper on each one of these. throw it in there. how much salt is in each one? five
and five, right? what's up with the puke faces? salt. salt. i always just lose all my shit.
where's my salt? i need an assistant to take care of this shit for me. all right. get them
in the pans. turn them on. ready. here we go. one, two, three. one, two. why does one on the
left look dirty? all right. potatoes are almost done. i think most of them are done. i'm
gonna dump them out and find ones that are not cooked and then put them back in. this
one's not cooked. all the ones that aren't cooked are gonna go on here. not cooked. the
rest are cooked. yes, they are. get them off. okay. oh, fuck. stop flipping. flip. i forgot
these don't take very long. fucking get on there. fuck you. it's done. i don't care.
whatever. they're done. all right. turn them off. kill the heat. god damn it. all right.
potatoes. done, done, done. turn it off. no, this one's not done. oh my fucking god. why
did i pick that up? that happens. whatever. this is a fresh one. good. all right. these
ones are done. they're ready to be plated. i got the potatoes. let me get a couple plates
and two of these. ready to go. done. are these cooked? not yet. two of them. and then
this one needs to be flipped. don't fuck it up. whatever. okay. potatoes are almost done.
it's about time to start. i need another plate. grab potatoes first. i got three of
these already made. i should be good to go. yeah. by the time this is ready. 17 seconds.
clean the kitchen. i don't need to clean the kitchen. i'm fine. all right. let's start the
day. this person is going to get a fresh one. salmon first order coming up. it's going to be
burning hot. this is like sumi hot. that's french fries and a steak. that's not what i
thought we were going to make. this is already to go. all right. don't fall off
immediately. steak. salt and pepper. it's four and four, right? point four. and how do i turn
that on? baked steak. that's gonna be disgusting. so cut potato into sticks. oh, i gotta make
french fries. okay. i need more. these are still cooking. oh no. just get them in the
potato holder. okay. potatoes. i'm just gonna get a ton of them. i'm gonna make a ton
of french fries. like too many. i'm gonna add french fries to every single dish. all
right. that's fine. i'm gonna chop these up into french fries. how's the steak looking?
why does it say salmon filet? it's done. there's a salmon in here. okay. i got potato.
let's cut this all up. these are gonna be just standard french fries. these are gonna
be like steak fries. hold on. you're making pringles. pringles. thousand potatoes a second.
are they done? all right. these look. these are like steak fries. my game's gonna crash. oh god.
okay. give me the fryer later. where's my fryer later? it's on the ground over here somewhere.
where's the fryer later? where's the fryer? why are there potatoes in the soup over here?
it's on the ground somewhere. where the fuck is it? ah. wasn't it just sitting on the ground?
see? they're like steak fries. all right. there's a whole potato in here though,
unfortunately. i'll. it doesn't matter. i can cut it up later. is the oil coming up?
is the oil in there, right? yeah. okay. they're gone. all right. good.
uh. i got a few minutes left. i'll be fine. this is good. they don't take very long.
and then i gotta salt them up. all right. good. almost done. potatoes are done.
a sick fuck to do that. all right. just like five guys. that shit happens.
oh. look. it's my camouflage thing.
that does happen at five guys. they give you like a joke amount. all right. here we go.
already done. got it. bingo. five stars. incoming.
ooh. tasty. duck. you know i got that already. what was what? whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
what's matter with it? not enough pepper. too much duck breast. what do you mean not enough
pepper? what? did i fuck up the broth? i didn't fuck up the broth, did i? all right. speaking of
broth. here. because look. this is. this has been sitting here for like at least two weeks.
this is going to be fine. see? i must have screwed the recipe up. espachio with uh.
there's already one end here sitting on the edge. all right. these are good.
what's next? i gotta pick up these potatoes. uh. it's gonna be salmon, i guess. i'm guessing.
no. another duck. but this is not right. this is not seasoned correctly. i have so much of it too.
too much duck. maybe give them only two pieces. let me see. it's gotta be something i messed up
in the seasoning. yep. i fucked up the broth. i'm gonna have to remake the broth. god damn
it. yeah. not enough pepper. too much duck? not enough salt. well i'm gonna salt it in
pepper before i give it to them. yeah. that didn't do the broth right. uh. it's all good.
tomato soup. i got that over here. all right. that's good. oh. it's because i put
way too much duck in the broth. all right. that sucks. i'll make this one perfect.
pepper time dill. i'm gonna do it perfect. i can't rinse it off. okay. did i? pepper. not salt.
pepper time dill. time dill. pepper time dill. this is dill, right? yeah. and then horse
riders, when it comes out, go in. clown cooking. all right. i need a big bowl for
this. a big plate. thank god. what? the water? hey, i got plenty of potatoes. these look actually
pretty good. they look like kind of yummy chips. they actually do look kind of good.
let's stick these over here out of the way. nice. nice like flavor explosion.
what the hell? all right. i need duck. it's gonna be fucked up, but whatever.
too much duck. i'm gonna go one piece. this is all fucked. doesn't matter.
i'll fix it for tomorrow. at least if i don't lose points, it's fine. it's a net zero.
horseradish. and then what is it? what else do you need? a lemon into quarters, right?
hey, our special of the day is salmon. oh, just kidding. it's actually duck five times.
this is the third or fourth time it's been duck. there's only been one salmon.
okay. new plate. horseradish. trout's not burning. it's good. i need a horseradish
right here. nice. lemons on there. get this one perfect. and then it's parsley. six. this
one will be good. this should be at least five stars. four or five stars. that's perfect.
yeah. there we go. i'm bringing it back. is something still cooking? the oven is just on.
there you go. not bad. duck broth again. we're going for not losing points on the
duck broth. i'm gonna season it. salt and pepper, right? let me get this out quickly.
perfect. so what was wrong with the duck? do i need more salt? is it salt or pepper?
and where's the salt? that looks like a mess. salt. i need like a salt in every corner of the
room. okay. i seasoned it up. let's put some duck on here. and hopefully we can at least
get three stars. net zero. thank god. still under seasoned? too much pepper and too much salt.
so i needed to dilute it with water. i'm here. it was too much. all right. i need another trout.
okay. here we go. duck. too much salt and too much pepper. let's see if diluting helps.
yep. yeah, it does. now there's not enough pepper. bake trout. i can do the trout. i'm
gonna make this one perfect again because i'll get more fame points. and what do you know?
i got this right now. ready to move. all right. it was... okay. it's black pepper.
pepper time dil. other than a minute. come on. pepper time dil with time. into the oven.
throw gazpacho out. it should be good to go. gazpacho. bethesda's live? no they're not. is
it... what time is it? why are you saying that? you almost got me there. all right. new music.
okay. where's my trout? it's not even close. all right. i need to do pork chop.
i have a pork chop just sitting out. yes i do. what? no. cancel. what are you doing?
turn off the fucking water, please. if i lost my mind... there's nothing in here. oh,
i almost got it perfect. uh, i need... what's the... it's... what's the seasoning? salt,
pepper, time. oh my fucking god. why does this have so much on it already? when did i season
this? okay. lemon. plate and lemon. oh, it's a little... it's off. it's off. it's okay though.
it's fine. it's just barely hanging on the edges. actually, presentation-wise, it looks
pretty good. parsley, right? why? where'd the fish go? where's the fish? where did it go?
it fell into the ground. i don't see it anywhere. okay. well, that's fantastic. great. i'm glad. um,
okay. what just came in? come on! hurry up! go go go go go go go go!
come on! 30 seconds! 20 seconds! it's almost done! i had to get it out. it was still
fine. not gonna lose points. all right. we got the pork chop. that's it. we just need the
potatoes. we just need the cooked chip potatoes. i don't have any of those. we'll just use these.
plate. that's way too many. i gotta take some off. done. it was the potatoes. sorry,
i'm not gonna lose any points. that's it, right? anymore? i'll clean up. i'll make this one
perfect. i have to. and i mean, like, the best i could possibly do. i don't have another one
that was made. all right, hold on. salt, pepper. let's get them both out here. these two
are gonna be good. they're both just salt and pepper. this one... i already got the boiled
potatoes. this one is not... it's not clean, but it's okay. speaking of clean... is this clean?
10 in here. a little too much oil, but it's fine. all right, so now i'm gonna get these
going. salt and pepper on both. is it five on both or is it four on both? five on this one.
five on both. come on, i did it five times. why do you do that? i clearly just clicked
on it. salt. and this goes on the grill. this goes on the pan. all right, let's go.
bang. get it on. all right, now i need to do... i got the potatoes. this one's already done.
and then i need to lemon into slices. four slices. flip it. yeah, yeah, yeah. where's
my spatula? how's this going? pretty good. make lemon fries. that would actually probably
be kind of good. almost time to flip. and flip it. same deal over here. uh,
not quite. i definitely... i have to flip it again, though. take a look at that char. i know
it's a beautiful char. and this beautiful bird shit all over this grill. i'm gonna flip it.
okay, good. let it cook the rest. this one's almost going to take off. put on a plate,
almost. let's get this down. and i needed... what do you need with this? just two potatoes
for that one. and then this one needs the lemon slices and oregano. you got it. almost,
almost. go, go, go, go, go. bethesda is starting? no, it's not starting. i keep looking over here
and i see... bethesda, hurry! starting in five minutes. done. okay, this is just lemon slices.
lemon slices and then oregano. how many? eight. that should be the end of the day.
that's perfect. that's a lot of points. good. how does a full five star not have more points?
all right, i think we're probably gonna get a new recipe here. is salmon steak hanging
out? whatever. throw it away. all right, i need to do some cleaning. just put everything in the
sink. is this clean? this is not clean. let's get that set. turn off the stove. this is clean.
this is fine. there's a salmon just still in there. all right, let's get the repair man.
all these potatoes, are they cooked? no. put them back. can i put them back?
so much junk. i gotta get the bucket. clean up the floor. all right, that's in.
it's out. it's in. carrot on the ground. send this for food. that's not gonna work.
there's nothing to send. okay, i can clean that up. put it back up there. nothing in the ground
over here. there's a couple of these things. and that should be good. a little bit over here.
all right, dump it. set this back up. oh, i would throw these away, but i don't want to.
yeah, i will. it's a fucking mess over here. it's an absolute mess.
what is happening with this? why does it keep doing this? how much time? 20. i'm gonna stick
this down. and the person beeping the horn is gonna drive me insane. let's wash the counter.
put the horseradish over here. see, i'm cleaning. you guys think i'm not gonna clean?
i'm gonna have to get a repair man in here. because this is all messed up. this looks like
crap. i can't believe Todd Howard just announced Rat Movie 3. that would be interesting.
that would be really strange. i'm gonna put this away in the mop. watch out for the floor.
no more spills, right? nope. okay, now i need repair. i'm gonna fix all this bullshit in here.
need a new fridge? fix that. just fix everything. fix this. fix this. fix the
fryer later. fix the stove. anything else need to be repaired? i don't think so. what about
the counter? i can't fix the counter? yeah, i can. fix the counter. money well spent. how much time
do i have? all right, so i have to... i need to make some shit. i gotta make some stuff. let's
move this cayenne pepper back over here. i need a little spice rack. how am i doing on soups?
i need to make another gazpacho? no, this looks like enough. three, three. i need to make
what? yeah, i got plenty of tomato. i gotta make some duck. this is all junk, i think.
it's just not made right. this is junk. unfortunately, i had to do that. when is
the bethesda conference? it is in, i think, like 30 minutes? 40 minutes? let me check.
what just happened? what just happened? what's going on? what the hell just happened?
uh, well, that's great. it's been 90 minutes. yeah, so we got plenty of time. uh, that
just broke this raspberry juice. i need to just get rid of this, because this is just
every time i put this down, it just causes a problem. i have to carry this around with me.
okay, good. well, now i have more shit to clean up. that's great. i'm gonna make a
gazpacho. no, duck. let's try this again. 1.3, and then what? 12 salt, 12 pepper,
and two ducks. that's what the recipe was last time. so i'll season this up.
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve. it's 12 and 12,
i think. or maybe 10, but it's okay if it's a little bit over. again, i'm missing the salt. again.
yet again, i have no idea where the salt is. i'm just gonna buy five of them and put them in
every corner. i don't care. they're two cents. i'm gonna do the same thing with pepper.
there'll always be one, no matter where i am. there we go. okay. let me clean this up. my
bucket. still standing. that was weird. the bucket. potato rack. no, i need this over here.
give me the sponge. this is gonna give me, like, anxiety. i can't have that. i can't have, like,
blueberry juice all over the place. okay. up, down. i need another bottle of vinegar,
right? and then i can make the duck and we can get going. spatula, bring it back. all right.
this is looking a little better. is my salt and pepper? always put them right next to each
other. clean, clean, clean. why is there a blend in here? are we good? i think that's it.
now i'm gonna make the broth for the duck. one carrot, one onion. i've already salted and
peppered this, haven't i? i have not. are you sure? damn it. it's all right. no, i did. i did.
i did. didn't i do this? didn't i put pepper in there? do i need pepper in there? does pepper...
no pepper. okay, duck. it's two duck breasts. and that's it. and you start it up. yeah,
that'll be fine. Todd Howard is watching you play this on stage. can you imagine? didn't
level up. all right. is the critic gonna come today so i can finally do this? we got to fame
three and then it was immediately ripped from us. grilled tuna steak is the dish of the day.
you got it. it needs to simmer overnight. all right. tuna steak. let's get them out. salt them
up. okay. salt and pepper on every location. good. it's five and five. what's that? good.
good. good. put it on the ground. it hits... don't worry. it'll hit the ground. there's
plenty of time for this tuna steak to hit the ground. at least half of these will. two
out of the four will be on the ground. Todd Howard just said the new elder scrolls map is at least
five. at least five times as least... what are you saying? at least five as big as me? five
germas? shit. i just let this sit here like that. all right. hold on. fucking ruined it,
i think. how cooked is it? is it overcooked? it looks all right. you're wasting more duck.
no, i'm not. it's fine. let's get four or five plates over there and i can start the day.
i gotta get my tuna steaks ready. last one. i got my broth. just set them up in a row
here. we'll be good to go. we need more detail. all right. let's start pouring it. here we go.
the onion's a little burnt, but i don't think it'll be too much of a problem. be 25. 230.
as long as it's over 220. that's good. 290. that's a little over. 270. i can spread this
out a little bit more. that's good. all right. good. duck is cut. give me a plate. how much
time? five minutes. i can prepare the tuna steaks as well. slow and steady. don't explode.
all right. tuna steaks. these have all been salted. now i have to just grill them up.
i'm gonna put them all on at the same time. now give me a plate. transfer them all. what did
i tell you? this is at least one. well that one was dropped a double. we have one out of
four. i hit the gun twice. does that count? that's good. now i need lemons, right? lemons
into squares. four slices on each lemon. i need four lemons. get them on the cutting board.
excellent. four into fours. now i gotta move this shit out of the way. i can't do that.
there we go. these have to be good. they do. i should be able to get these. four.
what are you doing to me? oh whatever. that one's a little jacked up but it's fine.
all right. lemons are done. steaks. oh! oh! oh! oh! oh! saved. nice. is this cooking?
yes. all right. i also need how much... what do i need? parsley. i actually forget what it is,
but okay. now that we're almost done with that, i'm gonna get... my broth is already done. my
tomato soup. i have gazpacho. i have borscht. i think i'm gonna get a couple of these out,
too. there's always a herring. always. season these up. i don't remember what it is. it's...
um... give me a big plate. pepper, thyme, and dill. okay. p-t-d. pepper, thyme, dill.
well, i think it's gonna be perfect. tawd is beating up somebody in the audience. so
okay. sure he is. that one's not done. well, the edge of that needs to be cooked a little
more. okay. let's put this down. all right. now in the meantime, pepper, thyme, dill.
pepper, thyme, dill. okay. pepper, thyme, thyme. it's done. done. steaks are ready. now i just need
uh... thyme. i'll trade you. get these in the oven. two at a time. i'm putting a stamp on them.
i can do two at a time, right? we're open. okay. let's go. oof. i'm ready. right off the
bat. right off the bat. perfect. i just need to cut a lemon into quarters. give me one. you
guys are obsessed with tawd. you just are. do you think like tawd ever uh... just like reads
a twitch chat and just sits there and goes, this is really strange. do you think he knows
what everybody says? you don't think... maybe he just doesn't do social media. it doesn't look
at all when these come out horse radish. i need two of these. get it done. i can't even
imagine what it would be like to be like tawd howard. sometimes i open up my twitter
and like somebody will like draw a picture of me with like spit coming out of my nose and like
shit all over me. i mean can you imagine being tawd howard? people like draw me like five feet
tall like a clown and like puking and stuff. i can't even imagine. this is all cut. all right.
now i just need a plate. season it up. i need horse radish on this and then we can get out
of here. god damn it. did i actually get it on the lemon? i fucked it up. sorry. and then
this is just parsley. how many? six. all right. this one's all i'm gonna season this one up too.
what was so wrong with that? what was wrong with that? it was perfect. you didn't cut...
there was a problem with the lemon quarters. what was wrong with it? it was fine. what was
wrong with that? seriously. you didn't like how it was cut? what the hell are you talking
about? i can get a plate. i'm just gonna get this ready to go and move it. that's salmon?
i don't have any salmon made. where's the parsley? i'm just gonna move this over here
because it's done. now i need the salmon, which is... i have two potatoes already done here. i've got
salmon fillet. just cook it up. easy. where do you go? go back to cod. what the hell are you
talking about? go back to cod? i didn't play cod. that's way too much oil, but it's all
right. it's still edible. give me some more orders. i got them all ready. come on. two
potatoes. these are cooked. no, i don't want that one. put that one back. that one's dirty.
that one's like burnt. can i try? i'm gonna try this one. there we go. one that's not burnt.
this one's good. if i don't want to use the horrible ones, i'm not going to. spatula,
where are you? tod's crying. what the fuck are you guys doing? what is wrong with you guys?
you guys are so excited for this conference. you guys are just so
raring to go. i'm sorry to say, they're gonna announce like a new hat in the elder scrolls
online, and they're reducing the price of like all in-game purchases in blades by like 8%.
that's what you're getting. and then tod's gonna sneeze into a napkin and turn it around,
and it's gonna be like the elder scroll 6 on it. it's gonna be like blood. he's
like got blood in his... i don't know why he has blood in his nose. serve it out.
is it weird? i kind of hope that he does. no, never mind. i was gonna just say something
stupid. he comes out and does like the pendover gym carry thing where he like talks with his
butt. all right, is the duck worth it? i think this is good. we remade the duck. nice. okay,
good. we're so close to getting that extra star. french fries and steak. i don't have
that ready to go, so we're gonna have to make it. turn the grill on. salt and pepper.
get it on there quick. good. all right. oh, i still have the potatoes, but they're junk.
these are so junky. hold on. let me see if i can cut these into fries and then salt them.
give me a plate. if i can at least make these look nice, then it should be fine.
let's go with this. how many should i get? like four or five of them? cut them into little
fries and then salt them up. this should be good. okay, give me the... wait, turn this
in the knife. i cut these into fries. is that not doing anything? why? all right,
why did that work and the other one didn't? oh, who cares? why can't i cut these? they're
not salted. i got it. i got it. i got it. i got it. enjoy. good enough. you guys have lost your
minds. tod did this. tod said that. tod did this. tod went here. tod has the flu. got
this ready to go. this should be perfect. and i need oregano. so it's four slices and then
oregano. i'm so ready for this shit. one, two, three, four, and then oregano. and i got
the duck ready to go right there, too. this should be... i might get to level three here. this
is gonna be level three. tod just todded all the tods. we're now tod. tod achieved. you're
getting a little... you're getting smurf here. how... wait, how many of these do i have to do?
two... two ducks? i have to do three. grab the other one. all right, back to back. let's see if
there's enough. two ducks. everyone's so excited. everyone can't wait for this. i can't wait
either. i can't wait to see. i wonder what they're gonna do. oh, fuck you, game. that's
such bullshit. that's gonna bring me down. oh my god. can just get this off the fucking table?
what the fuck? i wasted two perfectly good soups. give me a break. why? those are perfectly fine.
what's the last thing? one more duck. i have another gazpacho, don't i? yeah, i do.
finally, some soups. 150. yes, finally. level three. what's the last thing i got? gazpacho.
i already got it right here. i'm low on soups. another steak dinner. no tuna. it's gazpacho.
i like saying gazpacho. finally, a tuna. i just hear gas. that's not a good sign. one, two,
three, four, and then it is oregano. give me a perfect score on this one, please. i'll take
it. i love how rowdy everybody is right now over this e3 tod conference. i would have had
it too. that sucks. this sucks. i have to make that from scratch now. let me just do the steak
quickly. salt, pepper, get on the grill. i think people are more excited for tod howard to just
walk on the stage than they are about the games he may or may not be announcing. okay,
the french fries. let's just dump these for a second. potatoes on this. why are they all
falling off the plate? flip, salt. i actually kind of want to eat those. one, two, three, go.
okay, everything's good. this is what it is. this just burns on. all right, now i need to
make a... i need to make the borscht. onion, carrot, parsley, beetroot. i forget what it's
like. how many is it? i haven't made it in so long. it's chicken broth. 1,700. how's
this looking? almost done. and then it's salt, right? let me look at the recipe. 20 grams,
20 grams. oh yeah, i forgot. it's like ridiculously seasoned. the screen fell.
yeah. are you guys really trying to tell me that the titantron fell down?
thank god i have one more of those. but i'm gonna make this first. looks good. 20 grams.
this is so salt-intensive. people actually eat this? this is like a thousand milligrams
of salt per serving. it's like drinking salt. no, now i need... i swear to god. get the
fuck away from me. just get them away. they're like magnetic. god damn it. am i cooking
anything? no. nothing's cooking, right? all right. i need to buy another bottle of
shit. what a pain in the ass. salt, pepper, again. do it again. where's the salt? i just
had it. all right. this is parsley, carrot, five beets, and an onion. i think that's it.
cook it. go. what else do i need to get? uh, gazpacho. i already hear it. it's right there.
that's fucking crazy. he just ordered... uh, come on. hurry up. i got that. here,
i got an idea. it's already ready. new order of what? tomato soup? i'm so excited.
too many lemons? now that's the right amount of lemons. see? making some good money.
all right. how are we looking? onion. take it out. and this is tomato, right? yep.
is that the song that's playing?
uh, hurry. hurry. hurry. perfect timing. i actually have to take that out now. come on.
hurry. hurry. hurry. hurry. hurry. good. saved it. apparently it was perfect. all right. duck.
careful with this. duck broth. right here. that's the last one. hopefully nobody else orders it.
and hopefully that goes through. and i got the last tuna. hopefully... wait. where's the last
tuna? oh, come on. it's another duck. i still have just a full herring that nobody ordered.
i'm gonna pee my pants. i'm gonna piss really bad. i gotta make sure i pee before the
conference. what do we team on is what? duck. i guess i can just make it right now. i need
well, shit. you got it. um, i need ten ten and then one carrot, one onion. e3 countdown on the
screen. let's get it on the screen. no. i don't care. no. i care about e3. i just don't care
about the countdown to e3. i know it's gonna happen. that's one more extra pepper. that's
fine. all right. now i need parsley and a carrot. right? no. carrot and onion. and then
put the two duck breasts in here as well. and then grind it up. we good. i need two
of these. that's it. what the hell? what the hell happened over here? skipping
interconnecting words now. is this on? these are clean. yeah. give them up. what's been your
guy's favorite part about e3 so far? and i need full paragraphs. if what you write is less
than four sentences, you're getting banned from the channel. Todd Todd Todd Todd Todd Todd Todd
Todd. at least i can use these. anybody a Todd fan here? oh, i don't think so. i think you're
in short company there. all right. get that onion in. is one of these duck breasts not cooking?
no. get the onion out. no reason to have it in. the Keanu Reeves is probably my favorite part
of all the things they showed at e3 this year. when he came out on stage
and made the references to the game that i liked, i thought it was really fun. see,
i did a paragraph. i pretty much only needed to have like two or three words there,
but i told you you're going to get banned if you don't do at least four sentences.
i'm not going to get banned. you might. someone will. okay, take this out. i just need to do
the broth. get the duck breasts out. cut. serve. i've really been feeling indifferent
about e3 so far. i'm not really a microsoft fan, so the entire show just went past me.
yesterday i only saw the soccer football conference for the fifa game, and that was
the kind of awful not gonna lie. all right, let's broth it up. Todd comes out in a
terminator costume. they making a new terminator game? i'd fucking play it.
i wonder if they're still gonna be, whatever the game is, still gonna be using the telltale
engine from like 2007. we'll find out soon enough. all right, it's time. it's time to,
the critic is coming today. i gotta get everything ready to go. whatever the critic wants,
i gotta make fresh. i do have some bowls to put out. i got duck here because we're at
fame level three. i have a full halibut ready. i've got my potato crisps. let me get some
bowls out because i need the broth. i'm ready for the critic. need it. gazpacho. i gotta make a
lot of shit here, don't i? yeah, the boar should be fine. i can probably fit it into three or
four plates, and then i need to make some gazpacho. gazpacho, gazpacho, gazpacho. every
time i say gazpacho, some of you guys have like your veins pop out of your forehead.
calm down. it's okay. just relax. it's not worth getting upset over. like, when people call me,
like, okay, for instance, my streamer persona video game online media name
is jerma. jerma985, right? don't forget it either. i get called sometimes jerma. oh hey,
jerma! jerma! it's all right. what am i gonna, that's fine. it's too much in that one.
people have different ways to pronounce things.
i know some people are freaking out about pouring with the handle.
don't worry. it's all right. it's, you can call me jerma. you can call me jerma.
call me joe. all right, i need a bunch of, i need a bunch of the g one. i need to make a
little bit more jerma. that's good enough. take this out. hopefully there's not more than
two borsts tomorrow. hopefully the critic doesn't want it. just remake the soup,
again, with the same pot. i need more chicken stock if that's gonna, let's just see if it works.
these are all empty. why am i still holding on to these? isn't this how grandmothers usually make
the food? they use the same thing over and over again. no, that's still good. it's still
delicious. no, no, no, no, no, no, we don't need to go to the grocery store. grandma,
the beets are green. extra flavor. people eat cheese, you eat cheese. that's gotten mold on
it. i mean, it's hitting, it's hitting all the onions and shit. are you happy,
you're happy you had the onions? are you glad you had the onions? are you happy you had the onions?
huh? are you glad you had the onions? all right, we still got time. anybody knows that that's a
reference to. you get 600 fucking million dollars from my pretend monopoly bank account
that i pretend to send to you through telepathic means as a joke. am i gonna say it? nobody
knows that. i don't think anybody knows. no, it's not from family guy. there's 6100 people
here. not one person knows this. it's not the simpsons. i'm not saying it again. well,
it looks like i get to keep my money. it was from this xbox conference. yeah, phil came out
and was talking about how are you happy you had the onions? are you glad you had the onions?
all right, what am i doing? uh, i got time. perfect. all right, uh, what was i making? uh,
this. no, this is all burnt. this is not even making the soup correctly, guys. it's
not gonna work. um, i gotta keep prepping. uh, gazpacho. gazpacho. get this right.
i'm walking around like an idiot. that's some curb your enthusiasm. yep, you got, hold on.
there you go. spend it wisely. and did i get it? didn't go in? 30 and 30, right? yes.
and then what is this? all right, there's supposed to be salt and pepper at every station.
there is. shit, i thought i didn't get it. come on, get in there. what? whatever. you
gotta get a new joke to pass the time. i'm not like a joke factory, guys. what do you
want me to say? i'm not like, i can't just produce. just turn the webcam on. no, i can't,
i can't just produce under fucking circumstance. i got, i've got, it's just gotta be natural.
you want to turn the fucking webcam on and start dancing? why would i ever do that?
what do you think i am? a vessel. ah, maybe, maybe in your, like,
fucking fan fiction. this is all burnt completely. that was loud. all right, so
i think i'm pretty much ready for the day. i got that. i'm gonna make up some,
what's the meal of the day? see, i dumped the hot soup all over me. don't, isn't that,
isn't that like a 10 out of 10 hysterical piece of human comedy? give me the bucket.
here comes the critic. i'm gonna impress the critic. and then at that point,
it's gonna be time for the bethesda electronic conference. we'll see what the fuck they
introduce. i'm so looking forward to it. my whole life has been leading up to this moment
when i get to see todd howard come out on stage, clap and go,
i can't wait. it's gonna happen. this first thing is gonna do. all right, i think i'm ready to go.
i am. whatever. i'm not gonna make the meat beforehand because if he wants meat,
it has to be fresh. i can't just give the critic the crap from the freezer.
all right, here we go. this is it. more exciting than e3. that was 916 dollars.
is that more than i've ever had? i've never received that kind of paycheck right here.
all right, we got some skills. all right, cheaper products, liquids, fame boost.
is it like a one where critics are less critical? taste tolerance is already up.
derpers and gourmets have their expectations lowered. is there a derper?
oh, i was gonna explain a dream. you're right. yep, yep, yep. i was gonna talk about a dream.
so i don't know how many of you other guys do this or not, but sometimes this happens to
me, and it happened like over the course of a few nights. so a few nights ago, i had a dream
that i broke my brother's golf clubs. i don't know why. i had a dream that i was golfing,
and i snapped the head off. i was trying to drive too hard, and i was really embarrassed,
and i was really scared about it. i was like, holy shit, this is bad. i just broke my
brother's fucking driver. it was like a golf club or something. so i broke it, and then i
woke up. and i thought that it was real, and after like two or three hours, it wasn't
really that real anymore. i was like, oh, whatever, that's weird. did that happen? did
it not happen? whatever, and i forgot about it. but like two days later, i had another
dream where i replaced the golf clubs. and it was so... like i went to the store and
i bought golf clubs, and i brought them back, and i gave them to my brother. so i woke up,
and i'm not kidding, i thought that i did a perfect like dream loop where i honestly,
to goodness still, even to this day, think it may even be real. like a day later. it was so real
that i broke the clubs, replaced them over two days, and i was going to text him, be like,
hey, like i replaced your golf clubs. i just want to like... you got them, right? i don't
know why my brain was going to text him that like this morning. you guys ever have like a
complete loop where you finish a complete story arc in your brain, and you thought it was
real over the course of a couple days? that may not have even been a dream. okay, here we
go. i definitely want that. you're just insane. you're just a freak. at least i replaced them.
let's go with less spices. all right, this is it. i fucked this up last time. bad.
you don't have a brother. espachos de... okay, this is... i gotta be ready. those of you that
don't know this game, if you don't give the critic at least a four star dish, he removes
almost 150 points from your score, and it takes like two hours to come back.
it's really bad. but i don't even play golf. i don't even do that. i don't play golf at all, ever.
all right, let's get right to it. i don't even need to prepare. let's go. of course,
it's pork chops. the thing... one thing that i don't have ready to be made,
but this is not the critic, so i don't really care that much about it. this is what? pepper
p t d, right? salt, pepper, and thyme. no. it's s b t. four four s b t. thyme. where is it?
that's... why is it not on my station? you all right? come on. what? what do you... what do you...
i just clearly did it. i clearly just put it on there. you gotta be kidding me. all right, 30.
these take a long time to get it in there. and then i also have the potatoes, right? yeah,
they're already over here. just gotta wait for that to cook. just stare at it. i got
one customer in the store. all right, whatever it is, i'm making it fresh for the critic.
oh shit, they have to be baked. they gotta be baked. just chunked up the potatoes. that's 11.
i keep making that mistake. i swear to god. it's all right. all right, chunk them up into
50 gram slices. i lose this knife every single day. is it on the ground? i can't cut it on
here. get out of the way! it's not the critic, i don't care. that technique's not
going to work here. good. all right. salt. e3? e3? e3? what do you mean e3? e3? in 30 minutes.
it's not right now. it's in 30 minutes. i'm not missing it. no, you guys, it's not even time.
the pre-show? why do i want to watch the pre-show? i am the pre-show! he's not wrong.
hey, what just happened to the view count? the view count just went to zero.
oh no, nobody's watching anymore. nobody's here. they all left. everybody wanted to go see the
pre-show. zero viewers. well, shit. hey, they all came back. did you? but how was the pre-show? is
it any good? i knew you'd come back. i knew you were gonna come back to this channel. come on.
i can't serve it on this. what am i doing? i gotta salt these. excuse me. yeah, we've
already talked about our e3 impressions. what more would you like me to say? what do i think
is going to happen at bethesda? you want me to give you my insider information that i don't have?
we've got to pay extra for the pre-show. you don't have to pay anything for the pre-show.
i would be happy if we got a game that had magic in it. like, with a wand. that's really
it. is this the critic? no. make sure you start screaming when it's time, because i will
forget. and i'm going to be late to the conference. all right, this is salmon. yeah,
i got potatoes already done. what's the big thing this year besides the xbox alexa?
was that it? what is nintendo going to show? new smash brothers person? cyberpunk? yeah,
but we've already seen them. is there anything new that we've never seen before? starfield. oh
yeah, they're making a starfield. i completely forgot about that. i wonder if they're going
to show any gameplay. you just activated my alexa? oh, i'm sorry. i forgot. i'm on
new speakers at full blast right now. how loud do you guys watch this stream? you guys
have like a subwoofer and you just blast it? does the low tones in my voice come out really well?
i don't know what my spatula is. high quality chef. come on, finish. finish so i can go see
bethesda. todd just did a backflip. i bet you he can do a backflip. i really think he can.
he doesn't seem like the kind of guy that can do like aerials and backflips.
i don't know why i see him on a trapeze. he comes out in one of those like circus
onesies. he's like the kind of like trapeze kind of guys i think. he's a nerd. you can be a nerd
and still use a trapeze. i'm not sure what was so bad about that. potatoes? all right, here we go.
food critics ordering. this is a big deal. i can't screw this up. whatever it is, i'm making it
fresh. no! we did it! i got a level up. new fame level. duck, coming up. what happened over
here? why? whatever. pee break please? yeah, what's that? i gotta get ready. 20 minutes,
right? hold on. almost. at the end of this day. we're almost done. i'm not going to be late. where's
the... i already made duck. where is it? where did i put the duck? oh my god, give me a fucking break.
all right, almost done. it wouldn't be germa if he wasn't late. i wasn't late today.
i was 10-15 minutes ready early. ready for the conference. it's duck again. i don't care.
it's not ready. let's flip it. uh, let's give me... um, where is it? what? oh, okay,
hold on. i made a little gravy just to make it taste a little better. that's frozen solid. all
right, in the time that i've just been being a dickhead, i could have just done this normally
and done it correctly and had a normal amount of stars. i can't put this in. just finish it
in the oven. i already won. it doesn't matter. oh, jesus, there's a lot of other stuff here.
okay, hold on. what's the critic leaves? who cares? best gazpacho i've ever had. and uh,
salmon, salmon, salmon. where's the salmon? did i just cook it? it's in the oven. yeah,
it's like buried somewhere down here. it's like mustard on it. well, i don't care. i
already beat it. it doesn't matter. i need the salmon right now. why? i'm getting a
lot of orders right now. this is not good. um, all right, steak. let's just get this out and
ready. go, go, go, go, go. pan, pan, pan, pan, pan. i'm going as fast as i can. okay,
what else? uh, i need the duck. duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
flip it. no, not yet. is it done? oh my god. i just almost pissed my pants.
i swear to god, i almost fucking pissed my pants. where's the spatula? i'm so bad.
i can't do three things at once. give me another spatula. all right, it's fine. all
right, get this on, get this on, on, on, on, on. got it. almost. look at that piece of raw
steak. all right, what? 57 seconds. this is a joke.
you got to serve this. this goes back immediately. good enough. three day old
video set. plus three fame. all right, this has got to come out now. i got the
salmon, salmon, salmon, salmon right here. here we go. watchio. come on.
took a giant bite out of that potato. two, three, four. done. 15 minutes. all right,
all right. one more time. one more time. wait, wait, wait. we'll be done in a second. one more
second. tomato. tomato and gazpacho. it's all right. still good enough. getting a lot of orders
immediately here. good. all right. the dog. i gotta do the duck. whatever comes in next,
who cares? gazpacho is really good apparently. oh, time, time, time, time. what do i got?
four minutes. um, two ducks. uh-oh. that's all right. i got enough. get out of there.
i only have one duck breast in here. i'm an idiot. just cut it thin. all right. good. uh,
two bowls. now that goes on after, after, after. wait, wait, wait. did i think that was going to
work? did i honestly think that was going to happen? 500. oh, that's going to cause a fire.
that's going to cause a fire. can i do it before the fire starts? a stainless steel pot.
what was wrong? i just gave you one that was fine. what was wrong with this one?
not enough duck, not enough pepper, too much onion. the other one was fine.
it came from the same bowl. oh no, those might... i had a potato or whatever.
what do i need? i need a trout gazpacho. i got one more. the gazpacho's been killing it today.
it's been really good apparently. the conference. i know, i know, i know. i'm going,
i'm going. they're almost done with the day. and then i can, i'll take a two or three
minute pee break and we'll come back into the conference. what's the last thing i need?
oh my god, another duck. i gotta, i have to get out of here. uh, oh my god, this is the longest
day ever. hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. um, just... what else do i need? okay, what do
you need? you need duck, uh, pork chop, potatoes, so we're gonna fry the potatoes, and okay,
put everything in there. i already got a lemon right here. perfect shot. okay, lemon, then
there's, uh, the potatoes. potatoes, i already got potatoes. i'm good. all right, uh, i need to make
the broth for the broth. duck broth. uh, let's go, let's go, go, go. i'm kind of panicking right
now. freaking out. anything in here? get in. e3, i know, i know, i know, i know. e3, e3.
no, not time. pepper, pepper, come on. how are you doing? the trout's not even cooking.
okay, good. come on, hurry up! what's going on? what's wrong with this? there's no duck in
there. for the duck flavoring. hold on. don't pick it up. good enough. okay, can i plate? three
plates. one. grab some of these. throw it out there. hurry up. that's really bad, but it doesn't
matter. i know, i know, i know. e3, i know. what time check? how much time? nine minutes.
that's enough time for me to finish this and go pee. why is there so many orders?
why is there so many orders? this is just... duck? just... okay, who cares? just get it in a bowl,
right now. bowl, bowl, bowl. i need a bowl. do i still have one of these? i do. perfect. why
are there a fucking million orders right now? this is the longest day ever. um, where's the
trout? where's the trout? where's the trout? 30 seconds. i don't even know what it is.
i need a plate. plate, plate, plate, plate, plate, plate, plate, plate. okay, plate, and then
the lemon, right? lemon. what's the lemon? and it's a parsley or something, right?
oh! zero seconds left. i got it. gazpacho. you're killing me here. i have to go watch e3.
i fucking can't even. just hit servant raw. who cares? it's a lot of... okay, gazpacho. quick,
quick, quick, quick, quick. i can do this real quick. gazpacho, right? yep. where's my lid?
where's my lid? where's my lid? where's my lid? i don't want to make any more duck.
where's my lid? i don't know where the lid is. e3 is on. no, it's not. how much time? i get six
minutes. i'm gonna pee. oh god damn it. that's all oil. no one would eat this. it's too much
oil. no, no, no. i can't make it up. i can't. go on. all right. i hope i don't need to do
another gazpacho. wait, i need that oil. e3. i'm going, i'm going, i'm going.
i'm going, i'm going. last thing is the duck. no, it's the tuna. i'm... i can't do that.
i'm just trying to get to the end of the day. this is taking forever. the announcement's
happening right now. no, it's not. i'm going. i'm going, i'm going. i gotta pee too. all
right, what's the last thing? salmon. go! four minutes. done! this is a fucking joke.
this is a joke. it's a joke. i gotta pee in my pants. all right, i'm going. all right,
i'll be back. i'll be back. i'm gonna pee. i'm gonna put it on the screen so you don't miss anything.