Let's do it.
Four, six, five, six, seven people on B now.
That's a lot of people.
Ooh, this is a good place to do this.
This is a good place to do this.
Can I get another one?
Oh!
I will get somebody.
Oh, I'm just slowly taking out your whole team.
Somebody's on C!
What? Somebody's on C!
Somebody get back there and get that...I gotta get back there.
Nice job. Beautiful.
Beautiful air blast. He's gonna walk right into this.
Where are ya?
Oh, there you are.
Damn it, I'm so awful!
Oh, now I'm just freaking out.
Now I'm just freaking out.
Holy jeez, I am totally freaking out.
I'm freaking out! I'm totally freaking out right now.
I'm freaking out!
I gotta piss.
I gotta pee so bad right now? Is that the problem?
Who is on this point? There's nobody on the point.
Where is this guy?
What the fuck? It was a pyro?
No, I'm not allowed to pee.
I'm not allowed to go pee yet until I win a round.
That's the punishment for me just like
whiffing on like nine arrows in a row.
Do it for the camera. Go...
Yeah! Nice. Good spin, bro.
Do it again. One more time.
One more time for the camera. Just for the camera.
For the camera. Come on. You got a camera point at me.
I got a camera point at you.
We're both...
Let's make this quick.
Because seriously, I'm going to piss my fucking pants.
Go to A first.
And Scout just kind of standing there.
He'll go down. Make it nice and easy.
Nice and quick.
Just like my old pancake recipe.
See, what you gotta do is you gotta do twigs.
No, don't worry. I'm not going to do that joke again.
That joke is going to be buried forever.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Scout, turn. Turn around, Scout.
Where is he? What?
What kind of fucked up magic trick was that?
Now I'm going to burn.
Do you have any milk? Got milk?
Hey, got milk?
I really am going to burn though.
Like, I really am going to burn. This is a stupid idea.
Hey, got milk?
Hey, need some milk?
At least the Scout is going to get it.
Come on, Scout. Get it.
Why is nobody pushing B?
They got a sentry? Is that the issue?
Nice dodge. I'll accept it.
I'll accept that dodge for what it was.
No, no. Fuck you.
I ain't going to die right there.
No!
Scramble the teams. No, I gotta pee.
Do not scramble the teams. I've got to piss.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Stack every single person on A.
Here comes a spy. He's not going to do anything
because there's like 12 of us here.
Just cap it. Nothing spooky.
Nothing fancy. Nothing...what?
How did you...
How did he get...
Okay, we're still...
No, that's a crit. Where are these people?
Come on up. Come on up. Yeah.
Come on up. I ain't losing this.
Get A. Please get A. We got it.
Three, two, one.
Beautiful. Let's move on.
Jerma's gotta pee.
He is going to piss his pants if we don't
hurry this up.
Where'd he go? He's dead.
Why am I...what am I doing at C? I'm like skipping.
I'm skipping B because I have to pee so bad.
Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep.
Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep.
Look at his knee.
Look at the balls.
Stop caring about that shit.
Just get the kill.
Get rid of that thing. Everybody get on B.
You know when you gotta pee so bad
that you can feel it inside of
like your neck?
I can feel this piss loading up
into my like esophagus.
That's like how much I have to pee right now.
I'm going to pee out of my esophagus in about 30 seconds.
Cap it, cap it, cap it. Go E right to C.
to see we got this i think i'm gonna get to pee i'm gonna actually get to piss this is gonna be
amazing look at all like well i'm doing because of this this guy's lagging so much i can't even
i was so distracted get it get it get it yes no no please get it please get it i'm gonna sprint
out of here when i get the chance man right when this wins are you a spy why are you acting like a
spy you are a spy yes you are you're running so slow what how did i not get that to begin with
how did i not know that to be at first hand that you were a spy i did i got a clouded brain right
now clouded brains i'm not seeing straight i'm not thinking straight did you get them good you no no
no no we aren't doing why am i drinking that why would i do that i have to pee really bad and i'm
like drinking more liquid do i want to piss my pants like is that seriously what i want to have
happen just run on the point knock an arrow randomly now just go with the ham i don't fucking care
let's go let's go let's go i don't care i'm gonna cap this right now i will win this right now
i'm gonna win this shit right now get the fuck out of my face i gotta piss wicked bad
get the fuck out of here no yeah am i gonna get my hopes up again this is it this is the one
thank you so much cap it right now i'm gonna block block block block block