I was thinking about waiting. That was a bad thing to start with. I should have done that
before. That's why I'm muted. I had an opportunity to do that before the stream turned on. I don't
know what... I shouldn't be in control of this button. I was gonna wait till 1 pm, but I'm here.
I'm ready. I'm just ready to go. I don't need to wait till... I've been sitting here for like
five minutes just going like, you know, okay, I'm here. Let's just go early. Not even that early.
But still, we're here. Good afternoon. If you joined us last night,
today, I talked about how Dead Rising 1 was gonna be the stream today.
And I also made a mistake talking about how... what was gonna happen over the next couple days.
I told you I had a doctor's appointment tomorrow. That's not true. It actually is the next day.
So, uh, I believe this game takes somewhere between 10 to 12 hours to do it. 13 hours.
So we're gonna do this today, and we're gonna do this tomorrow. I will then go to my doctor's
appointment. So we're gonna bang out Dead Rising the next two days in a row. This is a two-hour
game. No, it is not. This is not a two-hour game. Yeah, what I know about Dead Rising, at least the
original. In fact, all the Dead Rising, it doesn't matter which one it is. I've collectively played
maybe six and a half hours of all of them combined. Dead Rising 1, Dead Rising 2, Dead Rising 3.
So, I mean, I know how the game kind of works. I've played it off and on a couple of times,
randomly, 60% of the way through somebody else's playthrough on a couch.
Dude, take this! You guys, try Dead Rising. You can throw CDs at people, and it's like,
CDs? What are you talking about? I remember grabbing the CDs,
and the phrase being CDs at zombies. And I also remember having like, there's like a Lego set.
That's the only thing I know. And you have a camera. So we're gonna just, I'm gonna play the whole
thing. Seems like one of those games that I should have done a long time ago. Um, no, but I had this
two videos of Dead Rising 2 and Dead Rising 3. Maybe I'll just do them all. Not back to back,
but should I just play Dead Rising 2 and Dead Rising 3 eventually? Just play them
all the way through? Don't do Dead, there's a, wait, there's Dead Rising 4. Did I play Dead
Rising 4? I didn't remember. Did I? What's the one where you had to get the phone app from Microsoft
to like, call in an airstrike? Which one was that? Was that three or four? Three. Yeah, there was a
phone companion app that you could get for Dead Rising 3 to call in an airstrike from your phone.
Well, we'll see. But that's what we're gonna do today into tomorrow. That's the plan. And I'm
almost ready to go here. Just give me one more second and we'll get started. I don't know where
my lip balm is. This is bad. I mean, this, this is a, this is a total diva moment. I know, but like,
I can't, I cannot stream without my lip balm. It's not gonna, it's not possible. It's not possible.
I can't do it. It's the only way I can live stream. Where is it? I always have two balms right next
to me at all times. Whatever. Stream is canceled. Now, fuck it. Whatever. Let's go. I'll be all
right. Okay. So the stream sucks today. It's cause I didn't have lip balm on at the very beginning.
Don't forget that. All right. So I got everything ready to go. Start game. This is just going to be
Dead Rising 1. Let's see how fun it is. I heard it's fun. 72 hour mode. New game, right? That's
what I want to do, right? That means I have 72. That's three streams, three full days.
That's the one, right? Is this the PC? This is the PC version. Is that a bad thing?
No, no. Okay. So I'm just 72 hour mode. That's the one, right? September 19th, 11 at 27.
It was PM AM. Haven't you played this game? It's like randomly, like on a friend's couch.
I've never played through the whole game. Have I played through this game on camera? No, I don't
even guys. I've played like 12,000 games on stream and on video. I don't know. I have no idea.
Say buddy. No, I didn't. You mentioned something about research for a story. That's right. Got a
tip that something big's happening in a nowhere little town like that. They sure didn't mention
anything about it on TV. Yeah. Well, I'm freelance pal. I don't make my living waiting for the TV
to play for on the street. Yeah, I kind of remember that.
Not this one. Population 53500 characteristics. Jack shit.
The only thing to do in this town is kill time at the shopping mall.
All right, every quiet. Everybody said anything. I'm talking to myself.
Was that the army? Yeah, I took a sip out of my water over here. That's been here since last
night and it tastes like hamburger meat. I don't know why that's fucked up. I had to share that
because that's strange. I want to get shots of the whole town before the national guard finishes
roping it off. Take me over the main street. Cooked hamburger meat. All right, here we go.
Oh, I can take pictures. How do I take a picture? Zoom in. Should I take a photo? Oh,
okay. That's zoom in. X is shutter. Got it. Oh, you got you get points. You did points for things.
Okay, move camera. Zoom in. I didn't there's enough picture of nothing. How do we zoom out?
There we go. Okay, so zoom in and zoom out. This is Pokemon snap. I need more stuff going on. Here
we go. Zoom in. Nice brutality. Oh, wait. Action shot. Got it right when it was about to happen.
Damn it. I almost had it. Save this guy? Like, how am I supposed to save this guy?
Are they on the playground? No, zoom in. I would laugh so hard if one went down the slide. Wait,
here we go. He's gonna do it. Come on. Damn it. He didn't let go under the tire.
Oh, they're killing this guy. If I was just stayed on this,
I could have reduced the sensitivity on this camera too. Wait, no genre. This is genre for
the photos and everything. Should I get a picture of the skyline? That's not bad. Right here. Right
down like Main Street. Are they saving these photos by the way? Oh, I have 17 photos remaining. Is
that what that is? Should I wait? That's kind of interesting. I mean, that's not interesting.
This is just a guy standing on a roof. That's not that interesting. No, I gotta get better
on that. Perfect. I gotta make sure I get a good angle. Whoa, no, I got it.
I just barely got it too. What else we got? We're going up. Okay. Take a picture of your face.
I can't. Here we go. Wait, wait, wait. Somebody fighting. Nice. She's gonna fall off. She's gonna
fall off. She's gonna fall off. She's gonna fall off. I'm ready. I'm ready for the photo. Come on.
I'm gonna get it right here. Come on. And come on. Got it. Wait, that wasn't her.
I got it too nice. Off the titan trunk. Why is everybody calling me fucked up? What? This is
part of the game. I need to take photos and stuff. I'm a psycho. I can't save them.
Can you get me on? You gotta be kidding me. Man, you are nuts. Not with that attitude.
No, not with any. I got a camera in my hand. Don't forget to come back. We don't have like
grenade launchers in here. It's Frank. Frank West. Remember that name because the whole world's
gonna know it in three days. When I get confirmed for Smash Brothers on the next Nintendo Direct.
Now there it goes. A lot of helicopters flying really close.
Am I gonna make it jump for it? Get a photo of that one. Can I take a picture of this?
Big Bits came in. After the cutscene.
Gonna turn this up.
Didn't you? What did you see from the sky? Well, if it were just a riot,
I doubt the military would quarantine the entire area. The moratorium on information getting out
is a little extreme in my opinion. Frank is so ugly. What are you talking about?
Something else I can't put my finger on. What are you talking about? Doesn't sound like civil
disobedience. It's too quiet. Almost as if everyone's already dead.
Yeah, he looks like he's squished. So why don't you just tell me already?
What? Nope. All right, just listen to the cutscene. I think you'd better see for yourself.
This, my friend, is hell. Let's bring the camera up and just take a picture right in his face
so I can remember who this person is. I'd be taking pictures of everybody I came across.
Can you stand right here for a second? Let me take a photo. Frank must be on the heliport
at 12 p.m. on the 22nd or he will be left behind in the mall.
Okay. Pay careful attention to the time as you play. So the check... No, it's not tab. There it is.
All right, so check watch is left on the d-pad. So it is 12 o'clock on the 19th. Oh, that's fast.
Check watch. Why do I have like a world news ticker down here? Okay. Check watch. What about it?
I don't need to... Why do I... I checked the watch already. Looks like you're the only journalist
that made it out of here. Okay. I'm looking forward to some nice pictures. Oh, wait. Hold on. How do
I take a photo? Good. Okay. Security room. Why did it just want to tell me to check my watch five
times? You can save your progress at locations marked with S such as the sofa in the security
room or the mall's public restroom. Okay. I can save in the bathroom or in the security room.
So you can save your progress at locations marked with S. So just the sofa in the security room.
What's in here? Change clothes. All right. I guess I'm a golfer now. All right. What do I want to be
dressed as? All right. I don't know. I want the golf. All right. All right. Okay. So that's cool.
Am I sprinting or is there a sprint button? Is there crafting in this one? I remember playing
like the third and fourth one. You had to make stuff. All right. Um, hold on. What's over here?
All right. I don't want to like waste time because I don't really have any time. How much time? I've
been walking around for 20 minutes. All right. I bet. Just save the game. Where's the security
room? Which one of these is the security room? Straight ahead. This is the janitor's room.
What is this? I'm just wasting more time. What? Okay. All right. So that zero killed. Well,
actually one is killed. Uh, staff. I know. Where's the where's the actual security room?
Is it back here? Is it up the stairs? Where's the where's the security room?
The one with the green sofa. Which one of these had a green sofa? It's it's right here. There's
no security. It's not security room. This is the security room. I thought I had to go in one of the
one of the rooms was a security room. No, it's the security sofa. Okay. All right. Is there a
ladder? No. So what the fuck am I supposed to do? Just leave? Uh, I guess I'm going this way.
Entrance. I've never played Dead Rising 1. I told you. I had somebody handing me the controller
like 17 hours into the game to throw CDs. Who the fuck is this guy? Who are these people?
She's like, she just tackled me twice.
Without my precious little sweetie doggie. Oh, where is my my doggy shield? All right. Mission
one. Save dog. Hey, this is no time to ogle pretty girls, son. You're looking to get yourself
beaten alive by zombies. Holy shit. This guy's eyes. Did you just say zombies? Take a look out
there. If those ain't zombies, what would you call them? They're gonna get in. Why is everybody
getting so close to your face? Yeah. One is just jumping right into your face. Since last night.
Now, they're all that's out there. Hey, look on the bright side. Zombies are stupid and slow.
We should be safe in here. All right, then feel like making yourself standing in my shot. Take
a look around the mall. Bring anything we can use for the barricade back here. This barricade sucks.
You just threw a bunch of benches in the way. Where's the car that's parked in every mall?
Back the car up here. There's got to be at least two of them, right? All right. Find something.
Find something to block. All right. I don't have time for this. I'm on the clock right now. It's
been an hour. All right. Find something to barricade. Okay. It's drama. That guy's a gun. All
right. Whatever. Let's go. But I have to take photos of people. Hold on. Nice. More drama.
How many photos do I have? I don't want to just take photos of random shit. What's this?
Over the shoulder. Nice drama. Okay. I think I found something. I'm running around like a shit
myself. I'm fine. You right there. Do you have any idea what you've done? Why did you summon me to
this place? What are you planning? Would you calm down? I don't even know what you're talking about.
Can you open the door? I think they got in. No. So, it's the lady saving her dog is what starts
the whole outbreak here. I think the dog's a zombie. Okay. Well, there's so many character
introductions. What do I do? To the stairs. All right. I'm going. But what about everybody else
down here? HDTV. All right. Different items perform different actions. Some weapons are capable of
special attacks performed by holding X for a moment. You can attack or you can hold right
trigger and X's throw. Multiple items can be held in stock simultaneously. The maximum stock number
can be raised by leveling up. You can change the bumpers. Throw an item down. Down. Unequipped is
up. Okay. Sounds pretty simple enough.
Oh, no. It's dead. Kathy. Kathy, hold on a second. I'm coming. I'm coming. Kathy.
Stand behind me. Kathy. Yep. These things are scripted. They're supposed to die. It's scripted.
It's scripted. It's okay. You can't save them. This is scripted. You can't. Barley, come here.
What are you doing? Smoking a cigarette? What are you doing? Come here.
No, no. Get. What the hell? All right. You know what? It's scripted. It's scripted, right?
Whoa. When grabbed by multiple zombies, an escape command will appear on the screen.
None of the commands is directed before the time runs out and you can escape the dangerous situation.
Okay. Well, I'm sorry. I tried. Barley and Willis is dead. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Watch out. I made it. All this because grandma wanted the dog. Yeah. Oh, I made it out. No, I
didn't. Where are the others? Imagine like a zombie apocalypse happens and the first thing that you
do is you grab a bench and just throw it. They got away. Just into everybody. Why would you do
something like that? Like come up with a plan. A quick one. Not grab heavy object and throw into
friends because those things are in the mall. We better not use this door. Well, what are you
doing? The air ducks. They'll get us back into the mall and apparently those things aren't
smart enough to use the ducks so they won't be a factor. Wait a minute. You want to get back in
there? What for? He's gonna get grabbed. Hey. Nice camera. Are you a photographer?
No, no, no. Never ask anybody if they have a camera. They're a photographer. They're gonna
talk your ear off for like two hours. Show me some pictures, Frank. You really seem to know what
you're doing. Wow. This is terrible. Who are you guys anyway? Why did you take pictures of people
falling off of the building? I don't know. I've never taken this costume off.
She wiped your SD card. Oh 70. What? It's already been two hours or an hour and like 10 minutes?
Okay, security room. Wait, is there like... I know you don't eat food. You do, right? How do you eat
it? Okay, so I'm gonna take coffee creamer. I'm gonna take two coffee creamers. I can't answer.
Okay, I gotta... Okay, what's up? You're planning on going back down into the mall, are you? I
wouldn't do that if I were you, but you young... Well, if you're gonna do it, at least take this.
Transceiver with you. And you better take this. You obtained the mall map. You obtained the
transceiver. All right. You obtained the mall map. Okay, so how do I use it? Well, how do I...
Should I just go in? I'm going... Go in? Any quests or anything? I'm just going in. I didn't save the
game. Fuck. Whatever. I'll be fine. This is a timed game. I can't just like dilly dally. Okay,
I'm on the roof. Jeff! Jeff! Come here. You! Have you seen my wife, Natalie? She should still be
around here. Hey, hey, hey! I'll lend a hand. That's a pretty good weapon. Fellow golfer, I see.
The name's Jeff Mayer, by the way. I'm Frank. I'm telling you, that back nine here is killer.
Escorting survivors. Survivors each behave differently depending on the circumstances
and their own varying personalities. It was a good idea to escort as many as possible to the
safety of the security room. Call survivor or set goal marker. Okay, so that's right triggered in
Y. So Y is to be like, come here. Okay. Okay, join. So... Follow me! All right, so follow me.
We're gonna find... gonna find your wife is around here somewhere. Follow me! Natalie,
found you. Come on, Jeff. I don't know how you guys even got separated. It's an open spot. It's an
open space. Wait, wait, hey, hey! Okay, let's go. I'll never let you go again. We have to go now.
It's not safe. I know a place. I'll take the security room. Once the number of photos taken
exceeds 30, they'll begin to be deleted in order automatically. You can save any photo from the
imminent deletion by switching to keep Y in the picture viewer. What? All right, let's go. Come
on. Come on. Let's go. PP prestige points are awarded for actions such as escorting survivors
to safety or defeating zombies, right? When the PP gauge becomes full, Frank levels up,
right? Attack power increases. Speed is running speed. Life is maximum. Health stock is item stock.
Throw is item throw distance. And new skill mastered is a new skill learner as it does it
automatically, I assume. All right, come on. Both of you, let's go. What are you doing? Come here.
Hurry up. I'm on the clock right now. Please, hurry up. What are they doing? What? Why won't
they follow me? What's going on? Talk to them? I can't. Oh, I just fucking backhanded. Why can't
I talk to them? Okay, we're good. Hurry up. No, I let's go. All right, we're good. We're good.
I didn't even hit the punch button. All right, to safety. It's up here. Follow me this way. Come
on up. Can she make it? Come on, Natalie. Hurry up. All right, go in there. No, no, no, no, no, go.
Just call me a bitch. No, get in here. Did they go in? Okay, good. I'm never going to the mall
again as long as I live. I've had about enough of this. Escort complete. Freddy Dread just gave
5,000 bits. All right, on time to go back out. Level up. No, no, no, no, no, no. Save the game.
Anything else in here? Through here? No message from Freddy Dread, just a shitload of money. Thank
you, Freddy Dread. Seriously. Okay, I'm good. Yes, overwrite. Mid to late game, hand to hand is nuts.
All right, hold on. Give me another apple. Okay, I have two coffee creamers, an apple, and a golf
club. All right, let's go. All right, I saved the first two people. Go down the elevator.
I guess I'm going to go down. I learned jump kick. Nice. Somebody calling me? Hey, it's Otis,
back in the security room. Can you hear me, Frank? Let me give you a rundown of the mall's layout
so you know what you're doing. Right, on the other side of the warehouse, you'll find Paradise Plaza.
There's lots of shops. There are restaurants, sporting goods, books. It's a pretty big mall,
so you probably need to use the can now and then. Just check the... What was it, left? What was it?
Which button was it? I don't know. People are talking too fast. Stop. Frank, are you there?
It's me, Otis the janitor. He just called me. Why did you have to hang up and call again? Hey.
It's probably just a sprain. Oh. You've got to help Brad, or he's done for. All right,
she's a zombie. Give me your gun. I'm the reason you just got hurt. Let me help. No, I can't let a
civilian do that. That's against regulations. Yeah, well, I don't think they had zombie-infested
malls in mind when they wrote those regulations, kid. You know how to use this? No idea. Absolutely
not a clue at all. I've covered wars, you know. See, at this point when I hold it backwards and
aim with the handle forward and go, just use this thing, I don't know, and then you like
wink at the camera, and then you go, you scoff and you walk away. All right, case one. September
19th from 12 p.m. Case one, two. Okay. The case panels form a guide to solving the mystery behind
the incident. When you encounter a key event, a new case panel opens, taking you one step closer
to the truth. New development. The case. You've been handed a gun. You can take a look at the
current status of the case panels via the case file option on the pause menu, okay?
When all the case panels have been filled in, the truth behind the incident will be revealed.
All right, so it's open right now. So this is like the story. Back up for Brad. Don't cut me off
like that. It's rude. Anyway, here's what I was going to say. There's some young guy wandering
around in Paradise Plaza. He's carrying a camera like you. I guess he must be a photographer too,
taking pictures at a time like this. You're both crazy. Scoop queue. The scoop queue provides a list
of current requests along with relevant information on survivors. If you're able to fulfill the
objective laid out in the scoop queue before time runs out, you can receive PP or learn more about
the incident. So if you look at your watch, backup for Brad has more than six hours. If it's yellow,
it means it's less than six hours. And if it's red, it means it's less than three hours.
And then if it's gray, there's no time limit at all. Okay, so by setting a guide arrow,
you'll be able to more easily navigate your way to a given goal. Guide arrows can be set via the
watch screen or the map screen. Access via the pause menu. Okay, so when you open your watch,
it'll tell you where to go. Interesting. Backup for Brad. So here we go. Backup for Brad is
currently selected. I can select. Cut from the same cloth. I got time to do Brad. All right,
cut from the same cloth is currently on. I can get rid of the coffee creamer. And all right,
here we go. I'm ready. Let's go. Backup for Brad. No, not backup for Brad. Cut from the same cloth.
All right, gotta go this way. We have six, less than six hours.
Holy fuck. I just ended that person. Okay. Is it up top? All right, I gotta go up. Is there an
escalator stairs? That's fun. Going to the toy store? Oh, not yet. I only have six hours.
I have six hours to do this. I gotta find the photographer.
Got it. All right, this person's a gun. Hey you, you're in my way. Can't you see I'm hard at work?
I'm trying to take some pictures here. You've got a nice camera there yourself, but you know the
first thing about photography? Uh, yeah. Sorry about that. You know, I happen to be a pro too.
Maybe not as good as you, but you think you're professional, huh? All right, got you.
Do you really appreciate the way to the word professional carries? If you don't have the
talent, you can't just use that word like you own it. All right, so what do I do? Have to give him
like a good photo? Name's Frank Wesser. I got in way of your shot. I'll just get out of your hair
now. Okay, okay. Hang on a sec, buddy. Why don't I do you a favor? I'll have a look at your technique
and give you some pointers. Okay, don't be shy now, Frankie. Here, I'll even model for you.
Show me what you can do and I'll be the judge. What a great idea, huh? Sometimes I think I'm
a genius. Let's get started. Well, let's go. I'm on the clock right now. What? When taking photos,
note that the larger of the target marker, the more PP you will gain from that photo. Also,
if you manage to take a photo while attacking while being damaged or in some of the non-standard
status, the target marker will change to red, indicating an increase in potential PP. Okay,
right. The color of the target marker indicates the genre of the photo. The
genre that nets the most PP will take precedence over other genres that could be included in said
photo. Sexually stimulating images, horrifying images, humorous images, emotionally stirring
and violent images. All right. So, okay, first I want you to take a picture of me while I show
off my photography skills. What are you doing? Do it. That was fucking quick.
You did it. Nice job. I took a damn good one. Next, I'll treat you my signature cool pose.
You get 200, 700 PPs. Okay, what do you say we change the look out? He's going to die. Wait,
was I? You kind of not give me, you give me like, what are you doing? You're going to get killed.
He's going to die. Holy shit. That dodge. Get a good one of me. Perfect. No, he's doing like a
fuck. He didn't get it. Hey, I'm not posing over here for no reason. You got to take it.
What is he doing? That was not cool. That was really uncool. Okay. No, do you pose? There it is.
That's not drama. Am I in the frame? Hey, I'm not posing over here. No, you got to take it right.
Let me take a photo of you, please. All right. That's not his pose. All right. For the love of
God, stop. Do the thing you want to do. What do you, what do you mean it's no good? I'm not
posing over here. No, you got to take it. You got to time it right. I need to get 700. This
vision is wonky. I'm wasting so much fucking time. Stop. Come here. All right. Do your thing.
No, you're trying to avoid the photo. He's not going to hurt me. That's not 700p. Okay. I have
to leave. That's not working. He's just going to keep doing this. I have no, no, stop taking a
photo of me and help me. Help me. Take a picture, man. Don't you even know how I'm going to die.
What was that? So, okay. What am I doing? What am I doing wrong?
It doesn't make any sense. So people, everyone told me this was a wonky mission, but I don't
understand. I need zombies in the photo. Okay. I can't, I'm trying this one more time and I'm
fucking just going to leave. What the fuck is going on? I just leveled up. I took like 30
fucking pictures. Why won't this complete? Okay. So is this mission impossible? Dude, my camera's
out of battery. I did it. Okay. I took, I took, I took a photo of you fucking a hundred times.
Well, it's in focus and I'm out of battery. Uh huh. That ain't half bad. Okay. Here comes the next
one, Frankie. But first feast your eyes on my work. Now this is my most emotionally moving shot.
Now this is my sexiest shot. Uh huh. Uh huh. I have to go to the camera store. Fuck.
This is my most violent shot. Check it out. I've had a battery battery. Okay. Okay. Here's the deal,
Frankie. You got to go out there and take even better pictures than the ones I just showed you.
You think you can handle that? Huh? Yeah. Okay. Did it. So I have no battery in my camera.
So where's the camera? Where's the battery store? Is it back here? Somebody said the battery store
was down this way. There's a camera shop. There's a bat, a battery store. It's the first floor. All
right. That's kids clothing store. Right. Okay. I know. And this is like the funny thing to do.
Okay. Uh, let me look at the map. Where's the battery store? Okay. Hold on.
Child's play, kids clothes, jewels, warehouse, shoes, cams, cameras. All right. It's literally
the next store down to the left. Two stores done. This doesn't do anything. Just get rid of it.
All right. Here it is down here. Jewelry store, cams, cameras. All right. What do I need? Batteries,
film. Do I need it? What? How do I get it? Camera store, camera batteries. Were they right at the
front? No. Oh, to stop. Somebody's barricaded a women's clothing shop. All right. That's fine.
It's two people are hiding. All right. I'm trying to pick up batteries. Leave me alone. Oh God.
Damn it, man. Okay. I got scooped. Okay. Please. Oh my fucking God. No, that's not a gun. How do I
aim the gun? Battery power is depleted. Please charge the batteries. What the fuck? Where are
the batteries? Batteries. I just was over here. I didn't have an indicator when I went over there
last time. All right. Let's go to any of my watch. All right. Barricade pair. Hey, let's go that way.
What are you doing? I hear noise. I need something else besides an apple. I need like a weapon.
All right. What's in here? Let me go this way. Okay. There's a support store. What about here?
Anything in here? Like suits? Return clothes. What do I mean by return? Did I just put on a
pair of socks? Okay. This is I need something to use as a weapon. Okay. A hanger. That works
this way. Toy store. Wait, people are going to scream at me if I don't go in here.
All right. What's in the toy store? A novelty mask. Oh, okay. No, I want to change clothes.
All right. Okay. So I'm gonna put the I'm gonna have this on. I mean, this is this is funny,
right? You know, I'm doing like the funny thing. Hoomerang. Good. All right. Toy laser sword.
Um, all right. Replace the coat hanger. I'm ready. This is awesome. It makes a cool noise too.
Actually, it works pretty well. All right. What's over here? Barricade pair.
The outside? Where the hell are they? 67 hours. All right. Barricade pair A.
Oh, wait. Just take a real thing. Use an actual rip. I want. No, it's fine. All right. Backup for
Brad is still on there. I need to can I go faster than this? Run faster. I know I can run faster
than this. I need to upgrade. I need to upgrade my speed. So this is another section of the mall.
Okay. I get it. I need to get more PP. Okay. I got you. Just hold my hand.
Don't get surrounded. Don't get surrounded. That's stupid. Come on. Wait. I see a lawnmower.
That's way more important right now. I can get extra PP. I think I'm gonna. Okay. Lawnmower time.
How do I drive a lawnmower? Do you have to eat a fucking apple?
Fuck. Okay. I need. Oh, this is bad. This is really bad. Really bad. Who just threw somebody?
Somebody throw that? How do I drive it? Ah. Shit. Not good. All right. It's over. It's over. It's
over. Otis. I found somebody in a jewelry shop. Okay. Yeah. It's on. They're in the cutscenes. I
know. I look like a fucking moron. By the way, how many drugs are you on?
Ah. Shit load, man. Way too many.
Stay out of trouble. Are you up to it? I feel like I got picked up at a rave.
But yeah, I'll give it a shot. All right. Next time he reloads, I'll lay down a suppressing fire.
Coachella. I'm counting on you. Make your way over there. Okay. One. Let's go. Two. Three.
Do I have a sneak? Otis. Don't cut me off, Mike. Yeah, it's rude. Nope. That's not gonna work.
Otis, leave me the fuck alone. Don't cut me off. Anyways, I was saying. I don't know. Whatever
you're saying. And then somebody in the jewelry store. I know. I found a woman in the jewelry
shop. Not a good time. Okay. She's moving around an awful lot. All right. Great. Oh, oh, oh. Which
window? Which window? Where's he going? Which window? Same one. Don't use that many bullets.
I don't want to use them all. He's got half health. Oh, shit. Shit. Hide. How do I, how do I duck?
Oh, fuck. God damn it. How did none of those hit? What the fuck? Wait. Frank this. That's a grenade.
Where'd he go? I'm gonna climb up. No, no, no, no, no. Bad idea. All right. He's almost dead.
Is he shooting himself? He's shooting himself with a gun. He's gonna kill himself with a grenade.
What the fuck? Oh, shit. It was a decoy. How many, how many grenades do you have?
I'm gonna go this way. Wrap around. He's gonna come over here. Run this way. Come on. Over here.
Bait him out. What is this guy doing? He's burning his hands on the gun. I shot first. Bullshit.
I, excuse me. I don't understand. Um, I'm in trouble now. I was literally shooting him with
the gun. Now what the fuck do I do? I'm gonna try, okay, I'm gonna throw the grenade back up
to him. It's risky, but I'm gonna try it. Is that possible? Throw anything up there?
Can I throw the cash register up there? Shit. Okay, I think I can do it. Oh, shit. Wait. Corn.
All right, I'm gonna throw the bottle of Tabasco sauce at him. Right in the skull.
Where is he? Where is he? Is he still hiding? Can I get up there? What if I could sneak around
behind him? Wait a minute. I'm going up there. Come on. I can't do it. Let me get up here.
There's no way for me to climb up this. There has to be, right? Can't reach this. Oh, what about all
the way around? Yeah, I can get on these boxes, but can I go from here? Can I pick up the boxes?
I guess I can. Well, I can't go this way. Where the fuck is he? Where did he go? He's gonna unload
a clip on me. Imagine how embarrassing this would be having a guy sneak up behind you.
He's not, where is he? Where'd he go? Did he come jump down? He's behind me
in the restaurant over here. Is he the pair of pants? Is the bare pants? I can't, you can't hit
the bare pants. Wait, this is fucked up. No, I need a better picture than this. Okay. Just
leave and come back. Well, I'm going to try to throw a table at the pair of pants. Not the barrel
right here. All right. I'm going to, I'll just Donkey Kong this guy. How did they, I thought
I was going to roll it. Just because I say something's going to happen doesn't mean it's
going to happen. Okay. Kill him. Murder these fucking pants. Oh Jesus. I can't do anything
about this. That's not the boss. What are you talking about? So is he another pair of pants?
Okay. I'm going to leave and come out. Can I even leave? Okay. I'm going to leave and then go back
in. Go look for the angry pants. Okay. Now. All right. Barricade. There he is.
All right. What? I don't even have a weapon. I got to get a chair up there.
He just killed himself with a grenade. They've evolved. Wait, why am I still holding a chair?
What? This motherfucker is still up here. Okay. I've got a chair up there. Chair is up there. I'm
going to kill him with the fucking chair. I'm sneaking up behind him. I'm going to bash his
fucking brains in. Where is he? He's gone again. What? If this is a pair of pants down here,
I'm going to be so mad. Uh, what, what am I supposed to do? What's wrong with my game? I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know what's going on. I, this is the first time I've ever
played this. So I leave and come back again. I hear something over here. I've wasted so much time.
Is he back? Okay. I need to just go up there and punch the fucking shit out of him. Don't,
don't disappear. Okay. I got to keep my eyes on him. Okay. He's still talking. Good. Good, good,
good, good, good, good, good. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. He's still up there. He's still up there.
He's still up there. He's still up there. He's shooting. Good. Excellent. Okay. Great.
Get this up. Chair up top. God damn it. Did he blow the chair up? I'm just punching him in the face.
Fuck it. This is ridiculous. Oh, this is so much fucking time wasted. Yeah. He just reloaded too.
Why did he have to turn into pants? Brad? Where's Brad? Brad? Brad? Brad? Brad? Where's Brad?
Brad? Food? No, no, no. Go. Food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food, food.
Brad? Wait, Brad's the pair of pants. Brad's the pants. Brad's the pants. I gotta hide. I gotta
get the fucking food in here right now. Quick. Am I eating flour? No, eat the corn. Quick.
What am I doing? No. Okay. I'm just taking like fucking five frying pan. I have to end this.
I ran out of bullets. This sucks. How am I going to do this? Can I get ammo from Brad?
Okay. I'm going to spend the next 72 hours here. I can get ammo from Brad, but he sees a pair of
pants. He can't even talk. Where is he? Brad? I can't even track him down. Where'd he go?
He's a fucking pair of pants. Okay. Come here. Out of ammo. Take this. God. Holy shit.
Give me a break. That only took like two to four full hours.
Okay. Who was that anyway? Well, thanks for your help. The name's Brad. I'm Frank West,
photojournalist. And right now I'd rather have an explanation than your thanks, Brad.
You have a gross dad bod. Sorry. I've got nothing to tell you. Look, I do have something to tell you
what Jesse told you. But as far as I'm concerned, we're through working together. So you cover your
zombie story and leave the rest to us. You guys are looking for someone here, aren't you? Who is
that? Where did you take it? You help me, I help you. The rat man. Phylactery lich, $50, 5,000 bits
from Phylactery. Thanks a lot. Huge money. Damn. Thank you again, Phylactery. You're one hell of
a journalist, aren't you, Frank? They say all the times I've played this, I've never seen Brad turn
into a pair of pants. By the way, get used to being on time crunch because you probably won't
be able to do everything. Nothing better to do than to invade people's privacy. Well, I'm already
like four hours behind already. I try. You got a point. But thank you for the 5,000 bits though,
seriously. You win, Frank. Let's work together. Jesse and I are DHS agents. And yes, we are looking
for the man in that picture. You're with Homeland Security. Is that guy a terrorist or something?
I took that picture in the entrance plaza. Right near the front door.
The entrance plaza. You're sure? Hey, I gotta save the picture. Do I have permission to cover this
story or not? Okay. Case one. All right. Case one three. Engaged. Psychopath defeated. Barricade
pair A is still live. New skill mastered. You mastered the zombie ride skill. Should I follow
Brad? Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Picture viewer. Keeping this one. Any
others that I want to keep? Okay. Just look at this. Look at how many times I did this.
Wrong. Let's go. I want to, you know what? Fuck it. I want, I want to see. Wrong. Wrong. Wrong.
Wrong, apparently. Wrong. No, they weren't. They were correct. This is the, where's the right one?
Okay. This is the correct one. This is the wrong one. No, this is the correct one. This one's
incorrect. I don't, I don't get it. Now let's go Brad. That's a great, I like how it stops.
All right. I'm going to barricade pair A. I still can do that. Nice shot. All right. This
people, is Brad just coming with me now? Why are you standing still? You're going to get
surrounded, man. Don't die. Brad. Okay. They're in here. They're right there. They're right there.
Hey, let me in. Let me in. What? Let me in. Let me in. Let me in. Somebody help me.
Nice. Dammit. Just what I need. Another crazy person harassing me. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's because of the mask. I have a mask on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's because of the mask. Hold on. All right. Stay away from me. I am fucking crazy. You know
what? I am crazy. Okay. I need to, don't move. Don't fucking move. Oh, he's still alive. Oh,
knock it off you punk. I'm not here for a fight. Just listen to me. You win. Do whatever you want.
Talk to me. Kill me. Whatever. What about Aaron? Listen to me. I came here to help you guys. I can
take you someplace safe. Shit. Why the hell didn't you just say it first? Get me the hell out of here
already. Come on, Bert. I want to go too. All right. Let's get some weapons here. Okay. Hold on.
Here. You take this and you take this. Okay. Now give me that and I think we're ready. Let's go.
Wait. I want to break the mirror. All right. We got to go back to the security. Okay. How do I?
Um, shit. How do I get back? How do I get back to the security room? Okay. So here is where we are.
We got to go. Where the hell is it? Is there a way I can get there faster?
Lexan. Just follow Brad. Follow Brad. Wait. Follow Brad. That's an odd, an odd old man, right?
Okay. Let's go. All right. Don't die here, guys. Come on up. Come on up. What are you doing?
What did I just do? What are you doing? Come on out and help. You have frying pans.
Where's Aaron? Okay. Come on. Where's Brad? Shit. You guys good? Oh, they're not good.
Well, what the fuck are you guys doing over there? Who's that? Here's me crying. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. Oh, you okay? What's the matter? You all right? Aaron's fucked. Hey. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What's
going on? Get off me. Grace. Grace. Grace. Grace. Get off of me. Oh, fuck. I didn't mean. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to. All right. We gotta go. You got set. This is bad. We gotta go now. We have
to go now. Ow. Get up. Just follow us. Aaron's gonna die. Get up. Aaron. Aaron. Aaron. No. Oh.
What the? What? What? Aaron's dead. All right. If you don't. What? You want to stick around
them with little ones that ate your girl. Okay. It's not happening anymore. We gotta move.
Like seriously, we gotta go right now. Go. All right. Get up. Hurry. All right. Clear away. Clear path.
Give me this. What am I doing? What? I have to carry this person?
Barry, please. You're blocking the way. He's alive. He's alive. He'll be okay.
He's fine. He's good. I'm gonna give him some. I'm gonna give him the food. Where's the food?
Oh, it is. Hey, there's a space rider machine in Wonderland. It looks fun. Don't die.
Fuck everybody. I'm out. Have you ever ridden a roller coaster? I'm gonna die. I can't. I can't.
You're dead. I don't care. I can't help you. Hang up the phone. Get over here. Get up. Up, up,
up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. Otis, I don't care about anything you're saying right now.
All right. Where's Brad? Brad. It's fucking over, man. There's too many of them. Hey, pick me up a
large iced coffee on the way back, could you? Okay. Let's go. Are you gonna? Now what? Are you
gonna open the door? Why? I lost two people. I know. Unfortunate. I need to get down for a
second. Space rider machine in Wonderland Plaza looks like it's out of control. That's weird.
All right. I'm gonna bring it back. So where is the security room? It's somewhere over here,
isn't it? Oh my God. What the fuck do you want? I didn't even cut you off. You hung up first. You
hung up on me. You got Alzheimer's or something, man. Okay. Thanks for calling again. All right. I
need to bring you back. Where's the security room? All right. Look, I need the security room. Where
is it? Does it have like a different? This is the food court here. This is the warehouse. Okay. So
I need to go just down the hall and to the right. So down here and a little bit to the right. No,
my God. Why are we doing this? Sir, if you could just kindly come with us, we can wrap this whole
thing up. No, I'm leaving until you can guarantee me safe passage. Just open this gate. Just open
this gate for your protection. I am not opening any gate. He's trying to see through the bottom of
the mask. Dr. Barnaby. Sir. Dr. Barnaby. Well, what happened? You can't just arrest him.
He turned down my offer to protect him, said he isn't going anywhere until I can guarantee
a secure route out of here. Jesse has a direct line to HQ. That's like the first thing we need
to do in anime. If they, if I was in a costume in anime and somebody said something, it would
zoom into the inside of the costume and I'd be like, oh my God, I'd have a bunch of reactions in
here. Somebody gave a 10,000 bits like 10 minutes ago. Oh, that was Gibbler. Thank you for the
$100. 10,000 bits 10 minutes ago. Hey, Jeremy, I'm so glad to see you playing my favorite game,
The Thing again. Wait, I was mistaken. Sorry about that. Hope to see you play The Thing again soon.
That's thanks for the thing money. Appreciate it. Thank you, Gibbler, though. That thanks for the
there's been huge money drops today already. So thank you all of you. All right, case one,
we're almost done with case one. Frank, right now you're in the entrance plaza.
Looks like you got the shutter open. If you want to change it to some fresh duds, just
hang up on you. What? What did he say? Fresh changes from fresh duds. Can I go up? What did
he what is it? Was there like a out of control? A temporary agreement was almost done. You're
almost finished with the first part. Yeah. But so what did he say? Where can I go? I need to like
get back to the safe zone. Go to Paradise Plaza. Because I know I got to go this way and into the
right. Because I need to go to the warehouse. Yeah, I got to go to the warehouse. So is it
this way? Wait, no, it's not. Where the fuck am I going? Is it this way and into the right? Or is
it up the stairs? Everyone scream if I'm going the wrong way. Alright, everyone's screaming.
Alright, so no, okay, let's turn around completely. And then it's to the right.
Okay, so it's up that way. Everyone got timed out because he's going the wrong way.
So then this way. Can I even get in here? Does this even open? This shit don't even open. I have
to go up the stairs in that way. Okay. To go all the way back around. Oh shit. Okay. That's annoying.
Go to the arrow. Well, I'm not. I'm not trying to go to the arrow. I'm trying to go to the
safe zone. Is that gonna is that taking me to the safe zone? No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, so where's the from here? Where is it? So now I gotta go. Do I have to do this? Current
mission is back to the safe zone. So yes, he follows the arrow. Oh, but fuck it's right here.
So I follow the arrow. I keep getting fucking phone calls. Just go. Okay, I'm just gonna call
the arrow. The door is welded. It's a dead end. Alright, alright, alright, alright. So I have to
go back down. I'm getting confused here. Downstairs and then that way. That's the way I was going.
I'm not gonna throw her off the ledge. What the fuck? Why so dark? Oh, it's because it's
nighttime. Holy shit. I have like no time left. All right, grandpa. If you but dial me one more
time, I swear to God. It's like, if I were to go and get my computer infected with a bunch of
viruses to make sure that I got scam phone calls. And I mean, I mean, go to every website and give
my phone number to every single website. That is like a scam site. I wouldn't get called this much.
All right, almost there. Okay, I remember this. I have to go all the way. Wait, wasn't I back here
already? I'm going the long way. Wait, what is happening? Okay, they're in a, this is good.
Where are they even going from here? Really? Oh, all right, I have to stop this.
Do I still have my gun? It's scripted. I can't save him. Are they in the car?
Where's the car? All right, this is actually concerning. I don't have any heals or anything.
Sophie, I'm okay. I'm just gonna make my way over here. Sophie, come here. Just follow me.
I'll get to help somebody. Help me. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Over here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's go. Come on, come on, come on. Hurry. Let's go.
What was that? What the fuck? Oh, shit. Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Just get in the door. Get in the door. Get in the door. Get in the door. Sophie.
Oh, fuck. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's aiming at me. Three. Okay. What was the last time I saved? Save status and quit? I haven't.
Oh, no fucking way. Save status and quit, right? Don't quit. Just load. Welcome to the main feature
of the game. Will load game? Just always load. Always load. This game is not easy. That's all
right. If you restart, you keep your level. Oh, my God. This is like, I feel like I'm going to pick
the wrong door here. Do not load. Load the game. Do not save it. Save the game. You idiot. Load it.
I'm just gonna load game. What? No. Oh, quit without saving. Shit. Save status and quit.
Oh, my God. This is, this is the most I've ever seen chat. Completely saying three different
things. Day one. 1357 level three. Whatever. It's done. Holy shit. This is like literally the
beginning of the game. Oh, my God. Okay. So, speed run time. Holy shit.
Save the game every 15 minutes. Okay. Hey, welcome everybody. Hope you're having a good day.
Let's go. Is there a way I can turn the telephone off? I've already seen this. All
right. We're speed running this. Holy shit. I did not realize that it was this big of a deal.
There's no autosave or anything. There's no restart from like check. No, it's just,
it's just maybe this game's like 12 years old. All right. Again. All right. All right. Let's go.
Let's go. Oh, my God. This is awful. This is really bad. I did. Okay. I didn't realize how awful this
was. This is, this is like a catastrophe, but it's not, I'm fine. Everything's gonna be fine.
It wasn't that bad. I know exactly where I'm going. Back up for Brad. What? I can't get in here?
No, I know there wasn't an autosave, but I didn't realize that like it, it wasn't,
it was kind of, oh, I don't know. I thought I could like potentially start at like where,
I have no idea. This game's hardcore. So we're going to treat it that way. How did you even
grab me? That's right. What? I don't understand. Where'd you even come from? What? All right. Back
up for Brad. Let's go. Photo guy. Photo quest. All right. I'll get, where was that? Up top?
I don't remember. I'm so disjointed right now. I'm like right now, I am so miserably sad,
but I'm bottling it up. I'm just, I just drank it. I just gulped it down. It's going to come out
as diarrhea in like fucking four hours, but we're good. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. We're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Hey, what's going on, man? No, that's the wrong
one. Yeah. I can, I can take photos. I'm going to get it immediately. First try. Yeah. I'll do it.
Oh my God. I'm saving the game. Literally. I want everyone to scream in this chat.
Like I want it to only say, save the game every 20 minutes. All right, let's go. Okay.
Photo time. Model for you. Yep. I'll be able to get through this very quickly.
Okay. Here we go. Take a photo. Look at all these cool things. Awesome. Huh? Show me your skills.
Got it. Nice, huh? That's no good, man. Got you. Okay. Cool. Food. Give me some pies.
What? Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Cool pose. Cool pose. Here it is. No, I fucking didn't,
I didn't mean to press X. All right. Here we go. One, two, three, take it. And I did it wrong.
It's gotta be right when he pumps his fist. Don't run away. No, I'm not reliving the same
thing that just happened. Please God. I don't want to do the whole thing again. I just want,
it's right when his fist goes down. We just did this like this whole stream.
Do it. What are you doing? I'm just reliving the same day. Take it.
That's not, it's a different, that was a different pose. Oh, you've got to be
fucking kidding me. This is fucking Groundhog Day. Give me a break. Okay. Please do it.
Got it.
Get the kick. Yeah. It's like, it's a half, it's like a tenth of a second.
It's 3000 points. Okay. Good. See you later. Okay. Bye. Damn it, man. I, I already did this.
Why did I not? I'm gonna make a post-it note that says like, oh, no, no.
And I have to do this stupid ass mission again. What is, what the fuck? Why, man?
And that was perfect. He's covering his face. Cool. Good.
Thanks. Save the game now. Where's our safe point? I want to say point now, right now.
There's not even one around me. There's a bathroom. Where's the bathroom? No bathroom here. Oh, what?
Why is that not the default? Oh God. It's not, it's first floor. Okay. First floor.
Go down. Bathroom. First floor. Let's go. All right. Brad, you're gonna have to just wait a
minute. I'm gonna do this correct. All right. Bathroom. Where's the, where's the bathroom?
Not that way. Not that way. Where is it? It's behind me. It's just behind me. And what, up the
stairs? It's all the way down. What do you mean blind? I couldn't see through here. What are you
talking about? All right. We're good. Give me this. Good. Change clothes. Who cares? All right. Here
we go, Brad. I'm ready. All right. So I gotta remember it's a cross from Bachman's Bookporium.
Oh, all right. That's the comedy thing. Didn't know that. All right. Let's go, Brad.
God damn it. I'm so sad. I'm so sad. My words can't describe my sadness.
I missed the katana. It's all right. I need to, I need to get to the point where I just was.
Any bosses yet? I think there's been two, but we've rewound an hour and 40 minutes. I blame,
I blame, what was her name? Lucy? I had two guys that had like weapons and then they both died
because we were rescuing Lucy from the jewelry store. And then I got run over by a car. Did I
beat the thing? Oh yeah. I'm going to be under leveled, under leveled. Wait, this is my opportunity.
This is a new timeline so I can try the, I always said flamethrower. New timeline. All right. How
do you work it? You have to hold X. Okay. Good. Okay. Good. I'll make it up for the lost PP that
I had. Where's the knife? I need that knife. All right. Let's go. All right. Get off. And
another one with the knife. Where's the knife? Right there. Just don't waste bullets. Just grab
the knife. All right. I'm up. It's only 67 hours left. Okay. I have some extra PP. Get through. Oh,
you fucker. Come on. No, don't. Food core. Here we go. All right. I'm ready.
Not going to screw this up. I'm just going to win. Don't just fire, fire, fire, fire, fire. I have
two guns. You can't even hurt it. You can't even hit him. He's unhittable until he stands up.
Where's he at? Fast. Just do it and I'll be almost there. Ammo. Where'd he go? He's over here, right?
Rad ammo. Holy shit. Wait, that's fun. Hold on. That's fun. That's fun. I want to do that.
You know, this is actually going to be a good thing because I'll beat him quickly.
Okay. I didn't hit him with any. Is he healing? What the fuck was that? Oh, almost dead. Almost
dead. It's okay. It's all right. Don't worry. I would say. All right. All right. All right.
Don't be fucking greedy and cocky here. Heal just in case. It's this. It's this. It's this. It's
the success ringing of the telephone. It's like, I just leave me alone. Why would I answer this
phone call right now? Ammo please. Okay. Thanks for the tip. Right. I know. But scoops. Cool.
Great. Can I have ammo? Thank you. Somebody just like tap. Okay. Somebody just muted by stream and
then unmuted it. This game is freaking me out. Okay. Go. Where's the safe point? Right here.
There are sanity effects in the game. That's not true. Okay. Safe point. Right here. Out.
Bang of right. This is a place called flexing. You got it. Yeah. Flexing. Where is it? Okay. It's
out. It's going to go this way straight and this is right. Flexing. There it is. How do I save it?
I have almost officially caught up with myself. Whoa. Okay. I have weapons. I'm going to try to
save everybody now. I think I'm just going to leave Lucy. Watch it. Watch it. Okay. Where are
they at? Do I even have that data? I do. They're right here. Okay. All right guys. Come on out.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Get. They're in a different store. They're in this store
right here. They have food in here too. I need these two. Okay. This guy freaks out. I remember.
Oh fuck. Okay. Let's go. Give me your food. Everyone's all good. Knock it off.
Talk to me or kill me. Okay. All right. Aaron. Let's go. Good. Join the party. Bert Thompson
has joined. I'm taking all the food. Okay. You take this. All right. Now you take. Yeah.
You take dumbbell. Okay. Give me the bat. No. You idiot. Why don't you eat those? Here. Take the.
Come here. You have to get out of the way. Those are my rice crispy treats.
All right, fellas. You ready? No. Give me that. You got it. No. You give me this.
I. Well, it doesn't matter. Let's go. Three Stooges episode. Bert. Aaron. Anytime now. Did you block
you? They've rebarricaded the door. You idiots. Idiocy. At its finest here. My fucking god. I just
ate the. Get out of the store, please. All right. Come on. Good. Keep going. We're gonna get. Nice
job, Aaron. Poor Bert. I don't even know who it was. Guys. What about Leah? I don't care.
No, that's. Is it food in here? It's a restaurant. There has to be food in here. Cooking oil.
Nope. Here we go. Orange juice. Drink the cooking oil. I'm not going to drink it.
Let's go. Good. We both made it. Here we are. Both here. Everyone here. Found somebody in the
jewelry shop. Oh, did you? Oh, just missed it. So she's looking for somebody. Just missed it.
What she called earlier. Let's go. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I know. I know. I know. You got separated from the kid. I know it's bad.
Aaron. That's my baby. I know. Okay. Yep. Yes.
We'll help you. Come on. Aaron. They ate her. Okay. Yes. Oh, God. I know. Goodness.
Good. Thank you. Stick around for a little bit. I don't have any more weapons.
Okay. Sure. Come on. I'm not gonna let you die here. All right. And three, two, one. Action.
How do I get out of here? You... Guys, how do you...
Just trapped in here. He's just facepalming. Get away from the counter. Come on. Stop. I trapped
him. I'm gonna scream. Does she not know how to climb? How do I get her out of here? Let's go.
You guys are the ones that have the weapons. Fellas. Oh, my God. What are we doing here?
Are they seriously stuck there? They are. Brad, I'm... I traded.
Fuck. No. Go... You go over there and stay over there?
I can get there in time. Where the hell are they? Where are they? Where are they?
He's just falling. Let's go this way. Me? To me. To me. This is un-fucking-believable. I'm gonna
throw a sofa in there. I have to throw a chair or something at him. I'm gonna get trapped in here.
Can I pick him up? Yes, I saw this already. Go that way. How do I just punch? That's why. Come
this way. This AI. Holy shit. You guys are brainless. Finally, Brad. Bert, you got up.
I wonder... All right. Good. Nice work, everybody. Now move.
Don't care. Go. Come on. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. Come on.
I got orange juice when you're done. Give me that weapon. Trade me.
Heal with the orange juice. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Out. Out, out, out, out, out, out, out.
Leia's being attacked. I swear to God, if I die here, I am going to fucking throw them. Throw them.
What's wrong with me? He's got his hands on his fucking hips. This is un-fucking-believable.
Who cares? This is on. They won't listen to me. They got stuck behind the kiosk in the jewelry
store, and they wouldn't come out. Oh, no. The original timeline is happening now.
They would have had full health. I don't care. Fucking idiots couldn't figure out how to walk
over a jewelry counter. Should have just left you. You're supposed to drink the orange juice, Bart.
Okay. Where's the bathroom? Save point is behind me. I think we just have to get through this.
Reload? What, for somebody else to get stuck in a store and then two people die or one person dies?
Sir, if you could just kindly come with this whole thing. I'm not doing another reset.
Until you can guarantee me. There we go. Here we are. Done. Temporary agreement. Let's talk.
I'm at entrance plaza. Yes, I am. We're safe for now.
Take what you need from the clothing store. You got it. All right. Here, Bert. Give me that.
Drink that. Give me this cooking oil. Okay, whatever. I don't know why my brain is like
this. I thought that said one of seven killed in the corner. Okay, I am going to go and get
some fresh clothing. What is that? We have to go. We have to walk all the way around.
Save the game. But I don't even know what the save point is. I have to just go there.
Just follow Brad. He doesn't know. If only there was a map. Yeah, but the save points are like,
here, look. Okay. So if I go up, I guess I could, I have to go this way. So no, I am going this way.
I can save. I'm saving the game. I can't even go this way. I'm going to piss my pants. Speaking
of pissing. No, I, I, everyone was like, you got it. You have to just do the thing. You have
to go the right to go this way. Go to the running guy icon on the map. What the fuck does that do?
There's a safe point right here. Otto. Otto's in here with me. I don't have that. Why are
you guys giving me bogus info? Okay. Where's the safe point? It's right here. All right.
It's just flexing. Make it to flexing. Let's go. Move it. Did you just trip?
No, you know what, Aaron? You come over here. Give me that bat. You're useless with that thing.
My God, you are so useless. Just go ahead and stand there.
Bat. These guys are so bad. Give me your bat. Give me the bat. You take the cooking oil.
Take your, take the cooking oil. I don't care what you do with it. Just fuck off.
All right. Where's flexing? Almost level six. All right. Flexing. Time to save the game.
Guys, are they dead? No, they're standing around in circles, bumping into stuff. Look at,
look at their icons. Just in case. All right. Where you guys at?
What are you guys doing? What is he holding? There's only so much I can do.
You guys are just walking into stuff. Like, do these guys just die? Like, why are they,
why is this so difficult? Oh, fuck the both of you. What is going on right now?
Frank, I need help over here. Frank. Frank. Oh, I'm just walking into walls. Frank. Frank.
Frank, help me. Fuck you, Bert. A waste of time.
Damn it, man. It doesn't even make any fucking sense. Well, I, now I have no one. Before I had
Leah. What is it? Frank, you're on the food court. Yeah. Okay. Try mixing different food in the
blenders. What are you talking about? Mix the food in the blenders? I mean, this is still,
where's the blender? Actually, a lot of wine here. Microwave? Oh, I can't even cook food? This is
strange. Okay. I don't see a blender on the other side. I can't believe everybody's dead.
Corn. Zucchini. Okay. Any blenders? Another store, maybe? I'll check another store.
Taco shop right here. I mean, a coffee shop would have a blender, wouldn't it?
Oh, is it a blender? Okay. Um, examine. Juice power. Insert two food items into a mixer and
you can create your own original juice concoction. Different color juices possess different properties
and effects. So, um, I need to get different juice. What just came up? Juice. Quick step. What?
Hold on. I'm cooking oil and wine. Pick it up. All right. So is this just temporary? This is just
temporary thing, right? That's cool. I'll figure out some stuff to do later. Mixed drinks will
fully heal you. Okay. That's cool. That's super useful. Um, I'll have to figure that out later
when I have more health. Put corn in there. Oh, wait. What's this? Yogurt. Okay. Yogurt.
Yogurt and ice pops. What'd I get? A quick step. Cool. Entire box. All right. I have, I need,
okay. What do I have for? All right. I'm good. Get off the counter. All right. I gotta go.
Yeah, this is Frank. Space rider machine and wonderland pizza. Looks like it's out of control.
Maybe there's somebody out there. Go there. I'm just going to let it talk.
It's, I know it's a, I know. Let them talk about the phone.
Uh, using the dumbbell as a phone. Use the quick step. All right. I'll save Sophie. Maybe not.
Should I do the quick step? What does it do? I'm gonna see what it does. Holy shit. That's
unbelievable. Oh my God. This is the best thing ever. Sophie, come here. Let's go. Come here.
Can you run as fast as me? Take one. What? Oh, do I go faster? I can't just take holder and just
drag and run. No, go this way. They're in the, they're in the thing where they're driving to.
Can they shoot that far? All right. Ladies and gentlemen, we have made it to the portion where
I've had to rewind to now. All right. We're good. This way. People dance. This is kind of a people
dance, isn't it? Just open the door. All right. Let's go. Come here. All right. Where's the save?
Save point is to the left and down the hall. Do I even have any weapons? Pretty good dodges.
I don't have any fucking items. Oh, yes, I do. Come here. Um, just go to the whatever. I need
to close. Anything in the urinals? Come here. I don't even need to hold your hand. Why am I
doing that? Okay. We're good. Fucking itchy eyeball. Nice push. I have no weapons at all.
Bad. Give me that back. Let's go. All right. Now I got to go to the save, the safe zone,
which is hold her hand. She's hilarious. She'll be fine. All right. Safe zone is down this way.
Okay. I think that's just where we're going. Let's go. Nice hit. Wash my hands. There's no time for
that. I'm sorry, guys. But in a scenario like this, you're going to wash your hands.
You're not going to go to the bathroom to pee. You're just going to go over there and just piss
all over the wall as fast as you possibly can. You're still going to use the bathroom. Good.
All right. This way. All right. There's the exit. Let's go. Damn. Not washing hands is exactly how
a zombie apocalypse starts. But if it's already happening, then there's no it's already over.
Oh shit. Got it. You killed them. Whoa. What a plot is developing right in front of us.
There's a zombie playing host to a queen parasite in every large gathering of zombies.
Defeat that zombie and get your hands on the queen to use it as an item. Queen infected zombie.
Capture the queen. So they're the ones with the red eyes. Found a couple of survivors in the
bookstore in Wonderland Plaza. What was that thing? They looked Japanese. Probably tourists.
Okay. All right. Let's go. Follow me. I brought somebody. I got a survivor. Oh, queen. Get out
of the way. This guy just puked in my mouth. Hold on. I want to get a good one of that. Turn
around and do a big shove and action. Turn around and shove the zombie. Go for it. She just pushed
me. Every time I put the camera down. Give me the queen. Let's go. I'm taking this. All right. I have
somebody to deliver. Oops. Do I get money if it's a fake person? What if it's just a mannequin?
And then I can save the game. There we are. Let's go. Sophie Richards. I can't believe those maniacs
killed him. I never got a chance to tell how I feel. Very good. Escort complete. Level seven
reached. 24,000 pp. Extra life cube. Nice. All right. This is the next part of the game.
So that's what Dr. Barnaby said, huh? The old coot's not dumb. He wants us to call for help first.
We got to line out or what? The signal's being blocked. I can't even contact HQ on the emergency
line. Still in the same costume. I was right. We want to get our hands on Dr. Barnaby. We're
gonna have to secure a way out of here ourselves. All right. We've got to deal with the situation
we've been handed. The boneheads back at HQ might be working on something, too.
There's a thing to save every single person, right? Can you imagine how annoying that would be?
At noon, it's my ride. Is your ride reliable? Absolutely. That's how I plan on getting out
of here. All right, then. I'll see to it that the DHS picks up the charter fee. Can we take Dr.
Barnaby as well? Sure. As long as you tell me what's going on. Okay. I'll tell you what you want to know.
Later. We have more pressing business right now. All right. If we have to wait here for three days,
we'll need supplies. Water, blankets, and the like. We'll get Dr. Barnaby here tomorrow morning.
I want you to keep an eye on the monitors. How much money would it take me to save everybody?
It just wouldn't happen. All right. That's the first case completed. The next case will occur
at 6 a.m. Oh, man. What time is it? Okay, so I got some time. All right. I need to save the game,
then I have to pee. Oh, it's out the other way. Why is my eye so itchy? I want like a new pair of eyes.
Let's go pee on the wall quick. All right, we're good. Image in the monitor. Oh, right. All right.
I'll be right back. I'm just gonna pee. I'll be a minute, two minutes. See you in a second. All right. Okay.
Crisis averted. Where I was. Okay. All right. So I have some time. Should I go for it? Should I try?
No, you can't even do it. What about like food and shit? Don't they leave stuff lying around?
Didn't wash hands? I didn't have time to do that. There's Jeff and Natalie. See, I'm saving people.
I'm not doing terrible. I think I'm good. Yeah, there's nothing else. And this is where just they,
all the survivors go. I get it. I have a queen. I have the drink and I need something
that Apple's probably better. It's good. It looks good. Time to go. Wait, image on the monitor,
but the zombies going berserk like this. I don't, the press is going to go in. You know what I'm
saying? Sorry to get involved in all this, Frank. You might want to consider spending the night here.
Image in the monitor. Kind of running out of time on this one. Image in the monitor. Where the hell
are you trying to get me to go? Image in the monitor. Can't do it. Okay. Photo to out of
control. All right, Japanese tourists. Let's go. I have time. Otis, stop calling me. Okay, let's go
back down. No, no, that's kind of, how can you guys still use the elevator? Kill, kill, kill them,
kill them. I'm trying. How did they all get down here? I saw somebody in the North Plaza. He was
leaving the supermarket. Yep. He was in a real panic. Something must be happening. Don't hang
up on me. Oh, just, I'm just Otis. Can you and I, can I just keep the line open? Just keep your
phone turned on. I'll keep my phone turned on. You can just talk to me. Anyways, here's what I was
saying. Go ahead. Say what you need to say. North Plaza, leaving the supermarket, right? He's in a
panic. I know. Something's after him. Good. Cool. Is this the shoes? I need, like, I need a new
costume. I can't just have a pair of, like, sneakers. Dermot, you're Otis's only friend.
Well, whatever. I can't be. I got stuff going on. I got stuff to do. I can't just take every one of
your phone calls. Eat that. Eat that, bro. Okay, give me the knife. Just tried to stab me. Almost
got it too. What's in here? Pant and barrels. New shirts. New anything. I need anything else besides
this t-shirt. No, here we go. Sure. All right. What are we at? Let's see what we got going on here.
Uh, there, what's this question mark? What, what's that mean? Question mark. Does that mean the
person's here? Why is there a question mark over here? Book. Engineering. The act of holding a book
is enough to activate its properties. Different books have different effects.
PP gain from photography or defeating zombies is increased, and learn skateboarding or cycling
tricks or valuable skills that can make the escorting of survivors easier. Some books have
an effect on other items in your possession. Items affected by these books are marked with
a book icon. Restored power of food consumption is boosted with a heal plus. Multiple books can
be held in tandem to further increase the bonus. Items covered in a book's contents
experience an appreciable increase to the durability. Okay, so what? Engineering.
Engineering? What's the plus? Press X on the book. Hold on. Item plus. Hold on to tools and
construction related items. Three, three times as long. Okay, so tools and construction items.
What is that? What counts as a construction item? Wood. Is a knife, knife, a tool. Oh, great. These
guys again. Quick step. Not a bad idea. It's actually kind of to the beat of the song.
Holy shit. They came out of nowhere. No. Oh my god. Bad. Bad. Bad. Oh.
Fuck. Oh, that hurts. That hurts. No, come on. This is bullshit. This is actual bullshit.
Get it. Thank god. All right, get rid of the uh, get rid of the bat. I want more health.
This is a tool, right? Okay, where are these tourists? This way. They'll be marked with a
purple book icon. Oh, that's cool. Hitbox. Okay, we're looking for the tour. Frank, you're in
Wonderland Plaza. The most popular attraction is the space rider roller coaster. The I can't move.
I can't move. I can't move. I can't move. All right, who made the roller coaster tycoon ride
where you can't get off of it? Is somebody on it? That's really fast. All right, where are the
tourists? Well, I need to get something from here. Run like the wind. Shoe store. Just a hat.
What about new sneakers? Yeah, sure. I need a lot of shoe stores. I gotta get this shirt off.
I've had the same shirt on the whole game. This is a default clothing. Bowling balls. I can't pick
up the bowling balls. All right, sporting goods. Hanger. Worthless. Tennis racket. No. All right.
Here we go. Right. Skateboard. Oh, a skateboard. I can use it. How do I use it? Okay, you just use
the skateboard. This is awesome. That's all I can do. All right. Tourists. Here comes another one.
Hello? Can you get... Hey, hey, easy. Talk? How do we... Can I talk? Oh, wait, what's this book?
What does this one do? Learn to speak rudimentary Japanese. Hey, I can... Listen. Wait. I'm different.
Not one of them. Who are you? Frank, photograph taker, journalist. Are you go safe? What? Oh,
shit. Hold on. How do I just attack without drinking? Can I use the ball? I need something to throw.
I need something. Anything. This... Just apples. What is this? What does this do? Hold on to edged
weapons three times as long. I need the Japanese one. All right. Give me the register. No, not this.
Give me the register. Somebody's... He's gonna die. One zombie is gonna kill this guy. Move.
Move. Think seriously first, friend. What kind of journalist would come here for a story? There's
clearly something wrong with this man. Wait. I know Japanese. She'll hear you. I can... I know
Japanese. Don't worry. His Japanese sucks. He won't understand. We can't very well stay here by
ourselves, can we? Let's just follow him for now but remain suspicious of his tricks. This is all
your fault. Of all the places to vacation, why were you so keen on this dump? What? The other
one who said it would be a good time. Anybody want a drink? Anyone there? So you're gonna follow?
Okay. What's this? What is this book? Skateboarding. Okay. I got a skateboarding book.
You coming? I need the Japanese book, don't I? Where is it? I have it already? No, I don't.
Skateboard. Is it... What's the... Talk more than once? I don't have an option to because I don't
have the Japanese book on me anymore. I can't talk. Where the hell is the Japanese book? There it is.
Okay. Come here. There we go. Come. No. Come. Decide quickly, please.
Fantastic. Pardon our rudeness. Here she'll go. Got it. All right. They both joined. I don't have
any weapons though. I got a new skill. Kick back skill. That's so easy to do that. To just
accidentally drink the fucking thing. Health book. That guy's almost dead. Here, take some snacks.
How many sloths do you guys have? Come here. Drunk skateboarder. All right. You guys are good?
I need to get rid of this. Like, seriously. You know, I know what this does. By the way,
I've been watching somebody play this like 10 years ago and I know what this does. It's like
a grenade. All right. I gotta bring... Let's see. What time is it? 1 30. I have to 6 to do... I can
only do... What do I have here? Image in the monitor. We're gonna go back. I'm gonna take
him back. It's time to save. Save. Yeah. Save the game. Anywhere I can do this. Where's the nearest
save point? I have to go down and then behind. It's downstairs and then around. Oh, let's faster.
This way or that way? Probably this way. Learning Jap. Wait. There's a gun. Wait.
Wait. I probably need to talk to him again. The one thing that's actually kind of hard for me
to get used to is how left trigger is not aim gun. Left trigger is aim camera. Right trigger is aim
gun. What the fuck did I just do? Good. All right. Are you guys still... Seriously?
Coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. Y'all just stare at him. Let's go.
Come on. Give him a gun. Come on. You can make it. I know you can. Weapons. We can't use like shoes
for weapons. How many shoe stores does this mall have? Like half of the stores are shoe stores.
Come here. No? Nothing? Here. You take the gun. You do it. He's got a knife. Give me the knife.
Let's go. Player in a path. Here. You take this knife. Whatever. Just take... You guys. Anybody
take a knife. Let's go. All right. Where's that save point? 200 zombies killed. PP bonus. Nice.
He just shot me in the head. Thanks. Okay. Let's see. Where am I going here? Food court. And then
there's the save point. And then I have to get back over here. So I can't... Okay. Roller coaster.
Roller coaster. I gotta save these two. They'll still be on the ride. Don't worry. Look at my
watch. Out of control. There's still plenty of time. Where the roller coaster is a shortcut.
Well, I'm already almost there. Like I'm going to the save point over here. Crazy. This way,
right? Yes. This way to the right and the save point's right there. Here, right? You'll get
grabbed really easily by these people. Just cover yourself in fucking butter. You'll be fine.
Are they all right? I give you a gun and a knife and you guys can't even handle yourselves?
Let's go. Now, where are we at? To the right. Not this way. This way. I just want to save it.
Come on. Thank you. Shoot me again. I have no health. This is horrible. I need to go. I need
to go to a restaurant or something. The gym is right here. All right. Cool. I'm going to get
this. You know what? Fuck it. I think I know what this does. Let's do it. That is what it does. I
knew it. Now I have to. I'm dead. I'm dead. I gotta go back. I went the wrong way. I'm dead.
Goodbye. Wasted the bees. I don't care. You guys not make it through. You guys are fucking useless.
You gotta let everybody die. Who cares? Is this even the right one? They just stand there and let
the zombies hit them. Look at all this extra work I have to do. I have like a case to solve.
They're not going to get out of this. You know, the amount of times that you've cupped your hand
to say, help me. You could have shot the gun five times. You guys have weapons. Use them.
Let's go. Go, go, go, go. Over here. Are you close enough? Holy sheep shit. I'm dead.
Why? What happened to my watch? Why is nothing selected? I have to clear a path for them to
walk in a straight line. Oh, fuck the both of you. Come on. Here. I want you to have a drink.
I'm certain I would do better in a zombie apocalypse than everybody in this game.
Like one thousand percent. A million percent positive. Who cares? I don't even want you to
have a weapon. Okay, let's go. You definitely wouldn't. You have no geography physics intuition
whatsoever. Are you actually saying that in a video game when I'm walking around a mall
that I don't know how to like drive my car around the city that I live in?
What? Wait, where the fuck are we going right now? What is going on? Oh, it's out this way.
All right. I've got stuff like fucking fighting chat. I'm dead. Yeah, guys, during the zombie
apocalypse, I'm just going to get up and sprint as fast as I can and ram my body into the wall
and knock myself unconscious and die. That's what's going to happen. We'll let that be the
cannon. I'm so sick of babysitting these two. I'm multi-boxing on three accounts right now.
My fucking god. What are you letting him do this for? Jesus Christ. Just run and call them.
That's what I was doing. No, not you. The guy. We're dead. We're fucking dead. Are you serious?
I have to go through the. Oh, we're dead. We're dead. There's no way. Just run. Go. Go. Stop
running into walls. You fucking. Holy shit. There's no way I'm going to make this back.
There's no way. Not a chance at hell. They're both dead. What a waste of time this was.
God, Jesus Christ. You gotta be kidding me. I need a shortcut. How do I log a short.
Oh, my God. How the hell am I going to do this with these two? Do the roller coaster shortcut?
God. So you're saying go back to the. I don't think this is humanly possible to get these guys
across with what I have right now. Go to the gun store and get a gun. So I have to leave these
guys to die because they just stand around and die. Use the V. Everyone got mad at me when I
used it last time. I'm going to use it. Well, he's dead. He's killing me so I can redo this.
Oh, my God. It's such a mess. Help. Help me. Hey, you're still alive over there.
Crossing the gym is Home Depot. All right, I'm going to go to Home Depot.
Come this way. Get in here. Both of you. Go here. Take one of these. I can't get this to you.
It's already broken. All right, that's why this way. This way. This way. This way. This way. This
way. This way. My God, we're fucked. OK, I need to have weapons here. I've got skill up for this.
I dropped it. Everything I have is fucking broken. OK, I need to fill up on shit. What
do we have here? Toolbox, propane, two by four. I really, really need health.
God knows what the hell that is. All right. At least it's not a total shit show right now.
All right, what else do we got? Anywhere else? All right, we need to go.
Let me look at the map. So there's a save point here. Everyone keeps telling me to go to the guy
that's running. Go to the instant message logo. Aim logo. OK, I'll do it.
It's like every time I look over here, everyone's yelling at me to do this.
All right, here. You take this. How many are there anymore? Two by fours.
Yeah, like lead pipe. Good lead pipe. Plenty of weapons here. You don't even knife. Here,
take the lead pipe. It's much better. What else is in here? No, I don't want that. Sledgehammer.
There's a sledgehammer. Brake. Shovel. There's nothing. Oh, here it is. OK. OK, you ready?
Let's go to the instant message logo. Bang a left and then bang a right. I need health to die.
Fuck. God damn it. But the gun keeps shooting me. He shot me like five times.
There are so many motherfuckers down here. There's so many people here. What? Don't even give me this
bullshit trouble. OK, I have to go heal. Oh, boy, I'm in trouble. I don't remember this game being
this difficult. Oh, please. Did they increase the amount of enemies on the screen in like the PC
version? Maybe it's because I was throwing CDs at people. Well, they're just dead. There is no
physical way I can save those people. Impossible. No way I could do that right there. Holy shit.
Oh, I'm dead. So what have we learned? We've learned that this was a mistake to come this way,
and I'm going to go the other way and go to the roller coaster. That's my only option at the
moment. I don't even care if these guys die. I'm going to go get a weapon. Good luck. Good luck,
you two. I think I'm wasting too much time trying to take care of every single person I come across
when no fucking way. They just die. Who cares? Good luck. I wish you the best.
I kind of want the gun back though. Give me the gun. Here, you can have this.
No, where's the gun? Give me the gun. Give me the gun. I'm going to get healed. Holy shit.
I'm not going to shoot this guy. I'm going to. I could have healed the other guy too. Is he dead?
Well, the other guy was just standing and letting the zombies fucking punch him in the face.
That's been what the survivors do this whole game. This please hurt me.
Take him more. Let's go. You can do it. Wait. Good. Did he not make it? You gotta be fucking
kidding me. I don't care. I'm not going to need that book anymore. Okay, here we go. Hey,
I'm at the roller coaster. What's here? Rover? This is a shortcut on the roller coaster. I just
want to make sure we understand. That's what everyone told me to do. I'm never listening to
the chat ever again. Do I have to fight this guy? I don't. Jesus.
I have to kill this guy. Whoa. I'm going to get. Okay, run him over. Run him over with the car.
Run him over with the car. Got him. Already figured it out. I already know what to do. I win.
What? I did it. Technically. Oh, shit. I'm all the way back here. Not good. Not good.
This is not good. Oh, boy. This is going to be fun.
With me, with me, with me. Both, both, both, both, both, both, both, both, both, both, both, both,
both, both. Fuck the hardware store. Don't read the book. Nice shot. All right. I can keep you
guys both around. Will they help me during this? Okay. Both of you. Come on. We got some drinking
to do. Heals. Come here. Take this. Give me the gun. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't worry.
I'll take care of it. You idiot. Here. Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink. You can do it.
Here you are. All you have to do is walk up the stairs. It's really easy. Just walk up the stairs.
You guys are just bait. Just drink the wine. Okay. Give me the knife. I need,
um, I need to bring a hit. No, you die in one hit anyways from the clown. Here we go. Let's go.
Nothing in the way. All right. Stay with me. This time. Don't get lost. Go on. Good. Go on. Good.
Okay. Here we go. I need to get prepared for this though. Is there anything else down here?
There's probably something I can take. Like a bigger, better,
gotta be like a better weapon down here. This is, this died my hair. Okay. I'm looking for
something strong. It's a prop. It's not, is that two? No, it's not tuber here.
Just cause you said that I have to change it back. Something else. All right. So how am I
going to kill this guy? Save the game. Is there a safe spot down here? There is. Okay. Down all the
way down here. We're going to save it. Trade that knife out. So good. Let's get the game saved.
Good. Finally, you guys have a shred of intelligence. This can't open the maintenance
key to open these. Fuck. Okay. Let's keep going and save the game. I'm in a much better position
with this health though. Just take it slow. No reason to go fast. You're going to die in two hits.
Yeah, I know. At least I'm going to die in two hits and not one.
What? Oh, good. Swimming through this guy. So now the game is saved. Is it worth it? Should I?
Okay. I'm going up there. You can be the one that shoots. I'm just going to trail them around. Okay.
Here we go. Throw some jewels at them. I think that's a great idea. Good. All right. Handgun.
Handgun. Handgun. Handgun. Okay. Cool. All right. All right. All right. Here we go. Wait.
Everybody take a handgun. Take one. We're going to do this together. Look, if we light him up,
he can't do anything. If we fire three guns at him at the same time, he's dead. Don't aim at me.
Okay. You ready? Three guns. I don't care if you miss. You're at least a distraction.
So where am I? I just have to run back here. I'm going to light them up. Good. This way.
I want you guys right here. In here with me. So you can make sure. Here we go. Let's do it.
Here we go. Shoot him. He's blocking. He's blocking everything. Wait. Is he coming?
Shoot him. You can't shoot him. What's that? Oh, whoa. Whoa. What is that? What's that? What is
that? Oh, I stunned him. What happened? Did you shoot the balloon? Follow me. Follow me. Follow
me. Follow me. Follow me. Shoot the balloon. Oh, no. Shinji. Shoot the balloon. Shinji,
don't you have a gun? Shinji, shoot something. Oh, sorry. Light him up. Give me your gun.
Oh, balloon. Follow, follow. Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Balloon. Shoot him. Run. This way. No. Get out of the way. Kill him. Quick.
Somebody hit him. He was going in with the dumbbell for the last hit. I freaked out. At
least I got him. That was horrible. Hardest boss in the game. Psychopath defeated. Guys,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't run away. Small chainsaw. You obtained the ID card. Okay.
Excellent work. You two were worth saving and let's go home. Get on the ride. No, who's this?
He just looks over and goes. Greg, any other survivors around? Yes, there are. The three of
us. I'm sure everyone's in the security room. It's safe there. We got to go. Security room? I know
a shortcut there. Where is it then? Greg, I'd love for you to show us. Small, how many small
chainsaws can I have? This way. Come on. Which way? I was ahead of you. Holy shit, this weapon is
incredible. Wait, I couldn't do a PP there. This is so much better. Imagine playing the game with
anything but this. Wait, there's some sass there. Hold on. Come on. Will this instantly kill Greg?
I'm so scared to accidentally kill somebody. I will instantly kill somebody if I hit them.
Don't walk into me, please. This way. I got four of you. Shinji, let's go. This thing's gonna break.
It's gonna break. Do we have another one? Yeah, but should I save it? You guys good? Shinji. Uh-oh.
Shinji. Shinji. Let's go. They respawned. Oh, fuck. All right. Get. Come on, you guys. Made it.
Everybody? Do I have everybody? Just head through here and we're already at Paradise Plaza. Nice
shortcut, huh? What do you mean head through here? Oh, oh shit. Okay. Bathroom. Okay. Let's
go. How we doing? Image in the monitor. We're almost there, right? Now we down here. Bang it
left. Let's go. You guys aren't all stuck in the hallway, are you? One at a time. Okay, it's fine.
I got him with the end. No, somebody's caught. Who is it? Shinji again. Shinji. You're killing me,
Shinji. You're killing me with this bullshit. It's always you. It's always you. Always. Be better.
Okay, now is it up or is it to the... I think it's straight ahead, right? Yeah, it's just this way.
Stop running away from your problems. Okay. Just follow the arrow. Yeah, I know, but sometimes it
can be upstairs. Oh my... Stop standing still. Get over here. You idiots. Oh, you're gonna get me
killed. Let's go. Oh shit. Somebody get that. Go get it. I'm not doing this. I'm dead. They need to...
They have to do... They have to take care of it. You guys are useless. Absolutely useless. Don't
shoot me with the gun. In fact, give me the gun. Here, you take the knife. You take the dumbbell.
Give me the gun. All right, I feel much safer now. Go in there. Come on. God, I just... I would move,
but I just don't have any health. Come on. No. We good? I need all of you. What happened to Greg?
Oh, he's not as... Okay. Somebody... Somebody get this guy. Get in there. Get in there. Get in
there. Get in there. Get in there. Get in there. Get in there. Get in there. Get in there. Get in
there. Get in there. Just press the button. Oh my god. That was horrible. Get up here. Nice jump. I
got three survivors. I feel good about this. I did it. I'm honored that you helped me. Please accept
my humble gratitude. Got them both. Escort complete. 90,000 pp. Hell yeah. Save. That's what I'm going
for right now. Let's do it. Save game. That was... My whole body just hurt when that elevator opened.
No more puny inventory. Oh, thank god. Okay. Start next mission. Image in the monitor.
The zombies berserk like they tell the professor going anywhere until morning.
Not this one. Might need to spend the night here. Yeah. No, no. Okay. What? Did I just do that
with like 30 seconds remaining?
Holy shit. Okay.
Brad, it's just a screen. That's not really here.
Case two. Yeah. Let's save it. All right. Rescue the professor. Okay. I gotta do this now.
Look at this inventory. I feel so great. Oh my goodness. Look at that. It's so much better.
All right. I gotta do this now. We gotta go. I can't even get rid of the book.
I don't need this, right? Yeah. I can't even throw a book over a fucking fence.
Okay. So let's do this. Rescue the professor. Shadow of the north of the plaza.
Yeah. I bet that shit would happen to me when I first came in here.
It's too late for that. Yeah, there's no one doing that. Oh, there's Otis calling.
Sorry, Otis. I'm running around. All right. So I've got photo challenge, wherever that is,
and then now the professor one has to happen now. All right. Fine. Frank, looks like the
shutter leading to the entrance plaza is open now. Maybe the guy dragging the old man around
opened it. Anyway, you can get to the entrance plaza through paradise plaza now. Well, that's
great. Look at that. Uh-oh. Don't be daydreaming out here. Sniper? You're gonna turn into a pair
of pants or you're actually gonna help me this time? Frank, that's not a sniper rifle. Ah, shit.
That's right. Hey, it's the professor. Look out! The professor's gonna end up zombie challenge.
Oh, great. This is gonna be wonderful. I'm going for it. You just worry about staying alive. Got it?
Good. That got chunks on my face. That's disgusting. Action shot. Okay. Stay alive.
I think I can do that. Bag of chips. Uh, okay. I'm just gonna go this way. I'm coming to save you,
Barnaby! Look, I'm blocking his vision. Good strategy. All right, Barnaby. I'm here.
That didn't work. Here! Catch! Actually, I need those. I need those. Can I shoot them?
Sorry. Can I shoot the rope? That was really, really, really bad. Can you get off? Thanks for
the help, dude. Appreciate it. Nice work. Well, I'm dead. Um, it looks like I'm going up. Do I run
faster like this? Imagine turning around as Brad and seeing this. You would have no time to even
react to this. You'd be like, what? What are you doing? No, stop it, man. What's wrong?
Holy shit, Brad. Why is he holding, like, a .50 caliber sniper rifle like this? Oh my god.
That's awful. Brad, just, Brad, just hit some coffee creamer. Brad! So, I need to just go up
there and kill, I guess. I guess. I don't know. You guys both suck. I ran over to the professor,
and I thought I had to, like, cut him loose. I might need it later, I don't care. Don't get
the chainsaws. Oh, lead pipe. Nice. I can't take that call right now. So, where was that shortcut?
The chainsaws respawn. That's kind of insane. So, is this the shortcut that takes me down
to here? Where's the red one? Can I now open these? All right, so I'll go there. Like,
can I do all those now, or do I have to have specific, like, keys to open them? So glad I
have more space. All right, so then now I go straight this way. This game's fun. All right,
go ahead and tell me what you want to tell me. All right, listen. Okay. Give me the gun. Oh,
no gun. Just a night stick. Well, shit. Grab the chainsaw. How am I going to use the chainsaw
against the guy with the sniper rifle? Don't. I think it's just to the right. It is. It's an
early 360 game. Of course it's janky. That's all right, though. The game came out, like,
12, what, 10, 12 years ago? More than that. Like, 14 years ago? Okay. Wonderland. Let's grab the
chainsaw. He's back this way, right? What was that roller coaster? That's the roller coaster, right?
Oh, did you guys just bounce off that guy's head? Are there two up here or just one? Oh, actually,
I'm one of the guys. I wasn't even trying to do that, and he's gonna kill me. A lot of motherfuckers
over here. Ah, for the love of God. I'm gonna have to use the chainsaw to even get out of here.
Bingo. All right, now let's go. I can cut through here, can't I? How much fall damage is there in
the game? A lot? How much is there? Barely any. Okay, now I want some more food.
That's such bullshit. I need food. I'm going through the food court. Ah, no, this thing sucks. I don't
want it. Let's get rid of this. All right, chainsaw and knife, and then I want a bunch of food. Okay.
There's about a two people holed up in one of the shoe stores in Wonderland Plaza. I can't do that
right now. I'm sorry. Must be a couple looks like something's wrong. Oh, that's not a whole lot of
time. Let's get three full heels. In fact, just eat this and get a bunch more. Okay, cool. All right,
I have four full heels, a knife, a gun, and a chainsaw. I'm ready. I got some scoop. Make some
quick step. Not a bad idea. Why do I keep getting the same ad for Nerf Ultra every single ad?
They still make Nerf guns? All right, we're gonna do yogurt and popsicle. We'll make like two of them.
Nerf or nothing? They still been using that same slogan too. Let's do ice pops again and yogurt.
What about milk? Milk and yogurt? That's like... All right, I'm running out of space here. Okay, I need...
Okay, I need... Come on. Come on. Just make it so it's not... Recommended. Nectar.
So sweet and irresistible. Even these can't resist this brew. What is it? Recommended beverage.
Nectar. All right, whatever the hell that means. I got two quick steps. Let's do wine and milk. Oh,
that would be disgusting. What is it? Quick step. Try does it only get quick steps and just use all
my wine. This is a full heel, isn't it? Pink Russian. Quick steps not gonna get you drunk.
Okay, don't accidentally drink these. All I have is a gun. Let's go. So now I take the shortcut back.
Wait, I need to save some of these. So bang, I can go up here, right?
Or should I save it? Save it and then go this way. That's what I'm doing. Yeah, so we've got to save.
We've got a place to go back up. Oh, I pressed it. I did. I was just holding the gun to my head.
I am now ready for the boss. Let's go. Go through the exit door, which is over here.
All right. Check it. Yes, it is. I don't have that. I hear people screaming. Who is screaming
right now? Here's the entrance plaza. What? This is holy shit. That's for real. I thought you guys
were fucking with me. There we go. Okay. One, two, fast and oozy. Hacker. Hacker. I just got like
pre-fired. Fucking shoot me. Just chugging protein shakes. Are you kidding me? I should
have a chainsaw in my hand. Pick up the sniper. He's unconscious, but alive. Damn. Is he all right?
Yeah, I'm not in any condition to carry him. You're gonna have to carry me and him. Just go.
Go to the bike store. I'll get on the pegs. That's not a good way to carry somebody. You
would pull his arms out of his socket. The sedatives take an effect. Carrying him by
both of his shoulders. I managed to stop the bleeding, but he's running a fever. He needs
medicine. A fever. Medicine, huh? Yeah, that's what I said. Case two. Case two, three. Met it. Oh god.
My mom's out of time. Holy shit. That's no time. No time. No time. No time. No time. I have to go
now. I need to save it. I'm gonna be all hopped up on protein drinks. Save it and go.
I would not hold your hand on the trigger and lie down on your chainsaw as a pillow. All right,
run. I have to hurry up. I'm not gonna drink this yet. Not until I get out there. Medicine, run.
You fucker. Get out of my way. How many heals? Drink it. No, it slows me down. No, it doesn't.
Get off the phone. God. Am I out of juice? All right, I think I'm all right. I have to go this way.
Do I really? I hate these guys. Time until helicopter arrives. Where am I going?
Frank, we made it to the north plaza. All right, I'm out. Tell me what you want.
Don't hang up on me. There's a supermarket there along with a gun shop, a cutlery shop, and a home
center. Every time Otis calls, take a shot. I would not suggest doing that. I need another weapon.
Fuck. All right, food store. I can heal, right? Just you're in the supermarket. I know.
You can get to the pharmacy through the door between the butcher counter and the seafood
counter. I couldn't know. Oh, this is fairly healthy. There's somebody inside the home and
garden shop in alfresco plaza. I didn't get to look at him, but I'm pretty sure it was a man.
Okay, he looks scared. Lettuce. Grapefruit. No, I need like apples. I think that heals the most.
I can make this into a smoothie, couldn't I? Okay, is there a save point?
There is outside back here. Okay, I'm gonna do that first because I have no idea what's
going on in here. Lettuce and cooking oil for a smoothie. I mean, what time is it?
2 15. What time is his end? 2 16. What are you talking about? Are you serious? Did I make it?
Okay, a person riding in grocery cart. Somebody pushing. We're gonna have to do like bumper cars.
Scream so loud he disconnected my ex-wife.
Bitch said when she came to vandalize my store, I don't take kindly to vandalism.
All right, so just throw a bunch of shit all over the place. Break everything in the store,
throw everything on the ground, and he'll get stunned. Do I got it right?
He looked like a puppet. Like somebody had the hand up his back.
Oh, he has a gun too. He has a gun too. All right, that doesn't work. It might. Holy shit,
that was. Don't vandalize, right? He hates this. He's in the corner. How do I get him out of the
corner? Shit. Sneak. Sneak. Snack. Is he going this way? All right, jump across and chainsaw.
Ready, three, two, one, go. Did I do good or did I do bad? I can't tell.
This guy's freaking me out.
Don't shoot yourself in the head.
I have to get a different clothes. I have the same shitty outfit on. Is my hair a different color?
One tough cookie. Can you stand? Look, I saw you at the entrance yesterday. You needed medicine too.
Maybe we should work together. I don't need any help. He's got a pretty sick bugleberry jacket
though, I would say. You're the one who caused this nightmare. You ruined Santa Cabeza and started
all this. Oh, a key. Wait, I still have to. I have to hurry up now. Medicine run.
How do I get in? A key? Use the key. Use the key? How do I get in this? How do I get inside? How do I
get in the medicine store? How do I get in there? How do I get in there? Come on. Use the pharmacy
key. First aid kit. I have to bring this back all the way in how much time? What do I need? Where's
it going? I don't know. Should I go up the stairs? Use the cart. Okay, grab the cart and where am I
going? Just follow the cart. Okay, I have no time for this shit. I have to go cart and just run.
You think I can make it? Okay. I didn't mean to do that. I was trying. No, I want to
I need to put this down. I can't leave with the cart. How do I leave with the cart?
What? No, don't go over jumps. You idiot. It's not worth spending the time. Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Go. No, no jump. What? What? Do I have to pick this up? Pick it up. Pick the cart up. Wait,
did I miss this? Did I miss a shortcut? No. I was trying so hard to just get behind it.
It's over. I'm not going to be able to do it. I pick it up. Stand behind it. Pick it up.
Fuck. I'm so angry right now. I'm going to take the car. I'm going to kill him and take the car.
I can't believe it. That's what happens when you have the same button mapped to everything.
They've learned since then. Get the fuck away from me. Okay. Where is it?
Bang A left. No, just go straight. Is there anything else I can go faster with? I had that
stupid shopping cart. I lost this shopping cart and that was a huge problem.
Okay. The next case will occur at 11 a.m. All right. The professor's passed, but that's
why is that so blocked out? Save it. Yep. Not that way. Not that way. Crap. Where am I going?
I'm coming down. You know when you're coming down after being really stressed out playing
something and then your brain sort of starts to try to unwind. All right. So I'm good. Free
roam time. I appreciate that. Thank you. Why don't you guys pose? I understand. Perfect.
No, I'm not. I'm not drugs. I'm talking about just when you don't matter. All right. Now look up.
Give me sad. Okay. What? No, turn back around. All right. I want a really good cinematic shot.
All right. Stop wasting photos. What happened? Free roam. Not enough time. He stabilized.
I had enough time to go to the bathroom. Are you all right? You have blood on you.
Huh? Yeah. Must be from that girl I saved. Girl? Was she hurt? I offered to help her, but
she took off. Must be from that bus full of children that I saved, you know.
Anyway, she was saying something about Santa Cabeza. Santa Cabeza? I think I...
Somebody turning? Dr. Barnaby, you're awake.
Santa Cabeza. I should have known. I thought Santa Cabeza was over and done with.
You plan to dispense justice now? Calm down, Dr. Barnaby. We're only following orders.
We have to protect you. Protect? More like imprison. Professor, if we're going to protect you,
we need to know the truth. I know who this is. All of it. Please. Who is this? Talk to us.
I take it you know what Santa Cabeza is. Am I right? All right. I have to get out of this
WWE 2k20 created character clothing in here. I'll just get my information somewhere else. Thank
you very much. Maybe if I can track down that woman again. All right. Let me see what I got.
Case number three coming up from 11 a.m. The next case will occur at 3 p.m. Oh, so I got
some free roam time. I actually really do. All right. I got some time. Is there anything else
I can do? The hatchet man and the coward. Coward. Say lovers A and B. I'm not gonna get there fast
enough. I'm the coward. Well, I'm not gonna get there fast enough. It's not all about doing the
missions. It's about I need I want to go and get some cool weapons and I want to change my clothes.
I want to press just press it up so I can throw further now. I think that's the last thing I
leveled up with. I sure did. Let's test it. Nice. Okay. Okay. Let's get some clothes. This is a
reading store. It's recharge the battery. I need a new weapon. They don't have anything. Oh wait.
Toy store. Fine. I'll put on like the joke outfit. Okay. Fine. Frisbee. That's actually pretty fun.
Check this out. Ready? Oops. Wrong button. Change clothes. All right. I can be the roblox guy.
What else can I do? Oh super soaker. Nice. Now this I remember this. This is what I remember.
I remember. Hey dude. I gotta go to the bathroom. Like you want to play for a minute?
Yeah sure man. And I did this for about 45 seconds. This is kind of fun game. Yeah. Yeah man.
Ready to go? Yeah. I'm ready to go. I'm not making this. This is not a joke. This is actually
happening with my time in Dead Rising 1. All right. What about over here? Kids clothing. Can I pick
the color shirt? No. I want a different outfit. I don't want just like the kids clothes. I was
already in this. There's no other style. It's only this. I have to be in like the man-child outfit.
Bowling ball. Nice. It's perfect for you. What about this? Oh wait. Hold on.
Oh no. I'm gonna Lefford. I'm gonna Lefford that myself. I think this is even worse.
Yeah. What about this? What's in here? There's two sides. Is it the same thing?
What the fuck just happened? All right. Can I? Is there a horse body that I can use?
Is it like a furry outfit? Is it like a furry suit? All right. Let's do the coward. What we got?
Weekly photo magazine. What does this do? Get a visual cue to indicate prime photo timing. That's
kind of cool. I'll use it for a while. I lost a scoop. Sports. Hold on to sporting goods three
times as long as usual. I'll use it for now. Hey Frankie. Did you get your homework done?
What? What's up? It's you again. I get it. We're all nervous when we're beginners.
Okay. Let me take a look. Show me your best shot. Uh oh. Am I gonna get judged? Get your
best erotica photo ready. I don't have any. This is just somebody sitting down. This one?
Beginner's luck. That's all. What? Did I just complete the mission? Just one more contest Frank.
Be here tomorrow at noon. We'll settle this. It's like an old medieval helmet. At noon tomorrow.
Cool. All right. So uh I have some of these. Okay wait. We're gonna go to the smoothie shop.
Pie. Can I? Is there a blender back here? Can I make a pie smoothie? That'd probably help.
Pamela. Wait. You'll be fine. Pamela. Pamela do you want a pie smoothie? I'm making two.
Wait. She's gonna die. No. Don't read. Fuck. I don't have any weapons.
I'm the worst help you could have asked for Pamela. Fuck. No. You brought the fucking sicko.
I need an actual weapon. Give me the cash register quick. Who the fuck are you? Heather.
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. You're in a weird spot. I mean I'm fashioner headed
but it's working. All right get up. Come on. Up here. You just please move your body up this way.
There's no more cash registers. There's no more cash registers. Oh my god. Nice job. I need that
book. What? Okay. Why can't I not just deselect? Like okay. If I have the book in my hand why can
I just select it? No unarmed. I want to keep the book but I don't want to have it in my hand to
read it. Why is it I cannot have unarmed? Follow me. Up on the d-pad. Take one of these.
Fuck you. I'm trying to help you. Stop that. You can't break...
I'm the worst guide. Okay so if I go this way I can go up right? No I don't need that. It's
right there. It's literally right here. This is very bad. This stuff sucks. I need... Okay I'm
gonna die. I'm not dying for this shit. Track this way. Follow me. Of course you guys are in
the toy store. Give me that book. Where? What are you doing over there? No. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. This way. Okay. All right. All right. Nice work. Now I need to... All right. Jesus.
Straight up the way that I'm facing. Come here. Can I just... Let's open it again.
They'll give me an opportunity to try that again. I guess.
This is the one right? Where's the coward? Okay. All right. So now I'm going to...
I'm not going to be upset by that. I want some heals though. I don't know if there is any.
Is there any healing? What? I need a photo? Of what? Go take a... Wait I didn't take it?
All right. I'm just gonna take the same photo. I don't want to do this. I'm not... I didn't want
to zoom in on... I didn't... I just... Okay. I'm out. I have to be in this every single time.
It's just a nuisance to press the button in the elevator. All right. I'm gonna take some weapons.
So where was... Where's the photo contest? I think I kind of accidentally ran into it.
Second floor cafe. That's the one. Tell me what you want to tell me. Sandwich shop at Paradise
Plaza. I look pretty overweight from what I saw on the monitor. Okay. He's not going there to get
food. He's a restaurant man. We'll do restaurant man after coward. All right. Here we go. Camera
shop. Well I won't have time. Probably not. Upstairs cafe. Is it B? Oh it's a B. Nice. Cafe.
Which is over here. Remember we talked about the pie. Where is he? Was he over here or something? He
like ran into a... Where was this? Remember this is where I got the pie. I think it was another store.
He'll just come to you. Where are you at? Any clothes I can get in? Skateboard. That's good.
I'll take it. Golf club. I'll take it. Come back at 12. It's almost 12 right now. I'm gonna make some
smoothies. All right. So what we got? We have uh cans of drinks and uh pie. What do I get?
It's one pie. The ketchup or something I can dump in there. I ate the other pies. Why did I eat the
other pies? All right. Almost noon. I'm ready. Oh apples. I like apples and mangoes and shit.
All right. This is an apple pie. Different. Untouchable. I hear him. This is different too. What is this?
Nectar. All right. Hey. Where'd he go? I just heard him. Hey you are Frankie. Uh I just hurt my throat.
Beginner's luck. Come back tomorrow at noon. Beginner's luck. That's all. Here we go. And now I
have I have an actual weapon now. I have a skateboard and I have a pipe. Back to the
smoothie bar. And it's time to help her. Okay. I got I'm gonna make a double pie smoothie. Quickly.
Quickly. Quickly. Hurry up. Hurry up. Okay. Good. Let's go. I've got that. I've got a bug. I have a bug.
I'm gonna use it here. Bingo. You're safe. Picture first. Ah it's uh I fucked it up.
Thank you very much. Pamela Tomkins has joined. Okay. Let's follow me this way. And you.
Don't just let the thing attack you. I got both of you. All right. What should I give you guys?
How about um you guys got any boards? New skill. That one. I mean that was like a weird uh they were
doing like okay that was weird. Okay. New master the power push skill. How do I do that?
Here. Both of you take one of these. You can't give it to him? All right. Oh very important.
All right. Let's return. Let's go this way. It is the how do I get out of here? We're looking for
it's just this way into the left. Very easy. Just be able to get out quickly.
Don't have to hold both of their hands. I'm running out of time for the coward man.
What are you doing? Here. Why did you let go? Good. Hold on a minute. I got this.
Where's my weapon? Don't have a weapon? This way. Oh shit. Go. Go. Go. Go. Knife.
Seriously. This is bad. Nice push. Nice push. Nice push. Nice nice nice nice nice nice.
Made it. Stay with me. Stop. Don't cry. Don't cry. Come on.
Like yelling like their mother. Am I going the right way? I passed it. It's behind us.
Where are you going? Almost there. All right. We're safe. I might have to do restaurant man
though. Pamela. I know you can do it. There's no zombies. I'll take care of everything. Just
follow behind me. Let's go. I'm ready. In. Bingo. Pamela. Heather Tompkins. This place sucks. It's
dirty. It's cramped. Isn't there a shower around here? 60,000p. That's a lot of p.
Yeah. Speed up. Good. Speed increased. All right. I need to look at the move list.
Do I have enough time to do a coward? Okay. What about status?
Speed. Okay. Skills. Jump kick. I know that is zombie red. This skill allows you to climb on
unsuspecting zombies. You can even walk along the top of zombie crowds. Press A while pushing
left stick towards nearby standing zombies. I've done that. Kick back. When grabbed by a zombie,
repeatedly push left stick in the direction Frank is facing to deliver a kick to the attacker.
Repeatedly. Does that mean go? What does that mean? Just hold it. Okay. Flying dodge. Push
left stick in the same direction twice in rapid succession to throw yourself in that direction.
So it's a dodge. You are invincible at the beginning of this move, but the end will leave
you open for a moment. Okay. Avoid zombie attacks with this skill. When grabbed by a zombie,
repeatedly push left stick to the right or left to repel the attack and escape danger.
Save the game. Save it. Hurry. What am I holding? This is a really strange thing for me to say,
but that's inside computer shipping foam. That's exactly what that looks like at sleep.
If you buy a computer and you have it shipped to you, or if you make a computer for somebody
and you send it to somebody to protect the components inside, you put this weird foam
shit that you put it in it. Like it grows and it conforms to all the components. It's really
actually kind of an interesting thing. All right. I'm going for the coward. You are fucking demented.
No, people know what I'm talking about. I think I probably could do restaurant man too.
I just realized what character I am. I'm Rorschach from Watchmen. I'm going to keep this on.
Oh, the green mask. Rorschach's log. December 25th.
Stench of blood and foul things plague my nostrils. Hey, that was rough.
A camera. Oh no, he's going to put this on the internet.
Salvation. His blood must flow. He must be burned. Yeah. Why would you be filming that?
Why wouldn't you stop that? Yeah. Let's go. Hey, holy shit. He just charges forward.
And you guys coward. How about this one? Don't have a cow, man. That's not a heart
Simpson. What's wrong with me? Get off of me. Did I just end up in a box? Wait.
It's scripted. Some kind of old fashioned lock device. I need to enter a passcode.
That's your dad. That's it. Nice try. They all keep doing the same move.
I got to get it. I got to get it on camera. I've got to get it on camera. The three of them.
The charge. Come on. There's some Resident Evil shit here.
Resident Evil 4. It's the same dialogue. Holy fuck. He's running fast. I'm not going to put
you back in the box. Are you? How am I going to get through this? Oh, I thought I jumped over.
Give me a knife. Where's the knife? Give me a knife. Oh, I love crunching on their
Doritos is what gets their attention. That's a lot of PT, right?
Oh, fuck. That's so many people.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Not back in the box. That's it. How did none of these guys are dropping
knives? This is bad. I'm running out of time. Good step letter. I thought I died. Oh, fuck. Oh,
what? How do I get out of here? What is this? No, no, no. I need a better picture of that.
Better picture than that. Get fucking stuffed. Carve a box. I just like paper cut that guy's
face in half. You get the passcode. All right. Get rid of this thing. Did I already get it?
I already did it? I got it. Okay. Jennifer, are you all right? Why am I out here?
Oh, where's all my stuff? It's gone. Um, there's a wait a minute. Jill's sandwiches.
I don't know. I'm not gonna do either one of these. I didn't know where I am.
Where's their car? I'm not gonna be able to cover. I have to go back. I'm starving to death here.
What? Ronald? Ronald? Hey, you got some food, right? Split it with me. I'm dying here.
I don't have any food. I have to bring you food. Here, have some ketchup. Sorry, pal. Fresh out.
Trying to bowl guard it all for yourself, huh? You're just gonna eat every last morsel?
Okay. Well, I need to bring food then. There's nothing in this whole restaurant.
Well, okay. I found restaurant, man. What the fuck? Ronald! Now would be a good time.
Oh, this sucks. Um, I have to go back. Craft something? What do you mean craft something?
You craft something? Heat up a pan on the stove. I don't think I have time for this. Another...
I'm almost... This is almost done. Okay, and then it's on the frying pan. And now how do I...
What do I do? This is just a hot pan. I don't have any food. Flour? Uh, you're gonna have to stay there.
I have nothing. I have to go back. This is bad. I gotta go back to another source.
I gotta go back to another source. This is... This is just... My free-roam time is up.
Let me don't leave the map. Let's burn this... I bumped into his face.
All right, I have to go. I don't have food. I'm sorry. I'll go to the guitar shop.
Just take all the guitars. Food? Wait. No. Ronald, uh, you're dead. Goodbye.
I'm dead, too. I'm dead, too. I'm dead. I'm fine. All right, so where do I go from here?
We've got... Uh, I gotta go just down. I could save it. I'm gonna save it. Just because I die.
That was awesome. Now we just go back. Straight this way. And I end up right...
Straight ahead. Another source incoming. Why did I do this to myself? What do you want?
I just fucking breezed through that. That was stupid. What do you mean I'm soft-locked? Why?
Why would I be soft-locked? Oh shit, this is bad. Made it. Just in time. Motorcycle outside.
Okay, case four. There's a motorcycle now available. Girl hunting. Plug it back in.
All right, so I got plenty of time. Is the restaurant... Is he still alive, do you think?
Is the restaurant man still alive? He might be. Ah, he's dead.
I understand. Shit, I missed the... I missed the hands in the air. This is an intense conversation.
Wait, now I gotta get it from the side. Because they're doing the exact same thing. This is a
mirror. All right, wait till the... Wait till the big... The big one. Here it comes. One, two...
I haven't saved any pictures in a while. I'll make sure I save those ones.
Where's pants? There it is. Thank god. All right, I need to heal. Any more things to do?
Above the law. Okay, so let's do above the law. Do I have time to do them both? We'll find out.
Save one Ronald. It's the only mental we have of him. Got a little cocky on that one. Why don't I
heal? Because all I have is like fucking oil and hot sauce. Is there food here? Where is it?
Where is it? Is OJ here?
Where? I don't see any OJ. Does it respawn every time? I've already drank it.
I guess it only spawns once. Pepe hint. OJ. I'm not over here, right?
Okay. How was that? How's that a bronic? Oh, I just... Okay, I took it. That's my bad.
All right, let's do it again. Above the law. I think restaurant man is still alive. I think
Ronald's alive still. Let's see if I can get down there and eat something. I can get to bait him
out and throw the... Just throw shit at him. Now he is soft-locked. That's right. Yeah.
What? I understand. Go the other way. What do you mean other way? This is the only way I can go.
Like this way? Oh, a soccer ball. Oh, what's this? Did he fight the clown yet? Yeah, and I kicked his
ass. I died. Yeah, I died once. Yeah, I died one time. You got it. That's correct. There's some
good shit up here. No wine in there? All right, just tell me. There's a pretty big mall that you
probably need to use. Check the map. Otis, I know. All right, above the law. Let's do it.
Oh, let's get rid of the... Well, let's do something funny with the hot sauce first.
You know, throw it at somebody. Is that right? I missed. Does this explode? No, unless you do
something about it. All right, here we go. I just lost the only health that I picked up. Great. Nice
work, Jeremy. Everybody is cheering you on right now.
Restaurant. Restaurant is still up there. If I die again, I'm gonna fucking scream.
This... No, too many people. Cafe second floor? Is that now? That's today.
Ronald Shiner is dead. Food. Food. Gray hair. Nothing else I can wear?
All right, give me a suit or something. Why couldn't there be a suit store?
And no suit to wear. Yeah, yeah. That's not bad. I don't hate it. You just... I'm turning into the
Grand Theft Auto V cartridge. Nothing in here. Okay, sporting goods, energy drinks or something
I can take. I need healing right now. So badly. It's unbelievable to me.
Out of sight. Glasses? Cool. I'll take them. Let me look at the map. I gotta get used to hitting select.
So, there's a save point back here. Digital ladies space in the closet. Special gifts.
Men's apparel. Books. I need like a grocery store or something. Cosmetics. Boutique. I gotta go back
downstairs. Don't jump. Cheese. Burger cheese. Cheese tits. Cheese tits. I don't want to go that way.
That's dangerous out there. Food first. I've got plenty of time. We're gonna get something to eat.
Children's store. Grandma's kids. This thing's still burning? That's kind of unbelievable.
All right, where do I go? Where do I go for food? I'm not doing another big mission until I get
some food. Sports high. Gramen's space. Fashion. Apparel. Nothing back here. Uh, how about over here?
Hamburger fiefdom. Turn around and then take a left at the end of the junction.
But what did I say? What is it? Beef? Fife?
Yeah, that was very awkward. All right. Hamburger, uh, beef. Dome. Actually, this way?
Am I stupid? No, it is this way. Don't die here. Is it? I gotta get an opening.
Yeah. Hamburger. Fuck the closing in. Hamburger fiefdom. Found it. Please, we have to be food here.
Orange juice. Oh yeah. Perfect. Any other cans of beans or anything? Canned sauce. Can I eat this?
Can you actually cook? Or were you guys lying to me? You can't. I'm almost certain of that.
All right, I got orange juice. Good to go. Let's continue. We've got weapons. We've got health.
Got a pretty good spot here. Ah, all right. Listen to me. There's a woman taking over the
children's clothing shop in the entrance plaza. It looked pretty bleak. No more food. All right,
there is food here. There's milk. There's lots of milk. A woman. That woman who didn't make it.
Holy shit. That was unbelievable. I don't even know what to say. That was fucking insane.
It's a pinball machine. Okay, uh, get rid of the brown sugar. I want the milk.
The guitar sucks. Give me the other two things of milk. Did I already get them? I did. All right,
let's go. There's pies. I'll take both pies. Safe point. There's one right here. Blender. Ooh,
is there now? There is a blender over here. I didn't even see it. Milk and pie. It is a
zombate. Okay, pie and milk again. What does zombate do? Let's take a look. Spitfire.
Flushes harsh functions from your. All right, no more ingredients. There's two pies.
Can do double pie. Am I insane or was that like something that they did like glitch out or what?
It did. Okay, pie. I'm kind of, I need to, I'm running out of time here. Untouchable. Now I'm
good to go. Let's replace the guitar with the knife. I would say. Yeah. Save. Don't do that.
Select. Okay. Uh, banger right all the way down. Okay. All the way down. Save the game. Go this
way. Oh fuck, that's a lot of. Was that a mistake? Huh? Why did I just turn into a ball of like
bostura? These guys give a lot of experience points. It's worth it. Okay, that guy had
no hitbox. Oh, he's, he's exploding himself. I get it. Explode. All right. What's that safe point?
Bathroom. Slip right here. Dumbbell. Take two dumbbells. Save. All right. Out. Here we go.
So above the law is over here. Is it up or just down that way? Uh, is it in a restaurant or is
it just down the hall? It's just, it's in wonderland. Ooh, that if it's in wonderland, I can get a, uh,
a chainsaw. My special red wine shoot. Why is it going again? Sally? Uh, why is the thing moving
again? Help. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Stay right there. Don't move. Try just to kill them. Um,
this thing's supposed to break. No! Shit! Zombate. What does that do? Are they coming after me? Oh,
Nick! It baits the zombies. Well, come on over here, guys. Football tackle. Oh, shit. That was
a lot of people. Yeah. Okay. Come on. Keep going. Okay. Just a little bit further. How do I get them
down? Uh, I don't, I need, I need some more damage than this. They're not going to, I don't think I
can. This is too many. I'll be back. Hang on tight. I don't know what the hell I did that for,
but I think I missed. Wrong way. Fuck. I gotta go. Excuse me. Oh, God. Why? I just got up there,
too. They're okay. They're still hanging on. Watch me. Okay. Chainsaw. Now we have some fun.
Here I come. This is going to be ridiculous. It's already broken. Are you kidding me? Too
much effort from just one person here. I just like almost spit. When they fall, they land. I'm
going to take a picture of this. This is going to break too. Pick up the queen. I didn't get it.
There's so much shit all over the ground. Okay. Got a queen. Don't use it. Yes. Queen. Yes. Queen.
Yes. Queen. No, no queen. No queen. All right. Queen over here. Don't you dare. Queen it. Okay.
Um, fall. I got you. How do I get you down? How do I get you down from here? Jump. Can you walk?
I'm fine. It's nothing. All right. Sally Mills. Um, do you have anything? Do you like have anything?
I can. Thanks. Here. Take one of these. Take it. All right. Are you good? Nice dive, pal. You hurt?
I'm all right. Take me with you. Let's go. All right. Now above the law, I need something else.
This way. There's got to be like a store over here, right? Fashion house. Kelly and Lily.
There's too many people. They're throwing at me now. There's too many people.
I've got four people here. Beat up this cop so I can get the gun. Give me that. I swear to God,
you guys. Just fuck up the fucking stairs. Don't you dare do this to me. I don't care. What?
See just how shameless you are, you dirty little skank. Say hello to my new friend.
Not again. Help me. Officer. Officer. Can I talk to you for a minute? I mean,
uh, look, what did that woman do? Throw the camera.
Shut your pipe. If you interfere, official police business, start with you before I get to her.
Is this a boss? Where's my friends? Where are my friends? Are they in here? Here. Take the gun.
Use it. Use it. Shoot her. Somebody do something. Shoot her. Go and get her. Get her. I'll just do
this. I'll do this. You, you shoot. Oh fuck. He's going to die. Oh God. He's going to kill him. He's
going to kill him. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. What do I do? I need to throw a chair.
No, don't do something. Just keep getting in the way. I don't know. I'm scared.
Good job, Sally. Sally, good work. Stay right there. Sally, don't move.
No matter what you do, do not move at all. Stay right there.
What has he done? I spotted a guy in the cosmetic shop in the entrance closet.
I think he looks a little odd. You should check it out. I don't have any more weapons.
This might compromise Sally. Is he going to compromise Sally? I think. I don't know what to do.
Fuck. Look at all this blood. Gun? No.
I needed more guns. I needed more weapons. I had an interesting opportunity. Okay. I have
to save Nick again. I just thought that was another person and it was me and it freaked me
the fuck out. Okay. Above the law, I need guns. In fact, I've got a better idea. I'm getting
only chainsaws. Oh, I can't do that. Never mind. I'm just going up there with a chainsaw.
I just need a couple of distractions. I'm not going to use the chainsaw until I get there.
I'm ready. Let's go. Get rid of the dumbbell. That was a pretty good throw. It was. Okay. I also
am going to pick up the other chainsaw and I'm not going to use it for down here. I'm going to
kill a few people and then I'm going to get a bug. Understand? Do we understand? Mini chainsaw.
I'll come back. In fact, I could probably use this. Let's put this in place where I know it's
going to be. You know what? Fuck it. Let's go. Go get that chainsaw. Excellent. Don't use it.
Back over here. Here we go. I'm going to just, I'm going to get a queen.
Somebody's going to have a queen in here. Where's the queen? Somebody who's got red eyes.
Which one of you has red eyes? Show yourself, please. I appreciate it. Picture thought about
that. Let's get them both in the picture. What do you say? 5,000 points. Pretty good.
All right. Let me queen. Swing. Swing. What are you doing? You really just let that happen.
No queens yet. If I die right now, I will be so upset about this.
I don't want to use the chainsaw. Didn't the queen drop by this point? Man, this is bad.
I don't need to kill every zombie. No, I just need to kill one queen. Just farm chainsaws.
That's kind of cheating though, isn't it? Who cares? It's a gray area. Is that a queen? I think
I got one. That'll be huge if it is. You know what? I'm just going to use it a little bit.
Just a little bit. That's not a queen. Imagine not cheesing at dead rising.
Okay. Reading chat. Reading chat. Mistake number one was read chat. I just read it again. I just
read it again. What am I doing? Fuck it. Good luck. No, I'll come back. Here we go. Don't kill
her. Don't kill her. Don't kill her. I need a photo. No, that's not good enough. That's so good.
I'm saving that one. Wasn't centered. It's okay. I can't believe a worthless prick like you.
You killed me. What the hell? Oh my god. Okay. You obtained the handcuff key. Yeah. Stun gun?
Okay. So, let's... How do I unlock the keys? I have so... Wait. Stay here. Don't do this yet
because they're going to get attacked. Right? Oh, this is really bad. I need to... They're coming
in. They're coming in. I need... I have a queen, right? No, I don't. I still have some of this.
I didn't leave anybody, right? No, not hold hands. You're injured, but this is going to be really
bad. I'm going to sneeze. Anybody know? Is the chainsaw spawned? Stay there. Stay there.
Chainsaw respawned. I need a confirmation. Nice. Beautiful. All right. Now we're going to save
everybody. We're going to have six people coming. Stay up there. Are they okay? They're fine. They're
just hanging up. I need a queen. No queens. Finally. Took you long enough. All right. Get down.
Get down from there. Okay. I apologize in advance. All right. Let's go. Take me with you. We're going
to have so many people. Any more queens? Queen? Let's go. Talk to me. Talk to me. Talk to me.
Talk to me. Where do you go? All right. Let's go. No, no, no, no. Nick, where are you going?
Nick, are you running up to like the girls up here? All right. Everybody follow me.
We're going to make this real quick. Oh, we went up to the marker. Okay. So this is important.
What's the fastest way to get over here? There's so many people. The shortcut. Right. Okay. And
that shortcut is over here. Right. That's the shortcut. Correct. Downstairs and over here.
Everybody listen to me. This is a shitload of people. One, two, three, four. Sally. I'm going
to give you guys some weapons or something. Even if it's a toy. I don't care. We need to like work
together. It's too many people. Let's go down. What can you guys carry? I don't know. This is
a lot of pressure right now. Which way is it? Up and to the left. Here. Take the gun.
Kelly, take the gun. Nick, take the gun. Nick, here. Take the gun. Let's go. He's so bad.
He's so bad at this. Okay. Keep going. Oh, why is he on top of me? Oh, shit.
Hey.
It's too many people. I'm fucking crumbling. I'm crumbling. Okay. Come on. Hurry up, Nick. Shoot
somebody. Let's go. To the left. Bang a left. That way. There it is. Sally, make it. We get six.
One, two, three, four, five, six. We do. Nice work. You know what, Nick? No. Fuck off, Nick. Give me
that gun. Here. Give me the gun. Janet. Oh, it was Kay. Nice work, Kay. You're way more useful.
That way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Bathroom?
Bathroom. All right. Let's go. Nick. Nick, give me the chainsaw back. How do I take it back?
Somebody hurt somebody. Use the chainsaw. Run. Run. Run. Uh-oh. Something's wrong. Sally,
give me the fucking chainsaw. No. No, Kay. Come on. Go. Let's go. We're so close. Good. Good. Good.
Good. All of you. All of you. All of you. All of you. All of you. Nice shot. Into the bathroom.
One. The only fucking reliable one, Kay. Only reliable person. You motherfucker. Get in.
Get out of the way. Sally's in trouble. No. Turn. Give me this chainsaw.
Get out of the fucking way. Stop pushing people. Oh, my God. I'm gonna run out of time.
All right. Get in the bathroom. Get in the bathroom.
In. Oh. Just press it. They're not gonna all make it. Don't they all have to be in here?
They all have to be in here, don't they? Is that gonna work?
None of them made it in. I just want to make that real clear. All you jokers in here.
Not only one person made it in. He's blocking the way. He's blocking the path. That's the problem.
Nick Evans defected. I'm gonna fucking throw up. Hello. I spotted somebody in the cosmetic shop.
Holy shit. That was awesome. What are we supposed to do?
Did she just shoot herself in the head? What happened?
I just heard like a gunfire and then a flat landing person.
Set the marker in the bathroom. Get in here. Oh, now they all. Now they all comprehend it.
You all get it now? Interesting. I didn't do anything. They all just went one, two, three,
four, five, six. Follow me. Okay. We all good? One, two, three. It's like wow nameplates. One,
two, three, four, five, six. We're good. Save it right here. Give me that fucking weapon.
I can't get it from them. Okay. Now from here, it's as easy as coming out this door,
taking a left, going in the elevator. Set a waypoint. One, two, three, four, five. One,
two, three, four, five. Let's go. Who's not in there? Who's not in there? This is so bad.
I need a weapon. I'm going to teleport. Hold on. Wait, what is that on the ground? I'm going to die
over here now. What happened? Trade. I don't even care. Just take this. I don't even care if you
heal. Can I give this to you? Take this, please. I need to use. I need that weapon. This is a fucking
mess. This is a mess. I just took the zombie bait. Oh, that's bad. Wait, everybody stay back.
Go that way. I'll be back in a minute. I just need a weapon. Books. Books. Books. Books. Books.
All there is is books. Books. Books. Books. Books. Books. Books. Books. T-shirts. Books. Books. T-shirts.
I just need a board. A piece of wood. A cash register. Anything. God damn it. Okay. Now I
got to get out of here. How did the glass not break? Okay. Move out of my way. Okay, everybody.
Which way do we go? This way. Make sure I'm facing the right direction. Straight ahead. Let's go.
Let's go. Wait, you have a gun. Let's go. Don't stop. Don't stop. Don't stop. Don't stop. Don't
stop. We got to move now. Who's in trouble? Just make your way over there. Who's grabbed? Who died?
Kelly. Kelly, you're the smartest one. There. Go. No. Okay. No.
To swap weapons with Nick? I can't. I have to, like, I can't give him the cash register and
all there is is shoes. I'm gonna die. Um, Jesus Christ. What happened? This is fucking terrible.
Okay, everybody stay in the bathroom. Stay in the bathroom. In fact, I still have a heel. Okay,
this is fine. All of you do not fucking move. Stand in the corner. I need to get a bat in the
sports store. Where's the sporting goods store? You already fucked it up. Sporting goods store.
Where are you? Let me see. Toy box. Book store. Let me see the map. Optics. Clothing. Jewels.
Kids store. DVDs. Reading. Cameras. Shoes. Sandwiches. Toon makers. Where is this?
Bookporium. Oh, come on. We're the bats. I'll take a skateboard. Golf clubs. Got it.
Nice. Take just, like, three of them. Who cares? Everyone's gonna have a golf club.
At least four of us have to have golf clubs. And, you know, get rid of the fucking skateboard. Give
me that. No, all of us are gonna have bats. It don't matter. It don't matter. It don't matter.
It doesn't matter. Save it. Where the fuck did I just go? Okay. Hi, guys. How are you? Take a club.
Nick, take a club. Nick, you welcome. Why won't they take the golf club? I don't have time for this.
Oh, let's go. Okay. This way. Left. Down. How we doing? We're not doing that too bad.
We're getting a hairy situation. I have a little bit of chainsaw left.
Everybody good. Keep going. Don't you dare. Move. K, come on. We're so close. Come on.
Come on, K. Almost there. Oh, no. No, no, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Guys, just go,
go, go. Run, run, run. They're slow. They're really slow. Holy shit. The golf club sucks.
How do I leave? One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. Get away from
my backswing. Lily, away from the backswing. No, don't fucking ruin this. Everybody go that way.
Go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Go. Go. Who's dead? I got six turn-ins here.
Jerry. What was his name? Nick. That was not cool. Come on. Come on. Come on. I know. I know. I know.
Everybody, this is important. This is really, really important. I need you all
to just stand literally right there. Okay. Good. One, two, three, four, five, six.
I'm going to get like fucking 500 million points for this. Two, three, four, five, six. Come on.
You can do it. Nick, you take, you take up like the whole thing. Just somebody please go.
You just have to be in this right area. Guys, stop this nonsense. Get up.
Up. Up. Up. Go. Thank you. One, two, three, four, five, six. All of them. Did I level play? I still
have like three times. 240,000 people. Holy shit. That's a lot. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, time. Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, no. Where is this? I don't have to go. I have no time.
I have to save it, but I have no time to save.
All right. Help me out here, guys. Help me out here. Uh, is there a shortcut? Should I take a
shortcut? Well, help me out here. Or do I have to run? Just, I have to just run. Just run. Just run.
Grab a skateboard. Nice. Get off the. Oh, this I screwed up. You come in at the wrong fucking
times. I got, I can't, I gotta go. I gotta go. No, I don't. Movie land. How did I do three golf
clubs? That was so stupid. All right. Oh, you can talk to me now. Old man in the antique shop.
He seems weird. He's calm. No, I'm good. There's more. Spotted a guy at the cosmetic shop at the
entrance plaza. That's fine. I'm not going to go there. There's a sniper over there probably.
All this stuff. I was too busy saving six people. Okay. Give me this. Give me this. Get out of the
way, bitch. It was rude. But circumstance. It's not this way. It's not this way. Turn. Don't blow
that up. I'll get there. Big bits of rude streamer. Uh, thank you. Nits cat for the 5,000 bits.
Appreciate it. Thank you. I can't believe you got all six. Thanks for the laughs. Trying to round
them all up. Loving the stream. Keep it up. Am I going to try to chase this person? I have to beat
her before I run out of time. Oh, this is not good. This is bad. No. All right. Let's go.
Did she just crash? I didn't get a single hit. Well, at least I know I can get over there.
I can go to the gun store. Yeah. I'm going to go to the gun store. That's not a bad idea. All right.
Let's pull it up. Uh, there's probably a better save point I can do besides this. Just go get
the OP chainsaw. Let me see if I can do it without it. That's, I don't want to use that as a crutch.
I have plenty of time to get down here. The gun store is near the bus anyways. Okay.
Okay. Plus there's a shopping cart there so I can get there quickly.
I'm just going to get down there. I'm going to save the game in a bathroom that's over there.
I'm going to use the knife. Not bad. Wrong way. I don't really care about Otis. He's going to
say the same shit that he said in the Times already. Find the person. Yeah, I don't have time
for that. I took too long. Okay. Put some shoes on you freak. No, better traction. All right.
Big deal. I'll get this wall and then when I get in here I got to find a save point
so I can go right from here. There we go. Not bad. And then in here I'm going to do a little bit of
investigating. All right. Let me take a look. So in here we've got home and garden,
movie land. We've got, wait a minute, this is here. Hunting shack. So if I bang a left,
is there no save point? Okay. There is a save point, but I don't, I don't. Okay. So if I go
down here through the plaza and then bang a little right in here, there's a firearm shack.
Okay. You got it. This bullshit. Time for the shit. Okay. Let's go. And there's a save point
right down there too. I can't take a call and I'm driving. That's not safe. All right. Now wait.
It's behind me and in the little corner over here. This way. There it is. All the way down.
Okay. Leave that. Why is this like a cut scene? Who's this?
Okay. But they're dead. It was just a random person. Now they're dead.
This is a boss fight.
I didn't even, I'd missed completely. So there, is this blocking? I don't have any guns.
He's loading. He's loading. He drinks. Drinks. Drinking. Drinking. Drinking. He's drinking.
I'm dead. I'm gonna die. I'm dead. How many times have I been like, I'm dead. I'm dead.
I'm dead. I'm dead. No, that's it. I'm dead. It's bullshit. Oh, it's actual bullshit. Oh well.
Damn it. Go load up on baseball bats. No, I think I could kill her. It's going to take a little bit
of crutch bullshit, but I can do it. I also need to save some for tomorrow too.
Oh, whatever. It's been six hours. Yeah, I don't, I don't, I don't, I want to save it for tomorrow.
This game's long. Yeah, I'm having fun. No, no, let me just do this first.
You're only halfway through. That's what I mean. Because I'm streaming this tomorrow.
So I'd like to have another full stream tomorrow too. All right. This way and then
let me look at this. Once I get over here, I'm not gonna, how do you even get down that far?
It's like another six hours. Yeah, that's perfect. I'll, you know, I'll give this one more attempt
and then we'll call it. If I do it, I do it. And if I don't, I don't. We'll do it again. We'll do it
tomorrow. Because that will be a good six to seven hours then six to seven hours tomorrow.
And that lines up pretty perfectly. Don't run straight into nothing. The golf club's really
awful. Am I going to do death stranding? I don't think so. I don't. And not because I don't think
the game is going to be any good, but because I think it's going to be long and a lot of story,
which is good, but I'm not sure that's something I want to scream. No, why would you do that?
I have plenty of time. I don't have to freak out.
And now I'm going to try to save it over here. I'm sure it's going to be interesting.
Go all the way. Where's the safe point? Do I have to go all the way? Maybe I don't have to.
I'm going to save this in a different slot. Can I bang a right? Where the hell is this?
Right next to me? Easy. Different slot, just in case something horrible happens.
Okay. So regardless, I have a way. I'm going to beat it tomorrow because I'm stuck here.
It's either this or nothing. I have to do it. You were just off camera. Let's see if I can kill him.
There we go. Got that gun too. Any weapons up here? What's that? A nail gun. I fell off.
I don't have any heals either. No, I didn't get it. There's no time for this. Just kill her.
Where are you going? What? Wait, what? Is she coming back? I see a headlight. What the
fuck just happened? She's not going to come down. You've got to be kidding me.
All the way up. Am I safe? I'm safe in here. She's a fucking maniac. Have you ever
rode on a motorcycle before? I'm almost out of time. She just drove away again. I'm going
to try to crash into her. This is fucking outrageous. She turns so fast like on a dime.
What if I stay in the corner? She can't get me here. I lost. Okay. So I got to kill her quick.
I'll give it one more time. One more time. Maybe just hit her in the head with a board.
I don't know. I wonder how do I get, can I get it off of the, there's a sword shop next to her.
I don't even think the shopping cart's not doing anything for me right now.
Wait, is there? What is it? Sean's food, CD crazy, and then Ripper's blade is just straight ahead.
Try the bomb cart. I have to make it explode, don't I? That's a lot, asshole.
You don't have any time to do this. This is precious seconds I'm wasting.
Just for the love of God, this is fucking sacred. Get away from me.
Okay, let's try it. Can I just put it down in front of her? Um, it's gone. Just true.
They don't really give you even one tenth of a second, do they? I just want to see what's even
in the fucking room. What the hell is this encounter? It's because I'm not wearing shoes?
That's not real. What do you mean yes? I have a handicap because I don't have shoes on.
Don't tell me that's real. Is that real? All right, she's not going to come in here.
And if she does, then she's in trouble. Okay, what do we got? I can't even open the goddamn
case. Thanks for opening the case. Why are you even in here? Oh my God, I want to fucking bury you.
Katana. All right, all it takes is one good Katana swing. This is like the sloppiest fight ever.
I feel like I'm playing GTA right now. Jesus. She's stuck. She's moving around like a mouse.
Okay, got it. Got one hit on her. I have an idea. I'm gonna try to bait her into the shop
and have her stuff in the shop and get stuck in there. Let's see if it works.
You. Give me your gun. No gun? Didn't have a gun. Any more police? Here we go. She's in.
She's in. Come on. Get in. She was in. God damn it, she was in. I had her in. This is the most
absurd thing I've ever seen. Let's go. Now you're gonna use your gun. Get in, get in. In, in, in.
Is she in? Fuck. Wasn't the best. I'll take the sword. All right, time to slay the dragon.
Can I like queue it up? That's the play. That's the play. That's the only way this is going to
work. I have to do that like 10 times in a row. Well, she just gets. I don't even know what the
actual strategy here is. What are you actually supposed to do here? What's like the real way
to do this? You have to use a gun. What if I don't have a gun? I need food and guns. Well,
I don't have any time for that. I have to win. Is there any place over here? There's food over here
I could get a bunch of food, but I'm not going to do it in time.
Guns. I need a gun. Police. Come here. You got a gun. Give that to me.
Get the fuck out of here. All right, hold on. Give me the O2 tank. You've got two? No. All right,
I have a gun. You've got two? No. Okay. Where's that O2 tank? There it is. Don't shoot the O2
tank. Give me the tank. It fucking despawns. Oh my god. That's so stupid. You have no time.
I can't even go in the... Is there somebody else in here? What? Okay, so you can't go in there.
I have to shoot her with that gun. I have to shoot at the propane tank. It has to be more
perfect than landing a fucking triple axle in the Olympics. Where's the guy with the gun? Over here.
I've got three guns. I've got to save it right now. Get the fucking stupid NPC shitheads. Get away
from me. Get out of here. Is this three? Oh, I am so angry right now. You have no idea. This is so
stupid. Give me this. God damn it. Don't tell me it's because I don't have any shoes on.
Nice climb, Frank. Where are you? Where? This is fucking unbelievable.
How do you ever... Mouse and keyboard. How do I aim? How do I aim with mouse? What's like zoom in?
What's aim on mouse? It's not right click. W? Q? Get back here. Why would Q be... I'm so upset by that
one. Where did she go? This game makes no sense. What the hell is going on right now? What is going
on? This is fucking ridiculous. This is like I'm dead. Oh my god. Just throw katanas at her.
Strategy number two incoming. It just happens every fucking time. Keep using the gun. I can't
get a good shot. She rips around so much. Even when you shoot her, sometimes you hit her in the
motorcycle. I'm just going in here. Go ahead, spin around. Nice turning. Great programming on the
turning of the bike there. Who did that? It's bad. Give me the knives. Fuck out of here. Let's go.
She's spinning in circles now. No fucking way. It's possible, but can I even do this in time?
I don't know how much time I actually have left.
Okay, okay. No, man. No, no. I have to swing when she gets close. It's my easier set than done.
Just jump kick her. All right. Honest to god. I'm going to break this thing in half. Why does
this Xbox One control suck such asshole? I don't understand. She hasn't even run into me. It's
already over. My god, this thing sucks. You got to be fucking kidding me. What a piece of dog shit.
Why is it disconnected? What? She was waiting for me to be plugged back in. At least I appreciate
that. That's nice of you. I think I might just lose this. Hey, wait a minute. That jump scare is
out the window. Hi, guys. Yeah, we were just waiting for you. When you turn the corner,
we just all bite you at the same time. The thing doesn't even do anything. And the guns,
I feel like they do like a sliver of health. Throwing the katanas was doing more damage.
You had a bigger gun. Look at the time. I might have to go back to one of the other saves. It's
actually fucking broken. I'm going to mail this thing back to fucking Microsoft. This is so fucking
broken. No, she was just, she was just stuck right here.
This is unfucking believable. Just shoot her. Just shoot her. I can't even do enough damage to her.
All right. Is it like a chandelier that I can drop on her fucking head or something? Like,
seriously? This seems so outrageously stupid. Even with a gun. This isn't it, man. I just don't have
enough time. So I just lose. I'm just going to lose. Go get the gun from the fountain. I'd love
to play. All right. All right. All right. All right. I'm done. Game over. I'm done. I have to,
I have to like fix this. I can't play with keyboard and mouse right now. I'm playing for like
seven hours with controller. I have to figure out why this keeps disconnected. We're going to do
it tomorrow. I'm going to figure it out tomorrow. I'm going to go to the fountain. You know, just
kill me. Here she comes. Oh, insult to injury ran over my head. You got to get shoot. All right.
Where was, I'm just curious. So this is, I have two saves here. Where is this one? It's all the way
back. All right. Fountain, Uzi. I don't even know how to use the map. Is it M? Okay. Where's that
fountain? I have no idea even how to control this fucking game with a keyboard. What is going on?
All right. There's the food court. Where's the fountain? Not up here. This game sucks laughing
my ass off. It doesn't though. It actually doesn't. All right. So it's here. Can I get here
and then up here? I'm going to have to just run over this way, grab a skateboard and skateboard
all the way around. Is that going to work? I don't know. Into the food court, grab some food.
Hold on. Do I even have like another plug I can try? I'm so irritated by this. What a cheap piece
of shit. Seriously. Yeah. Like coffee pays like fucking 500 million of these things and then
dump them up at 80 bucks. Give me a break. We'll go ahead and send that to our quality control
department and maybe they'll figure it out. Oops. All right. I'm done. All right. That's it. That's
it. I'm not going to search around. I'm done. We'll come back tomorrow.
This is the real anger time. Real anger hours. No, I'm having fun. It's just what the fuck is
going on here with this controller. Why are you doing this, man? Don't want to rant. All right.
I'll tell you. Let me tell you something about fucking Xbox. No. We'll go tomorrow. We'll go
tomorrow. Let me get like a new controller because here's what's going to happen. I'm telling you.
I am going to get to where I was with the keyboard and mouse and I'm not going to get the control
right and I'm going to like right click when I should have hit Q and it's going to be the make
or break the rest of the stream and I'm going to be very bad and I'm going to go back and I'm going
to talk about Microsoft again. I'm going to go on a huge rant about how I should have had the
controller and if I had a controller it's fucking stupid. We'll start tomorrow. Just rewind to
right click. That's so close. Damn it. Whatever. It's all good. We want a rant. No, it's all good.
It's all good. We're good. I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're going to finish this game
and hopefully by then I will have a controller that doesn't just disconnect for no reason.
No funny zoo game? Um, no, not until this is done and maybe not again. I don't know. We'll see.
We're just playing at zoo. I just played it yesterday. No, no, no, not. I don't know. We'll
find out. We're going to be stuck on the boss for the whole next stream. No, we won't
because I'm going to look up how to beat it by incredibly cheeseball dog shit strategy.
I'm just going to type in motorcycle lady cheeseball strategy and just look it up.
Whatever. Who cares? And we'll see what happens tomorrow. I had a lot of fun with this game,
though, besides the random like three or four times where I was just like,
so it's been fun. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Same time, same place. Did you hear the dog?
I think he's yelled at me. That was Dead Rising part run, guitar part run. Actually,
that was what I was doing the whole time. Let's do the bits. You know, sometimes I just check to
see if this works, but it doesn't. That's all right. That's going to be the YouTube title.
All right. So seven hours ago here we had a dog. Oh, good boy. Thanks to the 500 bits. Are you
going to attempt the seven day survival challenge after you beat the game? Uh, I don't even know
what that is. We'll have to see, uh, after what happens tomorrow. Thank you. The 500 bits judging
by how well I am able to manage, uh, most of the survivors. I don't think that's going to happen.
What is that? If you die once, you just, it's over. It's like hardcore mode. That would be so
horrible. Seven days is like hard mode. Yeah. Don't you have an appointment tomorrow? No,
I had it wrong. It's the next day. So we're streaming tomorrow. Sticks renegade. Thanks
for the 250. If memory serves me right, the best weapon is the mannequin torso. I remembered it.
One shot most zombies in this good durability. That's a good tip. I'll take it. It's seven real
days. A long time. It's a very long time. Uh, I'll try it out. I'll try it tomorrow.
Rock Esper. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jeremy, you never talk about this sort of stuff.
The character, Jesse, the blonde girl. Do you find her attractive? Just say yes or no. I paid money
for this. I don't even know. I don't even remember what the hell that was. I have no idea. Is it a
character in this game? There's a lot of people that I've come across. All right. Good answer.
Okay. It's the only answer because I really don't even know who they're talking about.
But thank you for the 250. Appreciate it. Thank you. Bobo Durango for the 300 bits.
Jeremy, there's a secret Katana sword weapon on the awning. If you jump off the second floor,
food court real. Right. I look, okay. I know that there's like secret weapons and items.
I don't know. That's there. I have no idea. Jump off into the awning and grab the Katana.
That's meta gaming. He told you. Well, now I know it's there and that's cheating, but it's
okay. We're cheating now because I don't care. Tell me everything. Tell me where the bazooka is
so I can stuff it into that fucking girl on the bike's face. GTA hacker. But yeah, I'll start
picking it up. Thank you too. Kimono friend zone. Thanks for the 1500 bits. 15 bucks.
Jeremy, not even kidding. The mannequin torso is the most powerful weapon in the game.
He's like, I was like angry with me right now. Why? He just like, Hey, what is he doing? He's
like, let me out. Let me out. Where he's going. Let me see what he's doing. Let me just see what
my door going like, Hey, he's eating. He's been outside and now he's just hanging on. Okay. Well,
see what you want in just a few minutes. He talks. Yeah, but I'll try the mannequin torso tomorrow.
Maybe I can even kill her with a mannequin torso. Thank you. Dark soul for the 250. I feel like I
should leave a serious one. Thanks for all the streams and I hope you don't take our memes too
seriously. Don't worry. I do not. We only tease because we love our streamer. Jerma Hart also
chat. There's a burner cell phone taped underneath your chair. Go to the basement of Caesar's palace
and call the number. Jerma isn't who he says he is. Thank you. Okay. Thanks for the 250. Appreciate
it. Thank you. Al 2653 for the thousand bits. Jerma, let me give you a couple of basic tips
for the game. Always keep a couple of healing items on you. Arrange weapon and a couple of
good melee weapons at all times. Keep it out for save points too. Save anytime you enter a new area,
baby. And ultimately keep an eye on your main quest religiously. Keep it up, man. We all love
you. Even when you get, we get angry too. I mean, I was told that dead rising is an angry game.
Before I played dead rising, somebody told me, Hey, the bosses in that game are dog shit.
I was like, we talking about what? Yeah. You're going to get really annoyed with them.
I'm like, no, I'm dead rising. This is me in the mirror, by the way. Somebody, somebody just,
somebody just said that like 40 minutes ago. And then because somebody said it in chat, it was like,
I can say it now too.
I really like dead rising, but like the boss is really like fucking like dumb.
The boss is like dumb. The boss is a dumb. I didn't say it. The boss is a dumb.
And then I'd say people like, what are you talking about? Oh, somebody said that. Like somebody said
that in chat. I'm just like, I, yeah, that's, you think that too? Local comedians stealing
joke from the audience. I was saying that a boss is dumb, a joke. I'm not going to get on
Johnny Carson with that one guys. I never said it was funny. That's true. You know, you're right.
All right. Colusia. Thanks for the 250. Hey, let's put the credits up too.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Colusia. Thanks for the 250. Hey, what's up? It's my birthday this Friday. So here's some
pre-birthday money. Also, do you think you could say my name Mia so I can edit it into the rat's
birthday mix tape? Yeah, absolutely. Thanks, Jerma. Much love. You don't even need to edit it.
Happy birthday, Mia. Mia. It's your birthday today. Ice cream and shit is on the way.
Use that. Thanks everybody for your subs. You continued subscriptions. It's sorry. I just like
fucking completely blanked. I'm looking at my phone. I just like thanks for the subs and
what I said. Like I had a notification on my phone and my brain turned off. Okay, we're back.
No sirs. Thanks everybody for the subs and your extraordinary support of the channel.
It means a lot. He would rather look at his phone. No, no, no. I just it was like a like the
my light on my phone lit up and I have like the brain of a fucking squirrel or something
like a rat phone. Yeah, because I don't have notifications to sound on during a stream.
Otherwise, he would just be like, you guys don't want to hear that. But happy birthday to Mia.
Thank you. Sad Vega. Thanks for the 250. If there is ever a zombie apocalypse, you don't get to be
the leader. Yeah, people were like giving me shit about you'd be so bad. There's all the
apocalypse. You don't know where you are. Like as if I'm just blindfolded walking around my house.
You know, I don't need to know where I am. I just need to move my arms up and down left and right
real fast, really hard with a sword. I can do that really well. And a shitload of canned food.
Oh, okay. So I'm apparently doing it wrong. I'm just gonna have a go kart that's full
with like a train of wagons behind me that all has canned food in it. That's all gonna be covered
up. So nobody knows what it is. He's gonna starve within 24 hours. That face when you got to kill
zombie germ of Pepe hands. No, I am returning. It's not gonna happen. I'm too sneaky. But thank you.
Sad Vega. Gnarly. Thanks for the 250. Ever gonna do another system games collection stream like
you did with the dreamcast and PlayStation might be something might be fun with something like the
GameCube or DS. Um, not in the immediate future. I mean, the GameCube is really cool. But I would
need to, you know, I at one point, I was thinking about I wanted to do an Atari stream. Just get all
the old old Atari games and play them all. There's many as I could. And over the course of a day or
two, that stream would probably get really boring though, because every Atari game is almost the
same game. So after like 25 Atari games, it'd probably be like, okay, there's only so many
stick figure jumps across the lake that we can do in a row. But I think about it sometimes.
I guess the the progression PlayStation, PlayStation 2, Dreamcast, GameCube,
Nintendo 64. There's a lot of them. Are you ever gonna play code vein? I forgot about that. I bought
it to to stream it. I don't know. You said you were gonna play it. Yeah, I know. Well, I said I
wanted to. And then I put a vote up, I think. And like 12% of people clicked on code vein. It was
like, at least make a dumb character in it. That's because we had the thing. That's true.
Maybe I'll revisit it soon. I don't know. I can't get I don't want to get everybody's hopes up and
just be like, yeah, maybe. I don't know. I don't really have a plan. But hey, errorless. Thanks
for the 250. Jerma Saturn. Cool. So underused emote, I think. Dr. Clay, thanks for the 250.
I haven't even I haven't seen you get that mad since Hotline Miami. When? Wait, what this what
just happened? When did when did I get mad? I mean, during the motorcycle part? Oh, absolutely.
This was that was seven minutes ago. So angry. Somebody already has a clip of this.
Yeah, I mean, well, come on. Like I'm getting like turned on a dime with a lady on a motorcycle.
That's like that's that's bullshit. She's driving through debris like it's nothing.
Stupid like NPC shitheads. Get away from me. Get out of here. This is three. Oh,
I am so angry right now. You have no idea. This is a stupid. Oh, I cooled off right there. That's
fine. It was a little bit. That's not Hotline Miami tear anger. It is not. Not. No, no, no. I
can tell you as the guy sitting in the chair, not even close. Not even close. Oh, Hotline Miami. I
was just I hated it. I like hated it. There was like three levels in a row there. I was just like,
oh, it was inconsolable. I hated that. He hates it. Hotline Miami. No, it was Hotline Miami 2.
That's probably the most upset I've ever been on stream like recorded. Hotline Miami 1. I don't
think I had a problem with it. It was two. Yeah. So if you got a level between like Hotline Miami 2
is up at the top and drinking while playing Nintendo Labo is at the bottom. That was probably
somewhere into like the thing stream number two when I was walking around that corridor for like
20 minutes. That's like maybe like two or three rungs below Hotline Miami 2. But that didn't even
last that long. And no, no, no. Yeah, that that clip right there was like the extent of me being
upset with Dead Rising. I was like, no, I was mad at the controller because my controller kept
fucking going crazy. I'm out of the game. I know that's incredibly that's a meme. I was mad at the
controller. My controller is fucked up. My controller is broken. It was. I didn't do it.
I didn't even need to prove that. Imagine if I was just unplugging it on purpose over and over
again and like pretending to be angry with it. That would be such a pain in the ass. That would
be a pain in the ass. But imagine now I said it and now it's in people's heads and you can never
take it back. Anyways, thank you to DrSteam for the 500 vids. Jerma, are you going to participate
in the big Minecraft streamer only event that takes place on a huge world map? No. Do you even
know about it? I do not and I probably I'm not going to be participating. Yo, that sounds pog.
I mean, that sounds pretty cool. We already signed you up. That's not how this works. You
you guys aren't like my parents making sure I do some extracurricular activities. So you
signed me up for like the French horn. That's not how this works. We said you would host it.
Oh wow, that would be ridiculous. No. Okay, I need to stop talking because let me be very clear
here. I am not going to participate in that event. I wish him luck. Sounds cool. I will not be
participating. There you go. Hey James aka Bath Bomb Boy. Thanks for the 250. Hey Jerma, MrBathBomb
here again. Changed your name. That was not the name before, was it? Hey Jerma, MrBathBomb here
again. I feel like it was a different name. I work at Lush making bath bombs. Well anyways,
most of the people are especially so when especially what is it? What English is two English
people are speaking English. What is it? What are you talking about? There are two. Most of the people
are ESL. Oh okay. You should have a career day stream where us fans can show you our unique jobs.
Well I'd love to chat more but it's uh but it but at his point it's cheaper to talk to a
sex hotline instead of giving you bits. All right BF Bugleberry could use a bath bomb. What the
fuck is going on here? BF Bugleberry could use a bath bomb. What are these comments? I mean I kind
of get the gist of it. Have a career day though? That's that would be like interesting I guess.
Oh what oh I didn't put up no turn that no no this one is worth it. Errorless at the final bit.
Thanks for the 250 and take care everybody. That's the final one you're right.
All right guys I'll see you tomorrow for the conclusion the second half of Dead Rising 1.
Thank you. See you soon. Have a great rest of your night. Join us tomorrow. I'll have a new
controller by then and I will be locked in and push that fucking lady off her bike.
You got it. Take care have a great night. A grace night. A great night. I could probably use
some peanut butter or something. Good night. See you tomorrow. I just have a cat falling out of
this tree. That has not left me in almost two days. All right good night. Goodbye. See you tomorrow.
Take care.