Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Demo Knight.
Well, not really half Demo Knight, I guess you could call it, because I'm still using the lock and load, I'm not using the Wii booties like you typically would if you were using a strict Demo Knight setup.
But really though, what really is the Demo Knight? Is it just any Demoman with a sword, or do you have to have on the Wii booties, or do you have to have a shield on?
I would probably assume that if you're running around with a shield on, you are a Demo Knight.
Because really the charge mechanic and the crit you get on your melee weapon, it's, you're a Demo Knight. If you got a shield on, that's the way it is.
And I've actually become more accustomed to using this type of setup where you have that long range option with the lock and load or the grenade launcher.
Because the Wii booties, really if you think about it, all the Wii booties are gonna do for you is give you the extra 25 health and a little bit better turning accuracy.
But really though, it's just the 25 health that really matters in that situation.
So if you don't care about 25 health and there's medics on the team and you're getting overheal, it's okay to not put on the Wii booties.
Plus it is also going to solve a major problem that Demo Knights have.
After you charge somebody and you miss if they get away from you, you do absolutely nothing.
You run backwards or you just try and wildly mad men swing at them and a lot of times it doesn't work. Sometimes it does.
But this gives you an option to step back and go, okay, I'll pull out my gun if you're going to pull out your gun.
And it also really doesn't matter if you're going to use the default grenade launcher or you're going to use the lock and load.
It's just personal preference. Let's say you tell yourself, do I want to be able to spam around this corner and then charge over there and smash somebody in their skull?
Or do I want to sit back and try and get those direct shots, kind of like I'm doing, even though I am failing pretty miserably at it.
Later on in the video, I do get a couple of good direct shots, but it really is just personal preference.
So now I want to briefly talk about a couple of things and not about the gameplay really at all. It's going to be in the background.
I want to discuss a lot of you guys have a bunch of concerns about the giveaway I'm doing and I want to be very clear with this.
I want to clarify this to those of you that are concerned. No, I am not quitting Team Fortress 2.
I'm going to keep making videos on Team Fortress 2. I have plenty of backup items.
I have a lot of people, a lot of good friends that are willing to help me with this.
So do not worry about me. I'm going to be here for a long time, guys.
I don't think I could even if I tried. This game has a real deep clench on my heart and in my brain.
I love this game way too much to quit it. So nobody be concerned about that.
I am not going anywhere. Jerma is here forever until I'm 157 years old.
I'm going to keep making Team Fortress videos.
So now that that is out of the way, I want to talk about the Steam Workshop thing that I'm doing.
Like you all know, I have a modeler that is diligently working on these couple of things.
It is not one thing. It is multiple things and they are all for the heavy.
And I'm going to make sure I make this clear again. It is not a weapon.
It is not an item that you equip to gain stats or to shoot. It's not an item.
It is a hat and a miscellaneous.
Some of you have already started to speculate it because I think I've talked about this before.
But it's coming. It's great too. I wish I could just show you and tell you because I was laughing my ass off.
When I saw it for the first time, at least one of the items, I was dying laughing.
So expect more information and maybe even a few images in the next coming weeks.
So that's all I'm going to really say about that now.
But speculate away and if you already know what it is, then congratulations, you know what it is.
So let's talk about the gameplay for the last minute or so here.
Playing on upward. I think I forgot to say the map we're playing on.
This is defense on upward and right about now, they're coming to the last point and I'm not really doing a whole lot.
I'm kind of just, oh, let me shoot over here and let me shoot over there.
I'm not really doing anything.
Probably should have changed to the sticky launcher at this point and taken this off, put on the default grenade launcher.
But I don't do that and I end up doing pretty much nothing for the next 50 seconds.
To be honest, I was being a little too overconfident.
I was telling myself, no, I just got to get one or two kills with the eye lander.
Get myself with my health up, be able to run faster. That does not happen.
I act like a scrub for the remaining part of this video.
So here comes my most glorious moment in Team Fortress 2.
I'll make sure to slow it down because it really is.
You start taking notes now, guys, because I'm the biggest pro you could ever meet in your life.
So I turn around here, see an engineer building something.
So yeah, that's definitely something you want to do any time of century is right next to you.
Shoot it and get the blast damage killing yourself. That's a great idea.
So anyways, guys, this is going to be the end of the video. I go for an eye lander attempt.
Doesn't happen. I fall down in the pit of despair and we lose the game.
So thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all soon. So take care, everybody.