I want to be in the video. I want to be in the video. What? I want to be in the video. What do you mean? What are you talking about? Please let me be in the video, Jerma. Get out of the way. I'm trying to snipe. Oh, what the hell, Star. Ruining my like meta. I want to be in the video. I want to be in the video. Oh no, you screwed me all up. No, you have to go pyro. I have to go pyro? Pyro with the
flag and the detonator. What? Pyro with the flag? I don't even have the flag. I'll go rainblower. No, don't go rainblower. Yeah, I'm going rainblower. Let me get a hat that isn't disgusting. Hold on, I need to recharge my mana. What are we doing? I can't play like this. I think I know how to detonate. We need to wait until they push the card up. Then we start to become
champions. But right now, we just need to... Whoa, you just lagged out. I'm still here. What are we supposed to do? Oh, it's heavy up there. Heavy up there. Oh, I got the dumbass ham. Oh, backstabbed. What are we doing? We're going up here. We're going up there? I did it. And by I did it, I mean I can't do it. You got to do it. It's just like a rocket jump. You don't have to right click. I'll get it. I'll get it. Don't worry. I'll get it. I'm not going to get it.
You got to get it, Jerma. I'm so bad. I'm so bad. I'm so bad. I can't. Give me your keyboard for a second. All right, take it. There's a mini sentry too, so I think we're doomed. Where is it? Dude, I legitimately can't even see with the rainblower. Everything is like blending together. All right, so what's the next super secret strategy? Oh, well, you need to get some health, bro. So we're going up here. I just respawned.
I see the big Ben. Big Ben. Spice Boy. Scout going. All right, what's Big Ben? Oh, that. That Big Ben. Okay, be moved by the cart. I'm at the cart right now. I'm right behind you. Let's go over here. You could do this one. Yep, I can do that one. Everybody's a pyro on this team. That's the meta. Every single person is a pyro. Did you die? No, I'm alive. Come back. I'm just rain blowing. I need health. Watch out, Scout. Where's the damn health?
I really need ammo. Oh, all right. Rain blow is coming off. I can't like I can't even breathe when this is on this season of Highlander. Oh, the season. The season of your Highlander. Yeah, you're just Oxy.
I'm going to sing you an Oxy Highlander song. Star is my favorite Highlander friend. Are you honored that you're in that song? I'm so honored. Yeah, I was thinking about one day playing Highlander.
That's how you have to say it. I'm not ready. Actually, I was spending too much time being a weirdo. Probably going to get headshot right here. I got the collateral. Oh, you did. Oh, you didn't play the noise for you. Do you hear the noise? Yeah, I got to listen to the noise.
Hey, I was too busy trying to not get shot in the face as an engineer. Okay. Okay. Okay. God damn it. No, son of a whoever walks in this teleporter is going to die instantly. Ready? Watch this. Yep. Let's see if this guy. Let's see if what whale tar dies instantly.
All right. Well, it's our let's see. Let's see. Let's see the kill. Let's see the kill cam. Let's see what happens there. I'm watching them. Boom. I like how the whole time you could have warned him. You're just waiting for it. Well, it's like, oh, it's too funny. I don't even know what the hell I'm doing with this thing right now. All right, we're going to have them on either side. Center right either side. Yeah, come on. What do you got pyro? Oh, my God. I get out of town. This in here. No, you need to level up your.
Dispenser because we have no medics. I'm going. I'm working. I'm working. Where's that sniper? Where is this sniper? He's there. Oh, my God. It's that same motherfucker. Seriously. I'm going to die. No. Oh, did you get him? Yeah. Here we go. Here we go. No, you fucking.
I. All right. That guy. That guy turned the corner and like quickscoped me. No, damn it. My cover is blown. Blew my cover. You want to get you want to you want to get slaps up. Oh, my God. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I got my revenge.
Oh, he's chasing me. They don't know. I'm back here. Oh, there he does. No, he doesn't. How? OK, I'll take it.