Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here. Welcome to Cactus Canyon. This is the second of the two
new maps. I just made myself very well known to the snipers over here, so I might as well try to
just debate out a headshot. And he's using the Sydney Sleeper. I could have seen that by looking
down at the left of my screen, but you know, sometimes you just don't pay attention, and that's
exactly what happened. But anyways, I'll give you my thoughts on the map. I like this map a lot,
because it reminds me of Frontier, and I don't know why, but I like Frontier a lot. I like, like,
the inclines and the declines. It adds for some cool dynamics, but hopefully I don't get killed
again here. Let's get behind this medic, and then this guy too. He doesn't know. He doesn't know. He
doesn't know. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, easy. Don't throw those
in here. There's somebody in here. I'm trying to use the bathroom. What is going on with that door?
That door is going, like, insane right now. I'm also using this thing.
Pyro. Pyro. What do I go for here first? This guy, and then this guy, and then this guy too.
No. No. Yes. No. Yes. No. Absolutely no. Make my way back around. Let's disguise as a spy.
Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. Don't. See if we can get that sentry
before he gets it built to level three, and I will be able to. It's okay. It's okay. One hit.
Nice shot. Excellent job. Excellent job, team. You deserve every reward. Hmm. They're really far. I
don't know. How are we at their spawn right now? This doesn't make any sense. Come here. The card
is all the way up here, and somehow we're at their spawn. That's odd. Um, okay. Well, just get. Watch
out. Watch out for the Pyro. Uh, this is not good. I'm gonna go. I'm going on blue. We're gonna do the
switch right now. I can't. I can't make the switch. I'm dead here for sure.
Hello, everyone. It's me, the Spy. Today I'm going to be using the Kunai, the Le Chargé,
and of course my Sapper that I undoubtedly love to use. As you see here, I get covered in Gerate.
It's too bad because the Sniper is an asshole. He won't kill me, though. I will bait him into
this room where I will keep baiting him around the corner. He will fall down, and I will shoot
him. Just watch. Keep your eyes peeled. Keep your eyes peeled. Hold on. Oh, there he is. I found him.
I told you he would come down eventually, and I would kill him, but I didn't. That was part of
the plan, too. This next part of the plan is to follow the Sniper up the stairs and step him in
his bed. See? Watch this. Shit. Whoa. Too much going on there. Too much going on there. I wonder
if I'm being healed by this guy. How obvious of a spy am I? Hi, I'm just being healed by my medic.
Hope nobody heard that. Hope nobody heard that. Hope nobody heard that. Whoa.
Thanks, man. Really just saved my ass right there, Pyro. Whoever knocked me in the air.
I thought I was dead, but I just wasn't. Hey, Scout. Oh, just out of reach. Still might be able
to get him. Come on. I gotta land that. I gotta start landing those with the medic. What am I
doing? What's happening? What happened? I got him. Okay. A very weird chain of events is happening
right now and allowing me to be a moron and play spy correctly somehow, some way. Come here. I knew
you were gonna do that. I knew you were gonna do that. And the series of unfortunate things
ends up getting me knocked into the... If that's not like a... That was like scripted,
what just happened right there. You are... Oh, no. Look out. Look out. Look out.
Look at me. I'm standing on your stickies. I'm a spy. You might as well blow it up,
but blow up the stickies. Hey, look. Hey, I'm... There you go. This fall is gonna kill me.
In this next clip, I'm going to show you how to properly take out a sentry. A lot of spies
don't know exactly how to do it, and it gets them in a lot of trouble. As you see, I used my dead
ringer to make that soldier think I was dead. But in actuality, I'm actually still alive.
Come up around these stairs. There should be a health pack up here in this room. If you see
another spy, give him a nod and go on your way. So taking out your sapper, move to the sentry in
question and stab it. No, wait, that's not right. This choke right here seriously rivals some of
the craziest chokes in the game. There's only one spot that people can come through, and it's right
here. I just bumped into a spy, I think, somewhere. But man, this choke is insane. They have to come
through this door. How do we do that? I'm gonna have to just barrel my way through everybody.
I can't even do that. I seriously can't do that. I need to wait till they push out a little more
and just use the revolver. I wonder if I can, like... See, this is a good time to put on the...
This guy just, like, dancing over in the corner by himself. Well, we're gonna go for it. Hopefully
this pyro doesn't light me. And I'm coming in P. Nope, that ain't happening. Make our way back again.
And... Rinse, repeat. Can we do it? And here we go. Nobody pay attention to me. Oh, I'm doing...
Okay, there's a lot going on here. This is gonna be tough. Oh, you bumped him right into me. Oh,
come on. Oh god, no! He got in the way! Get him out of here. You give me that uber? You give me
that uber and things are gonna change. Oh, jeez! Oh, random crits. Oh, boy. Oh, dear. Oh, that was
a... That was a lot of other teammates, team members, or whatever that didn't make it out.
There's a... Where's this... Oh, it's all over here. That guy got telepracked. Oh, dear.
Let's get the little trap. That's not a very good trap. That was a great trap, Jerma. Very good.
That was a good trap. Did I do good? Mommy, look at my, like, finger painting I just made.
Oh, I'm so bad at putting traps down in the same spot. 30 seconds. 30 seconds. We can do this.
Dear, that's a lot of people. This map. This map. Oh, I need heals. Oh, dear.
All right, where's my weapon? Five seconds. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Not much longer. Not
much longer. We did it. No, it's over time. We didn't do it yet. Now we did it, right? Yeah,
we did. You can't escape me, Scout. You can't escape me. Well, that might wrap it up, but I do
want to say, if you do want to see more just general kind of live comms, like lightly edited
live comms, I have five dominations, right? That's impossible. That is literally it. Look at all our
dominations. My God.