Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary,
and tonight we're gonna be playing as the Engineer with the Widowmaker, the Mini-Sentry
Gunslinger, and the Pistol. It's gonna be on Barn Blitz defense on the last point, but
we are not gonna talk about the gameplay. We're gonna talk about the update stuff and how
tomorrow, Wednesday, meet the Pyros coming out and we got a bunch of new stuff, a bunch
of new items, some new sets. My brain is wracked right now. I cannot wait to talk about this.
Now, how I typically do my update videos, guys, is I wait till it's all out. Wait till
I can actually get my hands on this stuff before I give, obviously, my demonstrations
and my first opinions on them and stuff like that. So that video will be out tomorrow.
The second I can get my hands on all these items and make a video, it will be live on
this channel. But in the meantime, let's talk about what we've seen so far. So Monday, they
showed us, in my opinion, the best part about this entire update. We're getting a new official
game mode to Team Fortress 2. The last official game mode was DeGroot Keep, and a lot of people
don't even consider that a game mode. And we've gotten stuff like Saxon Hail. We've
gotten stuff like Prop Hunt and WarioWare. Those are all great community mods, but we
haven't seen an official one in so long. So this is just so exciting to me. I can't wait
to play this. Can't wait to try it. I have no idea how the game mode works. But the way
it sounds on the Valve website, it's kind of like Left 4 Dead 2 scavenge mode, where
you had one team had to fill up a tank and the other team had to stop them from doing
that. And if the first team fills the tank up and the rocket takes off, then they win
the game and then they flip a course sides and vice versa. So I think that's kind of
how it's going to work. Maybe red team is defense or maybe not. Maybe it's you're both
fighting for the same rocket, blue team and red team. That would be pretty interesting.
You know, you have a bar on the top that goes back and forth depending on how much fuel
the certain side is put in. This is all speculation at this point because I have no idea. But
I do know one thing. It's probably going to be a lot of fun. So today, Tuesday, we got
a bunch of different items for some of the classes. We got some scout stuff, sniper,
soldier and pyro. And I actually really want to talk about the pyro item. I'll go over
the stuff obviously tomorrow. I'm going to do a big, huge video on all this stuff. But
I want to talk about the pyro item mostly. Link will be in the description for all these
items and you can scroll down and see what I'm talking about. This pyro item is a secondary,
I think. But the stats on it are very, very odd. So for instance, it's called the scorch
shot, right? Flare knocks back target on hit and ignites enemies in a small radius. And
there's a minus 50% damage penalty on this thing. So my question is this. If this is
a secondary, why would you ever equip this rather than the flare gun or the detonator
or the shotgun? Knocking somebody back for a secondary, it's essentially a compression
blast. But as a pyro, we use our compression blast to utilize our secondaries. So if I
compression blast somebody and then switch to this and shoot them, I'm going to compression
blast them twice. I don't think it crits. I'm not sure if it even does any of those
things the flare gun does. And the minus 50% damage penalty, I feel like this is a primary.
I feel like it should be a primary because I can't think of a use for it if it was a
secondary. If it were a primary, think about launching somebody in the air with this, then
switching to something like the reserve shooter or the detonator or the flare gun and getting
the crit. That would make some sense. That would be interesting, especially because of
the minus 50% damage. You could essentially turn this into a compression blaster and that's
its job and that's what it's used for. But I think I have to stop making all these assumptions
on this item before I even sit down and use it. But that's my favorite part about Team
Fortress. Sitting down, speculating on items because we don't even know. There could be
more stuff tomorrow that complements this item. I don't even know yet. Nobody knows.
That's the beauty of Team Fortress. So tomorrow is Wednesday, which is the launch of the update
and of course the launch of Meet the Pyro. So here's a little fun facts for you. Meet
the Pyro comes out tomorrow. Meet the Medic came out exactly one year ago. And before
that, Meet the Spy came out two full years behind Meet the Medic. So it's kind of interesting.
They took two years to make Meet the Medic and pretty much less than one to make Meet
the Pyro. I remember looking at that coming in 2012 image that's on the main page and
I thought to myself, there's no freaking way they're going to introduce Meet the Pyro in
the first or second quarter. There's no way. I thought this was going to come out in like
November or December, right at the very end of 2012. And I was proven wrong. And that's
pretty awesome because I can't wait to see it. So yeah, that's going to wrap up the video
guys. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And let's see how
this update comes through. Let's see how awesome it is. Let's see how cool Meet the Pyro is.
I'm sure we're all going to be talking about this tomorrow. There will be a video on this
channel tomorrow as well talking about all the items in detail, showing them in gameplay
form. Just wanted to make this video telling you how excited I am and I can't wait for
Meet the Pyro and I can't wait for these items. But yeah, anyways, I'll see you guys all next
time and take care everybody.