Are you trying to shoot me?
Kinda, I don't know.
You look like you're about to be painted.
It seriously looks like you're about to be painted by an artist.
Like, pose right there for me. That's beautiful, yes.
I like how I'm not even breathing or moving.
I'm like a statue.
You really are a statue.
Just stay like that the whole time.
I'm just delivering my statue to the art museum.
You still look like it.
Alrighty then, let's go get a helicopter.
Alrighty then.
My car right now looks like...
You know when your dog gets into one of your toys and absolutely ruins it?
Yeah.
It really looks like a dog chewed up this car.
It's like this is the most messed up car I've ever driven in.
Everything is exposed.
I'm at the airport right now.
Let me guess, that's you in that right now.
That is you.
Yeah, I can tell. What was that?
What was that?
I just ran you over.
You just ran me over from behind?
I was driving so fast.
Dude, on my screen I just instant died. Nothing even happened.
I just felt like...
Look at these guys coming in.
What? What the hell was that?
What just happened?
The WASD and the number pad.
Where's my parachute? Where's my parachute?
Good, alright.
So meat, that thing is going to kill a lot of people.
I feel bad for whoever that lands on.
Oh my god, I'm watching it go down.
God, it's so scary. Who's it going to land on?
Alright, I'm parachuting down to the Empire State Building. Is that you right there?
Hey, what's up, stealth?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is not happening. You're not doing that.
You're not doing this.
I'm not even going to be able to land on this thing.
Stop shooting me, please.
No, this is not going to work! No!
Before we do that, let's hope it works.
I almost just fell off.
Alright, boo. Hold on to your hat.
What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing?
No, wrong way!
That was the wrong one again.
What is this like?
Alright, we're good. We're good.
You better not shoot me off at the top of this.
Oh my god, driving in sand.
I got it. I got this. Don't worry.
I got this. Don't worry.
Here we go. Ready? We're going to get up right now. Here we go.
Why are you just now getting in the door?
Oh my god, it actually worked!
It actually worked.
I thought you were just going to crash nose first and just stop still like driving into a brick wall.
Me too, but we Spiderman'd up the wall.
Alright.
Wow, this is like a challenge in itself. I feel like I'm playing Trials.
Alright, we made it to the grass.
I would describe this route as unconventional.
This is it, baby.
What's your guys favorite Kelly Clarkson song?
I really am sorry about this, boo, but this is going to be really, really funny.
Oh my dear.
No, I'm going to go off too!
Are you going to clear the building below you?
Yes.
Oh my god, you are right there.
I'm so tempted to shoot.
Oh, Jerma!
We're good. We're good. I'm good.
My helicopter is still below me, like where I landed it.
That's unbelievable. How did you do that?
Landed that? Very carefully.
Okay, so I just have to stay stable.
It's a stealth. You've got to be the judge. How close am I?
Pretty close.
Oh my god, you're like right next to it.
Should I jump into it?
I went through the blades!
You went through the blades?
How is that even possible?
How did you go through the blades?
Oh, no way.
Oh, Jesus.
No!
I looked away from my screen temporarily.
I look back up and I just see this toppling helicopter going instantly downwards.
Climbing up again.
Is that a cop right there?
Never there for the good stuff.
I do that. I spawned all the way back.
Oh no, I'm here.
What did you do?
Oh, my head. I have an instant headache.
I have an instant headache.
Is that a cop right there?
What did you do?
Alright, you guys are behind me.
Are you guys on the highway behind me?
Where are you guys?
You guys are literally within 10 feet of me.
How did you get that?
How did you time that so perfectly?
After I hit you, I did a 360 and just kept driving at the same speed.
How did you even hit me?
That was unbelievable that you actually connected with me.
I walked out in the middle of the highway.
I was like, where are you guys?
Then you just ran into me.