So I'm looking at my phone and so I apparently never tweeted last night. I didn't tweet last
night. Yesterday. So I opened up my phone. This is the first time I've opened my phone.
And I'm pretty sure like the entire 24 hour period since yesterday.
And it's just Twitter is open with the tweet from yesterday. So I just have to delete a few lines
and I'm ready to go. Look at this. I'm just gonna write. Oh, it's at X. It's at PS1. I'm gonna write
Xbox time. It's like already done for me. This is perfect. All right. Okay. How you doing? How are
you? So today we have the X, the original Xbox is set up, ready to go. I have been playing. Oh,
my mic cut out. Oh, whoops. That's because I'm delayed by like a full second. That's right.
So I'm on the original Xbox. It's one of the reasons why I wanted to do this is because
there are actually a lot of games that are not backwards compatible with the 360 or with any
of the newer consoles. So some of these kind of just got like lost forever. And I have,
I'd say half of the games that half of the Xbox are like that. They're still here at some here
that work on the 360, but we've got the original set up. Let's see how long it takes us to go
through the originals. So first up, which is kind of surprising that you can't really play
it anywhere. But I think it's on PC, but it's like a Windows. It's an old Windows game,
very old Windows game. So trying to get the old like Windows, what Windows 2000.
Okay. Sorry. So he's fake typing. No, I'm not. Why would I? I'm real typing. Why would I fake
type? No reason. Please see your evil face. No. But anyway, so what was the same? Okay.
So a lot of these old Xbox games cannot run on the 360. I have a 360,
but some of these don't work. So I've owned some of these games for four or five years.
They've been sitting on a shelf because it's like, oh, fuck. I can't play these on the 360.
I thought 360 was backwards compatible. Maybe one day I'll get an original Xbox somehow.
Maybe I'll do it. But here's that day today. We're there now. You are about to see
games that are no longer available. So that's a, that's not true. You could probably, I mean,
look, I know that this is going to be, somebody's going to be like, whoa, what about just get an
emulator? It's original hardware. I like original hardware because, I mean, yeah, emulators are
great, but there's this period of emulation where once you hit the PS2 and PS3 arrow, like that PS2
Xbox into PS3, a lot of games have a ton of problems on emulators. They're, they get messed
up. There's tons of bugs. There's graphical problems. You got to like, oh, no, no, no.
The problem is you need a different BIOS. I don't want to do all that. PS3 emulation is
actually pretty great now. I hope that's cool because it wasn't a few years ago when I, you
know, three, four years ago, but also I also, I don't know if the game is still available
and like, I, if I can play it on the original hardware, I'm going to, if it's not, then of,
and of course I have a different opinion, right? But we're, we're on original hardware today.
When are you going to play boom blocks? This dude is lawful neutral.
That's what you took out of that. Oh, he's lawful neutral. No, I'm not. Am I? What's that mean?
Lawful neutral Andy. No, I'm not, I'm not chaotic neutral. I'm not going to say that. I'm,
I'm really not even that chaotic. I'm really not. All right. Give me one more second. Uh,
we're going to be wearing a turtleneck. Why would I be wearing a turtleneck right now? All right.
I'm going to get started. Let's go. It's time to play the matrix. That's the first game I've got.
It's enter the matrix. Weirdly enough, this game never got any, it's probably, honestly, a lot of
this is probably for licensing problems, right? You have to imagine that some of these did not
get ported to the newer consoles because of that. Why did somebody just write? Ha ha ha ha ha. Why
did you do that? Explain it. This game rules and I'm on original hardware. So this is, oh yeah,
baby. All right. I'm ready. Let's go. No more stalling. I'm ready to go. Can you do an agent
Smith impression? Mr. Anderson, it seems I am not the only spy. You are in deep trouble, Mr.
Anderson. Pretty good. Pretty good. Pretty good. You know what was really cool about what just
happened right there? That was the same audio clip three times in a row. And I just did it
just from my mouth. That was fucking awesome. And I'm going to, I will die on that hill. That was
actually really interesting. What just happened that there was no difference in how I said all
three of those. It was perfect each time, the same exact audio clip. And it was me talking.
I win the argument by the way. It was no argument. All right, let's go. Let's go. I made sure this
was playing the whole time because I was so afraid of the screen burning it. This trailer
has been going on for, oh my goodness. It's got to be at least 20, 30 minutes at this point.
I've just been playing this. So I've had to sit here and listen to this a while. All right,
you guys ready? You said you weren't chaotic. What's chaotic about saying pretty good three
times in like a cool voice? I think that's pretty lawful neutral. That's, that's 100%
just neutral, right? Like I just said it perfectly. If I was chaotic, I would have said it differently
three different times. I win. All right, let's go. New game. I'm not playing on hard. All right,
we're doing the no save file. Let's go. That matrix save is good enough for me.
Your account do hacking. No, I'm not. I want to play. Why is this in 320p? Because I'm on
is the burn in from there from last night. No, but I am actually so paranoid about it.
Let me check. Hold on. If I turn this off. No, it's not there. Thankfully. All right, quiet.
This isn't a movie.
I haven't seen the move. I haven't seen the matrix hidden. All right, I, I saw the first
matrix. I saw the second matrix and then I didn't see the third one. Stop watching this.
It's part of the video game. That's fine. This is exclusive footage. What the fuck? Quiet. Stop
talking. Just got out of the post office. Is the drop still clean?
Naomi, this won't be easy. I'm not just watching the matrix. I swear that is what's my friend.
I knew him. He never used to drop before. He didn't trust him. Whatever's in that box costs
that he has his life in the lives of his crew. And I have a feeling if we don't get to it first,
it's going to cost us a whole lot more. So are you red or blue on this?
Yes. You know me, Naomi. It's not a choice. Wait, didn't, don't you already have to take the pill
to do this in the first place? Wait, I thought they already took the pill to be able to be in
this universe or something. I know how valued my opinion is on this ship. I won't bother to tell
you, but I think it's insane for you not to wait for a support team. And for the record,
when I cart your bodies back to Zion, I prefer cremation or the gardens. Sparks,
balls. No, because this is flipped. It's all both ways. Then can you shut up and hit the button?
Your wish captain. My captain is my keystroke colon double backslash execute command.
Okay. Oh, okay. Pick. I'll pick ghost. Why do you do that? Do what? Check your guns.
I can turn it up. It's a program. They get loaded every time the exact same way.
Hume teaches us that no matter how many times you drop a stone and it falls to the floor,
you never know what will happen the next time you drop it. It might fall to the floor,
but then again, it might float to the ceiling. Past experience can never prove the future.
So, so you never know. Here we go. Cool. All right. It's time. I would doesn't matter how
many times that happens. It was scared the shit out of me every time post office closes. There's
a ton of heat in the area, but the package is still untouched. Box number is seven three one
two two two. Got it. And hey, can you ask ghost if he doesn't make it? Can I have his boots?
To me, it's kind of like when a plane lands, when you're just like, you know, I've flown planes
hundreds of times at this point, right? And the plane is like landing and it's just like,
okay, we're okay. Right? Like everybody kind of has that moment.
It doesn't matter how many times you fly a plane. It doesn't matter.
There's that one second moment where you're just like, and that's it. And that's it. And you're
fine. Save matrix. Yeah. Is it burnt in? No, it's not. No. Why did he just check? No, that's fine.
All right. Let's do it. Xbox night. The instant messaging window below is where
me message will appear from your operator sparks. All right. What's what do I have to do?
I didn't get it. I thought I didn't get a tutorial. What the fuck is happening?
I don't know. I don't know how to play. All right. Where do I go?
New tip fighting multiple enemies. What? What do you mean tip? I didn't even tell me how to play.
All right. What do I do? All right. That way. How do I play? Okay. What was the mission? Okay.
That's punch this combos. All right. Cool. You're supposed to read the manual and I don't have time
for that. I don't. Okay. I have gone to, how do I open doors? It's just, dude, just, just kicking
punch. Don't care who cares. Don't worry about anything else. Wait, press the action button to
activate switches. That's the telephone. This is blocked. Read the manual. There's no manual guys.
I don't have a manual. Oh, it's okay. That's locked. That's locked. Should I restart? Did I
do something wrong? Why are you so violent? What does it say? Kick the doors open. Okay. What do
I do? Stop asking the question and play. What? Why am I doing this? Why am I asking you everything?
Just walk around and figure it out. What am I talking about? I didn't like that was in one ear.
What did he say? Okay. Pause menu and select objective. Oh, here we go. First person mode.
You can view the environment from a first person. Press enter exit. First person to enter first
person. Enter exit first person again. What? What? I can't even read the sentence.
You can view the environment from a first person view for the eyes of your character.
Press enter exit first person to enter first person mode. Press enter exit first person again.
What button is that on the Xbox? They didn't tell me what button it is. I have X, Y, B, A,
left. Oh, first person mode. There it is. Sorry. First person exit enter.
Okay. You can punch. You can kick when running from agents to exit hand to hand combo. Either press
move away from the enemy. Press fire or press first. I need to see these controls. Multiple
enemies at once from nearby all angles. Tap movement. Okay. Yeah, I get it. I need the
con- there we go. Focus movement. Weapons menu. Pause weapon select. Target lock. Action. Where's
it? Okay. First person. Cool. All right. Let's go. What box was it? Second floor upstairs.
I found a way inside. Try the security door behind the clerk's desk.
Okay. How does this run? I'm in. I'm going to watch this whole stream on the toilet.
Make sure you stand up every so often because your circulation is going to get all fucking up to me.
I'm in. Why did you tell me to come to this door if you're not going to open it?
Why did he do that? Did you hear a word he said? Yeah, he said go to the freight
station somewhere over in the freight area. I don't know. I thought he was going to open a door.
Press fire to draw a weapon. Well, there is no bumper on the original Xbox.
What's fire? I don't have- I changed weapon, I thought. Wait, what's fire? Fire is-
What are these two weird buttons? What are these two weird buttons? What the hell are these?
Huh? There's- I- What are these two buttons? There's a white and black button? Holy shit,
I didn't know that. Look at this thing. There's two buttons here. I- They were invisible to me.
Why are you such a zoomer? I never had an Xbox. That's actually- I don't like pressing that all
the way down there. Stop. Put it away. That's so far away. This is the worst controller.
He has small hands? No, it's just- What is this? What a bad controller this is.
White and black were bumper equivalents. Really? Okay, well, what was that? Why are we in like this
split screen? How did I just do that? I don't know. This game is awesome. This is- What a fun game
this really is. How would this not- Why wouldn't they get the licensing figured out to get this
game on the 360 or something? What are they thinking? There's a PC version? Yeah, but PC
version, you have to jump through like 10 hoops to get it to run sometimes, especially on a new
computer. If it has like Windows 10, Windows 11, it's just like- You have to set up a virtual
machine at some point. Yuck. I missed so many times, but whatever. The climb fence is moved
toward the fence and your character will begin to automatically climb it. Shoot him. Shoot him.
Shoot him. What? I have no more ammo? Wait, these are- Okay, wait, these are-
What am I doing? What's the point of that? They just do that to that guy.
Dude, if you're in a full sprint like that, what do you do? Stop that. Stop doing that.
Special moves? Ow. Go over there and fight him. Go over and jump to him.
Wait, there's weapons. Wall press? I'm all right. How do I wall press? Reload firearms. I don't know.
Shoot around corners. How do I get out of this? Oh, I got him. This game is so fun. All right,
cool. This game's fun. Grenade.
Stay above the gas. The cops are sealing the doors. Where's Niobe? She's trying to find a way
into the building. You're flying solo. Stay above the gas and find a way out of it. Yeah.
Stay above the gas and get out. How do I do that?
Where do I go? Stay above the gas? Wait, this room's not full of gas?
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
Oh, the gas is in here. All right. I was confused. I got confused. I got confused. It's fine.
First, I wasn't getting hit by the gas and then I was hit by the gas. I get it. I understand.
It takes me a second. I was too busy making the dumb joke. I got it. Jesus. Whoa. Pretty sick.
All right. Here's the help. Oh, I just punched him right in the throat.
Okay. Now I'm not messing around. All right. The gas is over here somewhere. Shoot him. What
are you doing? Just attack somebody. What are you doing? You need to wall run. Damn it. How
do I do that? Face an object such as a wall, then tap movement forward as if to walk into the wall.
Your character will turn their back and press up against the object. Okay. Wall press. Wall run.
Is this correct? When a wall press, strafe left and right or move left and right to move along
the object. Okay. Cool. All right. I get it. All right. Let's do it. Don't turn around and
and go the wrong way. So the correct way is over there. Where am I going? I don't understand.
But I'm going to go out of this gas down here. Can I jump on this?
Need to use focus. Climb up the fence. Get up there. What are you doing? I don't get it.
Somebody said I hated this level when I was a kid. Where are these vents?
What? I don't think this is correct. Go back. Go back. I don't want to. I don't want to do this
again. I really don't want to do this level again. I don't want to do it again. I really don't.
I just had three arms. Ow. Look for us. Skylight. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Get down. Get
down. Get down. Hey, get off the first person. You idiot. Skylight. Ah, holy shit. I made it.
Okay, we're good. I have 2% health. Did I soft lock myself? I hope not. Is there health anywhere?
There's no health. I have to actually be stealthy. I didn't even fucking see me coming.
I just shot myself in the face. Hey, wait, wait. What are you doing? Oh shit. Oh shit. That's
fucked. That would be the quickest way for you to die. This dude is fucked up.
I'm coming through the grate. No, you're not, man. You're not going to make it.
If I sit here long enough, it'll recharge. Just anger overtook this character. I'm going to get
through that chain link fence. I'm saying happy birthday. Okay, wait. I'm waiting until full health.
I'm not messing this up. Holy shit. I just destroyed that guy. That was awesome.
Health is recharging. I'm not going to be stupid. This game is hard.
Just run by. I can't hurt. I can't hit them. Wait, what about behind the energy drink container?
No, go. Just run. I'm good.
The 85th birthday.
There was once a jail or bank or something. I need some guidance.
Oh, there should be a control room located very close by.
Find it. Call me back when you get there. This dude can't hear me through the wall.
It's a window. It's soundproof. Die through glass. Oh, no way. How do I do that?
Kick through glass windows by running. Okay. Make this fucking epic. What's with my health being so
reduced? Nice. Shoot this guy. What are you doing? Your character will automatically duck under low
hanging. Okay. How do I crouch? Is there a crouch? Dude, stop kicking. I put too many inputs in.
It's locked. Oh, hold on. Go. Can I talk? Is there a talk button? No, it's not talk.
I'm not going to do it. I need to power up the lobby elevator. There should be a switch somewhere
on the control panel. All right, guys. I had to come in and press the big button.
How's the audio? Is the audio still okay? You want to do a couple quick tests? Hello there.
My name is Jerma. Does it work? They say it's good, right? He just hit me right at the fault.
What was that? He just went like that. Okay. The combos. Who made this game?
Who made this? What company made this? Shiny? Shiny Entertainment? Because this is pretty good
for thinking about how it holds up. This actually kind of holds up pretty well.
This is fun. Wait, the Shiny Entertainment that made Earthworm Jim? Wait, Shiny Entertainment.
What? The devs that made Earthworm Jim made Enter the Matrix and MDK. You know what's crazy about MDK?
I remember that being on a demo disc way back in the day and I played that demo disc a million
times. I didn't even know what the game was. What happened to that guy? Yeah, there was level one
of MDK was on some old demo disc and I remember just playing it over and over. Those old demo
discs were so awesome. Do you know how many times I played level one of Parappa the Rapper?
It had to have been hundreds of times. All right, let's go. Were they awesome sauce or just regular
awesome? Please do a demo disc night. I feel like it wouldn't hit as hard as it did back a long time
ago. Do it, please. Oh, this is a long first level. I feel like I've been here this like
tutorial level. Where are they going? What? Let's go. You used to get them in magazines.
Yeah, you know, I might be just completely speaking totally completely out of line here,
but do video games really do anything kind of funny and fun like that anymore? Not funny,
but you know what I mean? Like, oh, looks like a little thing we're going to put in the box.
People don't really have a box, right? Like, oh, here's like a preview for and it was weird
because some wasn't it sometimes it'd be like two discs in the PlayStation one case.
It's like, oh, here's, by the way, here's like some weird DVD extras. Like, oh, cool. No, good
riddance. What? You don't want like some fun thing just to kind of browse around when you're
just kind of bored one day? Why? What do you mean good riddance? That's DLC now. A special edition
of Halo 2 and 3 had extra discs. It was awesome with behind the scenes stuff. Hold on, I gotta
pay attention for a second. I have an unbelievably brilliant idea and I don't want to tell anybody
because it's so good that I feel like somebody would steal it. I might just figure out how to
do it one day. It's actually like a 100 out of 100 on a point scale for like how cool this would be.
I wish people would do it. I can't tell you because somebody's going to hear this and you'll be on
Shark Tank in two weeks and I'll be like, that was my shit and I shouldn't have said it.
That's such a weird flex. I'm telling you, I have an unbelievable idea and it's so good. It's so
good. It makes me angry that nobody did it yet. It makes me fucking mad that nobody's done it yet
and it's there's only two people on earth that know what this is. Ollie and Otto. I told Otto
very very detailed information about this. Otto is a spy. Dude, one time,
this is completely unrelated but it's just so stupid. One time, so I like, okay,
I don't want this to burn in. I have to do something. I have to like literally run in a
circle. It's so annoying that I have to do that. It's gonna be hard to talk. I don't care. Okay,
so I like to, it's a new hobby that I have. I'll tell you about my hobby. So I like to collect
at this point right now playing cards. I like cards, you know, like ace, king, queen, jack.
There's so many different decks. There's so many cool things to kind of find and, oh wow, this like
there's so many different artwork that you can collect. There's so many different kinds of styles
and it's fun. It's fun. They're not that expensive. It's just like, okay, cool.
You're a psycho. Yeah, some people collect coins. I like playing cards. Let him cook. Exactly. Let me
cook. So sometimes it's fun just to kind of play cards on the couch. It's like, you know, like
Polly's right here, I'm right here, and Otto is like asleep kind of on the couch over there,
like over here, like to the left, and we just deal Otto in and like we were playing poker.
It's just like, okay, like here you go. Here's your cards. Here's my cards. Here's Otto's cards.
And it got to a point where we just started laughing and we're just like, what are we doing?
Because it's like, oh, what do you got? Oh, no, no, I fold. Oh, this is what I got. And I look at
Otto's cards and I go, oh, Otto folds. He's just like lying on his side, just sleeping and snoring.
It's like he's not even participating. Why is he in? Why are we doing this? Like, oh, Otto folds.
Like, what was the point? This is that was that's cute. It's just for fun. I don't even care.
But anyways, this is fun. Like he's not giving like, oh, look, look, he's playing too. Isn't that
cute? Otto has no idea what the hell we're doing. He doesn't care at all. He's just asleep.
You should let Otto win. You should ban Otto. He counts cards. But anyways, yes, I've been,
I've been, I like, I don't have that many. I probably have seven or eight decks total.
It's fine. Some people collect coins. Some people collect. Look, all right. You know what? Some
people collect cars. I don't, not going to do that. I'll take the, I'll take the cards. Did I say,
what did I just say? Did I say? No. Yes. Some people collect cards. Cars. Right. I ain't doing
that. Okay. Jump from behind cover. Cool. You, hey, whatever you want to collect, that's up to you.
Go ahead and collect whatever you want. If it's cars, if it's coins, if it's playing cards,
if it's video games, people, old video games, collecting old video games, who's Otto?
I don't, I hate, I turn this off. Turn the sound off. That's really cool. Oh my goodness.
Dude, how do you fucking win? Dude, how do you, how do you win? There's too many people.
My God. Skill issue. People that don't have the context that Otto is a dog are confused.
Like there's just some guy, Otto, that's here. Oh, you know what? Otto folds. Just a guy lying
there. Otto is a dog. Otto is a, my Dachshund mix. Okay. Don't mess it up here. I'm just going to
hide. I'm going to hide in the corner. Just, yeah, that's the best way to do it. Wait,
how long ago was this? This is so long ago. Why was there no checkpoint here? Why was there no
checkpoint? Skill issue. I'll show you a skill issue. Hey, rate this one. All right. Let's not
mess this up, please. How did you choose Otto's name? Uh, that was Otto's name already. So Otto
was a rescue and he was already two or three years old and kind of already knew his name.
So it's just like, yeah, we'll just keep it that way. All right. Here we go.
Do it. Shoot him. I just got so angry. What the fuck? This level is so hard.
I just, you have focus, but I shot those guys like a thousand times. Oh, come on. No. What?
I, those guys weren't even, my eyes are so itchy. Okay. The whole game is difficult. It's very cheap
in the later levels. Oh, great. Well, it's a good thing we have a time limit on all of these games
we play. I wish there was a checkpoint here. Spamming is the meta. Don't be afraid to spam.
So wait, I, it's not about looking cool. It's about just spamming as much as you possibly can.
Are you going to play Elmo's preschool? No, probably not. That game's way too hard.
Especially the last boss is just like fucking stupid.
The dodge mechanic in that game is so annoying when you're in like the,
when you go to that, uh, like kind of, hold on. What the fuck? It's too hard.
It was just the underworld level is just like, I don't know. They give you like five health potions
and you can, they think you can beat that like Satan character with five, which is like, you,
it does, you, it's just, I don't know. You can only heal like a few times during that fight.
True. I don't know. It's all right. That's not bad. Don't do that anymore. Something is in my
eye and it's causing me stress. Ow. No, you piece of shit. This game is impossible. Holy shit, dude.
This game is like not even beatable. Oh, excuse me. I don't understand. I, those guys were on
the ground dead and then they, all right. I'm, I'm not, I'm doing this for real this time.
I'm not going to talk about like, oh, Elmo has a funny game with like a dodge mechanic.
Stop and play. You didn't see him blank and plain view. I want that health.
Actually, it'll read, it'll go up. Stop walking into bullets. Watch this clip. It's as, this is
as bad as singing the braids song. What braids song are you talking about? Why am I losing health?
Okay. I am going to try as hard as I can. I'm not going to talk. I'm not going to say a single
sentence. I promise. Where are the enemies? What am I doing? What's happening? What am I doing?
All right. Go. Nice. Pick up that phone. That's just kind of scared me.
Yes. Thank God. Thank goodness. Did you play Peglin? I did not. I'm still in the first level.
What is coming out of that?
From the second floor. Sorry. That's a big ice maker. You can make it. It's money. Oh, it is money.
That'd be so cool if there was a counter up in the top, right? That was like, like hundreds,
hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, hundreds.
That guy almost just killed me. There's no side jump. There is. I mean, I can side jump out of the,
out of cover. I want to like side jump right now. I hope I'm going the right way because I have
absolutely no idea where I'm going. See you. Okay. I think I got it. This game looks pretty sick.
The game is pretty sick. Can you wall run in real life? You know, I actually feel like I probably
can. You know, those things that you've never really tried that much before, but you're just
so confident that you could. I think I can. I could probably get at least one, two, three,
four, five steps or at least one, two, three, four. If I, if I was in full sprint and I was
like, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh. I could do at least four. Where these guys even come from?
Do it on the battle act stream. I, all right. That's fine. Well, I'm going to add more things
that I can prove that I can do. We'll get a list. I'll do them all. How did you shoot me more than
I shot you? Oh, that's how you do that. Oh goodness. What did I just do? I just did a split in the air.
That would be so scary. I have no bullets. Oh fuck. What are you doing? Oh, get out. What am I doing?
I don't know. I don't understand what to do. Am I, should I run? What? Am I missing something?
Or do I have to fight? They can definitely see me. I kicked that guy through the glass.
Dude, what the? I gotta climb this. No, I don't. It hurt me. Where do I go? You gotta eat. Dude,
they're just coming out of nowhere. They're actually spawning out of nowhere. I'm not,
I have to go somewhere. Come on, man. That's the same. Is it the same model?
Something's burnt into the bottom left of the screen and I don't know what it is.
There is text burnt into the bottom left. What is it? Is it loading screen?
I, is it select? No, it's loading. Yep. That is slowly being burnt into the screen.
How old is your capture card? Hold on. Something important just happened. What am I firing at?
It's inverted. Dude, this sucked. There's nobody to shoot. I could be inside the car right now.
There's nobody to shoot. Oh, now there is. Unreal engine demo. This is so
fucking loud. I, can anybody even hear me? Why am I doing this? Dude, you know, I have to tell you
something. It's very important and I have to pause it for this because you can't hear me.
This reminds me of arcade games that are, you know, light gun arcade games. Can somebody explain to
me please? Tell me why. Explain to me. Why is every light gun game stuck in like 2003?
Every light gun game, they've, they're on the same technology, the same kind of graphics engines.
Why are they all so kind of scuffed? Every game I've ever played at an arcade that,
it's never progressed past like 2003. No, they did not stop being made. There are new ones. There
are new ones that come out and I've played some of these new ones and they are terrible.
They are brand new games and you know what they do? This is what they do instead. Instead of
looking good and playing good, you go into this weird audio world where it's like,
we have subwoofers built in. So don't, don't, it's like, don't pay attention to the 25 FPS
awful shooting game. They, they, they make these like weird sit in Disney kind of rides
where it's just like, oh, okay, I'm ready. It just shakes and screams at you, but the game's
terrible. What happened? Why are all these games just stuck in the same era? Is it hard? Is it
just, is it impossible to make a game that's got like 2015 graphics and plays well? Why are they
all running like such shit too? Burn-in. All right, sorry. I'm so paranoid about the burn-in.
I thought the health 93% was burnt in. What if I just don't shoot anyone? I don't know if that was
scripted or not, but I would be dead. My head would have been crushed five times. I'm not
shooting anybody. This guy sucks at driving. What is happening to the car? Oh my God. Wait,
wait, I, I, wait, I'm not, no, I'm not driving. Who's driving? I would be driving better than this.
This feels like I'm playing GTA online. This is exactly what it's like. Did the bridge just spawn?
What was that? Why did the bridge just spawn? It's the matrix. Oh, it is the matrix. I'll tell you
something that has increased. You know, it has increased, not the quality of the light gun games,
but how much they cost to play. Interesting. Exit. Tell me it's close. It's close. The fire escape
on your left. Hurry. Does it make this phone on the roof? The phone is behind the roof access door.
Oh, thanks sparks. I couldn't have been on the ground floor.
She aimed that gun like she was casting a spell. Oh, here he is. Yeah. No pinball tables. It's
bullshit. You know what? There are a lot of places that are starting to kind of try to do the old
fashion arcade stuff. That's really cool. If I ever had an arcade, it would just be free pizza,
but you had to be like playing. That's a casino. Nevermind. Free pizza. It's just like a waiter or
a waitress rocking around. Pizza. Anybody want some pizza? Oh yeah. I'll take a slice instead
of alcohol. I'm sorry, but that's fucking cool. That's, I would go there, but then the logistically
would be hard because people get greasy fingers all over the controls. Imagine somebody walking
around with like a piping hot pizza, walking around the like, I almost just said casino floor.
Imagine walking on the casino floor. Where's that? I just, I didn't know what like the constraints
were of the video game. I actually didn't mean to do that one. Greasy controllers are given at an
arcade. They always have bar food. You know what? What's going on here? You come to my arcade. Okay.
As long as you're playing, you know you're playing. Hey, I'm having one like slice. How are you doing
over there? By the way, no toppings or no bullshit. No toppings. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse
me. Oh yeah. Pepperoni and olives. No, no, no, no. This is cheese only by the way. What do you mean
fuck that? No toppings. You know how difficult it would be to actually logistically put that
together? Hold on a second. Oh, I had an opportunity. I just need to, I'm sorry everyone. I need to do
this. This is for the video. This is for the video and three, two, one. This is for the video.
Let's go. It is I, Superman. It's going to be, I can see it. People can rewind and watch it rewind.
It's going to have a huge hump for replayed part of the video. Ladders. How do these work?
That place would be disgusting. They would just be, people would drop full cheese slices,
cheese side down on the ground. You know what I'm talking about? Just like, oh, thank you.
They appreciate a full slice. Cheese like sauce, cheese side down on the ground.
This place would be a mess. You got bread side down. That's not a big deal. Cheese side down.
That's a carpet clean. Oh, yes. Cheese. I'm talking like with this, like cheese and sauce
side down. Like if you dropped it on the ground, new tip impossibly fast, incredibly lethal
and fearless are hands down the deadliest enemies within the matrix. You can never completely kill
an agent. They'll just acquire another body that is plugged into the matrix. At best,
you can temporarily defeat. All right. So it's like, you just can't kill them. I don't even
know where, where am I going? Yeah. And you could not order a full pizza. It would just be a slice
of cheese is what you could get. Am I missing something here? I'm, that probably looked on
purpose and it kind of was, but I thought I could go, I don't know. I thought I could do Spider-Man
on the wall. People are going to be pissed. I'm sorry. People are going to be pissed off now,
but that's going to make people angry. It's like, dude, just stop doing this. Not fucking funny.
I'm just trying to see what I can do in the game. What are you doing? So I need to go. Oh,
there's a ladder right here. So now from, where do I go from here? This way over there. Climb
over the fence. You can jump a thousand feet in the air. Oh, oh shit. What were you, why were you
two in here? What is in here? Why are they were just sitting in here? There's nothing here. What
is that? Just a big, is that just like a, what is it? What is it? Oh, Mr. Anderson, Mr. Anderson.
Okay. So just don't, just don't bite them. Oh my God. Okay. This actually sucks. I just gotta run.
This sucks. It's so far back. Mr. Anderson, seven minutes. How many people in the chat even
understand what that was? Some of you do. Some of you, not very many. That is Albert Wesker,
but why did I say that? Trivia, some channel trivia for people. Stop. Old video, dude. That's
right. No. Oh my fucking God. You've got to be, I, oh my God. I got caught on the lip and I didn't
jump. I got stuck and the character went like that and I couldn't stop doing that. I'm sorry.
I'm not doing it on purpose. I am telling you, I'm promising you. I actually got, you think I
would be at the very end like that and do that? No, I got caught. You should change the game. I'm
kind of, I kind of like this. I'm giving this another 30, 20, 30 minutes. I, I get to, I'm going
to have the streamer reverse veto where I'm, I'm playing this like at least another 25 minutes,
at least this is, I like this a lot. This is very fun. Okay. Come on. Don't screw it up. Okay. Now
I have to sit here. The health region. Okay. What is this? A little shortcut. What is this? I didn't
see this. What do I go? Where do I go? I fucking freaked out. I freaked out. I'm going to take the
disc out. I, I thought I had to jump over there. I don't, I don't, I can't fight them. Oh shit. I
look so stupid. I look so dumb. I would, I, where do you go? It doesn't look like there's a, to the
right. Don't jump to him. What? Where am I supposed to go? I need to go left. I, that's what I tried
to do. You were at the right spot. I just missed the jump. This breakable wood. I, that, that's
what I saw. And I was like, can I jump into that or through that? I almost didn't make that jump.
What? Stop. Oh shit. Is that him? Now where? Here. Oh, I pressed it and it didn't jump,
but I made it. I'm fine. Oh, we got a cut scene. Perfect. Okay. You want a shot to feel good,
can fix you up. Right now, all I know is what's on that disc. Sir, we just received an emergency
broadcast from the Logos. She did it. Yes, sir. The last transmission of the Osiris.
This is Daddy's, captain of the Osiris. It is 1803 on 1214 and I fear this will be our last
transmission. Less than two hours ago, we were pinned between two search units near BZ 218.
We tried to outrun them on the surface when our sensors went completely berserk.
We didn't believe what our equipment was telling us until we ran smack into the middle of it.
An army, their army. It's massive. Hundreds of times the size of anything we fought.
We're under heavy pursuit and have sustained critical damage. We're going to attempt an
emergency broadcast drop in the matrix. After that, let's hope that somehow this disc reaches Zion.
And if it does, it's not too late. We had an opportunity.
Drop down in Zion broadcast. I want this data transmitted immediately. Emergency encryption.
What are you saying? Wife of Barty? Lieutenant. Yes, sir. Is the Logos still in contact?
Yes, sir. There's ants in your hair. Get me Captain Nyope.
Black feed from Zion. Jesus, it's deadbolt himself. Give me that.
Captain, you and your crew to be commended. What you have done may prove to be the turning
point in this war. Do you have a plan, Commander? Right now, I want every ship to return to Zion
all as fast as humanly possible. I leave the recall hands kept.
Yes, sir, Commander. It's all on one disc, by the way. That's pretty remarkable.
Nyope, please be careful. As careful as I can be.
That's just one disc. It was a DVD. The power of the DVD.
No, it's weird about the Xbox. When that first came out,
that's why we're going to use the airport. All those different pay phones will make a trace
impossible. We can split up and stay mobile. What could go wrong?
I am calling to confirm that your order of Red Orchids will be delivered tomorrow by midnight.
This is the Great Beyond Travel Agency. We will get back to you as soon as humanly possible.
Operator. Jax.
Nyope, is that you? I'm not sure I can talk right now, Jax.
Nyope, listen to me. They got Axel. Soren led everybody in after him. It's bad,
Where? The airport.
What? We're at the airport.
Please, you gotta help us.
Agents have cornered Soren. They're moving Axel to the tarmac. If they get him in the air...
What the hell happened? I thought you said be discreet.
It wasn't me. It's Soren.
Agents pinched one of his crew. Now they've come in and tried to rescue him.
You? Yeah.
What? Lucky for him, not so lucky for us.
It's Axel.
Shit. What do you want to do?
See if you can help Soren. I'll go after Axel.
Well, good luck.
I'm certainly due for something.
I have no idea what just happened. Okay.
Okay, stay calm. Help is on its way.
How many of them were there? I swear I got them.
Did you see any of them?
He was right in my sights.
Why did I... No, put this down.
Emergency evacuation.
Can I... How can I...
They're just gonna lie down and get scanned by the machine.
I didn't even go through security.
What? What... I don't...
Oh, shit. It's Agent Smith.
Shit. What's going on?
What? I just made it through.
This isn't Hitman.
You unlocked the cartwheel.
This guy does not know where I am.
What'd he just drop?
Ooh, how do I use that?
Wait, how do I use the cartwheel?
I'm holding gun, hold down, focus, side step.
Okay, so you have to have a gun out.
How does this not work?
Okay, I think I missed something here.
This dude's flailing. I was told flailing is fine.
All right, I'm back.
Why did that guy climb?
He climbed on top.
Okay, what do I do?
Is this supposed to be a stealth mission?
Well, I...
Like, the character picked up the weapon.
I didn't want...
No, look, I don't want this stuff.
I didn't want to do that.
How do I use flashbangs?
Circle strafe.
Use your strafe controls.
Well, how do I strafe?
Oh, hit strafe left and strafe right.
That doesn't help at all.
Hold target lock.
Wait a minute, what's strafe?
Press strafe to strafe.
This is not a cartwheel.
I'm sorry, but it's not.
I'm not dying in here.
Fucking get down, what?
I can't adapt how you do it.
I'm gonna die.
Please don't do it.
Where am I supposed to go?
This is gonna keep spawning on me
until I find the right door to plug into or whatever.
NVIDIA, the way it's meant to be played.
Holy shit.
It's linear, just go forward.
Isn't that where I just was?
Oh, I was not here.
Oh, all right, all right, all right.
That guy, the only one that got affected by it.
He looked over here.
Oh my God, I just want to...
Fuck.
They can see pretty well right now.
This is where you go.
Everything's fine.
Oh, this is awk.
You need to throw a grenade at the window.
No, I don't.
He didn't read.
Use the grenade.
An actual grenade.
I don't even have grenades.
Is there a different grenade button?
That's a flashbang.
Okay, but I don't have actual grenades.
Weapons like fire, secondary fire.
First person, kick, jump.
Do I... I don't have any grenades.
Shoot the glass.
I don't think there is.
No, I don't think there is.
Do you think it was trapped?
Try the big wall.
Hold on, let me just make sure.
No, I didn't miss something over here.
I don't get it.
I think you need to use the superman dive.
Okay, where does it want me to go?
I think I might actually be soft-locked.
It's the white button.
Yeah, the yellow...
Is something yellow in the room?
The yellow box?
Yeah, I can't touch it.
In the lockers?
This actually might be bugged.
The flashbangs might have soft-locked the box.
That's the grenade box.
Oh, should I just refresh?
I'll just refresh.
How far away is the load, though?
No, no, no, no, no.
Just shoot it.
Wall?
Run?
Follow the arrow.
I can't.
You could probably blow your way out of there.
Yeah?
It's broken.
I'm just going to relax.
It's...
Okay, everything's fucked up.
I'm just going to...
I'm scared that if I do this, though...
Where am I going to be?
Shoot the box?
It's not shoot the box.
It's not...
I guarantee it's not shoot the box.
I guarantee it.
This is not that far back.
That's one of them.
Get to the guns.
See?
Okay, I just picked it up.
All right, so now...
Flashbang.
Why is it back?
You broke it again?
How did I do that?
You weren't soft-locked.
You didn't break it.
Change to different...
Hold on.
What was that?
Oh, I thought I shot...
I thought I shot a harpoon out of my chest.
All right, hold on.
Do I have to do it again?
Equip the grenade.
I didn't know where to...
Okay.
It didn't tell me to do that ever.
Let's go.
Okay, now where do I go?
Oh, dude!
Maximize your experience with Pentium IV.
That...
A lot of computer ads.
What?
Stop!
Am I right?
Why did he go so fast?
I thought the helicopter was inside of the building for a second.
Like, this is no way.
Why are you saying F?
F?
What?
Small F?
I don't see it on my end.
The only option is to fight.
I didn't even have a second to understand what was going on.
Maybe the switch is having a problem?
Okay, so don't...
Fuck you!
Refresh my health!
Why is the health not counting up?
I can't.
Fourth wall break when he looked over his shoulder like,
Whoa, man, this is crazy.
The music is fucking me up, too.
It's just like...
The disk is to get things.
How do you do this without...
Where's the helicopter?
Hell are you talking about?
Oh my god!
I'm so dead!
Oh my goodness.
This is...
This is ridiculous.
What's the way to actually go about doing this?
Just use grenades on the helicopter?
I don't think that's gonna work.
Why would you do that?
Well, the helicopter's cycle is so weird.
Like, where is it?
I give up.
What are you supposed to do about this?
Dodge the bullets?
Okay.
Excuse me.
Just dodge the bullets.
That ain't gonna happen.
Where's the helicopter?
It goes around.
It goes...
So then wait for it to turn around and knock up.
God damn it!
I thought they were spawning.
That was a good cycle.
Wait for the machine gun fire.
Go across.
Yep.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Go.
Maybe one more cycle.
Get off my screen!
Yeah!
What does it want me to do?
Check the area for useful gear.
What does it want me to...
I don't get it.
I have to get it.
I can't leave without it.
Is there a crouch?
I don't know what it wants me to do.
Hey, did you ever heard of up dog?
What is that thing you just said up dog?
I don't know why it wants me to do this.
Good.
I think it was just broken.
I'm having a good time, but it might be time to move on to...
I don't know.
Moving on sounds like a bad idea.
Hold on.
Not yet.
Another...
I can't get past that gate.
The other walkway.
I don't know where I'm going.
How'd you guys get over here?
This wasn't open!
That was not just open 15 seconds ago.
I was gonna say I almost like fogged too hard there.
And went out the window.
Lower the resolution to the face cam.
No, it'll break.
I have it set perfectly right now.
I don't want to fix it again.
The piano will help you reach the roof.
Is it piano?
I love this music.
Butter!
I almost made it.
Grab it!
Wait on the piano.
Piano?
Aim, you idiot.
Where's the piano?
I have to pee so bad.
Why is he looking for a piano in the ceiling?
I'm not.
I'm...
Where's this piano?
Wait for the piano.
Where's the piano?
I'm being loud.
Okay.
I don't...
I don't know what was...
Guys, this is a...
It's a...
I'll go pee.
We lost some time in there.
Where are they now?
Soren and his men have been cornered.
Give me a minute.
AT-28 in the annex.
How's Naomi doing?
She's not dead yet.
Okay.
I gotta pee a beer back.
Got about the burn in.
But something else that's very interesting.
So I had this computer.
This room gets really, really hot.
Because this computer and, you know,
streaming and encoding and things
pretty much just cooking over here.
The original Xbox is almost, I think,
generating more heat than that computer.
I went from just out of this room to back in here
and it was at least 10% to 20% hotter in here
than it's ever been.
It's like a sauna in this room.
This is ridiculous.
You should play Halo.
I actually...
I thought about it.
Maybe one of these days.
All right.
So I'm not leaving yet.
But I do want to give you a couple of options here.
It's not over yet.
But I want to pull in the chat.
I'm going to give you three options to pivot from here.
The first option is Cold Fear.
The second option is Star Wars Obi-Wan.
And the third option is Legends of Wrestling.
That's a tough one.
That's a very tough one.
Is there a fourth option?
Go offline.
It's a little too early for that.
Okay.
Coming back.
Let's see.
What do you guys want?
It's still pretty early in the poll.
Are you ever going to return to A Dead of Night?
No.
Never.
That's just not going to happen.
I couldn't do it.
All right.
Unless the Obi-Wan fans can really pull this through,
Legends of Wrestling looks like it's going to be what we're doing.
It's really not even close.
Go ahead and close it.
Legends of Wrestling is up next.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'll play this for another 15 minutes.
That was the lamest action movie jump I've ever seen.
So loud.
Is it?
Oh, I didn't turn up the music.
All right.
Does anybody else get like this when there's an escalator
and there's nobody in front of you?
Just go.
Hurry up.
Right?
Sometimes I just sit there though.
Sometimes I just like, you know what?
I don't even care.
I'm going to let the machine just do it for me.
Are you not afraid of escalators?
Because to me in my brain,
an escalator is an incredibly basic contraption.
All an escalator is, is just a thing.
It's just a tread that moves in a circle.
There's nothing really that mechanically ridiculous
or strange about an escalator.
It's a very basic concept.
It's the stuff that has the complicated shit in the middle
that freaks me out.
By the way, where am I going here?
Shoot.
What did I just, did I just command bullets to fly?
It's still open.
Now's your chance.
Oh, move.
Check your gun.
Give the signal.
So open it.
Oops.
For a second I thought he was talking.
I thought that was the person in my ear.
Escalator up at the second floor.
Technology.
How do you miss every single one of those?
No, my goodness.
I'm going to die.
Not if I hide over here.
Oh, escalator.
What?
Why can I not take the escalator?
Take the stairs?
It said take the escalator, didn't it?
Something I have to do with it?
They're different.
No.
Anyone want to help me?
The different one?
The game is chugging so hard right now.
Okay.
It's a different escalator.
Oh, all right.
There we, whoa.
Where did it go?
What?
It went into the escalator.
There's a door leading there at the end of this hall.
Right here.
Over the railing.
Come on.
Oh, and I didn't even do it in slow motion.
I'm pissed.
Don't die here.
Hold on.
Hide next with a bunch of exclamation points.
Relax.
Okay.
He came, he's behind me.
Where?
What?
That was a cardboard cutout.
Exactly five to 10 minutes from now.
We're going to do Legends of Rest.
They get Axl off the ground.
He's dead.
Who's this?
Find them.
Can't give him a car.
Binary.
Or like a golf cart.
We'll take you to such a double back.
Ghost, can you cover us?
Do they have to run?
I got it.
What is your field of fire?
I've got the runway.
How about the hangar?
Provide sniper cover.
I can cover that too.
I've got activity below.
Top of the stairs.
One of the suspects.
The female.
Clear shot.
Confirmed.
Take them.
That was so, like such a,
I thought we were on the same team.
That was so overdone too.
Like I just, I'm on edge right now.
Why?
I, in my brain,
it was, I thought they were talking to,
why am I in this room?
And why is everybody looking?
Honest, that, please.
I need to relax.
I need to calm down.
Okay.
That was so completely overdone.
In my brain, it was like,
there's not a single reason ever.
Like I thought we were on the same team for a second.
It was like, oh, get the sniper rifle and support.
And they were talking.
Why am I even in the room?
Is what I'm trying to say.
Why do I shoot this?
How do you, how do you zoom in?
Was that my teammate?
I don't know.
Was that the guy I'm supposed to protect?
Fuck.
I think that was,
I think that was a good guy.
He was just in the cut scene.
I'm so stupid.
I don't know.
It's just like, there's a,
just a trailing short-term memory where it just ends.
There's a period where I'll remember anything,
but it just ends here and it just moves along on a track.
And it's just everything that's back behind here is gone
in short-term memory.
I can't believe I did that.
Do you see people are talking and it's like,
look, help.
We were all talking about helping each other.
I've got a clear shot.
Confirm.
Take the shot.
Sure thing.
Cover the stairs below the roof.
Okay.
All right, all right, right, right.
No, that's somebody else on the team.
That's somebody else.
Where do you want me to fight?
What the hell are you, what?
Cover the stairs below the roof.
Why can you even walk forward?
Why can you walk forward there?
What is your field of fire?
I've got the runway.
How about the hangar?
I have a blindfold on.
I've got activity below.
It's one of the suspects, the female.
A clear shot.
Let's take the shot on the tower.
Machine gunner, lower balcony.
I have to throw this guy out.
Okay.
So where, what do I have to do on the lower staircase?
Shit.
Down here.
These motherfuckers right here.
Get to the balcony downstairs and help.
Okay.
Come on.
There's no way.
That kills you.
There's no way that kills you.
How far down do we have to go?
Times up.
No, it's not up.
What is your field of fire?
Who are you talking to still?
This is such a weird angle too.
What do you mean I passed it?
Guys, come on.
This is a fool me once scenario.
There's always just a dead end.
Five feet in front of these doors.
No.
I'm back to the top of the tower.
Are you serious?
I just, okay, we're good.
All right.
In exactly five minutes, I'm moving on.
I promise.
They shot the cover off the front tire.
Take the tire out of the plane or the car.
I don't think that's how that would work.
But you know, whatever.
Where are they?
You have to take out that copter with a sniper rifle.
Okay.
It was like a little animal.
Give me a chance.
2.5 minutes left.
Yeah, I have to do that again.
Oh, I hope I can do this twice.
This game is awesome though.
I might just come back and play this another like later.
Okay.
All right.
Get out, get out, get out.
Where is the where's it right in front of me?
Is he alive?
Was he dead?
I don't know if he's, is he dead?
That was unfair.
That was actually unfair.
I thought he was still alive.
I thought he was going to shoot me like three or four more times.
Time's up.
5.46 is the prediction.
Okay.
I had that too.
That was annoying.
You have 15 seconds.
5.46.
So the mods have told me.
I wonder.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
I got it right here.
You just got to go right in.
What?
Get the help.
Who just did that?
What's this?
Did I skip a cut scene?
There was no way to go down.
Did I skip the cut scene?
I heard hurry up.
I'm I'm I'll get it right now.
I got the strategy door opened.
You didn't even look.
I did.
But I didn't know I had literally five seconds to move.
It just was like, oh, get the heck out of there.
Okay.
Get the heck out of there.
You know, many times we've heard get out of there in this game in the last two and a half hours.
Okay.
I was going to say there's not a single chance that would happen.
I can't believe I shot this guy in that.
We'll need a car.
Wait, what?
Weren't we just going down?
Why are we back up?
I thought the whole point was to get out of here.
Is this a full letter grade?
Because if it is, I am not leaving.
That person's dead.
That person is dead.
I thought it was supposed to be exactly five more minutes.
It is.
But if there's a if I get to actually drive the car, I get to add it.
Hey, ghost, I've tapped in.
No, I don't care.
Do you want me to leave now?
No way.
Don't lose it.
Drive the car.
Drive.
Now he's on that plane.
I love the way he's driving too.
This is a great game.
I love this game.
It gets it.
I know it's like an old lady.
Is there a horn?
What are they dropping?
Someone fell out of the plane.
Who fell out of the plane?
Who is this?
What is happening?
Did they fall out of the plane?
What am I supposed to be doing?
I just don't understand.
Go up the ramp?
This car is smoking.
There's a ramp?
I'm on top of their car.
What ramp?
There was a ramp?
There's an arrow.
Follow the arrow.
Don't do 10 HA's.
Hey, ghost.
I'll get it right now.
Tapped in.
Car CB radio.
Keep following the plane.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I couldn't see the ramp with all the mud on the screen.
Play Breath of the Wild.
Not today.
I'm just waiting for him to turn around and do that look.
Okay, all right, all right, all right.
Pay attention.
Someone's falling out of the plane.
Okay.
Pick him up when he lands.
Don't lose him.
I didn't see anybody fall out of the plane.
I didn't even see it.
I accidentally just did that.
How would you?
How did you even see that was here?
How did you know that was here?
My car can't even fit through this fucking hole.
Am I going the right way?
This is insane.
Oh, no.
Please push me.
Push me, push me, push me, push me, push me.
Push me out.
Drive forward.
Please drive forward.
Drive forward and push me out.
Please.
I don't want to do this again.
Drive forward.
Push me out.
Oh, it's so close.
Do it.
Keep going.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Yes.
What the fuck are you talking about?
This driving level is...
I just...
Damn, he's going to beat you to axle.
What?
Whatever you do is that car.
This car is...
I can't have control.
I can't see because of the smoke.
Am I going...
He's getting away with the axle.
Which way?
Did I accidentally pick the right door?
Oh, my God.
That was unbelievable.
That was ridiculous.
That was so hard.
I loved it, though.
Pretty good wall run by that car.
Hold on.
Okay, I'll call you when we get close.
Wait.
This is fun.
I guess you were due for some luck.
Did you get Soren out?
Yeah.
And call the rest of the fleet.
Good.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Remember, I fully support you.
Just play this all day and do Xbox another night.
Let's just watch this last DMCA cutscene and we'll figure it out.
Axel, that's your dust-off.
I think we're all right.
I'll move on.
I'm sorry, guys, you wouldn't have done what you did.
Thank you for it.
Depends on how interesting the next mission starts.
I'd rather kill you.
You know what I mean?
I'm just glad fate brought you to the airport.
I'm not sure you'll agree with that tomorrow.
Just tell Soren midnight.
He'll know the place.
He is fast.
I will say that.
Come back to this game.
72 hours.
72?
What did you just say?
That's exactly how long, Zion.
What do you mean and who are you?
Me?
I thought that was Adam Sandler for one second.
72 hours.
I don't know why.
Actually, how?
I don't know.
It was like 72 hours.
It's just 72 hours.
Right?
That was a bad imitation.
No, it wasn't.
That was fine.
You're here.
Ghost?
No wrestling?
No, I-
We're waiting.
Just wait.
Has everyone arrived?
That sounded like Yoda.
I have a Kineser.
Figures.
Think for an entrance.
Captains.
Captain Niobe.
My crew and I appreciate what you did for us.
It's not illegal if it's on a video game disc.
He's alive.
Happy to be.
Let's get going.
Because you know Morpheus is not going to show up until we get started.
I agree.
I don't like us all being in the same place for too long.
Why don't you tell us what this is all about, Niobe?
The machines are digging.
Tell that to the judge.
Shit.
It's the feds.
Get to your exits.
You know, they could just cut the pipes up there so nobody has to duck anymore.
Get some pipes, these cutters, and just cut the top.
People don't-
You've clearly cut them already.
They're perfectly cut.
Straight across.
Go up by one- two feet.
All right, here we go.
Is this-
Beginning of this mission interesting enough for me to keep playing?
Let's find out.
I'm telling you, if he hops on a motorcycle, I ain't going anywhere.
All right, that was pretty funny.
I might have to stay.
So Legends of Wrestling is coming up next.
Seems like a fun thing to do.
Seems like an interesting game to play.
That was the Matrix.
Enter the Matrix.
We're going to move on.
Let me just make sure I don't burn the screen in with the next thing.
I just-
I don't really want to climb up all that right now.
All right.
Legends of Wrestling, where are you?
Did he beat it?
No, I didn't.
I did not beat it.
Will you go back to the Matrix?
I mean, that was really fun.
Maybe.
I don't know.
We gave it a solid three hours.
That was double overtime.
That was a double overtime.
Usually it's about 40 minutes to an hour for each one of these.
I thought it was double, triple overtime almost.
Okay, here we go.
Hold on.
Can you see?
A great disc loading action.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm interested.
Everyone is so hyped for me to play this, but I don't know.
I feel like this is maybe-
Wait.
I don't know.
I'm not going to pretend to know.
Because this could just be kind of not that fun.
I don't know.
This game is legitimately not that good.
That's what somebody just said.
Okay.
Hold on.
Ban that guy?
We're creating a wrestler.
Barrel chest?
Heavyweight.
Muscle?
Skinny?
The audio is bad?
All right, fine.
How about Mean Green?
That's fine.
Wait, modify.
Oh, hold on.
Light, medium, or heavy hair?
Oh, it's how much hair is on my body?
Okay.
Upper body.
I like this one.
He has sprayed on clothes.
All right.
Right arm?
Hold on.
Can I have like a huge arm?
Okay.
He's going to have a huge right arm.
Goodness.
Should I have diney hands?
Like, diney hands are huge hands.
Hold on.
This is really loud.
Tiny?
Let's see what it looks like when it's huge, though.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's that.
Wait, diseased?
Oh, what the fuck?
I'm going to do ripped.
Okay.
Left arm.
Wait, torso.
Torso, torso.
Should I?
No, no.
Keep it that way.
Lower body pelvis.
Should I have a huge?
You're making a crab.
That's just strange looking.
Okay.
Do these all be tiny?
Make it opposites.
You couldn't even stand on these.
This is...
Okay.
It just looks like somebody pinched and went like this.
That doesn't look right.
Please mute the sound.
There.
It's not as bad.
I don't know.
No, it's definitely tiny.
I kind of want to take the mask off and have it just have this.
I love how it's coming through the mask.
Okay, hold on.
It stays on skinny.
It's staying on skinny.
Yeah, take it off.
Take...
Yeah, just none.
Okay, I think we're good.
Entrance gear?
Iron?
A flag?
A scepter?
A spear?
He's going to come out with the US flag.
He's going to come out with a scepter.
I don't know.
He's coming out with a cape.
He should come out with a hat.
This guy sucks.
Okay, you know what this looks like to me?
It's just like what...
This looks like an AI-generated person.
It's like, oh, a man with a hat on holding a scepter has big legs and is very muscular.
It's like this is what it makes.
Kind of like that.
I like that.
I can't wait to lose every match.
Okay, I think I'm ready.
Weight?
What about attributes?
Strong?
Super charismatic?
That's all.
I can't do any more points.
No, fuck that.
Everybody just loves this guy.
You know what I mean?
Brawling?
All right, high risk.
Cheating?
Hold on.
High risk or cheating?
What's better?
Definitely cheating.
There's no way.
I'm definitely cheating.
Okay, size?
That is just...
Okay, that's not...
That doesn't do anything.
Okay, appearance.
I already did that.
What do you think?
The name is very important here.
Make him short.
Five, six.
The crab?
What did you say?
Look at...
He's such a cheater.
No, I'm not going to name this guy Berserker.
The Berserker.
Okay, fine.
Crowd?
Names?
Music manager?
What do you mean, crowd?
Eat dirt?
Or, no, loved.
Do I have a manager?
Music.
Wait, can we hear it?
This is not Hulk Hogan's music.
This is not even close.
What is this?
Are these all just DMCA versions?
Yeah, they're all royalty-free versions.
But they're not even close.
I know...
I know Bret Hart's music.
No, it really is royalty-free versions.
Why would they have the rights to the wrestlers
but not their entrance musics?
Somebody said these are iCarly beats?
iCarly beats?
It's this no way you're going to convince me
it's not this one.
This one is so dumb.
This is Jerry Lawler's music but not...
It's...
This is the...
Okay.
These are the dream versions of this music.
Like, that was...
That was what was playing
but that's not what was playing in the dream.
Look at iCarly.
These are all so good.
I don't know.
Wait, hold on.
We have to hit a drop on this one.
This is just the intro to Monster Rancher.
Oh, no, it's not.
It's...
It's that song.
I think I have to go...
Look at how many there is.
I think I have my choice already.
This one has lyrics.
This is Persona music.
This plays in Persona.
It's like Persona 5.
I don't know.
Our character eats bugs.
I don't think this is...
No.
We're at a joint.
That's been cooking up burgers since 1950.
Off on the corner of 1st and 2nd Street,
there's Hank.
The atmosphere.
I love the food here.
It's just so good.
And we're going to talk about his homemade meatballs.
Hold on a minute.
Hold on.
I have to...
What is this here, man?
There it is.
All right.
Let me take a bite.
To the onions.
When they really get in there
and you've got the...
You got the thyme.
You got the cumin in there too.
Oh, you knocked out of the park, man.
Out of the park.
Killed it.
This person doesn't have music.
Oh, yeah, they do.
I don't want to do any more reality TV shit.
I'm gonna...
Now, when you...
You don't come back here
and tell me how to run the store.
Whenever you run a store
and somebody comes up with an item
that just looks like it's worth a thousand dollars
but it could be worth millions.
This guy...
This guy came in with a sword.
I don't want you buying that sword,
you fucking idiot.
Hank Chumley.
Chumley.
Go get us lunch.
It's 1230.
Wait, there's the same song.
Dude, Storage Wars.
Storage Wars.
Every so often somebody comes in with an item.
That floors everybody.
Wows everybody, you know?
Wait, that's a one...
Oh.
I'm just having fun listening to these songs.
This is more fun than the game.
This one...
I like this one
but I just want to hear the fucking
take a bite out of the food diner's drive-ins
and dive song one more time.
I think it actually might be the song.
I think this is the song.
Right?
Just make it this one.
This is the song that plays.
I think it's the royalty...
I'm...
Hold on.
This one...
It kind of has to be this one
because if I get hit in the chair
and get injured...
If I get hit in the face of the chair
or the first match...
Fuck.
Okay, fine.
I gotta pee again.
Let me pee one more time.
I press...
Wait, there's this button.
I have a question.
Are there more episodes of One Piece
or diners drive-ins and dives?
How many episodes of One Piece are there?
One Piece?
There are about a thousand.
There are over a thousand episodes of One Piece.
How many episodes of diners drive-ins and dives are there?
Are there a thousand?
There's probably a thousand.
Google says 419.
So it's not even close.
Never mind.
All right, what about Naruto?
Are there more episodes of diners drive-ins and dives
or...
Don't burn in the screen.
It's happening.
I did it.
Okay.
It's 700.
500.
Mail average.
What was this person's name?
Crab?
Just keep mail average.
Bob Berserker?
How do you spell Berserk?
Bob Berserker.
Is there an R?
Is it like Berserk?
Or is it Berserk?
Bob Berserk.
Okay.
Short name.
Berserker?
Wait, do we need to...
Wait, what do you mean the list?
Does it say the name?
Wait, does it say these?
Hold on.
It definitely says these.
It's definitely...
Bruiser!
Burnout!
Cabbage!
Captain!
Cowboy!
Oh, you know it does.
It has to be a Z name?
Zebra!
Ugly!
Weirdo!
Zap!
Zodiac!
Here he is.
The weirdo!
Oh, man.
I'm telling you, Bob.
The weirdo is having struggling in that corner there.
Let's hope that the weirdo can get out of this without that many scars.
Middle of name?
Do Uncle Bob.
Bob.
Uncle Bob.
All right, all right, all right.
Bob Berserker?
No, not Uncle Bob.
Shit.
Okay, that's good.
Finisher.
The Double Roundhouse.
Does it matter?
The music is very loud.
The...
The Grinder.
The Crusher.
The Smoosher.
I'm not calling it that.
The Stern Talk!
I like that.
I love...
The Stern Talk.
What is that?
Imagine if you just like...
I like it.
Hometown.
I don't know.
Fucking L.A.
Where...
Who cares?
All right.
I don't want a manager.
I did save it when I came right back that first time.
Let's do it again.
I made sure before I took off because I was scared that something might go wrong.
Oh my goodness.
I forgot what it looked like.
All right.
Are you guys ready?
It's time.
Career.
Where's the...
Where's the character?
Did it need to be a legend?
Okay.
Good.
Let's go for it.
Pick a region.
Las Vegas.
Of course.
Options.
Costume.
Advice on.
Okay.
All right.
We're going down here.
Let's go.
Dallas.
Yes.
I wish to load wrestler one.
Why?
I thought I didn't have a manager.
Where's my...
What was my music?
Did I have it?
I don't even know how to play.
Wait.
I'm not even playing.
Why am I not playing?
Uncle Bob.
Bob Berserker.
Are we going to do this for everybody?
Everybody's going to get one of these.
All right.
I'm skipping the rest of these people.
Is it Aquaman?
Don't skip.
So what's the match?
Are we just going to hang out and just...
Shit.
This camera angle is so bad.
How do I fight?
Oh, shit.
What?
Did I lose that fast?
Aquaman was doing the same face.
Boring moves.
Ignored your partner.
Minimal combos.
Zero percent popularity.
Okay.
Good.
I guess we're staying here.
I'm telling you.
Buttons didn't do anything.
I pressed X.
I pressed Y.
I pressed V.
I pressed the trigger buttons.
Nothing seemed to do anything.
Why are they booing me?
I'm supposed to be a fan favorite.
Okay.
Let's not lose immediately, please.
I did a move.
Oh, shit.
Extreme damage.
We're playing on concrete right now.
There was no give to this ring.
Shit.
How did you do the same move?
How do I...
I want to get out of the ring.
That's got to hurt with an arm that big.
How do I climb the top?
Let go.
I think it's like a fighting game.
I think I have to do like down...
Like left down up.
Left down up.
Hey.
Left down up clicks.
Nice.
Oh, shit.
They don't like it.
They are actually pissed.
Uh-oh.
Where are you going?
How do I run?
How do I run away?
How do I pick that up?
Pick that up.
How do I pick it up?
Pick it up.
Pick that up.
How do I pick...
How do I pick the chair up?
Oh, I am fucked here.
It's over.
There's no way I'm getting up.
No.
My goodness.
I'm dead.
I'm not getting up.
Run.
Run away.
Oh, my God.
It's so hard to control.
I want that chair.
Give it to me.
Pick it up.
How do you pick up?
There's no move list.
I'm trying to...
I'm trying every single combination I'm trying.
I swear.
I want the chair so bad.
You have no idea.
No.
Pick the chair up.
How do you pick up the chair?
L?
I'm pressing L.
Up on the D-pad.
D-pad up.
Get more weapons.
Ow.
No, give that to me.
I'm nothing without my weapon.
Give me the weapon.
Give me a weapon.
I need a weapon.
It's an exciting match at least.
Why is he up immediately?
Get off me.
This chair is huge.
Leave me the fuck alone.
No.
Stop it.
Dude, his ass is insane.
What do you...
Oh.
I need a weapon.
Please.
All right.
I have a guitar.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
I got it.
Wait.
Yeah, I can throw this?
Everybody loves it.
This is the greatest match they've ever been to.
Wait.
Pick it up.
Ow.
Oh, I blocked it.
Give me a weapon.
Hurry.
What the hell is this?
Should I pin him?
Dude, his health is transparent right now.
He has no health bar.
He's out?
He has, like, a little cut on his forehead.
Dude, look at this excitement.
159%.
Oh, look at this popularity.
This game is great.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not fun.
It's not very good, but it is at the same time.
It's actually pretty good.
Oh, yeah.
We're in Vegas and we're going to a joint tag team.
Is that a gun?
Oh, no.
Is it?
No.
What is it?
It's a gun.
Rob Van Dam.
Bob and Rob.
Are we going to fight this guy?
Not this again.
Wait, I'm cheating.
Why does it say cheat?
How do I cheat?
Holy shit.
How do I turn?
Hey.
Wait, tag.
Tag in.
Oh, shit.
We're in.
Uh-oh.
Pick the weapon up.
What?
Oh, I blocked it.
Tag.
Tag, you idiot.
Pin.
Pin him.
No, shit.
Tag in.
All right.
Let's do it.
He punched his own brother.
Why can I hit two of them together?
Why is the rev out?
All right.
Pin.
Turn around and look at this guy.
Stop looking at the other guy
and look at the guy fighting in the ring.
Oh, shit.
Get him.
Oh, my God.
That's a dangerous move.
All right.
Get in here.
And I need to get it.
I need to pin you.
His body is lifeless.
My God.
Okay.
Pin.
What's the pin button?
Yeah, I could use your help right now.
No, just take your time.
Don't worry.
I got both.
I pressed every single button.
What's he doing?
Pin.
Oh, my God.
That was a centimeter.
No excitement, Andy.
I tried to tag the partner.
It didn't work.
You're going for a no pin run.
I mean, I'm going for a maybe one more match
before we move on.
This is too much in my brain right now.
It's D-pad plus X.
There's a QTE on the health bar to cheat.
Wait, what did I do?
Oh, it's the iron cheek.
Okay.
Why am I against two people?
Oh, wait, I get it.
I see what you mean.
I have to time it.
I get it.
How do I do a finishing move?
How is this not exciting?
That's never not going to be funny.
That was sick.
You need to cheat, cheat, cheat, cheat.
What?
Of course, I bring out the weapon
and all of a sudden everybody thinks
the match is cool again.
Look at that.
I brought out the weapon.
I got 30% excitement meter.
Dude, you should hit the ref.
I think I did accidentally.
Huge power bomb.
Oh, hold on.
Grab him.
Hit him.
Stop winning.
You don't get up immediately from that shit.
Come on, dude.
Stop reversing that.
Why do they just cut to that guy?
All right, I got to get it.
He's going to get it.
He's got a weapon.
You like that dodge?
Reverse it.
Hit him.
Get him.
How are you doing a one count
after a move like that?
Shit, it's got to be it.
Why are you doing it like that every time?
Just pin him regular.
Pin him normally.
What is going on right now?
Look at his health.
I've had enough.
It's so stupid.
The ref is speaking Simlish.
He had to flex.
Reverse.
I can't hit him.
I need to win one by a pin.
Dude has zero health.
I just have to knock everybody out.
Oh my God.
That was a big excitement match.
All right, I'm moving on.
This was too much.
That was a great one though.
Two back to back great ones in a row.
Although I do want to see one thing though.
I want to see something.
Okay, versus four way tag team arena.
Arena.
I'm just checking to see if there's any other game modes, all right?
Like four way dance.
Yeah, I think that's it.
Very limited.
There's no Royal Rumble.
All right, it's time for you to vote.
Are we playing Obi-Wan or Cold Fear?
You get to vote.
Obi-Wan or Cold Fear?
Please vote.
I don't know.
We've been sticking on the Xbox games a little longer.
There's been some quality stuff here.
It's going to be close.
It's 43 to 57.
This could, I'm going to have to wait for a second.
Uh, Star Wars fans are losing out here, I think.
Cold Fear, I think, is running away with it.
Somebody said Obi-Wan is haha funny.
Cold Fear is a horror game.
Well, do you want a haha funny Star Wars game or do you want a horror game?
It's up to you.
Uh, looks like it's going to be Cold Fear.
Okay, now that's it.
That was close, but that's it.
45 to 55.
Close.
This game's on PC, isn't it?
One of those games that, I think it's on PC.
But it doesn't really work.
I feel like I tried to play this on PC.
Maybe not.
Did I?
Did I play this before?
Lights off.
Okay.
I'll do it.
That, just auto exposure.
It got brighter.
Hold on.
How did it get brighter?
Hold on a second.
It's because I have auto exposure on.
There we go.
That's better.
That's what it actually looks like in here.
Is this actually scary?
Or are you just memeing on me?
All right, let's go.
Extreme to be what?
All right, be quiet.
How do you look like you're in a part of Mexico in a Netflix series?
You can see how, like, sweaty my face is.
I'm not getting anything here.
Marcus.
Law.
Can you hear me?
Somebody, absolutely.
Is anybody alive?
I'll get me another asset of their product.
Anything we've got.
Anything.
Does this have tank controls?
It's a tank control game.
I'm taking it out of this.
This is the USS Ravenswood.
We arrived at the vicinity of the vessel
and will now initiate a search patrol and look for it.
Ravenswood out.
Yes, of course it has tank controls.
Are you serious?
This is a granny like?
I don't think it's a granny like.
It's tank controls.
God damn it.
It's a survival horror game between 1992 and 2003.
Of course.
What am I thinking?
Of course it's going to be a tank control game.
Am I out of my mind?
Uh, not tank controls, by the way.
Not tank controls.
Already, already much cooler.
My image running is not suspended thing.
Combat systems are better.
They also put their downed hummers
and potential source of ammo in mid-kits.
You use the butt of your rifle in close combat systems
and only do the gain the necessary distance
to adjust your aim.
Your opponents will attempt to immobilize you.
Do not simply empty your foot.
Drag out of them, refer to yourself,
and shoot at point blank range.
This is generally how I respect it.
Okay.
All right.
Legends of wrestling has burnt into the top of the screen
and it's ruining my immersion.
How do I run?
This is actually kind of cool.
Whoa.
This is not tank controls.
This actually seems like it's going to be pretty awesome.
What am I supposed to do?
Ammo.
There's a monster right there.
I have fully loaded ammo.
What was the point of coming in here?
Booth cam top right.
Um, what am I missing here?
Find the emergency radio code.
He should be on the front deck.
Okay.
Get out of the fucking way.
It's burning.
How do I get to the front of the deck?
What?
Where?
How do I get to the front deck?
Can I go in a door that I didn't see before?
It's too quiet now.
Guys, help me out here.
I don't understand what this game wants me to do.
It's right here.
That door.
I can't go into this door.
Go left?
Off to the side?
What the fuck is this?
I did it on purpose, but I had to see.
I had to do it though.
You know I had to.
Now I know where to go.
Get up there.
Do I actually have to fall and shimmy?
I went in a fucking circle.
You guys told me to do a go here.
Never mind.
That's where you started.
What do you mean never mind?
Everybody told me to go over there.
Everyone said go.
Go.
Oh, yeah, you're not gonna do the troll face and tell me.
No, you all got that wrong.
And so did I.
You all got that completely wrong.
All of you did.
Other side?
You walk past the stairs.
Yeah, we haven't played this game.
You guys all told me to go this way.
Dude, if the front of this fucking boat is this hard to find.
I'm sorry, but this is stupid.
You did it again?
The other side of the...
Do you want me to link you a walkthrough?
The left staircase.
This staircase right here.
This one right here.
Okay, I've been up here before.
I was already up here.
It just takes you to the other side of the boat.
What are you talking about?
Just go to customer service.
There's a door.
Why are you yelling?
Because it's really loud in my ears and I have to talk really loud to hear myself.
That door?
Dude, this door is just a scary jump scare for five seconds.
Look, nobody knows where I'm supposed to go.
This is not the front deck.
Go to the...
Try the opposite side of the boat from where you started.
Maybe.
I don't know.
This is...
I don't understand what it wants me to do.
I've been every single place.
Go to the poop deck.
That was actually kind of funny.
Go to the tip of the boat.
Believe it or not, you're not in the right area now.
Go find the area you're supposed to be in.
Over here?
Have I looked back here?
How do I reload?
I'm sorry, that was impossible.
I had to accidentally touch every piece of this boat.
The door is locked by an electrical system.
Damn thing's locked from the other side.
Maybe I can shoot this thing.
It's unlocked.
Get off!
Stop!
Stop it!
Why are you touching it?
What are you doing?
Hey.
I haven't saved it yet.
All right.
Now, I don't remember even where to go from there.
I can't believe you can get electrocuted by the thing.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
Steady.
Watch out.
You can use ammo.
Put it in your gun.
Yep.
Sounds great.
Excellent.
I can't wait.
I'm not going to shoot anything.
Why would there be this much ammo around here if there's no enemies?
It's over here.
Straight ahead.
The one tiny, teeny, tiny, itsy bitsy, not even the width of a human being.
This is what I needed to see.
Look.
It's not even the width of a human being.
And this is where I have to go down.
Who's this?
Who's this guy?
What happened?
Why did that happen?
He got killed by the waves last time because you took so long.
You got to be fucking kidding me.
How do I, how do I do this correctly?
What are you doing?
Shut up.
Shut it up.
Save.
How do you save?
Now what?
Okay.
He should be in the front.
I got to get to the front deck.
The tank control games are stupid.
They're dumb.
I have to say it to you.
That was, that took me way too long to, oh, okay, good.
You're a weenie.
I'm okay with that.
Yay.
Hey, hey.
Ah, what are you doing?
How am I supposed to see?
Where's the door?
It's a scary game now.
You're being too quiet.
I'm trying to focus.
Main deck.
This door ain't opening.
Save.
A note about the armory.
Smoking is forbidden.
Okay, so this is where, this is death.
That was Resident Evil typewriter music, right?
We need some comedic relief.
Can you put in a bit more effort, please?
Electrical boxes.
Yeah, I know.
Trust me.
I, I wish I had that info like 20 minutes ago when I got electrocuted to death.
It's locked.
Watch how much I'm using.
I ain't got an unlimited supply.
Why would I even take that?
I thought it was a health pack I could store in my inventory.
That's not what that was.
I had full health.
Have you been, I'm not going to read that.
A page from the, wait, I ain't reading all that.
Nevermind.
I wish I could just turn on, I wish it was a thing like a caveman filter
where it would just be like, this is like two or three pages of info.
And I can press like, I can hold start, select and press both the trigger buttons.
And it'll just give me one sentence.
Like, electrical box.
Danger.
Touch.
Do not.
Key.
Upper hallway.
Like, hallway 1B.
All right.
I just wish it would be, I would, I would pay extra for that.
Me die from electrical box.
Me leave key.
Hallway 1.
Door 1B.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
What kind of way of ship is this?
I'm going to need an electronic key to open this sucker up.
Shit.
You need a journalist mode?
That's not Eve.
Come on.
No, I just want like a condensed mode.
Okay.
Well, good thing I already killed the zombie.
I knew it was going to happen.
Thank God.
I got the key.
Can I do something about this?
What do I do about this?
Okay.
All right.
I need a handle for this door.
I have the upper deck key.
Let me just see if these doors, if any of these doors work after the next electrocution.
The damn thing's stuck.
There's too much water pressure.
I can't.
Upper deck.
It's unlocked.
I need a save point right now.
This is really bad.
Nothing even in here.
Really?
This is a stupid idea.
Shut up.
Shut up, idiot.
All right.
Please raise your hand if in five minutes you could get back to the front of the boat
where we were.
Good luck.
Because I have no, I have no idea.
Why did he do that?
Dude, just if you just waited five seconds.
Okay.
Should I check this door?
What was the point of that?
Front deck.
I think I made it to the front deck.
All burned.
Must be downstairs.
Where?
Page from the diary.
Boy, it doesn't hurt.
Infection.
Antidote needed.
Appreciate it.
The gun sounds, sounds like they're coming from a different room in the house.
It sounds like they're...
The thing's stuck.
Lansing?
Man.
I'll give it to him though.
This is pretty good.
This isn't, this ain't bad.
At least I found the code.
This isn't...
Find the radio room.
Good luck.
I have no idea.
Actually, I'm probably going to actually ask somebody to look that up.
And because this is, how am I ever going to find that from here?
Yeah, I'd like to save.
Weird pop-up.
But who am I, who's playing as who?
Oh, it's me.
Wait.
Oh, get out.
Where's the radio room?
Wait, the radio room is the first room at the very, the beginning of the entire thing, isn't it?
That's the radio room, isn't it?
That would be correct.
Yeah, I would imagine, right?
It has to be.
This game's...
I don't, I don't hate it.
It's fun.
It's fun enough.
I just wanted to see if those things actually explode.
Okay, this is where we have fun trying to go all the way back to the very beginning of the game.
To make the ship roll realistically, the developers had to write a completely new program
dubbed the Darkwave Editor to allow them to control movement on both vertical and horizontal axes.
They also used real physics to simulate the movement patterns of inanimate objects on the ship.
Through the random nature created by this, the player character required nine times
the amount of animations usually seen in third-person games.
Ultimately, the game contained more than nine hundred...
What else?
It's cool.
This is a good game.
Look, this came out...
I don't even know when, but like, this is cool.
Look at the swaying back and forth.
That's really cool.
Hey, we've played at least one other game in this genre of survival horror like this.
This is the only one that I wouldn't eat.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
It's the only one I would keep around.
I would eat the other ones, but no, I wouldn't eat the other ones.
It's just the only one that I wouldn't break.
I don't know.
I thought eat was a different...
was like a cooler way to say like throw away or like break.
No, we got to know who that is.
Damn.
What's this?
It looks like this will do the job.
Handwheel for the fish hold door.
Ooh, that was a health pack.
Dude, you're not beating the you're not human allegations.
Is he dead?
What the fuck?
I have to shoot their heads.
See, I told you I'm gonna ammo.
Thank God.
It's actually scary.
Where do I go from here?
I got, I got, we can turn around.
I can't.
All right.
Well, sorry.
How do I get out of here?
Holy shit.
You got to find the fish stick door.
You're so greasy.
Sound is so decent.
Is it?
Is it what did nobody tell me for like the last five hours?
No, it's not.
Not at all.
It's fine.
No, it's fine.
Sounds fine.
It's a stream.
Oh, I mean, yeah, I'm going to get like a little moisture all over my face.
I'm sitting here.
I've got an Xbox sauna in the room.
I've got a GTX 3090 going at firing at all cylinders.
I've got three monitors blaring light into my face.
I have a ring light up here blaring sauna like heat into my face.
You have a 3090?
Yes, I do.
All right.
How do I get out of here?
Oh, I remember this.
This part.
And then I'm close.
I'm really close.
Privileged streamer.
Oh, do not be mistaken.
I am a moron.
It sucked.
I didn't want this.
I did not want this card.
I paid so such a stupid price for this because there were no graphics cards.
There were none.
Do you remember a few years ago, two or two years ago?
They were bots just waiting and anytime like a 3080 or like a 3070 came up,
there was whole websites, there were whole discords and bots
dedicated to scooping them up at the second they were available.
I found one 3090 for a stupid price and I was like, I hate myself for doing this.
But I waited like probably four or five, six months.
I was like, what the fuck, man?
I want a new computer and I want a new graphics card.
I really didn't want to do it.
This door ain't opening.
You look like a wax model.
I wanted a 3090.
No, a 3080, but it just was never going to happen.
And I didn't want a 3070 because I got streaming.
It was like, I want to stream and be able to play games of good quality
and stream it and stuff.
So I was like, whatever.
Okay.
Where do I need to go from here?
It's back this way, isn't it?
Yeah.
And then where?
Here?
Where's the way out of here?
Is it this one?
No.
Okay.
This is the armory.
What was the price?
I don't remember, but it was, it had,
it was definitely more than a couple thousand dollars.
It was, it was, it was, it was, it was just like,
this is just her stomach ache thinking about it.
It was a stomach ache.
I got a stomach ache looking at it.
It was so bad.
I ended up getting a 3060 TI for two and a half times retail.
Can somebody help me here?
What brand of 3090?
I actually EVGA, maybe.
Then can somebody help me go down the stairs?
Thank you.
This is with the electricities down here.
It's unlocked.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
They stopped making Nvidia cards.
Yeah.
I mean, I, who even makes good graphics cards now?
You don't play games that require 3090.
Have a streaming requires a very powerful machine,
especially if you're going to do the GPU rendering.
Swag.
Ooh, boy.
Son of a bitch.
He's still alive.
That it?
But yeah, I don't, I typically do graphics cards every,
I want to say I usually wait at least two or three generations.
So if I have a 3090,
I'm probably going to wait for at least like the 6000,
like the 6090 or whatever, a 6080.
I usually wait two or three generations.
Before the 3090, I had a 1080.
So what's that?
Two, two generations, three, maybe.
Took a while for the 30 series to come out, didn't it?
The damn thing stuck.
What am I missing in here?
It's a latch.
And let me be really honest.
That 1080 lasted an incredibly long time.
And do I have permission to swag out?
Yeah, you don't have to wait.
I don't, I don't want to just buy shit just to buy it.
I'd rather just get what I pay for and use it
and get the best out of it whenever I can.
I don't buy a new phone every year.
That's kind of, I feel like that's an overkill.
I buy a new graphics card when I buy a new phone.
The damn thing stuck.
They happen at the same time.
So what am I, what?
Is it an item I didn't get?
Who buys a phone every year?
Didn't I get a fish key?
How come I can't use it here?
You got the radio room key.
I got a fish thing though.
It said like the fish thing.
Didn't it say that?
No.
So what's the point of coming down here?
Just to get scared and then leave?
Yeah, I don't need new phones.
I like the stuff that I have.
And I get, and then I, I don't know.
Cause then here's another thing, right?
You buy a phone every single year.
You're just going to have like a bunch of fucking phones.
And then what?
I mean, you can try to use one of those recycling programs.
I don't know.
I just, I don't want, I don't just don't want it.
I mean, you could just turn them in.
But I don't want a new, because when you get a new phone,
think about what happens when you get a new phone.
When you get a new phone, it's like you have to re,
your whole life has to reset.
Like you got to get all the applications
and you got to get all your contacts.
You got to, hey, you got to do this.
You got to do that.
You got to update this.
No, I don't want it.
I don't know.
I have, but I have works and it's fine.
It's up to date.
All right.
Where do I go from here?
Can you help just transfer your shit?
But I don't want a new phone every year.
They don't change very much.
I don't need new shit.
I, okay.
If you have like an iPhone, if you have an iPhone,
let's just say like an iPhone 12 right now,
right now, like you have an iPhone 12 or an iPhone, like 13.
What is going to happen next year where you,
you need to upgrade it?
What's a, when you go on Twitter,
when you're on Snapchat,
like the filter loads 0.2 seconds faster.
What is it?
What's the need for it?
USB-C.
I'm telling you, two or three years,
you'll get some new, there'll be some new development
to make it worthwhile.
You're just getting, it's like buying Madden every year.
It's like Madden 2021, 22, 23, 24.
You know, I just buy Madden 20 fucking 20
and I just update the rosters.
I don't, I don't need a new Madden.
Or I go into the character creator
and I just make the motherfuckers myself.
You know how long I played MVP baseball like 2004, 2005?
And I just made every single fucking major league
baseball player, I didn't care.
You can just replace them.
It takes a little bit of work, but it's worth it.
It's an iPhone rant.
No, no, I like phones.
Oh, wow, the Galaxy, like super cool, cool.
That's fucking cool.
But you don't need one every single year.
You know, you get a Galaxy, a Galaxy phone, sick.
That's fucking awesome.
You're going to get the Galaxy phone seven months later.
You already have the Galaxy 2.
You need the Galaxy 3.
You're already on a different goddamn,
you're in a goddamn nebula at that point.
You need another Galaxy.
It's the, you already have the 2.
You don't need the 3.
What does the 3 give you, the 2 that you're still,
you're in outer space already.
Somebody tell me where to go.
Somebody tell me what, like door to open?
Go down the hall, electrocution door is on the right.
I can hear it.
Where is it?
Am I going the right way?
Yeah, the right is the crew quarters.
Just use a guide.
This is the right way.
It's right through here, right?
It's right through here.
Yeah, no, it's not right.
I hate backtracking.
I just want, just go forward.
Or I need a map.
If there's backtracking, I need a map.
You're cheating already.
I feel like I'm so close, but so far away.
They just spawn randomly.
It's randomly generated spawns.
I just did not expect anybody to be right here.
Next game.
All right.
But I need to at least complete this part.
Draw your own map.
I can't.
From where I'm standing right now, where do I go?
Just help me.
I know you guys can help me.
Do whatever you want.
Up.
That was like a Twitch staff member.
So I'm going to listen to that.
Back and up.
How do I go up?
Just be yourself, little guy.
How do I get out of here?
Just help.
I'm playing Obi-Wan.
This is why I need a map.
Just give me a map.
Backtracking sucks without a map.
Hog, I made it up.
Literally nobody's played this game.
We can't help you.
Fuck, I just want to complete this one mission.
So I can say I got through chapter one of Cold Fear, at least.
How do I get out of here?
No, it's one of these seven or eight doors.
I have to take the disc out.
It's not this door.
Please, did you try the far left door?
This one, it's right here.
It's right here.
I remember we walked over here and I was like, oh, cool.
What the fuck?
Other left.
It's right here.
Don't give up.
My cat would be disappointed in you.
Fuck.
It's not that one.
It's not this one.
This one doesn't open.
So what door is it to get out of here?
Stop yelling at people.
It's that one.
Okay, I didn't have any guns.
Okay, I'm almost there.
And then after I turn this in, I'm going to play Obi-Wan.
Can we have a break?
You'll have a break in the time it takes me to take Obi-Wan out of its case
and put it into the disk tray.
It's about five minutes.
Why am I going back down?
What's happening now?
Why would it take you five minutes?
Time it.
You don't have a fucking head.
You can't do that.
I've been really on edge tonight.
I can't wait till we get to here.
This looks like a radio.
Apollo 7, Niner.
Can you hear me?
Who am I speaking to?
This thing's dead.
This is Hanson.
Everyone else is down.
Bloody hell.
Then I guess we're stuck with each other, Hanson,
but you're not the only survivor.
There's still a very dangerous man loose on that ship.
Colonel Dmitry Yusupov.
He needs to answer a few questions.
Round him up, and then we'll get you out of there.
Who's we?
Babe.
Okay.
Find that person.
Got it.
Why did they just turn me?
Wait, where am I?
All right, that was fun.
That was cold fear.
It is apparently January 15th, 2001,
and it's somehow this clock is wrong,
but not by very much, which is weird.
It's 2001.
I'm not alive yet.
What?
Pog, I'm not even alive yet.
All right, that was fun.
It's time for Obi-Wan.
I would rate this one.
I'd give this like a B plus on the tier list.
It was like a B.
I think there was some fun.
That was great.
Okay, so how long does it take to put a disc in and to load it up?
Here we go.
You ready?
Start timing right now.
Opening tray.
Grabbing Obi-Wan.
Opening Obi-Wan.
Taking Obi-Wan out of that.
If that was bionicle, I am going to be furious with you.
It wasn't.
Okay, remove about 15 seconds because of that.
Open going in.
Something wrong.
Obi-Wan going in.
Okay, very cool.
Opening it.
It's not ready yet.
It's been like a minute.
It's no, it hasn't.
We're not ready yet.
That was cute.
It's been over a minute.
It's we're not.
I'm okay.
Now, how long has it been since I did that?
Two, three minutes?
Jedi one.
Is there German noises?
What do you mean?
No, they're not.
How about, I'm so bad at making real names.
Darth, Darth Vader Jr.
I hate it.
Wait, aren't I playing as Obi-Wan?
Why would I need?
Why wouldn't I just be Obi-Wan?
This doesn't matter.
No, that's lame.
All right, here we go.
Real FMV cutscene.
Are we going to get a beep?
Yes, we are.
Obi-Wan, for thousands of years,
the Jedi Knights have served the Republic as defenders of peace
and justice throughout-
A little bit faster on the prompter, please.
The galaxy.
Young Padawan Obi-Wan Kenobi,
who studies to become a full-fledged Jedi Knight,
must prove himself to his master,
Qui-Gon Jinn,
and the Jedi Council.
As part of his ongoing training,
Obi-Wan is commissioned by Maze
when due to investigate the rise of a dangerous new threat
in the lower levels of Kurosan.
Hover over that X.
I know, I saw you do it.
You didn't click it, though.
Some of you did.
Some of you were just like,
I want to see this stupid fucking Star Wars game,
but I wish you would stop talking.
I got you, don't worry.
Everything has been quiet, Master.
Nothing unusual to report.
Are you sure my presence here is necessary?
Yes, Master.
There is an Elkhart transport station nearby.
Why are you holding him?
What?
I thought, aren't we like Batman?
We don't use the powers unless it's necessary?
What?
Why am I doing this?
He's screaming help.
That guy's got a golf club.
Why would you even come over here?
What's the mission?
What am I doing?
What is he doing?
Wait, what is it?
Why can you do this?
Why can I do this?
I missed everything.
It was just like, oh, I'll be one.
Go over this way, and that's all I heard.
I only have four attempts remaining.
I don't know what just happened.
You're supposed to be the good guy.
Well, what happened?
We need to see that again.
I need to fully focus on what's happening.
Okay.
Look out.
So what if I just don't?
Okay, that's enough.
I didn't want to kill that guy.
I think I was doing the right thing.
I just jumped.
This game is fucking pretty good.
This game is good.
I'm back to defend the order.
You ever see people do that shit?
I've seen videos.
If it's like, oh, look at somebody doing back handsprings.
This many.
Don't you?
You know what I'm talking about?
Like during like a musical,
they'll just kind of go across the screen.
It's like, doesn't that make you feel sick?
I would feel so awful after that.
You have to, you can only backflip only run.
Fine.
You wouldn't believe how hard it is to actually get that done.
Who needs help?
I don't know.
Is it safe to go down here?
Boss fight.
Front flip Andy.
Over here.
What?
How about?
Take this.
Did I get it?
Why can you do that?
Guys, I gotta be honest.
I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing right now.
New objective.
Clearly obstruction that is blocking the transport.
Are you a bad guy?
How do I do Jedi moves?
Like that.
Hold on.
I can pick that up.
Holy shit.
All right.
Transfer at council stop.
What's going on here?
Okay.
All right.
So go.
It's not.
Wait, you have a big health bar.
I suck.
Just needed a little extra time.
I think the disc was spinning.
We've identified the group that attacked you as the black.
According to the authorities, they are a group of wanted criminals who up to this point have
been involved in this sudden escalation in their criminal activity is most concerned.
I thought that was Yoda talking for a second.
I was like, what?
That's Yoda?
Yoda looked like ruffled up piece of paper.
I'm sorry, but he did.
Okay.
Hello.
Wait, the robot was a Sith?
Wait, what is this?
I'm sorry, but do not give anybody in our group a red lightsaber.
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you give him a red lightsaber?
Give him green.
Red is evil.
I'd be able to handle it though.
I would have a red lightsaber, but I would be good.
I could handle it.
I would have a red lightsaber and it'd be dark and mysterious,
but I would still be a good guy.
That's me.
Well, this is where this playthrough ends.
You can monitor the informant on your
What was with the early 2000s and having games have just hard fail stealth missions?
Is that what this is?
Did I lose?
It's not.
What did I do?
It is.
It's a fucking hard fail stealth mission and they were obsessed with these
back in the early 2000s.
Why?
Nobody wanted to do this.
Hard fail stealth missions are the worst of the worst.
The worst offender.
What?
No, I didn't even get to start them.
No, fuck you.
You don't get to sound the alarm.
Anybody come near this button, you're dead.
I'm just saying.
Nobody's pressing this.
You know what?
I can break it.
Fuck that, let's go.
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Just destroy all their alarm system shit and nobody can do anything.
That's gonna kill me.
No, it's not.
Infiltrate the lower levels.
I need a lower level.
What was that?
Holy shit, you got me.
Did I do it?
Is there anywhere lower to go?
Come here.
More!
He's bloodthirsty.
Minus two plus two right next to each other.
Rare.
They're really quiet.
Did I push him even further?
Wait, this could happen to me too.
One more layer.
Do not.
What kind of lightsaber would you have?
I would want like two small lightsabers and have them be like Raphael from Ninja Turtles.
No, I would want a throwing knives made out of lightsaber.
I would have an ice blue lightsaber.
Nice.
Nice, dude.
This game is kind of fun and I'll tell you why.
Because the right analog is swing.
Remember that trend back in the early 2000s where every single game had to have
movement with the right stick to attack and fight and stuff?
It actually works kind of well here.
It's kind of fun.
That's why I loved this as a kid.
When do I unlock a horse coat?
Imagine doing this actually stealth.
This would be such a boring mission.
It would take so long.
This is layer five.
This would be awful.
How would you even do this stealth?
That's it?
That didn't heal.
That was not even...
The health I just gained was just removed.
That's it?
That's so bad.
I'm okay.
Secret?
There are lightsaber helicopters?
What?
All right, I got the bar on the bottom right is 100% getting burned in.
Yep, because it's already there.
I have like three different games sort of burnt in.
This health and mana, whatever it is, is burnt in right now.
Thankfully, after the monitor was off for the whole evening, it was fine.
I'm not concerned about it.
I'm not worried about it.
How come they're talking like Lord of the Rings characters?
Back off, scum.
Man fell.
How come they...
Don't lose because I didn't save the game.
You spawned.
That's absolutely bullshit.
Where do I start from here before I freak out?
Where...
I don't know.
Where am I?
Is this bad?
I'm making it read the discs so hard right now.
Hey, hey boys, go!
What?
What's...
I spawned a secret.
Game just crashed.
Oh shit.
Who's this?
That was the person I was supposed to save.
Why were they just staring at me?
You killed the hostage.
Why wouldn't you be like,
Obi-Wan, over here, save me?
All right, I think I've had just about enough.
Something's wrong, by the way.
Something's wrong.
We lost contact.
How did you lose contact?
Does the guy have an earpiece?
What are you talking about?
Can't just...
Why is there no cutscene?
Why is...
Okay, I can't fuck this up again.
I can't fuck this up like a ninth time.
Just do it...
Get it right.
All right, I have a plan.
Why would they shoot him?
Whatever, just run.
And then when I get down to the second level,
I'm just gonna kill everybody.
And another thing.
Don't fuck it up.
Do not screw this up.
Take it easy.
Take it slow.
Full health.
Lightsaber out.
That means it's I am ready.
And let's go.
Why would they...
Shit.
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Why is he not sitting in the middle?
Where did the guy go?
You weren't even tied up this whole time?
Excuse me?
What do I...
What is this guy saying?
What are you saying?
Oh, don't come near me.
Don't come near me.
What do I do?
What do I have to do with this?
You need to die right now.
You speak perfect English?
Like very eloquently.
What's going on?
This game is just kind of chaos.
I kind of love it.
Man, some real bangers tonight.
I don't think there was a game that I didn't even slow at all.
These were all bangers.
All of them.
Damn Xbox.
Xbox, you got some good shit.
Uh-oh.
I can't wait to hear it.
Here it comes.
I could do that this whole time?
That's scary, isn't it?
Where do I go from here?
Kind of hard to hit, aren't I?
Where am I supposed to go?
This is not connected to anything, is it?
Oh.
Don't.
God damn it.
I'm okay.
These guys are so hard.
All right, get me out of here.
Don't even have to let him do it himself.
You did the Dark Souls PvP near the ledge thing.
We've all been there.
Sucks.
But surely the process of synthesizing cortosis into armor and weapons is far too
expensive and sophisticated by the Jinhal.
Those be involved.
It is well you succeeded in placing a tracker on their ship.
You're sending Master's Klo Koon and Eeth Koth to investigate.
We shall soon learn more.
Now to proceed to the trial arena, Obi-Wan.
You must be prepared.
Somebody said that Qui-Gon looks weird.
Like there's something off about Qui-Gon.
Yeah, something's off about Qui-Gon's model.
Another another Sith Lord robot by any chance.
Okay.
Hi.
So what do you want to teach me?
Now, okay, that hurt for real.
That hurt for real.
I just want to make sure you understand that hurt for real.
We're not using wooden swords.
What a lame fight.
He just killed me.
You killed Obi-Wan.
Sai Sith Tim gives no quarter.
When you defeat him, you will be ready.
You would like to try again, Padawan.
You're going to revive me?
Use force lightning?
That's what I would want more than anything.
I don't want a lightsaber.
I want to just be able to be like boom lightsaber.
That's hand to hand.
I don't know.
It hurt.
That was quite an intro.
You can't be serious.
Sai Sith Tim gives no quarter.
When you defeat him, you will be ready.
Stop jumping.
What the fuck?
I like to try again.
It's just mapped to A and I press A all the time.
I'll get it right now.
Where's like where's force bite?
Didn't expect that, did you?
Your little WWE entrance got interrupted, didn't it?
Stop.
It's hard.
Sai Sith Tim gives no quarter.
When you defeat him, you will be ready.
You would like to try again, Padawan.
Oh, I'm not a journalist.
And there are tons of very talented game journalists out there.
A lot of them, tons of them.
You don't know any.
What do you know?
I tried to just kill this guy.
That was not a sparring move.
I'm trying to bury this into your head.
I think I should end this game now.
Don't be a weirdo.
Sai Sith Tim gives no quarter.
When you defeat him, you will be ready.
You would like to try again, Padawan.
Say something.
I am focused.
Down on the right stick to parry.
Does that work?
Holding left trigger blocks.
I think that worked.
Why would they not tell me that?
They told me this guy was going to teach me shit.
And he didn't teach me anything.
He just walked in and started swinging at me.
In every other video game, it's like, let me show you something.
When I swing at you, what I want you to do is,
I want you to dodge to the left and press X, right?
Like, he just walked in here and attacked me.
The saber is most impressive.
The force is indeed strong in you, young Obi-Wan.
I get it.
But beware.
Obi-Wan, Master Tin, come quickly to the council chambers.
Something has happened to Master Plo Koon and Ith Koth.
It's a surprise birthday party.
This is what they did.
They got rid of me for a minute.
So they could set up the surprise birthday party.
Like, come quick, hurry, back to the chamber.
And it's going to be a big birthday cake.
Somebody said, who the fuck are all these people?
You must not consume very much Star Wars.
But I don't know either.
I know who Luke is.
I know who Darth Vader is.
I know who Qui-Gon Jinn is.
The situation has become very serious.
I know who the Ewoks are.
Where is he going?
He just walked in a circle.
You take the lead.
Go.
I want to see what Master Qui-Gon Jinn can do.
You're kind of not very good.
The families are going to be so sad.
Watch out for snipers.
Snipers.
Hurry Obi-Wan.
Ow.
Help.
Dad.
I know you probably need a dad.
But where's the...
I need some help.
Where did he go?
I got sniped out of the air.
All right.
I might...
It might be time to call it for tonight.
Another one or two attempts.
No help.
Can I reflect it back?
There are animals here.
That's cool looking.
Where's Qui-Gon?
I don't think I can kill them.
Honestly, where is he?
Where the hell?
This looks like a developer area.
I feel like I'm not supposed to be up here.
Snipers.
What?
Is he in a tree?
Fuck off.
You've got to be kidding me.
Oh.
Hurry up.
We have to...
Wait, did...
Now let us press the attack.
What happened?
Did I...
Did we get teleported back?
I don't want to lose Qui-Gon.
Dude, what are you doing down here?
Ow.
Stop.
I'm just...
I'm just going.
No.
Please.
I'm done.
This was fun.
This was a good one.
This was fun, but I don't want to do this anymore.
This level sucks.
This level is just like a big green plane.
And you just walk forward.
This is like a thousand G-Mod spawned sniper people.
This mission is...
One more.
Token.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm invincible.
What direction do I go?
This way?
That's water.
I'm dead.
I've survived my facility and discovered the source of their weapons technology.
We can still turn defeat into victory.
Can I do it?
I think it's beautiful.
Oh.
That works.
Master, I found the entrance to some kind of large mining complex.
Undoubtedly a cortosis mine.
I'll wait till there's some kind of manufacturing plant inside.
See what kind of evidence you could gather down there.
I'm not sure.
I'm done.
I'll see you later.
End of the stream run.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
One more.
We'll go out last when I try to run through it.
But do another game?
This is so much fun.
Don't worry.
We're doing this again.
Very soon.
One last run through.
How did I fall the second fucking time?
How did I fall the second time?
All right.
That's it.
That was fun.
A raid just came in too.
Well, thanks for the raid.
Welcome.
We are ending right this very moment.
That was console gaming weekend and there is...
So remember when I said the reason why I was doing this
is because I wanted to get through some of the ones
that I didn't do years ago?
Like, oh, I still have like 10 or so 15 games to play, right?
Well, I added 30, 40, 50 more.
So now instead of having 10 or 15 to do left,
there's like still like 25.
I added more.
We got caught on somebody.
There was two.
They were fun.
Hey, you get caught on them.
That's fine.
Do a DS scream.
I probably will eventually.
I want to do N64 as well.
Ratchet and Clank.
We are doing this again.
I'm just going to make another pile and just move stuff
we've already played to another section
so I don't accidentally do it again.
That was the Xbox.
That was Xbox Night number one.
Probably of at least three or four,
judging by how much is sitting in front of me here.
So the next time you will see me live,
this is where it's going to get interesting
because Ster and I are going to do the Elden Ring co-op
this coming weekend.
I think either the 21st or the 22nd,
I think is what we were thinking.
So that's happening this weekend.
So we'll probably just come back with the Xbox
in a couple days on Wednesday.
So we'll do Wednesday Xbox
and then maybe Friday Xbox
and then whenever Elden Ring happens.
So I'll see you on Wednesday.
See you in a couple days.
I'm just going to keep it all here.
I'm not going to tear it down or anything.
We'll just keep going.
Thanks for hanging out.
Thanks for watching there.
Um, it's a ton of fun.
I love doing this.
We talked about it last night,
but one of the big reasons why it's so much fun to do this
is because you can just move on
or I play it for three or four hours.
You just kind of never know what you're going to get.
But yeah, and then the Elden Ring co-op stuff.
I don't know if we're going to do that
for more than a couple of days.
I can't imagine that's going to be something that happens.
I mean, we're going to do randomizer co-op.
It's going to be a mess.
But oh, I love tweet.
Thanks for the raid.
I think there were a couple of raids tonight that I missed.
I was too in it.
But if you just came from Love Tweed's stream,
thanks for rating.
Sorry that we're turning it off immediately after you get here.
But appreciate it.
Vinny's playing a Star Wars game right now, too.
What is Vinny doing?
Let's see.
Star Wars Dark Forces.
See if it's as good as Obi-Wan.
All right.
Yeah, we'll raid Vinny.
We haven't raided anybody in a long time.
So let's raid Vinny.
It's been at least a few weeks,
at least a couple of weeks.
Go say hello to Vinny playing Star Wars Dark Forces mod.
Very cool.
Give my best.
And I'll see you later.
See you Wednesday.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Call your mother.
See you later.
Oh, I'm not muted.