So we're having a competition who can make the worst one.
Yes, the competition here is whoever makes the uglier person wins.
And in the comment section, please take your vote.
Whoever makes the ugliest, worst, disgusting character wins the hundred bucks.
Why is it always a hundred bucks?
Because it is a hundred bucks.
Why do I... Can I like plug my gamepad in? This is awful. This is horrendous.
Yes, that looks like it healed nicely.
Ow! My fucking head!
I just made myself an instant migration!
Okay, skip, skip this. Get out of here.
Everything's going black for a second. Oh my... Where are you?
What is going on? What are you?
Look how my sideburns match my beard.
Yeah, look real close. Look real close. I'm Schmiegel.
You really are. You got boobs, dude.
Okay, so in the comment section, go ahead and vote.
Who has the ugliest character?
Hey Jerma, wanna have a lot of fun?
Have fun.
What the hell are you doing?
Have fun. I'm never unpausing it.
Look at all your options.
Look at all the things you get to do. I'm leaving. Bye.
I'm done. Bye.
We've got dumb shit to do.
Is he really gone?
Star. What?
Oh, we have to go this way. This way. Get back in quick.
Before the cops show up.
This helicopter is really close to the ground.
Look at this helicopter. Look how close to the ground this is.
I'm wedged in.
Are you dead right now? Did you die?
No, are you dead?
No, I'm backing up and going forward. I think this guy is dead on my lap.
Where are you? Just get in the car.
Just get in the car.
Now I'm dead.
You're telling me the helicopter that was five feet off the ground crashed?
I got you. Revive your dead homie.
You're ugly. I don't want you to revive me.
Will you please get in the car?
You get in the car.
Before we can make our daring escape.
Or can we?
This guy right here.
I forgot you could do that in this game.
Come with me.
Star, you want to play a game called throw the guy at you?
What?
How do you do that?
You didn't need to kill them.
Fairly certain I just ruined everything.
Pretty sure I just ruined everything.
How do you buy shit? What do you fucking stop?
What?
That guy went through the windshield backwards.
Gas station.
Gas station where?
No, dude.
We needed to get gas.
Let's go. Fill her up, sweetie.
How do you blow up the same gas station twice?
I don't understand.
I think we got him.
I think we got him. What is this guy doing?
You gotta revive your homies, okay?
Calm down and revive your homies.
I can hear you clicking.
Yeah, you get him. You get him.
No, you get my guy.
What?
Can I do that again?
I have to see if that works again.
Wait, how do you?
You have to have a gun out.
Come here.
Hold on, I'm trying to get a hold of somebody.
No, you don't need a hostage.
Yes, I want you to hit both of us.
Fucking ass.
That's vicious.
So you hold control now?
Hold it.
You have to like count down.
Oh my god, there's another fucking fire alarm in this building.
I'll see you later.
Hopefully Star is okay.