Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Soldier with the Default Rocket Launcher, the Conqueror, the recently buffed Conqueror, and the Escape Plan.
And this is also gonna be a coffee commentary of Justice and Doom. Just wanna let you know beforehand, in one, a two, a three, that's how many licks it takes to get to the bottom of a Pyro Pop.
So let's keep going here with this coffee commentary.
Okay, so a coffee commentary is when I just hit record, and I just go after drinking a couple coffees, and I'm just crazy and out of my mind.
Let's go! So playing on Coldfront again with the Soldier, and this is a very underplayed map.
I wish I could play on this a lot more often, but every time I do the server browser, it seems like there's only four, or maybe even two, that are in the entire server browser, which is unfortunate.
But I know it's a five control point map, and they take ages on public games, because they just go back and forth.
It's always just a stalemate. It's always just a stale, smelly fishmate.
So that's what I gotta say about Coldfront. No, I'm lying. I actually have more to say about Coldfront.
Any time I hear the word Coldfront or the map or whatever, I always just think of some weatherman just standing in front of the green screen just going,
Yep, today there's gonna be a Coldfront coming down from the northwest section coming down to the northeast, and it's just absolutely gonna wreck your house, and you're all gonna die.
I've never heard a weatherman say that, but he could. It might be one day a weatherman's gonna come on the screen and just go,
Ladies and gentlemen, there's a giant tornado coming straight for your house. Please run! And we're all gonna run, and hopefully we all survive.
Also, why does this guy have a blue face? I've been realizing this right now. Why did I draw him with a blue face?
What is he, Grover from Sesame Street? Like, what is this guy? It's like Grover and Bozo the Clown had a child, and there he is on the screen for you.
I promise, I'm so bad at drawing, I will never draw anything ever again.
So, soldier, Coldfront killed a couple people, a soldier and a scout.
This is a great place to hang out as a soldier, because so many people just stuff down this left side, or right side if you're on the blue team.
It's just crazy, so many people just filter into that little area, and plus you have this little gate right here to protect yourself if somebody comes after you.
Like there, I just got a two-piece because of this gate.
And oh, my HUD, I keep seeing the numbers pop up. I keep forgetting to do this, and I really am sorry.
I am gonna put my HUD in the description of every Team Fortress video now.
It's actually stars. He took KN, the KN Garmin HUD combination, and he made it his own. He did the little things, too, and he tweaked it.
But it's gonna be in the description of my videos. You can get it from his channel page, too.
But that's the HUD. That's the big hubbub of the HUD.
So here's my favorite part of the whole video. I got nowhere to go, so I just...
I get shot right in the back by a sniper. If I had stood up and tried to go around that gate, that sentry would have lit up my entire Christmas tree, and I would have died instantly.
But we're gonna transition here. This is a second gameplay, a one-life gameplay. Both of these are one-life, back-to-back.
This is defending the final point on Coldfront, and I think... I don't remember if we push forward or not.
I think we do, but my brain is swish-cheese, so sometimes I forget things, and this is something I absolutely forgot.
So we're either gonna push up or we're not gonna push up, which is pretty much the outcome of any video you watch on Team Fortress.
Hey, you're either gonna lose or you're gonna win. Which one is it gonna be?
So let's take on this soldier right now. Me and you. Here we go, buddy. One, two, rocket. Scott, you landed. Let's do it.
And miss. And just shoot 150 rockets at him and miss every time. And the Pyro got him, though, so that's a good thing. Good job, Pyro. You are my friend.
Blowing the horn. Let's see what I can do with this now. I'm just gonna shellcast. I have no idea what's gonna happen.
So, turning this corner, seeing a couple friendlies running away from the front line. Something to miss must be happening.
Crit rocket, shooting this guy. That's actually a spy, and here's a spy tip for you. If you're gonna play as a medic, I'm sorry. If you're gonna disguise as a medic, you want to make sure you want to do one very important thing.
Don't run around with a syringe gun. Change to the Bonesaw or the Medigun, because if you run around with a syringe gun, everyone's gonna think you're a spy, and everyone's gonna know you're a spy because you're actually running around not healing anybody.
So please use that as a tip and killing that medic in the meantime, in the process.
But I'll slow it down for you. If you're gonna play as a spy, make sure when you're disguising as a medic, pull out the Medigun, switch to your secondary and hit B, because then at least you're running around with the Medigun, and you look like you're doing something medic-y.
Not shooting people with a syringe gun or something. It looks a little less suspicious.
Coming down to one minute left in this coffee commentary. Watching this heavy explode makes me sad, but that's kind of funny at the same time.
Anytime anyone explodes in this game, it's actually pretty funny.
But in the last 40 seconds I have, I want to say one thing. The Conqueror is really, really good now. They made it so much better, it takes like no time at all to charge this thing.
The health it gives back is not really that spectacular, but the amount of times you can do it in such a short duration, it makes it worth it.
That's gonna wrap things up here, guys. Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And if you like this video, go ahead and throw me a like, because it really does help spread the infection of the germs. Help spread the infection.
But yeah, guys, of course, I will see you guys all next time, and take care, everybody.