Hey guys, how are you? Yeah, sorry for starting like 20 minutes late here. I was not in the
house. I had some last-minute errands that I had to do. I had to take care of them. They kind of
popped up and I was like, well, these have to get done. So that's why I'm about 20 minutes late,
but we're here. Hope you had a good Memorial Day. Hope you had a good weekend. I did see you
a couple days ago, but you know, hope you're doing well. I have to start changing my
diet and life and everything here. Those of you that don't know, I mean, I've talked about a few
times. I'm going in for like a full colonoscopy at the end of this weekend here and I have like
a lot of foods that are off limits as of tonight, I think. So I have to eat like baby
food for like a couple days before. So I don't know. That's not supposed to be there yet.
I'm not supposed to hear that yet. I can still eat solid food. I just can't eat anything with
seeds. Anything that has red, blue, or purple coloring. There's a lot of things I'm not... I
can't... I don't think I have milk anymore, like any dairy, I don't think, for the next like
three or four days. I'm not gonna be really on top of this because if you fuck up,
you can't do the procedure. If you have a glass of milk like the day before your exam,
or you have like some beans like two days before your exam, you have to reschedule it. You can't
do it. So I have to like really, really be on top of this. I'm gonna be eating jello for the
next three days. But we're not without wasting any more time because we are a little bit
late here. We're gonna do salmon max. I am going to restart the episode. This is episode
three. This is season two, episode three. Last time we tried this, I was having all kinds of
internet problems and the first... we got like maybe 15, 20 minutes into the episode
and I couldn't really pay attention to it. It was... the frames are dropping. It was
irritating. I couldn't really focus on what was going on. So we're just gonna restart it.
I'm just gonna restart the episode and then go from there because I think we would not
even like 10 to 15 minutes into it. So those of you that are wondering what we're doing
for the next few days. We came up with potentially playing Heroes of Might and Magic tomorrow.
I think I want to do it. I think it depends. That's one of those stream ideas that I have
no idea if people are gonna like that or not. It could be great but it also could be...
who knows? I'm willing to give it a shot. Layers of Fear 2 came out but I also heard
that Layers of Fear 2 is not very good. Isn't it getting really bad reviews? Yeah, yeah. I heard
it's just like really not... it's not good at all. Even better. Right, Layers of Fear 2 like
kind of isn't that good. Even more of a reason to play it all and beat the game, right?
That's the worst thing like we just said. Neither was Days Gone and I still play that.
I know that's gonna forever be something that's held over my head forever. No matter what
video game or whatever stream that I decide to do, right? Oh well, I'm thinking about doing this.
I'm not sure if I want to do that though. You might be... you might bore you guys a little.
You play Days Gone for a whole stream. It's like, fuck. You know, I did do that. I did.
Okay, we'll give it a try. Okay, fine. Nothing can be as bad as Days Gone. And Days
Gone wasn't even a bad game. It was just a bad game. All right, here we go. Starting a
new game. We're gonna do five community subs from Great Niddy and Frick Club. I think I'm
saying that right for the first time in like 5,000 gifted subs. Thank you so much for the five
community subs. It wasn't a bad game. LaserFear 2... LaserFear 1 was not good either. Well,
we'll see. I'm completely open. I'm gonna get a little like weird over the next few days too
because I'm gonna try to... I know that like two days before the colonoscopy, like I can't
eat. So I might have to do short streams over the next... like not this one, or you know,
I'm talking like in a couple days. We might have to short them up a little bit because
I might not have enough energy. Because if I don't eat, I become like a monster.
It's fucking Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Burger King. You understand? I go nut. We're gonna restart
episode three. No, you get your death.
I remember this guy.
After you are dead.
Well, it looks like this is it little buddy. There are references that I can make, but I can't
because I don't want to like talk about like story stuff. My wallet? I can't even remember
how we got here. How should I say it? Remember, we were back in the office just back from
Easter Island. That's not a spoiler for anything, is it? Oh, all right. Somebody
might accuse me of spoilers. I can't say anything. Wait, I gotta use my gun. My voice
is low. You know what? You're right. It is. My voice is low. Thank you. That should be a
little bit better. I mean, you give me like a crosshair and I'll say one, two, three,
get count to one. Ready? One. I almost had it. Have I beat this game? We did
season one. We're in the middle of season two. Doesn't being high priest of Easter
Island and president violate the separation of church and state?
Oh, I remember this part. Crazy frog. What's going on? That's my favorite part
of the whole song. That's the only part that I like.
Mm-hmm.
Words. They're coming from someplace called the zombie factory. You wander
around aimlessly and see what you can turn up. I mean, zombie attack. I'll
actually figure out where they're coming from. All right. So we did do
this before, but in the middle of every other dialogue. Yeah, I just
don't understand how these companies are allowed to do this. You know, I
should get, I think I'm gonna like figure out how to like, I'm gonna have
to turn the router off. So, you know, let's actually enjoy the episode. And
let me, I remember I went this game. Survived being thrown clear. Did this
shit. Let me do this again. Not nearly as surprised as the guy it
landed on. Ready? Pretty accurate. All right. This joke is going on long
enough. It's time to leave. He's too good. All right. For real this time.
We got a bomb. One, two, three. Oh, I took a ton out of me. I'm fucking tired,
man. Oh my God. That took like all of my brain power. I'm gonna, I gotta go.
Uh, yeah. Thanks for watching. I can only do like one big thing before I
like strike it tired and the streams have to kind of turn off. So, um,
thank you. Appreciate it. Not even the joke. That does happen though. If
you were here on the last stream, I like went crazy. I was like, I've
stepped on the gas for two and a half straight hours and then I was like,
I'm tired. It happens. All right. Let's get, let's see what this
happens. Isn't that cute, Max? The rats have set up their own little
casino. Where's Jimmy Tootie? I want to show him a new sleeper hold,
I learned. The boss is busy. He can't be too busy for us. We're the
ones who gave him his big break. Not to mention various smaller
fractures and sprains. The boss is busy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All
right. So remember if we can get, we get like the Stein. Remember
this. So the zombies drink beer, uh, flu perhaps. Zombies drink beer.
The zombies beer. You don't pick up the beer Stein. All
right. I remember. Don't we go get an antenna for the car?
Yeah, we do over here. Let's go get that because I remember it.
You have to like throw the papers out, right? You do paper boy.
I am cops. Do you know? Don't spoil it.
What? No, not really. Well, those days are over. Welcome to a new
type of internet access. So simple. Even a zombie could use it.
Cox. Yeah, I'm getting deja vu. Do you know anything about a
place called the zombie factory processing? We have gathered
extensive marketing data on zombies. Zombies need an easier,
less expensive way to access the internet. That's why we
developed Stuttgart online for the greatest concentration of
newly active zombies. Stuttgart Germany. This is the
last end of that stream. Yeah. The crashing internet.
We do not know. My internet sucks. I turned it. I was a
zombie. I turned into a zombie. When I'm done yammering,
remind me, we got to drive to Stuttgart quick like a
zombie. Drive to Stuttgart. Right. Forgot it already.
Okay. What happened to bluster blaster? There was a
processing accident while developing our latest
invention. I'm fine, Sam. Haddock is the best kind of
fish. I'm fine, Sam. Haddock is pretty good. We regret any inconveniences this may have caused.
I'm fine, Sam. Thanks for asking. Is the internet
better? That is to be determined. Because we've seen essentially like
1% downtime every stream since they fixed it in
quotes. So who knows? We it's better, but I
don't know if it's fixed, unfortunately. But who know?
I'm just gonna let it fly, right? We just want to pimp our
car. We no longer offer car upgrades. Our income has been lower than previously
forecast. But this neighborhood has the highest
accident rate in five states. We have spent a lot of this year out of
town, Max. So we've devoted our resources to
developing the ultimate online experience.
Shit out of luck, right? You're selling the internet to
zombies? Not just the internet, but much much more.
From trivia to music, lifestyles to death styles,
and inventive new recipes for brains. My mother says that.
From mere online zombie destinations. If you guys ever used the internet in
front of your parents, open it next time. If you have
like, you know, you know, if you have like a
parents that use the internet or they don't really use it that often,
you open up a web page and just browse. They freak out.
Something like, okay, click that, click that, drag down, get that, open
that tab, scroll, you're going too fast. And then when it stops loading,
if you have like a, you know, internet slow or something, you say you open
too many windows and you're clicking so fast. It's you're clogging it up.
That's my dad. Yeah, that's everybody's parents.
And then if you misclick, let's say you click and you click, oh fuck, I
didn't mean to. I'm gonna hit the back button.
See? It's like, then they're justified in saying that you're
going too fast. After all this time, you are not offering
any car upgrades. None at all. We regret the inconvenience.
There's a new invention. It is much too dangerous. Intrigued? Go on.
It's the super high powered antenna for wireless internet access while
on the road. There are problems. Using it could result in catastrophic
electrical failure and spontaneous explosion of your vehicle.
We see. And what are the problems? Can you guys fix the blaster blaster?
Can you guys fix blaster blaster? They had me fixed before they
brought me home. Okay, but we want that in. We'll take
that super high powered antenna. We spent our entire savings on
development. We can only give it to you if you help us market SOL.
Take the provided CD launcher and use it to give installation discs to
zombies. I told my dad to press shift five times. They got sticky keys.
And we love shooting things. They like wearing short pants.
Would you like to begin driving now? Affirmative. Initiating augmented
reality driving sequence. Alright, so it was right click,
right? You may not miss any. Remember that you can now drive
using a computer keyboard in addition to your mouse.
Okay, ready? I'm not gonna miss one. Please deliver the magic of
ready? Let's not miss one. Let me let me show you why I have a twitch channel.
Okay, I need to prove it sometime. You want to strafe. I call this
I call this move the sway, right? When you're playing as the scout,
you hit A and D. Hold on. No, that's three,
two, one. Hey guys, welcome to the video. Three,
two, one. Hey guys, welcome to the video. Here I'm going to try to get
every single one without missing. Hey, three, two, one. Hey guys,
welcome to editing fixes every problem. My name is Jerma. So if you're wondering,
I can go into a server and lose 500 times and then
win one time and show you that I'm really good at something
because you didn't see the 499 times. So what you want to do? What
I think you guys should be doing? Wait, did I lose?
I'm lacking the sound of this more and more.
Please demonstrate the operation of the antenna to our big winner.
Not too late. I don't want to see the bright light again.
Very well, you get to figure it out for yourself.
All right, so we have this antenna. We've got an antenna
and okay, three, two, one. So we got an antenna.
What was wrong with the first one? I don't know. I'm second-guessing my
video. Okay, let's go into Bosco's. You
can't, right? It's closed. Bosco went into hiding when we
convinced him. Cut. Remember back when I was doing
YouTube? I thought like a funny video would be to
cut every word. Try to have one of those videos where it was like an
IRL, let's talk to the camera videos and cut every word
and try to have it flow together so it would be, it would make sense. But
do you understand how long that takes? For me to get like a six-minute
vlog where every word is a new cut and I'm not talking like cut
after every word's in it and I'll just make it look like I cut it. No, I'm
talking like say individual words and make like a fucking Frankenstein.
All right, so let's take a look at the zombies. I've got the antenna.
All right, quick question. No, I don't have the antenna.
Can I put the antenna in the beer stein? I just want to try it.
Wow, the cops actually installed something well for once.
Just record the lines and let's see. I also was thinking about, but then I
decided against this. This is gonna be one of my like
fucking weirdo, like I disappear for three weeks and then like a video
comes up randomly after like a month. I was going to, you guys are thinking
fucking crazy. I was gonna read like 95% of every
word in the dictionary and just upload it, but then I
was like, ah, I probably shouldn't do that because
like then, oh, I bet people could like make me say anything.
Oh, that's probably a bad idea. That's not a good idea.
You would have a never-ending supply of every word.
All right, let me try this. Let me get, give me the antenna.
We didn't go into Sybil. Well, actually, I did go into Sybil last time.
The cops actually installed something well for once. I won't be able to just
pull it off. I did the green screen. Yeah, but the
green screen was, I mean, this would be like probably
20 uploads of like 10-hour videos. I'm telling you, I'm fucking insane. Wait,
I can't take it off? This parking meter could, wait, am I just
being dumb and building the same wall and taking the same
wall up in Minecraft? The cops actually installed something
well for once. I won't be able to just pull it off.
Okay, so I was just building the same wall and deleting the same wall in
Minecraft while talking. I've done that before a bunch of
times. All right, so let's go into Sybil's because we didn't really get
to do that last time. This is what happens when I like talk.
I just like can't do anything else. I remember
like years later after I uploaded those Minecraft videos, MLC Stealth was
like, hey dude, do you know that like 12 minutes of that video was
you building the same wall while you were talking?
I'm out of applications right now, so
let's just be friends. Sure. I can't help it.
I'm sure I don't know to whom you are referring.
So, Mr. Mollman.
Sorry, Harry. Tell me more about you. Well, let me see.
Interesting things about me. This is where we left last time. Okay,
so we've got a photo of Abe Lincoln. We got the, let's talk to Harry.
Harry Mollman, last time we saw you, you were... Yeah, yeah, on the moon.
What's all this I keep hearing about zombie attacks? Have you been outside?
You boys have guns, right? Are we just not getting through to these people?
Yeah, we're really not that complicated, Harry.
How's the suitor business? How are things going with you and Sybil? Oh, she's
playing hard to get, but women have a hard time
resisting my charms. Oh, she'll grow to love me.
Yes, she will. Can we fold this guy like up on the sofa? I don't like, I don't
want to be here anymore. Can I just like, can I just close
the George Foreman grill right now and just leave?
I hate to break it to you, Harry, but Sybil's not that into you.
She's more into the whole hard rock scene. Just wait till she gets a load
of my oboe. Was that clumsy innuendo or a
pathetic attempt to sound cool? Both. Do you remember the type of dude to
walk up the stairs one stair at a time? Actually,
I go up two stairs at a time. I go up two steps at a time.
I'm sorry, that literally was one random comment right there. I have to
respond to this. My grandfather does it, my father
does it, and I do it. We go up two steps
at once. We don't go up one step at a time. I remember I got like
called out for this when I was in, when I was in college. I remember going up
two to three steps at a time sometimes,
and this person was just like, what are you doing? I'm like, what?
Why are you doing that? I just, that's what I do. So I'm gonna have to correct
that. I'm sorry. Do you know anything about a zombie
factory? I'm not gonna let that happen. I'm not gonna let somebody make something up about me.
No, it's a factory that makes zombies. Inconceivable!
That's like making hate, and evil, and awfulness.
So you're saying you don't like zombies. Okay.
What have you got against zombies? Disgusting creatures.
They're always breaking things. Zombies are why we can't have nice things.
We need breaking things. The reason you don't like zombies is that they
break things? Yes! Stupid clumsy undead. And that
bothers you more than the brain-eating? They're hell on knickknacks.
Okay. Do you really think you have a chance with Sybil?
I'm in it to win it!
He's saying that's when you crawl up the stairs. Have you ever seen a dog
run upstairs? Four hands and legs. Four legs.
They fly up and down stairs. They go up in like less than two seconds.
Have you seen a dog run up fucking stairs? It's like
because they're using four, while you're using two. Get down
on... how do you think I do it? Hands. One step.
You know, let's say you have your left foot on like the bottom.
Your right foot is on the second step. Left hand on step number four.
Right hand on step number three. You have... it's almost like um
it's like doing the worm. You have to like do the worm up the stairs as hard
as you can. And you'll get up there in less than
fucking two seconds. Start betting people. Hey dude bitch I
can get up those stairs in less than a second.
Shut the fuck up. I bet you won bitcoin. Oh yeah you're on man.
Alright. And then you fucking go down on all fours and do like a worgen
run up the stairs and the guy owes you one fucking bitcoin.
Do you really think you have a chance with Sybil? I'm in it
to win it. Are you still into prismatology?
Oh no. People are going to try that and get hurt. I wasn't that into it in the
first place. You just relocated to the moon for it.
Well, think how great Dozen looks on a resume. No, no, no. I have a
disclaimer at the beginning of every stream that
uh this is comedy. Everything that you see in here
is comedy. Don't try this comedy at home.
It's on it's a disclaimer every single stream. Do not try this comedy at home.
See you later Harry. Zombie! What gives Sybil?
Did you start your dating service again? The street is supposed to be funny.
All my clients are applying for dates with me.
Um as kind of officers of the law we have to point out that that's kind of
illegal. Does that mean we can shoot her to
regain health points or something? Jesus. What? No. Get your heads out of the
gutter. It's not like that. I'm looking for my soul mate.
Um I hope it's not that guy. How are you going to find your soul mate?
Not by jumping in with the first reanimated statue that comes along.
That's for sure. I've got the initial screening
and then rigorous interviews and finally
the soul mate. Oh the soul mater right. I want it.
What does the soul mater do? Not sure. I want it in an online auction and
the instructions are all in Sanskrit. Something about ripping souls from across
the plains to reunite them with corruptible mortal vessels.
How much money do you think? Doesn't that sound romantic? Okay so. I could just die.
I have a Starbucks here and I'm drinking out of a straw.
Like I'm like what do you think I could like get for an auction for the
straw? Would I be able to get more than
ten dollars for this straw? One bitcoin. 150?
I think somebody would just be insane and it would be like a like a thousand
dollar joke to somebody. And then I would buy a thousand more
straws and do it again and get a thousand more dollars
a thousand more times. I think I'm all I need is just
that's all I need. Sure you don't need help with that soul mater Sybil?
If you're not married by now there's not much time left.
There's plenty of time. I still have a lot of data to analyze while I
figure out how the soul mater works. Have you had a lot of applicants?
A few. If you know anybody, anybody else of course,
send them my way. A lot of these guys have no chance
but I'm still interviewing them to be polite.
Speaking of which, what kind of movies do you like Harry?
No I don't go to the movies that much because of my stigmatism.
I hear that. Yeah I gotta sit at the front row in a movie theater guys
unfortunately. Do you know anything about a place
called the zombie factory? I'm the one guy that sits in the front row.
I can't see. Irrational fear of zombies. Interesting.
But yes I did get an email about something like that from some friends
in Europe. Can we talk for a second about this?
Rights for the undead thing. I can't remember where exactly.
Can we talk for a second just for a second about this? I know people want
I know we get to like move on and play the game but like I need to
talk to you about this. This is very important.
That's a lot of no's.
All right fine fine never mind never mind.
Okay you know what you know are you sure?
I'm gonna do it anyway you know. Remember to lock up tonight
so the zombies can't get in. Get in? There are zombies right outside.
I'm not going to lock my door. This is a public place and they have the
right to peacefully assemble just like
anyone else. Okay what about Abe? Don't you want to give Abe another
chance? Abe who? You were telling me more about
yourself Harry. I was detailing my various
prescriptions and inhalers if I remember correctly.
All right. How can you afford to keep your shop simple? Let's see let's get
some clues. I'm still getting residuals from when
I was queen of Canada. The new location is a lot better for
me. Not as nice as Edmonton with its
temperate summers and outstanding cost of living.
Tell us. Wait you guys flipped really well very quickly on this.
Good luck finding your soul mate. This has nothing to do with luck Sam.
Is that merchandise? Yeah we got t-shirts. Technology. T-shirts.
I was gonna do louder but I thought my voice was gonna crack so I panicked
and stopped halfway through. Notice how I did two t-shirts because
I was gonna go t-shirts t-shirts but I thought it was gonna be
t-shirt and it would have been really embarrassing so I
fucking immediately stopped. All right. Can we drive around with this
car now? Does that antenna do anything?
Well I can't go in here. The lucky vermin. The lucky vermin.
Oh now showing Robert Goulet's hamster.
What was I gonna say? I was just gonna say why does the movie theater have
like even the first five rows? You know what I mean? Pull it back
and like add the rows up top and like a balcony. Nobody sits in those
rows. That was it. I was gonna talk a lot about it. I was gonna talk about how you
could have like a performer there before the movie.
You guys would have thought it was really funny. Let's go to Stuttgart.
Like pull back the first five or six rows and before the movie starts
hire like a circus performer to like fucking juggle. I don't know.
Instead of those previews that nobody fucking. You've already seen the
previews on YouTube like three days ago.
I am looking forward to when the previews are gone
and we don't have to watch them anymore. Hey look there's a gaggle of zombies
politely lining up outside. Oh classy. Yeah Europeans make the most refined
undead. This must be the place. Yeah and then
they do like all the commercials and stuff. It's like
dude I paid like a ton. I paid like fucking
15 bucks to watch this movie and like 20.
I have it's like a 40 to 50 dollar bill for two people to go to the
movie and get like popcorn and shit. Because the movies are like the
airlines. I wonder why did that happen?
Yeah you're in and by the way everything is uh times 10 money
and you can't bring anything in here. Welcome to the airport.
Why the fuck is that? I don't understand why that happened. That makes
no sense. Why is a drink like seven dollars at
the movie theater? It's just makes it's just like this weird fucking
wormhole you go into where everything's just 10 times more expensive.
For no reason. Burger Boy used to bring in cheeseburgers. I mean we
would go to fucking McDonald's and he would get like six McDoubles
and he would just keep it in a jacket and we would eat it. It was better than
popcorn. But anyways get rid of the previews
before the movies. Hire a fucking performer hire like a
stand-up comedian. Imagine if you had like instead of 20
minutes of previews there was like a 15 minute like
act in front of you. A guy like doing like jokes and stuff.
You could like tip him. Maybe better than watching. Yeah like the same like
Coca-Cola commercial you've seen a hundred times.
Stand aside undead. We have to get inside. Yeah go film a music video or
something. Typical zombies with their overinflated
sense of entitlement. Well you wouldn't have a stand-up
comic out there before like a like a drama or like a
horror movie. It would be there'd be different things
for different movies. If you were going to see a Will
Farrell movie they'd have like a fucking couple of comedians.
Like get you ready. If you were going to see like a drama
I don't know that'd be like a a mime smoking a cigarette that just was
silent and you it was it read poetry or something. I don't know.
Beat it zombies. Go back and bury yourselves.
Are you gonna pay for that? It's already paid for. Let me go ahead.
Have it be a full bar down there. Yeah.
Are you serious? Oh hello sir Mr. President. Agent Superball.
The place is being overrun with zombies. Yes ladies night is always packed.
The master is a genius at promotion. Okay so Superball. Superball.
No didn't work. Superball. Superball. Okay what about kids like a mime
smoking before. Well that's an R rated movie. If
there was like a R rated drama or something there wouldn't be any kids
in that theater. And plus they would just be on like
like a filter above them. Who's in charge here?
Master Jurgen the greatest leader ever. You said the same thing about Hugh
Bliss and the evil president. This is different.
Master Jurgen has a castle. He does have a point.
Okay. What is this place anyway? This is the zombie factory.
I knew it. I told you. Ancestral home. Garrison of his undead army.
Best doors in all of Baden-Württemberg.
We're here on official freelance police business Superball.
Sorry sir we're at capacity. You'll have to wait in line.
The master insists. Okay we have to stop. We only need to get in.
The line won't move any faster if you keep interrupting me sir.
The line's not moving at all Superball.
I don't see your point sir. This is a Beetlejuice thing if we say that like
10 times he's gonna like take a mask off.
Maybe a few uh Washington's will help speed up the line.
Or even a Lincoln. I hope you're not trying to bribe me sir.
Okay well yeah we always have to come back to time. We're very crowded tonight.
What's over here? A coffin that's been opened
from the inside. Wait you mean zombies?
Coffin has been opened from the inside of the open grave.
Have you ever seen Young Frankenstein? Yes I have. Looks like the
deadbeat undertakers and opportunistic German rats got to him first.
The master of all cinema, Gene Wildman.
When they put a stone slab over your corpse you know they really don't want
you coming back. Okay so we got a brain. Anything else
over here? What about this? Gravestone? It says irony 254 BC
to 80 2004. I wasn't expecting that!
Eat brain. I'm not gonna eat the brain. 254 BC
to 80 2004. I wasn't expecting that! All right this is the tomb.
Tome I know. Tome. Tome. Tome. I said it right the first time. I usually
say tomb. No I say tome. The tome. What do I usually say? I
usually say the T-O-M-E right? I gotta get this
brain in me. How do I get it in? Can I like entice the zombies with
the brain? I was going to wait but I think I'll dig into this
tasty brain right now. About to eat me along with it. Sometimes I
wonder if you're really dedicated to this job.
Can I throw it? Can we think throw it off the cliff?
Here come here. What about you? Can you do something? No way.
Can I do something? I can do it. Can I put it in the coffin?
Maybe they'll like go into the coffin. Yeet the brain.
No siree. One day I'll be able to show you guys.
Pack of clove cigarettes in here. I can throw shit real far.
Gilroyal's brand garlic clove cigarettes.
For that extra stink of sophistication.
I just put all like my anger and all my energy and all my like adhd and
like all my fucking explosive personality
and I just get behind it. I fucking yeah and I can literally throw
of rock like farther than anyone you've ever seen.
Like it's ridiculous. If I in another world I would have been like
a center fielder. I can hit home plate from all the way back.
I take like one two three one two five like five crow hops and just
fucking my arm explodes. I've already told you about this and I
could and this has been documented by other people that have been at
arcades. That punch the thing to see the
pounds per pressure on your punch. I go over eight to nine hundred every
time. Do you guys know the thing I'm talking about? I've already talked about
this. That like punch the punching bag arcade
machine. I like break the fucking thing. I'll prove it one day. One next time
I'm in an opportunity to do it. I'll get a video
and you will see my just my fucking my power.
It's I have power. People think I'm making it up.
You'll see. You'll see my like explosiveness.
Well in the trash. We'll go in the trash right? The zombies would just
reach in and snatch it. Will they get out of my brain?
The bottom of the screen is cut off. Um I think it has to be because
it's like has to run in a window. I'm sorry. I can't fix it.
All right um well I have these garlic clo-
Won't this like kill them? Well that's for vampires.
Nobody can do anything with the brain. Nope. Well let's just go back then.
One punch germa.
Uh let's go home. Oh wait. Hold on. Can I?
Of course not. Can I like put the brain on the antenna?
No come on. That would.
So I can throw these. Hit zombies. Yeah.
So what what is this going to do for me?
I couldn't even click. Couldn't even click.
Couldn't even click. Couldn't even click.
It's not clicking. Wait why is it out of 15 now?
Congratulations you won. Oh a decal. Would you like to keep trying for more
decals? Um no. No way. I don't want more than
one bumper sticker. Remember we talked about this?
I don't want. I'm gonna end up with a bunch of bumper stickers. Not good.
Would you like to try the driving challenge now?
No. No. All right so I have brain. I have garlic. Cigarettes. And then I
have. What do I do with these? Oh whoops.
I haven't even gone in here. Oh stinky. Stinky. No not good enough.
Stinky. That was our. Yeah maybe you should talk about this with your
therapist. She was my therapist.
Oh good Lamont and Wallace you're here. Sam and Max actually. Whatever your
friend here is driving me crazy. Take him up my hands would you?
Do something about these flies. One time I was in a restaurant
and I was ordering food. I heard I just got done like putting the
order in and it was maybe five. It was
probably like less than five minutes later.
I'm sitting down waiting for the food and I hear from the back
gotta do something about these flies. And I was just sitting there going
oh fuck what do you mean do something about these flies.
Does that mean that they're back? What does that mean? And you kind of can't
like I couldn't just be like ah hey
excuse me. Can you just like not make that food?
So I just ate it and it was it was pretty good. It was actually really
good. I'll never forget that. You don't
you don't think you'd want to fucking scream that
with customers in your restaurant. What's this sticky black goo?
That's my gooey molasses tar cake. It's a recipe handed down through my
family for centuries. All the way back from the primordial ooze from the
looks of it. It's like you don't you never want
to go to like the doctor and like the doctor is just like about
to do surgery to you and he looks at the nurse and just
goes I don't know really like if these tools have been
cleaned in the last six months or not. Do you know? No I have no idea.
Oh well whatever. You don't want to fucking hear that.
Why would you want to hear that in a restaurant? All right let's talk to
stinky. Any more zombies?
Give him a break.
Come on give Abe a break. He's on the rebound. He keeps trying to pay me in
confederate money. Who does that? That doesn't even make
sense. Okay so have you heard from grandpa stinky lately?
Like from beyond the grave? The dentist is in your mouth.
You gotta do something about these flies.
All right if there were flies in a doctor's office like a shit load of
flies I don't know the first thing I'm
gonna think of is that where's the body? You know what
I mean? Like that's fucked up. What the fuck are you? Why is that here?
It's like the first thing I'm gonna think of and it's gonna freak me out.
Like why would they be that many flies? Dentist office? No.
There would be no reason for that. They're so clean.
There's no... what do they eat like a fucking steak and cheese sub and
just let it sit outside like on the counter? What's with a
sun lamp woman who will call stinky for the sake of convenience?
So that's what that is. Oh I mean of course that's what that is.
Have to look my best you know. The magazine set such an
unrealistic standard of beauty for grandpa murderers.
How do you know it's clean? Because one thing that I'm certain of at the
dentist is that the tools are clean because this is very important. They do
this to the doctor too. I'm not gonna just talk shit
about the doctor, the dentist, they both do this.
They come with the tools in the bag that is sealed
and they open the bag of tooled chips. They
sealed new tools every patient. That's how you can tell.
Can we have your sun lamp? What could you possibly need it for?
Max needs a uv bulb for his teeth bleaching regimen. You think a smile
this white comes naturally? Well go ahead. I don't need... I mean
I'm done with it. Okay so we can take the sun lamp.
We'd like to order something. Supplies are low because of the zombie
attack so uh we're probably out. You do realize that's not going to
stop us right? Go ahead. Why would they have... what do
you mean? What are you talking about? They don't do
brand new tools? They they're like sealed in this
like plastic that just rips open and it's brand new.
New tools. It's not new tools every time.
So you tell me that like the dentist like scalpels and
scrapers and scratchers have been inside somebody else's mouth.
No, not if they open up a new sealed bag.
I think I've asked this question to the dentist before and they're new.
Yeah they are new. Yes they are. No no if they're in like a sealed
bag sealed like I'm telling you they're new.
Seared grouper in a maple syrup reduction with bacon wrapped dates and
toffee chips served on a bed of Venezuelan newspaper
clippings. Sal, number three. Chicken chow mein with
chocolate covered raisins and a caramel swirl.
Sal give me a hyperactive spider monkey and a powder blue cardigan
and why don't we go ahead and wrestle him to the ground and tickle him till he
pees. I have got to see what goes on in this kitchen.
I'd do this for a living. They... what you're a dentist for a living?
Do we have a one dentist in here? Dentists don't use recyclable tools.
Is there is there an actual dentist? All right Adventure MFDN is a dentist
like is a real dentist. Guy can you look at this for me
for a sec? Can you just take a look real quick?
Where is this? Can you look at this for me? I got this like fucking painful
tooth right here. Can you like take that take a look at
that? The special. Ah my special gooey molasses tar
cake. It's an ancient family recipe. Ancient?
You've heard of the Brant's Harpits of course but have you ever tasted them?
So I'll take two slices. Sorry I used up the blowtorch on some
zombies who didn't tip. It's impossible to cut. You're welcome
to look at it though. Just don't touch. They're new.
Nothing for us. They're new tools. I look I'm gonna just
I don't care I'm gonna just say that they're new
every time because that I don't I don't want to
you know I used to have this really really horrible problem when I was
younger. I'm fucking out of my mind right
let's get that let me let me preface this really quickly
when I was like 12 13 like 11 12 13 like just kind of turning like
adolescence and into like teenagers sort of like in between there
I was terrified of hotels because I didn't want to sleep
in bed that like somebody else slept in and
it was one scenario in particular was somebody had a note
that they left in the hotel room we got like Disney
land or something Disney World when I was younger with my parents and my
family and somebody had a note that they
left a previous person that was in the hotel room
it was like Bob or something to Bob and it was a guy who I don't
know what the note doesn't matter what the note says I only know that Bob was
here and Bob in my brain was this like fat
guy that like didn't shower and he slept in that part of the
bed that I was going to sleep in and I wouldn't sleep in the bed
I was like crying at like 11 12 like no but like what if Bob was sleeping
there and they're like it's fine Bob wasn't
even in the room but they try to like make some story up
just to get me to like calm down Bob may have slept on that side
he smells so I I had like an issue with like
things that other people used don't ruin the dentist for me
bye want to help me carry this thing around max I just want the bulb
did you just get deja vu just close your eyes and it'll pass
Bob Bob Bob farted on your pillow I don't know you guys know what the
type of fucking crazy shit people do in hotel rooms
all right let's talk to Abe what's shaking Abraham
she's gone left me this is a new dentist every time yeah
the new dentist with new tools in his jacket
new jacket jet like all everything has to be brand new
what do you know about zombies pests uligans
they always gather outside the memorial with their
million zombie rallies and groanings
always playing that awful music they listen to
how do you stop something you stop a zombie beats me
just between the three of us I'm pretty hopeless at anything except
making speeches oh what Sybil's looking for a new
boyfriend fine I don't care aren't you jealous
do I buy a new toothbrush in my mouth
talking no matter what she says because it's my mouth
no I didn't put the toothbrush into your mouth and then say
did you get clean and then brush my teeth is my mouth
you really blew it with Sybil huh it was just a simple misunderstanding
like I can't understand why you aren't as hot as that moai head
she took that completely out of context how do I know that it's
only been in my mouth because they make them in a factory and they seal
them and they come in a sealed package and then they you open the
package and it's new don't nobody there's no such thing as a
toothbrush they manufacture them at a plant and they send them out
there's not recycled toothbrushes at like cvs
who's gone Sybil she dumped you like yesterday's
breakfast when she caught you macking on the moai
it's not fun I'm sure it was just I don't believe that they test them
no there's no toothbrush recycling program
well you you don't like send the toothbrush back to the factory
just clean it you just this needs to be cleaned
oh my god no you guys are fucked no way
no way what do you mean google it yeah maybe like some of the material
but recycled plastic is not the same as like
then you don't like send a toothbrush to the factory and they run it onto
hot water and like reseal it keep a stiff hairless upper lip
always yes they do oh please all right so we got uh blamp
we're gonna bulb cigarettes in a brain maybe can i put the
what do i need to put this i have the antenna
i didn't even realize stop lights could become vikings
can i put can i put the brain inside of the socket there
it's literally the first link no they but this is not like
when you go to see you don't we're talking about two different things here
guys the toothbrush at cvs in the package
is not the same exact toothbrush that was
inside of bob's mouth no no no it's not it's not it is not
i am no it's not i i'm looking this up right now this is
horseshit no fucking way there's no way
recycled toothbrushes are toothbrushes recyclable
it is recyclable but if you recycle it with the rest of your plastics it
will ultimately be sorted and sent to a landfill
sorry guys are toothbrushes biodegradable
no they recycle toilet paper
crazy oh yeah they recycle toilet paper
that would be like so ridiculous of a process
yeah you wiped your ass with bob's ass
please all right let me let me think about this here we got the ceremony
you'll earn how do we put the brain in the
urn nope nope desk lamp not particularly illuminating
oh yeah what if i put a super light in it the bulb's too big
plus i don't want to read and get a tan simultaneously but
braces were recycled i'm not sure quite where i'd stick it
what okay the beer stein definitely is something here if it's in the light
socket can i do something with the beer stein
what about the cigarettes anybody want a cigarette no i can't except cool people
not even sedation no i can't condone smoking
for anyone um was there a socket or anything in
stuttgart that i remember hydrate i i'm fine
and i know everyone's gonna talk about i could go off on a million years
of a tangent here oh your water what about your water
your water is recycled what about your water you're drinking pee
oh it don't matter it don't matter you understand i have a water
purification system it removes everything everything
so i'm sorry you can tell me that's recycled that's fine
i'm perfectly fine with that you have you tested oh yeah
oh yeah it's the real deal i don't use a brita filter oh please what do you
think i am some kind of fucking dummy brita filter you don't oh please do
not come at me with this nonsense i tell you i have a
pure water filtration system and everyone thinks i have a brita pitcher oh
my god i'm offended i okay i didn't like i gotta stop like
fucking around and like actually play it's too fun to fuck around though
i have yes i have supreme filtered water supremely filtered
i will put that up i'll you know what only fits in the light socket
it is fucking supremely filtered i'm gonna go back to uh
stuttgart where we headed sam let's go to stuttgart
i could probably do that i could probably piss into this thing and
drink it i really i'm serious it's that good you could put
red food coloring in your water and your water would come out clear
you understand the level of purification we're talking here i
don't think you guys understand you want me to like shout out a
company right now i will i'll do it don't make me don't make
me don't make me turn this into like a sponsored
stream here i'll do it okay all right fine i
no no you figure it out for yourself no siree all right let's let's what can i
do with this light i use a burkey i use a burkey water
purification system it's the best in the fucking world
there you go you want the best fucking cleanest water you can fuck
in the world get a burkey you know that's bullshit
go do your research look it up why do you filter your water
i don't want bob's piss in my water okay
what the fuck are you wait what are you talking about big perky filter
what is this what is this nonsense uncertified it's bullshit let me read
this this is a hit piece it's definitely some kind of hit piece
this is a hit piece what is there another way oh wait wait wait wait
hold on pull wait everybody pull yourself out
don't just jump to conclusions here before you read this article don't
everybody don't everybody get go relieve your brain of all things
is there a water filter that they're pitching in the end of this let me see
here how long ago was this no it's the
clean it's the cleanest water i've ever had
this is like a year it's nothing it's one one review
from one one review what about all the other
lab tests how about how about this one how about healthy families for god
let's take a look at this one it works it's very good i can say i know i've
seen the tests that article links to pure filters
well better not why don't you just boil it you can't just
how do you boil like fucking a gallon of water every day you know it
would be so annoying is it a reverse osmosis filter
i don't know maybe it's good it's good i like it it does what it's
supposed to do i told you i wasn't supposed to
save brain i knew this was gonna happen i'm always gonna let me fight
the article that says what do i do with the brains
nothing doing fucking perky water filter it was expensive
it's good i like it i like it i'm gonna move on i'm moving on i'm gonna put
this back into writing i'm gonna recycle these things
all right i'm gonna play the game now everyone's just trying to make me
look bad because it doesn't it's a it's
where it didn't work it's better than a bretter filter it's way better
it's way better all right i can't tell if he's supposed to be barfing or asking
us to tithe both are scary maybe he's supposed to
be an embittered waiter spitting on our food
even so i'm gonna go drink a glass right now oh shit okay
something i'm gonna get this good i'm gonna get a glass of water right now
we found a non-violent solution to our problem
yes ripping the brain from a freshly buried corpse was the start of a
kinder gentler salmon max he's just kidding doesn't matter what it is
next that'd be us i could tell you guys
that are you sir god to leave any hazardous items outside
actual god part of the clouds holy water
taboo
and you're like there he is please have a taste of the cleanest most pure
water that we have up in the heavens
taste it it's so clean from the clouds above your clouds
wow and i would take a sip and people would go as a scam
it's just i know somebody would write an article about it
so god god parted the seas and took water from the clouds above
heaven and we tested it and there was
two percent fluoride still in it what is what are you talking about
there's a little bit of uh inorganic compounds are still
trace material you should get a breeder filter instead
what it doesn't matter what it is let's go in let us end
sorry sir you'll have to leave any hazardous items outside
garlic clove cigarettes not allowed holy water
taboo all right so put them in the trash i don't have any holy water on
me all right let me in let us in
very well have your ids ready please do the voice
yes sir welcome creatures of the night
to the zombie factory stream yourself testing the water i don't
have the tools to do that welcome to the 80s sam we've been
waiting for you blah don't drink the water in this
hour trace about you we're sam and max
squirrel food
only her pheasant is truly acquainted with the darkness
so what's your story emo i am juergen i'm not surprised you don't know me
no one truly knows me there's thumbs through the rings of the undead
wow okay all i take my army grows larger oh i did not just reveal my
master plan it was easy back foul monster we're here
to put a stop to your evil scheme yeah cut it out with the zombies i just
don't want to talk over people so many others have tried
that is how you say played yo now you must excuse me for i am away to dance
i never knew vampires were so fruity not all vampires max just the
european ones please living oh what are you gonna do
you're gonna drop a couple more one ones zero mana one ones
that sounds easy to me what does he got all right
i'm thinking i um thinking about using a guy with a taunt card here
be nice if i did it if i did it durin you would have laughed at it if you
thought it was funny it's hard stone not cool anymore am i
am i did i miss the boat on that or something
i wish the people making these fake books would at least try to make them
look real it was never cool yes it was you played
it you bought like a hundred dollars worth of cards i know you did
don't tell me that like a couple years ago you didn't like it
why do they always have bottles of water and raves because of all the
drugs sam and we better take one all right so
we're gonna ash a garlic cigarette into this water
and we're gonna give him unpurified water god damn it
i didn't learn to like just when you thought things couldn't get any better
close my mouth dead fish ready to drop some
fat beets or something i'm okay i went before we left
whoa all right will we go so we're gonna make them dance
torment sub zero
okay embrace sepulcher parents
parents desire desire succubus try to do a combo here
abyss blood you guys remember these things
letters this is just the the device that you could pick it it would be
like i'm gonna make a putrid revolting puke
let's all make a slimy stinky fart holy shit i used to love these
misery they still make those embrace pure energy pain
they still no no no it's like a it's a physical device you bought it
like a toy store i'm only 19 what was that oh
that's why all right well i don't know what these are for so i could figure
that i like that one so eventually i'm going
to figure out what song needs to be played here
there's some poetry inscribed on this coffin my dark mistress longs for
death to return to her velvet sepulcher
her only passion the voids embrace or else she'd reply to my letters
okay hold on poetry i didn't say it was good poetry
wait a minute so i think those correspond to the
those correspond to the dials there my dark mistress long dark mistress longs
to return to her velvet sepulcher her only passion the voids embrace
or else she'd reply to my letters oh let me go take a look
how much to make me shave my head on stream i would not do it
okay so there's a lot letters sepulcher sepulcher
that was a death right abyss succubus succubus sepulcher letters succubus
sepulcher letters maybe has to be certain b what was it again
wrong wrong wrong my dark my dark mistress longs for death
to return to her velvet sepulcher her only passion the voids embrace
embrace embrace embrace okay so this is this death is not on
here suck embrace letters
i don't know is embrace uh embrace sepulcher
embrace sepulcher letters i guess that's not all of them
well let's just maybe i don't have the whole thing because i don't know
what what the beat's supposed to be what is this one this one has
something here there's a poem inscribed on this is a poem here everyone relax
it's been worn down i can't read it that doesn't even rhyme
yeah these just change this these just change the song
yeah yeah what what what razor oh yeah okay
all right here we go so it was embrace
death sepulcher embrace death sepulcher letters letters embrace
death sepulcher death sepulcher embrace sepulcher embrace embrace the letters
letters
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
saw it open i'm not an idiot razor death adder see a thing your hand oops
sorry little buddy okay so this brings you up here a spotlight
it's the spotlight for the zombie's dance i have something in my
inventory check this out
it's gonna it's gonna go and aim the spotlight at his head
it's the spotlight for the zombie stands for okay
well that's in can i move this around but
no what else is up here find the swinging razor sharp pendulum
what razor was in here before oh so jurgen's the only one who's allowed
to redecorate let's see what else is in here
you're too dumb for this puzzle ban that guy for life
i've been in this room for like three minutes ban that guy for life
i just put the bulb in ban that guy for life
no no i wanted no i want to click on the x a purely decorative display of
violence kind of like max he's power hungry
yes i am you've seen me throw a fucking rock before
a fireplace with no fire no logs and no chimney
nothing suspicious here let's keep looking typewriter ribbon
that's odd somebody dropped a typewriter ribbon all right what is
i'm not we really need our healing just hear me out on this
this is important right here no like right here right no like right
here i thought this was like one of the
m&m's i thought this was an m&m i don't know
why like one of those cartoon m&m's does that okay well i just got the
ribbon typewriter ribbon what is this that is not a medically approved
use of nipple rings kids okay what's over there
nothing nothing nothing i'm just looking around i'm just
browsing it's like every time you go to a store
just do a hurry up and finish the puzzle wait wait when you go somewhere
and you go to the store you just instantly go by the way you just walk
in a straight line to the one item you want at the store and you fucking
walk to the exit and pay for it no you walk towards the area you want
to go to and then you may make a left into
like home section oh what's that let me look at like the
microwaves then you keep going you go to what you
what you need you take your browser on the other shelves
actually i need a new hdmi cable come on and my latest dance is called
the inconsolable methylene he's dead check it
it's okay no problem they're still cool
not so cool now are you master yergen it is but a minor setback
my zombies still know who is the master of style
am i right no it's us okay so do i feel like
poison him let me just check will he drink this
i'm gonna ash the cigarettes into his water like he's probably gonna be like
oh i'm thirsty now right they don't look thirsty no
having a good time they're about as articulate as your
typical clubgoer okay i mean can i move um
i have this like typewriter ribbon now i'm not necessarily sure what it's for
i mean can i aim it at him again he's just like off the dance floor
hey yorgen yeah do you have a source of power where is the source of your
power exactly just curious yeah we just want to look at it
americans the source of my power is not something you can buy and own
it is my style the zombies love me because of my rhymes
my mood my style follow me it's give me a small rock to throw is the only
thing that is truly a mausoleum apart from vampires which i am also
do you know if you have one of those punching machines is
so you're big fans of midtown cowboys over here
ja is deutschland's most popular program
all the young people in the gymnasium wear the t-shirt which read
you'll probably hide the cow her federalist world is eternal confusion
and pain i appreciate the show on another level of
course which is why the zombies love me new location unlocked
what was that you haven't heard the newest club hit
new location unlocked oh you are so tragically on here
okay new location unlocked zack you know for a master of style
you don't seem all that great yeah you're just kind of dated and mopey
i don't get the thrall though my zombie is not how late it is
i speak to the bleakness of our existence
winner of mtv bavaria's most doleful lyrics competition for 270 years
running you've got a castle and a zombie army what have you got to be
down about yeah we're at least twice as miserable as you are
would you like to prove it how do we do that
every night is open mic night at the zombie factory
you may try your pitiful best to win over my audience and then i will
assault them with my freestyle melancholia and they will continue to
be in my throne open night you won't cheat
i never cheat yes some of my rivals have been found with the blood
drained from the bodies but this is mere coincidence
it's on oh it's on oh very well but i always emerged victorious
i gather one could say it's in my blood
he's doing it again sam being all euro freaky
don't let him psych you out little buddy let's show him how the real
goths do it what's with the bands out i'm going
for southern gothic my name is um here we go
uh this is where this is where we don't we i don't think we have the info for
this but account cryptwind death grasp
mc rhyman canine i would pick this one mc
rhyman canine and i'm uh that's a tf2 one so i have to click it
mc lagomore and we're gonna kick it out awkward style yo
we're the freelance grave robbers and we're ready to go
see we'll knock you out better than we're taking over your house like we're
nancy pelosi apologics that long ago
rocking sundance like we were we like our breakfast
because it's sunny and cozy that one i'm saying top or bottom
because we're too good the guys heat to the row
and we're kicking those schools like pop rocks and charo
our world is endless torment and it is sorrow
we build technology for the rider tomorrow this one
torment and sorrow our world is endless torment and sorrow
despair you blood sucker mc's best get out of our way
because you're black and pink like a salmon for the lake
because i've been to snappy like a david man mick play
we're stupid we're stupid um there's all the creation ends in death and
decay this one indefinite entropy gee peace out
that's it you have all the street cred of white 30 year old video game
programmers hey ouch now take a listen to how
far it is done bleeding wounds self-inflicted
baffled morning hecka tag bitch queen nurse has no other stuff there
bandages cover scarves of despair
that's terrible that's terrible terrible terrible terrible
uh so what was wrong with that hold on do i need like more info what
was wrong is it the introduction gotta go full emo okay yeah
max and i want to challenge you again we'll prove we've got the bleakest
hit it my name is um my name is this one count crip win death grasp
that's just your name no no it's definitely
this one count crip win death grasp and i'm
something else uh barren bat anguish von nightmare
yeah i clicked on the instantly clicked on the tf21
barren bat anguish von nightmare and we're gonna kick it out awkward
style yo we're the freelance grave robbers and we're ready to go see
uh this is like politics no no no this is like nice it's it has to
it's
because we're the good guys no we'll kick it out of school our world is
endless torment and sorrow yeah our world is headless torment and
sorrow despair you blood sucker mcs best get out of our way
uh because all creation ends in death yeah
entropy g weak children of the night yes
you have managed to impress my brainless zombies
no matter i will still defeat you most easily
but first an energy drink hey no fair
to taste the blood of one who believes he has beaten me
it is energizing intoxicating okay our world is
endless torment and sorrow all creation ends in death and
stealing
hey you just stole our rhymes it's not what you'll say
but how i said i am smooth like cotton of velvet
huh so what's up with that bullshit he just stole we definitely have to
poison this guy right like we have to like just can
i just go ash the cigarettes the clove cigarettes in there
and just dump on his head or maybe it can like if he bites
maybe hold on there's a pack of clove cigarettes in here
can i put it in there he won't just he won't smoke them
no i can't condone smoking for anyone smoke him if you got him smoke
cigarettes in real life so he drinks he'll drink the water
i need to fill this up do i have the bottle okay so we have the we have the
bottle of water i can't like do anything with this i need
is there like a church anywhere let me go back in here max is a priest
yeah holy i don't have any holy water though no i'm gonna let me go back
here i'm gonna check the other places we're not leaving are we tv studio
new location let's go to the tv studio let's go to the warp studios
oh boy you're here let's get this started
a very special midtown cowboys scene 14
wait we just walked in the door we're just we're just going
i come back like this actors oh fine take five everyone
just come talk to me when you're ready that happens very quickly
i want to get cactus because we're supposed to be cowboys
see trophy number one how so what's the point of coming back here
i must be a prop in the episode i wish i'd read that out loud but look
max it's our old co-star let's just move on
the name is featherly i thought you didn't like us calling you by your
character name are you method acting or something hardly
i've legally changed my name to mr featherly
philo featherly no mr featherly it simplifies the licensing contracts
considerably okay you're pretty big in germany
really popular in germany did i know it changed my life that ill-conceived
dalliance and prismatology left me penniless
you should have thought about a nest egg when i was poor i would have taken
offense at that now i say ha ha ha
okay do you have any crazy fans crazy fans a miss
gretta grunwald i should go change my real name she insists on sending me
scandalous photos of herself with messages about how she enjoys
dark meat oh gretta she keeps sending me messages
about house and pepper okay with your new popularity do you
need some freelance bodyguards no if ms pandemic rejects my
application to be her suitor i may need to call on miss grunwald
a wise actor must adapt and adjust all right what happened to your love of
the theater so we're gonna film a new scene
let me see i could play torvald in a doll's house two shows a night for
an entire year and still not make as many euros as i
get from licensing a single poster of my beak not my face
just the beak change your name to presto e majesto are you ready for a new
season of midtown cowboys i've been ready for several months but
the director insisted that you two appear for some unfathomable reason
didn't you receive her phone calls well we have been busy
becoming president saving the world deleting random messages from the
answering machine what's the secret to a great
performance the true art of theater it is all about
improvisation uh an oral surgeon from houston during the french revolution
well now missy looks to me like what y'all got is an impacted molar
damn you robespierre and what is the e the e stands for e
a great actor must be ever prepared yeah in twitch chat
people just said it all the time so i just decided it was gonna just be
e all right so long bird the e stands for e
yeah the e stands for e lowercase ee as fake as myra's nose lips and hair
all right is there any items i can take from here is the whole
entire studio open to hey look around no wandering around
record the scene or get out oh what come on
what's this bullshit eileen come on up what's going on here exactly
oh nothing special just the biggest episode of germany's top rated we have
to do something here we have to make something interesting
it's all time no what that is i have no idea didn't you get my phone
messages midtown cowboys is a surprise hit in
germany okay what's this episode gonna be about
showed about it's the climactic mr fatherly's
intervention episode sounds hilarious this is no
laughing matter this is quite possibly the most important episode of television
ever made it's good to see the television industry
tackling important social issues like addiction
right social issues whatever i'm talking about product placement
this is going to be pure gold what the fuck
okay so what what are we doing our motivation
i feel like i'm skipping ahead here is to not get fired
just read your lines from the cue cards keep away from the props and
follow featherly's lead he's the one who's selling the t-shirts and
soundtrack cds okay uh let's see what happens we're
ready to start filming it's about time all right people
places everyone let's make some money art let's make some art
tonight a very special episode of midtown cowboy
who is this there's a narrator do i have control of it
ignore the problem and hope it will go away mr featherly needs our help now
oh there he is now there's a lens cap on the camera still
i must have left my bag in take the lens cap off
you're filming the most important tv show in history you're not you're not
there's no feed that's right mr featherly we have been hiding a cow
but you've been hiding something much worse what
what you're talking about for the love of god mr
featherly stop with the radio just look what you're doing to bessie
we saw what's inside your bag how do you explain
this old gut smack brand boltlegger we see you drinking it all the time how
did i break it and just click the let's go button i'm addicted
how could i not be it's got the smooth hickory age taste
that makes every night a special night it sounds delicious
let's go buy some right now boys aren't you forgetting something
right about that looks like you'll need to buy three bottles of old gut
smack brand malt liquor well thankfully i don't have to click
anything and cut hey good job least drussberg once
said excellent work everybody old gut smack
malt liquor breaks german okay so coal i believe that's it
she never thought to televise poker all right well i'm gonna go back
nothing beats watching the brick rise in the morning let me leave here
you can't go that way i can't go that way
poker knight of the inventory that is a game you're right
this thing's peeling worse than max after 13 hours on the surface of the
sun all right let's get out of here are
we leaving already yeah um let's go
just make sure i feel like i'm gonna i want to click on everything hold on
please not even fictional characters have time to read these days
the characters we play are champion horseshoe skippers but in real life
we're champion horse skippers cow doesn't do anything
or does the cow do something hello bessie
still not speaking to me i see did something happen in that scene that
i was supposed to see it's mr featherly's bag in the
scene there's a bottle of malt liquor inside
sort of it's mr featherly's there's a bottle of malt liquor inside can i take
it it's mr featherly's bag in the scene
there's a bottle of water inside oh yeah okay okay i get it
i get it yep all right it makes sense
let's do the scene okay we want to film can i see it this time
sure why not repackage it as an alternate take
it'll be huge all right let's go people no i want to see it
for the love of god mr featherly stop with the lies
just look what you're doing to bessie all right we can skip this though
skip we saw what's inside your bag how do you explain
this
what a smart smoking choice and they make you look so
cool let's buy some
remember the flintstones sounds like bessie wants her own pack of gil royals
playing garlic clove cigarettes flintstones used to do cigarette
commercials see that boys bizarre that is active
all right there we go cool germans say yeah to garlic clove cigarettes
there it is so now um it's mr featherly's bag i don't think i can
garlic clove cigarettes inside should i take them back or that should do it
right i wonder if i should keep like take
them or keep them do i need the liquor for anything i feel
like i could put do something with the liquor
i'm gonna put my gun in there i'm gonna hold on to the liquor for now
let me just get out of here so now all the germans
are addicted to cigarettes right are we leaving already
yeah let's go back to the office let's go back to the office
every time that happens it's like where do we just drive from we just
fell out of a fucking airplane all right so uh
they should be smoking cigarettes wait nah no the zombie's beer stein i can't
do anything with that uh i don't want to water that wait a
minute maybe they um where we headed let's just go back
see if anything changed you're in america all right so now everybody has
cigarettes here is germa endorsing cigarettes again
no i'm saying don't smoke cigarettes all right let's see cigarettes
why would i tell you
so we're just killing him from the inside out who's the master now
master jordan your attempts to discredit me will not work
my z-boys still go to my back yeah the level z-boys all the z attack back
there it's like really fucked up it's like
really distracting to see uh the zebra the z attack
all right so he's smoking that jordan creep is pretty uncool
huh i heard he wears corduroy z fighting
z attack i was trying to pull back from last dream all right so he's just
over here smoking cigarettes and it's killing him hey jordan
yeah should we like dare him to inhale
what i don't mean what i mean we will end you jordan
and incidentally what was the source of your power again it is my style
the zombies love me because of my rhymes my moves
my staying all so he's gonna get he's gonna smoke and it's gonna fuck
him up yeah let's go max and i want to
challenge you you know me i'm count cryptwind deathgrass and i'm
bearing bat anguish the nightmare okay we're already wowed you but
here's an encore so just skip to jordan and you've
already heard our melancholy rhymes so we're not going to
repeat them you know you love us
that's it okay we don't have to do anything
so now he's gonna be fucked up he's gonna slow down he's gonna start
coughing and cut that out i hope you got something in mine here sam
i'm getting kind of woozy i max has to have something in his
body
what oh they didn't like that that was bad
that was terrible that was fucking awful that i cannot take away
so all right so he's already like kind of fucked up max has to like we
have to give him something you have to take in like garlic
flavored water or like holy water or i don't know we got to figure
what like how to get him drunk come here yeah that
makes sense i can't condone drinking oh what come on it has to be water
just when you thought things couldn't get any better undead fish
undead fish i need to find like holy water
yeah hold on because he's not gonna drink this he'll drink the water
oh yeah yeah yeah games are fun games are fun video games are fucking
fun all the three-dimensional polygons and
programming that require it it's wonderful shit yeah let's head back home
there is water i don't know if it's holy water though
no one likes games games just like i yeah fuck them
who needs games i don't think this is holy water
i think it's just it was bathing in it but what if you were bathing in
it wouldn't you taste bad where high priest max takes his holy baths
uh yeah but he was already covered with it maybe he's just consuming it okay
this is yeah got it
okay all right it's time to win so max drinks this he gets bit and
then all of a sudden he's just gonna pass out or
something no i how how am i gonna get this
in there he said no holy water and uh no cigarettes
just drink it before we go in right that's not
will it last where are we headed sam let's go to stuttgart
make it cool on the show yeah fuck yeah
free game with holy water i mean that that makes a lot of sense
but he could also drink it and then he gets bit but he has to drink it out
here will he know let's try that let's
try it i feel like but why would he just
buy holy water if it's not allowed in there are we
that's probably gonna work let's see if this does it
i don't want to waste it to anybody else it looks just like regular water
yeah only your priest yep so he has to drink it outside
are we leaving already it was an interesting idea i'm
just gonna humor it and see if it would work let's go to stuttgart
let me go into he's like it has holy water bats in his
room all right yeah i'm gonna go with the original plan
come here you try this drink up now delicious tastes like righteousness
let's go sorry sir you'll have to leave any hazardous items outside
garlic closed cigarettes not allowed holy water
i don't have garlic see yeah you guys all telling me that i was wrong
see i can't go in there with that it was the first season of midtown
cowboys with so much battle all right here we go hey yorgen yeah
he's got a halo on his head max and i want to challenge you again
you know me i'm count cryptwind deathgrash
and i'm baron bat anguish fun nightmare
all right bite him and turn to fucking dust so we're not going to
repeat them you know you love us
yeah all right that should do it
drag me to hell the scarred arms
down below very soon need diarrhea segment excuse a moment
not god hold your holy water yorgen you dare defile my oh wait hold on
he's going very quickly to the bathroom that was gruesome
that's not enough time to do anything oh that is the very last of the
straws i don't care i did not become the
prince of darkness just to make the friends
didn't wash hands didn't wipe ass i think that's more important
who needs them anyway zombie pile up save some of the entrails for me guys
we're not escaping to his inner sanctuary no go this way
go go in here there comes a torture chamber
dumb zombies like me anyway they're so stupid
stand back foul creature we come to cast you back into the unholy
pit from whence you were spawned what he said
heard it i should have i'm sorry
now your two souls will fulfill my own holy contract
and i will make the entire earth my non-stop
house party of evil and then there was the most epic battle of our entire
career oh yeah i remember the rest so what
do we do now didn't feel like animating it
jean i got so wrapped up in the story i forgot to think of a plan
we could make
all right cool that's it well that was unpleasant that jerk
your didn't got my suit all dirty i'd like to give him a piece of my mind
or take a piece of his they actually kill him that does sound
tasty we suffering serpent and the rainbow
max we've turned to zombies why are we standing like this sam
oh i thought you knew zombie lincoln zombie abraham lincoln
what are you doing here i don't know this doesn't look like the theater
something different about you you're not wearing your hat
and he's got a body and he's not 20 feet tall
and he's just come out of a grave yeah why is he this isn't our lincoln
why is he a person i know you he was the head
how did you end up in germany germany i've never been
apart from my family's cemetery plot just outside stuttgart
i have absolutely no ties to germany whatsoever
well okay there's the explanation uh i just crashed the game
autosave right autosave right please i was too
no it autosaves like every fucking it does it does like every other scene
it does unable to create audio buffer now autosave is going to be right here
how are you enjoying the play what is this part of the game
is this a joke are they making like a joke in the game thank you zombie
abraham lincoln for helping us teach kids more about
irony i asked him like how the play was and then he couldn't talk anymore
what you want to know how the want to meet
civil hey we've got a friend we'd like you to meet
should i get out for you you're a lot like her ex-boyfriend and i've suspected
for years that she's a necrophiliac it's kismet i don't hear no more of
this i'm a happily married i'm a married man
all right hold on wait wait wait i gotta get out of this because why
uh let me save the game oh fuck no what come on
the whole thing crashed oh yeah okay well here's hoping that i tried to save
it oh boy it saved it had to have right
but it's it's just black what is this
it's just black okay all right uh i'm gonna i'm actually
let me take this opportunity to go pee because i i just got like
really scared so i have to relieve myself i'll be right back
i just rebuild this drink with some water but oh you got it from your
from not to scan i filled it up from the toilet so it's different now you
can't make fun of me all right so this is saved zombie abraham
lincoln what are you doing here i don't know okay yeah and he's got our
body there's an hour lincoln little buddy i know you
all right here we go how did you end up in germany don't do that again
i've never been apart from my family's cemetery
stood guard remember this one we're salmon max
freelance police never heard of you so who's the head
you know i save emergency elections thrilling car chases
adventures on the moon easter island ruining your reputation
hitting you with a missile making you throw up they just announced a game
called pokemon sleep ridiculous all of it
wait is this one of those hidden zoetro programs
what does pokemon sleep you just watch like pokemon
sleep you're enjoying the play oh it's ripping but i was disappointed that
booth fellow wasn't in it i hear he's quite the actor and i
was hoping to see him thank you zombie abraham lincoln for
helping us teach kids more about irony
all right uh you might not be able to catch the rest of that play mr lincoln
want to know how it is no no don't tell me spoilers
the villain was hue bliss germs destroy the martians you see the
statue of liberty you get jesus shot and turn into one
of the walking dead uh i mean that's should we just try
to like well i mean don't we have to have
for time travel to work don't you have to things have to play out
exactly how they're supposed to right you get shot and turn into one of the
walking dead oh that sounds horrible this way we're
not time travel let mary keep dragging me to these things
oh right which is undead never mind that's a different genre entirely
hey we've got a friend we'd like you to meet she'd be perfect for you
you're a lot like her ex-boyfriend and i've suspected for years that
she's a necrophiliac it's kismet i don't hear no more of
this i'm a happily married i'm contentedly
i'm a married man all right well it was nice seeing you what
why lincoln we got to do some investigating
why are we zombies what happened how do we get our bodies back
what happened where are we you're gonna try to kill us
do we eat this guy sir mr president i can't understand you
never learned to speak zombie would have been useful in retrospect
yes sir it is warm for this time of year
i don't agree sir the advantages of a common currency like the euro outweigh
any nationalist concerns all right i think we're gonna get a
translator factory does not have free wireless internet access
how do we get back to normal that depends sir in terms of geographic area
or population density
yeah yeah yes sir that's very funny i hadn't heard that one before what are
we supposed to do now about 11 25 sir we're open till 3 a.m
well i think we have to just go back in here good night sir
can we wait can we actually have a conversation with the zombies now what's
going on here oh you're the americans right
thanks for the brain guy hey max we can understand the zombies now
it was as good as my nana's homemade chemo spliner schnitzel
i think understand is a bit extreme sam okay so uh what happened you're gonna
put us in some big machine and then we ended up here
oh yeah guy you're totally dead now okay
but we're the freelance police we can't die
i know it looks like me none of us can it's extremely excellent
okay we've got to overthrow jordan and get our souls back
overthrow the hey what no way boy the zombie factory is where it's at
friend don't you want revenge don't you want revenge on jordan
turning you into a zombie oh i was already a zombie silly guy
my company makes experimental new drugs until something goes horribly awry
yeah what is this accent race of super soldiers male enhancement
he's doing like german but then he's shifting over to
surfer how do we get back to normal we're not cut out to be zombies
yet another of my life's ambitions down the crapper
yeah i could tell you shamba like you've still got your souls
glad you like joy we gave you oh yeah it was delicious he must have been
really smart we don't have any more we don't
have any more brains to give you no problem eh the gang went down to
the village to get some more from now on can we drive eat them from higher
gargoyles like american style
american style what do you mean we act like we've got soul
no offense guy lots of zombie kids thinks it's cool to act like alive
these days we call them zombies but it's cool hey
all right well if it's all the same to you we're gonna kill
still taking down your gun oh okay save me the wishbone eh
hey save me the wishbone eh how do we get our souls back
don't know they say you're gonna do something with them
but i've never been in the vip lounge all right
vip lounge catching you later on the flip side
zombie brother uh did we leave anything in here a bottle of holy water
in here we probably can't touch that sorry sir garlic what if we drink
holy can i sam come here no i want to save this after max went
to all that max come here does it kill me
how does that make any sense yep sorry sir
you'll have to all right holy water angel zombie heavenly zombie let's just
i want to see what the reactions are in here
see what happens when we're going since when does holy water work on
zombies well a vampire like bit us i don't
know doesn't that how it works let's talk to these guys now
excuse me eat bullets chump hey
i guess you have to be a zombie to appreciate how good flint is at killing
them the man's a consummate professional
all right which one of you undead creeps is going to tell me where
you got salmon matt where over here what happened
i feel the original sin again the holy water wore off
did you make a no-no while i wasn't looking no
okay so um let's do a little introduction here is he not going to
recognize this not you guys too hate to do this fellas
but sam and max always said they'd rather die to become one of those
things i don't remember ever saying that did you max
nah i'm pretty sure he was making that part up
not a good shot not a good shot at all
and oh he's he's he's not can they not die
this is like dance here all right what uh
he just keeps killing them over and over again all right well
what about the inner sanctum what's going on out here is lincoln all
right this is lincoln's brain it's what's
left of zombie abraham lincoln's brain eat hot lead walking dead
so we can't go near all right what if we can we can we make him like
drink here take this doesn't like booze i can't condone
drinking especially this stuff do i have a gun still better not no we
can't go over there all right well can we shine a light in his eyes
smells like musty cobwebs and half-digested corn dogs in here
whatever i can like shoot nothing to do with the cobwebs
or like shine it over here all right shine it
over his eyes like what the zombie stands for it's like
drop it or shoot it or want to break it
why don't we mean you don't want to break it i don't want to break it the
flashing lights may yet induce a seizure
well we're gonna have to maybe try the dj board
i wonder if i can like aim it in his eyes no
no no no it's only in the dance floor
well let me just go into the inner sanctum it does have a lot of
bullets oh great they're back keep quiet and stand still maybe they
won't notice us hey look max it's vaguely ethereal versions
of ourselves are they ghosts now probably just those
soul things we keep hearing about well what do you know i do have one
right did it just go back in i don't think so
right you guys run along and play we'll be over here until our ride
comes what why don't you want to get back
together looks like a delicate piece of high
precision medical equipment never die batteries they're dead
okay alchemy machine i bet my lifetime
subscription to the 40 and times that that's an alchemy machine
okay monster diagrams we're gonna have to do some potion or something
these diagrams are so scientific i couldn't possibly make sense of them
jurgen's monster we need abraham lincoln's brain to go in here building
himself a playmate brooding is more fun when you do it
with a pal bringing life to this decaying lump of
flesh we mock death
yeah that's odd it lives our creation lives
happy birthday
birthday who the fuck is this guy can you help us oh well
and i suck the horror right out of it huh
all right hey let's talk hey gruesome you're not master jurgen
who are you a mob of angry villagers zombie ninja monkey pirates
prismatologists we're from the church of prismatology
offering a completely free session to test your bliss level with our patented
blissometers well it's not very blissful in this
dungeon leave the science to the professionals pal
now bend over we're just kidding we're your creators
master jurgen is my creator oh did he well we pulled the switch
now we turned you on and i wish you hadn't
the sleep of unlife was preferable to the bitter pang of loneliness
all right um why so glum charm do you have any idea what it's like
being a misshapen freak the only one of your kind
nope it sucks no it sucks no one to love
that's a deep deep level of uh you to get over yourself i reading there
we've got the perfect bride you're in luck buddy
we've got the perfect bride for you master jurgen
promised the same thing long ago but ours is ready to go right out of
the box no assembly required sounds intriguing
let's call me the civil say anti-pasto why
hey monster what's the italian word for an appetizer
on t posto uh hey monster what do you call a ham and cheese sandwich
that's been breaded and deep fried monty crystal
hey monster wait let me do one what california coast city is home to
cal poly university coalinga monsters are awesome what's so bad
about being a monster master jurgen only built one i am
alone all right well you've got us please kill me
let's go meet civil introduce you to our french civil i can't go like this
what woman could be attracted to someone as incomplete as i am
all right what do you need yeah trust us civils used to guys who aren't all
there all the same i must be fully
assembled before i go all right i thought you took forever to
get ready sam he needs an arm he's an arm
what's your job around here do you kill stuff or are you mostly
brain from lincoln master jurgen created me to prove his ultimate victory over
life and death never thinking that he'd have to
feed you and walk you every day typical all right you don't like you
are gonna do you well he did give me life and tried
to help me feel complete with self-help books and weekend retreats
yes but mostly by experimenting with the items on the operating table
okay what's the plan how jurgen turned us into zombies
what gives i don't know the details uh something about stealing souls and
creating a zombie army looks like an army of you monster guys instead
i'm a conscientious objector doesn't look like me
yeah farewell yeah all right operating table we've got
we need body parts let's see what he's got what do we have a body
max for the last time sam no oh with the monster sure all right egg beater
foam finger computer chip stone oh let me fucking throw this
heart choke heart listen brothers can you not hear the song of the earth
mother okay and uh foam finger for the hand
i can't wait to see him floss with that egg beater
computer chip for the brain yes that's much better i'd operate at a much
greater efficiency if you'd install limits i don't expect you to understand
the reasons why of course shut up yes sir i can't wait to see him floss
with that no no what about egg beater no feather
dusting clock anywhere else i need like a
a rock i can't see how that would work i think we need something
cauliflower doesn't go there
that clock must be a little slow um no yes that's much better i'd operate at a
much greater efficiency if you'd install
linux clock heart yes sir clock heart oh no i've over slept
i'm late i'm late i don't think any of this shit is supposed to be here
what about rock can we hurry this up guys i've got a dozen foreclosures to
get caught up on today and that's just the orphanages
just do this a few million more times and i'm guaranteed reelection
um listen brothers i think we just need we need to get it right
yes i yes yes let's all right we're gonna leave this for now
i think we're missing stuff gauges i can't understand these
therefore they're not important let's just turn them off
yeah we definitely need to get the brain so we need to get the brain to put in
there power socket what is that oh nuts the batteries are dead
please charge the batteries we need to strike the lightning on the battery
we need the brain the soul sucker it's the machine that removed our souls
from our bodies there's a television here what else
is over here alchemy book just look around and colter a life alchemy
for beginners you're gonna made it up to chapter 14
turning chocolate to gold oh but build me a machine that turns
gold nuggets to chicken nuggets and we shall have power unlimited
you're gonna must be sleeping off his humiliation at the zombie club
let's chop off his head then set him on fire yeah go for ice cream
we can't hurt him while we're still zombies max then let's put his hand
just put a bike lock on it and say tell us how to get our souls back
okay fine's fine but get back in here i'm already tired of being a zombie
well perhaps you should have thought of that before you treated me so
abominably maybe now we'll get the appreciation we
deserve crispy chicken nuggets all your beef
against us chicken nuggets you're right never paid attention to me
i could go with some extra crispy back in if we have to
you can't make us do anything okay uh we need to get that we've got to get
the brain from lincoln to put it in this dude
we also need to get some kind of heart or go in
you can't die twice scary when we're already dead
okay so what do i i have bolt cutters
steaks looks like a trophy case from all the vampire hunters who've tried
to defeat yordan how do you like your steak max
okay another steak shoot doesn't do anything all right
so i have some items here uh let me see if there's anything i
can do up with the guys shooting the zombies
maybe put the steaks in their hearts no that wasn't vampires these are
zombies i'm mixing genres just for shits though like
does this do anything like will he stop shooting if i stab them
that's only good for vampires yeah i know and tense
what about the axe can i do anything with the axe not as sharp as
it looks kind of like max that doesn't need cutting
liquor typewriter nothing else in here all right i need some stuff i need to
find some stuff i feel like it's not here
uh get i can't get the brain the brain is um
he shoots at you if you go click on it wow the cops actually installed
something well for once i won't be able to just pull it off
can i do that look away max aha this is the kind of
symbolism that turns your stomach nonsense i embrace all kinds of
vandalism now i'm going to electrocute this
hold on this is an illegal item eat hot lead walking dead no get out of
my way i'm not even walking towards you
oh i mean i i am technically walking towards you
yeah why would the stakes not be illegal to power this
and i power this by sticking this in here
and then striking with lightning so then the batteries are charged and then take
the battery i'm like how do i turn how do i make
this strike this will it or it's gonna strike him
they're dangerous the best kind of neat i bet that gave it enough juice
now the table works never die batteries they're undead it's an
alchemy machine so can i do anything with this yet
or did i just kind of it's an alchemy machine
what about can i turn can i turn liquor into gold
what use is a gold one of those gold it'll just turn it gold what use is a
gold one of them i need hold on gold it just turns it
to type written on what use is a gold one of
gold stone no i need something else i can't pick any of this stuff up
james bond no that's been done before all right well i think that's all i
can do here i don't see anything else i think i've
set it up let me go back to the real world
germany's the fake world no no we're very much in a fantasy land right
now like a castle with like dracula and zombies and
shit i'm talking about like non-fantasy it's like new york
we're just like on a street not like in a castle
castles equal fake castles like this don't yes
but not enough fake fiction let's okay let's get back to non-fiction
okay does that make you happier let's get back to non-fiction
are zombies allowed to drive cars i don't see why not
my license is just as expired now as it was when we were alive
yeah let's head back home gothic germany equals fake no but like the
vampire living in like the dracula castle is fiction
new york city this is non-fiction here is just great
that's what i meant come back here you stupid hand
vampires are non-fiction i don't shoot i'm not gonna give that a response
talk to me this parking meter could withstand anything
hey fun you just can't come into our office and take what doesn't belong to
you oh that is like the black there's the
hand calling names at the kettle which is also black
it's different when we do it we're professionals
what do we got here just stabbing through the heart
get it over with can i pick this up beer stein so i'm a zombie so it could
be my beer stein right i wish i could put the liquor in
there not happening can i do anything over here
yeah it's just here for fun rats only okay rats only what about
in here so we're looking for a heart the
brain is lincoln's brain obviously look for a heart and a hand
the hand like just ran that way so we're looking for a heart
now another bear head frog machine wait what is this i need to see this
in spanish frogs are called frijoles which explains why i eat them with rice
take the banang banang tastes great and fun to say okay um i don't see any
like heart stuff in here let's listen to some machines this is
civil could you please tell honest a that i'll never speak to him
again in my whole life ever even if i'm being dragged through the
streets by wild donkeys thanks i don't see any body parts in
here the hand did run into not stinkies
just checking just checking just checking kill lennard
i you can't kill him hey lennard that's only good for vampires
it's stacom oh horrible that's too gruesome even for a zombie to do
i don't want to waste it on him hey lennard
all right let's go into the into the restaurant
and arms ran in there
whoa that was for i don't know why for a second i was like holy shit they
just like murdered her it's jesse james's
reanimated shoot man surly even in death
okay so another case of somebody shooting gun at us
um pie sticky goo it's stinky's gooey molasses tar cake
okay so let's put um the steak in there let's throw that into him
let's shoot at the hand no he's too quick shoot at the goo
shoot at better not i want to throw goo
it's just a pie it's not something you really talk about
it's stinky's gooey molasses tar cake i can't like touch it
i can i just walk around i guess i can keep going this way
um can you give us a hand here great zombies as if my day couldn't
get any worse well um maybe i'm missing something
anything over here i can grab or do behind
coffee pot something fall something to throw
typewriter ripping this is the perfect thing to defeat the hand
or it would be if it weren't a worthless typewriter ripping
i can't like dip anything in there that doesn't need cutting
no i don't know what to do maybe i can't do anything in here yet
let's go to civils why are you not shooting max
wait oh no okay i got it shoot me no no no this way shoot me do it
it's stinky's gooey molasses don't put over there
it's stinky's what don't just groan and point do something
oh what oh come on you saved me zombie max my heroes
weren't nothing man what i'll take the hand
oh never mind what the fuck come here i'll take that mr james
now we need a heart we need something that can be a heart
civils wait can we like untie you i'm kind of just leaving you hanging
don't serve zombies in here do you have any idea how expensive brains are
i mean i'm trying to help you i can't cut you out you look like a pine
cone even for a zombie to do well all right fine eat my brain see
if i care it's all pointless now anyway let's go
check on civil i got the hand eat again soon
i'll try anything new going on in here any items any hearts any body parts
oh hey guys you haven't seen this yeah whatever so i think i've narrowed it
down to two guys but i'm still not quite sure you
didn't mean any cool guys out there did you did you narrowed it down to
these two god those aren't your guilt gifts i can't
understand you my good man diction diction narrowed it down to
two i want that soul matter i know sam i'll
use it once i've narrowed it down to one fire
so we get the gotta get the brain and the heart
gotta bring the entire wizard of oz movie to frankenstein frankenstein comes
in here they hit it off they fall in love we
get the soul matter bring the soul matter back
to the castle bang roll the credits let's just get it done okay i still
can't get in here can i talk to any of the other
zombies beat it deadbeat it's a free country
pal okay you don't have anything to say
go back go back go back whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa oh my god help easy bolt cutters on door why is everybody
screaming this cutting tell me again oh um tell me again what
do you want me what do you need again doesn't need cutting
okay should i try it one more time before i get screamed at again
oh we baited him see you yeah you can't pull that you can't pull that
on me is it okay is there anything in here
tattoos sign anything on the fox no the fox is innocent
ah i'll take that i need that i'm about to bolt cutter this guy
okay like come here harry what are they doing
that's only good for come on how do i get rid of you there it is right
there better not what are they doing i can't
condone drinking especially this stuff are they okay now serving 46
now serving 47 this is diana here plus two plus two plus two plus two plus
two plus two let's go to stuttgart let's at least give the hand as it's
taking up inventory space i hate when and you know you know what you're
playing diablo 2 and you gotta go back to town you gotta
flip through space plus two plus plus plus plus plus plus plus
two plus a bit minus two plus two plus plus plus plus plus plus plus plus
that one went well zombies back off stop i just try to stop doing the
resident evil camera thing where you get to the certain threshold and it just
you have to go ah yeah
not playing diablo mobile is that game ever gonna release
or do you think that this internally just like put it in the big
incinerator how you gruesome all right come here
there body parts all right you have a hand now
uh you got to get the chip in there you got you're all right you're ready to go
let's go hey gruesome let's go meet our friend sebo
it's a frightfully long drive isn't it are you sure you want to go now
yes yes let's go right now quickly before sam gets distracted and
all more switches well i never travel without my belongings
just throw them in the trunk already we're wasting daylight
all right let's get there thanks for coming gentlemen i know it's difficult
for you to travel having to carry all your stuff with you
i'm used to it well until i figure out how the soul
mater works i'm going to have to do this the old-fashioned way
i'll ask each of you three lucky bachelors a series of questions
based on your answers i'll decide which one of you advances to the final round
of being my boyfriend
are we just in here please i'll have to ask you to leave if you don't learn
to show some tolerance they're going to break everything
and eat my brain nonsense sam and matt's have just as much
right to be here as anyone alive hmm which question should i ask first
all right well yeah what are they doing
why did i put my finger in his mouth my finger in his mouth
all right um um um um let's see what what other questions
let's see i still can't decide which question should i
question should i ask i don't know question two
no i can't read that uh do question one
good idea sam i'll ask this one bachelor number one my last
boyfriend was a real jerk i'm looking for a man who's kind
upstanding good to everyone and never cruel
prove to me you've got a heart of gold
i love the spirit of all the earth's creatures
i need that heart the tiny bean sprout i can't touch it
mighty sequoia the tibetan yeah let's move on
number two same question i am as you know the go-to performer for troubled
characters with a heart of gold landlords lawmen gangsters nuns
hookers and pimps i've played them all
big phony got it and bachelor number three prove to me
you've got a heart of gold oh i've clearly won this one
unkind compassionate wouldn't hurt a fly
weren't you the don of the toy mafia that put a hit out on me
well yes but there were extenuating circumstances i was hypnotized
i felt bad afterwards i see we gotta get rid of this how do i i need
this fucking heart how do i get rid of you like we have to
ask a question that he doesn't know question three
good call sam he's gonna free go this one bachelor number one
the only thing i liked about my last boyfriend was that he had a way
way with words he always just knew the right thing to say
so what would you say to me in a that's definitely
that that's that's the brain let me optimize your inner loop that's the
link in brain we can focus on debugging and bachelor number two
i would quote from my award-winning one act play the cloaca monologues
to wit oh no that's he's got the computer brain
bachelor number three same question what would you say to me
in a romantic moment here it comes most romantic thing to say
it's a good question i feel like he's stuck now
well no wait was he stuck not taking it or put it back is he stuck
he said yeah i've heard enough he started yeah i can take it
i did i still can't just question again do it again do it again do it
again i can get it bachelor number one you
do
it's not right creature what i expected better from you harry
but i wasn't talking about you the zombies you're out your anti-zombie
talk isn't making things any better i think you better go dumb
motherfucker get out of here get out of here and then thank you
slam the fucking door notice agent a super ball was it what my pleasure
you're looking radiant sweet all right so we need to
hold on follow your heart easy for you
so i need to turn this into gold at the alchemy table
and then we need lincoln's brain he's no longer protecting the door
so what can i could i bring something in i think we need to go back we gotta
go back to the lab anyways i don't think i can take anything yeah
let's go back to the lab let's head back to stuttgart please
don't make me get back into the trunk are you sure
uh yes yeah i miss i want to put that heart in
put the heart in he's got the hand he's the lincoln brain
let's turn it to gold chocolate goldify it plus two does not
like a way of bad joke you're being you're being sarcastic you
did the smiling face hi gruesome yeah
there uh can we just put it in get me my checkbook quick
i need to give to charity okay that's it
the arm is there the heart is there we just need the
brain the second best brain in the world yep so it's in there it's jesse james's
hand looks good no i'm not gonna put rock
brain we need lincoln's brain but i need to figure out how to get that guy
out of here i think i just hit a wall because i
did everything i had items for put rock in brain they're not
gonna stop like you guys know they're not gonna
stop you're like a dog and a surgeon that's like
give him a gold rock brain all right well we
super super ball is no longer at the door so i feel like that's part of it
so let's go back and bring what's in the trash right now
now the cigarettes in the trash that has to be something
nobody guarding the door there's a bottle of holy water
bottle of holy water it's empty that's it
i can bring where the cigarettes cigarettes back at the tv studio
cigarettes are like back in the tv studio
i feel like the no liquor would get bit of that good guy give it to that guy
hmm the axe is like i chopped the head off or something
but i can bring this in let me just see can i give it to him
like will he just shoot me no i want to save this after mac
all right max get over here why am i milking this stream what are you
talking about it's playing the game
holy hey flint can you help us out here zombies
no he doesn't think he still he won't look at max
how do i make it so i can pick that up Abraham Lincoln's brain
can i like bolt cutter this and drop it on his head
they just don't stay down much like stinky's food
let me see if i can bolt cut that again bolt cut
i don't think i tried this that doesn't need cutting no
there's a poem inscribed on this poem can't read it's been worn down
can will that work i'm pretty sure this is useless
no talk to the zombies i mean they're going on they kind of just die
came in suddenly shooting everyone he's a crazy man what's the big deal
you guys get right back up yeah but it's steams it'll probably
get the book we're trying i'm trying to stop the violence
that's the intention here
pressure ribbon yeah i've what why is it we're talking with there's a poem
inscribed on this yeah i know that i know there's a poem up here i can't
read it i've already tried this i'm pretty
sure this is useless it doesn't do anything
there's a bowl clean it like throw holy water at it
no i want to save this after max went to all that trouble sanctifying it
nope i don't think i can clean that can i like shine light on it
clean it with lead quantum mechanics it's quite complicated
looks like a trophy case trophy case literature like a painting of jordan
in the club when he was younger oh it's behind his head looks like a
paling's parents he was younger pain looks like a painting of jordan in
the club pain parents razors looks like this
razors razors pain pain parents parents look sam i did not expect that thing
over there to open okay cool so we can go in here
and is that gonna probably take us why is the floor so sticky there's
gonna knock him out possible answer to that question that i like
he did the thing i've been telling him to do for an hour what why do you just want
me to cheat and just look at every answer
ah too bad i didn't like cheat and read it immediately
rated one guy yeah but like i can't believe it he's he's trying to figure out this puzzle
you should have just read it in chat an hour ago isn't there no reason to play this if i'm
gonna do it like that like i could just read you the wikipedia article of each episode if you'd like
and is that would that make you happy he's dead i'm disappointed flint fell for such an
old trick okay so we've got the brain let's put the brain in the body put the body into the
chair come here you it is at times like these when a monster is driven somebody else's play
through history are we not all but misshapen combinations of flesh and feelings bodies and
souls yeah just like we get it it's like i get to the movie theater to watch the movie
i haven't seen and there's somebody standing in front of the theater doors
hey don't go in yet well why not oh because i'm going to tell you the whole movie right now
don't even go in and watch it i no don't don't don't i want to see the movie so you see what
happens is no no actually that's even better that's like an hour before we get to the
theater somebody calls me hey heard you were going to see this movie in and out
yeah yeah i am let me hey i'm just telling you everything don't go you know what don't
even go just hang up oh shit please i think he's ready hey gruesome heart of gold brain of power
hand of the dead let's go let's go to sybil's again it seems we just got here are you sure
yes let's go right now all right we've got your new boyfriend ready to go
article okay bachelor number one i'm looking for a man with a heart of gold
how would you prove you've got one what's that i'm terribly sorry i was distracted see
i used your restroom earlier and i'm worried i might not have remembered to leave the seat
down could you repeat the question hmm what i think i've heard enough wait wait wait why
he has a heart of gold doesn't he has a heart of gold in him right now what he has a heart of gold
she liked it well she's like i heard enough well all right bachelor number one i'm still
looking for a man who's good with his hands how good are you with yours what are you doing
it's the only way i know how to express my feelings ma'am oh and i killed the little turkey
over there does that please you okay bachelor number one my last boyfriend always knew the
right thing to say what sweet things would you say to me during a romantic moment well
it is all together fitting and proper that i answer your question but in a larger sense
our love would be so pure so harmonious so rapturous that my mere words could do little
to add or detract miss pandemic marry me oh i mean yes bachelor one we did it perfectly
adequate well i think the choice is clear bachelor number one would you give me that
soul replacer like to go steady at last i feel complete preposterous please no cameras i need
a moment after years of searching i finally found the perfect man what oh of course you're
right max this has all been a lie in my heart i've always known who my true soulmate is
i just never wanted to admit it what what i've been so stubborn and foolish i only hope he'll
take me back thanks a lot jerks i suppose a weekend in cabo son lucas is out of the
question as well all right well that's that's how that plays out give it the soul
soul matter i guess civil won't be needing this anymore let's go get the soul the two soul
okay i think we're gonna suck them in there anything else in here that i can take
maybe maybe maybe maybe who knows what about the gifts have never heard can't buy me love
oh free stuff a free office full of stuff motion balls knickknacks coming now let's go
so we have the soul thing i feel like it's gonna be a little bit more elaborate than just
point at the soul where we headed sam let's go to stuttgart we'll find out
whatever this is episode three episode four is coming up next all right it's time for the
climax sorry sir you'll have to leave any hazardous items outside
garlic smoke cigarettes not allowed holy water are soul machines allowed in here
thank you all right so let's just go in there and see what they say about this
did you ever figure out how that thing works sam there must be a button or a switch is it
this easy i guess it is just this easy huh all right that's it did it okay i guess there's no
switch i wouldn't say that oh did anybody get tall and chubby all of a sudden hey give my
stuff back ah so there's where you keep your gun uh sam and max you keep returning but you
know you cannot defeat me that's max and say no matter i will take your souls once again
but this time your bodies will be obliterated obliterated you know cut off your head set them
on fire salt the earth oh nothing doing you're gonna regret you ever tangled with me so weird
i mean sam how's your american the audio is coming out the wrong way
oh all right steak steak them right in the heart all right uh see you later murder them
right in the heart do it no please too slow i need another one wait i need a drink give
him alcohol i bet those candy-ass vampire hunters just didn't know how to do it right
he's just to catch the bullet yeah we get a drink here take that i can't condone drinking
especially this stuff should we go put alcohol on tv and make him drink it
is you just make it like alcohol what do you got in here no wonder zombies always slouch
go make it right let's do a tv commercial quick what is that here we have a vampire in
his natural habitat does the gun ever work i don't think it does um wait you help us
hey gruesome i am help us no he's not gonna help us is he i mean can we like electrocute
i can't condone drink what are you supposed to do all right what do you think that's in here
all right cage you think a guy with his own should i just die
hey what happens if i just die the soul meter pulled our souls right back and i still feel
overdressed i just i don't know i didn't know if like what about some of these things i barely
got a handle on max's body i can't like do anything with them like the monster party
part i got a handle on i can't even click them what else do i have here i've got the
typewriter last time i went at him barehanded he just about killed me minus the just about
can we leave the room try but like i'm pretty sure this is useless try wait till he's like
no more this probably isn't gonna work no just does the cut scene so we gotta slow him down
or we have to be faster than him but i feel like there's something that has to be done
first we have to like crush him in that thing we have to crush him in here somehow i just
don't know how jesse james is fast hand yeah i can't i can't um take it from him
hi gruesome i am i can't like touch any of this stuff i barely got a handle on max's body much
less the monsters maybe i should drink the holy water here what about this nope
i don't think anybody can drink this condone drinking especially this stuff
yeah nobody can drink this the monster can't drink it max sam can't drink nobody wants
to drink it what about the coffin behind you can i do something with the coffin i wish
he'd just go back to bed i don't think the monster won't like follow me either
hey monster think fast wait can we actually do this why'd you do that so let's let's die
again it's your console sucking machine uh okay let's die for a third time we both just go in
well this is a step up at least it's too crowded in here oh no okay so we're
do you think a guy with his now we shoot him i don't have any i don't have a gun
give me a big one all right it's time to stab but wouldn't this gotta be slower
frankenstein is really slow
that hurt i don't what hope you got the point you suck juergen hey my line was better
but i cannot be defeated brush i am the prince of darkness
it should have like blood just fucking spray out of the center of that thing
take this me we'll need it for
oh sad hey sammy you're back what about max time too what's up plant you know i've been tailing that
bosco mug right now the trail's gone colder than a dear john letter written on no tell motel
stationary bosco's just loud and easily startled we'll help you dig them up that's the rub see
bosco's vanished off the face of the earth cliffhanger what will it be we'll have to
find out in a minute or two that was night of the raving dead by sam and max well actually
by dan connors and kevin brunner but you know and all these other people that worked on
next episode that was all right i don't know i don't know if i put that one in my top
three it was okay it was good i put somewhere in the middle it's not top three how dare you
the next one is really good but that's good looking forward to it why is it so silent
i'm just noticing this now it's very quiet to a point where i'm just kind of freaking me out
ah we're gonna have to do it all again we'll just do the whole thing again i'll just restart
it all right episode four let's change this to the episode for 204 is what is 204 chariots of the
dogs is this episode 204 can we do a p break yeah we'll do a little break here thanks for
watching we'll see you next episode in less than a few minutes oh and what um did i hear
correctly that they're deleting all these forever i think all the telltale games are actually
getting wiped out completely yeah you can't buy these anymore i don't think so if you like these
games and you don't own physical copies of them i would go get them i would download them and
just have them because um this i don't know if this what's gonna happen to them i think you
can get them in some random places but it's a little bit of pain in the ass right you'll
still be able to download after they're pulled you just can't buy them okay but still though
just in case if you if you wanted them on steam they are i believe all of them are disappearing
all right let's uh take a quick little p break we'll start episode four when i get back
and we'll do episode four i will be right back see you in just a minute hey look at that
that was pretty quick wasn't it that was a nice little speed piss not really i thought
that was fast i thought that was really fast but look at the games already here that was
pretty fast it usually takes me like five ten minutes set this up i'm ready to go
bingo done here we are ready to play you ready okay you back episode four one two three breaking
into bosco's okay we're in boys bosco three anti-mind control helmets for the first 50
lunatics to come out of hiding i've been telling you little pals he's just plain
where'd he go we'd better look around the joint for clues find blasco yes that's why they call
you guys in for the brainy stuff and leave the senseless violence to the likes of me i deeply
resent that comment mr paper yeah flint we're gonna have to join together and use every
detective skill we know to find bosco the white line i know because when you open these
games you don't get to go to the menu anymore ideas so once i get the menu i can change it
like right up it should allow us to do this
there it goes does that look that looks all right to me make it bigger
to make a huge white line what happened to my that lose what am i what the fuck is it black
screen no it's not um why does that disappear am i gonna play season three on stream yeah i mean
let's get to the end of season two and see i would assume because we're doing just one two
i would probably just do three there are a few things that are way ahead of season three
though there's a couple of games that i really want to play for a while so season three
won't be like this weekend or something it would be like a week or two from now
okay there we go that was odd let's do it in a year all right so we need to look around see
where we can find evidence of bosco's disappearance it's just gone trash no bosco's in here
nothing in the trash what about uh we never go behind the counter i always wondered what bosco
keeps hidden back here i've always wondered if he's wearing pants back there might and magic
yeah we're doing my magic tomorrow heroes of might magic three is going to be tomorrow
and if we are enjoying it it's still fun i'll probably do it the next day as well
it's everything we needed to solve last year's hypnotism conspiracy
i'd kill for a time machine right about now there's a landmine in the corner for just about
anything okay keypad this keypad must control the laser grid blocking bosco's bathroom
oh use it to spell boobies i love that bosco lasers and pushing random buttons are three
things that don't go well together little buddy it says the code is in my head we better find it
soon then it must be getting lonely code is in my head this shotgun no just two pipes
can i pick up the tapes or anything no we finally have a weenie no different weenie
all right but there's a keypad we need a code nothing else here wow it's everything we needed
to solve yeah all right let's get out of here as informative as max impeachment weekly is i doubt
it'll tell us where bosco is let's check over here photo company no clues here sure bosco
everybody else is watching you can we look through his periscope we already checked the
roof just a pigeon a meeting nothing worth mentioning oh we'd love to go in here we can't
get in until we get past this laser grid oh we're actually gonna get to see in here
the laser grid first you have to forgive the laser grid freezer freezer is he in the freezer
what time is the stream gonna be for here's my magic the regular time between three and four
pm pacific it's a head it's bosco's my first moai head toy well it's in the head how do i
get it in this head moai head can i like break it i heat it up or something not happening
can i freeze it can i read it oh siree nobody can read it no microwave x-ray all right let's
have a look at here we go mr moai head we'll see what's causing that persistent tinnitus
prognosis sam either this toy is a tumor the size of an overfed cat or it's too dark to read
it the x-ray at the moai head is all we need all right so x-ray can i put this under on
something sure photos here everybody else is watching you so can i leave here is there a
lamp or something is like a heat lamp or something light the x-rays plenty big enough
it's just too dark to make out light we need some light photo equipment no clues here light
are you gonna have like a light in here no way nothing doing hmm can we just read it out in
the sun bosco didn't take any pictures of himself his camera no doubt thinks him
i'd not like you to give up on a case samo you're right flint don't know what came over me
well no we cannot just go outside we need a source of light well you have an x-ray viewer
up here apparently looks like say it it looks like bosco's as clever as you are at cutting
edge intellectual humor you gotta admit that is pretty funny all right so the password is
bosco's moai head a piece of paper five three one eight oh oh eight zero zero eight yeah it's
i'm not saying let's check in the bathroom for more clues bathroom reveal let's see what it is
i'm actually pretty curious it's been off limits for like two and a half whole seasons
let's see if there's anything in the bathroom to tell us where bosco's top secret bunker is
or maybe the bathroom is his top secret bunker this is exactly where i'd want to spend an
advertised shirts i sense that something terrible happened here oh you don't know the half of it
bosco's been ordering nothing but baking soda and paper mache you can do a lot of baking soda
and clean deodorize it's good stuff the bosco tech drain liberator 6000
i'm not going anywhere near that demonetized what it did to that sludgy delivery guy the
sound alone still haunts my nightmares if you explore it they will come if you explode it
not explore it and if it's brown flush it down hot toilet wine everything bosco would need to
survive for months oh nice from the looks of it these wine bottles haven't been touched in
decades i'm pretty sure i can hold it until the end of the case pretty sure all right
urinal urinals such a crude and barbaric means a bladder relief says the guy who uses the fire
hydrant i agree we actually both agree on that all right so we get disguise kit bosco's high tech
100 convincing disguise kit so jerma's water filter a jumbo size bag of cotton balls
don't open it sam i can never eat just one i use a fire hydrant bosco keeps plenty of
baking soda and to keep the bathroom fresh so we got some baking soda we it's an industrial
size industrial size well this volcano rampaging roy neary with a meat in two sides
recognize that from easter island max it's a model volcano i'd say it's downright exemplary
okay there's no way i'm touching that towel not after all the people who've been using it but
bosco and i are the only ones who ever come back here exactly who's used this bathroom
all right well i mean the scientist in me wants to do this all right now we just need
um we need vinegar tons of model volcanoes just like the one on easter island it's like
bosco was obsessed with this shape like i'm obsessed with the shape of bosco's unnaturally
bulbous forearms a little like that but slightly less creepy do you have any vinegar in here
baking soda plus vinegar equals eruption yeah well where do i get it baking soda
plus vinegar equals eruption sounds hot but they didn't leave a phone number
can i use like the toilet wine no i would clean up in here i don't want to disturb any
evidence hmm a nice aged bottle of well there it is nippy valley wolf for party time or anytime
that was a pretty good idea left the cork out max it turned to vinegar let's see make an
explosion make it make it reach the ceiling put your eye into it it's like i'm always telling
you sam we need a much bigger explosion this time you might be right max uh okay so
it's an invest and just dump it i don't know how to open the barrel hmm can i dump it in the other
one no it's an industrial-sized barrel of baking soda well we gotta get the barrel open what was
that for sam that barrel was looking at me funny dump it in there the gun actually worked
the gun does work sometimes and the school board said our cases had no educational merit
do it again do it again what's that noise aliens alien episode they've come for us max
it's t h e m good about time we found out who's responsible for this travesty
whoever was upstairs is straight up dead yeah i'm gonna get here we go boom boom boom boom
you ready don't miss once three times change the ending that's got flashbacks of the pepper game
the one that was unwinnable hey guys look i can explain did you get a haircut bosco
there's something different finally see a doctor about that uh personal problem you guys done
yeah that's all we got good now shut up and help me what seems to be the problem bessie
that that elevator over there it's horrible i went inside looking for t h e m but when i
got out i saw my mother yeah it gets worse i ran out of there fast as i could and when i
came out i was like this you gotta fix it guys yeah i want to fix this is unsettling
i just stood up on the hind legs was mooing and walking really fast okay uh what are you doing
what are you doing on an alien spaceship i got tired of being scared of t h e m i finally said
bring them on i built this device that let me predict where they were going to show up next
then i let them come on and take me so did you get udders or are you a boy cow that's
none of our business max what happened next bosco i use the device on myself you know i hate this
i don't like this it's like freaking me out something to do with like that just that
perfectly like normal human face and then like this where's this t h e m detector device you
were talking about i don't know i must have lost it in that elevator after i got turned
into the back neck yeah the back neck is fucked right here it's duh what is this place bosco
you guys still don't get it this is it the center of the entire operation of t h e l kind
of sparse for the headquarters of a sinister cabal bent on world domination you don't need
much room when you can go gamer you want through time and space
no that's not gamer neck that's like rooster that's like a chicken neck
that's like bird neck what's with all the volcanoes back in your store
god god try to keep up haven't you figured anything out yet the volcano is what summons the
spaceship fools nerd neck is bird neck are we being scolded by the guy who's half cow
but where are they seems pretty empty where are t h e y hanging out i don't know but you can bet
they're around here somewhere just waiting to probe us and turn us all into freakish
animal human hybrids bosco sam is standing right here okay so where is this t h e m detector
device you were talking about i don't know i must have lost it in that elevator after i
got turned into this this this this thing all right let's go to the elevator don't go anywhere
bombs go take a look around now where am i gonna go looking like this help me get back to normal
guys probably we'll get you back the way you were before but uh we're not promising more
than that i don't want to talk over the audience okay elevator let's just say hold on this
captain's chair hey max what do you think this thing is calibrating complete i now
have mastered your primitive but no less valid language please choose from the following topics
of conversation system identification owner into obvious query elevator usage well
identification were you i am this crafts artificial intelligence i supervise the
operations of this craft and the activities of its crew okay who owns yours the crew
they are currently occupied with the craft's primary mission they will arrive shortly to detain
you for your own safety okay time limit what happened to bosco the intruder made unsanctioned
use of the time shuttle how do we use that elevator simply elevators whoops additional
destinations can be opened using convenient pre-printed time cards okay pretty much how do
we use that elevator simply choose a destination additional destinations can be opened using
convenient pre-printed time cards there's more system settings what are my options my personality
can be configured to respond in the style most appropriate to the user please choose from the
following options politically correct suggestive abusive passive aggressive passive aggressive
selection acknowledged i'll just alter my entire personality matrix to make you more comfortable
all right please i cannot print a time card until the captain chooses a destination
well then can we terminate so long fine leave it's not like i was still talking
that's pretty creepy all right what we got here elevator bosco's time card does this just
take us back down to bosco okay we find other time cards bosco's again how do we end up back
here judging from the lack of safety railings and ready availability of guns and ammo i'd say
we've gone back in time seems to be some time in the early sweet mother of mole sauce you
fool's gonna buy something or do you want to make a baby well uh-oh it's mama bosco carbon
data remember that old carbon data we got from civil last year yeah we gave it to bosco so he
could keep scanning his weenies looks like he's made some modifications to it guns baby needs
baby making machine looks like a weird bread making machine don't be silly that's my
baby maker you take a spit sample from the mother and one from the father mix them together
a spit sample comes a happy little bundle of perfection finally somebody explains how that
works that's not the generally agreed upon method max so are we gonna are we gonna spit
in this this sample has been completely contaminated by milk it'll have to be replaced
this sample has been completely contaminated by milk okay to be replaced
hmm this sample says mama bosco don't touch that so do we have to go when my spit was most fertile
we have to go again what's this it's my chemical sampler get somebody to spit on it
and it gives you a sample test tube for the baby maker mind if we borrow it go ahead we
spent already got all i need all right max spit in this i think i'm better off not knowing
what max is made of oh fine what a waste what a senseless waste no that's comedy that's true
timeless comedy crying over spilt milk baby food and bum wipes if you use less of one you
wouldn't need as many of the other i thought you said you weren't gonna be playing porn games
they're they're they're beautiful guns garbage can the one constant across
all human cultures of all times is a massive amount of waste
all right i want to have a conversation with mama bosco you must be mrs bosco
that's ms bosco i don't want any part of your oppressive patriarchy fair enough ma'am
miss you who are you sam and max freelance police finally the police maybe you can help me catch
that police what do you need the police for oh who did you say makeup baby what was that you
said about making a baby i'm made uncomfortable by this line of questioning sam that's just
because you're scared of a world where career-minded women don't need to be tied to a man
to have a family this ain't the past anymore it's the 1960s they can talk about putting a
person on the move and i can invent a baby making machine okay who do you want to catch
which fool did you want us to catch exactly that that man who just came in here yelling
about conspiracies and busting up the place bosco always did know how to make
a memorable first impression can you tell us more about the man who trashed your shop
he took one look at me and screamed that should narrow the list of suspects down to
any man with eyes then he stumbled back and ran right into my baby maker
we're here to help your son i don't have a son you think it's not enough i'm a business
woman an inventor a woman's only useful if she's got a son it's not that we're friends with him
well acquaintances we know him we've spoken to him more than once doesn't matter i'm not
defined by my children but when i do have one she's gonna be the most perfect little angel
well watch out for store records we can't take the case but we'll keep an eye out for your
vandal miss bosco i swear if i ever find him i'm gonna make sure he gets no pleasure in this life
oh i haven't heard a tale of motherly love like that since the manchurian candidate
so how does that baby maker work making machine work you just take a dna sample from the mother
and the other person and combine them in that machine so let it bake a couple hours and you've
got a beautiful baby girl are we going to yes are we going to i've already got my own samples
in there i'm gonna test it out tonight after closing are we gonna go get her get the dna
samples isn't that obvious dna and put it in there saliva fools well naturally oh of course
is that what is happening what do you mean no what are you talking about what it was the
milk it said there was a milk container the milk in there and it was fucked up by milk and then i
get bosco infinite loop i don't know i don't know i thought i for some reason i just
i thought i had to go like make like another bosco you are where'd you get the father sample
oh him well i was just in washington dc for a special occasion and when i was touring the
white house i met a nice man in a dark suit he was polite and didn't say much seemed like
his spit was as good as anybody else's so i picked him who okay see you later miss bosco
we're gonna pick up some swinging 60s chicks and start a groovy hello man cut it out max
you don't even like girls oh right right you got a problem with women super ball just never
interested with all the general malice i have to get done in a day girls are just i was gonna go
get bosco saliva i have never been as turned on as i am right now uh what you just never found
the right woman and i never found the right man forget the baby maker catastrophic temporal
anomaly detected run away with me max my white stallion curse my irresistible animal
magnetism you should reconsider my office is strict violence it's not you it's me i'm not
prepared uh you should reconsider miss bosco i don't think you should reconsider they can
already see us living next door to that nice detective well it would be nice having someone
to do my laundry you don't even wear clothes and yet i always end up with so many blood
shirts here's a mystery what about the children i don't know what about that i won't need kids
once i have the love of my max he'll be my new little pet project i'm not prepared to commit
i'm a bad seed i can't be faithful to just one woman oh i'm enough for at least a dozen women
you dog you let's go lady you just don't get it i'm just not into you
all right we're gonna have somebody blow a snot rocket into this thing and put it in here
wait what's in here we're better to crunch numbers than in the jar sorry everyone's
fucking really upset about that one my paws are spotless oh the germs look so young
so count again we're better crunch numbers than in the john no time out needed wine hmm a nice
aged bottle of nippy valley brand vinegar yep some idiot left the cork in sam it's still wine
why let's just let that breathe for a few decades max oh we did it we're the ones that
opened up the bottle to make sure that we could use the wine bottle it's a bottle of proto
vinegar that should be very useful about pour into the container of the baking soda to blow the
hole in the ceiling for us to go up and then go in back in time and be here it's a perfect loop
can i leave all right well we did a i have the carbon data i need a sample at the carbon
data at the cork let's just see if i can do anything back here what do you think you're
doing you know the usual traveling through time and stuff override you've caused a catastrophic
temporal anomaly you're going back to the ship so you can think about what you've done
what are you talking about i opened up the cork i opened i opened the wine up
oh wait he's starting not to exist sam what's a catastrophic temporal paradox
that what the hell did you guys do max when you made mama bosco decide not to have a baby
that meant bosco was never born but if bosco was never born then we never would have gone
back to meet mama bosco in the first place neat are you fools just gonna stand there
explaining everything are you gonna fix me give a guy a cool cow body and all of a sudden
he's the owner of the time stream that was gonna be really cool i mean like george washington like
time streams everybody we can actually see stuff from the past adjust his webcam and get in there
all right so sampler am i gonna do the thing i can't think of any part of bosco that i'd
want to carry around with me that's not how time travel works yeah because if that's time
travel you need you will go back and kill your grandfather and that means that you never
exist in yourself there appears to be an 18% so you couldn't go back it wouldn't exist
it'd take me four days to fix you have 30 seconds what did you say
i can't even get over that louis armstrong voice what
oh what the fuck all right so stop doing that you're interrupting me
can i just go in here ray romano could spring out of there any moment
now it is more like ray romano to open it there's no way to open it that that's more
like ray romano what was i doing i was going well okay no i was doing it i was doing ray
romano you're right all right so we have to looks like some kind of weird alien radio
i got a cork the carbon dater bosco already scanned himself with this thing can i sit in
the cabin's chair appears to be made of the finest leather from only the finest and mutilated
cattle scanning joke about that scanning scanning let's scan each other it printed
a time card with stinky's logo on it whoa he said this thing prints time cards it printed
out a card with the intergalactic freelance police logo what sounds intriguingly futuristic
are you shitting me right now can i scan the computer nah all right well let's go to stinky's
stinky's uh and freelance police one there are one two three more to get
we're going to go to stinky's now i gotta scan everybody and get more time cards grandpa
what do you two want it's the one true stinky are we glad to see you why still it's a new person to
talk Abraham Lincoln's voice look sam it's us as impressionable preteens exceedingly well done
no we can't go i'm gonna we're gonna go talk to ourselves and it's gonna cause a problem
you have to avoid your past selves what is this mess old stinky was the only one who
could make a restaurant feel like home well let's just go ruin time hey champ what are
you working on i'm not supposed to talk to strangers but we're strangers who have candy
and cool guns you can play with well that should be okay working on my new arcade game
bluster blaster okay what is it what are you doing with bluster blaster so we made
now i'm just working on the internet now i remember you used to be a total nerd sam funny though
all this time we've spent talking to the cops and you never once mentioned you're the guy
who built bluster blaster it just never seemed relevant i guess okay shouldn't you kids be
outside playing or dating dating outside it's eight o'clock at night when i was your age i
would have set fire to at least four different categories of things by this hour
nah uh you would have been playing that video game all day just like he is don't you sass me
boy you're lucky that you grew i love the only little sam's voice machine kid little baby sam's
voice is just regular sam but a little bit like this you know it's like auto aren't you
worried you're turning into something of a well dweeb doofus dorkwad who cares i don't need you
guys or anybody else max never calls me names that's right poindexter oh come on you gotta
have like a little baby version all right what else do you like there's gotta be something
more constructive to do than work on this game all night well there is that prom at the school
this year's theme is summer of awakening desire
the smooth kid like you must have dozens of girls wanting to go to the prom with you
don't lie to the boy sam no all the girls are into max because he's mean to him
and also he doesn't complain when they dress him up in their doll clothes
the precious memories let's stick to one neurosis at a time max okay
look how cool i am wouldn't you rather grow up to be as cool as i am
with a boss car and a detective job and a huge gun hmm would i have to be as bad as you too
whoa whoa you're not gonna kill you're not gonna what the fuck you know that's you man
that's you you can't do that don't you want to get out and meet more sexy young people your
age yeah who's got time for that my video game is so close aren't they like six
oh what the hell you know me too well what's wrong with the video game it's fine i guess
but with only a one megahertz processor and this eight bit i.o adapter the ai doesn't get
enough cycles turn the dork lingo chubs just give me the recount it'd be easy enough to
download a new ai but i haven't found one new all right i need a new computer
okay i'm gonna go to the current present don't you want to get out and meet more
sexy young people your age yeah who's got time no okay i didn't want to ask that one again
i didn't want to ask that one again didn't want to ask that one make good choices son
didn't you guys say i can play with your guns we like kid remember this it's a good life i
didn't think i clicked whatever can i borrow that screwdriver well as long as you promised
to bring it back i hate to think what would happen if i had to stop working on computers
uh yeah sure thing kid uh-oh we've changed the timeline now i grow up to be uh sam all right
what about little max hey little guy what are you scamps up to i'm only playing bluster
blaster the newest and best video game ever made duh nice try you guys are nerds
shouldn't you kids be doing something constructive or at least less nerdy
today i get to do anything i want you do anything you want every day max you're the best
wow you really love that game are you kidding this game is the only thing that really
understands me you rock hard see what i mean games are dumb people rule wouldn't it be
healthier to get your validation from other people people are dumb and they just don't get
me you're the greatest see it's like the game knows what i'm thinking games will stunt
your growth playing that game so much is unhealthy little guy you're awesome unhealthy
to hear the truth i don't think so all right hey what's going on today remember something
very important about this day what was it there was my party don't forget party
prom and after prom kissing retreat tonight max boring great job you're getting better
that prom sounds like a fun and informative time for a young person why aren't you there
like just couldn't you get a date i can't even loser you're the loser loser no you are
jenny tallarico asked me to go but i turned her down she just doesn't get me like bluster
wasn't jenny tallarico the girl who had a crush on you for years max i don't know
i never noticed they call her jenny tongue a rico because she'll kiss anybody and she uses
her whole mouth grody grody we're still here doing this there's lots of neat stuff about
girls you'll realize once you take that first step to adulthood why bother i've got everything
i need right here you're the best go outside go meet girls go outside and play why would i go
outside when my best friend's in here gee max oh yeah sam's here too you're radical
all right that's enough just say no little buddy word up can i talk to bluster blaster
it's our old pal bluster blaster wait your turn no way i'm gonna break the screen
okay memorable toast is that toast lincoln no i was trying to break the screen i was
trying to hit like the screen i was just trying to break the screen everybody needs to relax
hi you stinky are you the parents of those two parasites well not exactly although we do
still have a time machine so i wouldn't completely rule out the possibility that's
gross max i'm just trying to break the screen just trying to break the screen i'm just trying
to break the screen hey we're from the future we bring a warning from the future in about
25 years you're going to be murdered murdered my swollen pancreas i once wrestled four rabid
grizzlies while standing on the back of a rutting alligator while being pelted with
karate tipped darts and fighting off a case of irritable bowel syndrome i'd like to meet
the man who could murder old stinky hi i'm max really you're gonna die we're detectives
and we've seen all the evidence you're gonna get offed when how and who's going to do it
well we don't know exactly detectives is really more of a catch-all term for guys with guns
some woman claiming to be your granddaughter has taken over your breaking things granddaughter
mike left palette i never had any children really a cantankerous misanthropic hairy old cuss
like you would be great with kids perhaps someday yeah i don't want to rush you stinky
but if you're planning kids you're gonna have to get on that pretty quick
we're health inspectors from the public health board almost none of the vermin in
this establishment are wearing federally approved air nets government types we can
take the lot of you you can't even begin to comprehend what i'm doing here
my dishes will challenge the weak we know the inferiors like you jelly-jawed lip flappers
only the strongest will survive it will be glorious
that was a terrifyingly awful laughing lipstick or what that was scarier than anything else
how are the 80s treating you stinky what are you two still doing here
no animals allowed in my diner it's okay we're service animals uh can we be seated could we
be seated already no shirt no shoes no service we're being discriminated against sam
we want to order something too bad we'll take a pan-fried red panda with what get
can't you see i'm so close to perfecting my gooey molasses tar cake i can't be
arsed to cook for you hooligans when i got so much cooking to do what's a gooey molasses
tar cake it's based on my ancient family recipe but my proud knuckle dragging forefathers
never thought to use my secret ingredient the blood of innocence nutmeg spit you're
all stupid it's the one thing no one has ever thought to use before he's gonna he's gonna
spit in it he's gonna pee in it i'll test your tar cake for you stinky sam can and will eat
anything oh you'd like that wouldn't you to just waltz into a restaurant and order something to
eat you're just trying to find out my secret ingredient well you won't because it's the one
thing no one has ever thought it's gonna be like a beard hair or something thanks for the chat
stinky i just go away and die but most of all thanks for just being you looks like girl
stinky was telling the truth for once the gooey molasses tar cake really is an old family
recipe well let's put this on you grandpa stinky what do we get weird it doesn't work
on him for some incomprehensible reason we don't care enough about to pursue further
good keep your fancy you gauze and who's your watch it's away from me
it couldn't hurt to take just a sample we should have those results for you in
about a week mr cake now turn your head and cough cake sample can they be scanned
i've already scanned myself with this thing all right oh now let's go put the cake into
the other thing and all right let's go smell you later homeboy totally we're gonna have a cake
baby uh let's go to bosco's see i'm telling you he spits in his cakes speaking of uh scanning
do you have a card what was that yeah it printed a time card with a presidential seal
and some strange numbers here we go no i'm pretty sure bosco's father wasn't a tar cake
what this sample has been completely contaminated by milk it'll have to be replaced what don't touch
that i made that sample when my spit was most fertile this sample is i can't i always what
i do with the tar cake sample not happening no i'm pretty it's mom about the mother sample
is locked i'm telling you i'm gonna have to get bosco to like spit in the jar let's put
look sam it's my summer office i don't think so max take a look around towards washington to
the oval office visitors next tour begins in 30 minutes this is a long time before the horrific
sequence of events that led to your presidency i'm not leader of the free world here this will
but i have the tar cake sample i need another sampler okay this far in the past i assumed
the earth was still flat i'm guessing they couldn't fit a television on there
all right okay so what's going on now i wonder who's in this picture it probably came with the
frame came with the frame anals of americana is the war room rat hole if i remember my
history correctly today's the day of the pivotal rat piece of cords we better not
disturb them foreign policy for ninjas hi i'm george washington shove your nuts in my mouth
and i'll crack them please don't make fun of nuts hi i'm george washington shove your nuts
in my mouth and i'll crack them please don't make fun of nuts they they really like dialed
up the like crazy shit in this episode huh hi there random secret service agent i can answer
any of your questions please don't touch anything i'm agent superball superball it's a code name sir
i'm a bouncer secret service humor in the future we know a guy who looks just like you
with the same name i've never seen you before and there couldn't be another agent superball
sir the code names are unique oh superball i get it did you see momma bosco did you see
a strange woman in here a while ago assertive career woman asking everyone to spit that's the
one yes sir i admired her independent spirit and sass and you spit where's the president
he's in the war room important national crisis and when i said national crisis i meant to say
he's just watching television we are not at the brink of war with cuba all right sam our
mission is clear nuke the commie best i think we've seen enough of the war room for one
lifetime max yeah you're right sam having to hurt people from a distance takes all the
fun out of it anyway okay um what do you think of the president what do you think
greatest man who ever lived sir oh these poor bastards of the 60s having to grow up in a world
without david arquette god how long have you been working for the white house just a few
months i've already been assigned my first door that's all you first door this door not at all
sir i also provide tours run the patent office and narrate public service announcements that's
a lot of work for one man i'm still new in 40 years i'll be promoted to receptionist
what's the gossip gossip about the president extra toes or nipples can't talk to the press
without slices of ham stuffed down his pants stuff like that the president is beyond reproach
sir i won't hear any more of it okay we need something we need your help with something official
what will it be sir we want a narration we want a patent we want a narration we want to
hear you narrate a public service announcement all right are your cigarettes killing you as
unbelievable as it might seem cigarettes made outside the u.s actually contain chemicals that
are addictive and possibly even harmful for your own safety and that of your children smoke only
homeland grown tobacco the kind doctors recommend for your good health now you know
for a better america okay um we want a patent we want exclusive rights to produce our latest
invention we wish to crush competing inventors to see them driven before us and hear the
lamentations of their patent lawyers very well what'll it be what self-rocking baby crib
cat litter formula gooey molasses tar cake we'd like to patent our tar cake recipes super
ball it's a special recipe we made up ourselves and anybody who says different is a damn
i see and what ingredient makes that a unique invention
uh i'm gonna say slap them with a dmca takedown
it's probably like this one or it's probably this one or this one i don't know it's probably
the love one that's like the easy one right it's made with love i can't issue you a
patent sir that ingredient is not in that sample oh come on how could you possibly know that
i'm a government official sir i know these things i'll need to know the unique ingredient
to issue you a patent all right well come on we need your what will it be sir we want
exclusive very well or tar cake i see and the ingredient is wombat guano quiescently frozen
wombat guano sorry sir that ingredient is not in that sample i'll need to know the unique
ingredient well i don't think i don't think i can do this so might as well just scan them
it printed a time card with our logo on it you're brute forcing patents okay well i can't
do that what was the other one another option here we need your help what will it be
a tour we'd like a tour of the office very well sir that's a desk there's a couch
another couch is there a calendar some pictures the door you see behind me is 100
percent northwestern white pine with an interior flat jam and that's plenty thanks
okay we want to hear another public service announcement do you know how to recognize a
communist look for the telltale signs all tell tail are double-jointed in their necks and
elbows to aid them as they steal american secrets communists also secrete a brownish
viscous residue from their palms which can be found on their homes children and pets now you
know for a better america jesus just keep guarding that door gladly sir oh jesus christ
we came here from the far off future aren't you amazed and surprised isn't that shocking
i've seen a lot of things sir it takes a lot to shock me oh really okay uh we can shock you
i bet we could surprise you can't be done sir i'm imperturbable
uh we're from the future we come from the beginning of the 21st century in the future
television is delivered through thick cables instead of being sent through the air does that
not blow your ever-loving mind not really sir i'm not easily startled what was that water
glass of water give me that water where can we get that water and we want to live in your house
and raise my children of questionable heritage he's gonna spit in our faces both axe murderers
and i'm voting for berry goldwater nothing it's like i said sir i'm not startled easily
we killed your dog i'm surprised sir really yes surprised that you try that one again it
never works all right we give up that man's a rock sam nice try sirs i almost felt my
pulse rate increase there keep up the good work thank you sir we have to do something shocking
and he's gonna spit that into our face cork no no this is not gonna be shocking i don't
think better not better not no we got a new time card i think we have all the time no
is one more missing one final missing time card after this one so let's hold on a minute here we
need to go we haven't gone here have we gone here i don't think we've gone here yet just give
him the jock jock shock jock it look sam more visitors i don't know how to use a light bulb
with that there there i love old sam old sam is the best character i already know
all right hold on here there's a volcano looks like we kept bosco's model volcano after all
these years blowing things up for science will never go out of style what's in here is he
still in here whoa geez that's a lot i hate pack rats it says stinky stick tight adhesive
based on an old family recipe number one throughout the entire galaxy with secret ingredient
bitumen 13 maybe secrets are different in the future 13 bingo we got it hello future me
i can't shoot max apparently all those years of adventuring have taken their toll i can't
use these things together scan of no areas can't hey future max oh hey guys look sam
more visitors for your special day comically backwards past versions of ourselves
no i want to keep these shoestrings that's nice sam so this is the future is a baffling
potpourri of peculiar sights and odors yes our advanced world must be frightening
and confusing to you i'll try to speak slowly so that your 21st century brains can understand
uh how did we do this how we cured bosco of his parentage problems
oh he's the guy who invented skynet isn't he no i was hoping i'd be the one who did that
i don't remember much about that case uh something about spit wasn't it so much in
the office has changed oh the wonders i could show the two of you if i wasn't afraid of violating
the time stream yeah the time streams asking streaming right now well okay nice man in the
future we can make phone calls to other people even when we're not at home my god
and our cars now have additional brake lights above the rear seats everybody hates that
someone gives me energy okay uh any interesting future cases have been having a ton of exciting
future adventures in space no we don't take that many cases anymore we try to stay mostly
around this street and the neighboring shops still i'm glad to see the old freelance
police are still in business are we in business dear stupid past sam but of course now we're a
wholly owned subsidiary of stinky corp so stinky corp took over the whole world
what's stinky corp get a load of this sam these yokels have never heard of stinky corp
i don't feel like playing darts right now yes well anyway stinky corp is the mega corporation
that owns everything in the future stinky made enough money from her diner to take over the
world i'm gonna take that patent no no cretinus max from her super adhesive
what's this about stinky super adhesive it revolutionized the whole galaxy now it's
used for everything from scrapbooking to alien spacecraft she's claimed in interviews that it
was based on an old family formula but sam and i think we figured out the real secret
it's made from mole men mole men vitamin 13 what about robots do we have robot slaves in the
future with lasers oh you uncultivated savages robots are used for controlling our spaceships
these days surely you've heard of the main tron 28 000 line well of course right sam
everybody's heard of that i can't shoot max that's my hang out with you can we just hang out
together and we just look at we just look out the window and stuff if you're not taking cases
what do you guys do i've become an expert in vulcanology and sam is well sam is in his own
world now great transmogrifying vapor wolves of right hill 17 booster rocket through the
van ellen belt i'm in my office get rid of this one what's this about stinky super adhesive
it revolutionized the whole galaxy now it's used for spacecraft she's cleared out the real
yep it's all men okay what's wrong with the other me oh he's fine mostly the years add up
it's linked from my pocket this should be useful later are you seeing you all right we gotta go
that's how we say goodbye in the future you gotta go talk to the mole with this bad boy
we'll never need another file cabinet can't do anything with it i have a screwdriver a cork
sampler i have this tarot stamp okay so i still have the sampler i need to get him to spit
into my face rats what future dystopia is this and then scrape it off and put it in there
not much use for this anymore but first we need to uh we need to go fine we're gonna find the
mold did i do all the how goes the case future me i can't reach it keep up the good work
can't reach it i think i'll leave him to his memories what do you mean i can't reach it the
spaceship's artificial intelligence unit is stuck on the elevator i probably take this off at some
point right all right let's go here we haven't gone here yet he's been helping some tachyon's
in a gravy boat at the grand duchess's bot mitra what disgusting hell hole have we ended
up in this time looks strangely familiar like super ball i'm not here sirs you can safely
ignore me is he following us around boxing betty remote max have you been sending boxy betty
what hey buddy throw us that remote control would you the hell is going on you're gonna need this
thanks buddy be you later wait there's a couple of hooligans ruckus making down there they just
throw me an egg and all right are we looping into each other are we am i gonna throw that
egg up there in like 20 minutes probably what are you doing here in our office investigating
the president's disappearance sir so you're back with the secret service then sure okay well
max was getting interesting we've been on a case we got beamed on board a spaceship
that's ridiculous sir must have been a weather balloon that was no balloon it was a spaceship
bosco saw it too gas leak mass hypnosis two abductions on the same street in the same week
and you're going to just try and cover it up i can either confirm nor deny a cover-up sir
god can you help us with our case what seems to be the problem bosco's been abducted easily
explained sir and he's trapped in a time traveling spaceship there's no such thing
as time travel sir look into my eyes please what were we talking about you'd said that mr
bosco is having a perfectly rational vacation in pago pago yes pago pago hey look max it's
agent super ball you were saying something sir uh very good sir we met a guy in washington
who's a dead ringer for you that would be me sir that was 40 years ago you couldn't still look
that young is he going forward he's going forward sir there's no such thing as time machines
what the hell don't you feel better now that you're no longer working for bad guys like
you're gun uh yes i enjoy working for the secret service fighting the good fight protecting
the president that reminds me sam can we wrap this case up pretty soon i've got a
health care system and five foreign governments to topple and i'm way behind schedule okay so
how's the wife and kids up with mrs super ball that's a negative sir we spoke briefly it ended
badly she says she can't talk to me when i'm emotional like this how'd you find out we
were missing there was a rat sir claimed he was de facto owner of this office since your
disappearance he was quickly taken away for questioning wow it always takes us ages to
get rid of jimmy two teeth he must be slipping max all this time i never thought to use rendition
all right so we need to um he stayed positive every time life closes one door it opens
another that thought disgusts and terrifies me sir so what are you seeing super ball we can't
seem to avoid it all right so you've been scanned is this what if it's a different super
ball weird it says i've already yeah that's the same super ball we met over the same person
i'm aging gracefully sir yes it is this was making sure i didn't want to be with what they
were lying it didn't know what there's about more than one all right we have an egg i need
to go find a mole stinkies where's that mole a civil with symbols who have i not scanned
can i say the secret ingredient i wonder if that if i can say vitamin 13
we need your help with something what will it be patent we want exclusive rights to very well
this tar cake we'd like to patent our tar cake recipes i see and secret ingredient is vitamin 13
vitamin 13 very well that seems to check out okay so now we own the patent that patent grants
you exclusive rights to make market and improve on your invention this must be just what thomas
and felt like minus the stealing and time travel of course oh sam you're so naive
so now we have the patent for we have the patent for the cake so now we go back to where
the cake is and we do is he gonna have we have a different conversation about the cake
let's go back here and see let's go to the office are we gonna be on that poster
we're not even here anymore you're still here but all points bulletin we need a new
boy oh this is the run is the wrong one wrong one wrong one good place for a bath right in
front of the window remember easter island yeah me either the flora brady has twice the
style the fauna one ever did turn on the tv there's nothing good on news can we see the
data
i like that one better that was my laugh what's going on what the
fuck was that what am i doing i'm like fucking myself up here
and that kind of was my laugh like damn it whatever all right so i have the patent
i need to go to the future not stinkies elmo i kind of sound like elmo all right so hey look
we it says stinky stick tight adhesive based on an old family recipe with secret ingredient
vitamin 13 what sue them we get the patent no siree 100 years in the future i'm gonna
patent that well sorry stinky sorry stinky but we're gonna have to uh
claim that cake we have to insist that you cease and desist all future production of gooey
molasses tar cakes mr stinky we're not angry very unfair from us just very very disappointed
boppy cock that recipe's been in my family for centuries now we'll go for the US patent
office says otherwise grants the US patent office can fuck my ass
actually i don't believe that falls under their jurisdiction fine i'll throw it out time
stream altered oh all right so we have the uh the ai now so is that it
sorry about that patent hope you're still not holding a grudge about that tar cake business
i hold on to grudges like a man pushed overboard holds onto a ship's rail clinging to it with
bleeding fingers as a one thing saving him from a fatal plunge into the briny abyss
we missed you stinky oh that's interesting that's cool
so the ai can't stick on anymore because it's using the adhesive that they know they no longer
make so now what happens in the future i'm just curious to see if this is any different
uh-oh the bulletin board's all wet and ruined we must get careless in the future
who cares all right any new dialogue here what happened to stinky have you heard from stinky
lately of course dim-witted sam she owns the mega corporation that owns everything in the
future how'd she manage that she invented a spray that repels reanimated zombie hands
it turned out to be surprisingly lucrative still still did all right apparently so long
what's that big elaborate goodbye hey hold on wait a minute will that will can i give that to
him this thing is just like a computer right will this actually do what i think it's gonna do
portable ai are you gonna do this will this work wow i've never seen anything that advanced
it must have at least 640 kilobytes of ram yeah whatever kid this is exactly what i needed for
my video game i'll just download the ai yeah you do that then go outside and play or something
fine she know the bad guys i'll just have to make more but no problem bitch
jan you made the game even friendlier oh he's passive aggressive is rejecting the new
programming i'll change it back nice try you almost hit it that's better okay what is the egg
i want to throw the egg up we gotta go oh we gotta go here where's um just go home
the personality of the thing has to be really nice you gotta have a really really good personality
really happy friendly one uh system settings what are my options my personality can be configured
to respond in the style most appropriate to the user please choose from the following
options i actually know they play it because it's tuned from nice but wouldn't it want it to be
um oh yeah i wanted to be like really really
abusive good choice you moron did you come up with that yourself or did your idiot friend help
out hold on let me see the other my options my personality please this abusive suggestive
suggestive oh that is exactly how i like it that's what the fuck uh this is like this is like
what are my options my personnel no i'm not using that one abusive we're doing abusive
so long get lost let's try it suggestive or riot no i'm not doing suggestive take another
look at this talking computer dingus kid thanks mister
this like totally blows now let's go to that dance and make the moves on some chicks
but i was going to penn station to pick up some power converters beat it nerds make sure
you check out the snack table little me if i remember correctly the pigs in blankets were
decadent time stream altered jackass so max feel any different i feel like it's been too long
since the maxinator taught a lady what sweet sweet love is all about that guy is happy
gilmore to me pick up some primo early 80s you suck jackass it's our old pal bluster
blaster all right can we do anything else with you want to screw that it's our old pal bluster
okay so now they left there's just the one song as stinky would say if you don't like it
go deaf all right what do we got inventory let's take a look we've got the egg the cake
sample which we don't really need that anymore the ai we've used we need to get
we need to get spit on what's the cork for can you scan inorganic things i've already
no no i want to scan this no way i've already scanned both of us i've already scared the guy
in the suit has to spit on me super bowl has to spit on us and i have to capture it how do
we get him to do that something's shocking in this but still missing a card calendar it's
the official calendar of the united states the best part of being president is changing the date
for the entire country i don't want to change the date right now i'm temporarily confused enough as
it is i don't think i have anything let's see do i have any other options we could surprise
can't be done sir no i don't have anything here all right we give up keep up the good work
thank you sir let me go back to get spit on put in the thing i didn't look at like bosco
hello miss b did it get freaky sexy in here or is it just you what'd you do to my max
the better question is what oh because he went he went to go like hang out with girls right
all night long don't look at me miss bosco he's been like this ever since we were kids
get you the pooch so you can give me a special tour of the store i've been wanting to see what
you've got round back i thought you were different max that does it i'm done with all of you
men temporal anomaly corrected jackass all right so that so anything in here we need to get the
spit from the guy to put in here to make the baby did i miss something let me check the
bathroom i think i missed something in here wine can i take the wine it's a bottle of proto
vinegar now it has to be there nothing else can i don't think you can do anything else in here
all right so let's go through them again anything else nations rise and nations fall
but those hot weenies will outlast us all well not here let's just see i'm gonna go
through them again see if i missed anything we'll take a gander that was a weird rumor that
was like a rumor that was run out of gas on the road all right you need to spit on me
spit on me how's the cover-up going very well sir is what i'd say if there was a cover-up
which there isn't all right be seeing you super ball i'm surprised this game survived being
thrown clear of the play land and casino explosion not nearly as surprised as the
guy it landed on i wasn't really expecting to play this i just happened i thought i
didn't think it was still working i still got 20 i didn't think it was gonna even pop up
i'm just started shooting randomly eagle statue i'm guessing they couldn't a true weasel scout
would keep his merit badges on him at all times be prepared be very prepared
nothing in here whoever chose this lamp was taking liberties with the concept of good taste
i didn't even there's another little section down here uh that looks like a perfect please
take me item doesn't it oh well i can no what are you doing i'm just gonna go through them all
but i'm gonna look around i don't see i have something i still don't have again reviews f plus
i'm not sure if that's failing well or failing poorly memorable toast the blaster
devil memorabilia letter display check this out it's from 1963 and it's signed by the
president my dearest maxine meet me tonight at stinky's wear that dress i like the one
where i can see your holy i didn't think they knew that word back then the president's wife
wasn't named maxine what is this the temperance league lighten up looks like this case has a
screw loose oh well i've got something for that for me yeah what what somebody's trying
to break into your display case classic cartoon money classic cartoon got you what about this
satisfied customer definitely all right so we've got all right all right here we go time to get
it let's do it i'm ready let's put a cap in this case check it out ready are you ready
to have this person undulate liquid out of their mouth directly into my face sip
my dearest maxine meet me tonight tender caresses down your hand a donkey love the
prez that's very shocking sir where were they going to meet inside stinky's diner
get it i can't believe the president would eat at stinky's i've lost all respect for the
man i'll take that and now we can complete it super bowl excellent let's go put it in the
machine let's make the baby and let's see uh no no no no no no no no no i didn't mean to
click didn't mean to click it's okay he misclicked bad gamer unbelievable i can't even
comprehend now somebody could click on the wrong thing get him okay here we go see
see uh that was great i was on that was an unbelievable fucking reference to what we were
talking about like fucking two hours ago unbelievable you get like a that's you get
like the stamp of comedy approval time stream altered check us turn it on it's mama bosco's
baby making machine the mother sample is locked but the father sample is open all right so let's
go it's a sample of agent super ball spit it's mama bosco's the mother sample so wait
do we just have to go in the future now can we just leave is that all we need to do is
he gonna be fine wait you're back to normal hello fool mr president fool hmm i suspect
we got the wrong dad max so bosco are you feeling like yourself of course sir never better oh my
god okay tell us about you can't you give us any more details on your father it's straightforward
enough fool i was a test tube baby first in the country no idea who'd make a spit donation
to your mom no more cracks about my mama mr president or i'll have to ask you to step outside
don't worry bosco we'll get you back to normal thank you fool
i suggest you hurry even when he's riding us he's too polite it's unnerving
how are we going to get off this spaceship hadn't given it much thought sir
you care about h e m coming back to kill you not really sir i'm sure there's nothing to worry
about i don't like bosco like this max we've got to get it back to his paranoid self
that's pretty fucking fun don't worry bosco we'll get you back to normal
thank you fool i suggest you hurry even when he's riding us he's too polite it's unnerving
oh all right i gotta get around i gotta get out of this will this work bosco already scanned
himself with this thing i do have no more uh dialogue must have mentioned the other spit
donor at least once said she met him at the white house said he was a nice man not
particularly interesting we'll see you around bosco so what what how do we fix this
what do we do with the egg i mean office so we can't get in here
we need anything else we can do official tour no just keep going keep up the good work
thank you sir nope i don't know what i was thinking there the father of our country
i wonder who's in this picture it probably came with the frame that's level okay i have
a cork but i still have a scan painting why would that wouldn't do anything nothing doing
no that's not gonna do anything according to that letter this isn't the only thing the
president liked should be plenty of dna rich spit left on this envelope i never i would
have fucking missed that forever i would have walked back and forth a hundred times
coyotes yeah all right let's try this again i need to fill a test tube with something
before i can put it in here huh oh okay time stream altered time stream altered again
is it do we do it done looks like we did a pretty good job patching up that cigarette
burn on the fabric of reality yeah that's right ladies come on up and give daddy max
time fixes some sugar you're a lovably lecherous tool max there salmon max now you've seen just
how dangerous it is to mess with t h e l dangerous all that stuff we just fixed was your fault
shut up all right let's go home how do we get out of here they know we're here relax
yeah they're probably the grotesque but misunderstood kind of aliens who just
come to earth because they hate cows and fields of weed well you two go first
i don't we've never seen box go from like waist down before crossing 98 percent complete
prepare to deliver on my mark it's it's t h e m oh
we've never seen you from the waist down what are you guys doing here
we can't explain everything weekly and simply no that is not our way
don't we have frogs are the frog mariachis
is
different right
hey
we sold off the dam then we send them to places i know i don't want to go
where do they go
our lives suck
are they gonna they're gonna kill boss go oh oh the cow man has had a heart attack
boss is dead begin the soul crouching so as i was saying we had to sit and stare at nothing
for 1000 years straight help me salmon max okay um um the suck button it says suck by the
looks of this place somebody's been pushing the hell out of it time controls looks like
some weird clock it can't take hundreds of years to cross a soul senior so we make the
time vortex to speed things along um why are you not being like look here pedro reprimanded
boy you people from the past are backwards you think just because i'm mariachi with
the big sombrero and mustache i'm some two-dimensional cultural stereotype you're
right i've been insensitive we're sam and max freelance police what's your name
i just kidded my name really is pedro you've got to free bosco you maniacs
nothing personal but rumor just went by that was a lot of rumor to pick up two souls in
germany but we only got the one the cow man will fill our quota where are the cages if
you're delivering trapped souls where are the cages cages we don't got no cages we don't have
to show you any stinking cages we keep the souls on that platform see yeah but where do
they go after that you guys are pure evil oh that's not nice we're not evil and after we
deliver the cow man's soul we'll have paid for the spaceship and then you can claim oh no senior
there's still so much for us to do with our time machine so many deep questions left to answer
like what about the far far future how will i die i can find out i can think of a few ways
and what is it like at the beginning of time before history was written which came first
the chicken or the egg chicken egg is the egg i have it in my inventory see i must keep on
until i find out for sure egg care i got the eggs see you later guys it's right here hey check
this out what is that it's from uh the beginning of uh keep cool sam i got it it's just the egg
it's from the beginning of the universe you're a terrible liar senor peru oh i admit it now do
you understand why i wouldn't make you vice president you're just dead on the ground poor
posco the horror of time traveling mariachis was too much for him how do we get how can
we use this machine still no sir wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait it worked the
birthdater doesn't work on these no reason hey a portable birthday checker pretty clever
how come it doesn't work on you the mariachi can never have a birthday for himself it is our
course all right what's over here bridge button attempt to enter soul crushing area
please acknowledge override captain pedro arriba burro chipotle voice print match
bridge override accepted i had a feeling those mariachis wouldn't just stand by and let us
take bosco's soul back how do we stop him from doing this can i scan the soul scan these
nope you you're in the back you're right there it may look like a zebra but my mexican friends
assure me it's a donkey in zebra clothing okay so what is my wife for items ai cake the cork
what's this printer it's some weird alien device that looks so funny not again just leave it
seems like everything on this ship you've forced apart these days it looks like some
kind of futuristic look ribbon printer it's an ink ribbon for the printer please don't touch
don't have one of those just have to change it again i had an ink ribbon before all right
screwdriver gun cork no stuff it in there shoot it break it come on ai egg cake nothing
screwdriver i really don't want to screw them hey don't don't touch that don't touch that don't
touch that it's the mariachis colorful pinata steel pinatas steel people of the future are
kind of missing the point steel pinata what the hell um all right i'm just gonna leave
okay do i can i just leave putting course on screen hey face look we are on course for our
most difficult mission yet triplets keep the time shuttle open for emergencies where i figure
out how we tackle this wait most dangerous birthdays whatever issuing time card for
embarrassing idols oh shit the final time card go go go quick run run sprint it has the
embarrassing idol logo and more of those strange numbers no mutiny what the they're
killing bosco they're killing bosco i had to at least see let's go he's already dead
yeah but i mean i want
man that song is even worse than i remembered i can't believe i voted for you keep it down
max we don't want to mess up time any more than we already have you really nailed that
high note and you're less sloppy than my brother in you've got my vote hey all of
the remaining judges have agreed we have a winner congratulations sam here's your recording
contract bin bottom records it's like a dream come true specs i'll get you for this if it's
the last thing i do after i get back from mount rushmore rushmore i'd better go after him i
just remembered i have to feed my goldfish are we still taping uh be sure to join us that's
our cue little buddy shick them don't forget you don't forget to feed your goldfish listen to our
words have a time every day every day every time do it routine you don't just do it whenever
who are you clowns where are you guys from your distant future heed our dire warnings i
always thought i'd be taller what are you guys doing here um congratulations on your recent
embarrassing idol victory now hand over that contract no chance we need it but that's supposed
to be my contract i want it fair and square and i help them cheat forget it clones that
contract is ours now take a hike beware santa claus and mr spatula and you bliss no you just
ruined the game tried to kill us this could take a while nonsense yeah all those guys are our
friends you just did the thing you just told me all the answers got any questions about
your immediate future hmm nope can't think of any what number am i thinking of right now
28 that's all there's nothing you're curious about we'd rather see it for ourselves keeps
the mystery in our relationship okay well we just came to say hello somebody's got
trouble letting go of the past i'll be glad when i grow out of that attitude problem
all right well hello okay that's done let's get back to our time machine max yeah i've seen
more than enough of this place for one lifetime time machine oh cool wait a minute
we're too little buddy just hit random buttons uh he's let him go in well so that's bad right
yep what in the future we've got our own spaceship and our own industrious and no doubt
completely legally hired crew incoming delivery and prega entranti you jerks you made us go
through the last year and a half all over again yeah we've got a very important case to solve here
let's do it all again so wait what the hell are we all doing here i want to ask you something
hey now i'll ask the questions here but this is freaking me out what is he waiting for be
patient max it takes a while to think up the right thing to say max and i have to get to
the moon how do we get there i have to get to the moon you drive to the moon yeah you just drive
why don't you just drive there you can't just drive to the moon bonehead sheesh sam our future
selves have no respect for plausibility you need a toaster with wings all right where do
we get one of those uh you got you need a toaster with wings you need to go ask
stinky in early 80s and no you need to just room your way there no you need to go to
super bowl no super bowl yes ask agent super bowl in the future well there's two hours we're
never getting back just between you and me pal i don't think those future versions of
us know what they're doing hey buddy hey buddy i've got a question ask away how okay how do we get to
the moon you uh take a really big trampoline you need a really big trampoline all right
where do we get one of those oh there was a way there was a down arrow ask mama bosco in the
city why do we keep listening to future us hey buddy i've got a question how can we
how do you get to the moon okay holy shit there's a lot all right the heart you need the heart of
a champion you need 20 pound can of beans your time traveling phone booth how do you get to the
moon how did we get to the moon you need a time traveling phone booth all right where do
we get one of those drive ask agent super bowl in the future what is this place all right memory
this is not our beautiful house how did we get here yeah because he does like the men in black
thing where he do do i know you how do we fix this weren't you gonna ask me something
how to get to the moon for instance oh right how do we get there you just drive
you drive you need a screwdriver you need a screwdriver all right where do we get one
of those you gotta go to stinky's in the 80s for that oh no take mine got one we'll trade
you for a recording contract hey sam don't we have a recording contract yeah but we need it
for um i can't remember it might be important
along with that carton of missile pops you promised don't push it max all right here you go
well done salmon max that was the last of your quests you have scored 234 out of a possible 500
weren't you gonna trade us something uh yeah here's that screwdriver you guys wanted
goodbye we'll never forget all you've done here today have fun on the rest of your adventures
i'm even more confused than usual so then now look what i got i've got something here
do you see what's in my hand here you go captain your ticket to musical stardom my very
recording contract now i can ditch this dead weight and become the international super star
a mariachi superstar yeah well good luck with that oh no signor mariachi music is old news
i'm going to sing songs about trains
what what about the other wait can we appears to be made of the finest leather from only the
finest and mutilated cattle all right well what about the other um what's your job around here
buddy quiet did someone say oh no false alarm my life let me guess you spend all your time
listening for people to say birthday okay did someone say birthday yeah sam just said birthday
please sing yours my job is very important okay this work is beneath you it's tedious and error
prone frankly we think you should leave nonsense i have got six of the birthdays today alone
six look of happiness and auto confusion that's all the birthdays that's all the birthdays that
exist we demand you return our pal poshko so i can't do that in your the cow man soul
will help us pay for our meeting why do you hate the birthday so much
hey max say earth day hey max what happens on april 22nd hmm i think that's earth day
okay showtime people attention wait did you make the joke on me huh pretty sneaky
uh hey tell me about western australia what do australians celebrate on june 11th every year
hmm by any chance would that be perth day did someone say got me again hey let's max want to
go watch pride and prejudice and all the bridget jones diary movies back-to-back you know it
girlfriend it'll be our collin first day did someone say all your guys how many times are we
gonna do this all right so sayonara okay so we need the dog said goodbye so we need to where's
the speaker she's used it to listen across time and space for special occasions we have to bring
this guy away to her birthday it's the elevator's emergency recall button how do we get enough i
want i need a birthday birthday whose birthday is it he doesn't need to be screwed is it
can who's i need to find a birthday but it doesn't hmm it's your birthday these guys
i need a birthday shit wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on hold on is it on the
hold on yeah wait wait wait where's it wait wait wait wait wait i think finally getting
the hang of this time travel stuff let us change the course of time without fear or
confusion and somebody's birthday on your change the national date today sticking up today the
official date has been no wait is it an anniversary so it shall be somebody's birthday is on here
god damn it it's today's birthday is today your birthday by any chance no sir not particularly
how do we find out his birthday keep up the good work thank you sir are we about to brute
force the birthday no right here official date is september 12 that's sweet the president left
a reminder for his anniversary by jay had good advice for anyone's anniversary is it your birthday
today i mean like cake and ice cream or beyond that's right hey super ball is today your birthday
by any chance no sir not particularly keep up the good work thank you sir um you have like a
card or something where are we here we're already there 17 the official date has been
happy birthday hey super ball is today your birthday by any chance
no sir not particularly what we need what will just gladly keep up the good work thank
this is 1963 0917 that's not your birthday according to that letter what the fuck oh god
damn it the official happy birthday hey super ball what day is it today it's the 6th of september
sir it's my birthday i said it's my birthday sorry i'm late amigos did someone say first day
all right what do we do what do i do what do i do what do i do i don't know what to do
uh kill him push him out the window wait up guys i'll be there in just a minute
gracias for the song señor this has been the best birthday ever
oh he's gone okay we just can never go back there ever again that doesn't need to be made
radioactive to listen across time and so there's like there's one more even in the future they
get reruns so how do i get this guy to leave can we do anything else with you guys future me
i've got a question go ahead uh what are we doing here again we all agreed you were going
to stand out of our way and play the quiet game for a while we'll take the case it's
one last thing in here i can't use a harpsichord with that can i talk to wait where's
the other where's the other max you come here it's last year's version of max the egg yeah
shoot future me but i don't think i can you know i can't like scan the egg i mean i was
handing him the egg scan yeah what do you mean scan the egg i can't scan the egg
he just tried to shoot you is that what happened
i can't shoot him i thought that was me because i was taking out the i thought it was like a
bug in the game
i don't know i just clicked on this i thought i he was trying to kill me
all right i can't shoot future me somebody's controlling him right now
okay we've got you've got deep questions you don't seem like a bad guy pedro
quit this evil job i told you señor i can't quit at least until i found all the answers
like how do i die and which came for the chicken or the egg or the egg
uh what do i have to do with this egg do pass chat is going crazy i want to see that chat
room right now how much they're laughing and can i give gonna show you this egg remember
the egg no no you don't know what the egg is how did i get no way i'm never going back
can't go back there this is the office let me look at just the these things here again
put a red fridge here it says suck by the looks of this place what a callback
it controls the time vortex around the soul crushing area or something
ah fuck i'm stuck wait wait wait wait egg egg in the machine egg in this in the printer
nah i don't know egg in the printer it keeps showing me the piñata we'd like to get a time
card please issuing time card for embarrassing i already have one of these uh we really don't
need another embarrassing idle time card toner low pc load time card we'd like to get a time
card please issuing time card for embarrass uh we really don't need enough toner low i need
i need that ink so long i gotta get that ink i need a car i need to make a i need a um cake
tar can i put the can i put the tar in there printer has low ink hey don't touch that i just
changed it really didn't hey it's it's low you you're wrong not happening
okay try it it's gonna work senor perro this is very sensitive equipment get out of here get out
of the way can i talk to anything else in here egg what are you guys i'm throwing the egg in
the perimeter triangle right after the volcano erupted obviously it was a signal flare for
the carvers to come get us see we're not so good with the direction throw the egg come on nope no
way nothing doing shit paypal must be nice finally getting out of that dirt after a thousand
years he's been buried all that time that's so sad he's shrinking funny seeing you guys here
again if there's nothing funny about it it's what we were carved to do hey lighten up on sam and
matt oh you're one to talk mr one offensive stereotype after the next now you're just being
me they're shrieking him he's got like a there's like a zebra may look like a zebra
but my mexican the bridge doesn't do anything attempt to enter soul crushing area please
acknowledge override in san pedro voice print match what about that bug that can talk
i gotta get this down how do i get it down i can't shoot it steal how do i get it down
no way i can't shoot it nope there's no i can't shoot anything can't like drop the string
they are focusing the camera on that thing so many times appears to be made of the finest
leather from only the finest and mutilated cattle still haven't figured out what to do
with the cork let's go back here i haven't been here in a while let me get from here
anything see like that's i thought they were like frogs or something so it was foreshadowing
see that's what i was talking about um it's the model volcano that started this whole mess
it was very thoughtful of future asked to bring it back as a souvenir what's that do
it's for the good of the future max what's that do i'm stream altered what did that do
check out what's this do what does that do what i just do what's the model what did i do
wait a minute what i do what happened it's bosco's model volcano safely sealed up it's
sealed up it's just sealed up but looks like our trusty bulletin board is still in good shape
what somebody died local mariachi pedro died this week due to complications from
inhaling ink ribbon fumes what a waste wait wait wait wait wait wait that's how i get
them out of the room not much use for this anymore i say you're gonna get ink poisoning
so long all right let's go warn him he's gonna have it says we got it game over
that's one of his questions yeah i never i don't know i have to had to bring him like his own
obituary it was like a little thing on the bulletin board yeah so what was the purpose of
the ink ribbon last episode good news senor we found the gruesome details of your horrible
demise oh what a stupid way to die i can think of stupider ways and i could help kind of makes
you want to quit your job huh oh no there are so many no the egg thing again fucking
jesus screw that stupid printer oh no he doesn't care about the printer good nobody's
gonna need this worthless ink ribbon okay there's the ink you can't just throw litter
into the time vortex yeah sam somewhere a time traveling native american is crying
where did it land at the rate we're going last month at the castle in germany oh
okay well there you go i was just talking about how useless that item was wasn't it
well okay timing i guess
so now we'd like to get a time card please can i get you in time card for embarrassing
idol it's blank so long get lost blank time card what does this do can i put it as anything
uh what is it what the hell just look at it max yeah what am i looking at exactly
everything our entire universe before the creation of matter and energy and quantum
particles or something it's at this spot that everything you know or will ever know will be
mr featherly oh hey guys what that's the singularity from which the entire universe
is going to spring in a mind-bendingly tremendous oh the chicken is the chicken is
here the chicken came first we need proof mr featherly sam and max are you really the oldest
living creature in existence or are you the last of a race of terrifying elder gods bent
on restoring chaos to our upstart universe neither i assure you i arrived here quite by
accident how do you like it here why did it take me so long i thought dinner theater in
color florida was i was busy paying attention to like the singularity nothing being here at
the start of it all can't be all bad well i will give it one thing the acoustics are outstanding
how'd you get here i was filming the climactic volcanic eruption scene in midtown cowboys the
motion picture suddenly i found myself abducted onto some type of alien spacecraft after a
frightfully amateurish song and dance number i was deposited unceremoniously into the beginning
of the universe oh that old story the midtown cowboys wait wait wait there's a midtown cowboys
movie uh yes well i'm sure we were going to call you but we decided to go in a different
direction oh we have got to get a new agent sam all right let's go come with us mr featherly
i'm sorry i can't let you do that salmon max that chicken is the source of all life
in the universe can we at least take a photo removing him would cause a catastrophic temporal
paradox catastrophic temporal paradox mr featherly is not the only chicken around here
apparently i am and there's the rub oh that's so cool that's a wicked awesome reference
that's to star fox can't let you do that star fox that's so awesome come back to existence
with us mr f it appears i cannot leave without violating the laws of the universe you'll have
to find a standing see you around mr featherly probably not sam since he'll be long dead before
we're even born that's from 2001 of space odyssey spilo strangle him strangle him you've
been doing a good job mr featherly but we decided to cast someone younger very well as long as i can
leave this accursed wait what are you doing put me down at once suck it up featherly it
only takes a day or two to get used to sam's caustic bo curse you max and sam time stream
altered check us okay so the egg is just there so now let me prove that this egg is real
wait don't throw the egg let me prove that the chicken is the first thing how is this going to
prove it though so the egg did come first but the egg is the first thing so why would i bring the
chicken there it's the time elevator put me down at once not yet wait where are you going
it's he's just with us he's just with us right now okay well can we do this hey look
dear god man do you ever wash that coat he's from before time began yeah turns out the chicken
came first hmm it makes no sense if that's the chicken what's there and now well we left an egg
likely story i love to see that egg but but i'm just kidding boy you past people are so
gullible wait wait wait no don't put me back in there any more questions about the nature of our
existence no the chicken was the big one vaya con Dios bye see you later now the spaceship is
ours to command since sam set course for ancient rome our mission to hug Caligula stop
goofing off max we've got to extend that bridge and return Bosco's soul what's happening
i don't want to go oh no he's through whoops great now we'll have to figure out how to get
all up in there check this out max thousand years spent shivering in and stopping time
you stop time neat now make it go backwards
oh yeah you sure about that slow it down with the molasses
all right now do anything while time is frozen time is now frozen can i turn i can turn this
on let's turn this on attempt to enter soul crushing area please acknowledge but if time
was frozen just make with the bridge already all right all right how would this be happening
this wouldn't be able to move some maps you don't know us but we are time traveling mariachis
with a warning from the future whatever you do to not extend that bridge bridge extended
foreign bodies in time vortex self-destruct sequence engaged
here dumped it over there some more birthdays okay Pedro you take the bog in the diner Pedro
you take the statue loving lady on eastern island i'll take the monster oh yeah good luck max
so now we have to get up uh well that's the ship setting course for the beginning of the
universe total destruction imminent please evacuate evacuate so sam is not gonna save
the game start pulling my hair out and wetting myself in panic knock yourself out now better
hurry though no rat movie okay we're gonna get out the soul vacuum is only strong enough to
suck Bosco's corpse up halfway they can make a time traveling spaceship but they can't invent
an interdimensional portal that doesn't lose action you're gonna go halfway guys speed up
time or something so i say no i'm not going to start an earthquake and he's all whatever
and i'm all what does that mean well that's the kind of fun that doesn't last okay so
this is not strong what do i have i got ai can i do the tar again
uh the list will this help at all and all those oops so what's up maybe do something while
time is frozen okay so get them up there and then freeze and then suck again it won't do
anything well i kind of have to wait what if i just walk over here no okay here we go
so suck them up freeze suck them up so i say no i'm not going to start an earthquake and
freeze everything so then i can't do it again it's already sucking and can i go over there
no it's gonna unfreeze whatever i don't think i can get over there
wait wait wait what just wait wait wait wait hold on a second i can't get over there
let me see what happens so i see yeah okay approaching beginning of the universe
destruction imminent go a little buddy it's now or never where do you think this put up
there anywhere that's not on a spaceship set to self-destruct and hurtling towards
the beginning of the universe all right sam this doesn't work i'll see you in hell
what about bosco okay you can't just leave bosco out there that's bullshit
terriots of the dogs i think it's um somebody said there's an after credits thing well wait
we got a huge cliffhanger yeah they have to what about the egg you got the bad ending
it's real quiet in here it's fucking quiet in here man
so um i uh what did you guys do this weekend did you do anything uh i guess
moan really loud no why would i ever do that i watched this guy stream his name is germa985
why would i read that i don't know why the hell would i there's no reason on earth that was
fun though that was a i like uh time travel shit it's interesting it's fun how people do
time travel stuff and they try to make it work all right let's see you get the singularity
oh that's not good get off your phone i was just checking the i was just checking the time
wait what happened did the game crashed no they get yeah it crashed when i hit the huh no
get off your phone it's the end of the movie the credits are rolling people like
at the very end of the movie the credits roll people start getting up they pick they take their
phones up they haven't looked at it in like three four hours did i actually miss something
like the game just the game actually crashed no i didn't miss anything you leave before the
credits scene no i don't i just like you people start stretching they start moving around
don't be that guy the movie's over the credits roll and people are getting up from their seats
and making sure they have all their stuff sorry i'm rude i i'm ruining you reading the guy's
names not the people getting up standing up going oh that whoa that was fucking awesome
did you i love that part when he yeah when he flew no that was awesome yeah me too
what are you hungry no but me taking my phone up and looking at it for a second is bad
at the end of the movie where the credits are rolling on the screen what has gotten into you
what's gotten into you all i've been on but uh jokes aside did i actually really
did i actually miss something at the end because the game crashed or is that supposed to happen
okay so i what where's our loading screen here what happened all my saves put me down
at wait where are you going you missed the quick time event but yes but there is something
am i getting i'm just being lied to all right well then why are you doing this
everyone said i missed something because the game crashed i i just asked if there's anything
after the credits because the get the the client literally closed the client closed and like broke
that was the joke yeah i don't know but like twitch chat's like you idiot you missed it
you're crazy you're stupid oh i have to check go crazy go stupid all right that's going to be
it for tonight that's a solid place to stop i think that's a major cliffhanger for the next
time and those of you that are saying well there's only one episode left just do it now
well i've kind of had this uh this way to do it and if you think about it that it's actually
a pretty good idea because i don't ever play just one episode like of salmon max leaving
one episode means that i'm gonna start the other season if i would do it now i maybe i
could just be like oh that's it uh salmon max season three i'll do it like a few weeks
you know what i mean doesn't that kind of make it so we do the third season
because i wouldn't do just do like one episode i don't know you know he's depriving us now six
hours is a good stream because then we'll do the bits and everything gets to like
you know seven hours just about i'll be live tomorrow don't worry because another episode will
take us to like a nine hour stream and i don't have the energy for like nine plus straight
hours not today because each episode takes us about two and a half to three hours because
you know we talk about stuff we'll stop we'll go off on you know talking about things doing
things i don't think i have it in me for like a 10 hour stream right now but i'll see you
tomorrow we're gonna play uh heroes of might magic three is the plan so that should be really
fun i'm really looking forward to that i think this you know i'm gonna give you a
prediction here i think the heroes of might magic three streams tomorrow are going to be
i think a lot of material available in here i think some of your favorite characters of
the year might show up here i'm just throwing that out there it's possible there are so many
weird characters and weird creatures in these games you're gonna get you're gonna get attached
to one of them but now i'm not gonna do any multiplayer single player can you can you even
do multiplayer in the original might magic three don't you have to play that like over
like a lamb i don't think so but it should be a lot of fun we're just on a black screen
right now we shouldn't be another really really good important thing here um the internet didn't
drop out at all really i dropped 600 frames in six hours that's really really good hopefully we
can pray to the internet gods that this is going to work and um another thing i wanted to
ask so heroes of might magic three had a remake and apparently it's kind of not good
let me see is it on steam or is it on uh good old games yeah it's on steam here's a my magic
three hd edition am i crazy to say that i shouldn't get this because this version is bad
and like fucked up just get the one from gog the gog one is this actually better okay
yeah i'll just get it from gog doesn't have any of the expansions or anything either
what resolution does it run in i wonder because it is a very old game but i'll probably get it from
gog i'm really looking i haven't played this in a long time and i love this game so we'll see what
happens tomorrow i'm looking forward to it should be a lot of fun but sam and max i will
complete season two and we'll move on to season three i don't see why we wouldn't just
do them at least just do all three seasons i don't know if i'm gonna do the other ones
i know people are like oh there's all this one there's like hit the road there's
sam and max go to hell there's sam and max i'm not sure if i'm gonna do them all
i at least want to get through like the three seasons of the original sam and max and then
take it from there i also don't want to like overdo it where sam and max is like every
single week you know i feel like people would start to get exhausted of sam and max's half
the streams are sam and max at that point i feel like people would just be like uh can you do
anything else so i don't want to like exhaust it and have people not want to see it so we'll see
but anyways uh we're gonna do the bits and the subs and everything so
thanks for watching everybody see you tomorrow that was sam max that time travel episode was
great hit a lot of notes for me it was like really funny too like the first like hour of
that game was like fucking really funny so i think that was that was a good one it was very
good but six hours ago we had uh two dollars oh by the way starting at the regular time tomorrow
i just had um some stuff i had to get done today so i wasn't really i couldn't start it
like between three and four i had to go at like four fifteen four twenty or something
but tomorrow it'll start normal probably like you know in that three to four like three
thirty-ish kind of range i won't be starting late tomorrow there's no reason why i would be
so normal time tomorrow but thank you invader z for the two dollars fifty five cents just
wanted to thank you because you always cheer me up when i'm down even if i only am able to
watch pre-recorded stuff thank you germa really wait didn't i read this why is this
showing up from today that was from a few days ago that's weird well thank you thank
you for that from a few days ago too mr comcast thanks for the three bucks i wrote you
an end of stream song no instrumentals though sorry here it is so it's the end of the stream
i hope you had fun laughs and goofs we sure had a ton but now it's time for the bits we will
read i need you all to behave your silence i will need so snuggle up in bed and turn off
your nightlight there's no kim in my closet i checked it's all right for those of you
leaving i think you are lame watch tomorrow's stream because we're playing a porn game
that's pretty good pretty good i like it i like it thank you for the three dollars thank you some
guy for the five dollars so much for my sleep rhythm germa pluto uh anyways here's a meme
video sometimes you just have to take a risk sometimes you just have to take a risk hello my
dear i don't understand why this is here why does the green goblin come out here
you want to put it on screen all right well let's break this one down
oh this is disney footage now i'll go to jail for like the rest of my life
yeah what's going on with the screen why is this it was like 4 000 by like 880 why is it
doing this what is this resolution feed your guild members and stream legends okay i'll feed
you don't worry we'll do it at the very end actually no i'll do it now i'll do it well
that's nightbot was telling me that nightbot stop i you want to some i've reacted to that
before too somebody said please feed you guys i was like i will i will i gotta remember to do
that that was also nightbot i thought that was somebody in chat saying that you do the
command that's fucking funny uh but thank you dork cube for the 250 yo germa i just got my
first paycheck for my new job so now i can give more bits guilt-free anyways i went back and
watched the e3 streams today and it gave me the warm fuzzies watching it again hope you'll do it
again this year yeah i'm still contemplating whether or not i might go to e3 this year i'm
not sure it depends on a few factors but we'll see it depends on a couple of things thank
you dork you for the 250 and um congrats on that new job i always love the streams so
we can just do whatever they're like so much fun to me thank you for the 250 thank you saucy bird
for the 250 appreciate your streams a lot can you do a larry david impression okay what are you
doing no hold on what are you doing oh my god thank you for the 250 that's old man adam
sandler i actually could do larry david but i'm like a little winded for some reason
that sounded like seinfeld where they both very worked very closely together
a lot of seinfeld's humor actually is larry david i'm not sure how many you guys know that
you learn something every day go watch curb your enthusiasm it's the best show it's like the
top two best shows on television that are comedies everyone knows that there's at least
five people here that didn't what's number one it's impossible i can't tell you
the top there's like top three top two i wouldn't be able to give you number one
always sunny in philadelphia that's up there yep that's a that's in the top two
um that's curb your enthusiasm and always sunny philadelphia this is the best two tv
shows ever made that were like comedies yeah that's my story i'm sticking to it
south park oh shit yeah that's up there that is but no i wouldn't say top two
i think south park maybe south park five ten years ago i really really liked was it was super into
it i haven't really watched um much of the newer seasons but i would have to argue that the
first like the yeah that somebody just said the first 10 years yeah you're josh yeah first 10
seasons of south park were yeah they're really great they're awesome are we talking about
cartoons um no i think just in general the new seasons were great i just i haven't seen them
i've seen a few episodes from the i've like scattered them around of the last three
seasons or four seasons i've probably seen maybe six or seven episodes yeah these are
like just favorite shows that are like comedies i would say my favorite tv show ever made was
game of thrones i don't think i would say that anymore um i'm not sure i would say that's the
best show i've ever seen anymore breaking bad is like up there for like just shows that are
great that need to be watched okay what was it freaking out better call sol it is that i gotta
see the newer seasons that i watched seasons one and seasons two of better call soul and
i thought it was fantastic i just didn't get the gulf i just haven't had like the time it
i kind of season three came out i just didn't watch it i want to though it's kind of on the
list of never-ending tv shows did you enjoy what else peters are dave chapelle i love dave
chapelle dave chapelle is fucking hysterical his old tv show on comedy central is is just
he's a just brilliant comedian i do have to check out chernobyl that's true i've heard it's
insane i've heard it's like the best show ever i have to watch it there's a lot of just good tv
huh talk about chernobyl the new hbo show you're my favorite tv show wow thank you
that's so like no thank that's thank you damn that like i feel like great what the heck i feel
fucking fantastic right now thank you though no for real that's that's very touching i'm blushing
but hey thank you to uh gnarly for the five dollars here's five bucks give me the straw
no this thing would probably go for a couple thousand if i did it on camera if off camera
i said hey here's a straw that i put in my mouth i don't think it would go for very much
on camera if i like stuck it in there and i bit it and pulled it out you'd have a document
and if i signed it like if i did something to it so you knew it was the right one you would have
a documented twitch clip of me doing that and having the thing written on it so you'd be able
to prove it it would be asset backed you know that it would be an asset backed clip what
time do you usually start streaming uh i don't have like a day schedule i just usually about
three four times a week starting between three and four p.m pacific it just happens about four
times a week today i was a little bit later but i've been the last like two weeks i've
been starting at like before 330 the last six or seven streams at least the last two weeks
i've started before like 330 it starts between three and four p.m during that one hour window
and the reason why that is a thing is having the one hour window makes it so
if the stream happens after four it's like actually fucking late i was actually really
actually late today but having that window means that i can't because it you guys have
known this you know i've been streaming for like almost four what four five fucking years
now having a time a hard time that's like four p.m that means like 4 15 every time so
it means like having that window of an hour is like you can get in there you can set it up
you can get your errands done you can get your stuff for the day done and ready and then
because essentially what happens is you know i'm here for six to eight hours right and
this when i oh i'm gonna take a pee it's like two minutes you know so you kind of have to get all
your shit done like for the day before you start because i'm here it's been six and a
half hours just about and i went pee once you know i'm saying so it's like it's you kind of
have to get all your shit like front loaded because sometimes if you stream for like eight
you know seven eight nine hours which i think the average stream time of the stream is
somewhere in like between like six and a half to like seven and a half usually it's like a seven
plus ish hour average for streams on this channel so that's just that's like seven hours
of i can't like go do you know i can't like hey i'll see you later i'm gonna i'm gonna
go like do this i'm gonna get like my tires rotated i'll be back you get to shit front
morning bathroom visits well that's nothing like going to the bathroom
here's like a streamer insider thing when i'm like to make this more clear
if i'm here for eight hours straight what i don't like go to the bathroom i can barely eat so you
have to like front load everything and have everything done before you start streaming
because you know you know i'll go take like a piss and grab a water but i'm not gonna put
like the b-write backup screen up for like 15 to 20 30 minutes you know because well why not
because people leave if you if you hit that brb button and you've gone for more than five
minutes 10 minutes people just will be like yeah whatever see you later you know it's like
kind of one of those things you have to juggle between like do you want to have like
a good straight stream or do you want to break it up or some people do two streams a day
right they stream for like three four hours in the morning and then like three or four
hours at night i i i think that uh i'm pretty sure like average stream time is not that long
for most streams isn't it don't i'm thinking of most people that i know that stream like four
to five hours is typical usually like three four five hours max for a lot of streamers
most are like three to four yeah that sounds fun yeah but remember i i mean i also only stream
like three to four times a week i'm not straight i don't stream every day so if i stream for
six seven eight hours at a stream and i do it four times a week kind of makes up for the
fact that i don't do like a three to four hours stream five six days a week you know
all things to consider right but uh what the hell were we even talking about
are we talking about front load and shit oh yeah yeah i'm just because we're talking about
errands and sometimes if like something comes up that i have to get done and i need to do
like that comes up in the day it's like oh fuck well kind of have to do it what was
my longest stream the simpsons uh i don't know 14 hours i think is the longest 13 14 hours
oh cman was like 12 lifeline was 12 how long was clock tower 10 9 i think simpson's hit and run
was 11 it's to a voice game i don't know how people i know it's not a thing that people do
that regularly but streaming even streaming more than more than eight to 10 hours and one
stream it's just you get so i get so like tired like talking you know 10 12 hours you
like i feel like i'm gonna bite throat's gonna explode i can't imagine like doing
10 plus hour streams on on a regular basis like 12 it was 15 hours yesterday
i would turn to dust streaming that long worries me yeah i've always been of the opinion i mean
i remember i come from youtube i i like i don't like to do like super long long long long
form content and i don't think i'm even capable of doing it i i have these like weird extreme
moments of like super high energy super low energy so if i do like a super high energy
you know three four hours that gets like i'm all right that was really fun but i never want
to get to that point where i'm like pressing more than i should or want to you know just
for the sake of having like a six to ten hour stream i i can't do it and i don't i don't want
to do that either because then it starts to become it starts to become something that i'm
making myself do because i feel like i have to when i think the best streams that we
do here in this community that best streams that i've put on the channel are ones that i
just i'm just doing what i want to do you know looking at the clock and it's like oh
it's been like seven and a half hours i really should probably keep going i should keep
going and you get tired and it's just not as fun and you're not as i've had that mentality
for a while just do drugs because i remember i want to try to give you guys the best that
i know that i can try to do i think i owe that to you till i try to give you the best
stream i can do because i want to have the most fun and do the most i don't want streams
to turn into like phoned in they have to be this certain length and they have to be this
certain day and they have to be well it's got to be like 10 hours you have to because
then it becomes that thing that is like oh i have i have to stream this long and it kind of
puts a wrench into everything that i like to do because the nature of like streaming and youtube
and is you know are you guys having fun all right you guys think the things are interesting
or entertaining and i can't like force myself to do that i can't make myself like be entertaining
i just i i can't make these streams fun i have to have fun you know what i'm saying now you
guys know this we talk about this every you know a few weeks we kind of bring up something
about it you can't push your stuff and streaming is no longer fun yeah i know then that's
i don't want to do that even if it's like to the detriment of
like don't know my like but what about like the money and the and the clout and the and the
career and no i have to like doing this i can't just like force myself to do it i don't like
i have to enjoy it otherwise i'm not going to be able to do it
oh i need that clout i don't i could care less just be a tuber oh wow what a mood as fuck
no you guys get it i just i feel like sometimes i like to talk about it because
i want you like the streams i want you to think this is a fun place and i hope you guys
say it is me forcing myself to do something is not going to be fun for anybody for the sake
of just being on camera longer or doing something in particular it's not going to work that way
but yeah don't be forced yeah i i think i take the necessary steps to make that a thing that
i don't do stop being wholesome and start being funny i like the variety of the games
well that's just because i can't i can't do the same thing over and over again i can't
team fortress 2 was the last thing that i really was super into that i could do every day
for years nothing else has come along that has done that since and i mean maybe it is
because i'm getting a little older you know i turned i'm 34 this year maybe i'm getting
a little bit older and my tastes are changing and it's possible you know what i'm saying
streamers that hate what they're doing yeah i don't want that to happen because then that's
a detriment to your viewing experience if i don't like what i'm doing and i'm not having a good
time when i'm doing it and i'm just doing it because i think i have to it's that becomes that
sort of weird dynamic where it's essentially like a routine just going through a routine
and i don't want that to happen here you're really 34 yeah i turned 34 and uh date to be
determined grandpa no i don't feel forced i don't i just want to give you my side of the coin here
but why some of these things are done a certain way i do not feel forced at all do
not worry about that just giving the reasoning behind why there's some things on this channel
that are the way that they are and how they kind of just have to stay that way but uh we
are almost through the bits here we have a little bit longer to go we've got a smelly boy
thanks for the 250 there's nothing funnier than watching you get gas lit by chat into thinking
toothbrushes are recycled now i knew that was bullshit for the first thing that somebody said
but the real embarrassing thing is like the water thing i i have no response to any of that
shit i knew i knew i shouldn't have said like a brand name oh i'm gonna have a big tall glass
of that water he's a piss drinker thank you though smelly boy thank you germa lied about
taco bell for the 250 germa don't drink water all water comes from the ocean and fish
pee and poop in the ocean not to mention all plastic and chemicals doctors say you should
exclusively drink drink delicious mountain dew baja blast from that restaurant you've got the
manager fired from you know which one germa chomp great stream germa love all your content
thank you for the tidbit there i love how your name is germa lied about taco bell
yet you reference the lie of me getting somebody fired from taco bell it seems a
little odd was it a lie or was it i don't know i got two uh two different sides there
thank you frody and weapon for the 250 nothing to say just happy tuesday happy tuesday to you
as well frody and weapon thank you thank you big ren for the three dollars germa your streams
have been consistently my favorite things to watch and brighten my day i lost my best friend
last year to suicide and the bright atmosphere you bring to every stream has always helped me
smile thanks so much for helping me laugh and seeing the humor and things shout out to chat
too much love to everyone germa hart i drew a screenshot of you from the first stream in
vegas hope it's all right first informants i'm really really sorry to hear that that's terrible
that rips my heart in half to hear that but i really am happy that you mentioned chat here
because you know people say oh like i love your streams i love your streams that they thank
you for the streams there's so many people here that are fucking awesome people that are
really funny that are really interesting that make these streams what they are i think
so let me uh see the art too this is great comedy geniuses attract yeah it's we're all just
we're all just a bunch of geniuses come on you watch this stream because you're a genius
uh i'm gonna let's put this artwork on here so you can see
me this is from the landing of the balloon look at that sun look at that sun in the
background that's awesome thank you so much for this and i'm i'm glad that there's a
community here and this stream here is is something that can brighten your day
especially considering um something so terrible like that i'm really sorry to hear that
but thank you so much for the three dollars thank you the artwork this is very very good
thank you i'll give you a link for those of you that want to link uh thank you to mac
dazzles for the ten dollars hey german just recently got back into watching twitch streams
a few months ago and i'm glad to see you're still streaming i used to watch your stuff back
in 2016 you've been the highlight of my week and keep me company while i work so i drew some
pictures of you i remember when you had that weird wrestling sound as your sub noise if that
serves my memory correct thanks for all the fun times you're the most unique streamer
music right it's a little album here well welcome back thank you for the ten dollars
here's this imgur album here destroy yeah that was a while ago that was like at least like
two or three years ago yeah that sub sound was like 25 seconds long can you imagine if
i had like a 30 second sub sound still they wouldn't even be a live stream it would be
like a hundred times weird flex no that's not supposed to be a flex that's supposed to be
like a i don't want the streams to be bad i want to show this one i like this one here
is the one of them from the uh album i'll just bask in its glory two different sides of uh
of jeremy here tonight back to back i got so many different i got so many different looks
i've got i can do old characters senile characters men i can do uh my voice can get really low
some of you get that one some of you get it i don't have to even explain that some of you
get it but uh thank you these are these are great thank you so much welcome back to the
streams that was mac dazzles yeah appreciate the artwork too we only have a couple more
to go so i'm gonna throw in the credits thanks everybody for subscribing to this channel
you're all fucking awesome let me feed the stream legends crowd i'll see you tomorrow
for heroes of might and magic 3 could be a good one let's get the credits on the screen
thank you everybody for real thank you thank you thank you so god damn much where are ads
i don't want ads on my streams unless you get one randomly in a pre-roll that i have no
control over here come the credits thank you for supporting the stream and now let's feed
everybody stream legends see tomorrow at the regularly scheduled time not late i think it was
today much love to everybody have a great rest of your night a fantastic evening get some good
sleep we also had uh another one or two bits that came in here we had a 250 come in for
error paradox thanks for the 250 hey i got a job too here's to you and chat reminder i'm
coming to vegas around october for my birthday and the best present ever will be to meet you
and have jexcon in the mgm grand just a reminder no need to act on it love your
streams and how wholesome and sweet you are jexcon i wondered like how many people would
actually be interested in something like that jerma lied about jexcon
i didn't lie about jexcon i was saying am i never allowed just to like come up with
an idea on stream you know what i mean like is it a lie or is it like a hey do you think
this would be fun i want to like do something like this it might be fun that's not a lie
that's like coming up with a it's like something fun i can't wait for the jerma lied about
jexcon jerma lied about like level up lounge jerma lied of this is gonna be like four more
of them we add like there's gonna be more people that are in this chat in like another
couple years that have those names there's gonna be it's gonna be full of jerma lied about x
it's gonna be half of you guys yeah maybe stop lying
if you don't play ace attorney i already talked about it talked about ace attorney
jerma lies at the bottom of the ocean holy shit are you trying to fucking oh my god
thank you for the 250 though error paradox
what the fuck okay i'm getting out of here you guys are starting to get fucking dark
i'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna try might and magic should be fun
take care everybody have a great rest of your night see you real soon good night guys