What's up? How you doing? You doing good? Where you been? Oh, you doing that? Oh, man. Me too.
He's in the bathroom. I'm not in the bathroom. Sitting at my desk. I missed a huge raid?
Uh, I did not. I'm looking over here. I don't see anything. I was already raided. You can't raid an
offline channel, can you? No, you cannot. You can? You can. I did not know you could do that. You can
raid an offline channel. That's just dropping a bunch of people off at like an empty movie theater
with the screen blank. They're like, enjoy the movie, stupid. And just taking off. Like,
I bust you guys into a movie theater in this new movie playing. It wasn't any scheduled movie for
that day or that time. And then what do you do? Where do you go? You guys all like shake hands
and like, oh, see you later. I guess there's no movie here. And you go out of the movie theaters
you're in. And you start just opening up other doors to other movies. Hey, dude, dude, Force
Awakens is playing over here. Oh, this is not cool, man. Like 10 of you go that way. You just go in.
Like 40 of you go see, I don't know, what was it? Popular movie that came out like last year or two
years ago? Nightways? I don't know. What was that? 2010? I don't know. I don't see movies. I don't
know what movies have come out. Anyways, today we're gonna play Speaking of Star Wars. We're gonna
play Star Wars Jedi Knight Jedi Academy. This is one of the most requested games that I've gotten
on this channel in a long time. People are like, dude, get in that game right now. I don't care
what you're doing. Stop doing everything and play Jedi Academy. I played Jedi Academy multiplayer
with Star like six or seven years ago. I never played the actual video game. So we're gonna play
the out that was loud and I good thing I muted the desktop audio because a bunch of you would
have just flew out of your chair like I almost just did. You can thank me later. Slaughter, slaughter.
I love this game. Yeah, I'm looking forward to it. I just did. Fuck you. Fuck you. What's going on
here? You're gonna murder younglings. I am a youngling. So no, I'm one of the younglings.
Hey, easy case. Thanks for the 10 community subs and cry Thor TV. Thanks for 515 subs right here.
Thanks guys. He thinks he's young. I am young to heart. That's all that matters. A 35 year old man
and at least like 26 year old man's body. And then when I'm like 45, I'm gonna be a 45 year old man
in like a 32 year old body. And then when I turn 50, you're just 50. You're just 50. That's where
you start to become you just become old at like 50 plus other way around. No, that means I'm I look
young. I'm a 45 year old man and like a 32 year old man's body. Like I'm I still I look like a 32
year old at like 45. 40 is the new 30. Anyways, I don't give a shit what anybody says. All right,
let's go. Let me unmute this. The new game here make sure you have new game selected.
45 year old cams not on better not be killed. We got Star Wars Jedi Knight Jedi Academy.
I think I make a actual Star War, right? Why don't I use that as a noun? Like it was a person.
I okay. I'm not gonna do anything hard. Extremely difficult game, difficult game,
normal game or easy game. I'm just doing normal fuck all that bullshit. We go. All right. Are you
you buckle your seatbelt? Good. Here we go. All right. Species. Hold on. Turn on. Turn this way.
This is there's a character creator. Keldor male. Maybe. Rodian male. Zabrak human. Should I just be
a human? I feel like if you can't play a human because that's just like making a human in
World of Warcraft. Like I'm on my like eighth character. I guess it's going to be another
human. No, you don't want to make a human. Maybe I kind of do. I think I want to make a human.
That's so boring. But whatever. Don't fucking do it. Oh my God. But I don't know. All right. I
changed my mind. I think I want to be this guy. No, wait. This one. No, no, no, no, no. This one
is Big Rideau. I don't want to be Rideau. OK, I think this one. All right. So that's the head
torso. I don't want to make any more World of Warcraft references, but this is all
like starter gear. This is like level one tabard. I'd be level one tabard non-human
Rodian male. I made my own guild. I haven't even gotten the 10 signatures yet. And I tried to make
my own tabard. Tabard. Whatever. I'm going to make wild jokes today, I guess. Relax. Relax. Relax.
Oh, wow. He made a World of Warcraft joke again. It's just in the top of the mind. I don't know why.
What color do I want? I like the gray. Yeah. All right. Looks good. Hmm. That looks good too.
What do you think? This? I like those boots. This is a good setup. All right. Yeah, this is fine.
Oh, shit. OK, hold on. This is incredibly important. What? There's only one lightsaber?
Oh, man. Hold on. Which one of these do I want? All right. I kind of want the kazoo. Yeah, this
thing you go and you can put it in your mouth and be like, um, it's a blunt. No, just don't hold it
the wrong way. You press the wrong button. You don't press like the kazoo button. It just goes
right to the back of your head. Um, what do I? I don't want to be like the Luke Skywalker. Look,
I'm not going to do this. Maybe I am. Orange is kind of cool. Although I would probably have like,
it would probably be yellow or white. No, no, no, no, no. Of course it wouldn't.
I would have the darksaber. It's only one and it's mine. I would use it. I would be my blade.
I think I want to do purple school while you're out partying. I studied.
What? All right. No. OK. Well, how about we do the one that's on the shelf at every like target?
This one. I like it. I think I might want yellow too. All right. Medium combat style. Medium.
I can't. I can't change that. All right. I cannot change the combat style. I just have a medium
saber. Green if you're cool. No, I want the I like I want the like yellow or white or dark saber.
I'm ready. Let's go. Oh, here we go. Star Wars. You can't DM see a this stream because it's in a
video game, not a real fucking movie. You can't. I've read all kinds of threads about how this works
and this is allowed. Is it 10 years after the Battle of Endor, the Imperial remnant continues
to be driven back by the New Republic, forcing the Imperials to adopt increasingly desperate tactics
in the ongoing struggle. Meanwhile, Jedi Master Luke Skywalker moves to restore the Jedi to their
formal place as peacekeepers of the galaxy at his Jedi Academy on Yavin IV.
What's with the space? Jaden Kor, a promising student from Crusant, is en route to the
Academy after achieving the impossible, creating a lightsaber without any formal Jedi training.
So he's a fraud and he's being brought to the Capitol for justice and prosecution.
Crusant. I don't know. I couldn't read it at me. We'll be arriving at the Academy in
just a few minutes that Mark Hamill Mark Hamill has to be. That would be so great.
Wait, why is this like Harry Potter? Does this happen? Aren't you excited? We're going to be
Jedi learning the ways of the force building a lightsaber. Of course you already have one.
I'm going to get one of those stupid training sabers. I wouldn't worry about that. Wait,
what? I talk? I can't help it. I want to make a good impression. I'm not silent protagonist.
You seem really nervous. Aren't you? I mean, why would you be? You already have a lightsaber,
so you're probably way ahead of me. I'm Rosh, by the way. I'm not supposed to have this? Why
do I have this? What's your name? Jaden. So where'd you get that lightsaber? Well, it's kind of a
long story. I found myself on. What? That's the noise you make when you have a wedgie,
not the fucking plane is going down. What? We made an emergency landing several clicks west of the
academy. Oh, there it is. Is everyone all right? I think so. We'll send a shuttle to pick you up.
Can you lead the students to the nearby Masasi temple? Is that him? Affirmative Academy. We'll
meet you there. All right, let's go. But who is this? I'm lost on the characters. Holy shit,
you go fast. Jaden, we can't get to you. Make your way to the temple. All right. Jaden. Hey,
I'm stuck. Can you help? Hold on, Rosh. I'm on my way. Jaden, see if you can make your way around
there. All right, let's go. I bet you wish you had one of these, but I don't know how to use this
though. Okay, let's go. Should I put the thing down? Maybe you can use your lightsaber to cut
those trees down and make a bridge. Oh, maybe I can. Yeah, that'd be cool. Come on over here.
Thanks, Jaden. Let's get to the temple. All right, to the temple. Oh, watch out. We've got.
I don't know what I think. What? Jaden, see if you can make your way around there.
I'm training. I just killed the motherfucker. Maybe you can use your lightsaber to cut those
trees down and make a bridge. I didn't know I could kill him. Let's get to the temple.
Do I have a blast? Maybe I shouldn't do anything. Put this thing away.
Just flailing around like a kid on Christmas morning that just opened it up. Okay, cool, cool,
cool, cool, cool. This way. Follow me to the temple. Kill him again. I'm not gonna kill him again.
I can't. What's in there? Oh, checkpoint. What's wrong with me? What's wrong with me?
Yeah, I would stay the fuck away from this guy. Like, stay at least like five car lengths away
from me, man. I'm not going near this guy. What? Why can't I hit him? Pretty cool trick, huh?
I learned that at the. Didn't go to the academy yet. We haven't even stepped in there.
Haven't done one class. I watched a few YouTube videos. What do you think?
Self-taught Jedi from YouTube tutorials. Hey, maybe you can use your saber to make another
bridge. Hey, dick. Why can you die from that? Such a shitty cadet.
All right, just let him do the work. Well, this is what happens, man. With two cadets,
we have no idea what we're doing. I just evade this lightsaber. I don't know how the hell I'm
doing with it. Kill. Shoot it. You didn't have a chance. Like, I'm not cool. I'm not with it. I'm
just a guy that bought this somehow. This was fucking like $45,000 on eBay. And I thought it
was fake, but I was like, you know what? I'm going to go for it. What if it's real? Well,
at least it turned out it was real. It's just a murderer on the loose. Hey, maybe you can use
your saber to make another bridge. Hey, did he not make it? He didn't make the jump.
I am so disappointed that he didn't make the jump. How did you not make the jump? What? He
jumped into the wall. How did you die? I don't understand. Jeremy, use quick save. What button
is it? All right, don't kill him. Shoot him. Nice teamwork, man. All right, make the jump.
Hey, maybe you can use your saber to make another bridge. Um, did he die from fall damage?
Oh, my God, I'm so mad that I missed that. He must have died from fall damage.
Let's go. Let's go. I feel like I need to keep an eye on you in case you do something stupid.
All right, move. All right, go in. Wait till he's done. Dude, holy shit, we suck.
Mark Hamill right now is like forced TV watching us. He's sitting on his couch,
which is this forced camera pointed at us. Oh, man, I've got a lot of work to do on these two.
I finally sheathed the lightsaber.
All right, I'll check it out. Um, is this supposed to be getting this hot on my hands?
I mean, I don't know. I forgot gloves. It's really hot. It's really hot to hold.
Obtain a blaster rifle. Oh, I did. Is that a Sith? Oh, my God, what happened? Quick save.
Just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. What's the quick save button? What's the quick save?
Somebody tell me while I'm looking. F5. It's not F5. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on. Stop holding your head. I know it's crazy, but go. Hey, maybe you can use your
saber to make another bridge. Yes, they can't get over. We're fine. Let's go.
What is it? F12 and F9. Okay. That's fucking screenshot. Of course it is.
There's gonna be a lot of screenshots today. A lot of them. What's the point of this move?
I can't even hit them. Rebind it. Oh, yeah, I couldn't do that. I could do that.
Quick save is gonna be, um, hmm, like, I don't know, dash. And then quick, quick load is gonna be
equals. All right, we're good. All right, good. There are stormtroopers over there.
You're the one with the lightsaber. I can't skip it. Yes, again. All right, I'm going for it. Wait,
we're gonna use my force to save. Okay, then this, who, who is this guy? I'm not the lightsaber.
I'm Sith. Wait, is this a, this must be a cadet too. This is a Sith cadet. All right, kill him.
You lost to a kid. I didn't actually turn dismemberment on. I think it is. Turn on
dismemberment. It's on. It's not. Turn it on. Turn it on. It's not on. What? It can be more?
Yeah, what is actually, what you mean? What? The console command? Okay, I'll do it.
Who are you? Katarn, at your service. Welcome to a day in the life of a gym. What happened?
What did happen? Traitor. I saw a huge flash of light and ran over to find you. Just lying
unconscious. Do you recall anything? I saw three people. One was holding some sort of scepter and
it was glowing. That's all I can remember. A scepter? That sounds bad. Are you able to stand? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay. Peter. Stop. You always sense a disturbance in the force.
But yeah. No, he should look back and say, okay, Spider-Man. Residual dark side aura from this
temple. Absent. You'll stay here and investigate. I'd love to. Why don't you take the kids back home
now? Be careful, Kyle. You thought that was Yoshi singing? That was Luke Skywalker. It was. Singing.
Did you recover Skywalker's records? I have no idea what just happened. Yes.
With all the Jedi in the jungle, it was almost too easy. Excellent. Let's actually go over what
they're actually doing with their mouths here. I'd like to welcome all our new students to the Jedi.
It's like, you will learn to defend yourself with a lightsaber. You will also study diplomacy,
history, and more. Oh, it has been the practice of the Jedi diplomacy, history, math. However,
since there are still so few of us, we will be assigning multiple students to one master.
Ralph, you will be assigned to master home. I can't wait to begin my training.
Stop talking, dude. You're gonna get in trouble. What the? You will be assigned to master Katarn.
Jaden Kor, you'll also work with master Katarn. Now, let's begin with your first lessons. And may
the force be with you. And there was nothing, but the area around the temple felt strange.
There it is. Dark side aura was gone. Troubling. But let's look into this later. Your students are
ready to get started. Master Katarn, it's an honor to be serving under you. First of all,
just call me Kyle. The titles make my skin crawl. Okay, Mr. Kyle. You're not serving under me.
I'm gonna teach you, and you're gonna learn. That's it. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to offend you.
Don't worry, Rosh. You didn't. I'm offended by professionals.
This is the bad guy. Super relatable in the first 20-30 minutes of the movie.
Somebody that you start to trust. Bad guy alert. Bad guy alert. Call me Kyle. Bad guy.
This is one of the many training grounds of the academy.
What's the super dismemberment? When you're ready, Jaden, go through that door.
Wait. Oh, God. The chat's gonna be going so fast.
Here. Wait, wait, wait. Yeah, main character for the past three games. He was the hero of the last
game. Oh. Oh, well. Fucking completely wrong. I don't play these games. Oh, I have to download
a dismemberment mod. I'm not doing that right now. I'll do that. I'll do that on a break.
No, you don't. No, you don't. It's a console command. Somebody just gave me like a download
link. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. We'll get G saber dismemberment one. Is that it? G saber
dismemberment one. Is that gonna work? That's the one. Three. Set it to three. I don't- I don't-
Set it to three? What the fuck? God damn it. Three? But I don't wanna do- All right. I just
typed it in. I just did it. All right. It's in. What just happened? Why did I lose the game?
It's a simple- I just did it. Okay. All right. Let's go. What are we doing?
Well, at least I'm just burning him.
Teacher, teacher. Teacher, we have a problem. Teacher, teacher, teacher. Teacher, I don't know
what happened to him. How do I get in? He turned around. He like caught me an idiot and then like
he went forward and it went through his neck. I turn around for two seconds and this is what
you two fools do. What am I supposed to do? All right. This is my training, right? Hey,
why'd you close it behind me? This course will familiarize you with your core force abilities.
These are powers that every force user has. As you progress in your training, you will learn new
abilities. Both the light and dark sides will be open to you. Remember, abilities are not inherently
good or evil. It's how you use them. Every Jedi is naturally stronger in different areas of the force
and it will be up to you to decide what to focus on. Yep, dark side. I'm gonna go fold.
I want to shoot electricity at my hands. How do we do that? Kyle, how do I shoot electricity at my
hands? These will help you lightsaber. Ready? Was that him saying that three times? Like three, two, one?
Okay, so I just did the block. He's doing it automatically.
Oh, okay. I thought I was supposed to ricochet back like Luke does in movie four. What a spoiler.
Nice work, Rush. I just run through? You did well too, Jaden. Oh, he's talking about both of us.
Even when inactive, it can diffuse a potentially volatile situation.
Trust me on that. As you train over additional fighting styles, changing styles during combat
can surprise your opponent, allowing you to gain the upper hand. Okay. From here on out, we'll talk
via comm link in each area. Let's move on. Moving up. New objective. Okay, Jaden. Use the force.
I have to do a force jump? How do I do a force jump? I don't know. He didn't tell me how to do it.
What kind of training is this? What kind of training is that? Hey, Jaden, do a force jump.
How? I don't know. Just use the force. Yeah, you just have to believe, right? Isn't that the whole
force? You have to believe that you can do it, therefore you can do it. Okay, so how do I do this?
You have to look in the game manual. All right, key binds. Movement. Hold use plus step to lean.
Okay. Run, walk, step. Force powers. Push, pull, speed, sense, absorb. Force power. Force next.
Okay. Force speed. Hold the jump button. What? This is regular jump. Force power.
All right. Push is F1. Ooh. Hey, Jaden, this should keep you busy till I finish the course.
No, he's cheating. No, he's the bad guy. Okay, got it. Oh, that's General Grievous. Force,
push. It's just Tony Hawk. Oh, dismemberment. I see it. It just is Tony Hawk underground.
God damn it. That's exactly what this is. It's just they don't have skateboards. They have
lightsabers. Okay. What do I do? Oh, what is this thing though? Force push. Nope. Force slide.
Okay. Force sense is F3. Oh, I've never pressed that button. It just makes the FOV turn off.
Turn it off right now. Oh my god, that hurt. I hated every second of that. What are these things?
Use your force sense. It's health. Oh, okay. Is force sense just a little blue circle thing?
Or do I actually have to press F3 because I hate that? F4. Oh, I hate that too. I also hate that.
What am I looking for? A way to get out. A wall? I mean, I just have to get up there, but what?
Use your force brain. Use your force brain. Okay. So what do I do about these?
Press them. Force push them. Pull them out. Get up there. Use your force brain.
I just love deal of fates. All right. Wait. This is going to be dangerous. Force jump. Force sense.
In this next area, you can use the force to speed up both physically and mentally.
Okay. Force rugs. That's what that is. Okay. F3 is force speed. What the fuck? I'm being too slow.
No, I don't have any force power left. Hold on. Where's the force energy bar?
Oh, just barely made it. It wasn't a competition. I'm sorry. I am gizing too. It's no big deal.
Hurry the fuck up. Oh, here we are. This wasn't a competition. That's a I'm a punch puncher in
the face pose. Expel him. You're expelled. Doing a great Sims impression.
He just said something to Jayden that he did not like.
Apology accepted, Rod. That's settled. It's Kyle. Yes, Matt. Uh, Kyle. Matt?
Okay. Do you almost call him Matt? He forgot his first name. Sorry about that, Matt. Oh,
yeah. Your name's not Matt. Kyle. Right. Another first name. Did some research on that strange
mark from the clothing we found at the temple. It is the symbol of Marco Ragnos, a Sith Lord
that died almost 5,000 years ago. 5,000 years. Are you serious? Do you know Jesus? Of course,
you're serious. Holy shit. Be on the lookout for information regarding a group affiliated
with Ragnos. Sure thing, Luke. Jesus was like the original Jedi. You receive countless requests
for assistance from all over the galaxy. Since we believe in at the academy, students of all
levels help with these requests. Since you're an initiate, however, Kyle will travel with you
on most of your missions in order to instruct you and ensure your safety. Okay. So wait, did
my report card? I killed six people on my first day. What? Okay, hold on. Wait, this is missions?
Cult investigation, merchant rescue, emergency assistance, droid recovery, or mercenary activity.
Cult investigation on Corellia. Okay. The city of Coronet on Corellia has had numerous reports
of activity by the disciples of Ragnos. However, it's not clear if it's really the Sith cult
or if the locals are just being paranoid about after hearing about it on the holonet.
Go to Coronet and determine the truth. I still have a few contacts in Coronet. We'll hit a few
of the local cantinas and see what crops up. We'll also follow up with some of the people
who reported this so-called cult activity. It looks like Earth. The screen allows you to
increase any one force power by a single rank. The maximum is third rank. Look on any light or dark
force power icon to upgrade. Core powers cannot be upgraded. Once a power has been upgraded,
the weapon screen will be made available. Return the upgraded power to its original rank. Click on
it again. Oh, here we go. Dark side. Force drain. Allows Jedi to transfer the life essence of a
person to themself. Okay. Force grip is the Darth Vader choke. Darth Vader choke. There it is. I
don't care. That's what I want. Lightning. Allows Jedi to hurl devastating electrical attacks out
of their hands. Jedi launches a single bolt that fires forward to do instant damage. Wait, hold on.
Yeah. You're a traitor. No. I can control it. Said every single person before him. Unlimited power.
Weapons. This screen allows you to choose two weapons and a throwable device for the upcoming
mission. A lightsaber and a blaster pistol are given to you. Choose a weapon, click on the icon
to deselect a weapon. Okay. All right. Where's just, where's black robe and bare hands?
Destructive electro magnetic pulse gun. What's this? Thermal detonator? Oh, I want a grenade.
Okay. Mines or packs? I want the grenade. Pulse rifle used against droids. Ripping apart living
material. All right, cool. And the Wookie crossbow. All right. Begin. Let's go.
Jan punches the weak way right in the holy shit. Eyes on the road. Are we crashing or is this
normal coming from that cargo trap? Wait, this is like we're going down. Oh, we're on train.
No, we're not. How you fly this plane. You can't even see. We're just sitting in front of a
computer. You take the tram. I'll take care of these ships. Okay. How do I do the, uh,
uh, okay. Weapons, force powers, lightning has, I don't know. Okay. Mouse four is going to be
lightning. Oh my God. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. Good, good, good. All right. Let's go.
Open the door right now. Open the door. R2, get them to open the door. R2. All right. The other
side of this door definitely should have a video camera and just play that for the ad for the
company that made the doors. That's all you need. Is there a lever? Where's the lever?
Wait, I can't go in there. I'm trying to force pull. I can't force pull through glass.
All right. Let's, holy shit. Shock him. That's it. Get out of here. You're dealing with a Jedi
master. What? Oh, it's C3Ville. That cut his head off. Just member men. It's on. I turned it on.
It's level three. All right. Force pull. Force pull. Use your force hands. Dude, I'm trying to
interact with this. It's not speed. What's going on? Press enter. What the fuck? Enter. All right.
Nope. Sit down. Wait, I need to go back that way. Force hands. Press enter. All right. So now what?
We detached the train. Do the console command again. Hold on. Not yet. Save it. I just did.
Save. All right. We're good with this backup. Looking good. All right. Force jump. Wait. Use
this force speed. Good. Is that good? Good blaster or bad blaster? Okay. Green does not mean good
blaster health. No, I'm not a Jedi. Jedi in training. But thank you. I appreciate it. That
means I must be doing pretty well. Uh oh. Sith training. He doesn't know that I have Sith powers
too though. He's fucked. You're next. Tell me to stop. Stop. Stop. Force gun. Can I take the
lightsaber? Oops. Power up. Got it. Cut that arm off. That's a warning. That's a warning. I'm going
to give one shot to get out of here. I gave him a warning. I'm good. I'm a Jedi. I gave you a
warning. I said go home. Get out of here. It's not worth it. And he decided to charge me. I have to
do the commands in order. Hold on. What do you want me to do? Help us Obi-Wan, then G saber more
realistic, then G dismemberment three. What are you telling me to do here? What is all this bullshit?
This is gonna make the game like a joke. Not yet. I'm having fun playing Jedi Master. Oh my god.
I actually killed him. I killed him. Did I kill him? This is gonna give me at least like a
$50 an hour raise. No, no, no, no. What's quick load? Take it off. You have to do three commands
in order. All right. Well, I'm not doing them right now. Okay. I'm doing them in like 10 minutes.
Fuck. Fuck. In the head, in the head, in the head, in the head, in the head, in the head,
in the head, in the head, in the head, in the head and shoot him in the head. I'm a fucking Jedi.
They don't even use guns. How do I get up there? Jesus. You can tell I have low HP. He just knows.
That's why he ran over here. What happened to him? What? Why did he go forward? Why did he go forward?
Holy shit. Okay. How do I get up there? I'm gonna go up. Is there a force jump? Force sense.
No force sense. Force walk. Force walk to where? Force stairs. Is there a... Wait,
are there four stairs over here? Almost fucking fell. Wait. All right. I see a force. Oh boy.
Hold on. Okay. I'm gonna... What if I do speed? Oh, did you hear that? Oh my god. I landed like
roof. How do I get up here? Just fucking kill him. Obtain heavy repeater. Is there a door
inside that door? What door? Inside that door. Other door. I don't see a door. Use the force.
Yeah. Is this one open? This one doesn't open. This is a children's game. That's not... Not
everything is a children's game. I have to get up here. Go a full car back. Yeah, that's what I'm
doing. I'm gonna go up. Okay. Then we gotta go up. Up here. All right. Up. Fuck. No. In the door.
Okay. I did it. The other ones didn't. Whoa. Easy. Is there health? I need a health pack
somewhere. Force health. God damn it. I thought it was a crate that had items in it or something.
I don't know, man. What do you want to say? What? Okay. I have one health. Give me a fucking break.
Whatever. There's no health. I just have to be good. Quick save. Quick save now. God damn it,
Jeremy. Get up there. Use force heal. I don't have it. I got lightning ability first.
Okay. You guys are both in deep shit when I get in there. Believe you me. The second that this
drops, this is going right through your spine. You understand? I'll give you a little preview.
Yeah. What was that move? You have no idea. Bang. Electricity out of my hands. What, you have a gun?
A little blaster? Cute. Really nice. Cool. Sure. Can you do this? No, you can't. So give me the
fucking code to get to the main base and I'll think about letting you out because you're not locked in
here with me. I'm locked in here with you. No, no. Other way. You're fucked is what I'm saying.
That's one down. That's one down. I'm telling you. You're going to be in big trouble. Oh.
Fucked a big game on that one. Oh, that's right. I had one HP. Shit. Right. Right, right, right,
right, right, right, right, right, right. Sorry. I forgot. I forgot. I have to hide. I'm going to
hide like a gun. Wait. Okay. Hold on. I'm going to throw a grenade in there. What the fuck?
It's an explosive barrel. Of course it is. Get up. Go, go, go, go, go. Quick save it up here so
it doesn't happen to you. Quick save. Okay. Get rid of this shit. I don't want to accidentally
explode. Okay. I've cleared the room. I'm ready. Now I'm going to get rid of this shit and I'm
going to throw a grenade in there. That's that one. Quick save it right here. Okay. Where's the
grenades? How do you fucking throw these? Okay. Those things suck. Oh, is this beer? Holy shit.
This is what they were defending. Yeah. There's like the hops and the vats and stuff. This is
like a beer factory. Belt of thermal detonators. Wait. Oh, thank God. Okay. Heal. Yeah. These are
kegs and bottles and this is the shipment, man. This is the shipment right here. Quick save. I
got it. Oh my fucking glass. Of course. That was frustrating. It was glass. Now what do I go?
This way. Okay. Here we go. I'm going in here. What happened? You all right? What happened? I want
to go in here. Quick save. Here we go. Watch it. Head pack. Now that's... That's not fair. Why is
that not happening to him? All right. You know what? Just get over there. Just watch out. Dodge,
dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge. Too far. Oh my God. Ow. Oh. Oh. Shit. I'm getting too... All right.
It's the shaking camera. Fuck. Okay. I'm good. He actually hit me. You got to be shitting me.
What does this even do? Whoa. Did I dodge it? Okay. I dodged it. Got him. Okay. Save. Pile.
Oh, great. Whoa. Get out of here. Get out of here. Come here, you fucking dick. Push him off. Push
him off. Push him off. How much force juice do I have? I can't force push him. Wait. This is not
enough for him. Restart. Restart. Restart. Restart. Restart. Use a quick force grenade.
Hold on. I'm busy. Holy shit. Okay. I'm ready. Here's what we're gonna do. Detonation packs.
We're gonna play this so fucking cowardly. I don't even care. Okay. How do I blow them up?
They are. Come out here and find out. Right click. Jesus. That wasn't even the right guy.
That wasn't even the Jedi. Oh, shit. No. That was the wrong guy. Oh, come on. All right. Whatever.
Get out here. My lightsaber grenades will take you down. He's dead. I think he's dead.
All right. This time I'm not gonna screw this up. Oh, my fucking god. Get me in here.
This time I'm not gonna just have the one dude come out with a blaster and have me blow him to
hell. All right. Here we go. Ready? Come on. Whatever. Give me a regular blaster.
Okay. I'm ready. Oh, shit. What? It didn't do anything. I didn't do anything. I didn't do
anything. What happened? That's right click, isn't it? It's right click, isn't it? You guys
said right click. Is it proximity? Are you throwing on purpose? No. I thought it was
detonations. The lightning zapped the bomb. I didn't do anything. I didn't press anything.
The lightning hit it. Wait. Oh, lightning. You mean like environmental lightning. Are you kidding
me? I didn't press any button. Oh, would you die already? Okay. Save this shit right here.
Here we go. All right. Come get me. Yeah. Nice taunt. Good luck. Come on over here.
Why? I'm just killing this motherfucker right now. He blocked it. He blocked it.
Big mistake. Oh my god. He slit my throat. Get the fuck over here. Come on. Come here.
Just walk down this.
Knock him off. Knock him off. Just knock him off. Knock him off. Knock him off.
Got him. All right. Got him. What happened? What happened? It was the bomb. Yeah. I didn't touch it.
Wait. Should I press all the buttons? These buttons? That's a bomb. I have to. Okay. Hold on.
Hold on a second. Let me. What is this doing? Disarm the bomb. Did I get it? Disarm the bomb?
That wasn't so bad. Okay. Mission accomplished. Is it? Let's just pull the top up.
The tram is speeding up. I think they're going to ram it into the station.
You have to get to the control room and stop that train. What? Bye. Nice. They're going to ram it
into the station. I got to get down there right now. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Force speed. Force
speed. Go. What the fuck is this person? I thought he was going to go right.
Force push. That's an execute. Okay. Why does he always throw? What do you mean always throw?
A guy literally just jumped cartwheeled into frame with a lightsaber on and I had a little
bit of a panic. I got hit by a building. Oh my God. You motherfucker. I can't believe you just
headshot me. What the fuck? It's running. Turn and face me, coward. All right. That guy can
instantly kill me. Oh my God. Somebody told me this mission was hard. Well, I'm doing pretty
good. I think it's on easy. No, it's not. It's on medium. I always get shit for playing on like
whatever. Oh my fucking Jesus. How many times do I get? I don't have any health.
Die already. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let's hit him in the head. Okay.
All right. Here we go. Is he jumping over this? Go ahead. Do a dodge again. Dodge it again.
Careful. It's on your right side. Be careful. Careful. Ooh, that was a good one too. Careful
though. Yeah. What's going on with my eyes? What? What do you mean deserves? No. Oh, come on. No way.
No way. I have to something. I have to get like lightning to strike or something.
Come on. Lightning strike. Get me back into this. Come on. A lightning strike will probably fix it.
I need to restart the game. Okay. All right. I'm going to restart. Restart the game. Try restarting.
And all right. I'll turn on the alternative dismemberment shit after this mission. After
this mission. I will. I promise you guys see. Okay. Let's try it again. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa. Whoa. Okay. We're good. We're good. We're good. Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. All right.
All right. All right. I'm going to fuck this guy up. Come on down. Charge the sniper. How do I charge
sniper? I can just air shot him. I can't dodge everything, man. Okay. Now let's go up and hold
fire. Does that work? Just get over here. Get over here. Watch out. This guy's got blasters right
there. I got it. Did I win? Oh, okay. It's slow mode. That was weird. Come the fuck on, dude.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. How do you fucking miss? My god. Worst Jedi ever.
Get the fuck out of here. All right. My goodness. Can I get to the end? I made it. Thank god. I did it.
Rage.
Force you. I'm fucking begging you. All right. I will. I will. Darth Vader. It's definitely Darth
Vader. How about mercenary activity? A number of reports that the disciples of Ragnos have been
trying to hire mercenaries and smugglers to haul some cargo. If we can contact one of these
mercenary groups, we can find out the cult's base of operations. One of the smuggling rings that we
know about is based in Morse Isley. Go there and see what you can find out. This one sounds like
it could be nasty, so I'll be going with you. You'll find some of the galaxy's worst low lives
on Tatooine. My parents are from Tatooine, and I spent like 15 to 20 years there. Grown up.
Thanks, though. All right. Force heal. Jedi have the ability to heal themselves after injury.
Thank god. Okay. Jedi heal. What about weapons? I want to pick a different lightsaber.
I'll try the electromagnetic blaster, and I'll just take the regular blaster.
Level three lightning is amazing, though. Most force powers are totally useless until level three.
Oh. All right. Dismember. All right, I'm gonna do the- after this cutscene. Hold on,
we're gonna get ambushed. Relax. Do we know them? Kyle does.
Stay here and guard the entrance to the docking bay. If anyone tries to enter or
leave, detain them. I'll head over to the crate canteen and ask around. Don't let anybody leave.
Don't let anybody get in. You can- I won't let you down. Nobody leaves. Nobody gets in.
Oh, hi. A Jedi? Me? No, not yet. I'm one of Kyle Katarn's students. He's talking to some locals.
What'd he- I need to kill you. Don't let anybody out. Don't let anybody in. I have to kill him.
He has to die. I'm abandoning my post. I'm not supposed to be doing this.
I don't think he can kill Chewbacca. Wait! What? I'm so sad about it, too. I can't believe what
just happened. All right, Chewie. All right, Chewie! Chewie! What are you thinking, man?
Get in there. Smoke. Dismemberment. All right, fine. I'll do it. What is it? A console command?
Quick save. And give me the- give me the- give me it. This better be worth it. And you better
not ruin my game or else I'm gonna be very upset with you. All right, do I have to put in the-
do I have to put in the quotation marks? Oh, no. Okay, no quotation marks. Hold on. I have to-
every time I alt-tab, I have to fucking- give me a sec. Hold on. Okay. Help us Obi-Wan Kenobi 1.
I can remove this shit later, right? I better be able to. I'm gonna be very upset if I can't.
Okay. Help us Obi-Wan Kenobi 1, then Saber Realistic in this order- in the correct way.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Help us Jerma 1, then more ass dump truck 3. Stop.
G Saber More Realistic 3. Okay. It's one space at- like, G Saber More Realistic space 3, right?
G Saber More Realistic is right protected. I- I can't do it. I have to, like, do it in the actual,
like, INI file. So, I'm sorry. Didn't do the first one right. Yes, I did. Help us Obi- Help us Obi-Wan.
I did that already. Help us Obi-space 1. And then Saber More Realistic. I have to run this
as an admin. Just do dismemberment 5. Let him- yeah, I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. You need the
quotation marks. I'm done. I'm just playing the game. I'm done. Wait, how come- you guys haven't
seen any of this? Oh, uh, I probably should have, like- oh yeah, oops. Sorry. I'm done.
Worst gamer moment. I can't use the console. Yes, I can. I'm done. G dismember- G underscore
dismemberment 5. It needs to be quotes? I need quotes. He didn't put the quotes in. What the
fuck, dude? Help us Obi-Wan. That doesn't matter. That is stupid. You need mods for it. All right.
Yeah, well, you guys don't have any idea what's going on. You guys don't have any idea what's
going on. Oh, Chattis, no idea what's going on. You have to go to the config files. Yeah, well,
I'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna play the game. I'm not gonna turn the game off, do the config,
test it. Did it work? It didn't work. I have to go back into the console. It didn't work.
Whoopsie daisy. You gotta go fucking do this and then fucking do that. You have to defrag the
hard drive. So much false shit. How do I get out of here? Chewie, where do we go? Turn on the sex
scenes. Where are we supposed to even go? I wasn't paying attention. I was too busy trying to, like,
turn on, like, big head mode and, like, they're in go-karts and their heads fly off when you hit
them once. Watch out, Chewie. I'll do my best Han Solo, Chewie, for you guys. I'll do it as much
as I can. I'm gonna try really hard. There needs to be a scenario where I say it, though. I don't
know why I thought for one second I thought that was him talking. Chewie! That was bad.
It was supposed to be... I didn't expect him to shoot yet.
Oh! Chewie, Chewie, Chewie, Chewie, don't go out there. Chewie, that's a bad idea.
But I'm gonna snipe this person from, like, a hundred miles away. Whoops. Whoops. I don't
have it anymore. Where's it? Oh, come on. Nice. Took his leg off. Look at that dismemberment.
Chewie! Doctor him! Get him, Chewie! What happened? Oh my god, conserve your health,
please. Oh, shit. Chewie, that was a weird way to... What? Why did Chewie just go like...
I don't know how Chewie talks. What's force heal? Okay, controls. Drink rage. Okay, force heal.
Oh my god, that's so useful. I'm just gonna do it again. Like, I don't care.
Razor death adder, mouse five. Yeah, don't buy this thing.
Chewie! Did you... What the hell happened? Watch out, Chewie! Whatever the grade! Okay, I'm sorry.
To voice Andy. Chewie! Chewie! Chewie! Nice backflip. What do we do? Chewie, what are we
supposed to do? New offer. What do you got? Let me see it. Limited time offer. Four dollars off the
debt if you go and do all this shit in the autoexe folder. No. Honestly, I don't even care if that
was like fucking a billion. I wouldn't do it. I don't even care. Four million off the debt. No,
that's not enough. He hates us. All right, force press the buttons. Was there nothing actually in
here? In the middle of that, I just saw somebody write, good. That's an evil droid. It was walking
around and it had a gun all the way deep into his head and it was gonna come out and just go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go. How do I know? Because I had the intel. I know
the exact model number and the exact fucking serial code. What? Why am I looking at the cameras?
Where the hell are we supposed to go? We have to go like up there? Put on the droid zoom.
Just jump up here? I don't think Chewie can do this. Chewie's not a Jedi. It's kind of annoying
that they didn't... They should have eventually. I don't know why they didn't give Chewie a lightsaber
eventually. Or like a lightsaber gun. Like he shoots out like beams. Like lightsaber beams with
like the crystals. He deserved it. These computers? I don't... What am I supposed to do? They invented
a real lightsaber by the way. Um all right well I'm sure it works. Definitely doesn't. All right,
where the hell am I going here? Wrong way. Fuck. Chewie, why can't I just like say go? You go.
It does. Yeah it's one of... I'm sure it does. I'm sure it works behind a bunch of like military glass
and a high-powered robot holds it and slashes through something. Dude, you suck at games.
I didn't tell you. I'm... Look, I'm trying to find the way. Portable. There it is. Found it. Did I?
Yeah, lucky. Do it. Look out Chewie! There's a guy behind that corner! There's quite a few of them
actually. Why we just let them do this? Can you hold them Chewie? I don't know if that's a yes
or a no. That sounded like a no. That sounded like a no. That was like a... I don't know. Okay,
you're gone. Chewie in the next rumble. Guaranteed. Use the gun for a little bit. Guns are fun in this
game. Pretty cool. I don't hate them. You get to hear that cool Star Wars crunch. All right, what
we got? I have to shoot them. Doesn't work? Of course it does. What's that? I heard something.
All right, keep going.
All right, it's a guy that throws grenades. Cool. How do you not do that to yourself?
So this is just a guy... Okay, he's fucking crazy. Get out. Get out of the room.
Get out of the room. He's crazy. He's not that stupid, is he? What? Heal. Thank you for the
reminder. Enemy. Oh, watch out. C-3PO. Get out of the way. R2. Get out of the way, R2. Oh, sorry,
R2. Is it 33? I'm gonna leave him alone. But I'm gonna shock him once just to...
I'm gonna just give him supercharged powers. Now he's ultimately charged.
That worked. That's the different on droids. It gives him battery power, guys.
You just ruined Star Wars. Are you sure? Are you sure I did? And it wasn't that mouse
that just wears pants? Like just wears red shorts and that's it? Are you sure?
Elevator? Yes, we sure are. I heard Ravenclaw. I have one headphone in. Somebody tell me what
happened. Oh, shit. Squish him in the elevator. Squish him in the elevator. Get in the elevator
with him. Got it. Got it. Got it. That's a side slash. All right. Now what? In here. Two more,
right? Kubaka, get over here. Is he coming to me? Give me another fight right here.
No? Oh, no. Down. Okay. Get out of here. Yeah, I knew you. I had to find him. We just go out.
All right. Where's Han Solo? Han. Get this thing started. We gotta move, Han. Put this thing into
hyperdrive. We gotta get out of here, Han. Fight speed ahead. There he is. No, that's not. That's
Kyle. What the fuck? It was so much room to not have to do that. You could just walk around him.
He's snapping my neck. What's going on? I thought he was just gonna spin and snap my neck.
Thanks, Chewie. I got praise from Chewie. Leg attacks. I only jumped 14 times this entire level.
I used lightning more than I jumped. R2? Isn't it R number two? R2? R2.
How's your training going? I've been sent on a few errands. Nothing exciting. Same here. I guess
that's just how the training works. I thought it was just me. Ever wonder if your master is holding
you back? You know, making sure you don't become too powerful. Oh, evil? Why would you say that?
Evil? Kyle doesn't seem to really foster my talents. I've gone on a couple of missions with
him, but he doesn't let me do any of the really important stuff. Maybe he's observing you, you
know, seeing how you accomplish your missions. I wouldn't worry about it. I'm not so sure.
What do you think, Jaden? Well, I- Ready to get back out there? I learned electricity faster than
you did. So if you want to be the evil one, you gotta get in line. No, not at all. I'm ready.
Let's go. All right, we got droid recovery, emergency assistance, merchant rescue, merchant
rescue. What's this one? Academy has received a distress call from a merchant ship that crashed
on the planet Blengeel. It was pulled out of hyperspace when they crossed paths with an
inter- an interdictor cruiser. The Imperials, apparently not wanting their presence known,
fired on the merchant ship. The merchants managed to make it to the planet surface and call for
help. As far as we know, the planet is uninhabited. This should be an easy assignment. I think you
can handle it while Kyle is away with Rosh. Take a shuttle, land at the coordinates of the distress
beacon, and pick up any survivors. Sure thing. All right, we got lightsaber. Oh, hold on. I gotta
look at these. Jedi can absorb dark force power, force push, and force pull directed at them. Okay.
Better heal. Mind try- allows Jedi to confuse or misdirect attention. This is just like a defense.
Force jump. Allows Jedi to make a tremendous vertical leap. Okay. Jedi can jump three times
their normal height. Pull certain levels and objects and targeting. Can also pull an enemy.
So this just makes it stronger. Use it to get out of a force grip or drain. Jedi can sense people
in invisible markers at short range. Okay. 33% faster than normal speed. Lightsaber defense can
deflect projectiles and melee attacks in a small arc directly in front of them. Who cares? It has
to break saber locks and parries against other Jedis. Who cares? I'll just go right for the throat.
And a lightsaber flies straight from the player. Okay. Force drain, extra lightning. I think Jedi
can maintain the force lightning for a sustained forward attack. I want the sniper rifle. And this
thing is pretty cool. And I'll take the detonators. Here we go. Remember, this is the best mission in
the whole game. Okay. Well, I'll take your word for it. Again, we get shot down again. Any of these
easy just to like ride a bike to these places. Just land on the planet away from everything and
ride a bike. Why fly over everything? Just get one of those- Why do I have to fly over the base?
Hey, you there. Found the force. You've come. This place is-
Oh, watch out. We've got worms. Oh, that guy's gone. What was that? They introduced that guy
last seen just to get him killed by a worm. Okay. They even had- Did that guy have a name?
Maybe a merchant ship. I'm not going down there. I can wait this out. That hurt me. He's right behind
me, isn't he? Yeah, he was. Yeah. Uh-huh. Oh, look at you. Power up. Can I just upgrade that?
What the fuck? Oh, God. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up.
Get up. Should be safe here. All right. Jedi. Jedi, take a look. All right. There's something
in there. I used my Jedi. Take a look to see what was over there. I need a thermal detonator. Hold
on. All right. But how do I get up there? Over here? All right. Jedi, take a look. I got it.
What do I do with this? Force pull. Force push. Destroy it. Shock it. Oh, what? Okay. Power
converter. Now, what do I take this? I'm going to go over there? Oh, geez. All right. I got one.
New objective. Okay. Point. Now, I got to go get the other one. Where's the other one?
I got to go all the way down there. Okay. I'm going. Ow. Use the force. I'm not going to...
All right. You know what? I'm just going to say that word so people just think that I messed up
and said it accidentally. No, I'm not. Why would I? What? Get up. Where's this next part? Right
there. Right here. Ready? Hey. Hey. Oh. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch
out. Watch out. Watch out. Just give it to me. I'm not safe here. Just get the other one. I'm
right here. Oh, shit. What? I can't hold more than one. Oh, fuck. I got to move now.
Why is it so scary? That's not even... What? Oh, you shitting me. Okay. All right. Go.
Where is it? Over here? I can see you motherfucker. I can see you. I'm safe right here.
All right. Get it? We're going to go right back.
Scary. It's very scary. Very scary. All right. I'm almost... Wait. Where are they? Oh, fuck. Go.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Okay. Two. Put it in. What? I don't have it? Oh, man. There's more than...
Okay. This is going to suck. Absolute ass. Where's the next one? All the way down there.
All right. Just go. Go for it. Okay. This is it right here. Where are they?
Okay. I can go... We're going to go back. Backwards. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. He's
right behind me. He's right behind me. Oh, my God. I hate that sound. I'm safe right here.
Just say it for 500 million off the debt. No. It's not worth it. Yes, it is. Okay. One more.
Last one is all the way... I don't know. Where is it? Where's the last one? Oh, shit. It's so far
away. What the... Jedi Speed. That's the key is to use the Jedi Speed. I haven't been using it.
I can just run with Jedi Speed on. Don't get cocky. What's that? Shit. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. All right. I need to recharge my fucking force.
Okay. I'm fine. It was Morty Muriel. Oh, Rick. All right. I got all four of these.
Yeah. This part sucks. Oh, fuck. Don't be stupid here. Wait. Go. Go. Hurry.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Oh, shit. Oh. Did I save it? No. Idiot. You idiot. Why would
you not... What an idiot. I have... Why... Save it. Quick save. It's one button press. All right. Hold
on. Use force kin. There you go. Are you happy? Is everybody here happy now?
I don't want to be in the ground. I don't want to be in the ground. I don't want to be in the
ground. There we go. Okay. I'm all right. No deal. I don't even care about the deal. I just
want people to stop writing it. Oh, no. Don't... Holy shit. How did I not get eaten? I got it. Done.
Whatcha doing? Off this crazy rock. I get off this crazy rock. That was it? Sounds like those sand
birds. Holy shit. Nasty critters. Back safe and sound. We'll let Coruscant know to mark it as
hazardous. This is getting more serious. We have been receiving numerous reports of a Sith cult
called the Disciples of Ragnos appearing all over the galaxy. Okay. Emergency assistance or droid
recovery.
All right. Lightning three.
Anything in front of them. Sounds good to me. I want it. This is a droid level so we're gonna
have to go with droid specific items. Okay. Blue milk?
Moisture farmers?
Cult. All right. Don't worry. Jawas are pretty friendly.
Are they? Every time I've seen a Jawa on in the Star Wars, aren't they like just taking apart
robots and like attacking people? You're a fake fan. Am I? Oh, we gotta fight. We gotta fight.
We gotta fight. Jawas versus... Dude, shoot him. Okay. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't... Oh,
he just saw that. Don't tell anybody about that. Do it. Oh, now I understand what they mean when
you just have so much power. You just can't help it. You have unlimited power. The dark side is
just too strong. I got electricity in my hands. People can fly in. Holy shit. This feels very,
very good. That... I'm... Oh my god, dude. Sniper! Hey, okay. Oh my fucking...
It doesn't work that way. I just look angry. What the fuck is happening? Oh, this people.
I was like, why am I getting hit when I fire the gun? All right. Jedi mind heal.
Oh, that's a perfect room to just go in there and just go...
Ah, that move is unbelievable. This move is incredible.
I'm unstoppable. No one has any chance to beat me. No one. Even the emperor. He can't do this shit.
They should be concerned about me now because I have actually unlimited power with my lightning.
I went all into the lightning. I didn't even train a lightsaber move. I went right for that
book in Harry Potter right in the back of that room. I just opened it up. I didn't care about
a wand. I don't even have a wand yet. I don't give a shit. Oh, the wand chooses the witch. I
don't care. I don't fucking even want a wand. Don't even give me one. Just give me that book
in the back that has like the magic fucked up shit in it. He's mad with power.
No, they'd have to make a new house for me. I'd be so strong. You know what I mean? Oh,
you're Gryffindor. Ravenclaw, Slytherin, Jeremy. I sit alone at lunch. I can't even do anything.
Oh my god. You're slaughtering them. I am just... Look. Look. I'm unbeatable. And I'm going to try
to... I'm going to save the galaxy. I just... You find me somebody. You find me the bad guy
and just point me at him. You are the bad guy. It's me. You find me the bad guy. Go ahead. Point
to him and you say, ah, Jeremy, you should die. That's the bad guy. Well, I have to examine that
first and go over what you mean. What did they do? They are trying to rule the galaxy. They're
trying to take over the world and use a Death Star. Okay. All right. Okay. How big is the Death
Star? It's as big as an entire planet. All right. I can handle that. Well, I'm not looking for him,
so... Well, now someone's going to be looking for that droid. The guy who owns this house is
going to come out and be like, what the fuck happened to G3PO? Where? Yeah. Okay. In the face,
immediately dead. In an instant. Instant one headshot. All you have to do... I would just have
to come in here and hold my hands up. Like out. Forward. I wouldn't have to do any electricity.
I wouldn't have to even hurt anybody. And people would just be like, okay, get out of his way.
Get the fuck out of this guy's way. We know what he does. We know who he is.
That's fine. That's Jeremy from House Jeremy. Everybody... Just everybody leave. Just leave.
Everyone leave. What does he want? That's great. See? I chose the side of good. I chose the side
of good. I keep hearing... Somewhere in my ear. Deeply into my brain. Somewhere. I just keep
hearing, do it. I don't know who it is. I don't know what they're talking about. I don't know
what they want me to do. But they're in my head. Maybe just a little. Is that what you wanted me to
do? Do that? Do this? Gentlemen? Good to see you, gentlemen. Do it. No, not that one. He's turning
to the dark side. No, I'm not. I can control it. I really wish I had more control to launch them
up over the... Okay, now you... That's all. Just get behind him. Just distract him.
Just distract him long enough for somebody to come and just butt him in the head with a rifle.
Most powerful being in the universe still has like a soft head. So, you know, I guess that's true.
How do I get up there? No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. Come back.
Oh, man. When I get up there, I'm going to electrocute whoever's up there. I don't even care.
Oh, let's go. What happened? Oh, no, he's here. I feel like, I feel like they're all running
around going, oh, no, it's, it's Lu Bu. Lu Bu is here. Oh, shit. Everybody get the fuck out of the
way. You didn't see that? He doesn't know. Okay, apparently not. Oh, man. Okay, the party's over.
Party's over. Party's over. I don't know how to do that. I don't know how to use a lightsaber.
What am I doing? All right, let me heal. I'm gonna get the full health. I probably should do heal
too, right? That just will make it much quicker. All right, that's good. Good enough. Good enough.
That's good. Good, good, good, good. Okay. Can I put the lightsaber just away? Is there a sheath?
I don't even want to use it. Let's press one. Okay, lightsaber just kind of gets in the way.
I'll get out of here. All right, what's this open? Think fast. Think fast.
I almost made it. How do I get down there? How do I do that? Oh, my goodness. What should I do?
What do I do? I don't know. Speed. Speed. Oh, you guys all right? I need to save them.
All right, let's go. I did it. I saved you. You are free to go. Look, you can move.
I want you to move. I ain't saying it again. The hands come up. Both hands come out forward.
I ain't saying it again. Let's go. I'm trying to rescue mission here. Instantly dead. Okay, that's
whatever. No lightsaber. What are you doing? Wasting energy. Is it on timer? I think I've...
Oh, my God. He shot me right in the head. Just... Hey, German. Here's a can of whoop-ass.
Really? Can of whoop-ass. He's stone cold. Actually, German, lightsabers recycle power.
I'm good. And that hurt a lot, but I'm good. All right. What's this link spam? What are you
guys doing? What's going on here? German95 debt relief album cover art. German has made
song after song throughout his YouTube and streaming career, whether it be the rat birthday
mixtape, the giant enemy spider, or the banana bro's anthem. He's made musical masterpieces,
but none of these musical masterpieces have been collected in an album. Hopefully after this deal,
that can change. Here below, you can see the price negotiations. We hope you accept Mr.
Albertson. Okay. 100 million for covers of a song, 200 million for extended versions of the songs,
300 million for completely new songs, and 1 billion for an official raid song. Okay.
Beat boxes are acceptable. Let me think about this and take the first break of the evening.
I'll be right back. And we're back. Maybe we'll vote on this, maybe, eventually. I'm interested
in the deal, but I'm not saying yes to it yet. Hold on. I'm currently being brunt. Come back.
Catboy. Yep. Put on the ears. Look at all this catboy. Catboy, catboy, catboy, this catboy,
catboy, this catboy. What did that do? Oh, I turned it off. You can go. Go, go, go. You're good.
Go through. Go through. Hands up. I'm not going to. All right. I just hit him with like the
peripheral. Whatever. Don't go that way. That's where fire is. What did I just do? Oh, okay.
Elevator. Where's slug germa? Where's slug germa? Oh shit. Somebody was still alive.
Is there a lightning four? Can you do lightning four? I just killed like 10 people. I don't know
who's over there. Just guessed. All right. Got him. Lightning 10 is a nuke. Is it? You're okay.
You must be the droid we were sent for, but it doesn't look like there's any jawas left to
negotiate with. Well, I guess you better just follow me. Follow me. All right. Let's go.
Don't go out there. Wait, wait, wait. It's not safe. It's not safe. It's not safe out there.
It's not. Now it is. All right. Let's go. Do I even need to be at the academy anymore? I was
starting to get worried. Any problems? Not unless you count the sand people I ran into.
Well, you're still in one piece. This guy with training is not. This is terrifying. Wait, what?
82 people killed? Wait, what do you mean next mission? Next mission? I couldn't. What do you
mean go back to the academy? I only got one more. Officers from the planet Bakura have requested
our assistance. An unknown party is taking control of a power station up in the mountains.
They sent a team to investigate, but they haven't reported in. Their concerns are twofold. They want
to stop whoever has taken over the station, and more importantly, ensure that the station
itself remains undamaged. The station is built over a dormant volcano. And if the facilities
destroy the volcano, it could destroy a heavily populated city. The Bakurans need someone to
infiltrate the facility and thwart the group's plan. Oh, you can skip one mission per set of five.
Should I even do this then? Yes. Okay. All right. So I have lightning. Now I can do force choke.
Force grip, drain, lightning. I can't do any more points in the lightning. Force grip.
I think the weapons don't really matter. Okay. Mission five. Oh, how long is this game?
I'm just bored? It's pretty long. It's 50 hours. What the hell are you talking about? Okay. Force
powers. We got heal, lightning, grip. That was three. Like 10 hours? Oh, okay. So Kyle's in
trouble then. Kyle, where is this guy? Man. This is where I get into a little bit of trouble because
I get bored, right? I go into the side room and there's like a bunch of potions in there,
and I pick one up and I drop it. Stuck in here.
Should I go stop him? Oh, all right. We got to stop the count. What? I'm under arrest? Oh, hi guys.
I was testing my new move out and it sucks. I don't have to do anything, man. I'm unbeatable.
No one can stop me, even if there's a boss. Who the fuck were you guys? Did you guys spawn
in? Press all the buttons. Just press every button on the machine. Who cares? Uh-oh. Hold on.
I got to take care of this. The one thing that can stop me is environmental death.
Good. Nice. Got it. Watch out for the gas. Easy way to deal with this.
Oops. How did I jump over that? What? I got the security key. Nice. Okay. I'm too powerful.
I became too powerful. Way too powerful. Way too quickly. Oh, it's the bomb. Okay. Wait. Easy.
Easy. Bomb. What's the difficulty? I don't think that's going to do anything.
Four more to go. Now you need an apprentice. I don't think that works. I can't have an apprentice.
I can't teach somebody how to do this. I'm the only one that can. Should I go back up?
Um, okay. Well, I'm just going back up. What did I come down here for?
Jump in the pit for a funny laugh. Okay. That would be really funny, actually.
God damn it, man. Bring it. Let's go. Bring it down. Why do you just want me to cry?
Cry? Oh, cuff me. Cuff me. What was that move? Shit your pants. Shit your pants. All right. So,
I got to go this way. Okay. We'll go over here now. Wait, what? What did I miss?
This is not the Jedi way. I have the security key. Right. Well, I... Oh, why is it all the way down
here? That's a horrible place for that. No lightsaber. What's the lightsaber for, man?
I don't even need it. Who cares? I don't need a lightsaber. Uh-oh. Somebody else with exploding
hands up there, I think. I'm not scared. I'm not concerned about that. Like, you have good power.
You have a power, too. It's for your cosplay. That's right. Too powerful. Too powerful. Fine.
I guess I'll use it for a minute or two. What's another cool move to get? All right. Be careful.
Don't be an idiot. I don't want to, like, accidentally blow this up. So, we're going to
go from here and go that way. See? I'm careful. Look at how careful I was being. Three more. Three
more. This level sucks, to be honest with you. Is this why you guys told me to do this? Everybody's
like, do this one. Do this one. Next. Next. Because, you know, this one was bad. Where's this taking
me? You're going to get lost? Oh, I found a secret. What does that mean? Oh, I have the Jedi mind
look. I'll find it eventually. I'm going to stop flirting. Whoa! I almost just got crushed. Sorry.
Stop flirting with chat and play the game. What do you think? I am. All right. This one back here.
This is the one I already got. What was the next one? We're going to go, I guess, over here.
I don't even know who... I didn't even know you were there. You weren't even on my radar.
I don't think I can do this one. I can't go from here. Shit. Okay. Well, whatever. Coward. Coward.
Coward. Coward. Force the wall run. Can I get in here with it? I need a key card or something?
Well, this is dumb. Can you fart for us? No. Thanks. Is that one up there done, or does that
one need to be done? I need to do that one. I think I can make this elevator and then go up and
disarm it. Fart now. Fart now. I'm not... Why do you want me to do that? You guys are gross. Please do
it. Two more. Where are they? Is that one done? I can't tell. Let's get the sniper rifle out.
That one's done. This one's done. That one's done. All right. All three over here are done.
Now we go this way. Back over here. All right. Where are the other ones? I only see...
Holy fuck. I thought I fell off. Do a force fart. I don't think I want to do that. A force fart is
just shit your pants. I'm not... No. You don't force. That's what happens. That's a force fart,
and I'm not doing that. Worst noise. No, it wasn't. It was fine. Force puke. No. Force puke in
mother's bed. Oh my god. All right. So how can I get in here? This level sucks. This level sucks.
Level sucks. This level sucks. This level sucks. I didn't do this one. No. I did. Where are the
other ones? What the fuck? I went in a circle. Yeah. Well, where am I supposed to go? What's the
command to just complete a level? This one's... I don't like this one. I don't want to do this one.
Force just fall off. Soft lock. You're almost done? Yeah, but I can't... How am I supposed to
get out? I don't know where to go. Can I get in there? Look up the guide. Go back through the door.
All right. I'm through the door. And then I can go down this way or I can go back through here.
Back through. Force pretending. No, this brings me down. Force pretending. Forcing a joke. Force
joke. Save it here. Now I can go this way or down. I'm going to try it this way. Down. Okay. Force
look. One up there I got. This one over here which I didn't get. I remember this part. Can't get in
this door. I got that one. I haven't been down there though. Hold on. Kirby air ride waiting room.
I'm not playing that game. Here? In here? In here? What is this thing? Key on corpse.
Key? Where is it? Where is it? This guy? Give me a fucking break. Don't blow it up. I was trying to
shoot him. Okay. That opens. Where's that door? It's over here somewhere. I saw it. I ran by it.
Where is it? Where's that door? It's a red door. I can't. I couldn't. There it is. Goodbye. You just
got electrocuted. Oh no. I'm too good at the game now. And even with a high difficulty it wouldn't
even change anything. I can't wait to fight a boss. And just kill the boss instantly. Off a cliff.
Got him. Bomb right there. Now that was fucking cool. Alright. That was really cool. One more.
Only one more. Where is the last one? One final one remains and then I can get the
heck out of here. Please. Alright. No? I'm gonna cross this way. Don't go down. Go across.
There it is. There it is. I win. I win. I win. That does it. Better get back to my ship.
Where's the ship? This guy doesn't even do anything.
Where's the ship? Okay. I think it's this way. I feel like I'm hacking.
I put in cheat codes to make the game impossible to lose. You bad? Nope. You're good.
I didn't kill the droid. It just went. It was one little blaster. He's gonna be fine.
Where the hell did I just go? Oh. Come on. No. Get. Level sucks. Level sucks. Level sucks. Level
sucks. Now where the hell do I go? Back this way, right? Move. Move. Move. Bye bye. There's my ship.
Force change your difficulty. Stronger than the emperor. By far. He couldn't do this.
Mm-hmm. Uh-oh. Alright. Let's go. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. He's getting concerned?
Jayden, I was looking at how many people you've killed. It's over 50 per mission. Maybe put a
couple points into jump. Maybe into heal.
Relay some disturbing news. Someone sliced into my personal records and accessed some highly
sensitive data about places where I felt a strong connection to the force. Places like Cloud City,
Hoth, and Biss. What could they get from that besides a tour? Something nasty. I believe that
the sceptre Jayden saw was somehow used to drain the residual force power from the Masasi Temple.
Drain the force? How can anyone do that? I'm not sure. But I learned from the Jedi Holocron
that devices were created in the past that could absorb and store force energy. Those people Jayden
saw may have discovered some way to harvest force power with that sceptre. Which could be dangerous
indeed. So what are we going to do? We'll have to investigate any locations from my records.
That includes all of you students. This guy. You're going to wail. Mad eyes. Pissed off eyes.
The valley of the Jedi. It's real action. Who would they be stealing force power?
Sorry too much Jayden. I bet that these cult guys can't take on a Jedi.
Well we're not Jedi yet. We're just students. You may be just students.
We're junior heroes. So don't rush it. Jayden I'm sending you to Hoth where I had a vision of Obi-Wan
Kenobi. Imagine there was a pretty strong aura there. Rosh I'm sending you to the remains of
the planet Byss. It's very remote so I doubt the cult has been there. Don't stay too long.
The imperial remnant may still be operating in the area. No problem. That's everyone then.
May the force be with all of you. And also with you. Call me if you need any help. Let's go.
Investigate the site of Luke's vision of Obi-Wan Kenobi. Rosh I never heard that is. It's me. That's
not how he talks but whatever. All right I got my electrical amplification device.
Or a giant calculator. I'm not sure which one it is. Or the farting part of a cash register.
Am I giving this the finger? Whatever it is. What is that?
Come here. Come here. I want to get on one of you. Come here.
Get over here. Get over here. I'm just gonna follow the beacons.
Wait what about my friend? I can't just leave him hanging. I can. You want to go?
I don't think you know who you're fucking with here. Do it. You dead? Now you're a little scared.
I am the most impossible to destroy being in the universe. You want to taunt? Goodbye. He survived.
He's the chosen one. That's me. I just have to use it for a little bit because it's kind of like a
car. Like you got to use your car's battery for it to work otherwise if you don't use it it just
fucking not turn on. So it's gonna use it for a little bit. We're going the right way. I think
it's a whole I think that guy's whole body came off. Come here. I need to I want to get on you.
Somebody there. Someone there. Oh shit an AT-ST. This is the ultimate test of the ultimate power.
Oh shit that's a bad place to save. Stay back. Stay back. Stay back. Stay back. Hey you're not
supposed to be over here. Horse hide. Whatever. Saver. Lightsaber. It's my friend. I'm coming.
I can't open it from this side. Stuck in here? Let's go. No one is safe.
No one. Not when I show up. No one is safe. What did that do? Secret. Oh a secret area. Cool.
Grenades. Food. Health. What did that button press do? I don't know. I'm not sure.
He just summoned Boba Fett. He did? Oh no. How do I fight him? How am I ever going to beat him?
What door today is open? Down? How will I ever beat Boba Fett? He's going to show up and he's
going to have a rocket launcher. It's going to be impossible. Massacre. The little toaster bot.
Wait. I have to kill the toaster. All right. You get to live. You get to live. You get to live.
Not yet. What the fuck do you think you're going to do? The boss is not going to have
any time to even do his monologue. Right now the boss has seized the cameras here and he's just like
oh shit. Shuffling papers. My fucking speech. Hold on. I wasn't ready for this.
How dare you enter my domain without asking and without express permission in my restaurant.
I'm scared. I didn't have time to memorize my lines. Oh cool. Oh nice. I don't even need to use it.
Who needs the super cannon? I cannot be stopped. Follow the beacons.
This guy's just running through. This is fucking terrifying. Beacon. Follow the beacons. I'm just
playing battlefront 2 and I get to randomly get to be one of the heroes. I'm having lots of fun.
Oh did they get in? I don't know man. Maybe there's a secret entrance somewhere. I'll use my force
look. I don't see anything. You guys see something? I don't see anything. Maybe around the back? What
do you guys think? In the comments of this video you tell me what you think I should look. I'm
thinking maybe up top. What do you think? I don't know what to do. We get 5k likes. They literally
told you to get in the AT-AT. They did? I'm sorry I was too busy killing everything and having no
contest. Where's the AT-AT? Get in there. What do you think? I'm trying to find one. There it is.
Get in this? I can't get in it. It's shooting at you? Hey! Getting sniped. Yeah whatever.
All right I'm safe right here. Relax. Recharge. Heal. Recharge. Heal. 500 million off the dead
if you stop using the lightning. You may as well stop playing the game. Something exploded behind
us. I have no idea what it was. All right I gotta get in here. Do I get in? Oh shit. All right. All
right. All right. I made it. I made it. I made it. I made it. Get in. When I get in there you're
gonna get electrocuted dude. Why can I not just get in here? Shoot. I tried. I tried. I tried to do
it like five times. I had to do it in first person apparently. All right now what? What's the difficulty
if I like watching winners not losers? It's on normal difficulty just because I picked the really
strong dark side move. I can't play the dark side character. It's the most powerful in the universe
but you are a bad guy. This is a lesson to all of you. All right what's the new objective? That's
kind of fun. Right in the head. They were just heating up by the space heater. I kind of feel bad
about that one but I mean this is the this is the empire. This is the evil empire. What? So the evil
empire can't be destroyed by another evil empire? What are you trying to say? Look I I might be evil
but they're evil too. It's evil versus evil right now. You don't have there there's no somebody
nobody would rather win. It's just bad guy versus bad guy. There is no good guy right now. You press
M. Discover what the imperials are doing in echo base. I'm not gonna do it. Don't worry. I don't
even need a health pack. I have free health. Hi guys. Oh you lived. Look at you. You lived. Not for
long. What's next? How you doing? Research? Cool. I'm not you get to live because you remind me of
an old pepsi bottle. You're an old like crystal pepsi. You get to live. Or do you because crystal
pepsi was fucking gross. Can I just go up here? Pure evil. Unlimited power. Unlimited power but
still can't figure out how to fucking leave a base. Sense of direction. Awful. Don't matter.
IQ. Horrible. Doesn't matter. None of that matters. All that matters is power. Power.
But he's he's he's an idiot. You think that matters? Look what's happening. What matters right now?
Power. Total power. And then we hide. We hide because I don't have any power left.
Oh it's starting to affect me a little. I think too much electricity is starting to affect me. My
hair is standing on end. This guy would be running through the halls with this huge static electricity
here. Burnt like ears. His clothes he'd have like burnt singed ends of all of his t-shirts and shit.
Yeah like Marv and Home Alone. Just imagine Marv and Home Alone running around with a cloak on.
Oh too many computers in here. I can't do this.
What? I didn't even save the game. I didn't think I was ever going to need to.
He just cut me in half. I was on low battery. Crazed electrocutor. Oh shit. Made the same mistake.
I went the wrong way. How? No I didn't. Get back down here. Choke him. Get over here. I can't be.
Like that was embarrassing. Crystal Pepsi. Stop. Hey. Stop. Stop. Stop. You can't fight me.
You can't stop me. You can't stop the Jedi's. I'm not even a Jedi. Here we go. Wait. Bad entrance.
You know I wish there was just a punch. Okay here we go. Oh my god. He's trying to like block them
and just leave. What happened? How did he do that? Don't even matter. I'm killing this guy in one
head. One earbud Andy. Don't matter. Unlimited power. Go ahead. One, two, three. I gotta get out
of the way. He's coming. He's coming. He's coming. He's coming. He's coming. Man you gotta
get out of the way. He's way more powerful than me and if he's way more powerful than me then we
both gotta fucking run man. We are. Fuck. Are you this? This isn't good. I better find this Elora.
Get dunked on. I win. Get out of the way fucking abominable snowman. Yes master. Dagobah.
Skywalker didn't mention it in his journals. He must have been trying to protect something.
Uh oh. It's the apprentice. Not lightning wielding. I don't even use that thing.
I'm also 30. All right you want to go motherfucker? Oh nice job. You're dealing
with a lightning user. Ow. Eat that power. Oh shit you're doing evil laugh or yeah I'm kind of evil
too. I could I'll pull it. I'm the fucking evil one. You're not evil. I don't want I don't want
that. What if you have any hand? I don't want it. No stop giving it to me. I don't want it. I don't
want what you have. What do you I I don't what do you want? Hey let's talk. You and I should probably
I'm evil too. All right I'm the fucking evil one of the story. I'm looking on the lightsaber
shit all over me. No no you're weak. You piece of shit. Look what do you want anyways? What do you
want with all you with the empire? Like how about this? You're strong. I'm strong. I know I'm way
stronger than you but make could be one of let's just you play dice and see who can win this.
Maybe we should team up or something. Yeah and I I've won every fight I've ever fought. How about
you? How many fights have you won? That's how you win every fight. I'm gonna get in the dumpster.
Will you come in the dumpster with me? Get in here. This is where we're gonna have our
this is we're gonna have our our meeting. Get in the meeting. I want to get in here. Get in the
dumpster. We're having a dumpster evil dumpster meeting. Please humor me. Thank you. Okay so
first thing. Well now biggest fucking debate in the book. Now you're stuck in there.
Now you gotta listen to me. Yeah. Oh extra bounce on that one.
Oh shit it's a wall. What happened? Oh no.
Everybody just relax. I'm pretending to be dead. This wasn't going anywhere. Just everybody relax.
When she leaves I'm gonna get up and we can just go to the fridge and get a snack and shit.
Should I hold my breath? I think she'll be able to see my chest moving. I have to cough so
bad. I'm gonna sneeze. Fuck I'm gonna sneeze and she's gonna execute me. She's gonna fucking
execute me. Where is this? This is a bad save. Wait where the fuck is this? Where is this? Way to go.
Way to go Darth Ron. Holy shit this is a horrible save. Why do I have it so far back here?
Low checkpoint. He's swinging at me. That was stupid. That was really dumb.
I sneeze. I'm not allowed to sneeze. Remember this part. Look out. Oh I didn't mean to um
am I up? What the hell just happened? Can you? Can I get you to follow me down here? What if I bring
a giant like abominable snowman friend? Oh my oh my god you made it in. Oh my god you made it in.
Oh my god you made it in. Come on come on come on. You don't fit. Okay what if I put a grenade
behind him? Whatever. Here we go. Yep yep yep yep yep yep yep. I know. I don't know how to use one
of these things. Nice block. I have an idea. This is just crazy enough to work. I'm gonna get her
shit stuck in a wall and I'm gonna unload a machine gun into her face. So throw that at me,
get it stuck in a wall. Do I actually kill her? It's gotta be the dumpster. We'll meet again.
Two eight-year-olds. I can't wait.
Sprint sprint sprint sprint sprint. Push him in the back as hard as I can out the window.
You must have already taken the force energy from there.
Just as others have reported. Coruscant? Everywhere.
Biss.
Rosh hasn't returned. He's long overdue and we haven't heard from him.
Link link link. I sense he's still alive. I'm going to Biss to look for him.
Hold on I can't. I'll see what I can find out. Very well. What about me? Rosh is my friend.
You can help by staying here and completing your training. Kyle's right. There are still
missions for you to undertake and we can't neglect the training of one of our most promising
students. Promising? Yes. Due to your heroics on Hoth, we are promoting you to apprentice.
Thank you master Skywalker. Master-
New style, fast style. It's a short and quick style.
Master Skywalker and Master Katarn have left the academy.
They've been instructed to provide you with a set of possible missions.
Rescue, meet contact, covert operation, capture the crime lord, or investigate.
Now let me take a look at this link.
No more reload Randy. Time for Sith Andy. A truly powerful Sith lord never dies. To prove your power,
10 million will be added to the debt each time you reload a quicksave.
But what do I get? I get nothing.
No more reload Randy. Time for Sith Andy.
My Sith lord never dies.
No deal. This is just bad for me.
That fucking Harry Potter outfit with the lightsaber. Like what the fuck.
School recess. All mushed into one guy in front of the green screen.
No deal. Which one of these is fun? Which one- from those of you that have played this,
which is a good one? Capture the crime lord.
Covert operation. I will do crime lord first.
We've received anonymous information that a large number of assassin droids have flooded
the black market recently. These droids have been banned for a number of years,
and no public companies produce them.
Lenek Rakdo, a small-time crime lord on Crusant, is suspected to be manufacturing these droids.
Capture Rakdo so that maybe we can get- we can interrogate him.
We should be able to handle this no problem. Thugs like Rakdo are intimidated by the sight
of a lightsaber.
Okay. Force choke. Need to get Hewl.
Did you think you could just barge in here and take me into custody, Jedi?
That's gonna cost him a lot of money to fix.
I feel like this is- by the way, you could have just like hid behind a dresser or something.
He just hears that while closing the door. He's just like, what just happened out there?
Alright, so just get in the X-Wing, fly, park on the roof of this building.
I have an X-Wing. This should not be a problem for me.
Just fly and land somewhere else. I don't want to even- don't add- don't- I didn't agree to that.
I didn't agree to that. You did not- I did not agree to that.
Where am I supposed to go? Too bad. No, that's not fair.
Gain access to the office building. Alright, well, what the hell am I supposed to do?
This sucks.
Alright, make the jump in. Three, two, one, jump.
Jump. I have a question for all you Star Wars fanatics.
Is lightning- is the- is lightning just absolute dark side?
If you learn how to shoot lightning out of your hands, you're bad.
No, so when who cares? Good guys can do it too. So why don't good guys do it all the time?
Because it's evil. Kit Fisto used a lot of force lightning.
Yeah, so what's the problem then? It's emotion.
For me? For me, that's right.
They were just announcing that they were the target practice.
Oh, can I get a new lightsaber style? Yeah, this is it. I'm using it right now.
What are some of the dark side moves? What actually quantifies the dark side?
You've got the lightning, you've got the choke you.
Choking and lightning. Force gas lighting.
Holy shit, good aim. Force drain.
Oh my- where the fuck did you come from? Force push.
No, that's a good- that's a good guy move. I see Anakin does that all the time.
Obi-Wan does that all the time. Real drain.
Oh, you're still alive? You know, just kill that fucking guy, seriously.
All right, from here, there's this guy right here. Drop that shield.
All right, dead. And from here we go- I have no idea.
Over there? Watch out for the wrist rockets.
All right, sometimes you gotta pull like a gun and not just be a coward of lightning.
And then sometimes you put the lightning back in.
Watch out for wrist rockets. Watch out for wrist ro- I don't know why.
Super battle droid, knock him down.
That guy went further than anybody ever went. Watch those wrist- wait, is that like a Mandalorian
thing? Because he has like the- he's the wrist shooter that goes pew pew pew.
What the fuck, dude? Did I just die by my own lightsaber?
No, no, no. What happened? Have I not- did I not- why did- how is it possible I didn't save it?
It's impossible that I didn't save it. That's actually not even fucking possible.
Did I get a checkpoint? I don't think I did.
Cry, cry, cry. That's so annoying. What the hell?
How is it possible- I don't even- don't even fight anybody.
Just give it back to where I was. All right, I'll kill these guys.
Ooh, that hurt. You gonna cry?
No, sit up. No, I'm not.
I'm gonna do laundry tonight. Fuck.
I'm gonna do laundry tonight? Fuck.
You guys know what that's like, doing laundry, laundry day.
It's like six hours. All right, we're almost at the office building.
Jump. Can I fly this? This looks flyable, doesn't it?
Oh, that's unfortunate. It looks flyable.
I remember just laundry every six months.
No? I'm just saying, when you have a lot of load to do, it takes a while.
It's not something that just happens in like two minutes.
It didn't hit these two? Jedi Master.
Jedi. How big is- no, it's that stupid shield. It's so strong.
All right, keep going. Now from here, go this way.
Save, save, save. He's upset that his move doesn't instantly beat the game for him.
Not instantly, but speedily. I made it.
Okay, let's go. Where is he? I don't know who said that, but is it you?
Is that a Jedi? Hey, look out.
You say that's my third Jedi I've killed this week?
That's my third Jedi this week.
Cocky, all right. How do you like it?
Yeah, don't like it. Okay, don't like it, do you?
So it's a line of sight thing, right? You can't choke what you can't see.
I'll just kill your friend. Oh my fucking God, did I seriously get over it?
Did you kill me in one swing? Are you kidding me?
You see? I need full health going in here.
Or at least close to it. Full health and full Jedi meter.
Seriously shooting at me? I did not drop the difficulty.
I'm waiting for the Jedi meter to charge. Here we go.
No more messing around. Yeah, yeah. All it took was one.
What? He did- I did not change the difficulty. It's the same one it was.
Show the difficulty. I will.
Look. Setup. Video. Options. I don't even know where to show that.
I can't even show that. It's not on easy.
It's not on easy. It's not on easy. I swear to God.
I promise. I didn't- It's not on easy, I promise.
Next person to accuse me of this is gonna get tamed out for like fuck 10 seconds.
In his cube. And then somebody's shooting at me from outside.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, get away from me.
It's one. Three diamonds? I'll take them.
Two down. Did someone just call me Jerma Andy?
Did I read that wrong?
What would I do in this scenario?
I would throw him out the window.
Nice.
Uh oh. All right. Covert operation time.
Sneak around. There's something going on on this planet.
Or script three. Sounds pretty good to me.
So I can hold him and smash him into stuff?
Show the difficulty. I will after this mission.
Don't think they expected us to find it.
Targeting computer will lock on kids.
Place them on key structural points then get out of there fast.
Oh, this sucks.
I'll be flying in lasers blazing.
If everything goes as planned,
we'll have the defenses down before they know what hit them.
This mission sucks. I already know.
Okay, Jaden. Start with the shield generator.
Otherwise, this will be a short mission.
I don't want to play this one. How do I get in?
Wait, what? Is he shooting at me?
Wait, I don't understand. Get over here.
Oh my god. I can slam their heads into stuff.
Hold on. One sec.
I promise it's not on easy.
I think he did. He shot his friend.
I didn't. What's he doing? Did I get him?
Monster.
They stole this from Gmod.
I know. Oh, I know. I can do this.
Oh, cool. I think it broke his neck.
Back up or does it go down?
I can throw these guys. Come here.
Get in here.
Okay, is he gonna? No, no, no, no.
He's still alive. Holy shit.
Clear.
I don't think I got off.
Okay, you got it.
You can go into the hangar.
Go difficulty now. I can't show the difficulty.
I have to start a new game to show the difficulty.
You can't change the difficulty.
That should weaken their resistance.
Up here into the garrison.
Open. Oh, come on. Really?
How do I get up there?
Jump on the frame?
The difficulty shows in the save menu. Does it?
What did I just do?
I pressed what button did I press?
Oh my fucking god, dude. I pressed F9.
I don't know why I pressed F9. I don't know what happened.
Did I save it at all?
What was quick quick load was what?
I pressed F9.
Oh, no.
This facility is lightly defended.
I don't think they expected us to find it.
My targeting computer will lock on to your.
I hit F9.
I don't know why I pressed F9.
I just wanted to show the stupid difficulty.
Can I go back to the base?
I don't want to do this one yet.
I don't want to do this one.
I just hit M moves.
No.
Speed.
Go fast.
Go back to the previous save.
Finish that mission and skip this one.
What a good fucking idea that is.
Wait.
No, that goes way too far back.
I was one plus space.
Nice.
He's alive still.
Get out of here.
You're nothing to me.
Where do I go?
Save, save, save, save.
I did it.
Press the lightsab in the press one while it's flying.
Do the doi version?
Is that what you wanted?
Do doi version of duel of fates.
Okay.
Now what?
What is that from?
Oh my god, what's that from?
That scream.
What the hell is it from?
No, no, no, not Tom and Jerry.
Not Wilhelm.
What is it from?
No, not Howie.
It's very specific.
Shit.
Bop it.
You got it.
Yes, somebody got it.
It's the bop it sound.
It's the bop it scream.
I want to hear it.
Don't clip it.
I want to see it.
That's you failed bop it.
That's like that.
I want to hear it.
I need to hear it.
Don't clip it.
What do you clip it?
What do you come on?
Don't you want to know?
What is this?
You're linking.
I don't know.
This is not why.
No, don't link me the actual bop it scream.
Okay.
Now link me the clip that just happened.
We'll compare them.
Okay, here's this one.
Same exact thing.
Reverse it.
Where are we going?
Look out.
Activate order number 66.
Yes, sir.
Right away.
Activate number order 66.
John Oliver.
What?
Oh my God.
Did you see what happened?
A guy dropped somebody.
Activate order number 666.
This thing is ripping him.
Oh, he doesn't have a gun.
You're going to get out of him.
It's a crazy cycle.
Run, run.
He's crazy.
There's a crazy guy on the loose.
Activate order number 666.
Activate order number 6.
I just did it too.
I did it.
Enhance my order with extra things in it.
Hey, you're supposed to be dead.
Activate order 66.
Extra mayonnaise.
Side of pickles.
It's a family guy tear joke.
Nobody even said it, but I said it.
No, no, no.
I'll do one more.
That's a robot chicken joke.
Activate order number 66.
With extra pickles and a few toys.
I want a McDonald's toy.
I don't think they make McDonald's toys anymore, sir.
I don't think they make McDonald's toys anymore.
Get on it.
Where's it going?
Save the game.
Thank you.
We got to save Andy's.
Go back up.
I don't even care.
They don't send the guy with the electric hands to do this.
This is a mission for a covert stealth operator.
Not the guy that can do this.
I don't even know where they want me to go.
Where do I go?
Back up here?
Execute order number 66666.
Press M.
Yeah, I got to go on the top of the building.
There's no order in the quote.
There's not?
What's the actual quote?
It's activate order 66.
Execute order number 66.
What's the actual quote?
Activate order.
Yes, there is.
Execute.
The line is activate number 66.
No, it's like execute order number six.
What is it actually, though?
No, it's not.
So what is the actual one?
Execute order 66.
Execute order 666.
I get it.
No, it's just two sixes.
Now that doesn't sound right anymore.
Execute order 666.
No, doesn't sound right.
It's like activate order number 666.
Activate order number 66.
Execute order 66.
That sounds fake.
That sounds made up, doesn't it?
That sounds like a fake one.
Execute order 66.
I feel like mine was better.
What's happening?
What do we need to do to get out of the kelp forest?
Time has come.
Execute order 66.
No, it's activate order number 666.
Mine's better.
Don't worry.
George Lucas will redo these movies like five more times.
He'll use mine later.
Disney will remaster this like a remastered remaster.
They'll come up with a black and white version for fucking no reason in like 30 years.
Don't worry.
Oh, shit.
I just blocked that twice.
I need to go up.
Oh, I need to go up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
I can't go up this one.
Can I go up this one?
Why would he say 666 though?
Because it's like Satan.
Why can I not activate this?
Playing with fire there.
I got to stop.
It's broken.
Oh, well, I see people over here.
I just caught him by the neck.
Oh, my God.
That's horrible.
I caught him by his neck and the force snapped it when it came down.
That was horrible.
Don't I don't I don't I never want to do that again.
Big rectangle building.
I went up there.
I need to get up though.
None of these have like a way to go in or up.
Rectangle, rectangle.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm trying I'm trying to find a way up.
I need to go up.
Up, not down.
I want to go up.
This game is so painfully easy, Omega Lo.
You're fired.
I'm throwing one of the green shit.
Finally, I just had to press one button.
All right.
So I got to go that way.
Don't die from fall damage.
Hey, you.
What the fuck was I doing that for?
I want to do like a cool exit.
My God, please, Jared, stop.
You're gonna fucking freak me out.
Just stop.
I'm just trying to rush so much.
He's too high.
I'm not high.
I don't you know, I'm a high every day, guys.
Relax.
I'm gonna vaporize this guy.
Hold on.
How do I pick these up?
Is this Halloween?
No, no, no.
That was Duel of Fates.
This is Halloween.
Now they're different.
They're different enough.
Let's go up.
This goes down.
Oh, my fucking God.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
Come on.
What the fuck do I do?
I don't like this mission either.
This one's stupid.
I'm gonna stand right here
and you guys tell me what direction to walk in.
Should I go left that way or right this way?
Oh, immediate left.
Oh, a TIE fighter crashed in here.
The boss.
Yes, my liege.
All right.
Now where?
Wait, where do I go now?
Can you learn the toxic choreography for us?
I went up.
Now what am I supposed to do?
I hate this.
I can't go in there.
Oh, my God.
I fucking hate this.
Are you serious?
This is too easy.
Fire yourself out of a cannon.
Next, take out the communications array.
So they can't signal for help.
Okay, I will.
Here goes the communications array.
I gotta go all the way across the whole damn planet.
SpongeBob.
Yeah, SpongeBob.
Where's the communications thing?
It was over here.
Where?
Where is it?
Over here?
Going up here?
Why is this not fixed?
Stop fucking around.
It's up there, isn't it?
I need to get up there.
So I need to go in here and go...
How do I get up to here?
Activate elevator number 666.
I didn't...
Somebody in chat said that.
I just read it out loud.
Okay.
Open the door.
And I go to the communications depot.
Did you miss any funny German moments?
You missed a big one.
All right.
Boom.
Say the funny 66 line.
All right, sure.
How does it get from Boston?
It's down there, right?
All right.
I'm supposed to do the 66 thing.
Activate order number 66.
Clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap.
Wait, I can...
Star Wars fans are leaving?
Why would they?
I'm one of the only people playing a Star Wars game on Twitch right now.
You're all here.
Where is it?
In the command center.
Straight up from here.
Everyone here right now is a Star Wars fan.
Drop two and a half thousand viewers when the streams peak.
You know how many people had to go to dinner like two hours ago?
All right, I'm gonna get up there.
Now how many people went to dinner two hours ago?
I did.
I went BRB and I ate a bowl of spaghetti as fast as I could.
All right, so this is all the way up or where are we?
This is the last one.
It's like right up here, isn't it?
Go up even higher?
Who's saying that?
Oh, it's you.
No honor.
Just like throwing knives at him.
And the final one is...
All the way up.
Got the rocket ammo.
Dude, I got rocket ammo.
I don't know what that means, but I got it.
It's a different building.
Which building is it?
That one right here?
Yeah, it's this one right here.
Right in the middle, right?
Don't die!
Holy shit, I'm okay.
Secret area.
All right, it's right...
Where is it? In here?
How do I get in this?
How do I get up there?
Oh, he looked at chat once in the last 10 minutes.
Um, hold on.
I'm currently...
I'm a little busy right now.
I don't even know what's shooting at me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, fuck off with this bullshit.
Are you serious?
You gotta be kidding me.
No way.
This is so dumb.
Well, let's go back this way first, I guess.
I went over here too.
Yeah, this is all in a line.
Let's go.
I don't know, just...
I fucking fat fingered and pressed dash.
I pressed plus instead of dash.
I pressed...
They're both right next to each other.
And I just pressed them both the same goddamn time.
Whatever.
It doesn't even matter.
I'm gonna get up there and just wait.
Just watch.
I got it.
Everything's fine.
Yeah, I mean, give me...
Where's the fucking elevator?
Oh, go in that door!
Jayden, look out.
They've got tanks.
They've got...
How do I end up down here?
Tank, tank!
Where is it?
Oh, you're so scary.
You're so scary.
Just whatever.
Go.
It's the first one.
One, two, three in a row.
He's throwing.
I'm not throwing.
I'm fine.
All right, here we go.
One, two, three.
Have you been drinking?
No, I'm not drinking.
I'm just having a...
I'm just messing around.
Everybody needs to relax
before I get angry with you.
You know what?
Do you know how I can see him?
One, two, three.
Okay.
Over here.
Dude's in a drunken rage.
How much did I sleep last night?
Um, like an hour?
What even?
30 minutes?
All right, deactivate.
Go to bed?
I will.
Later.
No, I slept like seven hours.
Uh, two more over here.
No, it's...
Turn this shit off.
You're doing great, Jayden.
Only one more.
Got it.
That did it.
Get back in your ship, Jayden.
We're out of here.
All right.
Where's my ship?
Do you know where it is?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Big hanger?
Where is that?
Joe, what's your big hanger?
Um, it's down?
Oh, it just fell off.
Down there?
Where is it?
Over there.
Pretending?
No, I haven't paid a...
Guys, I have not paid a single attention to anything that has happened in this entire
level because I hate it.
I hate this level.
So I've just been going through the motions to just kill things and walk around in circles
till somebody says stop.
Like one of you guys says just...
Oh, they're left.
Like, okay.
I made it.
Good for us.
Hmm.
What's a good one?
Uh, probably gonna do one more.
What's...
What's the best one on this list?
Cult Investigation or Meet Contact.
Cult, cult, cult, cult, cult, cult.
People saying this one's good.
This is a driving level?
Done.
It is...
Holy shit, it is.
It's a full letter grid.
Oh, why did I just do that weird skip?
That was really bizarre.
Um, wait, why?
What's happening?
I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
There were no instructions.
There was not a single instruction.
I shook this guy's hand.
I did like a little frolic onto the motorcycle and...
Okay, I'm just...
This is really hard to control with a mouse and keyboard.
Okay, I think we're good.
Meet the contact that has outpost.
Where's this guy's...
Where's his outpost?
Wrong way.
Use your lightsaber?
What?
Why am I still alive?
I'm still alive.
With a long drive all over again.
What?
Just die.
How do I...
Die.
Okay, so where do I go?
This way?
You guys did still.
It's literally a racetrack.
Okay, but didn't it say I was going the wrong way when I went this way?
Yeah.
So what the fuck do I do here?
Do I have to jump through?
What?
God, what happened?
Jump through it?
I don't know what you mean.
How do I jump with this?
Oh, you mean like actually jump just me.
What the hell?
That's not fun.
Isn't that Luke?
Yeah, I ran into some trouble.
I really fucked up a few times.
Okay, so so far so good.
I want the purple one.
Give me any of them.
I can't get on it.
Get on the bike, dude.
Get on the bike.
Get...
I hit the gas.
I pressed the gas way too hard.
If you go in a go-kart
and you press down on the gas pedal way too hard,
you go fucking flying.
Major whiff flash.
I just did something.
What did I just do?
Just get me the fuck out of here.
Get me out of here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Give me the bike back.
Give me that bike.
Jump off.
Oh, shit.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Looks like I'm not going back that...
All right.
I didn't even...
Hey, he's coming kind of right for me.
He's kind of...
What's happening?
This dude, what's going on?
Why is he...
He's like, all right, man.
All right, you win.
Did he put a grenade down?
I don't even know.
No.
I'm going to pass out.
I have to hold on.
Hold on.
I'm going to pass out if I don't fucking stop.
The guy behind me.
He went very far, by the way.
This is so hard to control with the mouse.
Okay.
So should I go over there?
Spam D on your keyboard.
I'm not going to do that.
Where are the enemies?
Oh, here they come.
Stop.
Okay.
It's a tiny hole to go in.
Goodness.
Cool.
All right.
Keep going.
I don't know what is doing, but it was just dragging me around like crazy.
I do not feel very much in control right now at all.
What is going on?
Wait, didn't I just do this?
I had no control of what was just going on at all.
Get away from me.
What am I...
Why am I watching?
What?
Why did I need to see that?
Wait, I'm in the...
I can't move.
Get the fuck off the wall.
Why are they all doing this?
Turn this way?
Oh my fucking God.
Where...
Get off.
Get off, get off, get off, get off, get off, get off.
I can't control the motorcycle.
It just flies the fuck out of the way.
I can't do anything.
Do I even get on it?
I'm...
Stop boosting.
I didn't even boost.
It just threw me up there.
All right, I boosted there because I had to.
Wait, why...
You turn with the mouse?
Yeah, it's like dog shit.
It's so hard.
It's so annoying to control.
I can't.
I...
My fucking God.
I just fell out of the sky.
Like I fell out of the goddamn sky.
I don't have to nose bleed?
No.
What?
Did I just go in this building?
I don't even know what way is the right way anymore.
What's the correct way?
Just in the building.
Okay, five people just died.
Uh, did I do it?
Don't strafe.
I'm not doing that.
I'm telling you right now, I'm not doing that.
Okay, I made it.
By going...
Escape from the mercenaries and make your way to the far city gate.
Save it.
I think I'm getting close, I think.
I have no idea what just happened.
Is this it?
Why do I feel like I'm...
Use turbo to jump the chasm.
It didn't make it.
Uh, now...
This way.
Got him.
Give me your fucking bike right now.
My fucking God.
Oh my God.
I'm not doing...
Oh my fucking God.
Dude, why?
Give me one of your bikes right now before I freak out.
They just squished me with...
They squished my heads together like...
Too...
Get...
Leave me alone.
Give me that bike.
His bike is in better condition than mine.
It just fucking exploded.
There's the gate!
I made it to the gate!
Thank God.
Oh, thank goodness.
I don't care about that.
Just tell me what to do.
What time is it?
All right, I'll do...
I'll do one more.
We'll do...
I'll be the boss.
We'll do the next two missions.
Don't engage members of the cult.
What are you talking about?
Don't engage.
Don't engage them.
Okay.
Well, they can't take my lightning powers away from me.
Ah, feisty.
Well, I got caught so I could get inside without a problem.
Okay, I get it.
I have a proposition for you.
You see, it can get dreadfully dull around here, so I'm up for a bit of sport.
I'm going to let you out.
If you can make it back to your ship, you're free to leave.
But if I catch you, I'll have to shoot you.
After all, you are an escaped prisoner.
Hopefully, you'll prove more of a challenge than a bounty hunter I had to kill a few days ago.
Of course, I've never hunted a Jedi before.
And if I refuse to play along?
Well, then you can rot in your cell.
I'm sure someone might come looking for you.
Eventually.
Okay, Jedi.
The games begin.
Okay, let me out.
He's going to let me out.
Are there other people in the cells?
Can I let them out, too?
He gave me a weapon, too.
I don't even need it.
I got out.
Oh, I don't have a lightsaber.
The guy didn't even have a chance to load his gun.
Okay.
Oh, third person.
Helpful.
Holy shit, that was awesome.
That guy just got hit by his...
That was awesome.
I loved it.
Absolutely loved it.
This thing shoots fast.
Which door?
Well, this one.
That's the one.
P.
Open the doors for all the cells.
Let all the prisoners out.
Let them come out.
I need to pause.
I need to pee.
I can't pause.
Trying to do the next mission or two.
Firehose.
All right, let's go.
I'll let you take care of the lockdown.
Now, where's the hangar?
I'm crying.
Please give us a pause.
We'll pause after this.
Oh shit, hold on.
Pause.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
You want to take a break?
All right.
Break time.
Last break.
We'll do this mission and the one after,
and then I'm going to call it a night.
Be right back.
All right, I'm back.
Get back to it.
And it was just going in this door.
Okay, thank God I fat fingered right
in the exact same spot I just was.
Where should I go?
Where did this guy come from?
What?
Jerry voice?
Jerry.
I'm Jerry.
It actually kind of is.
That's stupid.
Jerry.
Oh, Jerry.
Where am I going?
Every door is the same door.
Gain access to the docking bay.
What?
Too many fucking doors opening.
Use the force.
Yes, I will.
I promise I'll use the force.
Like a shotgun.
This way.
Um, man, I wish I had a map.
Is this it?
No, this is the very beginning.
Oh, God damn it.
This is the beginning of the game.
All these hallways.
There's like 50 doors in here.
Too many.
There's too many doors.
Too many doors.
Too many elevators.
They got too many elevators.
Too many doors and too many rooms
that lead to nowhere.
A door and then to go to another door.
I don't even know what this is.
What does that do?
I bet he wasn't expecting that.
I had to do that?
Oh, boy.
I just took down an AT-ST by myself.
And a guy's gonna come out of the
the guy's gonna come out of the roof.
And I'm gonna headshot him.
Oh, well.
What do I do now?
What was that?
I could hit one.
The Jedi.
I'll be...
I singed my eyebrows.
Wait.
This door is opened elsewhere.
Shit.
Hold on.
Did I just kill the guy through the wall
and now he has to open the door?
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Open up that one.
No, I'm not Zoft locked.
Door to get to a door.
Yep.
Oh, there he is.
This Doom guy.
15, 20 years later.
What the fuck?
I'm gonna get in the fucking AT-ST.
I can't...
You can't get in an AT-ST.
Yes, you can.
That's too late.
I don't need an AT-ST.
I have me.
And I have powerful, powerful...
I'm gonna sneeze.
I couldn't mute.
I tried so hard.
I fucking...
I couldn't do it.
I'm so sorry.
I can't do it.
I lied.
I tried to capture it.
I'm a liar.
I'm lying.
I lied.
I tried to capture it and I got it.
It sounds like a dog sneeze.
It's a dog sneeze.
It's not like a dog sneeze.
Where is this saved?
I don't know.
No.
Ah, nice, Ron.
I'm freaking out.
I'm losing my mind.
Okay.
Hold on, please.
Just give me a minute, guys.
I promise I won't do this ever again.
Okay?
Just let me do one thing and I'll never do it again.
Nice, Ron.
Why sneeze?
I'm not allowed to sneeze.
Okay.
I'm so sorry, everybody.
I don't know if you're probably gonna be like,
I'm fucking out of here or whatever.
Nice, Ron.
Why sneeze?
I'm not allowed to sneeze.
Nice, Ron.
Why sneeze?
I'm not allowed to sneeze.
Nice, Ron.
Why sneeze?
I'm not allowed to sneeze.
Done.
I'll never do it again.
I promise.
I promise you'll never hear me do that ever again.
I will never do that again.
Ever.
You'll never hear me do that again.
You better not.
I promise I won't.
You can trust me.
I will never do that again.
What are you doing?
Where is he?
Where's the guy that owns this place?
This looks like a boss fight.
It is.
Just let me get up there and I can just shock him.
Just a shocker.
A shocker.
Where is he?
He's got to get up there and just get him once or twice.
Is he on?
Where is he?
I don't know where he is.
Oh, he's up there.
Okay.
Where'd you get that weapon?
God damn it, man.
I got him.
I hit him once.
Whoa.
He's gonna fall off.
What the fuck?
The whole screen shakes.
Oh my.
Whoa.
Easy, easy.
Don't kill me.
I just stepped on his head.
Why did that work more effectively than forest lightning?
Oh my fucking god.
Shoot him.
I...
Nice, Ron.
I did it again.
No, no, no, no, no.
It doesn't count.
That doesn't count.
That's...
It doesn't count.
I had to do the...
What?
That doesn't include the sneeze and the...
Got him.
No, let's go to the...
Fuck this.
You sense anger in me?
Better be careful.
Isn't that just a big dead rock?
It also happens to be the location of one of my father's strongholds.
You don't add a billion to the debt because I said nice brick.
Alright.
Time to be careful.
F.E. Forces.
Darth Vader in this game?
Great.
Looks like somebody's home.
Luke sure knows how to pick him.
Darth Vader in this game?
Testing my compressor.
It's acid rain?
Am I saying ooh?
Nice, dude.
Nice.
What's his name, Kyle?
Nice, Kyle.
God.
Oh, God.
Is he doing that?
Ooh.
Ah.
E.
Ooh.
What the fuck?
Oh my God, it's ruined.
Coming back.
Let's go.
Okay, you can't just run in.
You cannot just run in.
This level sucks.
Do something.
There it is.
Save it.
Go.
None of them are yours.
They're all mine.
None of us are free.
Yeah, men of the night swap.
I need help down here.
It's a Jedi.
Nice job.
You did it.
Excellent work.
If you can get away, nope.
Nobody left alive.
I don't know who you guys are.
No one left alive.
True way of the Sith.
Obtained golden arm.
You're joking, right?
Okay.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Kill, kill.
Nice.
Checkpoint.
Oh, I thought I could hit by the door.
I can't wait until Darth Vader shows up.
Shield recharge machine.
Oh my God.
I got it.
I'm right here.
Where are they at?
Two Jedi's walking in.
This lightsaber is weird.
It's like thin and blue.
It's not like a regular lightsaber.
There's a point in the end.
Oh shit.
Look out.
You're going this way?
Uh, nope.
Not being in front of the width of his saber.
All right.
Shield booster.
Oh boy.
Watch out.
This is a job for you.
Can he die?
Nice.
God, this reminds me.
Nice one.
Nice one, James.
Whatever they do.
Oh boy.
I'm going to die.
Where'd he go?
I can't just get in the fucking window.
Come on.
Music is...
Where'd he go?
Why is he not here?
He's dead?
No, he's not.
Take cover.
Did I fall?
Yes, they're expecting us now.
I have to get to that turbo laser and take out the bomber first.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, what?
He's not even with me.
I guess it's time to get the turbo laser.
Is that a big secret?
He must be...
My goodness gracious.
I almost died.
Is that the guy had like a launch code or something?
Here are the codes.
I'd stay here for a sec.
Die, die, die, die, die.
What?
Where the fuck did you come from?
Well, I could use your help.
Let's go.
I could use your help.
I got this.
Don't worry.
You're dealing with a real Sith Lord, but I'm a good guy.
Oh, fuck.
Obi-Wan, Obi-Wan, help me.
Obi-Wan.
Obi-Wan, get down here.
Obi.
Come on.
Get him.
Let's cut his arm off.
Nice job, man.
Let's do a high five with our lightsabers.
You're joking.
Sliced him.
Nice one, James.
I missed two times.
That means you get to live.
That's who's behind it all.
That's the wizard behind the fucking Wizard of Oz.
He just scared me.
Don't ever come up behind a Jedi when he's in the middle of a fight.
Wait here.
Let me know if I get it open.
A Jedi.
Did you change clothes?
All right.
Okay.
Guess who can do that too?
I can do that too.
You know, choking match.
Yeah, I'm a Sith too, motherfucker.
You want to see who's stronger?
Who can choke each other's fucking neck harder?
Put the lightsabers down.
Let's do it our way.
God, give me your best.
What the hell was that?
Oh my fucking god.
I'm his last save.
See, okay.
I just went back in time and just surprised the hell out of him.
He's just like, what?
How does he know?
I time traveled and found him.
Goodbye.
All right.
Where's the turbo blaster?
Blaster time.
Get on there.
I died?
Let's get to the castle.
Where's the castle?
All right.
Made it.
Turbo.
Everything's gonna be turbo.
There's a turbo blaster.
There's a turbo lifter.
There's a turbo.
Turbo graphics.
We got...
What do we got, Obi-Wan?
Turbo.
Let's go.
No one ever said being a Jedi was glamorous.
Actually, a lot of people did.
Like a dream of every child.
Like it's like it's the thing that everybody wants to do.
It's like being a superhero.
Everyone loves it.
In fact, it's one of the most glamorous jobs I think in the galaxy.
Everybody knows you.
Everybody respects you.
Everybody like loves you.
Who talking about?
How'd you do that?
What are you just doing out in the trash?
Did I do it?
Is it activating?
Why is there a huge trash base?
Holy shit, they all freaked out.
They freaked out when I put the grenades.
It puts them into a panic.
How do you...
He's in the vent.
He's looking up.
He doesn't care about this guy.
He just gets with the guy in the vent.
Get up there.
I can get up there.
Maybe.
I think I can do it.
Can you?
Maybe he can.
Come on, do it.
He has changed his target.
Oh, I shot him.
What is this guy doing up there?
We got to kill this guy.
Grenade?
All right, I'm going to throw up.
All right.
He's going to freak the fuck out in here.
I don't have any more grenades.
Hold on.
I wish I had grenades.
He's literally just spawn camping in here.
Like you're just camping.
Can we just leave him up here?
Got him.
Nice job.
Uh, Obi-Wan, Kyle, Kyle, Obi.
You get up this?
Um, is that wrong?
Oh, shit.
Where do you go?
I went in a circle.
Yeah, but what's the correct way to go though?
All right, where do we go?
Switch?
I think this door would open.
Up.
I did go up, right?
I just did this, didn't I?
I just did this.
So what?
No.
Then do it again.
Okay.
I guess that made no sense.
John Cena is killed thanks to the 20 community subs, John.
You break it?
He broke it.
We're all dead.
All right.
I'll turn the water off.
I'll be right back.
Just break everything.
Just drink it.
Turn the power.
Find a way to turn off the power.
You're going to leave him there?
That'll do it.
No cat puke.
Wow.
I really blew it.
It was a cat puke opportunity.
No.
Sometimes I just don't feel like doing it, man.
I don't have to do a cat puke every time.
I'm not just going to cat puke.
Do you just shoot lighting?
Are you learning from me?
Nice.
Ow.
Easy.
I can't take my lightsaber out.
What's wrong with the lightsaber?
Did I break it?
Why can I not take my lightsaber out?
The battery is dead.
Oh my god.
I can't take it any more, man.
All right.
I am done after this.
I'm absolutely done.
I don't know.
But apparently you didn't get killed by it.
Take the fucking lightsaber out.
Easy.
Can't just shoot it?
Okay.
I thought I had to like disable it or something.
Got one.
Got two.
Oh, he just sucked him in.
That was crazy.
You just die.
Whatever.
I have that ability too.
Cool.
Maybe we'll see it someday.
This is a long level, huh?
This definitely ends in a 2v1.
Absolutely.
I can't wait for the 2v1.
Versus like Darth Sidious.
2v1?
I'm only a master of evil, Darth.
Okay.
What are we?
Run.
Darth the Grinner.
Oh no.
Darth Grinner is on the loose.
Yo.
Help me kill.
Where'd he go?
He's just laughing.
Yeah, you're joking.
You're joking.
No, dude.
I'm not joking.
Get in here.
You idiot.
Whatever.
How do I destroy this?
Oh.
Thanks for the tip.
Appreciate it.
Not everything is lightning.
No.
Everything is lightning.
Everything.
Lightning is everything.
Wait, hold on.
Did you hear the splat?
That was a cartoon splat.
This is a fake person talking to me with a voice changer or something.
He...
That was a splat.
Imperials.
Oh no.
A fight chamber.
The mouse is coming for you.
I'm playing a video game.
I'm not screaming the movie.
It's okay.
It's allowed.
Now what?
Why do people like this dumb Star Wars shit?
2v1.
Wait, I'm the boss.
You idiot.
Weedlely and Tweedledum.
Oh, he almost just killed him.
No, this is one person controlling two people at the same time
with a controller and the keyboard.
Doing pretty well considering.
Lots of Sith Lords.
Oh, that's another thing I have to ask.
Do we have a Jedi Academy?
Is this...
I'm seeing a lot of red lightsabers.
Do they have like a Sith Lord Academy?
Because there's a lot of these little Sith henchmen.
Do they?
Oh shit.
Okay, that was pretty nice.
You're not supposed to ask that question.
Well, I just did.
Yellow means you're a sentinel?
Cool.
Let go.
He's powering up.
Are you serious?
You dishonorable.
Completely out of the fucking goddamn question
that you would do something like that.
Unbelievable.
Demote this guy.
Get rid of him.
You're going to shoot a guy in the back
in the middle of a 1v1 lightsaber Sith versus Jedi battle.
Are you proud of yourself?
No honor at all.
Oh, yeah, you are.
Yes, nodding.
Very good.
I'm going to torture this motherfucker when I get over there.
Karen.
Oh, yes, you are nodding.
Yeah, go ahead and kill me.
Well, I'm killing you too.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh my god, let go of me.
Stop that.
I'm using the powers of light.
I will use the powers of light to destroy you.
100 creeper blocks.
Be careful.
Let me go.
Shock him.
Give me that back.
Through the wall.
You can do that through the wall.
No, you can't.
Lie.
There it is.
Got it.
1v1 duel.
You're dead.
Give him the jock jock.
Shock jock him.
Oh shit, there's another.
Bye.
Where's that Sith Jedi?
Where'd he go?
There he is.
Big mistake letting go of your blade like that.
What an idiot.
Completely opening yourself up to an attack.
Why is chat rioting?
What do you mean?
I have to fight two-
No, I'm leaving.
Yeah, you come get me.
Oh shit, this is a bad idea.
Where is my friend?
I have to fight three of these guys at the same time?
This is unfair.
Really unfair.
Oh, I can hide over here.
They have trouble in tight spaces.
Oh my god, I don't even know what's happening.
They-
They're not powerful.
You don't think I'm fighting four of you guys at the same time?
And a choker guy and a flying mech suit.
I think I'm pretty powerful.
I think I'm very powerful, actually.
Oh my god, die.
Holy shit, he's got lightning too.
Nice.
Mine's blue.
That means mine's good.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, get out of here.
I'm busy right now.
Jesus, all right.
So what do you say?
You're going to catch up to me soon?
Doing what?
Where is he?
He's going to just come in on a giant fucking ship, isn't he?
This level is way too long, by the way.
It's like extended level.
What does he want me to do?
Back up there?
Go up?
Oh, that blends in, but that blends in.
That blends in.
I don't even care about that guy.
I don't even want to fight him.
Like, I don't care.
All right, this is the big climax right here.
This is it.
What's wrong with my game?
What's wrong with the game?
It's kind of stretched.
I got drugged by the droid.
Oh, okay.
Get.
Oh, I hate that.
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
I'm hungry.
That run.
Oh, damn it.
That fucking run freaked me out, man.
Get that chip.
I'm for a whopper?
No, thank you.
Rather, never mind.
It's like, those things.
I hate this stupid fucking shield.
Eat lead.
Oh, wait, what?
They have lightsabers now?
Since when do they have lightsabers?
Oh, they did once.
They fly now?
What's that from?
You know, they keep playing the Darth Vader song, but he's not in the game.
Bye.
No, no, I don't want to do that right now.
Oh, it's a double wielding lightsaber foe.
Oh, I thought I was going to get right in the middle.
What the fuck is this?
Is this going to be screaming?
Okay, run.
There's a lot of trash.
Holy shit, you have tons of trash.
Yeah, try to block all those.
Oh, what a one-line.
Here comes Darth Vader.
Treat it like doom.
May the force be with you.
What?
Oh, what?
Did they like phone a friend or something?
How did you come down here?
Was he supposed to be the whole time?
Was he supposed to be here the entire time?
Someone didn't like Vader much.
Wait, is that Kyle?
That's not Kyle.
Somebody just fell off.
What did he do?
How did he fall?
I can't.
He slipped on something.
I mean, how?
I win.
Guys, did you just hear it?
All right, I'm going to shoot a fake one.
Here's the real one.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm trying to stick it on the wall.
This is a fucking mistake.
All right, now why don't you come over here and get me, you fucking punk.
Oh, look at this.
Come and get me.
Stronger, no.
Smarter, maybe.
Pretty good.
Never take your blade down.
People always do that and it's the stupidest idea.
You just look silly.
How many times are they going to do that?
The MCA sounds.
Oh, this one has the Darth Maul.
Darth Maul-ding.
What? Did I win?
Okay, I got him.
Oh, shit.
This is like the chancellor, the emperor.
Yeah, of course he was bad.
Tony Hawk's Pro Skater Underground.
Darth Rosh.
Rosh, what are you saying?
You're a Jedi.
No, I am.
Enough talk.
Rosh, destroy this puny Jedi so we can complete our task.
Yeah, I think I know what it's like.
Yes.
I'm also Darkseid.
If you're too weak to join us, Jaden, we can't let you stand in our way.
Red.
Oh, no, it's red.
This guy, they're back facing me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's just up there.
He's gonna fall.
He's gonna fall, guys.
He's gonna fall and we're gonna all laugh at it.
He's gonna fall.
Get down from there.
Come on.
Come on, fall.
Fall already.
He ain't gonna fall.
He just fall down already.
I knew he was coming.
I knew it was still funny.
He hit his head on.
He even laid out for that.
He didn't even lay out that far.
At least try to land on your knees and roll, man.
You just went completely belly flop on your stomach.
At least give yourself the opportunity.
You're not like cave in your chest.
Why is he blue?
I can't.
It's a hologram.
Take this.
Oh, he's green now.
That means I have force power.
Shit.
Get away, get away, get away, get away, get away, get away, get away.
Get away.
Get the fuck away from me.
Get away, mom.
Oh, my fucking God.
Don't let him kill you.
He's shitty.
He's horrible.
He's like the little pretend antagonist.
All right.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Fuck.
I was trying to be dishonorable.
This guy's fucking running.
These guys don't even have any.
Where's rash?
I'm going to wait until it's 100 and then do it.
Die for rash.
All right.
Back up, back up, back up.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
And big head tennis.
That's what you're looking for.
You're looking for big head tennis.
I don't know where it was.
There it is.
Do it.
I would give up my apprentice so easily.
He's standing there the whole time.
You should have killed me when you had the chance, Katarn.
Your pathetic Jedi mercy is a weakness
that shall cost you your life
and the life of your academy's students.
But not you, my dear rash.
Come.
Yes, Tavian.
Rash, no.
Friendship cannot compare with the power of the dark side.
I know.
I'm incredibly strong in the dark side.
Stealing scraps of the force like some sort of intergalactic parasite.
Spare me your self-righteous pity, Katarn.
You may have shamed me when you spared my life.
I got much better lightning hands than anybody in this room.
Please.
Now, master.
One who has promised me that destroyed the Jedi.
Ragnos, what can a dead Sith Lord give you?
Everything I have ever wanted.
Not that I'm to see.
What?
It's quite the drop.
It's quite the fumble.
I can't keep this up for long.
Hold on.
I don't even know what just happened.
We looked everywhere after getting free.
But Tavian had already taken Rosh and fled.
Sitting.
So now we know who was leading this cult.
But that doesn't explain why there are so many dark force users.
Some of Desan's left over re-
A lot wrong with what just happened there, I think.
As for the cultists, Jaden has a theory.
If the scepter can store the force, maybe it can release it too.
Tavian could be using it to empower her followers.
Corrupting disciples with the dark side of the force?
That would explain a lot.
Did you get a good look at the scepter?
Yeah.
I bet it belonged to Ragnos.
We need to figure out what Tavian plans on doing with it.
If we're going to stop her.
Agreed.
You are going to need to build a new lightsaber to replace the one you lost.
Oh!
Try to figure out what Tavian's next move is.
Sir?
Jaden.
You handled yourself exceptionally well on Vajun.
To confront three dark Jedi and defeat them took bravery and skill.
Efforts?
I feel you are ready to join our ranks as a Jedi Knight.
Oh me?
Congratulations.
Yes, Master Skywalker.
Thank you both.
Jaden.
When do I get fired?
I felt the anger seething inside you.
You may be a Jedi Knight now, but you still must beware of the dark side.
Yes, Kyle.
I'll try not to fail you.
I'll try.
Oh, yep.
Dual sabers.
Two-handed saber.
Oh, what would I have?
I would have one big orange dual saber.
Or...
German 985 build.
Why can't I have three?
The Joker?
What do you mean the Joker?
Oh, that's...
Yeah, it kind of is, isn't it?
It is the Joker.
I'm going big orange that one.
Okay, I'm done.
But I just want to see what it looks like.
These are all level three already.
Force drain.
Drain life essence.
All right, I just want to see what it is.
I'm not playing this mission.
I just want to see.
Please don't ever stream again.
Well, I am.
I'm sorry.
Disappoint you.
Yeah, I'm done.
I will be back.
I'll see you guys on...
I'll see you guys on Saturday afternoon.
Oh, there it is.
It's one of those big demons, right?
I just want to swing it around for a second
and then end the stream.
Yeah, thanks for watching, everybody.
You can eat him or not?
Okay, really?
That was a lot of build-up, I was going to say.
Get on with it.
You care about me?
Who's the intruder?
There's a rancor over here.
What are you doing?
Look, I know we're enemies,
but there's something...
Look.
Look what's over here.
He goes up and just starts punching.
Did you see that?
He was like, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, I got this guy right here.
This could be...
I want to see.
There's an opportunity for him to break through here
and fight this guy, maybe?
Okay, let's see what happens.
Dad, why is he coming after me?
Really?
I was dead a long time ago, dude.
Please, eat me.
Just eat me.
He's thinking about you.
Mmm, this is...
This medicine is delicious.
Let me try it.
Mmm.
No!
It's too sour.
All right, I'm done.
I will see you guys on Saturday.
I'm not sure what we're going to do on Saturday,
but we'll see.
I mean, we could...
I could finish this,
but how much more time do I really have in this game?
What's the...
Anybody know how much time is left?
Like two or three hours?
Is it just this,
or is there another section after this?
This is the last section?
Okay.
Yeah, here's what we'll do.
On Saturday, we're going to finish this,
because I'm not going to be a never-finished-games Andy,
right?
Because this is fun and funny.
So we're going to finish this game,
and then we'll pivot to something else
for a couple hours, too,
depending on how long it takes.
I will see you guys on Saturday.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
We'll see you soon.
This has been Star Wars Jedi Knight Jedi Academy,
and we'll see you Saturday.
Here come the subs that came in today.
Thanks, everybody.
Kind of long.
Longer than recently, usual, you know,
but I was having fun.
Hope you have a good start to your weekend.
We'll see you soon.
Let's do a raid.
Yeah, let's raid somebody.
Who do we got streaming right now?
Let's see.
Quite a few people are streaming right now.
Quite a few people.
I'm going to dump you on Italics.
Italics is playing Cooking Simulator,
and I mean, that game is just fun.
I'm not sure he's ever played it before.
Maybe go say hello to Italics.
Cooking Simulator.
I will see you guys on Saturday.
Good night.
Bye.
Thank you again.
Feels bad ignoring Link.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Which one?
Ah-ee-oo.
Is this a huge ass?
Okay, this is funny.
All right, I'll allow this.
This is funny.
This one can slip through because I like it.
It's funny.
That's wrong.
Wrong Link is another one.
Press A for ah, E for e.
S for sneeze.
Audio jungle.
How did you make this website?
Nice rhyme.
I just did it, but I was just showing you that I have that too.
Hold them down?
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean hold them down?
No, that doesn't...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on.
That's not fair.
Okay, I'm not doing that again.
Audio jungle.
Yeah, done.
That was fun.
All right, good night.
I just blocked the rest of the credits with this shit.
Oh my god.
All right.
I'll see you guys Saturday.
Have a great night.
Go say hello to Italics.
Have a wonderful rest of your evening.
I will see you guys on Saturday.
Good night.
Good bye.
Take care of yourselves.
See you later.