Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Pyro with the default flamethrower, the flare gun, and the axe extinguisher.
None of it's strange, and none of it's vintage. This is a pretty good run, at least in the beginning as the Pyro.
I get a lot of good flare gun shots, kill a lot of people, a lot of people are covered in Jarate.
So thank you to the sniper that kept on throwing that on people, because it got me a lot of kills.
But this is not gonna be about really the gameplay, it's a big update video.
If you saw my Twitter last night, I made this announcement.
Here comes a big update, I got a huge thing to talk about in this next video.
And I do. What I want to talk about is I want to talk about my upload schedule, and how it's going to change dramatically in the next five days.
So if you've been around the channel for a while, you've probably realized I do anywhere from three to five videos a week.
Now that depends, it could be Team Fortress, it could be Grand Theft Auto, Binding of Isaac, I do a lot of different stuff.
But what I'm going to do now is I'm going to do ten videos a week.
And the reason why I decided to do this is not only from you guys, I get a lot of PMs, I get a lot of comments telling me,
Jerma, can we get more videos? Can we get longer videos? This is great, you know, four uploads, three uploads is cool,
but it would be awesome if you could upload every day.
And I do take that to heart, because I do want to upload every day, and I do want to get content out as best as I can, as fast as I can for you guys.
And I'm going to start to do that. It's the summer, I got a lot of free time, I had free time before,
but the days are longer in summer and everyone seems to be around longer, so I'm going to start to do this next week.
And what's going to happen is you're going to see a lot of content.
There'll be one video in the morning or mid-afternoon, somewhere around 12 or noon Eastern Time,
and another one out around 7 or 8 PM Eastern Time.
So I'm going to try and do two uploads a day, at least Monday and Tuesday, because of course I'm going to try and get for ten.
If I did two videos every single day, that would be two, four, six, eight, ten, twelve, fourteen, fourteen videos a week, and that's not what I'm going to do.
Oh, and also the livestream. The livestream is not going anywhere, it's still going to be every week, it's going to be Sundays now.
No longer is it going to be Saturdays, it's going to be Sundays at 1 PM Eastern Time.
So don't worry, it's not like I'm throwing away the livestream, that'll still be there.
And if you were at the last livestream I tried to do, where Team Fortress wouldn't work, I actually can't stream any 3D games right now,
because there's a bug between the 670 and XSplit.
So until they come out with a new driver update, or until I can figure out a solution, I'm going to have to stream lower end games for a couple weeks,
maybe less, I'm not sure when Nvidia is going to do their update, we will see.
So what kind of content can you expect to see in the coming weeks, in the coming future of this channel?
Well, I'll tell you. Pretty much I'm going to start doing a lot more live stuff, so everything that you already see on this channel is going to stay.
There's just going to be a hell of a lot more of it.
You'll get a live com pretty much every night, depending if it's Team Fortress, Binding of Isaac, GTA, there'll always be a live com on the channel.
And of course there'll be my normal post-com stuff as well, I'm not going to change any of that.
So the only thing that's actually changing on the channel is more videos will be uploaded on top of what already is uploaded, if that makes any sense.
So that's the plan of action, that's my schedule I'm going to try and stick to.
So 10 uploads a week, starting this coming Monday.
I've been toying with the idea for a while to do more uploads and longer videos and stuff like that,
but now it seems like I finally have a plan where I can flesh it all out and actually do it.
So look forward to that, starting on Monday, like I said, and we'll see where it goes, right?
So the next thing I want to talk about is the Pyro meet the Dust Lint Goldfish Woodplank thing that's going on in the latest update in Team Fortress.
I don't know what the hell is going on. I read on the forums that if you put on a certain set,
I forget what the name of the set is, but if you put a full set on, you can see some more cryptic text,
or you can look at the images a different way or something like that.
All I know is this, whenever Valve decides to do these in-game puzzle kind of adventure type things,
where you have to figure things out and it's all cryptic and all that, it always means an update is right around the corner.
Do you guys remember the dove situation in Meet the Medic?
Remember all the doves that were flying around and all the weird stuff with that?
And also the rockets, the Groddborz rockets that were landing?
Oh, you go to the skybox and there's this and that, and it's always about an update.
So I'm smelling the update bug. It's inside of my nostrils right now.
That did not sound good or really nice at all.
But anyways, that's going to wrap up this video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And if you have any more information on this crazy new update, then definitely let us all know.
I'm sure a lot of people in the comments would like to know, and of course I do too.
So yeah, I'll see you guys all next time, and take care everybody.