Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and today I'm gonna be playing as the Soldier with the original debuff banner in the Halfs of Taichi, currently shooting people out of spawn, and this is going to be a coffee commentary of Drusters in Doom. If you don't know what that is, this is when I go really fast, really crazy with the commentary, and I just hit record and I start talking about nonsense. I have no idea what's gonna come out of my mouth. Who knows, there could be like presents that come out of my mouth, so get ready to open up.
Anyways, before the coffee commentary gets started, I want to slow it down a little bit and talk about a more serious thing, and it's the Tip of the Hat charity. For those of you that don't know what's going on, they're raising a bunch of money, the TF2 community, for a day camp with kids with cancer, and I think that's amazing, I think that's awesome, and I'm gonna give as much support as I can. I didn't really know this was happening until like two or three days ago, so I'm kind of late to the party, but better late than never, so I'm gonna leave in the description
They're gonna be live streaming today, Sunday, it's Sunday, yeah, Sunday from 12 a.m. to 12 p.m. Well, reverse that, 12 p.m. to 12 a.m. It's gonna be going on all day, all kinds of cool things going on, and I encourage you to donate some money if you can, if you have a couple of bucks lying around, they're doing all kinds of raffles and stuff, it's very, very cool. So with that said, we're gonna move on now, talk about the coffee commentary, gonna go into this, gonna start talking really fast, as you guys know I do that sometimes, here we go! Currently capping the second point, which is actually the first point, which is actually the second to last,
point which is the middle point of Hoodoo, whatever you want to call it, capped that trying to push to the last point, Pyro coming in on Booman61, I don't get the crit off, but somebody else gets the kill, Bakasora apparently gets the kill, BakaOP, according to the kill feed, Medica behind us, and where am I? Oh, here I am, hey, my screen just froze, anyways, Bakasora gets knocked into the air of a thousand feet by a crit, sticky, actually I think it was just a normal pill, but we got a Phlogiston or a Pyro holding it down here with a WM-1, which is fantastic, because this hallway is
ridiculous, if you play Hoodoo, like I do, I try to all the time, this hallway is the ultimate choke point, like seriously, there's two hands wrapped around your neck choking you, shaking you back and forth, when you're playing at this part of Hoodoo, so it's really hard to push, it's really hard to, even defending this can be a pain in the ass too, because people are just piling out in droves, like it's the Android army of 1976 when the world collapsed, and, you know, whatever, I'm just, you know, coffee, let's go. And we're still stuck in this choke point here, this Chef Demoman comes out,
somebody complained about his bacon and eggs being a little bit undercooked, and he wanted to say something to the customer in question, he actually got himself killed, and his restaurant went under after that, actually they were two or three million dollars in debt anyways, so a lot of people think it could have been a suicide anyways to get away from the debt his family would have had to incur, but anyways, respawning here now, Pyro coming in, there's a lot of Pyros in this gameplay, a ton of Pyros just running at me over and over again, like this guy right here, and that Spy, help me Spy, kill this Pyro, got it, too late, where are we now, what am I doing, alright, I'm picking up this health pack, yeah, because I've just
blew up on it, that's a Spy, that Sniper is a Spy, and watch this, get blasted bro, get out of here, get out of my house, even though this isn't even my house, I'm just renting, I'm just renting for Christ's sake, let's keep going, shooting down the hallway, keep out of that door, don't know what's going on inside there, what is inside of there by the way, why does it say keep out, what is in there, is it like an electric fence or something, get a double kill Jerma while you're at it, thanks, no problem, and while we go down this hallway to get a couple more kills, I'm gonna talk about my Steam name right now, Fig Newton,
if you don't know what a Fig Newton is, let me just very briefly describe what it is, it is the grossest snack in the history of snacks, it seriously, it tastes like ground up jelly beans inside of like a pie crust, that's how, that might sound, actually kind of sounded pretty good, it's not good though, if you like it, some people like it, some people hate it, it has the same kind of polarizing snack factor as the Dr. Pepper does, so I completely understand if you like ground up jelly beans inside of a pie crust, you know, whatever, that's your thing, Dr. Pepper's my thing, so okay,
good, we've squared up right now, get out of here, spy, have we really been stuck in the same choke point for the entirety of this video, have I been sitting here for like two minutes, get wall banged by the way, Pyro, have I really been sitting here for like two minutes straight shooting people in this hallway, I think I really have, nothing has happened besides killing dead ringers or fake killing them, them appearing behind me and trying to backstab me, but whatever, we're gonna still sit in this hallway, I'm looking at the timeline in Premiere right now, and we've got at least another like 30 seconds in this hallway, wait, wait, where am I going,
health pack, that's okay, you can take your break from your work, but you have to get right back to your post in the middle of the hallway for like another four hours, alright, good, you're there, wait, wasn't I supposed to be shell casting too, alright, let's like get back into shell cast mode, Pyro coming up behind me, but Fig Newton gets the kill on him, trying to get stair stabbed by that spy, there are a lot of spies and a lot of Pyros on the enemy team as per noted, but this laggy Pyro's gonna take care of him, almost gets stair stabbed, but it's okay, Fig Newton, Fig Isaac Newton gets the kill on him, blowing the horn now to get the mini crits and somebody kill me, somebody
please kill me, like this is the worst thing that could ever happen, if you blow the buff banner and you turn into a spy, you can't bring it down fast enough, you're just gonna get smoked and having him stab you in the face three times and you are just completely defenseless is enraging, but we're gonna move, we'll move on from that, getting the crit on that heavy and a Pyro coming up the stairs, it's okay, I'm gonna jump down and launch him 50,000 feet in the air, do I get the air shot, I thought I did, I really thought I'd get the air shot, but apparently I did not, he killed himself on the fall damage, I really thought I had an air shot right there, I was so excited about
that, but it's okay, because here comes the reindeer Pyro on the other team, it's okay, we capped the cart, no we don't, we do not get the cart capped and I die, but this is where it gets very very intense, coming through the teleporter, because it's amazing, engineer is credit to team, and we're bouncing people all over the place trying to kill that medic, trying to shoot him with a couple of rockets, I almost got him with that, but it's okay, we got this soldier up here, he blew up from god knows what, I think it was a pipe bomb, but we have to push this, somebody get on it, somebody please get on this cart or else Jerma isn't gonna
flip out, Jerma is gonna start swearing, he's gonna start throwing things against the wall, does that crit hit anybody, it does not hit anybody, but we got an engineer on the cart, he's gonna cap it, engineer on the cart, here comes a Pyro, Pyro jump down, Pyro paint your gibbous, come on, get it, yes, come on, push it, oh you're gonna get it, one person, there it is, ladies and gentlemen, there is the win for the blue team, and thank you everybody so much for watching, that's gonna conclude the coffee commentary of Justice and Doom, also if you're here on Sunday, please check out the Tip of the Hat charity, because it's still going on probably by the
time you're watching this, I'm not sure it might be over, but you have at least nine hours from this recording to do it, so please support it, and I'll see y'all next time, take care everybody, bye guys.