Hey what's going on everybody, Jerma here with the first ever episode of Enlighten.
That's the title I'm gonna be using I guess. Enlighten is a series I'm doing where I go back in time
and I pick a title that was overlooked by a lot of people or didn't really sell that well but it was
still a fantastic game that you have to check out. And the first title I'm gonna go over is
something called The Neverhood. Some of you might know what this game is but a lot of you don't
because it sold so awfully and was released at such an odd time in gaming's history that
it went under the radar, very very much so. And it's unfortunate because the creator,
Doug Tenable, this is kind of his baby, he's the guy that if you don't know who Doug Tenable is,
he created Earthworm Jim. He's the guy responsible for Earthworm Jim so that alone is the reason why
you should check out this game. So what do you say we get started? I'm gonna do this very very much
in a review style, gonna show you a whole lot of clips, gonna show you a whole lot of stuff,
condense it down, you know the deal. So what do you say we go back in time?
The year is 1996 and the age of PC gaming is just starting to flourish. Large companies were
starting to realize that video games not only could function well on the PC but compete with
the popular gaming consoles. This was also the tail end of the adventure game era, a certain
genre that had players problem solve and pay attention to detail rather than shoot up a room
full of enemies. The Neverhood is one of those games and unfortunately the room full of enemies
I just mentioned is the reason why this game was killed. Selling just 42,000 copies, which by today's
standards is like getting hit by a tornado, the Neverhood died out fairly quickly, which is very
unfortunate because this game is absolutely in my top five greatest games of all time, all time,
and here's why. If you want to talk about style points for a game, the Neverhood is absolutely
off the charts when it comes to style. Everything you see, every environment, every person, every
character, everything was crafted entirely out of clay. There's no camera tricks, there's no CGI,
everything is real, in real space, and I think that adds a lot to the realism of the game and
how you can get lost in games like this. Too many games nowadays don't imply real space.
I find it a lot easier to fall into these characters and get sucked into the world when
they're actually real. I feel the same way with movies. You go back to John Carpenter's The Thing
or one of the Alien movies or any movie that actually had real creatures in it that were
crafted by an animatronic or by Jim Henson, you're going to talk about much more realism
and much more frightening things. So the plot of this game is you play a character named Clayman
who just wakes up on the ground with no backstory, nothing is there, there's no introduction, you just
appear on the ground, and it is your duty as the player to find out why you're even playing the
game in the first place. You do this by collecting these random cassette tapes that happen to be on
the ground all over the world. You then take those tapes and put them in these various tape
players that play the entire story. Once you collect all the tapes, you pretty much complete
the game. These discs are all that are left of the true story, true story of the closing of the third
age. This is a fantastic example of reverse storytelling where nobody tells you anything,
you don't get any info, you don't get any hints, you just figure it all out on your own.
And the story is actually very very interesting, it's not one of those games where you get to the
end and you go, oh well that was stupid. It's actually a pretty good story. Like any adventure
game, the gameplay revolves around problem solving and puzzles. The difficulty can be described as
stupidly easy to tear your hair out of your skull difficult. There's actually a puzzle in this game
that mimics memory, if you know what memory is. Memory is the game where you flip over tiles and
you have to match different icons. That's great and all, but in this version if you miss one time
or if you mess up once, the entire board is deleted. Which brings me to the next point about the
gameplay, get a pen and paper. You're gonna need to write down a lot of stuff. I would actually
say if you do not write down half of the information you see in this game, you will never complete it,
you will never beat the game. The game is also fairly short. If you blaze through every task and
you don't spend a whole lot of time exploring the world, you can beat this game in less than two
hours. But you don't really play this game for the gameplay. You play this game for the sheer amount
of style, the unbelievable cast of characters and you get to see a game that was created not for money
but for passion, art and creativity. Those are the reasons why you play this game and it's not
something you can sit here and watch, it's something that you have to experience. And hopefully there's
a rumor going around that the Neverhood is gonna make it to mobile devices, whether that be iPad,
iPhone, Android. So hopefully that all goes through because that would be amazing if we could all play
this game and pay a little bit of money for it, pay the developers what they actually deserve rather
than have them get thrown under the bus for years. So hopefully you guys check this game out, I really
do recommend you do it. I will see you guys all next time and enjoy yourself in the Neverhood.
Take care everybody.