I told you guys I was gonna be early. I told you. I mean I'm only five minutes early but I'm still
early. Still counts. Still does. How you doing? Are we doing good? I gotta tweet this. Today
we're gonna play some FMV games. One just came out that piqued my interest. If we're gonna play
the first one is not late. No, I'm not late. I'm precisely on time. The first one's called
American Hero and apparently this game is like 25 years old and it was never released. So some
company, I guess they like got 90% of the way through development and they just didn't finish
the game. So some random indie company, I don't know what the name of the company is. I kind of
forget. Got all the footage and actually released it. So this is a very old game. I'm very interested
in this one. You're a hipster king. Well, not really. This thing's on the Nintendo Switch right
now. So not really. I didn't like go get this on some secret place. You can literally get this on
Switch right now. What about Monster Breeder? It's possible we play Monster Breeder later today.
It really depends on how long these take. Because with some FMV games, some of these games are
40 minutes. Some of them are three hours. It really depends on how many. Maybe if we play
through it again, if we move on to the next one, I don't know. It depends. We'll see.
You can play among us. It's never gonna happen. It's gonna be awful or bad.
Is that what you said? Did I read that wrong? This is gonna be awful or bad. What about the
Goosebumps FMV with Jeff Goldblum? I did not even know that existed. But now that I know that
exists, I'm very interested. I'm like an FMV wine connoisseur. It doesn't matter how bad they are.
It doesn't matter how shitty they are. I have to play them. All of them. If I can. Also, I want to
make this really clear. There was a content warning on this game. Apparently it's pretty dated.
I don't know exactly what that means. But like I said, it's on the Switch.
I don't know how... I don't exactly know what to be looking for. But we'll be on the ready.
Are you gonna stream bad mojo? Probably not. So if we do come across something that's
fucking shitty and bad, you know, you fucking behave yourselves. Come on. Come on, Gwen.
You know what I mean? Are you gonna stream crab game? No, I don't. No. No, I don't.
Every one of these games it takes off, I don't play them. I watch. Okay. With like trends on
Twitch, it's kind of like how a lot of people jump into like the stock market and stuff.
It's like a game will come along and I'll go, that looks kind of cool. I would like to maybe
try that out. That looks like a great experience. And then I don't play it. And then two or three
weeks later, it's incredibly popular and everyone's on it. Oh, that's awesome. I
probably should have... Maybe I could get in now. I don't think I'm gonna get it. I, you know,
maybe. It looks fun. Now it's like the biggest thing on Twitch, the biggest thing in the world.
I don't want to buy the top of the crab game meta. You know what I mean? Stop calling me a hipster.
Why are you saying that? Why don't you stream McDonald's hamburger adventure? I don't even
know what you're talking about. All right. You guys ready? Apparently, this is something else
I read about this too, is the actor that's in this, they had to have him re-record lines
with the restoration. And I mean, the guy's like almost 25 plus years older than he is.
So I don't know how that's going to play out, but it might be pretty funny.
But this is American hero. I am ready. Our choices matter, apparently. Are you going to
play Fortnite or should I just go? You liar. You're a, how many months up? You're a six-month
subscriber. You've been here for six months. You know what happens on this channel. You're a liar.
You're lying to everybody. All right. You ready? Let's go. This is American hero. Viewer discretion
is advised apparently. And let's go. You ready? Oh, by the way, very important. That's the guy
from, that's my Bush from comedy central. Yeah. I don't know if anyone remembers that show.
That was a really weird reference, but here we go. American hero. Yeah. Okay. Well,
there's right off the bat, right off the bat. I hope there's, uh, I don't think, I don't think
there's any nudity. I hope not. No, there's not. Oh God. My home away from home. It's, I,
Crystal's looking good today. I think that's the, I think that's the voiceover. I think that's a new
line. You got something against me making a lemon. Relax. Just care. Asshole. There is nudity. No,
there's not. It's on the switch. It can't be. It's on the Nintendo switch. It's impossible.
They don't allow any nudity on the switch. That's a lie. It can't be possible.
Here's trouble. They were right. Now you can piss off. Sergeant. It's Colonel. BFD.
The old man has a problem. Why does it sound like he's in a bathroom? Not interested. It involves
Laura and a dangerous mind control virus. Dangerous. Okay. I think she's been kidnapped. Can't say more.
It looks like borderlands characters. What's the, what's the, it looks weird. Why are you interested?
Meet me somewhere a little more private. You're a big fucking dork. All right. Let me pay attention
to the game. A rock in a hard place. I have to make a decision here. What do I want to do?
Bad news. Bad news. Or party. What? Bad news. What's going on? What'd I do?
Did he leave? Oh shit. Am I going to get run over by a car? Why is there a truck?
Do I have to move the QTE? What do I do? What do I do? A ledge. Run. A ledge. Run. A ledge. Run. Run.
Jump. Jump. I'm going to jump. I'm going to drop. I'm going to drop. He's going to get run over.
New item unlocked? Oh shit.
Wait. Hold on a second. Hold on. So I was in a strip club and then I was either going to go do
this mission or stay in the strip club. And then he left the strip club. Started running away from
a, somebody in a Mack truck that ran my whole body over lengthwise, which is
fucking crazy. I got steamrolled. Okay. All right. No, Jesus. We have to do this again.
I don't want to have to show this again. I, all right. What should I do? Should I?
I'm going to go get the bad news. I'm not clicking party on a game that has been confirmed to have
nudity in it. No way. Not going to happen. Nope. Not happening. My home away from home.
I could run over lengthwise. That's fucking it ran over from my heels looking good today
to the top of my head. That was insane.
I missed that last time as well. He's drinking carrot juice. I don't get it.
I don't believe there's nudity on the switch.
Here's trouble. They were right. So now you can piss off. Oh, there's not. It's Colonel B F D.
The old man has a problem. I'm not clicking party. Not interested. It involves Laura
and a dangerous mind control virus. I didn't mean to click that. I think she's been kidnapped.
Can't say more upscaled with AI. If you're interested, meet me somewhere a little more.
It does actually, I'm actually kind of glad it looks like this because some of the old FMV
games we played in the past, they look like absolute dog shit. So this doesn't really even
look that bad. All right. No, no party. No, I have to get this right. It's like a rhythm game.
Bad news. Bad news. Bad news. Bad news. I clicked bad news. I clicked bad news. I don't want to
run away from the fucking truck. I clicked bad news. I clicked.
I clicked. What's the fuck? No, I'm how do I skip the cut scene?
I'm not going to get run over again. The truck is bad news. Oh, no it's not. I didn't do anything
last time. All right. All right. This time don't drop. This time I'm going to, I'm going to go
for the ledge. Ledge. Ledge. Run. Ledge. Run. Ledge. Ledge. Ledge. Run. Is he doing it?
What? He's not making decisions. What the fuck? Drop. Jump. Drop. I can't do anything. Drop. Do
you hear me clicking? Do you hear this? What? Why doesn't the game work? Mouse one. I'm clicking
mouse one. Oh, this is not good. It's not right click. It's left click, right? Maybe I should
unplug the controller. I don't think I have one unplugged in. I mean the mouse apps. Yeah,
that's left click. I don't think, no, there's no controller plugged in. It's just my mouse.
I was spamming too. 10 second reaction time. Try right clicking. Hold on. Options.
Dirty full screen. Set keys. Set. Okay. Select. Left click, right? Yeah. Action. Space.
Better be pressing. Well, why would it say left click? I guess I'm going to try to hit space.
It's also up, down, left, right as well. Well, I'll try space. God damn it. All right. I'll try
space. You better believe I'm going to try to make sure this, get this to work. You don't get
run over lengthwise by a car like that and not like play out at least some of the game. Are you
kidding me? No way. All right. Let me see what happens. The tutorial doesn't give you, it just
tells you, um, like the gist of the game. I read it already. All right. Can I skip this cut scene?
How do you skip cut scene? Escape. That's definitely a way to do it. Enter.
It's tab. I mean, it's tab works. My home away from home. Right click. No, this is definitely
a way to do it. Looking good today. I'm going to see if space works. Pinhead. Why are you making
us watch this? I'm not making you watch this again. I'm trying the game's controls are not accurate.
Here's trouble. They were right. So now you can piss off sergeant. It's colonel. D F D.
The old man has a problem. He needs your help. Not interested. Bad news space. It involves law.
It doesn't work that I don't know what I'm going to do. It's not the game. Oh, should I like,
should I plug it to controller in? I think she's been kidnapped. Can't say more.
Falls have ears. If you're interested, meet me somewhere a little more private.
And let's see. Base rock in a hard place. Come on, please work. Please work. Bad news. All right.
It's space. It's fucking space. What is that meter at the top? I knew you'd make the right
choice. Okay, Colonel, this better be good. I hope I still get run over by a fucking truck.
I'm sure Laura would be impressed. I'm not here on a social visit.
There's so many cigarettes. Kruger's escaped. It's up to his old tricks. Laura was working
for us. She developed an antivirus formula. They kidnapped her before she could get it to us.
Tell me about the virus. The old man will do that. What matters is you want Laura. We want the
antivirus formula. Okay. No, that's not, that's not Nick Cage. What do you think, Jack? Can you
get it up for another? Fuck you. Yes. Fuck you. Yes. Fuck you. Yes. What just happened? I just
blacked out. Why did I black out? What was the point of blacking out? Oh, it's censored.
Get it. Split. What? Lemo. Get it. Lemo. Split. Lemo. Get it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no. It's the elasticity of the Switch. It's
all the Switch. It's on the Nintendo Switch. It's not going to happen. It's not going to happen.
You should drink a big water. That's it. It's all Nintendo Switch now going to happen.
Things are looking up. No, they're not, no, they're not, they're
have to get out of this. It does three options. It's like, I'm playing a fucking Mario Party
game where I have to like hit the dice at the right time. Give me a break. That's weird.
I don't get out leave, leave, leave before I hit the escape button? Leave, run.
no leave leave now leave not actually I gotta get out I'm out I'm out I'm out I'm out skip
how do I skip skip skip skip get up no I'm not fucking doing this not gonna
happen it's on the Nintendo switch she was just
drinking water that's it not gonna happen I didn't even want to do this it's
this control system just watch it if there's no nudity right if there's nudity
I'm out no I'm out already no you don't say here comes the finale and no I'm
not happening I'm sorry I'm sorry I have no I have a clean record with twitch
I've never been suspended I've never had a terms of service problem if I let her
drop her hair and what is I'm assuming potentially some of her clothing
material I am it's not gonna happen no I know that's possible so what I'm his
gonna do I'll meet you halfway I'm gonna I'm gonna send to the spring for
a second and I'll let you know how it goes yeah what yeah what yeah um what
I think it's okay I think we're okay we're good so far I don't know what he's
like looking at the I don't know what he's looking at what is it what is it
happening she killing me what the what what is it boom escape dude I have no
she sat on me I don't even know what to say this has been it's been insane this
has been absolutely insane I didn't know what to say I jumped out of a window but
what I didn't know where the window went I want to go back and do what I wanted
to do I want to do what I wanted to do in the first place I want a new game yes
new game I want to do what I was trying to do before I'm not gonna get soft
locked into that I wanted to take the limo yes I'm gonna play through this
like 30 times don't worry this has been fucking hilarious so far okay let's try
it here we go oh god damn it I'm locked in I like have I actually have to do
this the game won't let me do it okay well then boombox is the right answer
then I think right things are looking up I can't just get the cutscene give me a
break whatever you're walking on eggshells I'm very aware I'm very
aware so that that's she's just wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no you're still wearing her fucking
underwear yeah what yeah she still has her clothes on okay we're back so it's
on a black screen yeah I know she's pretending like she's going to like
sleep with me or I guess I don't know and then she's just trying to kill me
that's I guess what's going on right now and then I've been like hypnotized by
this thing boombox I'm trying to feed back this thing oh it hurts me in real
life though all right get out take it I get I'm not gonna know hey I get take
that whatever that is I'm not jumping out the window again it kills you don't
okay limo shortcut Laura's shortcut Laura's shortcut Laura's limo cut
through limo limo cut through took me a long time to get here you know I
wouldn't be here I've died like four times this time he has created a
genetically old and brain virus and you lost Laura before she could get the
antivirus formula to you Laura's my wife let's check that toaster this guy's
reading like a parent that's just barely getting through a story at storytime
with a kid late at night
I'm gonna turn the game
volume up I turned it down because the feedback we got a raid what's the rate
from you got a raid from RT what's up RT RT game crowd welcome everybody I'm
gonna give you a very very quick warning we're playing a game that's got some
pretty fucked up themes I guess it's an old FMV game it just released it's on
the Nintendo switch though it's on the switch therefore you know I don't think
they'd be very much nudity or anything like that just know that is on the
switch but I'll welcome everybody thanks a lot for the raid I turned it
down wait I'm not even going anywhere I'm just getting out of the limo why
didn't we go somewhere like didn't I just do this Laura's KVK Laura's KVK
Laura's KVK that's too loud yeah those things are loud door looks open looks
like somebody might may have gotten in gate door climb gate door climb holy shit
you gotta pick quick anybody home why are they so much louder than everything
else the internal monologue is so loud Laura's left your purse money in there
looks like Mark Zuckerberg forget it need it forget it need it okay was it like
200 bucks 200 bucks in like 1990 was like fucking eight grand so I'll take it mm-hmm
gotta go mm-hmm gotta go wait was I gonna take a shower
Kruger's goons oh goons oh shit oh they're telling me I can lose these
creeps how what am I gonna do find the telephone pole hell of a day and it's
only two and I lose them wait hold on I will now I know how to play go for a
leg I think you have to get hit by the truck a leg run I think run is death
oh shit I did that sequence this guy's just walking in circles
they were still on behind me still hey would they hit it for the truck cab all
right run fight all right run fight fight I can take a nice but that wasn't
really a fight I just kind of run nice you want some to bring it on the tried
and true henchmen stormtrooper routine just don't have a helmet on shit all
right well now they're not gonna be following me right at super cab
drive drive just drive all right here we go all right where we going
the old man sent me told me to keep an eye on all you said you needed don't
distract I'm gonna get a little driving okay we got you coming got a gun that
on it
right left right drive in the car his decision not mine
oh you're dead why is all the stuff everywhere there's too much stuff
breaks gas fight all right yes like I blacked out
why is this hard for my head hurts hold on
are we driving these ripping the wheel back and forth I'm not the one behind
the wheel I'm not driving the car you folded like a lawn chair god that was so
stupid I know people saying certain thing I'm just gonna move on and scream
it's very funny oh my god damn it what an American hero I'm not gonna fight
this time I'm gonna stay in the car it's a break in front of me just match
the brakes you can't believe that happened this game is insane
hit the brake brake brake yes fight nice all right good decision good call I know
wait you're gonna break yeah fine no kids it's my lucky day we're good I
think I think that's I think that I thought that was the right decision it
was not the right decisions probably break yeah yeah okay what if I hit gas
here's what the other option this game is having a nightmare it is gonna have
a nightmare it's break break is the right play we're gonna get the same
ending it's my lucky day you smoke gas this is outrageous is brave the way Jack
would watch it be ashes to ashes dust to dust what was the budget for this game I
don't know but the crazy story about this game is that you weren't here in
the very beginning this game was never released it it was done filming and I
don't know if they've ran the studio ran out of money or something but it was
never actually released a new company came in and kind of remastered all the
footage and restored it it's the only reason why we're playing it today okay
it's a break break all it's because it was in a Jaguar right and the console
we're not arguing about McDonald's or Wendy's we're talking about life and
death here I know we're gonna be great friends right yes there we go okay we're
good on to the next sequence what are you waiting for let's go okay what is
this pretty tight security this is the lab why would I just walk to the front
door like a fucking sim that's a neighbor what are you doing oh what are
you doing he was wearing a suit under all that holy shit he must be sweating
good to see you again Jack well I was freezing food was just too boring
where's Laura everything in good time hey well I think I think I'm gonna try
to like melt me into the into the chemical that has one fatal design can
you guess what that is Russia Los Angeles is built on near desert what
try another 10 CC oh if someone were to say for instance here that was a fake
hand sitting there was a rubber hand I will release my virus into the system
within minutes the disease will ripple out exponents it will be the greatest
biological conquest of all boys in the waters I no longer have to remove this
primitive but clever oh that's why they're drinking the water out of the
big bottles another failed attempt oh sadistic bastard I got ready to turn and
fight oh no I'm gonna get like tortured what information do I have anyways I'm
just like an agent that's Laura Jack it was a story recap so far I was in
retirement I came out of retirement to solve this madman poisoning the water
supply done already on my case what oh no they took away the light that bulb is
so expensive that's very okay we're gonna take the solution here quick okay
all right right right here pin the guard here the guard do the medical solid I'm
sick I have diarrhea what well something anti-virus formula has an air yeah yeah
he's gonna get crushed what would you open the door without like a weapon yeah
I was in the middle of pressing the squish button do what good what do you
want we're gonna help you with oh yeah they told me never to do one thing I
forget what it was I think it was don't ever open this fucking door when people
are in it that wasn't even cartoon logic that was like they had a whole scene and
like they had like that the scene they threw the whole scene away and they had
to get an extra to be that guy like there was like a full ten minutes of
dialogue there left right left that was a reshoot left right they had a whole
sequence with a guard oh shit they went left oh god oh here we go oh no don't
push her into the way sound effect if you type in punch sound effect on YouTube
right now that's the first that's exactly the first one I have not had a
decision to make they're just doing it on their own the AI is just picking
direction left right oh god left right right that'll do holy shit she's running
way faster than me and she's in heels that's crazy left right oh my god I've
no idea let's go left right was the same guy this guy again we're gonna okay
we're gonna see this guy again like that's the wrong way I think if you make
the wrong decision you go in the circle you see that guy every time we're gonna
see him again right left right right that'll do we're about to loop again is
that guy gonna get up again can I just shoot that guy left right not again all
right there's no way that guy comes back another time it's not possible you
understand it's not possible that guy's back he flew off of a balcony like 15
no way look I need to know right I have no that guy's still alive somebody's
watching these cameras just going oh he doesn't they don't know he's back again
no more running why is that you see single shots there's two there now okay
oh no we just we got an we got the end card shit no oh damn it all right well
we'll get it we'll get it this time oh auto bolt action Uzi hmm okay well this
is this game is insane I we have to get at least some kind of other ending and
having far too much fun to stop playing this let's go again
let's try a new route let's go wait unlockables find every way to end the
game at Jack's funeral reach all the endings where Jack survives act on the
flatline like a pancake by 18 wheels of steel oh these are all the choices all
right let's go oh we can start from here sadistic bastard what wait what what
happened where's Laura this didn't happen
shoot me and you'll never see this didn't kill him later you still have the
gun shoot him in the face you have the gun still you still have
the gun all right I should just try start the whole thing over see if we can
get to the end from here well what I didn't do that before I didn't punch the
guy and grab the gun last time all right what do you think ones in the chat to
just go from that checkpoint and try it to keep going or two in the chat if you
want to start the game over and go different route that looks pretty that
looks pretty unanimously one all right let's go sadistic bastard okay so this
time I'm not gonna shoot grab the gun apparently where's Laura
shoot me and you'll never see okay don't shoot kill him later kill him later
later they still put him with a good dog so what I don't I just don't kill
care about having the weapon bar is a fight or flight meter yeah the more it's
on the right side it's aggression the more it's on the left running right we
have to do this again I need to play through this game one more time at least
it's too ridiculous not see everything else
try the hairpin
me and every other girl you bump into you overestimate how many past they shot
apparently a lot of footage all right let's try hairpin I'm sorry it's so loud
but it kind of has to be otherwise because there's no subtitles otherwise
you won't be able to hear anything I hope we get smush the guard
we're what are you what are you doing what are you doing what why in the name
of God no no no no no no no no oh that guy's fucking reaction oh I fucking oh
that guy just did like the butthead from Beavis and button okay no no no no
no no no no no no no I actually not gonna show this come on all right we're
good oh my god they just let us open the door okay don't screw this up okay I'm
gonna go right first I went left first last time left right all right now we're
gonna try I'm gonna go left all right wait they just went left boy here it
here he is let me out of here okay so now it's left left right that'll do okay
I think we made it okay now where right I don't wait where do I how do I go where
do I go where do I go where do I go help me left right which way which way which
way which way which way which way left left right no it's back at this guy
again we talking about no I'm not to see this can't happen again fuck just stay
right right right right only right only right right right left and then left
again it's left and then right left and right stay right left and then left left
right left left left and right left and right left and right not left
no it's left left right left then right chat chat stop what are you gonna get me
killed I don't I've no idea what's going on I think it's right left left left is
right no left right right left what do I do right oh god damn it stop doing this
to me what do I do right not again what's the first one
oh no just do left left right right right twice all right I'm gonna try
right right all right right twice come on right right right left right okay
right right what I do it I got it through the vent they filmed this in a
high school classroom sneak in break in sneak oh wait I'm breaking it with the
axe you better believe it we're gonna here's Johnny these motherfuckers
figure this out you made an error oh I told you you did that Jerry you move two
decimals hurry up hurry up kill him first hey Paul
well actually this is where you're gonna get off what I'm gonna take Kruger down
at the reservoir and there's no place for you safe place I'll see what I want
to be with you Jack yeah let's take it let's take a full 10 to 15 seconds to
kiss don't worry about the automatic assault weapons that are right yes there's
a long shot do it forget it do it what forget it do it forget it forget it we
just go back to the strip club who is that who is that I don't know who's we
on this team all right why is this guy dressed like Dick Tracy it's among us
it's yellow from among us whose team of these this is gonna be a bit oh it's me
I told you to stay someplace safe yes don't minus to me minus to the people in
Chad had said that I was just reacting to it don't touch those are like
electrified he's definitely you think snake oh wait a minute goodbye Hoover
goodbye Kruger double cross the deputy yeah they were working together the
whole time destroy the mobile app for the lab or is there another option or is
this it guys really desperate to get the old butterfinger recipe back wasn't
poison after all it's just not the same in the middle trying to recreate it
don't have much time minus two forced joke yeah yeah I'll take the I'll take
the I'll take the yellow that one can I get a decision it's gonna be a really
bad one to have to redo it's been people walking around setting up the like five
straight minutes Kruger Hoover drum Kruger Hoover drums
shoot the red barrel nice job son who the fuck was that why am I looking behind
me they didn't hurt you today Laura they get looks like she's got herself too
bad oh that definitely probably sounded way better in the mirror two days ago
looking for this I don't know I've been infected we selling your body is gonna
mutate you're gonna be another one of dr. Kruger's mindless zombies a few
seconds you'll be my own personal can you say that again a plane drover ruined
your moment exothermic reaction is gonna multiply that virus all right three
minutes take it away didn't he say a few seconds that turned into a few
minutes is this the lose did I lose within three minutes Los Angeles will
be mine perhaps you might enjoy sharing easy you're gonna spell that shit so
what do I do Hoover Kruger Hoover Kruger what do I do Hoover Kruger I can't
shoot him from up here oh I hope the checkpoints really close I thought I
was gonna snipe him from all the way back there that would have been so
funny oh I was right at the checkpoint good very good yeah it's it's not I think
it's time for this guy to go back to the drawing board mojo Jojo tried this like
three times already I god damn it all right whatever it's all right it's all
right we have to watch this whole thing again all right this time I'm gonna who
should I shoot I point the gun at Hoover who should I point the gun at then not
the barrels right I thought the barrels is a great idea I'm gonna shoot the
barrel which is gonna destroy everything and everyone's gonna get the virus or
whatever all over them right that was like okay but then the guy just came
behind me the extra came behind me and hit me in the head so I was supposed to
know that was gonna happen it's gonna take it's gonna take oh god it's gonna
take forever yeah I'm gonna aim at Hoover that's a good idea
give it I don't I can't you can't get cutscenes I don't get down there I told
you to stay someplace safe you need to watch this every time I think we'll get
it this time skip no way not in a hundred million years let's go all right
we're gonna aim the gun at Hoover I feel like Hoover is gonna be like no no no
don't shoot me all right hold this is what's gonna happen don't shoot me this
guy's a snake right goodbye Hoover goodbye Krueger
very excited yeah I said the guy looks like Joe Biden no it looks like it looks
like somebody took young Joe Biden and put them in one of those agify apps to
make old Joe Biden that's what it looks like all right we got to aim at this guy
go after him I feel like we'll probably get another decision guns don't even
have barrels really bringing the crane well it gets the same message
don't screw this up I don't want to watch the first five minutes of every
RTS phase no I don't want to watch this don't have much time okay here we go
Hoover construction complete building building construction complete unit lost
unit lost Krueger Hoover drums what the fuck who did that and they don't see me
do that all right Krueger I don't care about him yeah I fucking knew it god
damn it
we have to watch the whole thing get our whatever I okay okay why would you pick
the goon I know I'm I don't care about him he's nothing to me kill him it has
to be the main guy what can I even get to the main guy I damn it that's so
funny has to be a way to skip I really don't think there is it's space I don't
know I don't think it is yeah hey yeah this is very important to remember this
is 25 years old it's 25 years old how old are these actors now the craziest
part is the main character recorded voice lines with this remaster so how
old is the main character here probably in his I want to say probably the 40s
maybe early 40s probably so this this person the actor might actually be in
their late 60s into early 70s late 30s early 40s yeah that's another thing spam
every button no it doesn't do anything I'm telling you there is no skip he's
George Bush from that's my bush it was on Comedy Central he's almost as old as
you are now no I forgot about that's my bush yeah that was correct me if I'm
wrong but that was Trey Parker and Matt Stone made that show or at least Trey
Parker did South Park guys I think it was only live for like four episodes or
like six episodes goodbye Hoover goodbye Kruger here we go don't screw this up
Bill Murray is on the crane pay attention what Bill Murray pay attention
how preparing the virus somebody said I missed Bill Murray both times well I'm
not gonna miss him this time you said he's on the crane Bill Murray on the
crane so ready of over anticipating this I feel like it's not gonna be as funny
as you said it was okay where is he brain is the big moment that's not even
that's not even close it's his face is so pixelated in what this that's just a
guy that's just a guy with like Bill Murray hair actually hold on a minute
don't have much time that was actually pretty close that you okay here we go I
gotta be ready Kruger what if none of them are correct
no Murray's not in the credits drums then Hoover oh god drums then Hoover
Kruger is bulletproof Oh Kruger Hoover drums drums then Hoover wait what the
fuck oh okay right no no no no no now we do Hoover here okay it's true we it's
been proven that he's bulletproof remember I tried to shoot him earlier
but now it's go for him I forgot that was a second choice here you did Hoover
last time no I tried to shoot him from down here I grabbed his gun I tried to
aim up at him and he shot her in the head
with dr. Krueger's newest brain looking for this what you want
it's still a little bit in there I just picked that thing up and just start
going I would start inhaling right because you'd get like the vapors and
might help a little every cell in your body is gonna mutate gonna be another
one of dr. Krueger's mindless on me yeah or like just touch a little bit of the
wetness and get it like in your mucus membranes just put your fingers in
your nose all the way back and try to get it in there it get absorbed in your
mucus membranes I really don't want to have to view this whole thing again so
this better be right did Hoover last time no I didn't I tried to shoot up at
Kruger I was like I'm gonna shoot him from here and I aimed down sights and he
killed Laura it's Hoover I'm gonna pick Hoover
within three minutes Los Angeles will be my perhaps you might enjoy sharing okay
here we go there's only two options right oh no I'm the stormtrooper oh no
oh my god I just look them up wait that guy I wasn't even aiming in that
direction that shit ricocheted off the wall and hit that guy I wasn't even
aiming over there what a god game nice shot Laura wait wait till I leave oh we
definitely gonna dump the guy yeah I'm gonna dump the guy in the ask is gonna
turn to a skeleton holy shit this guy did not hit me don't let it dump come on get
up there no don't let us don't please what rabbit rabbit fight rabbit rabbit
fight how am I gonna grab it from here wait this is stupid this is stupid I
can't reach that wait what they kept like zooming into the thing they kept
zooming into it no this is horseshit you know why this is bullshit just think of
the other times where I've picked a decision where it was like oh go get
that guy and I just appeared tackling him that's happened like three times
guys there's been choices where he just had a gun in his pocket and he didn't
have it there before I think the game was showing me its hand
remember when I picked go for go to Hoover he fucking just was in mid tackle
after hiding behind a bush whatever the fuck was over there the game gaslit you
oh god damn it please tell me that no okay so to me fight would have been
stupid but oh grab the the plot device of the entire game but how am I gonna
fight a guy when I'm hanging from a ledge like that you don't plot device
plot device plot device plot device I've clicked the plot device put something
up distract us I have I have a really big apology here for you if I click out
of the window the game pauses and cannot play we have to work again this is gonna
be a bitch I can turn it down all right I turned it down we're gonna talk about
for like two minutes what should we talk about you need well you get to see bill
yeah you'll see bill Murray again that's cool that's pretty cool stuff what I
have a breakfast I had a coffee and then I had nothing else I don't eat it's hard
to eat breakfast when I get up in the morning and going all the way into the
early afternoon I can't eat anything thought of eating breakfast a lot of
times make me kind of like nauseous I'm just not ready for food the first three
four hours when I get up but coffee that I can do I usually eat lunch lunch some
kind of snack some kind of small mid late kind of afternoon meal and then I do
dinner breakfast is overrated anyways I mean breakfast is incredibly important
your body needs fuel to burn so you can function it's important to do something
you have any hue I actually don't have any heels left smoothies are good yeah
that's that's a good idea you're being played by big breakfast okay let me get
this remember this drum Hoover fight drum Hoover fight drum Hoover fight
drum Hoover fight the essential breakfast breakfast thing is legit just
Kellogg's propaganda well I mean if you if you eat just like sugary cereals all
right here we go a lot of cereals are just cotton candy with vitamin powder
sprinkled all over it pretty much the same thing Kruger Hoover drums drums I
feel like that would be a great Skrillex intro I mean don't shoot the drum call
them off or you're dead mods aren't allowed to minus 2 me in this channel by
the way game audit see plot device plot device plot device plot device plot
device here it is why would I not click the plot device they've just been
whatever
royalty-free movie night well this is my own personal this is pretty much not
royalty-free but it's a game from Hoover fight all right let's go for it
somebody said watch Bill Murray does this is the Bill Murray character here
get uh does he make it I hope so take it away hey within three minutes Los
Angeles will be mine perhaps you might enjoy sharing
he said scuff scuff Biden versus scuff bush all right here we go now there's no
other choices to make I wish you'd just shoot him now I just realized they just
did the Roger Rabbit routine same exact scenario that of the acid the juice dip
weasel falls over laughing hits the thing and it moves came out first
Roger Rabbit was what 80 no just definitely Roger Rabbit came out first
25 years old all right here we go don't screw this up dip was Monka s Christopher
Lloyd as the judge is one of one of my favorite acting my favorite characters
ever he's just so good in that role it was unbelievably good if you have not
seen who frame Roger Rabbit it's required reading for this stream okay
fight this is it this is where we actually get this correct fight there's
not a third option right let me just double check rabbit rabbit fight fight
that's it oh okay this is the last long enough there just oh god please what do I
do there's the green screen movie night thing where I'm like strangling you do
I take that I think I have to take that what do I do what do I do get it fight
no I don't know what should I do fight what should I do what I didn't make a
decision oh shit no I'm fine I'm okay I try press space I press space I swear
to god I press space I swear to god I pressed it I press space on get it you
hurt you could hear it you could actually hear it oh my god damn it
it's gonna be a checkpoint is my mouse on the screen or is my mouse off the
screen does that matter hold on professional game I'm not a professional
gamer by the way we talking about I don't know I barely can tie my shoes
correctly when did I tell you I was a pro gamer I please give me a checkpoint
please oh fuck all right keep okay it's rum Hoover fight fight or fight yet
should be fight fight this is your job so you have to be a professional how do
you be a professional at a full motion video game fight fight you have to get
it or you're gonna get yeah yeah that's right so there's a huge bait here the
first bait is this is gonna be a bitch I'm gonna turn this down because I can't
hear it all right so it's definitely get the second time around it's get for sure
it has to be cuz I'm gonna turn into the zombie person yeah I think so rum
Hoover fight yet rum Hoover fight get can I get that written down please rum
Hoover fight Bill Murray drum Hoover fight yet it's probably something else
after that too we're gonna do this shit a whole nother time if you want to go to
a furry convention with a fursuit how are you not a furry I just what just
cuz I'm gonna wear one drum Hoover drum Hoover fight yet right there's another
option to fight I'm gonna do that I think so yeah if the after getting and
taking it if fights an option then I'm gonna have my my wits are gonna be back
about me so I'll be able to fight and you do the annoying annoying orange sound
I'm ignoring whom what am I ignoring are you a furry answer the question no I'm
not there you go is that is that's matter of fact for you isn't it should
be matter of fact for you somebody said this is just golden eye except
everything sucks don't you love it though I'm so glad that we get to like see this
and experience this time harvester meets James Bond harvester was fucked I would
not play that game a second time all right let's start the process here get
the audio back where it should be all right let's go I didn't realize the run
he screams run at the people drum Kruger Hoover drum from over fight yet so it's
Hoover and if there's something afterwards again I have to remind myself
a thousand times it's fight if there's another choice is therefore I would have
taken the antidote marijuana is a memory loss drug I'm not high that would have
been a huge mistake for this dream these serious okay don't get it wrong
every cell in your body is gonna mutate you're gonna be another one of dr. Kruger's
minor zombies what if get it is wrong then that's not my fault because you all
we all have come to a consensus here that I need to get it when it's on the
ground because otherwise I turn into the zombie
exothermic reaction is gonna multiply that virus me a pole we get a short pole
as to what I should do on the second after I fight the first time and a pull
I need cuz I if I'm gonna be wrong I need a bunch of people to be wrong too
so we can all be wrong together so I don't feel as bad fight or get on the
second attempt and one that we just died at we go within three minutes Los
Angeles will be mine perhaps you might enjoy sharing do a prediction it's good
prediction to take too long okay Hoover Hoover Kruger all right that was a
perfect opportunity for a will Wilhelm Wilhelm okay fight what do we got 80%
yet so if I'm wrong you're wrong too this guy shoots so many bullets like I
probably gonna throw in a rock and hit me easier than his shooting okay fight
right yeah I swear to God if it's not like rabbit fight there we go I am so
nervous right now I act like I'm like my heart's kind of pumping because I'm
scared that this is wrong we have to watch this again please get it fight get
it fight get it no yes all right now I fight I don't know what to do now I'm
gonna fight if it's fight what do you grab on to wait it's gonna go in the
water baby baby baby scream I did it did you hear that like
you may well have saved us all why does why does Laura not get a medal
sometimes it's all worth what was what was Laura not get a medal for that he
sponsored her like kill count at the end there was like fucking 30 people I can't
do that without her that's cool we need an alternate ending all right I am
willing to play through one and not play through I just want to there's some
stuff early that I really want to see there's a lot of other shit that we
need to know where it goes play I always start from the beginning oh shit I can do
this checkpoint locked all this somebody locked checkpoints alright I'm not doing
party party torturing 14,000 people this is some of the most fun I've had in a
while what are you talking about I love this I'm loving this all right let's go
to I'm not doing party party is gonna lose all previous progress does that
mean I can I not start at the other ones I'm gonna do party but I'm gonna
censor the screen to make sure it's okay my home away from home crystals
looking good it actually censored this re-release the original game did have
nudity interesting okay voiceover lines were not in the original no no way the
actor actually came back to rerecord them I'm surprised they didn't port this
to something else here's trouble this whole thing was done even if it was not
on the Jaguar why would they not they were right so now you can piss off Sega
Saturn or something take a CD it's Colonel BFD the old man has a problem
not interested it involves Laura and a dangerous mind control virus shit we
think she's been kidnapped can't say more it's had an adults-only rating
walls have ears if you're interested meet me somewhere a little more private
I'm you nudity in any piece of media is gonna have that and especially in a game
ESRB rock in a hard place like real people on camera like naked I think that
would get bad news okay party oh it's just this thing again it's just going
okay we've already seen this we've already seen this nice dress lose it
we've already seen this she's not she's not drinking vegetable oil that's weird
like the bottle though all right I don't I'm really kind of playing with fire
here I'm not I can't I'm not I can't show this I can't show this like a
fourth time you know what I mean what's the matter I'm not I don't I can't show
this a fourth time what's wrong which TOS allows this yeah I mean yeah what
you're just watching it alone huh you can't I didn't okay I didn't mean to
press more but I'm curious I'll watch it okay okay the way you guys can see this
maybe you can
okay so we know what that does I want to go back to the car chase like there was
something else to see there it was a whole other place to go is home to the
area I can't stop seeing that is like sunflower oil lose it feel like drinking
vegetable oil is something that's gonna that's in some like weird like
dystopian game setting or something where that's what people are drinking
sort of water can't see this you're not old enough that's basically oatmeal what's
what do you mean oatmeal yeah what I'm old enough 37 18 plus yeah but I don't
know I gotta be careful what was the purpose for you 72 hour bit well this is
if I get banned for 72 hours I scream once a week okay that would just be like
I don't want to get banned I don't want to get like suspended oh the reason why
we give a given you a warning or suspension you showed the girl on top of
you potential sexy like eight times once twice three times okay that's pushing it
but you showed it like 12 times drama get out take it get out take it all right
so I take this so now there's a whole there's another area I did not see
shortcut Laura's okay shortcut Laura's already shortcut you short Laura's
there's a whole other building limo cut through limo okay cut through cut
through fucking goddamn truck again hell of a day and it's only two why is he
louder than you yeah his voiceover is louder than me on my microphone
he's the screamer not me all right I'm gonna try this a ledge run run then I'm
gonna do the jump I'm gonna see what happens rock jump there's a huge mattress
oh he's the henchman fake them take them fake them fake them take them
take them we don't even know who those people are I want the backstory on those
two I want to know what was that for there has to be an explanation who
these people are I guess that's my first name fake them take them fake them take
them all right fake no he's uh hey Jack that's him yeah that's definitely him
what oh my god I just got that guy killed that guy's just on a job what's
wrong with me downtown shortcut okay downtown downtown limo cut through no
no limo again cut all right we might be at the end they're still on me
here it is all right just get in the car right go to limo then KVK I think you
have a choice here where am I a shower door climb a door going to climb
somebody's here take a shower at the house who is this guy what no no no no
no no that same guy in the hallway all right well we'll do the next one we've
already seen all this going forward is there anything else I could have picked
here good to see you again I'm sure there's a few little things we didn't
get to see but that was an absolutely hysterical experience my head hurts
the next one that we're gonna play is let me see what it's called the next one
is called a death death stalker yeah the specter files death stalker is the next
one now what is gonna kill it here I'm gonna go pee right back I come back
we'll be in another one see you in a minute turn that off because that's
gonna be really annoying you're back hello get this open I really don't know
very much about this one the specter files death stalker are you suited no
nope play Elden ring no I don't want to play the first 10 to 20 hours of a game
and then just not be able to play it like four months I would get so hyped up
and so into it get a third of the way through the game and then just now what
February I don't want to do that that's all I would be thinking about for the
next three or four months this game has death in it I mean it's called death
stalker I would assume so it's kind of in the title all right here we go let me
just make sure it's not too loud which it might be I don't think so this one
looks a little more let's find out play okay a B and C I have to use the law you
can't see anything hold on oh can you not see it interactive film in oh my
god that's terrifying oh oh my god that was horrifying actually kind of play
this I'm kind of scared all right make a choice use the left mouse button to
select your choice pressing the spacebar skips videos okay in case we get stuck
somewhere and escape quits the game so don't press escape all right play play
some music video I play the music video I just quit the game I don't like this
there's scary I was scary I don't like this it's just very unsettling I don't
like it all right let's play the game Howard Howard Howard I I didn't like
that I don't want possibly there's probably spoilers in there change the
twitch category I'm gonna change this to this even on the categories on twitch
death stalker it is inspector files death stalker there we go all right I'm
ready ready to play it's time with to help things gonna be really loud I'm
really sorry if it is it is very loud okay so we do have to make choices you
learn two things in detective school first I like to keep your files neat and
orderly and second a case that involves a missing blonde will inevitably
drive you to drink something about this case intrigued me besides I was between
clients at the time and certain bill collectors paper said she was last
seen in durr hatchet hollow walking her chihuahua through a nearby graveyard not
much to go on but I had to start somewhere okay I'd like to go out the
window do you hide your wallet shout I'm not here or share I'm not here you
wanted money all right inspector mr. Vasileini wants to give you five good
reasons why you should pay him the money tonight I didn't give you a chance to
pay the money right dead losing consciousness is not healthy and should
be avoided touched by my secretary's concern poor kid was crazy about me do
you say sure thing start earning the reward money just drive to the Institute
or your hatchet Institute was founded by a Nobel prize-winning scientist who
disappeared in the late 50s leaving the place deserted for nearly 30 years
and turned the knob okay doors locked knock on the door look under the mat it's
gonna be a key under the mat that has to be it's Scooby-Doo music naturally there
was a key to fit the front door under the mat the stench was awful it was
like entering a tomb you were rotting stairs to my right in a room to my left
and I felt a cold chill on the back of my neck okay do you carefully climb the
stairs look over the shoulder look over the shoulders gonna be a monster right
okay uh race up the stairs ignore her make polite conversation run just race
up the stairs I did a fond farewell to the fanged femme fatale and ran up the
stairs I paused to see if I was being oh I hate this I was I hate this okay run
into the darkness give her a breath mint um what does that mean I'm not sure what
happened next vaguely remember staring into someone's eyes eyes appear directly
into your soul and you black out I don't know how long I was out but someone or
something I dragged me to a cellar below der hatchet manner okay I lost a health
as I struggled to clear my head I clicked on my flashlight and looked
around any fool could see that the place had more than its share of ding
bats and I was no exception this music keeps playing okay explore go looking
for trouble find the friend who dragged you here I'm gonna explore the cellar it
was there in the cellar that I discovered the little man with the evil
grin I couldn't hear him over the music what is he asking me Lance passed him
say don't turn around grab his coal shovel grab the shovel before I could
move he brought his shovel into my face I think I died I'm dead I woke up with
the feeling that I was at the end of my rope wait am I dead I was I was fit to
be tied the situation was bad and my life hung in the balance what the fuck
okay how do I this was no time for reflection this is the guy that knocked
me out mr. specter what do I do to get out of this take a deep breath stand on
your toes do something clever there's not enough time for me to think about
this I'm gonna do something clever I was trying to think of a diversion when I
started to slip away as the rope bit into my neck what do I do wait I didn't do
anything when I got up I saw that the minecraft made quite an impression on
laughing boy okay make good use of the rope take the candle and go uh take
I grabbed a candle and headed out a sudden breeze blew out my candle and I
could barely make out my surroundings in the darkness I should have taken the
rope or something use your last match go look for another candle uh match don't
have a flashlight since I didn't get the match lit I never even saw what hit me
it's him it's the same guy bad misuse of your resources you blackout am I gonna
be up on the gallows again I came to in an attic I'm supposed to be dead
someone or something was sitting across the attic from me at long last the
detective decides to pay a visit to his host have you enjoyed our hospitality so
far what the hell it was difficult not to listen his voice had a strong hypnotic
effect we never do I feel like we've met before you don't know me but I know you
is he drinking booze each time you laughs in consciousness I get to know
you a little better come sit drink with me it's something I picked out close to
your heart that was my blood he was sucking on did I drink it I think I'm
gonna drink it yeah check your pockets lunge forward and attack I mean it's
clearly a guy with a mask on right I tried to attack but thought come show
count your Chakonsky stared into my eyes and I knew I had failed I blacked out
you now haunt the halls of your hatchet Institute and the case remains unsolved
okay in hindsight you probably could have made better choices during your
investigation yeah we got gum shoot got the we got gum overconfidence was your
undoing never count your chickens before they're hatched I can't imagine the
spooky scary ghost person calling me gum shoe holy shit okay there's a lot of
stuff all right let's go you must solve the mystery to qualify these are the top
gum shoes shit all right let's go this time I'm not gonna screw up in other
words don't lunch at everything it's a game for children this is not a game
for children in detective school first always keep your files neat and orderly
I lost health in the beginning a case that involves a missing blonde will
inevitably drive you to drink something about this case intrigued me besides I
was between clients at the time and certain oh I can skip right okay this
guy's looking for money uh let's meet him let's just meet this person he
wanted money all right give us just for a good cause all proceeds go to the
orphan wait this is different person of course tax deductible I mean to pry but
your secretary mentioned that you might be driving out to dear hatchet hollow
that was like five dollars it's a very evil place I want you to have this oh
wait we're gonna get a save your life it's a pile of holy water what where was
this the beginning twelve dollars tax deductible okay send in the next okay go
find the missing girl I have holy water the dear hatchet Institute was founded
by a Nobel prize-winning scientist who disappeared in the late 50s leaving the
place deserted for nearly 30 years it's packaged up I walked up the creeping
front steps and turned the knob all right the ladies here I have a choice to
turn around or get the key from under the mat and then what do I do about the
lady try just naturally talk to the lady there was a key to fit the front door
under the mat the stench was awful it was like entering a tomb I just keep
running from the layers to my right in a room to my left and I felt a cold chill
on the back of my neck carefully climb should I carefully climb the stairs yeah
if I sneak I probably can as I ascended the rotting stairs I began to feel as if
I were being followed from the top of the stairs I could see a woman below okay
I don't have a weapon holy water use the holy water her skin erupted as the water
splashed on the stench was awful the second floor looked dark and uninviting
okay that was a waste I don't know if I could have got away check on her
condition run into the nearest room right I don't you have so much there's
not enough time my fear faded as I fled I felt fine till I fell so I flipped over
and found I'd been followed by a fanged femme fatale with a fried finger it's
her use the vial of holy water I don't do I have it kick her teeth out oh I
don't still have any left it wasn't till I cut my hand on the broken glass that I
realized that the bottle of holy water wasn't shatter proof I just well here we
go again I don't know how long I was out but someone or something had dragged me
to a cellar below der Hatchet manor is this guy as I struggled to clear my head
I clicked on my flashlight and looked around which disappeared after the
fool could see that the place had more than its share of dingbats and I was no
exception find who dragged you in here explode go looking for trouble find who
dragged you here I don't I think these are all the same thing it was there in
the cellar that I discovered the little man with the evil grin what's the
correct play here
okay stay for dinner all right so now what are the choices don't lunge at him
grab his shovel glance past him say don't turn around and you bait him he
fell for it so I took the opportunity to bash him in the chops I never hit a man
when he's down but I knew I should have made an exception when I felt his
fingers on my throat you can't be serious
I have to flip that second option is not gonna do anything
I flipped him into his coal bin and ran into the darkness
shovel and be like you know I don't hit a person when they're down even if
they're a degenerate murdering zombie person find an elevator find the
elevator I found myself ascending a steep circular stairway when a green
ghoul in a rented tuxedo made a dramatic entrance these people just went to the
Halloween store and bought everything on the rack and then just decided to shoot
stuff with it and they made choices around it they were just having a they
just having like fun for like a weekend let's make some small talk see if it
works I approached the zombie reluctant took his hat off and asked him who his
Taylor was his response was to push me backwards into a rickety old freight
elevator he took his hat off like oh it's me hello oh floor surprise me um
surprise me we arrived on the first floor and I got off I could hear faint
piano music coming from somewhere piano music this is it could be anything I
have no idea um enter the room on the left the room was crawling with vermin
but otherwise empty but they're so cute they just have that is vibing leave him
alone follow the rats yeah they know what they're doing the next room I came
to had nothing in it there was an old freezer on one side and a wall full of
potions on the other Frank one of the random potions just as I started to
examine them I heard a scream okay find a place to hide open the freezer I'm
putting the fewers in the freezer open the freezer be only to find another
prisoner of this horrible place
we have to keep this guy alive
you wouldn't have a car by any chance you wouldn't be going to your Fresno
area Fresno's really not that far he was unfortunately an obnoxious jerk who
didn't have anything intelligent off money or a cigarette you thought what a
jerk it's remarkably still alive what are you talking about this guy could
probably help see what he knows about the house what do you know about the
house you've been here probably for a while oh shit the fumes
wouldn't let me go this is a monster this might be a monster in the house
maybe this is not a person I give him five bucks I gave him five dollars and
okay leave this loony bin behind search remaining rooms search remaining rooms
that actually might have been a monster to the next room I heard the scream
again take the source of the scream we have to know we have to know returning
to the hall I glanced up to where the sound came from Jesus see run away right
but I don't know see what he does next run see what he does
so I backed up and gave him plenty of room fell on his head I don't but what
if what if he's not hostile I don't we might not be hostile the loony was
wearing a straight jacket how yeah but you know you never know
I was at the end of my rope when I realized that I was I was fit to be
all right so we got this right last time we have to like tie this guy up or
something this was no time for reflection if I didn't stream I would
probably be this guy like if I was in a streamer or did YouTube or something I
would have probably been that guy at some point something clever I was trying
to think of a diversion when I lost this was the right thing last thing hits him
okay you need to get the rope I got up by monster or the actor the actor on
the actor not the guy what he's doing the actor oh my god all right make good
use of the rope I told laughing boy he was bound to be out of circulation for a
while but he didn't appreciate the gag okay head for the hallway explore that
look for a sign and head for the hallway I guess artifacts you are that's what
the piano music's coming from artifacts or music worm we already the
elevator I don't want to go back in there artifacts artifacts the next
room contained an old writing desk under the derhatchet family crest on the desk
were many items of interest hey old coins wine cryptic runes decide for the
runes just as I picked up the papers the candle lit itself and a funky phantom
friar floated into the room
this guy looks friendly okay burn his papers enjoy wine and candle light he's
snapping his fingers the candle and a glass of the house vino and the phantom
friar gave up the ghost what I didn't want to kill him he just wanted to hang
out oops well I guess I won half of these monsters come up to me very non
hostile I'll get the golden split I'll get the gold music room I want to go to
the music room quickly leave the cellar search the cell where's the music room
just leave the cellar oh this guy again music room whistle a happy tune first
floor say second floor second floor we're already on the first floor the
second floor look dark and uninviting pick a room at random find the kitchen
the room I next entered was obviously a library of some sort great job finding
the kitchen there is there was a door to my left another dead ahead but most of
the action was taking place in the kitchen on my right someone was
practicing a bizarre form of culinary preparation right let's go right let's
see I couldn't put my finger on it but there was something odd about the woman
in the kitchen I think maybe it was her three-day beard okay grab some food and
go can I look in the fridge oh it's Edna fine a find the edibles find the
edibles everybody on this house is on him might as well join a clove of
garlic and a couple of potatoes definitely take the garlic and shove
that down the boss's throat of garlic okay I'm gonna leave sneak away quietly I
don't want to do anything else out of the kitchen and left her to her work a
faint breeze carried a musty odor to my sensitive nostrils okay well over to the
closed door okay we're gonna peek through that I'm not going in there just
yet this room seemed to be a laboratory there was something odd about it and
then I realized what it was the room suddenly I realized that someone was
coming up behind me the vampire see the teeth jump in the tub and quickly jump
in the tub thinking quickly I stepped into the shower and pulled the curtain
closed a hairy paw reached in and turned on the water I peered around the
corner and saw a she wolf busily primping herself for a night on the town
this is such a crack game it really is what do I do ah I don't know I'm not
clicking any of these I don't know what to do my dad I came to an attic
someone or something was sitting across the attic from me okay I have the
garlic I mean I'll be honest difficult not to listen his voice had a strong
hypnotic effect there's only one person that's really tried to hurt me everyone
else is kind of been just a weirdo hanging out like vibing like no one's
really attacked me or anything it kind of just bump into me
but I know you each time you laughs in consciousness I get to know you a little
better come sit drink with me it's something I picked out close to your
heart but that was garlic my blood he was sucking on yeah we're gonna put the
garlic in his drink like your pockets find something of value check you um if
you check pockets right is that I got garlic I checked my pockets my pockets
were empty what I took the liberty of removing everything from your pocket I
learned your Jedi ways by count this was count your Chakun ski sister grievous I
had failed when I looked into his eyes I was powerless to resist him
well we failed again I got 6,000 points you got to get the garlic up there and
get to him without being knocked out shit are you round up to 6,000 here all
right do we try okay I'm gonna speed run one let's just speed run did it crash
yeah crash again oh we're good okay there we go all right speed run time I'm
just gonna go in places I didn't go see what happens okay meet the gentleman
should be the priest you wanted money all right you're best for acceptable you
said that thing deductible all right send in the next client I'm cute have
another drink I decided to take a few moments to organize my thoughts so I
poured myself another drink and began to read it leaves to pay today or else easy
cat why am I doing this found these clippings in the newspaper not sure if
they mean anything but I thought you should see them what is this all about
dental clinic I passed out sometime around midnight
you passed out as I slowly regain consciousness I was touched by my
secretary's concern poor kid was crazy about me I didn't lose HP go find just
gathering clues find your car keys okay let's go doors lock try something else
naturally there was a key to the back of my neck I was there the whole time
weirdly enough it was taped there I am not sure why look over your shoulder all
right explore the room the room was crawling with vermin but otherwise and
I'm getting different things explains if I hadn't been so busy talking I might
have noticed that she wasn't really listening god damn it I shouldn't have
skipped it stop thought I took a different route that's right fuck it
that's right I took a different route damn it I don't have the holy water
yeah yeah shit okay Oh looking for trouble we didn't do that one I went
looking for trouble and found it in the form of a phantom friar with this guy
didn't appreciate interruption I no sense of humor I guess well this was
fast never go looking for trouble oh yeah I am with my lightsabers I will take
you look up with the feeling that I was at the end of my rope when I realized
that I was I was fit to be tied I'm what did I say I'm here with your
lightsabers I didn't have a chance I didn't even have a chance okay we know
what to do with this this is a this whole thing's a wash let's see if I
was trying to think of a diversion when I think they all do the same thing I
got up I saw that the pipe it made quite an impression okay use the rope
during this game sucks okay go all right look let's try look for a sign I'm still
very interested I want to get to the music room because the elevators up I
mean the music room is up and up the stairs on the steps above me a green
ghoul gestured gracefully this is the elevator guy okay makes polite talk he
puts me in the elevator I don't want to go anywhere though I don't want to go
back down I'm surprised but I don't what if I don't say anything will he keep me
on this floor back in the elevator right down the hallway the next room I came to
had nothing in it all right here's the hippie guy's are on one side okay we're
gonna try to get more info from the hippie okay do you know any escape
options what if I don't give him five bucks what about do you know anything
about potions I read the labels extra strength potion instant steak pill
anti-grav tablets instant steak instant strength steak or strength steak or
steak I wasn't hungry now but an instant steak might come in handy later yeah we
have to put this into his wine right because it goes in you and it's a steak
and you what about the stench why does it smell because then it'll the steak
will blow up in his body right it sticks to your ribs yeah that means that it's
gonna turn into a steak inside your body you could bathe more off all right I
gotta leave we're gonna we're gonna both die from this like poison I gave him
five dollars and left if the vampire eats this somehow whether we have I
don't know how we get it to happen to eat it all right we got to leave we're
gonna leave leave leave he takes it yeah but that he takes your stuff if you die
which I haven't died yet if I get knocked out again yeah I ran into the
next room I heard the scream again this guy we just do avoid this do not go
investigate this at all just keep no keep moving forward this guy knocks you
up I ran through the door and found myself near the elevator okay up I
pushed the button and waited there was a green door to my left and a stairway to
my right wait for the elevator but what if he comes out let's find the green
door I walked over and opened the green door well the last thing I remember is
staring at the hole in his chest where a steak should have been oh come on come
on I came to in an attic someone or something was sitting across the attic
from me I wonder this way I can it was difficult not to listen his voice had a
strong hypnotic effect maybe maybe it's too small maybe he didn't take it okay
yeah I don't know you I love this cause I know you each time you lapse in
consciousness I get to know you a little better come sit drink with me it's
something I picked out close to your heart that was my blood he was sucking
on okay uh should I offer him a bribe that's the only thing I haven't
my pockets were empty I love this guy this was count your Chakonsky I knew I
had failed when I looked into his eyes I was powerless to resist him
all right I'm gonna try this one more time come on at least well I opened the
green door and it was okay like I choose your adventure game there's a reason
why you hold your finger on the previous page because open door on right guy
kills you you know that's okay well fuck that I'm not doing that one and you keep
your hand your finger on the tab you go back and you choose the right one you're
cheating at books that's not cheating it's not cheating there's still so much
stuff okay where do I what am I doing wrong there's a lot more in this game
that I really thought there was all right one more try holy water and then
we're gonna leave he wanted money all right your best but it was for a good
cause okay it's nice to see you the okay don't send in the next client it's the
you so I'm gone under the mat of course naturally there was a key to the back of
my neck okay now what over my shoulder is the girl explore the room everything
is the girl I think the candlelit room should be okay the room was crawling
with vermin but otherwise empty she follows oh god damn it she follows you
both times he follows you in both scenarios I don't think you can avoid
this wait explain I can't run I could sense that she was attracted to me what
run tell her she has nice eyes what I don't understand what do you if I hadn't
been so busy talking I might have noticed what why isn't a run really
listening I can't believe there's not oh god damn it I could have avoided that
alright there's one here's how you avoid that one you just have to go up the
stairs and run as if you go to the candle I was out but someone or
something had dragged me to a cellar below der Hatchet holy water works but
she follows you up the stairs as I struggled to clear my head I clicked on
my flashlight and looked around all right these are these all don't go look
for trouble these all lead to the same place anyways it was there in the cellar
so what's the correct thing with this guy don't turn around glance past him
there's just glance past him but what if we don't attack he fell for it so I took
the opportunity to bash him in the chops he fell for me looking the other way I
never hit a man when he's down but I knew I should have made an exception when
I felt his fingers on my throat can you avoid this guy oh flip over backwards
right I flipped him into his colbin and ran into the darkness he Egypt ology
laundry look look for a stairway I don't think we did the stairway last time I
found myself ascending a steep here's the guy with the hat when a green ghoul
made a dramatic entrance I wonder if there's a wrong option with this guy
proceed small I don't think it really matters let's just do small talk I
approached the zombie I don't want to go I don't want to go down to the what if I
say mind your own business that's the one option I did not do I could hear
faint piano music coming from somewhere all right where's the steak kitchen I
don't I don't remember where the kitchen is is it straight I'm getting so turned
around like I don't even know what any of these options really go the next room
I came to had nothing in it okay here we go there was an old freezer on one side
and a wall full of potions on the other but that we want the steak one we gotta
give this guy money what about those potion bottles I read the labels extra
strength potion instant steak pill anti-grav tablets gravity I feel like the
steak is the is the correct option steak I wasn't hungry now but an instant
steak might come in handy later stick to your ribs I gotta get up the stair
okay well should I take the anti-gravity one to anti-grav tablets I noticed
something strange from the moment I opened the jar get some strength stop
get the I take the instant strength potion and run taking the extra strength
I gotta get out of here like a good idea till I read the fine print oh god damn
we're dead we're dead ask take a deep breath no run run run how do I get out
run leave the fumes in the room no I'm trying to get out and consequently I oh
come on so I blacked out well how was I gonna know that like it was there was a
feeling that I was at the end of my rope the anti-gravity pills fly up I was fit
to be I did the situation none of this matters I was trying to think of a
diversion when I started to slip away as the rope bit into my neck okay let's
get them make good use of the rope I told laughing boys to be out of
circulation for a while but he didn't appreciate the gag okay so now from here
look for a sign oh I don't think we clicked this yet I'm pretty sure this is
one I have not done look for a sign I did I need like a piece of paper that
has like the blueprint of this house it's just like teleporting around it's
like how my brain cannot remember where I am oh let's go do this the next room
contained an old writing desk under the derhatchet family we'll get points for
getting rid of this on the desk were many items of interest decipher the
cryptic rune and then that makes him come over and then we put it in the
thing and we burn up the papers the candle lit itself and a funky phantom
friar okay enjoy wine and candlelight I extinguished the candle in a glass of
and the phantom friar gave up the ghost okay so from here was filled down I have
the coins I need to find my way up to the second floor on the elevator look
for a way out okay I'll get the golden split we did this last time which takes
us outside we can go to the elevator okay get in the elevator I want to go to
the second floor second floor well then from here where do I go from here
remember second floor look dark and uninviting remember where to go from
here to get to the guy the kitchen all right yeah the kitchen already beat the
last score the room I next entered was obviously a library of some sort there
was a door I don't remember what time but most of the action was taking place
in the kitchen on my right where someone was practicing a bizarre form of here we
go we're gonna go into the kitchen get the points and towards the right I
couldn't put my finger on it but there was something good in the kitchen holy
shit it actually was good I think maybe it was her three-day beard Wow okay look
in the fridge no way are you kidding me this game come out like how long ago 10
20 years ago inside the cupboard was a rose a clove of garlic and a couple of
potatoes so let me get this right my memory is fucking dogshit after this
where do I want to go after this I don't want to do the um I don't want to deal
with the the wolf I reached in and took the clove of garlic wolf is a death
okay sneak away sneak away quietly right I need a drink I need the rose tiptoed
out of the kitchen and left from here from here where the fuck do I go from
here faint breeze carried a musty odor to my sensitive not I'm not going in
there okay peek through go over to follow the breeze all the breeze I don't
want to go in the bathroom this room seems to be a laboratory I thought that
was the closed door I gotta get out of here right now
what it was the room smells like a wet dog suddenly I realized that someone was
coming up behind me I do it I don't know what to do what do I do what do I do
what do I do turn around think quickly what the fuck am I supposed to do think
quickly thinking quickly I stepped into the shower and pulled the curtain closed
a hairy paw what should I do I peered around the corner half to flirt with the
wolf she wolf busily primping herself for a night on the town okay I'm gonna
try um I give a woman to show the flirt and giggled like a schoolgirl what then
she started towards me are you kidding me those eyes my life what do I do um um
um um pucker up pucker up pucker up pucker up pucker up pucker up she's
coming over I don't know forward and planted a wet kiss on my lips then
stepped aside to let me pass got it okay now what smile and leave enter the room
across the house say smile and leave the room alright bye-bye smile I don't want
to have to be followed I stopped for a moment near the doorway okay we've not
gone as far for good luck enough from here I rounded the corner and very
nearly bumped into a female vampire she was starting to leave when I gave
myself away shit okay well I have garlic confront her hide it um confront her I
have garlic I have garlic I'm gonna do it I have garlic I'm gonna do it I have
garlic I'm gonna do it could see she was in no mood for a
confrontation I have I have garlic in my pocket what I have the steaks I have the
guard why can't I attack I came to in an attic someone or something was sitting
across the attic from me I have garlic and I have the steak pill and holy water
decides to pay a visit to his host oh well have you enjoyed our hospitality
so many 500 points it's fine at least we seduced the werewolf it was difficult
not to listen his voice had a strong hypnotic effect
I did it well let's just get as many I'm trying to get to 8,000 points you don't
know me I love this guy but I know you you have in my inventory was all the
shit that vampires are weak against holy water steaks with me garlic I couldn't
use any of them I picked out close to your heart that was my blood he was
sucking on you have to this is guys this game came out like in 1984 1985 or
something find something of value I don't have anything quickly I checked my
pockets what is it what what's going on what's in my pocket
roll gold coin kick in the groin what should I do I tried to attack but count
your check on I can't do it into my eyes and I knew I had failed I blacked out
what would you pick the gold coins out why wouldn't you take why wouldn't
garlic it be an option why wouldn't the steak pill a holy water he didn't take
the shit out of my pockets this time I have coin where I throw a coin at him
why don't you give a coin because I want to try to kick the guy in the groin
alright this game came out in like 1992 are you serious you don't think it would
have been like a comedy routine where it's he goes like oh my oh my balls I
was going for like the stupid like 90s comedy routine this game came out in
2016 it wasn't yet but it wasn't filmed in 2016 it was filmed in probably like
1990 shit alright well that was fun game was made in 84 yeah come on well now
let's watch them well now we can see the music video wait did showing him dying
what the hell was that we didn't see any of this stuff we didn't get any of these
options behind the scenes yeah I think the skeleton guys mouth is partially
made from a baseball mitt is a physical wizard like cantaloupe no not really I
can't believe there's a wizard that can cast fireball at you play it again oh
you need to probably have the ace for that the thing with these old games
those you have to be so weirdly specific about everything to see some
of this stuff some random lady we saw that plenty of times wait was that the
real ending villain well that was fun actually in love with this game play
more play again use a walkthrough I could just use a walkthrough you look at
the respiration of a 16 millimeter film adaptation of the original interactive
text adventure designed wait this is an it's a text adventure that's why it
feels like this uh-huh over the chance to create a feature-length interactive
film I wanted to read that Empire's Wanted restoration that's really cool I
did not back-to-back games that just never released it's really interesting I
love this shit I really do it's kind of old-fashioned way to have the old 16
millimeter FMV games with all the weird goofy choices I love this shit
the people still make them now but the people make interactive movies right now
right there's been a few of them one more playthrough all right one more time
with I'm gonna get a walkthrough I'm gonna go pee though we're at that boys
and girls a little bit of an issue here we have a little bit of a small problem
here I don't think a walkthrough exists for this game I don't see any there are
no walkthroughs so that's bad make the walkthrough do you even go to the
bathroom I did I was promised to overwatch I don't I think you're in the
wrong place nobody's beaten this we'll help you you gotta be quick though you
gotta be really quick it's like two seconds it takes three seconds for the
stream delay to kick in for you guys to see what happened we're not gonna be
able to do it I can't elongate that slow your CPU down what if you alt tab does
actually let me test that let me see if this works if I like tab out will the
game stop no it just keeps going yeah it keeps going wait a minute wait a
minute wait a minute what if I had known this shit this would have been so much
better guys oh my god damn it take a look at this get a good view get a good
view the timer doesn't do anything when it gets to zero it's just points I was
panicking half the time cuz I thought are you kidding me it's just what's your
score up higher well you can help let's figure this out together and this needs
to be unanimous so the obvious play here is I can't believe this I could have
whatever we're gonna meet the gentleman the priest wanted money all right give
us but it was for a good cause thank you mr. Spencer go to the orphanage
specter whatever your name is the not deductible okay so this just means a
lot of points mid points not I don't care if I get zero points I supposed to
the end of the game okay we do click maps click max is gonna take way too
long all right the obvious thing here is I have the holy water I don't want to
send in do click maps I don't even I don't even have it like installed we
can do quick polls how long does the poll take just give us two seconds to
click hold all right well then give me a second I gotta like enable it again
obviously I might not be able to do it no click map the shortest poll is one
minute that's much easier click okay to enable click maps have you guys click and
me disable it is like 45 seconds a B or C let's go the very obvious one I know
how to get here it's B I know how to get us into the room into the door the
Der Hatchet Institute was founded by a Nobel prize-winning scientist
this locked is what okay finally we have not done we've only done look under the
mat what do you guys want to do let's open it up why not well we'll do a full
chats choice run how does that sound and I look I can look at this as it's
coming in and yeah it's not gonna take 60 seconds look at 66% of the vote wants
me to go a so I could theoretically just once it once it becomes like a 50
to 60% majority I'm just gonna go can you just close the poll like if you
cancel the poll right now just close it like I know that's 67% of voted for a
and there's no way bees coming back I can just do it right yeah let's go that
works on another way inside as I walked around the house I saw an open window
high above me isn't that where the guy is I found a ladder leaning next to
another window okay I think that's where the guy is well there we go perfect so
after the poll is over it gives enough time after majority is seen they just
keep going that's perfect timing okay we can do the climb the ladder look
around explore the extensive grounds or move ladder to access the open window
I'm just gonna tell you I am under the impression here that I think that's the
the Count Dooku guy the gravest guy is up there this is extraordinarily
unanimous looks like we're gonna see I moved the ladder and started I hope it's
him I was halfway through the window looking at the ground below when I was
struck from above by what felt like a Louisville slugger the gorilla covering
above me was a bat from the big leagues push its face in swing for the fences
or maintain a safe distance I doubt any of these work if I'm gonna be honest
with you a bat from the big leagues well B makes sense because B is part of the
pun right it's waiting for the fences a big bat from the big leagues all right
we're gonna be it's unanimous wait for the fence I grabbed the bat with both
hands and to say it looked angry would be a gross understatement definitely
hurt the actor okay snare the bat with the rope climb up to the rafters or use
the rope to escape snare the bat with the rope that's in that it's 80% of the
vote so far yeah okay it's near the bat I grabbed the rope and a trap door opened
as a wrong fell for what seemed to be a long long time they hit the ground hard
fortunately I broke my fall on something soft
well what do you think you're doing mother doesn't like anybody playing in her laundry do ya mom
that's right stay out of my laundry
why did he change his voice halfway through
this guy was obviously a psycho
this guy's a psycho
why does it sound like Bobcat Goldthwait
I mean I had to like make sounds and make voices and stuff like that it sounds like me
you guys say this to me all right give the psycho a closer look go find the
butler give mama a friendly smile well I think this is the death one but we have
to click it because that's what you guys want to do give mama a friendly smile
wow what are you waiting for
yet within striking distance casually gain his confidence or go find the
butler I'm convinced that you made this game and this is some kind of prank
stream I wish I did I wish I made this game all right we're gonna be I moved
cautiously towards mama's boy watch it right okay you guys got that double
wrong that's double wrong he flattened your nose I don't know how long I was
out but someone or something had dragged me to a cellar below Der Hatchet Manor
as I struggled to clear my head I clicked on my flashlight and looked
around any fool could see that the place had more than its share of dingbats and
I was no exception FMV game you know how badly I okay here's the problem
there's I have to be careful for like shotgun blasting out a bunch of ideas
that I think of really fun because I have to focus on only a few things at a
time make no mistake about it I would love nothing more than to put hundreds
and hundreds of hours of time and any amount of money doesn't matter how much
it would cost to make an FMV game that's like this but holy shit that is
like a monumental undertaking and there's no way I'm gonna be able to do
it there's only so many things I can be in the tank you can't load up too much
luggage in your car to the point where your car is touching the ground because
it won't drive yeah I can't weigh the car down with 500 cinder blocks make
that one the last bit before retirement I explore the seller it was there in the
seller that I discovered the little man with the evil grin I've actually talked
about it before with people in the community about like things that I've
wanted to do but it's just I can't I get if it's too much to think about too much
to do all right I mean we already know how this one plays out I probably just
did this on my own yeah we it's don't turn around and then we flip them he fell
for it so I took the opportunity to bash him in the chops I never hit a man when
he's down but I knew I should have made an exception when I felt his fingers on
my throat how fucking awesome how fun would that be oh man imagine making a
full FMV game and we just do it what you guys play it I don't even play it you
guys pick like this god damn it that would be fun yeah do it I don't tell me
to do these things because I will fuck up every other project just give me a
little bit more time and I have a lot more things to talk about it's a little
bit more time I want to do so many of these things a little bit more time all
right what are we doing all right well Chad is deciding to lose another heart
so we're going to tickle him he just tightened his grip and laughed well you
died I woke up with the feeling that I was at the end of my room it didn't work
realize that I was you lost a heart he tied the situation was bad and my life
hung in the balance but this was no time for reflection just make an unfinished
FMV project and have somebody else need to finish it in 30 years that's really
funny well it would have to be shot in 16 millimeter that's one of things I'm
gonna make it really incredibly incredibly clear if I'm if I were to do
this it's being shot in 16 millimeter I don't care how expensive it is this
needs to be led that way it's gonna be like two million dollars fuck it I don't
think it's gonna cause that much do 16 millimeter and then get it restored into
Wow now that's a big brain play that's a big brain play somebody say cringe all
right we all know this is easy all these are the same I was trying to think of a
diversion when I lost my footing started to slip away as the rope bit into my
neck have us pay for it do like a pay-per-view stream when I got up I saw
that the pipe had made quite an impression on laughing boy I wouldn't
want to do okay here's what I wouldn't want to do I wouldn't want to make it so
people couldn't watch it even if that okay let's say that this whole project if
it was ever if it was ever done remember this is not me saying it's
happening I'm just saying that's even I'm interested if it was oh here's an
idea we'll make the whole thing and then the stream will be you pay for the
stream like a pay-per-view stream no I want as many people to experience that
as humanly possible right maybe do paid physical copies yeah I'm honestly I
would not give a shit at all I mean obviously I don't want to like lose like
millions of dollars like that would be fucking devastating I don't have
millions of dollars it would be pretty bad maybe there's a way maybe that well
maybe I'll find a way all right what do you guys want to make yeah of course I
told laughing boy he was bound to be out of circulation for a while but he
losing millions is really funny though no really okay well all right this is
where it all goes completely off the rails what about getting it sponsored
yeah you don't know and do get the sign we need to be done with actors shot on
film I wanted to be old where we going I would make yourself an actor no I would
know I don't be the only actor I would be I would be in it for like 10 seconds
I'd be like the the old prospector that you run into in a hallway somewhere this
is also pretty you this is very unanimous look for some artifacts the
next room contained an old writing desk under the derhatchet family crest on the
desk were many items of interest you get streamers to be actors no I don't think
so I don't want anyone I feel like okay I want them to be unknown I don't want
anyone to know who they are I wanted to be actors I wanted to be I'd like to be
like real because here's the thing stuff like that would be really funny but let
you say it was like streamer X it's no it's it's like streamer X playing
character right it's not that's the that's a monster on the screen so if I
would ever do that exactly the same reason why I said I don't even want to
be in it either like I would want to be in it for like 10 seconds as like an
Easter egg I don't want to be in this I want to hire I want to like direct
actors right because then it's just oh look it's germa as this character you
know I'm saying so now it would be all just actors that we would be hiring and
I'm talking like this is happening soon but it's not if it did happen it would
be like that all right uh taste the wine you we already know how to do this one
we already know how to do this one why are you doing this as I reached forward
the candle lit itself and as if by magic a monk appeared well this is a
different option now play more of these games if you're a relatively new viewer
gold motion video games I've played almost all of them over the last five
years or so there actually aren't very many left that I haven't played some of
the new ones I haven't played the ones that have come out in the last year or
two and we're gonna be drunk the flame in the wine oh yeah okay wish the candle
and a glass of the house vino and the Phantom friar gave up the ghost at least
the ones that look like we'd have a good time playing them right some FMV
games that are very much meant to be taken very seriously and it's not like
oh my god look at how funny that was look at how bizarre of a scenario that
was it's just actors doing things in front of a camera so it's supposed to
be taken seriously and not like oh let's have a fun time and laugh at this all
right pocket the gold and split I think that's what it's gonna be it is you guys
cannot make another mistake hey you want to go I don't want to say anything
because it's kind of close what is the baseball stream baseball stream is going
to be at some point in the first quarter or second quarter of next year somewhere
when baseball is played it was a theory that we might be able to get it done
this year but it's not gonna happen too cold but that I refuse to not do that
stream and what about grotto beasts grotto beasts actually let's do this
right now I want to shout this out so grotto beasts I can't give you a time or
date for that but I really really want you to be able to have that stuff in
your hands the physical cards in your hands by the latest quarter one of this
coming year I'm giving a huge window for that because it's very very possible
that's way earlier but I don't want to rush people on the work that they're
doing so if you get it at some point at the end of this year or January maybe
you do but I'm not gonna tell you that because I don't want to put on a
dumb amount of pressure on people to have to get stuff done that's I don't
know I do not want to do that so whenever it's done and whenever it's like
okay it's ready to go and with that let's go ahead and talk about this so the
grotto beasts team has a Twitter and they post various updates I actually just
retweeted them on Halloween here's the official grotto beasts Twitter account
let me put it in the chat go give it a follow if you want to know more about
grotto beasts coming up they post all the time all the various artists and
here you go here is the official Twitter of the grotto beasts trading card game I
was holding off on talking about this until it was clear that we had sort of
like an end goal of soon grotto beast NFTs this these are not NFTs but now
there's not gonna be an NFT there won't be any grotto beast NFTs this is you're
gonna be able to hold these in your hand well not you get that it's a you're
gonna be a whole it's cards you will be able to purchase and open for yourself
packs of grotto beasts by the way let's make this very clear too if you think
that this was just gonna be a repackaged thing that I opened on the stream you
are so wrong there's going to be an astronomical more amount of cards and
it's gonna have a playable game behind it as well you're actually gonna be able
to play this with people it's a real game have a game designer and hey hope
you like it when it comes out because there's other stuff that I haven't
talked about yet with it too but you know what yeah fuck it let's just talk
about it why not hey I I'm the goddamn CEO okay um should I hold off on some
stuff so the grotto beasts card game is going to end up being a pretty
significant when people talk about like merch right oh what what should you do
a t-shirt I could do another t-shirt oh maybe I'll do a t-shirt maybe I'll do
something else so maybe I'll do like a toy or something in the grotto beast
card game there's going to be not just grotto beasts it's not just gonna be
grotto beasts it's gonna be tons and tons of this channel's references
characters it's gonna be a gigantic crossover so it's not just simply the
grotto beasts there's potentially lots of other things too that you'll be able
to have and collect it's the biggest crossover event ever and it's two things
that were created in on this same channel in this same community it's not
even a crossover event it's the same goddamn channel so I've been pretty
tight-lipped about this because I don't I didn't want to like hype this up until
I knew that it was gonna start to become a thing so it's a game you can actually
play it you don't even have to he's losing viewers no stay don't please
don't leave please don't leave please what about people that were in the
rumble actually 20 community subs of Anto uh yes so that there's a lot of
plans for like that project in the future maybe just know that it's gonna
have a lot of cards is gonna be I don't want to talk too much about it because I
don't want to get anything wrong and community Jake right now might be
fucking speed dialing me going like don't stop talking so I gotta be careful
I don't want to talk too much but follow that Twitter you're gonna get that's
where the official updates will be on that Twitter what about t-shirts yeah
they'll be merch we'll have some merch are they gonna be different rarities
don't do it right now Jake is fucking spam texting me stop talking stop
talking what about a sunflower update I'm sure it's November they've gone all
right let's go back to this what'd you get I don't even know what you guys
picked this is a nice get rich scheme no this is it it's me selling you card packs
get rich more scheme all right settle down settle down real life got you no
we're gonna okay I community Jake's gonna scream at me I'm gonna get
screamed at on the phone there's gonna it's gonna be don't worry okay no I'm
gonna I'm okay let's go there's no NFTs associated with this what the fuck I
never said that what about EU I I don't I I have no answer for that time I don't
I currently do not have an answer for this time I'm I think so I just can't
give you an answer I don't know I do not have an answer for this time and my
phone just blew up I've got eight unread notifications on my phone I see a stop
sign emoji a hundred times okay I probably should let's go ahead and play
the game what did you guys pick it was a I don't remember I can't it was B all
right B let's go on the steps above me a green ghoul gestured gracefully I'm
really really excited for not just the fact that the grotto beast are really
awesome but it's gonna be this interesting kind of mix of like a ton of
references to this the last decade plus of this channel and community it's a
really interesting way I was hopeful to do merch and we're going a proceed boldly
I approached the zombie reluctantly and asked him who his tailor was his
response was to push me backwards into a rickety old freight elevator yeah you said
boldly you end up gonna do the germa joke plus two minus two futures market
with channel points that seems like a fun idea yeah I did but that's the
problem this is why I get into trouble I get in a lot of trouble because we
pay okay I tell I tell you guys about four or five different things that
sound really interesting don't they but in reality only one or two of those
things can possibly be worked on so what ends up happening is you are like oh my
god he talked about like four or five different cool things going on when in
realities one of these things is actually gonna work these are all things
that I really want to do every time I talk it's things that I really want to
do but here's the thing right since the dollhouse stream there's been some
potential here to do more possibly maybe hopefully maybe find more people that
are willing to get on board and help us pay for projects and help us do things
there some of these things are possible now because the dollhouse happened and
the dollhouse was a really really fun time so I can't tell you exactly what's
gonna happen because I still don't even know but if some of these doors are
starting to open a little bit more with like okay now people are aware that I
want to do big projects and I need capital and I need people and I need
more crew members and stuff right like this is all stuff that's knowledgeable
to a lot of people now so if I can get some of these things to help make these
projects come faster that's what I'm gonna do networking Andy well you bet
your ass that I want to try to make some of these things reality right and if
they do become a reality that's what makes me happy I don't care about
anything else I really don't I don't give a shit about anything else I could
not make a single dollar from us any of the projects none of them zero I would
not give a flying fuck at all I wouldn't care at all I don't care if they that
the projects can be paid for and I don't have to worry about it then fucking
perfect that's exactly what I want I don't care he's lying by the way I'm
not I swear I promise you I don't care you've seen okay you've seen the leak I
don't even need to tell you that like we've made a jokes about it before do I
really need to make a shitload of money on each project because I'm I have to
no I don't care I'm for 98 yeah I'm not a liar says the life yeah all right I am
a liar I I'm a liar but not in not unimportant stuff like this I'm not
trying to make a bunch of money I'm trying to have things be paid for right
that I'm I care about and sometimes people will hear about some of the how
much some of this these projects costed right holy shit it was that much money
yeah I sometimes it has to be but don't get do not give me any money I'm seeing
people give money don't do that stop giving me money right now I demand it
somebody's give me a hundred dollars thank you for do not do not give me any
money stop that immediately I command it I demand it I demand it it ends at once
are we going stop reverse engineer Andy I'm just saying all right just know in
the future whatever projects we do I'm just I'm glad that they were able to
happen that's it just think about this this is like the kind of shit that I've
wanted to since I was like fucking 12 right I cannot even begin to tell you
guys just how how it feels to like something that I wanted to do when I was
11 you are 12 like I am I'm really I'm living every single one of my fantasies
from when I was a kid it's unbelievable to me and the fact that I'm able just to
do that alone just just by itself is worth more than anything anything so the
fact that I can sit here and talk like this is already enough just want to be
clear Jesus fucking Christ just play the game already I just I just had a major
announcement come on I just talked about the grotto beast that's a major
announcement I'm I'm going I'm going I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm going I thought
was a major announcement I have a major announcement and I don't want to be oh
look at me I'm so good oh I don't I don't care about money I'm a good guy
I'm a good guy no I don't want to do that either all right okay I'm gonna go
we're gonna go I'm a fucking bad guy all right I'm the bad guy don't worry what
you guys pick surprise me I don't want to be like a preachy asshole either well
you know I'm so much better than I look at what I do look yeah I don't care
about from only me oh I'm the only one that cares about not receiving a
monitor I'm the only one no I don't want you to think that either I love money
okay here we go all right walk straight this I don't think I've done this before
the next room I came to had nothing in it there was an old freezer on one side
and a lot of potions on the other just as I started to examine them I heard a
scream open the freezers the correct play we've all seen it like five times
already although there's opening the freezer stop whatever the laughing
screaming person coming in the room I think Coolsville sucks just open the
freezer ignoring the fumes I opened the freezer I love this guy uh can I just do
this on my own because I know how to get there please do okay I read the labels
extra strength potion instant steak pill anti-grav tablets okay so it's the
take the steak and leave I wasn't hungry now but an instant steak might come in
handy later where's your choice that's what everybody was gonna pick all right
this is it's a and then you leave these are both this is gonna kill us so don't
be stupid about this thank you
yeah we gotta get out of this room it's your one-year anniversary with the sus
face I want a divorce I gave him five dollars and left all right this is a
tough call because I don't remember exactly which one of these means you get
grabbed how do you feel about the rats becoming extremely popular and tick-tock
sorry say that again so that one more time I didn't hear that that well say
that again I won't say that again the rats are incredibly popular on tick-tock
the rats are huge on tick-tock I'm sorry I'm leaning with my ear say that one
more time what do we talk about like a few weeks ago what that I I am huge on
tick-tock and I'm not even there so I'm excuse me I'm just trying to understand
why everyone was saying that that was not accurate the rats are also huge on
Facebook all right let's search the room the rats are popular not you bozo as I
ran into the next room I heard the scream again I am the rats the rats are
nothing without me should I make a tick-tock video of doing the rat song but
make sure I'm doing it really poorly and I'd be pretty relatively unknown on
tick-tock would people like hate me for it would be like oh that was terrible
nice try my video is way better on the tick on the rats meme it's like I'm I'm
the one who made it talking to you talking to the guy that made it up keep
moving forward why you're not actually gonna do this are you I ran through the
door and found myself near the elevator oh I thought you fall I pushed the
button and waited there was a green door to my left and a stairway to my right
okay I know for a fact we don't do the green door this is a really important
decision but I'm just kidding I scramble up the stairs is it time to
release release release is it time to release the third rat song I wonder if
we're gonna get to the end at the top of the stairs I saw an ugly dwarf private
eye versus private eye gory how tall am I okay show him your license take
evasive action or put down that shovel take evasive action when he moved I
jumped over the railing it was a long way to the first floor and laughing boy
was no help at all that would hurt so bad holy shit that was painful looking
I think you guys are in some trouble here grab his shirt and pull punch with
your stronger hand or let go of the railing grab his shirt and pull is
winning by a way too much I grabbed his shirt and flipped over the railing symbol
crash the second floor looked dark and uninviting okay where we go I told my
friend who used to work for the company that helped with this game and he
thought that it was crazy that you were playing it and as we're having a great
time the last one too I applaud the companies that actually tried to restore
this stuff this is awesome I'm having a lot of fun ask your friend how to beat
the game all right we're going I don't know it's 51 42 a and C if it were me I
would probably pick the one that we didn't do yet which is probably whatever
medical records so and that's winning right now so that's what I'm gonna pick
the room I next entered was obviously a library of some sort well it's in
regardless I'm gonna get the garlic there was a door to my left another dead
ahead but most of the action was taking place in the kitchen on my right where
someone was practicing a bizarre form of culinary preparation but we don't
necessarily have to do the kitchen but the garlic seems pretty important huh
yes the library kitchen I couldn't put my finger on it but there was something
odd about the woman in the kitchen it's really cold in this room I think maybe
the breath coming out of you see that you see just how cold it is in there I
feel bad for the actor oh yeah we look in the bad we're gonna look in the
fridge of course I find other edibles we've gotten this right plenty of times
make the FMV game and make sure there's no references to you in it no they won't
be it would be it would be I mean well they'd be you'd probably know I made it
somehow but this would not be a like German 985 FMV experience it'd be like
an old Western game or something like an old horror game inside the cupboard was
a rose a clove of garlic and a couple of potatoes don't tell us you made it and
just play it one day well I think it would be really fun if the first
experience ever with the game was on the stream and you guys are doing this maybe
we'll build like an extension or something I have like some kind of use
of an extension for you guys to do it easier so you guys are get the first
experience of the game and then like I reached in and took the clove of God a
week later or something it goes on steam or whatever stop giving him an idea he
only cares about money I care about money I don't only care about money
money's somewhere on the list somewhere take the potato I feel like I'm gonna
get hurt I you guys really I think a is you took too much die and we get stabbed
this is a GG I thank you all right well I came to something was sitting across
the attic from me this doesn't matter oh I feel like we've met before
that's my favorite shot of the whole thing he's kind of leaned over you all said a
anyways I want this guy that was my he was sucking on this character okay this
is actually important I want that exact character in another game find something
value I should have the coins quickly I checked my pockets okay throw a gold
coin that's the only option that probably results in something different
that's a different video clip let's try it I threw it in his mouth expecting him
to choke to death what but instead when I looked in his eyes I knew I had failed
I was powerless to resist him that sucked that sucked it was a great throw
but Jesus okay you guys want one more chance at this I'm gonna give you one
more chance let's get to the end I know you can do it collectively I know you can
is there another FMV I have this I have one more that's ready for right now but
it's new and I don't know I'm not sure if I want to do it right now it looks
like it might be long depends on how long it is is it the battle royale one
omega lol it is why are you saying that omega lol omega lol omega lol no chance
what do you mean or tonight is not an FMV dude it's short all right well let's
try it this I this is really fun though I like this a lot
remember it's only been three hours um excuse me it's been four hours excuse me
that's right let's exit this that was the specter files death stalker was that
was great I had a lot of fun hopefully I got to turn this down because it might
be very loud was it called blood sure blood sure let's give it a roll it's
changed the game I cannot capture it why not yeah this is like it's a like
squid game well it's like live it's two viewers squid game type shit I don't
know why can I not capture this oh there is okay all right this is uh this this
looks kind of bright this is bright at least the subtitles can be on what
streamer mode oh yeah it's kind of bright isn't it I'll set those on
medium subtitle background borderless window streamer mode you can pause
choices I don't think German knows what squid game is I've I've seen squid game
I've seen the whole show are you ready name one character fine pop culture Andy
you're fucking pop culture Andy pop culture Andy name squid yes see it's a
game it's a game which they have a bunch of squids they get to come in and have
you know all of them have some type of money problem I don't want to give I
don't want to give anything away I was really high when I watched the whole
thing so I don't know anybody I don't remember any I don't remember the plot
either the front no I don't want to say that because that could be a spoiler I
know who the you heard me say some words there and you know that was a
character you heard me say it's that I just said something I you heard it you
know I you and I know that character is no I don't give spoilers away I just say
the main characters name don't say the main characters name get off the IMDb
page I the main characters name is Squidward okay just quiet the following
contest seems that some of you may find disturbing is not super for younger
audiences including graphic depictions of violence blood and death you were
discretion is get out of here oh my god I just have my hand hurts the squid
game name one character I fucking god damn it takes now you know I didn't see
it I'm just pretending to because I wanted people to think I know what I'm
doing the ultimate prize only people think I know pop culture and shit I
haven't seen one episode I've seen the whole show I can name ten characters I
just don't want to see it is like squid game I told you kill stream now
entering its 13th season has been criticized by human rights experts for
its brutality having claimed the lives of 210 of its 470 contestants thus far
showrunners allan crock claim that all contestants are fully aware of the way
I can get it's I got it
and are responsible in large part for the cutthroat society we live in Eugene
Christoph when you created the show you put the world's deadliest death row
inmates on an island to battle to the death the winners of the first few
seasons have become some of the wealthiest people in the world
yes that justice I guess I have what it took
glory in the past few years who do we play as have risen in line with the
economic downturn what good to everyone these people are a byproduct of the
society created by you some would say you're a coward having tapped out they
can say that's my face you have been inundated with applications they have
been ground into dust by the boot heel of the rich and powerful who are now
using them for their own entertainment if I didn't know any better Chris I'd
say you were accusing me of exploiting the pool I'm not the only person to
find your show utterly abhorrent terms are agreed upon by both parties to
witness deaths on television since the beginning of time man's been pitted
against his fellow man in combat surely we've evolved from a more barbaric time
I'm not so sure we have
we play as one of these people people want they keep watching what the fuck
they're like Instagramming this shit garlic influencer 207,000 followers
that don't sweat it people it doesn't get any real in this Otto strike Royale
player 400,000 followers oh shit Nick 900,000 followers to find an ally early
helps keep you alive through the chaos of the first few rounds no alone only I
don't trust anybody none of you sounds like that would get complicated
yeah extreme vlogger 87k fish video game streamer 40,000 followers
game streamers shooters mainly should come in handy what about the cannibal
life is all or nothing yes you know that I'm our people out there don't know you
just lost half your subscribers in the last six months a microphone I got
anything to do with this this what's the huge microphone travel vlogger it's time
for the world to see everybody British I don't know maybe it was made Ari 200,000
followers podcaster Oh stream remote okay okay guys so what do you think I
should do here honest I think it's a good it's a really good play discreet not
so sure about that one dude I'm gonna be discreet
reasons as everyone else you kidding me that's Nick fucking Romeo wait I feel
is it oh you didn't watch the Mikey lizard who these people do I hate the
least I wonder
don't we have to make oxygen masks I have no idea how this works guys I
you're gonna see do too late well you're about to jump out the perfectly
good airplane I feel about that move your cursor what if there's a decision
what they say about he who hesitates what what oh they the audience is not
on board with me right now all right so it's just it's you whatever it takes to
win right I gotta sabotage somebody's parachute right wait hold on okay Ricky
pro gamer 32,000 followers why is he not pulling his cord oh no we didn't even
get to hear that guy talk track how you're doing from the pause menu there's
escape tracker team morale audience opinion romance strength and insight
really okay let's go I'm very confused why don't we just use your parachute
come on I'm just killing each other I did right now immediately this is a pub
G doesn't work like this everybody runs around finds like a
fucking frying pan starts killing each other instantly it'd be over in five
seconds someone runs around till they find a gun and just start shooting
everybody I take it back Mikey you did all right one down 49 to go really we
don't get disqualified for this right this ain't on us yeah hey can you send
me that we just qualified a hundred thousand watching now had last season's
finale at over a hundred million concurrent viewers don't work it I'll
make sure million concurrent viewers that's like five cut that out come on
that's enough no way look how many people are watching this kid watching
this could be the season's first fatality take the camera off they can't
with their children kid watching seriously I said the camp it's like five
billion people watching at the end of the day you should head in 100 million
concurrent viewers is like billions of people watching over the course of a day
look sharp people you're on camera here we go kill stream 30 live
re-streaming it post-dreaming it
kill talk extreme vloggers psychopaths and wolf boys have we got a season of
kill stream in store for you we'll be checking in with our viewers and getting
your thoughts on this year's contestants a hot favorite going in wolf
boys that's the funniest thing so far our contenders will spend a night on the
island before this so grab a drink and settle in because the countdown starts
now there's a category wrong I was on this oh no it's it's good yeah
blood sure we have to spend a night seriously what is this this isn't the
island it's different every time it's different every time warm sandy beaches
we show up on a beach might want to be a careful where you stand they're
everywhere what you make light of the situation
kaboom they're smart minds they're using a force players close to each other
keeps the game interesting must be hundreds of thousands that explains
why they couldn't afford to send us to the Bahamas so we have to stay close to
each other we all know what it's like anything to get the views my agent's
gonna hear about this who cares we're not here for a vacation I'm just gonna
step on one of those probably really soon what's this where's the beach house
you're not catching on are you if they die in the game they die in real life
come on no dude that bad fucking paradise it's like they are ending six
weeks in the rain course with nothing no shelter except when you make for
yourself why some of this food here at least it's four weeks in the Amazon
what's that there there's no beds here you don't even know where here is he's
right judging by the foliage and I could give us a drink by the man it's probably
I'm gonna be sipping water fine I'll go look for I'll go see I'm drinking water
and we drinking I'm gonna eat and be like cliff bars is it not touching
anything else where's the view count no I'm not I'm gonna have be as close to
reality I'm not getting inebriated at all
what are you doing it like you must have done all right after them movies you
kidding there's no words in years got fucked over by the studio why don't you
mind your own business sorry man I saw it on TMZ big Bettson who dies first okay
uh here we go well they've introduced the comedy guy they give the word and we
go at it so he's absolutely gonna last at least 20 minutes killing each other
comedy guy might die first in a funny way right because they might go the
comedy guy dies first funnily I'm saying comedy guy for the early rounds watch
each other's backs through the crazy part and then what still breathing we'll
deal with it then I guess turning into the night yeah this guy right here he's
first well I mean teaming up I mean of course you are that's not for me I don't
we can play team game all right let's let's get a team thing going like the
final ten or go down first well like we said it's complicated we're gonna do
what we're gonna team exercise common sense no one fucks with a group the
bigger the better for now what no way chicken dinner all the way what you're
gonna win yeah who wins okay you can definitely not be me because I'm the
main character I can't win I'll be making a sacrifice at the end of the
game for me to die and it's all for TV no one believes in God anymore I need
the new church opiate for the masses Alan core rumba the Russians or the
Illuminati definitely the fucking Illuminati just a bunch of fucking old
white men making the rules whoever's the quietest person hello wasn't the
creator of kill stream black yeah where is he now you're just paranoid you know
there's lots of other landing groups and now that for yeah he's definitely not
calling me paranoid he's gonna say he's gonna step on a landmine baby of course
you're gonna kill the fake news guy first right you're going to there's no
way he survives one ten more minutes
especially with Hannibal over there you know the story don't it what is this
survival blogger he spent four weeks deep in the Amazon Bay this guy's gonna
last a while I think found themselves in trouble got separated from the support
crew we found dev alive and well should have starved to death would have starved
to death his partner didn't come back no exposition well that what do you think
he came back three kilos heavier I hope he's not hungry when does the battle
royale start they said that there was gonna be one night where they literally
explained some of the characters they can't just start killing people they
need to give you some backstory of people one night and then we start to go
kill stream who are these people yeah why was there was a kid come in I've
landed on the island location unknown you knew about this who am I talking to
location change was last minute and now that I have do you know where I am
it's great what about extractions you at least have a plan to get me out of this
place you have not seen squid game I want you to mute mute for a second I'm
gonna prove that I've seen my neck mute if you haven't seen squid game mute I'm
gonna prove that I've seen the show safe you don't even know where I am I am
gonna spoiler for squid game turn stop listening for a second 5 4 3 2 1 you
never seen this good game before I've never seen this good game before about
the doctor just said what do you have the doctor thing yeah what's going on
with that yeah okay so I've never seen it like this is what I'm watching right
now that I've seen it what happened all right everyone can come back it's now
safe make a joke I don't I don't I wasn't even listening what I just told
you you'd be too vague I don't want to be no I don't just spoil television shows
okay what's that I need to get I want to give like a full 30 seconds why open it
it's probably something I'm opening it I want it whatever it is whatever in there
okay 30 minutes to show time oh we hit the show I didn't even started yet where
are the starting soon screen he's gonna go step on a mine that was gone good that
guy was creepy he's gonna step on a mine I'm telling you this one too I'm
telling you what you'd love with that going somewhere there's no scatter
around shit on a mine is that what you do in war of duty what no he's a camper
what's that he's a pussy lands himself in cover and waits for the way this is a
camper hope he dies first it's bullshit I never camp let's screw this
and scout the area oh yeah get to the weapons drops first more like excuse me
you heard me what the fuck is your they drop weapons do you think this is a game
guys go on then leave get out before I use your head for fucking target practice
fuck this I'm not staying here this fucking psycho react I had there's no
way I'm side with a camper just making that really clear if you're not gonna be
a team player I don't see this working dude come on fine totally fine team look
react harder you didn't side with German Otto cool react to hurry up gives a
weapon drop nobody changes channels this best you have to spend at least 10
seconds to see what it is don't you know the double double double double double
double cross the animal style double cross the animal style double double
cross I need to make sure everybody here I'm not a threat to anybody but I'm a
threat to everyone the Korean no that was
oh wait there's more than us oh shit I was about to kill all these people
I thought it was just us like six who do you think you're teaming up against
holy shit imagine not paying attention to the first five minutes in the plane I
would have picked a brick up and started hitting people in the head really last night
alongside your busy listeners no offense and in more serious news this time
around we're changing things out of it this year there will be no tap outs and
tap out why not what does that mean fuck that's right you're all in it to win it
no rescues no tactical drugs this year you've got to give it your all this is
insane you will shortly receive your first weapons drops not too far from
your current position so move fast with half the planet watching you right now
you're already a superstar now go put on a show
bastards they can't do that I said it could be the first one today you read it
I mean I did it wasn't exactly finding on their part fuck you I'm calling my
attempt to inspire the team what's all right let's come to bring together no
no guys come on we got to keep it together this is just what they want
panic that didn't listen whatever fuck them you're all getting brick tomorrow
night anyways let's go get those weapon drops oh they hate me now loser don't
ever underestimate the underdog he can surprise you
camping but we should do we lay low and ride it out did the weapons crates drop
you know I just checked the map we should be right on top of it why are
kids watching this and why are kids analysts about this yeah I don't
understand the first Trump lives this guy's dead first I'm telling you I'm
telling you he's dead he's dead instantly it's he's gonna he's gonna die
very soon in less than 10 minutes how do we know how to use these kill her now
no I'm not gonna now that I know that we're a team wait which one doesn't
work I don't remember is the one on the left just okay is it my left or is my
right the thing I'm switching the poison on myself I don't want to do this is it
my gun on right like this one or gun on my left it's your left so it would be
this one is left and left is the one that does not work so I'm gonna give her
this one okay these are all pretty old you only use them if we need to that
screwed that one works damn it that one works shit I reversed the poison on
myself I actually did the thing from princess bread I freaked out investigate
don't shoot I'm not armed where's your landing group I'm on my own or shit I
overshot the landing been out here all night where where your bruises where
scratches horseshit shoot him shoot him yeah yeah seriously man you don't want
to do this shoot him shoot him no scratches no I probably shouldn't have
done that I've done that I could just oh I just landed no scratches no bruises oh
yeah I just landed away from my group yeah right look around they're out here
they're probably hiding dead yep and he had a gun thank you everybody wants to
I'm a psycho I just saved the goddamn team hesitation is defeat no if
everyone's look that's the thing if you landed away from your group you're not
going to hide behind a tree and approach another group choco boy 89 not a chance
why would you sneak up on another group that's not gonna happen I did what I had
to do camo camo so in right now really you never see it anywhere seriously
though what is this shite these guns are almost antique we should head for the
Sun see that what about it it's got to be something it's not in the
lock exactly there's a bridge up ahead from there we can either go straight
through or we can go I don't know straight ahead I feel like everyone's
gonna be going around nobody wants to do the straight shot because as well it's
too far in the open we don't want to be too exposed but isn't everybody gonna be
going around I think it's straight on I say we go straight through let's go see
if we can catch someone off guard no we go the other way and make sense we
serious I didn't just get telltale did I have the trust of his teammates what's
it gonna take to pull this back oh wait they don't trust me it's actually a
meter oh shit they won't listen to me that's actually kind of interesting
it's illusion of choice but it's not really an illusion of choice is this a
team morale meter and they would have listened to me if I if I didn't they
didn't hate me or something what's the difference between a liberal and a poppy
a puppy stops whining when it grows up landmine here comes the landmine or
maybe they're gonna keep him around long enough to like make everybody like hate
him and then they'll kill him I don't know I'm just gonna keep walking by the
way let's talk strategy here why would you ever talk like that with your
teammates in a life-or-death scenario where you need to like have each other's
backs but I feel I feel like you don't want your teammates to like fucking hate
your guts regardless of any of this right I would you want why would you do
that everybody is like hating this guy and he's like I'm being like political
and I like a dick isn't that hot look at me like why wouldn't you want to like
have your back with your teammates this is a life-and-death scenario with
everybody here what the fuck did you find any what's going on here I saw
something up ahead like a building what's with the blood don't point the
gun back at your face that was really bad
um I what why do you have blood all over your face I mean it's very very it's
very very very odd that it would be that high like okay have you shot somebody
like and they sprayed blood on it would be like kind of here here here yeah
she's blood like on her face up here why that's very that's that's a little odd I
don't you need to explain this here what you seem awfully eager to get us
this outpost what's waiting there hey hey is this the doubt is this the fuck you
Nick you're all fucked anyway good luck so what's the plan maybe we should camp
am I using that right I was supposed to be on the same team look she working
with another team that was really weird you have blood on your mouth weird I
don't know about that if it were me if I had blood all over my mouth it'd be like
look guys let me explain why this blood all over my mouth listen to me you're
camping right now anything to fucking survive man nice oh what I gave oh shit
it's the um that's that was the broken gun that was the broken gun no I'm not
getting up such a coward no I have to no no no no no I'll do it I'll do it I'll
do it I'll do it I'll do it hold on wait wait wait I'm gonna get up I'm gonna get
up I'm gonna get up I'm gonna get up fuck you here comes a team wipe hey what
does someone with blue blood taste like anyway this is easy easy you took the
good you took the good gun and didn't even use it oh oh oh man I feel really
bad I feel awful this is bad I need to redeem myself right now oh thank God
stream remote okay guys so we got three seconds left and I gotta be honest I'm
really not so sure what I should do I'm thinking that Gav has experience with
potential survival skills but tish had a lot of big brain ideas I'm not so
certain about this though she had some I think she's she's probably to keep the
smart person tish tish just suspects me oh shit she does you were acting sus
you've been acting sus towards tish if you save her then she should trust you
again but tish had a headshot that's right that's right hmm what I feel like
I haven't heard very much from from Gav in fact people saying who is Gav so just
because of that I think we have to kill that's it
yeah yeah that was not the annoying guy it's a good job I followed you down a
good work on the bridge there you really showed them it's your lucky day
death the cannibal has cornered his own landing squad
he did get a headshot that was the deciding factor for me that's what put
me over the edge I can't I forgot about her arms
and strangled you with tish led you to the bomb trap though looks like the
mines they must have figured a way to reuse them oh shit she's injured see
what happened to the others I didn't see shit I think scarlet went down in the
shootout though where are we oh thank God we're five miles inland you should
have stayed with Otto fuck yeah he said he was a camper you okay got louder I
just turned it over this it kills me turn that off you are too though well if
somebody wants to decide on taking me over somebody else then you know not to
take the camper it's great to be part of a real team I think you made the right
choice Jesus Christ what the fuck stop what's wrong with everybody well now
you're a star you guys shoot everybody over here sorry shoot everybody zombie
what the fuck kill stream would like to apologize to scarlet's friends and
family let's take a moment now in remembrance of her moving on I'm glad I
got the mature stream warning on this one oh fucking moly that was fucking
scarring yeah that was fucking horrible like forever changed from that one
let's stop watching TV actually good effects though not very realistic but
pretty good I mean it was fucked up how many people are even left on our team
let's take a breather there's something up ahead
we please stop playing this um I mean there's only two of us left what what
what are you looking for you need to tell me what's going on that headcase
Ari was almost right throw for content I actually have not thrown about that but
this game is fixed what do you mean winners picked out before the game
begins how guns are real the mines real how could you possibly stop someone from
getting killed it's not a sure thing but from what we can tell anything it's
fake and get them the advantage I'm too speed I'm not here to win tish I've been
sent here by a group called the Alliance they've sent me here to expose the truth
that the corporation used deep fake technology to rig the outcome of kill
with a deep fake stuff
are they deep faking people dying?
suits from the contestants estates them with audiences dwindling they had to
come up with a plan so they started fixing it we're not sure when when the
creator left their big changes behind the scenes the winners always became big
all the way up to the top and then all the way to the top man decided to change
that with the winners in their pockets they managed to keep things afloat for
a while longer but now they're getting desperate that's why the rules keep
getting more brutal so you were being serious about the no tap ups they're
doing it to boost the ratings and the puppet who is it? I'm not sure yet it's him
sure it's um it's I'm the bad guy probably right it's me who's I talking
to on the phone before on the walkie-talkie okay it's me it's gonna be
you're here to expose all of this how why do you be like not bad and send you
let's just say I have a reason to hate Alan we're all getting deep faked the
Alliance knew this and it was a safe bet my this is the last thing I'm playing
before I'm starting streaming they gave me this device payload that I need to
plant in the corporation's network if they can get in they can hijack the
stream expose it all the deep fakes the fix everything so why are you telling me
this why isn't the Alliance helping you it was the notion was up they switched
locations at the last moment
last dream ever wait I'm no I'm saying just for today what about GPS our phones
blocked this signals in and out of this place go through our own corpse network
we're almost done mice was meant to be an old to their control but the blast
back there must have knocked it out I need to find a way to our course
network a calm start maybe I can find a way to get a message out we can find out
where they're going to kill you gotta be something I didn't say this was bad
they're streaming from all these drones 24-7 let me see that even if the radio
is broken you should be able to get some info from the storage I'm not dying on
this fucking island for nothing why do I trust her we think I don't know I don't
think so I'm gonna keep hold of it for now they keep just doing the double
cross thing no okay it's getting dark if there's a predetermined winner it could
be anyone you have another tower then we know that so what if it's just her we
should take it in turns keeping watch and tell them to stop cursing please
toss a coin you're concerned about cursing you sure and there was just like
a gruesome scene with somebody's like face like blown off I'll have the
conversation how'd you end up here that's complicated answer why not not
much call for an aging child actor I didn't make the transition you bleep
this where's sure TV and film that all changed I will do that for you
reality kill the TV store you're breaking my heart Mikey you blame the
corporation for that you remember the other Nick what we're doing on a shelf
like this Hollywood shoes you up and spit you out what do you do anything you
can to stay on top I'm waiting I'm trying to get it so he did kill stream
season 6 it's all starting to make sense drinking drugs made him a different
person made him feel invincible he thought this was the only way out eat
fake it is for some of us I'm sorry I didn't mean I wanted to do something for
my family I wanted to look after that no you didn't want to do that to someone
tipping the scales add revenue for my channel since I've been in here that's
gotta be something for them right what do they think of all this told them be
hard for them to miss by now though oh my god all right this I haven't had a
complaint about this game until right now this is way too long
you're sleeping in the subway station I thought you didn't watch those movies
come on they were everywhere when I was a kid of course they were don't wait
don't kiss or kiss don't kiss or kiss we can kiss we can we can kiss I guess are
we going to both be kissing each other pre marital kissing gross so what
happens if you have a romance in this movie game thing I don't understand all
right don't we need it don't do it put a sensor bar on okay
let's get some sleep okay if it all right if it was I wouldn't have done
that unbelievable tish tasker and Nick Romero are still in the game
I thought it was like this will happen do not attempt in a what or this will
happen fuck off go Nick lucky son of a bitch slippery fucker Kelvin you heard
East keep an eye on him don't worry buddy I look after you hello how are you
that phone was terrible but this is why I did I mean what's going on here but
what's up where were you what what was really spent never mind that was weird
we should get moving yeah oh god damn it no I don't trust anybody
Calvin right you're not Calvin Biggs are you oh my god it is you you were in
America's most wanted right hey there was a crying shame what they did
goddamn lame stream media and their goddamn witch hunts I mean so what if
school kids hostage you only killed the teacher you're sure you saw something
I thought I might have seen an antenna yeah okay what's this about an antenna
oh don't even think about it no we were wrong I'm sorry I was very wrong six
could take me both down and why didn't you douchebag the math like that just
might Otto I'm so sorry we start over you were listening we need to work
together that's not what you said to me last time we met look I'm so sorry you
said you were a camper in Call of Duty whatever model there's more going on
here than you know lower the gun and let's talk and things a really good
strategy it keeps your kill death high you to enjoy the game you can eat a
sandwich while you're playing you don't have to have two hands the controller I
mean that's a pain in the ass what's the difference between this island and a
dead prostitute Otto hears me saying Otto and is walking over here now hello
well it's a different auto not you this island still sucks we got a new party
why don't get is if they can fake bits of it why not fake the whole thing why
bother going to the expense of hosting it in the first place so let's let's get
Otto involved here to be variables all the drama power struggles randomness of
people is hard to script plus I don't know whether you know him but seriously
cutting you want 50% auto cam 50% game everybody apparently hey man streaming
that there's just too many people involved but it's an auto can't see this
shit trust a handful of people at the top to stay quiet they've got the most to
lose the winner's gonna keep their mouth shut but what about everyone else
who is it another puppet the winners are you since it was all fake you know he
really believed it maybe he was onto something maybe it's you mysteriously
popping up after an explosion one foot in one foot out of the group seems a bit
suspicious could be anyone he needs something I've got my suspicions hungry
no you hungry fingers it could be more than one for all we know West I'm gonna
take them out and give them a little snack and that's where I saw the
building 50% auto complex my promise has to be something you get to a part where
I can freeze it there you go all right this is gonna be the last BRB of the
night I'll be right back and then we'll have a 50% auto cam let's see how the
auto cam will work auto cam okay if he sits down let's see I don't 50% auto cam
well you won't you can't see the game okay can you see the game cooking down
to the final ten who cares about the game this tension with a spoon Nick
Romeo is still and we think in your party maybe you're still hope maybe the
pieces is too small but this is strange they're not showing anything bullshit
fuck is going on the show's really gone downhill oh the show's gone downhill
that's two clicks West just pass those trees pass the mines we just go get
through the field isn't there another way around the winds around the islands
200 meters open ground it gives us an advantage so you're on like a bright red
blanket how can someone who joined this is way too then suddenly be so risk of
us it doesn't contrast well at all I don't know it's better than fumbling
around in the dark just hoping to come across something okay what are our
options well there's one thing that I think my live auto reaction go on well
you said those guys use the mines to blow up the bridge yeah that means one
of those assholes is figured out how to rig those mines to blow up on command
that means it can be hacked if they can be had to figure out how their arms and
give it itchy head so what we take a live mine and deactivate always it is
here that sounds like it's gonna take forever but only for the first one is
mine's a smart which means it's probably part of a mesh network they send the
signal to arm disarm from mine to mine if I can figure out how to break one of
these guys security I can maybe disarm the whole thing at least the area we're
in wow that sounds like okay then fuckers why don't you go grab a big
stick and get ready to prod and poke your way through the next 200 meters of
open ground meter by meter I'm sure there's no risk there at all I haven't
been paying any attention to this what happened but Otto's plan I don't even I
don't even know what it is I'm just gonna do it come on then nerd
it's autos here your mind to play with are you fucking kidding me he's gonna
blow himself up fuck it I guess he wouldn't be that big of a loss anyway
whoa whoa whoa what are you doing it's a toes playing I was gonna hat the mine
I need a computer it's not sending out anything that can track us
itchy to be dark it's not here itchy it's a year he actually had an ear
problem I needed to put this stuff in his ears this is a bad idea hey he's okay
well how do we know if it works well if I walk over here actually the ear for
him everything within a three meter radius should be disabled you had to get
this little goo put in both of his ears try it you fucking try it you're holding
it you're 75% Otto careful wait what if I was gonna go to sleep
fuck was that holy shit you fucking idiot didn't work oh really and this I
gave it a go you nearly got us killed not to mention wasted our time in the
corner we'll have to move fast what's gonna be again keep face doesn't matter
you step on the mine we're just as dead concentrate 85% Otto 10% movie 5% face
cam there are those people like aiming at this whole game I'm sorry I got out
of that alive and I didn't do anything I told you that was gonna happen I
fucking told oh wait what wrong person it was literally the wrong guy it's the
other guy don't go anywhere folks we'll be back in
yo you seen this on the subreddit defects yeah I'm not buying this thing
that's why Romeo is there
we've come this far yeah but where I was okay I was about to say I'm gonna walk
out of the theater but he said we've come this far
like shit like you they're right
moving he's not just some glory-seeking wannabe Otto here is convicted of
swatting another streamer well Otto did not do that no swatting call the cops
and said there was a hostage situation at the house of another player so they
would send an armed response and what happened to Otto is killed I didn't mean
I don't care about anyone's past the fact is we're already in this situation
and we have to keep going how do we know he's not the puppet how do we know
you're not the fucking puppet you want a fucking because it's me I'm the main
character is the puppet it's me what's that I might as well tell them at this
point shouldn't be out this far come on
yeah I kind of want to just finish this movie so I can put it back in the
blu-ray case and just put it in the closet must be close now you know I
don't want to have it be sitting in my ps4 after I just kind of stop watching
it you know I mean I it's like I've got to complete it so I can put it in the
case and put it in the closet all right well okay this is difficult because she
she woke up earlier before I did and she I don't know what she she like was do
we sit behind the building and then she's like what huh what and then we
already like kind of betrayed Otto but then Otto but Otto at low opacity and
put the stream behind him all right well I'll go with Otto because Otto was the
dog name and if I don't click Otto then everyone's gonna be pissed you don't
like that guy you like my dog you like this Otto oh look at him he's so long
and chunky look at his big chunky butt he's like a seal
no earlier a phone fell out oh it was switched on yeah sure just before the
drone came look I know coming from me what if he's making this up here's the
problem what if he called the drone he's just putting it on her but it's I tell
we need to confront her dude I think we need to get the fuck out of it we're not
just ditching her okay is he right oh is he aiming at my head he's oh god he's
aiming at me oh I thought Otto was aiming at me
Nick let her go in the spirit of the game now would it I do need you Nick
you're outnumbered anyway you shoot her we kill you you didn't think I'd come
alone did you I come the yeah remember us you and me we just need a little chat
what the hell is going on speedrun 100% auto no I mean didn't I tell you that
near the end I was gonna have to have a sacrifice but here's the thing what if
they're baking this up what if they're working together this could just be an
elaborate ruse this is an elaborate ruse they're working I knew it I told you
yep what are you doing we need him god damn it I knew it
no no no worries go I've been looking forward to this we had the root we had
the redemption arc too okay so now what what is the climax of this whole thing
right you're just at the beginning your face on autos he's using the webcam okay
I thought he was just saying he wanted to take a bath I wasn't paying too much
attention okay so what happens here how does this end the acting that well I
think it's not even bad was it that was like good acting that wasn't bad
acting what are you talking about I mean some of the acting is not good is not
good you think he's a bad actor I think that guy's pretty good I got this so
wrong I thought this guy was gonna die first and they kept him through the
whole game like comedy relief guy yeah stealth takedown how do you do a stealth
takedown if somebody's looking at you I don't know how I got over here what yeah
search where'd the knife come from I don't remember it was makeup no no I
don't think so what do you mean it was makeup all right dad it's makeup yeah well
fast fast fast fast fast really fast oh shit he didn't even say anything but
what do you have another gun upgrade nice go go get it hurry let's talk we
can still get on the blur and get this all sorted you awake again okay but
we're almost there the finale wait what what chance do you think you had you
fucking muppet see the decisions already be made okay but I'm still alive
around oh the deep fakes are out there as far as the world knows already dead I
can easily just show up and be alive they can't let you there will be
one survivor anyway oh my god I can't believe you just showed that what I
don't remember that happening everyone gets shot through their right eye by the
way now what put the gun down tish so we made it to the last two that's not
true doesn't have to end this what about what about the girl the blood in her
mouth you just dipped out there are no guarantees what then this right here is
the ultimate prize Nick that's bullshit you just don't get it do you you may
have lost your fame your fortune your friend but it's not seven times I never
had any of that to begin with I came here for my family and now I can have it
all hell with everyone else you can't change it Nick we gotta look out for
ourselves there's a better way we can put an end to all this bloodshed you
were better than this day you don't know me who I am you still have a choice I
never had a choice Nick don't do it your move fine don't make me do it don't make
me do it please dish never point a gun at something you don't intend to kill oh
you didn't tend to kill me okay well never mind
the broadcast is out you're dead anyway not if I skip the ending cutscene I can
do my own deep fake chaotic laughter I live nice do I survive that that's
really bad ending oh it's gonna be after credits it's a battle royale you went by
didn't win though because they bake the whole thing with CG characters like one
of the characters was saying earlier what is the point of even doing this
show if you can just have realistic completely uncanny Valley real people
CG of people doing this what's the point of doing this in real life that might be
the worst ending it could be it's probably at least like five endings the
full-screen auto well hold on not yet in one of the other endings you hack the
stuff and release the deep fake info okay all right let's get the credits and
see what happens there's nothing there that it gets it no morale nobody likes
me nobody loves me but I'm strong and smart I guess no one likes me but I'm
very strong and very smart okay decisions made 54 scenes view this 294
scenes holy shit damn okay no romances all right I'm gonna do one thing before
we go there's a short video I want to watch it's a short sorcery film about
this stream and the sorcery game but stream is essentially over next time
I'll be live it will likely be next weekend probably on either Friday or
Saturday or Sunday keep an eye on the sus likely Sunday either maybe Friday and
Sunday or maybe just Sunday at Otto first oh I know I'm gonna pet you I'm
gonna pet mr. Otto you have a scratchy bum do you do you oh my goodness you
have a scratchy day it's Otto it's Otto it's Otto showing you his
penguin stripe okay I'm gonna grab this video real quick me one second will I
grab it but that's gonna conclude essentially the gaming portion of the
stream and I think this video is like you two three minutes four minutes I'm
like that those either to have never seen the sorcery playthrough is one of
the first streams I really did on twitch when I went to quote I'm a streamer now
when he what 2015 2016 link is okay
slam the walk turns over behind you hold on don't know it's good look at the
first grade all right let me get this shit out of here first of all okay all
right you ready this is called zap the old man a sorcery tribute and here we go
three the door of the stone building is slammed and the lock turns over behind
you is this gonna be a better movie a bench against one wall is the only piece
of furniture where an old man sits we're gonna go talk to it's a better movie
greetings old man he ignores you he is concentrating hard on something on the
ground just in front of him you glance upwards to the stars and suddenly the
old man shouts her sorcerer I knew it you're mistaken you reply cautiously oh
I don't think so you'll get us out of here better yet I haven't played anyone
for months silly not anyone smart sit down sit down hey what oh I swindle
stones of course swindle stones stranger in town don't know how to play better
he shows you one of his stones it is a strange for value to die he pats the
bench beside him with one hand shit play we can talk while I beat you this is
really really well made I'll go first show you how it's done the game is
simple we roll and bet on what's come up for instance I might start and bet that
between us we've rolled at least two truth how do I know what you have three
twos didn't you hear my last bid that was a clue at least unless I'm trying to
mislead you four twos I think you're trying to sleep oh yeah he had fucking
two twos so I get the I win when you win a round of swindle stones the other
person loses a die this game is so good by the way well two ones should do
therefore 20 years now hold on I need directions three threes oh yes we're
two four three screamer meta so he loses another die and he's at even more of a
disadvantage so what do they get you for one one it's a mistake one two oh I
better watch mine was lifting from a red eye two ones you can't be a very good
pickpocket then call what do you know about the north gate of the city two
ones it's wizard locked with a spell normally the first noble knows it two
fours this is important so tell me everything you know three fours they say
the spell is four lines and four novels know one line each four fours that's
good advice call I win don't I there they go that's swindle stones I was
going easy on you of course rematch thanks for the game I enjoyed being
that's the door locked of course from the outside oh really is it really well
door you're about to get fucking zapped his explosions I wish I had a pebble
just below the door straight up well you know we can do dumb what are the other
options I'm just curious stop this pop zip cause teleportation I don't have a
green ring zap zap the fucking door cast the spell winding a powerful charge of
electricity inside your wrist ready to unleash zap the old man no reason to
listen to this old man's horse breathing what instantly is there the next the
room is filled with smoke and the smell of cooked bacon that's so fucked up you
settle down on the bench to wait out the night in silence I would definitely
subscribe the door of the stone building a slave yeah I would subscribe
that video is fucking unbelievable that was very very very well made that was
exceptional is the channel I yeah I would absolutely subscribe that was
fucking unbelievable even the zap in the CG is after effects you know what you're
doing swindle stones should be the new streamer meta I feel like that would be a
lot of content thank you for that video that's unbelievable that was by dr.
Masaki very nice it would just compare it to squid game yeah but not if you had
and I don't know it has to be no well I guess it was because the you know you
know those that have seen squid game we know he doesn't get it I look I
don't I guess I do of course I do I'll see you guys later I'll see you guys
next week and have a great week I'm it's probably gonna be Friday an eye on the
sus looking like it'll be Friday afternoon play sorcery I already did
though I don't think I can go back and replicate that new era of sorcery I
don't know I feel like it's it sits in a place for me where I want to preserve
that I had so much fun it was such a it was so many fun streams in a row that I
don't want to go back and remake it I feel like it wouldn't be as interesting
maybe sensory stream yeah I know I got there's a lot of stuff that I'm gonna be
working on this week maybe I'll go tap into that too that was a lot of fun all
three of those games had interesting things to experience although holy shit
man I still I'm like still thinking of that lady in her like mouth I'm gonna
need to go watch like baby sensory videos it was fucked up I haven't had
let me let me see my steam I think I have like another couple of FMV games
that I've just been sitting there that death stalker game I've had for a long
time let's see I swear to God this is at least not the two or three that I've
not played it's also I looked at this the other day at the games that I've
got on Steam and I kind of just did this some reorganization and one of things I
realized I said what are these I bought these like years ago with the intent on
doing like a video on them or streaming them and I just never did at least that
one I bought that one I know at least six months ago when did that come out on
Steam very curious yeah like I came out like almost two years ago for the year
you're more than a year ago I may have actually bought it last year like in
2020 let's do it all right I'll see you guys on Friday and one of the things we
might be doing on Friday is italics and I might be playing Resident Evil 6 it's
very possible we'll see we talked about it dark pictures anthology stuff yeah we
I want to play like Resident Evil 6 more and more than I think about I'm like
actually kind of like what I feel like I would have more fun playing that raid
somebody you dork are hold on let me see who's even live it's tallax is live
right now playing rimworld I just stole it from you right now before you got to
the copyright office so you just got screwed yeah we'll write it Alex we're
gonna be hanging out with him over this week anyway so I'll say hello been a
while since we've rated tallax playing rimworld if that's not your thing that's
it is then he plays it all the time and I will see you guys later have a great
week to carry yourselves see you Friday or another day take care good night
goodbye