Hey, what is going on everybody? Welcome to Scare Saturdays. My name is Jerma. Hopefully it's still Saturday.
I've been having a lot of problems today with rendering and uploading and stuff.
But if it's not Saturday where you are right now, then I'm sorry about that.
But anyways, let's go over something first. I need a haircut really badly.
I seriously look like Luke Perry and a mad scientist had a baby and it stars in a new feature film coming this August.
I look like a friggin' weirdo, but you know what, we're gonna leave it. It's Scare Saturdays. My hair's already standing up on end because I'm already scared.
So it makes perfect sense. But anyways, let's get started with Scare Saturdays. Welcome back to Scare Saturdays.
Gonna be playing an amnesia custom story by the name of Can't Remember.
Okay, so here we go. Can't Remember by Marv Studios.
You wake up in an unknown house. You don't know how you got here. You can't see anybody and the only thing you can hear is the rain splashing against the window.
Alright, so I'm apparently lying on the ground somewhere. Your sanity is now dangerously low. Make sure to stay in light and try to make progress.
This is like shaking my screen. Cut it out, man.
Can I turn off the screen shake? What the hell, bro? Come on, get up.
Look, just because you had a party last night and you drank too much tequila doesn't mean you can stay on the ground.
Alright, I'm trying to make jokes, but I'm actually pretty nervous right now. It's been a while since I've played a game like this.
Is there a reason why it's all red? What the hell's the matter with me?
Can I just go back to bed and end the video?
Alright guys, thanks so much for watching. I'm gonna go to bed now.
Hmm, but this is a mod. This is an amnesia custom story, like I said in the beginning.
Let's just open up this dresser.
Apparently my dry cleaning isn't done. I gotta bring this to the dry cleaner.
I really don't want to leave this room. I don't want to leave the room.
Look at how all trippy this is, man.
Something's gonna jump out of this door and it's gonna scream at my face.
Because it's all trippy and it's all weird looking.
Alright, is there anything in here I need, by the way?
What's on the ground? Can I get this?
No, it's just like a bong.
Oh no, one of the guys is all screwed up. He's been smoking like a bunch of weed.
Mr. Bonin forced me to drink this potion of insanity.
He said that things who live in this house will kill me, but then they won't harass the people in our village nearby.
I'm going insane and I will lose my memory, Mr. Bonin said. What else should I do?
Great, so there's monsters in this house.
God damn it, man.
Alright, I'm dilly-dallying way too much. Let's just go outside.
This night is gonna do something weird.
The mental's been added to the journal.
Hit M. Explore the house and find a way to get out.
Easier said than done, okay?
Please don't, like, come after me.
God damn it!
Do I have to go just walk down this hall? I don't want to go down this hallway!
Let's go.
Please don't jump!
Beware when standing in darkness your sanity will slowly drain. Turn lights on.
There are no lights around here.
There are no lights around here, man. What's that? Can I, like, break this?
I have no idea what that is, but I don't think I can go this way yet.
What about this door that I just opened?
Where am I? Oh, okay, so I can go in here.
There's a ladder.
And a couple barrels.
Is that a lantern?
No tinderboxes left.
Should I go up the ladder? Can I open this?
Oh yeah!
Got my lantern. You picked up a lantern and when filled with oil it can be turned on by pressing F.
Oh yeah, I can see.
I can see clearly now the rain is gone.
Let's go.
Can I put the damn lantern back on, please?
That's pretty gross.
Are these, like, decapitated body parts?
Look at this cockroach!
This cockroach is friggin' huge!
Alright, I got a pig. Where are we going with the pig?
I'm gonna bring the pig to, like, dinner.
I thought that, like, friggin' thing on the right was a monster.
It's actually just a bunch of leaves.
Get out of here, pig.
There's the key to the basement, I'm assuming.
Picked up the basement's key. Let's go, let's go. Get me out of here.
There we go.
Open.
Oh, open that basement door, you son of a bitch.
What the hell was that? Am I really going insane?
I don't know. I hope I'm not going insane.
Oh, the game didn't just crash, did it?
Oh, we were just getting, like, to the good stuff, probably.
And the game, like, no, no, I'm good, I'm good.
Okay. Note on the ground.
Somebody read this notice that you have to get out of here.
The monsters who live here kill everybody who's in the house.
You have to find some keys or tools to open the doors in the torture chambers.
One is in a small room in the middle of the basement.
Maybe you can find some tools in the kitchen.
The doors are very weak, so you can use a hammer or something like that.
People wear the monsters.
Alright, so I gotta break some tools open or something.
Can I open this thing?
Let's go. Let me get in this, like, trap door.
Oh, there's a lot of dead people in there.
Come on, open.
Come on, you physics engine piece of crap.
Wow.
Alright, well, there's a crowbar in here.
Let me get this crowbar.
Dave!
Where am I?
Pull up the lantern, pull up the lantern.
Get me out of this stupid, get me out of this, like, hellhole.
Get me out, get me out, please.
Alright, I'm making, like, a bridge to get out of here.
Alright, got out.
Sick.
That was insane.
See, I just cut that, but that really took me, like, 35 minutes to, like, get...
Oh, no, I'm out of lamp oil.
Oh, I'm...
Is that a person standing there?
That's a person standing right there.
Or is that one of those knights in armor?
I have no idea.
Ah!
Go this way, go this way, go this way, go this way, go this way.
This door's locked.
Oh, my God, I have no idea what's going on.
I don't even know if there's a person here.
What if I hide over here?
Oh, my God, I don't have any oil.
What a stupid idiot I am.
I used all my lamp oil trying to figure out how to put boxes on top of each other.
It's a monster.
Where do I go?
Oh!
It's a monster right fucking behind me.
I don't have any oil.
I don't even know where to go.
I have no idea where to go, guys.
I have no oil.
I have no lights.
Can I take the torch from the top of this?
Holy God.
I have no idea where this is.
Am I in the right spot?
I can't light that.
Do I have any oil?
What the hell was that?
Give me some oil.
What's in this cup?
I'm going to throw hot acid in this guy's face.
Eat this.
I have no lamp.
There are bodies everywhere.
Just eat this, you bastard.
I don't know where to go, and I don't know what to do because I spent like 30 frigging
minutes trying to figure out how to put things on top of each other.
Oh, my God.
All right.
I got back here with lamp oil, and I'm ready to try to go actually and do this.
Yeah.
I know he's going to come out.
I know.
Is there anything in here I need to get?
That's the real question.
What do I need to get in here?
I can't open that.
Where is he?
I don't want to run right into him.
Is he behind me?
No.
He's right there.
Just eat box, you prick.
All right.
Jump over the bookcase, please.
Thank you.
I knew that was there too.
Can I hide in here?
Get me in here.
Oh, let's do it again.
Wait.
Oh, I'm back.
He's not here.
He's not here this time.
Okay.
Okay, cool.
Don't do the lady jumping at me again.
All right.
She's gone.
Oh, I don't know how much lamp oil do I have.
What's that?
Tinder box.
All right.
Light these.
Put this away.
Holy crap, dude.
Anything here I can take?
You need oil or something?
Can I...
What's that?
Screwdriver?
I don't think I need that.
Oh, I'm burping.
Nervous burps.
These look like some type of tools.
Oh, what's that?
Picked up oil.
All right.
Let's see.
How much oil do I got?
I got a decent amount.
I can hang for a little bit.
Crowbar.
Definitely crowbar the hell out of this wall.
Nope.
Can't do that.
Anything in here?
Don't think so.
Just take all the boxes out.
There's got to be something in here for me to like to take.
Oh, wow.
That whole encounter was just like brain-numbingly horrible.
All right.
So I got to find some tools.
Don't, please.
Don't jump at me.
Now that that asshole's gone, I can probably...
Have I gone in here yet?
No, I haven't.
I haven't.
The crowbar's gone.
I can probably...
Have I gone in here yet?
I don't think so.
What's that?
A hollow needle.
Okay.
I thought that's where I came from.
This is locked, I guess.
Maybe not.
Can I like open this?
Open, you bastard.
I guess not.
Maybe it will.
Maybe I gotta shake it.
Shake the door open.
I can't go in there.
Can I pry the door open with a crowbar maybe?
Let's try that.
There we go.
Let's pry this thing open.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Oh, I got it, all right.
Maybe I didn't.
What?
Did I open it?
Yeah, okay, I opened it.
Okay.
Rat.
How much lantern oil?
Need that lantern oil.
Tender box, okay.
I don't need to use the lantern here.
Let's go out through this door.
Can I not go out this one?
I need another crowbar?
You kidding me?
Maybe there's something else I can grab.
Can I pick this up?
Can I smash this wall?
Oh, damn!
All right, so I just smashed through this frigging wall.
All right.
Oh, do I really wanna go down here?
Can I even get in here is the question.
Oh, and give me this box.
What the hell is even?
This is bad, man.
Something's gonna frigging,
like a spider's gonna run down this.
Left or right?
We're gonna go left.
Oh, man.
Grr.
I knew it.
I knew it was gonna happen too, and it's still.
It doesn't matter.
Can I break through this with the hammer?
What about the needle?
I'm running out of lamp oil, guys.
Running out of lamp oil.
I gotta conserve it.
I have no idea where I'm going.
Hmm.
I need more lamp oil.
We gotta go right.
It's gonna happen again.
Some son of a bitch is gonna pop up right in my face.
Lydianium.
Increase your health.
Okay, it's health potion.
Need to hold on to this lamp oil.
It is pitch black, but you know what?
We gotta make sure we keep that.
What's that?
Anything else I can do over here?
No.
Okay, well, I got something to break through
the rest of that door, I think.
I don't know how long it's gonna take me
to rage quit this game.
I don't think it's gonna be very long,
because they just keep throwing shit in my face,
and it's making me wanna die.
Now, let's open this door.
Break open.
Okay.
Hello, sweetie.
Any lamp oil in here that I can take?
No, that's a sanity potion.
Blood all over the place.
And a, huh, huh, huh?
What, what, what, what?
Yeah?
Hi?
What is this?
What is all over you?
No more lamp oil, by the way.
I can't get out of here either?
Oh, damn it.
I need more tools.
What else is over here?
Crap.
Oh, duh.
What am I thinking?
I still don't have any lamp oil, though.
Still, ah!
That guy's not moving, though.
That guy's not moving.
Is that guy, is he friendly?
Can I, like, talk to that guy?
Hey, don't mind me, I'm just, like, in your house.
I'm just, like, looking at some stuff.
Can I pick up the key without you freaking out, man?
Ah, he's right behind me.
Get this stuff out of the way.
Get out of the way, get out of the way, get out of the way.
Open the key and go.
I have to take the, wait, what did that say?
Oh, Jesus.
Floating like specters.
Where's the, I need lamp oil.
Give it to me.
Where the hell are we?
Oh, I don't, what is that?
Get out of my way.
We're in water now.
Get out of the way.
So, oh, I thought that was another lantern.
I thought that was another person down here.
Holy shit.
Get me on top of something.
Get me out of the water, get me out of the water,
get me out of the water, get me out of the freaking water.
Are you serious, dude?
What the hell am I supposed to do here?
All right, we're gonna run for it.
Go.
Run for it, run for it.
Get out of the water.
Holy crap.
And the bitch is laughing at me now.
Get me, get me on top.
Get me on top.
Get me, get me, get up.
Get up here, get up here, get up here.
Holy Lord in heaven, find me out of this little area, please.
Is that a door?
It's a door.
Oh, there's a key in here.
Damn it.
I can make the jumps.
Just gotta make the jumps.
Just don't be such a psycho.
Just make the jumps.
You'll be good to go.
Okay, where's the key?
Where's the goddamn key?
Ooh, what's that?
I don't know, but I'm jumping over to it.
I think these are Tinder boxes.
Okay, nice.
Maybe I can light a frickin' candle now.
Is that a key?
Can't tell.
Yeah, there's the key.
Okay, a gun.
Wherever that door was, I don't even know where I am,
but I think it was over here.
Yep, it's right here.
Let's get the hell out of this friggin' swamp land.
Yes, I did it.
Walking the last few stairs to get outside.
Did I beat the game?
I beat the game.
What the hell is that?
I need to light something.
I have Tinder, but give me some oil
so I can get the fuck outta here.
Thank God, lamp oil.
Save my life.
Thank, but Jesus.
Hopefully that's not like my friend.
I'm dying, a monster hurts me.
Run to the little house in the forest and call the police.
I think I won't survive, but I hope you do.
Take the potion in front of the door to blow it up.
So I blow the door up.
Ah!
What?
What the fuck was that?
Is that guy still in here?
Just run.
Just call the police.
Call the police, call the police.
911, what is your emergency?
Yes, hi, my name's Jerma,
and there is a bunch of people running after me,
and I'm trying to get to the house,
so I'm trying to call the police so you can come
and save me.
Oh, that was a good guy, that ghost was.
You called the police and they burned the house.
You survived.
The ghost helped you escape.
All right.
All right, I don't know what the hell that was
that came out of the door, but he wasn't there anymore.
Anyways, this has been Amnesia Customs Story.
The name of the custom story has been,
I like forget because I'm so like jumbled.
Can't Remember is the name of this custom story.
Pretty intense, pretty ridiculous,
but I beat the whole thing in one playthrough, so cool.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
Thank you so much for watching,
and of course, take care, everybody.